Teral Audio.
Warning, today's podcast may include Steven Spielberg acting, an orb wielding teacher named
Botanicus, and a pulse pounding analysis of Universal Studios ET Adventure.
Let's wrap in for the premiere episode of Podcast the Ride.
Hello everybody, welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three childless
men in their 30s.
We're part of Teral Audio, home of Doughboys, and many, many more great podcasts.
My name is Michael Carlson.
I am joined by my co-hosts, as always, Scott Gairdner.
Hi, that's me.
That's Scott, and Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
Yeah, so today's topic is going to be the Universal Studios Ride ET the Adventure, and
we're going to break it down and talk about what we would do with it if we were in charge.
So for those of you listening for the first time, we are the kids who got too into the Disney parks.
Yeah, I think so.
And look, there are people who have the disease worse than us.
That's certainly true.
Yes.
Yeah, we're like at least a little bit self-aware about it.
There are a lot of folks, if you go on these message boards, that do not have any sense
of humor about any of this stuff.
That being said, people on the message boards, we are your friends, and we...
Yes, oh, we like you guys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We are also of you.
Yeah, no, no, no.
Please listen.
But this is a thing that a lot of people listening might not realize the depth of theme park fandom,
that there are these message boards, and there are many, many fan sites, many, many other
podcasts out there.
We're going to try to be the one with the vaguely comedic bent, which I can only assume
doesn't exist.
We're going to do our best with that comedic thing, but we will get very serious about
this.
It's going to be like, we're laughing, and then we're like, but they should not have
made that change to my ride.
That was my ride when I was a child.
You will be shocked how non-comedic it is for the vast stretches of time.
It really is the area of all of our lives that we are the most or the least ironic about.
That's true.
We're going to share it with you.
Yeah, and then we're just going to get into stuff like Imagineers Who Created Rides, which
is the thing as a kid I didn't even realize, because the rides just feel like they've always
been there.
They're like these people, men and women, who have slaved over this design and went
through a whole political process of trying to get their idea approved.
They probably in-fought with other people and management and bled for this stuff.
Then Big Thunder Mountain Railroad was born.
Something that you just accept, the Runaway Mine Car Ride.
It seems very innocent and like it's always been there, but yeah, it took a lot of effort
and hard work to do.
There's so many rides that don't get completed.
In that Imagineering building, the headquarters of the Disney theme parks, there's so many
rides that are invented, fully cooked up, probably even built and then are never installed
in the parks.
A movie will come out and then completely tank and they can't justify spending the money
to further promote that movie.
Yeah, we never will see the creation of Dick Tracy's Crime Stoppers in real life.
It exists only on paper and the internet fan sites.
It would have been a great ride though.
Sure.
It's very disappointing that it never made it.
Join an animatronic, Warren Beatty, on a journey through the city as you fire guns.
Wow, mommy, I saw Dick Van Dyke's character, Raisin Man, whatever he is.
Is that his character, Raisin Man?
Should be, as far as anyone knows.
Correct us if you're listening, but also you probably don't know.
No one knows.
No one likes Dick Tracy.
That's a real problem with rides, especially today.
It really has to be intellectual property that people are familiar with.
I think actually, the intellectual property issue is something that kind of hurts the
ride that we're going to talk about today because I think this character is not really
in the forefront of popular culture anymore, but maybe he should be.
We're talking about E.T.
The E.T. Adventure, one of the great Universal Studios rides, a fixture at Universal Florida
still today.
An opening day attraction.
One of maybe the only opening day attraction that still remains in Universal Florida.
This and the movie monster makeup show.
This is the only remaining ride.
The show in the fake Pantages Theater, as I know it.
No longer at Universal Hollywood, dearly departed, no longer at Universal Japan.
We could tell you a little bit about this ride and what it is, or we could let Steven
Spielberg tell the tale.
Steven.
Steven, where are you?
Get out of here.
He's coming.
Here he is.
We don't have much time.
Steven Spielberg, and it's my pleasure to welcome you to the E.T. Adventure, but I'm
afraid we don't have much time.
See?
So I'm going to cut right to the chase.
The E.T. needs your help.
Now, we've just received the message that you're going to be on the ride.
We're going to have to wait for the ride.
We've just received the urgent message from E.T.'s teacher, Botanicus, calling for E.T.
to come home right away.
You see, a big problem has developed three million light years away on E.T.'s home world,
the Green Planet.
E.T.'s friends are in danger because their planet is dying.
Remember what E.T.'s friends look like because it's going to be up to you to help E.T. find
them once we get them home, and there's not a moment to lose.
Very important.
Because only E.T.'s magic healing touch can save his friends and bring his planet back
to health.
E.T. must go home, and only you can help him.
We have to go.
I mean, as a child, I think that's probably, I mean, it's for children, but like, yeah,
the whole thing is like, you really were like, I may die on this ride.
This might be a suicide mission on like, whether it's, you know, this or Space Mountain.
I'm like, I may hurdle into a star.
Like it may be over.
And there weren't ride through videos.
You couldn't look up what things were on YouTube when we were children.
So yeah, I assumed that any single ride that you got onto was going to literally murder
me.
Yeah.
The internet really opened up like theme park fandom because I think there was like fan
scenes like any other thing.
But like now there's just, you can watch footage of any ride and we will put footage of this
ride in the show notes for you to watch at home.
Well, what we just heard was like the pre show video that you see in line of Steven
Spielberg preparing you to ride this children's ride.
Which by the way, so we should talk about then what transpires, what the ride is.
So as Steven Spielberg himself told us, you climb aboard a bike.
ET needs your help.
His planet is dying.
The green planet.
His teacher Botanicus is part of it somehow too.
He factors in.
Anyway, you got to get to the green planet.
So you end up in the scene basically from ET where you're avoiding police officers
who in this case are portrayed by very stiff, barely animated dummies.
And there's cars coming at you like police cars and like FBI, like FBI I think cars,
some sort of secret covert agencies that are trying to capture you and ET before you can
make it home to the green planet.
Every agency's cars have all arrived in the hills of Tahunca, California where the ride
is set.
An obscene amount of walkie talkies like the redo.
No guns.
No one has a gun.
Did they do the gun change or did they never have guns?
Never had guns.
Yeah.
Steven Spielberg famously edited out all the guns in ET in like a DVD release a few years
ago and changed them all to walkie talkies digitally, which I think has gone back, but
that was in the digital changing craze of the late 90s, early 2000s of his friend George.
Now this ride, this ride hits like a very common theme park thing where you, you hit
like a big beat of, of the movie and then you get a whole lot of new stuff.
Like you get a whole new adventure.
In this case it is, yeah, you're, you're taking the place of Elliot.
You're riding the bikes, ET's in the basket and there is a little ET animatronic in the
basket that pops up and you're evading the federal authorities.
Does it, does it have a face?
I always wondered because you can't really see you're in the bike behind the ET.
Yeah, you're talking ET in the basket.
If you could see yourself in the ride, is there an ET face on the other side?
I think there is.
I think I sat in the front row and like leaned over and was like, yeah, there's, there's
his face.
There's a chance that like if you lean over and it's just like a blank robot face.
It's faceless mannequin.
Or just like circuits shooting out raw electricity at you.
I think in this day and age, in this day and age if like somebody were to put their phone
out and take like the selfie, it would have to be there because it would be terrifying
if there was, yeah, that creepy face.
If you felt like ET had his face ripped off, then the green planet dying is the least of
your troubles.
So once you have successfully evaded all of the federal agencies, spoiler alert, you do
by flying in your bike as in the film, then you end up seeing all the new stuff.
As Jason said, you go to the green planet.
You fly over a city.
You fly over a nondescript city.
I think it's Los Angeles.
I think you can see a Dodger Stadium in there.
It's a Los Angeles-esque city at least.
Yeah.
It is the same sequence from the Peter Pan ride.
If you've ever written Peter Pan, there's a very similar sequence because you're flying
in a similar type of ride.
These are called dark rides, by the way, both of these rides, and they're both called suspended
dark rides because you're actually hanging from the ceiling and moving forward as opposed
to it being on a car on the ground.
But yeah, it's like it's a similar thing where you're like looking over all the rooftops
and it's really just like a tiny model that's lit up that makes it look like you're...
And it is the same track layout as the Peter Pan ride, which is maybe something you have
to knock a few points down.
It's part of originality.
The fact that it literally bends the same way and then you go into a little sub-sky
room in the back right corner, whatever.
It works for Peter Pan.
It works for this.
I don't know why I'm trying to gotcha this ride right from the top.
You're really sticking it to him.
I love the ride.
I don't mean to criticize, but it is weird.
It's a copy and paste of the scene.
I mean, there's a ton of that in the theme park industry.
There's only so many companies that make massive ride track systems and all.
So they all use the same manufacturers.
Oh, that's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And certain types of rides, your wild mouses and the spinning rides and that kind of thing.
You are seeing a lot of copies of copies of this ride.
Universal, very famous for a lot of simulator rides, especially when the Florida park opened
in 1990.
Even more now, I think, you sit in a car, the car rocks around, there is a giant screen
and you're watching footage that syncs up with your ride vehicles movement.
Another common Universal Studios trope is getting splashed.
Yes, there's a lot of splash, errant water going on in a lot of these rides, not in the
E.T. ride.
Once you're on the green planet, you think maybe you get sprayed by a fountain of water,
but you remain dry.
Part of the one of the pieces of suspense that makes the ride so fun.
Let's talk about the green planet.
Well let's, should we break down, let's go through, because I want to save the green
planet stuff.
Okay.
Let me, we'll just tease the green planet.
There's a lot to talk about.
You end up on the green planet.
Now the green planet is where E.T. is from and it exists in some other forms of media.
And if you don't know about the green planet, it's a little weird.
It's a little strange that E.T. would come from this place.
Yeah, if you've only seen the film E.T.
Yeah.
If you've only seen one part of the E.T. expanded universe, you know, the movie E.T., you might
not know that, you know, E.T. lives in a world of plants and fluorescents.
He lives in, it's kind of a pre-pandora, you might say.
Yeah, so he has that.
I have that written down too.
It's a bioluminescent, which is the word I keep seeing in all of these Pandora write-ups
where it's like the bioluminescent forest.
And I was like, well, you know what?
E.T.'s homeland green planet was bioluminescent, you know, 25 years before Pandora ever showed
up.
Yeah, this looks very similar to Disney's new Pandora land of Avatar.
Well, Disney's striking back.
They're getting revenge after that Peter Pan.
Disney's getting revenge for that Peter Pan homage.
It's a game of cat and mouse revenge that extends over the course of 50 years.
Peter Pan, 1955, is ripped off in 1990, and in 2017, the Pandora shaman boat ride.
Like the Count of Monte Cristo, it takes a full lifetime to get revenge.
It's the long game.
Yeah.
Now the green planet is mentioned like once in the movie.
Doesn't Elliot say like, oh, E.T. came from the green planet?
Is that the full extent of...
Is it even in the movie?
Is it in the movie?
I don't even know that it's in the movie.
Maybe you imagine that?
Or is there a piece of dialogue where he talks about the green planet?
E.T. also doesn't have a lot of speech capabilities, so he probably couldn't get out a lot of information
about the planet, even if he wanted to.
In the movie or in this ride, as becomes very apparent at the very end.
Yes, his speech troubles and we'll get into that.
But the green planet is mentioned pretty heavily in the book of the green planet.
Yes, and there's a book called E.T. the Green Planet.
Now the first, I was just going to go break down because the first glimpse we get of E.T.'s
other world is in the line.
It's in the queue itself.
When we see a character that is named Botanicus, as Steven Spielberg calls him, Botanicus.
And that is he's introduced as E.T.'s teacher, which is, you know...
All you need to know.
He taught E.T. how to put on a wig and eat a Reese's.
Everything E.T. can do.
Also a question I have.
How old is E.T. in the movie?
How old would you assume he is?
I was thinking about this.
He sort of, I mean, he's paired with a child.
He's paired with other children.
Does that make him a child?
And when you see Botanicus, who basically, if you haven't been on the ride, is an elderly
E.T.
Yeah, Botanicus is old as shit.
Like Botanicus looks like shit.
We all have links.
The years of prop and kind to Botanicus.
Yeah, he's E.T. with like seven more layers of wrinkles.
And he talks like Master Splinter.
But he has a much greater vocabulary than E.T. himself.
Is this answered in the book how old E.T. is?
I don't remember.
Full disclosure, I have the book E.T. the Green Planet.
I haven't read it cover to cover.
I've also lost the book.
And I also don't remember if E.T.'s age is addressed in it.
Well, you're listening to real experts.
Yeah, but I have done some...
I think you made the right call losing the book of the Green Planet.
That was an accident, though.
I really...
I was cherishing the book despite losing it.
What do we know about the book of the Green Planet?
It came out like a few years after the movie?
It was a few years after the movie, yeah.
And it's about...
It picks up right where E.T. left off, the movie E.T. left off.
And it's, as Jason...
It's bizarre as shit.
It's so weird.
It's immediately... E.T. is immediately sort of on a spaceship and kind of longing for
Elliot.
He misses Elliot.
And E.T. all of a sudden has a vocabulary and there are all these different characters.
And it's basically a story where E.T. goes back and he lives in just the weirdest place.
I mean, it resembles the ride, but it's totally, totally off from the movie.
Now it's sort of a cute romp with these different characters.
There's a character named the Flop Glopple, which is described as a character that looks
like it's made out of socks.
Which, you're like, well, I don't know.
It's like he took E.T., gave him a cuddly little cute cartoon personality, and then
threw him into this weird adventure, which he eventually does go back because he misses
Elliot so much.
And Elliot also...
Here, I'm getting ahead of myself.
Elliot also is discovering girls and E.T. has a telepathic link with him.
And E.T. is coaching Elliot through puberty.
Oh my God.
Like across space though?
Yes, across space.
Because he's on another planet?
So E.T. will also project his astral form to E.T.
And the whole thing is just bizarre.
Does that imply that E.T. and Elliot had this astral connection before they even met?
Was E.T. from the green planet, before he got lost on Earth, commanding Elliot to do
things?
Is E.T. also?
To brush his teeth in a certain counterclockwise, as opposed to clockwise?
It's possible, I think.
Are they both going through puberty, or is E.T. just experiencing it through a residual
telepathic connection?
I think it's residual telepathic connection.
E.T.'s...
All of his species are asexual.
They do address that.
There's no...
So I don't think he actually...
E.T. does not have sort of a normal human puberty.
So when you're going... but you would certainly call him a boy.
You would call Botanicus a him.
When you're in the ride, and when you're on the E.T. ride, there's a bunch of other E.T.s
swinging around on vines and playing plants as instruments and stuff.
Are some of those girls, or there just is no sex?
Some of them are children, for sure, because they're smaller than E.T.
Unless it's some messed up culture where the smaller ones are the old ones.
And Botanicus is the youngest.
When you're in E.T., you lose wrinkles in size as the years go on.
And you lose knowledge?
Do you get stupor?
I guess so, yeah.
Like, bench and button rules?
And young people teach old people.
I better get all this knowledge out now before I lose it.
There is also, like...
Wise babies.
In this ride on the Green Planet, there's a lot of creatures that look like E.T.
And then he's got a couple other fucking friends who don't look like E.T. at all.
Yes.
And they're kind of upsetting.
They are upsetting looking.
If you were listening to the Steven Spielberg intro earlier, and are still listening now,
one of the things that Steven Spielberg tells you to do is look for E.T.'s friends, because
you will have to help E.T. find his friends.
E.T. doesn't remember what his friends look like, apparently.
So in that pre-show video, you see three quick shots of these characters, E.T.'s weirdo friends.
One of them's a weird mushroom guy.
One of them is a shrill doll with tentacle hair.
With spaghetti hair?
Yeah.
Who am I forgetting?
Mushroom, shrill doll.
Help me out.
There's another one that looks kind of like the little doll, I feel like.
But those are the main ones.
I mean, Botanicus and those two that you mentioned are the big ones that they care.
The other one looks kind of like the Little Shop of Horrors.
Right.
Yeah, the plant.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, I don't know.
What do you think they say?
Are they plants?
One of them's clearly a mushroom.
One of them's kind of a plant.
The mushroom guy, like I as a kid, I don't like this, but the mushroom man says a very,
very specific line.
He sings speaks the line, welcome home.
You've arrived.
And I don't like it, but I've written it so many times since I was a small child, it's
ingrained in my memory, and I cannot forget welcome home.
Like this ride having not been open at my local Universal Studios, which is Hollywood,
for many years and I haven't been on it in a long time.
There are things like that, welcome home, and E.T. saying ready and trouble that just
are permanently ingrained that I say, my wife and I say in our day to day lives.
If we have finished tying our shoes and are ready to go out for the day, we will say ready.
What a cool house, right?
I think that's endearing.
Hey, thanks.
Well, there's one vote for endearing.
Thank God.
What was I saying?
Oh yeah, the, no, the sing songy language that is so distinct.
That I find very charming.
It makes me like the mushroom guy.
I don't like the shrill doll, as implied by that I'm calling it the shrill doll.
The shrill doll says, kind of talks in sort of a manic.
Kind of screams that.
It's like join the celebration.
It's kind of horrendous.
Oh, dang.
Screwed up.
Blooper number one.
I looked up the names of these three creatures and I'm really proud that I didn't know this
already.
Some deep theme park knowledge I'm glad to have, like I.D. and O.D., Captain E.O.'s friends,
but I'm really glad I didn't previously know the names Teakley, Orbadan, and Magdol.
Is Orbadan the mushroom man?
I think, I can only assume Magdol is the scary doll.
I think Orbadan is the, I don't know what about the name Orbadan implies mushroom, but
yeah.
Orb?
Like he's an orb, it's sort of an orbish head I guess.
I suppose so.
And these guys don't show up again.
I mean the financial reality is probably that they're like, all right, we can afford like
three kind of big animatronics that move a little and the rest are just little fucking
E.T.'s that are just like.
Well they kind of wave or like they're on a conveyor belt so it looks like they're playing
ball but they're still.
The E.T. adventure in general is a pretty limited animation ride.
You will not be blown away as you would by the pirate auctioneer or the Johnny Depp figure.
In fact the FBI agents and the police I think do not move whatsoever.
They are essentially still mannequin dolls.
Probably a thing that could be improved about this ride although I find it sort of charmingly
cheap as well.
They do a lot of cool stuff though like in the in the forest when the ride first starts
with like lighting where it seems like headlights are coming through you.
There's a lot of neat practical effects.
Yeah.
I think it's a ride that where the environments and the production design is stronger than
the character animation.
But maybe in 1990 when this ride was built Disney completely had that market cornered.
And in fact I guess in general Universal Studios does not have like incredible audio animatronics.
I think you might say that their production design is better than their their characters.
Yeah.
Right.
Which is nothing to dock it for.
There's so many great universal rides and this one included.
Something we didn't talk about the line of this ride I think is fantastic.
And maybe the first really good universal line a lot of I feel like universal lines up until
that point were just like just turnstiles and you're outside and you aren't really in
an environment.
But in this thing you're in this this amazing lush forest kind of forest.
Yeah.
With which which smells this very particular way.
I'm sure you guys remember the E.T. ride smell.
That's a thing that like that's a specific thing that theme park people do I think have
an affinity for an obsession with is that smell.
To the point where I found a Facebook page where people were talking about like I found
for breeze spray that smells like the E.T. line.
Wow.
Which is kind of like mist and right fog like mist and condensation in fact.
But it is it is a very well there's many specific thing.
There's many rides like where you know the smell of Pirates of the Caribbean or the Haunted
Mansion like those like I think people would probably pay like a top dollar for like a
spray in their house or a candle that would smell like just some 60 year old building.
Oh yeah.
Like some old water some little packet of 10 where you could label them real fast.
Here's the midway mania.
Here's what are other smells.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
And smells.
Oh yeah.
No.
Or the famous.
Aren't there.
There's there's some rides out there with some like fart smells.
For it doesn't start fart in the city.
Yeah.
The minions Shrek farts Shrek farts.
Shrek has a lot of farting.
Universal locking down those farts.
Yeah Shrek.
The Universal also is has the most fart smells on any of the rides because there's a minions
fart and then there's a Shrek fart.
And I think only Stitch might fart in Disney.
So yeah.
Universal's got Disney beat by that.
If ET or Botanic is fart they are silent farts.
Yeah.
We'll never know what they smell like.
Anyway amazing line.
It's a really great line.
And I think maybe.
Yeah like I was saying maybe the first Universal Studios line that kind of builds gets you
into the world of it helps tell the story.
It predates really excellent lines like the Indiana Jones ride or I can I assume the Avatar
line is great.
That's what I've heard.
The one the one nitpick I have with the line is that it starts in sort of a movie studio
area like it starts in a spot that looks like it's like there's just pictures of ET on the
wall which like for me personally I like it to be like immersive right from the get go.
So I would prefer that it's a sort of trees immediately versus like you go into this room
with pictures of ET and Drew Barrymore and then you go on the ride.
But the reason this is the case is is that they have changed the actual the pre show
that Steven Spielberg and the speech Steven Spielberg gives you.
Yes.
Yeah.
I'm really looking forward researching this because I can only remember the one Spielberg
video introducing that I believe the sum total in the history of the adventures that there
were three different Steven Spielberg intro videos all sort of with the same components.
Him reminding you that we don't have much time.
Only et ceiling touch can save his planet.
But the the the first one which when the ride first opened in 1990 in Florida there's a
video that I'm very fond of where Steven Spielberg is in a movie theater.
He's eating popcorn watching I guess ET.
He's just rewatching it remembering how hoping it holds up and and he's eating popcorn and
then you cut close to the popcorn and ET's fingers reach in there and they go to stalking
him throughout the video.
So that video kind of like yeah he's not aware of ET until deep into it.
But that yeah that fingers always poking around.
And once he finally taps him on the shoulder and gets his attention that fingers creepily
hang in there for five to ten seconds before he says anything.
We'll post a link of this in the meditator.
So but yeah the context the context of this is that the ride itself in the for the first
you know ten years that it was around was that this was a sequel to ET and we were all
actors and we were going to play our parts while we were on the ride.
So the reason that the ride starts in a spot that looks like a movie production place is
because initially they were thinking that we were all going to be pretending to be actors
while we went on the ride which they eventually thought was like this is stupid.
So then they put in that much more exciting intro that you heard at the top of this whole
segment.
Well even that one is the third one because there was a second mid step the one that you
played was from the was from like 2002 when there was a big 20th anniversary re-release
of ET.
There was one in the 90s which was almost the same thing.
And it's unclear to me why they changed it.
It's almost the same stuff.
Steven Spielberg in the forest you're going to be riding bikes.
He's wearing a vest in that one though.
Yes.
He's different clothes.
And in the new one he's wearing a hat which I really like.
I like when a director talks to you in a cap.
It lets you know that they are a director because they're wearing their iconic director's
cap.
Probably for a battleship.
Yes.
Probably.
A battleship they did not serve on.
They were gifted.
Oh yeah.
The very James Cameron-y.
Ron Howard.
The stolen valor.
Well making a movie is like going to war.
They survived the SS abyss or whatever.
So anyway yeah there's two intros where Steven Spielberg is in the forest.
The original one is Steven in the theater telling you you're going to be in a scene
and ET at the end telling you be good actors which is a very clunky phrase to come out
of ET's mouth.
I don't know that ET could mentally handle the concept of filmmaking.
And the logic.
Do you know what movies are?
The logic of it is all wrong too because ET is treated as if he's a real person.
So ET in this world is an actor that's playing ET.
Well this is confused logic that's in a lot of things and especially rides where you know
like in some cases Mickey Mouse or the Looney Tunes are real people in the world.
And somebody calls action on their cartoons and then they walk away from the set.
You actually see this in another Universal ride the Hanna-Barbera.
The fantastic world of Hanna-Barbera.
Long gone Hanna-Barbera.
Yeah yeah yeah one of the original rides.
But I just watched the video of that where you know Hanna and Barbera are telling Fred
Flintstone okay they need you on the set and then he walks away and doesn't speak or do
anything.
So there's a lot of media that has this confusing construct where the character is real and
they acted as themselves.
I guess you're being asked to believe that ET is like an eight mile situation where the
guy is doing his life story as a film.
And Universal used to really skirt the line like when it first opened in Florida there
was so much like fake like you know lighting rigs and like prop boxes and like a lot.
They really made everything look like a set and that's kind of how they got away with
like you know the Jaws ride is next to the Back to the Future ride.
It's just like you're on a back lot.
Yeah you're on a back lot that's come to life and you're going through them.
And what is weird with these different Spielberg things is that like Universal's original marketing
slogan that if you find any old kids show where they would give away a trip to Universal
Studios they would always do that tag like Universal Studios ride the movies.
And like it really used to split the difference on attractions of here's how a movie is made
versus now you are riding the movie.
Yeah there was some very tortured logic in a lot of that stuff in the Ghostbusters attraction
at Universal Florida.
You were on the soundstage where they filmed the final battle with Gozer but then it has
been haunted by actual ghosts and almost everything on the Universal tram tour has that construct
where like we're going on to a hot set where they're filming a new scene.
Wait a minute they left it all on like it's actually real King Kong is in the fake set.
I think Universal had a lot at a long time where they were this was too confusing and
they had trouble calibrating this and I like that now they're a little more just committed
to the simple if you're going into Harry Potter land you're in Harry Potter land you're not
on the set of the new Harry Potter.
There was a lot of awkward stuff where like originally when I was a kid at Universal Studios
you would go to the ADR stage where they're doing a new episode of Harry and the Hendersons
and you'd be watching the ADR you'd be watching the Foley sound effects session for Harry
and the Hendersons in 1999 and then there'd be this weird part where like oh no the audio
dropped out we have to record it live.
And in what world is there a live episode of Harry and the Hendersons in 1999.
I did a similar there was a very short-lived like how do they make Hercules the Legendary
Journeys and Xena Warrior Princess making of show where they would put you in front
of a green screen and I remember like being a volunteer in this and they made me look
like a centaur in front of a green screen.
Were you humiliated?
No I was psyched I was all about that I so wanted to do that.
Well you gained some height probably.
Yeah I did gain some height.
Congratulations.
The mighty legs of a horse.
My mother did that at Disney's MGM Studios there's the they had the thing where you would
like be in part of the TV shows it would be like superstar television I believe it was
called and it would be like someone was Gilligan's Island and my mom was on some soap opera and
she had to like pull a gun on someone and it confused the hell out of me.
Like I really I knew it was fake but I was like but my mom has a gun in a fur coat now
and like everything is different.
Like I didn't I really I was very confused.
Do you still have nightmares about this situation?
Yeah I say even talking about it I just flashed back to it it was it's weird it was weird
I still it's attached to a weird feeling in my head.
I think probably a lot of our theme park careers have led to some scarring memories and the
things that have given us disturbing dreams and weird complexes and we'll get into all
of them.
Yeah.
And the stuff about Universal there is a great article that I have read a few times now and
I just read again this morning it was in the dissolve if you guys remember the website
that dissolve it was when pitchfork tried to make a website for movie writing for film
writing that was it was a lot of like AV Club writers who move.
Yeah.
And they got a lot of AV Club writers and then eventually it got shut down.
But it's I think it's all still online.
It's all good websites with good writing.
Yeah.
And there really was a lot of great articles and there was an article about Universal Studios
Florida and the writer was speculating that like well one of the things that was different
of Universal Studios when it first opened in Florida and now is that there was a lot
more shows about like how movies are made.
Like how did Alfred Hitchcock do all those iconic scenes.
And a few things happened over time.
One DVD special features became ubiquitous.
So it's not much of a mystery of how they make movies anymore.
And then two is that you can just shoot movies on your phone and edit them on a laptop.
And so like they they really got rid of a lot of those shows and went towards like these
immersive like you're in the movie.
This is a new part.
This is a sequel or a prequel or something and you're living it.
I would add a number three to that which I honestly only really learned in the last couple
years.
Three would be most people don't give a shit.
Oh yeah.
Most people do not care about how movies are made.
About how things are written.
How things are conceived.
Like I brought a handful of friends out here and have taken them on this Universal Studios
Tram Tour.
They could have given a shit about it.
They do not care.
Because I'm like oh this soundstage.
Like I took them to the Warner Brothers lot.
Casablanca shot here and they're like yeah uh huh uh huh okay.
Where are we going next.
Like and I was I was floored.
I was like but the movies were made here and they're like I don't we don't care.
But if King Kong attacks that tram.
Well now you got.
Now you're working with us.
Now do you want to find out how that King Kong was made for the ride.
No fuck you.
Fuck you.
Fuck yourself.
That is then you are us.
The difference is that we do.
We would like to know.
Oh absolutely.
Like I've got short sleeve old engineers like tirelessly worked on like the the crotch of
King Kong.
Like how to make his legs swing a certain way.
Like give us that red meat.
The other thing that's weird is that I'm always going to websites and learning all this information
and then it's like oh god I wonder who built the King Kong robot.
Oh it was a guy named Bob Gurr.
Oh like what else do you do with that.
That's the end of that story.
Are you going to read what else he did.
Yeah you're like oh wow I like a lot of this man's work.
Yes sure.
But it's it's often hard to convey to other people which will be the challenge of doing
this part.
Oh is there any of this interesting.
Are we doing this for ourselves.
Are all podcasts kind of for yourself possibly.
We have a lot of big picture questions we hope to get to the bottom of.
Anyway let's talk.
So that no let's talk interplanetary passports.
A great topic.
Explain what the hell this is.
Yeah so Steven Spielberg mentioned it a while ago.
But when you begin the adventure experience you are set up with an operator in the early
days of the ride probably AT&T who are the sponsors of it and you had to give your name
to the operator who would put your name on to a special passport a little like flimsy
card.
And if you're going on this ride in Florida today almost 30 years deep that is the most
flimsy falling apart unlaminated peeling off card you've ever seen.
Although I've seen them sell on eBay for like three thousand dollars.
It's crazy.
But anyway the payoff of all of this is that at the end of the ride due to the interplanetary
passport ET says your name.
He says your name to you.
Cool stuff right.
Uh huh.
Very.
Yeah.
Like wow ET is going to call me by my first name and then the reality of it is that ET
doesn't enunciate well as we said before and he enunciates even worse on the ride than
he does in the movie.
Can we all just like to try to say our names the way ET would.
Yes.
Ah.
Jason.
And Jason was the luckiest of the best.
I get it pretty close but my dad.
My dad is also named Michael and I feel like Michael does not come out like a very common
American name.
I went on it the last time I've been on this ride was went on this ride was three years
ago and he garbled his way through the hole like eight people that were on the ride vehicle
which is like ah ah ah ah ah.
Just like one after another of like butchering and like he was drunk or something like.
Boning it in more than like Steven Spielberg.
Like Brian Wilson being shoved in front of the piano at the Beach Boys concert.
He's kind of playing it a little.
Hey look we're just happy he's around.
We're happy to see him.
Happy to see our friend ET our friend Brian Wilson.
I think they're equivalent figures.
Dr. Landy worked with ET and Brian.
ET tried to do a rap song once too.
But so and it's never worked out great and you also you I feel like you were always like
a little behind it.
Like you ET is no longer in your frame of vision by the time he's saying your name.
Yeah.
They was never timed out to correctly.
But I the idea of this was so neat and I and this was so long before there was any customization
of of rides.
Now you go on star tours and it picks you to be the spy or there's going to be a lot
of interactivity in the upcoming Star Wars land.
But I think without ET saying your name you don't have those greater better pulled off
milestones in the future.
That's an early innovation that people have built on.
You would have thought though by now in 2017 they could have just fixed the fucking thing.
They could have done something that would actually make I mean I read today on something
that people were like like talk eat the ET voices working again.
But I don't know that they've completely overhauled it.
They really should just get a teenager to do the voice and say it like they really should
just get just print a sheet out.
Do it live.
Have an 18 year old kid.
OK.
Well do it.
If I can't.
I don't think I'm live.
And then ET just reads down the list and the kid because they do that.
They have like the fun like talking fountains and stuff in universal.
They have like charming performers college students.
There's a fountain over by the Harry Potter.
It's in the what's the what's the land by Harry Potter and the Lost Continent.
The Lost Continent.
Thank you.
A forgotten universe an original creation of like universal that most people walk right
through.
Sure.
That's what we did.
Except Poseidon show.
Yeah.
One of our my girlfriend and I's favorite memories is the fountain.
Well I had a very like cool like English voice and it was like talking to this little girl
and he was like Olivia.
Hello Olivia.
Olivia come over here Olivia.
And we were like very charmed by this talking fountain.
So I feel like they have the capability to make ET speak.
We're missing out on stuff like this British Olivia voice.
Yeah.
That fountain is a guy that there's a camera on that fountain and there's a guy somewhere
watching that person.
I know.
I know that.
So you're saying they should do that for ET.
I know it's not a real talking fountain.
I'm just saying they can have a clearer voice.
Do you know that?
I do know that.
I think you might just be a fucking idiot.
I am not a fucking idiot.
If you're lying.
Don't tell people that's what I am.
But that fountain every time I see that fountain it's sassy.
Like it's ragging on people.
It's like roasting people and shooting water at them.
Universal has a whole thing where they rag on you a little more than Disney does.
Because I got ragged on by those New York Street performers before.
Where they're like oh look at this guy.
Look at this guy here.
And they can't say anything meaner.
They can't swear.
So all they can do is be like this lady's wearing a funny hat.
Look at that lady's hat.
Like really like if it was a real issue you'd be like this fucking bitch.
But like they can't say that.
So it's just like look at that guy.
He's got a funny pair of pants on.
Look at that guy's pants.
It's devastating.
If those New York people get on you.
Oh man it's devastating.
You're starting your vacation off being humiliated.
What is this guy from Denver?
Yes.
Oh.
You live on a mountain pal.
Look at this mountain guy.
And like that does work.
The audience.
Yeah people like him.
But if you're getting roasted it's like.
I'd avoid that at all costs.
Still today they're saying all this stuff about the Star Wars attractions that you're
gonna have a reputation that carries you along through all these.
Somebody will criticize you for doing a bad job on the Millennium Falcon ride.
It's a lot of pressure.
Sounds horrible to me.
But maybe ET should roast you a little bit as you get off the ride.
Fuck you buddy.
Don't come back.
You were baggage on that bike.
Look at your hat.
Look at this fucking hat.
What are you from Denver?
You don't even like Magdahl.
You weren't nice to Teakley.
One of my oldest friends and this is how you treat him.
Sort of like grouchy Jewish ET that we're developing.
That would be an improvement though.
Come visit me more often.
Come on.
So my other question is how do you improve this ride?
What do we do to the ride?
We're in charge of the park.
Do we fix it?
Do we tear it out?
What happens to the ET adventure?
We've come up with an official grading system.
Let's call it an unofficial grading system.
So there's three choices that we should each pick of what we would do with this ride.
Would we one, keep it as is.
Don't do anything to it.
It's perfect.
We want to preserve it for future generations.
Two, keep the ride but plus it up.
Make some changes.
Make some improvements to it.
Maybe that grouchy Jewish ET at the end.
Or three, we hate the ride and we want to burn it down in an accidental fire for insurance
purposes.
Quote unquote accidental fire.
Universal Studios history is littered with quote unquote accidental fires.
Disney has one or two as well.
I suppose there are.
There's serious insurance fires.
You can get some money if something burns down and you didn't have anything to do with
it.
Look there's fireworks going off.
There's all manner of things.
You know.
Anything can happen.
Just grunled employees quote unquote.
A lot of water.
A lot of electronics.
I mean we've all thought about it in our daily lives folks.
Yeah.
About burning down a universal studio.
So alright Jason you go first.
What would your choice be?
Would you keep it as plus up or burn it down?
I think plus up because I do like this ride.
I feel like people like ET's not fully in the front of our consciousness but I feel
like people still like ET.
I feel like that's a classic family movie and this is this ride.
I think a lot of it is still fun.
I feel like yeah there is stuff that can be improved.
That weird room where they're giving you the passport that looks like a movie set.
They just turn the whole line into a forest queue or something.
And yeah put some more animatronics in and like make ET talk better at the end.
So I think keep it and plus it up.
And I think this will probably.
I mean I'm saying this ride will probably outlive us all.
Really?
Well it's an interesting note because they've gotten rid of two of them.
There was one in Orlando.
There was one in Japan and there was one here.
And the one here and in Japan went away.
And it angered Mr. Spielberg apparently and he put his foot down and he kept the one here.
It angers me.
I say you know I'm all for replacing rides if you have a better ride to go in its place.
And the one in Japan looks kind of cool.
I don't know if you guys have looked this up.
There's a ride called Space Fantasy The Ride.
And it looks kind of neat.
You get to like fly into the sun or something.
It's a spinning roller coaster.
It looks like a blast.
But here oddly similarly there's this mummy ride where you go into an eclipse or something.
That's the end of the ride.
You get spun around and they flash a lot of lights at you and somebody yells the eclipse.
What?
Where?
Am I in it?
Is it happening far away from me?
What's the story with this eclipse?
Yeah the mummy ride at Universal Studios Hollywood is trash.
I think it's an awful ride.
Yeah I mean there's a couple things to like a couple tiny things to like about it.
Yeah there's a better version of it in Florida.
And it feels very generic.
It feels like you're just in a warehouse on a roller coaster which is like fun viscerally.
But where's the theming?
Where is the adventure and the fun of going to the green goddamn planet?
Like it's a step down.
It's a bummer that that's the thing that replaced it.
And Spielberg helped make Universal Studios Florida.
Like he was like the big guiding Hollywood consultant.
So they want to keep him happy because he still consults on the parks.
Yeah I mean I am worried though if he dies.
If they go well Steven's dead and then like the bulldozers hit the ride in Orlando the
next day.
All the contracts are off.
We're all gonna die one day.
I know we're all gonna die.
I know that too.
So Scott what is your, so you want to, what would your choice be?
Oh yeah.
Plus it up.
Bring it back in Hollywood.
God damn it.
And you know what I think hurts the ride is that you don't really know who Botanicus is.
He's his teacher.
Okay.
What did he teach him to do?
What is the connection there?
What's the relationship?
I want to know.
Maybe in that pre-ride sequence you watch a little film or something.
Maybe we bring E.T. into the language of like the CGI movies.
The Despicable Me kind of animation that all the kids love these days.
Maybe you do some new stuff that explains who Botanicus is.
It explains who Mooc Mooc or these other Glip Glop, all these Green Planet characters are.
Maybe provide some context so by the time you see them in the ride you love them.
You want to reach out of the bike and give them a hug.
That brings up a great point.
You have to get E.T. back to the Green Planet so his healing touch can fix the Green Planet.
None of these other assholes have that power.
What is Botanicus' power?
Botanicus has an orb where it seems like he gets his power from.
There's a cool orb that's by him.
Is the power just to see E.T. and what he's doing?
Yes.
That must be it.
It's like a crystal ball.
My theory about E.T. is that much like Superman when he's exposed to Earth's yellow sun, that's
how he gets his powers.
He doesn't have powers on Krypton.
E.T. under our yellow sun on Earth has these magical powers to grow plants and stuff.
But I would imagine all of his species has that.
It's not like E.T.
They really present E.T. as a dumpy little boy in that movie.
It's not like E.T.'s this extraordinary alien that can bring something back.
This ride frames him as the chosen one.
I don't think the movie was not about him being the kid.
He was just a regular kid hanging out with another kid.
But in fact when he's gone the planet has gone to shit.
When you first arrive at that Green Planet.
It's a bunch of, it's just gas.
People are, characters are dying.
It does have that thing where the ride is like the movie and that it's like scary and
depressing.
E.T. is a very upsetting film.
And when you arrive at the Green Planet it's like you're watching E.T. in the incubation
unit frothing at the mouth and dying.
I guess he doesn't see, he doesn't foam.
But in my, I'll never know because I don't want to watch that E.T. death stuff ever again.
It's very depressing.
I did not care for it as a child.
It was very, yeah, very traumatizing.
My mom would ask do you want to watch E.T.?
Like no, please no.
Did I do something wrong?
But yeah, maybe you learn more about these people.
You up the stakes.
I think better animatronics.
Although maybe not those cops.
Maybe I like that those cops are apartment store mannequins.
They're brainless automatons the way the worst of the police officers are.
Really the very, very, we're not all of them.
You know what I'm saying.
Folks, the state has a monopoly on violence.
But we're not going down that road.
Michael, what's your verdict?
Oh, on that note.
I am going to also say plus it up.
And I have some idea.
We all are on the same page with this.
The first thing I have is that I would like Steven Spielberg to record the video again.
I would like a fourth video.
Every year.
Let's keep sending him out.
Because the last one was in 2002, I think, or something around then.
I think it needs an update.
And here's what I propose.
He isn't Steven Spielberg in the video.
You don't use his name.
You can be cute about it.
He can be like, hello, I'm E.T.'s friend, Steve.
And we can say Steve and there can be a wink of like.
Because I don't like the idea that it's this director of the movie.
He needs to play a character in the universe.
I want it to sell that we're in another adventure.
But is it going to confuse people?
Are they going to think that he's the store owner from the Blues Brothers?
The most iconic Steven Spielberg character?
If that movie was in the last had come out in the last 30 years.
Then maybe.
Why didn't he reprise it in 2000?
Oh, that.
Why?
That is a good question.
That would have been a good callback.
Old store owner.
So I want Steve.
I want him to play Steve.
And I also want a little more explanation, because in this ride, it's like, why is E.T.
back on Earth already?
It's not the same thing from the movie.
So I would like I would propose this.
That the video is sort of E.T. and his friend Steve doing something.
And Steve is like, thanks for coming back to Earth, E.T.
Like, it's so good.
Like they're doing they could be playing cards.
They could be watching a movie.
I don't care.
And then Botanic is on the video comes to them and goes with my splitter voice, like,
you must.
He's sort of like, it's like a warmer.
Yeah, warmer.
I am Botanic.
That's offensive.
I'm sorry.
E.T., where are you going?
We got to finish Bridge of Spies.
And then, yeah, that's good.
That's fine.
If you want to put a nod to the Steven Spielberg's work, but not reference that he directed it.
And then Steve explains to the audience that he can't go.
But E.T. had just got a transmission from Botanicus and they need to go.
And you guys are the ones to help.
So then that makes sense.
Now we know why he's there.
Now we know we're not confused why the director of the movie is there.
We just know there's a mission.
We're going to go help E.T. go back.
Then, yeah, you get rid of that thing where it's like a movie studio.
You put more trees in there.
You come up with a cooler way to do the name thing.
Like maybe E.T. asks you your name or something before.
Like you have to just say it to him.
And then there's a teenager behind there and he hears the name of it.
And then that's when he says it later, which I guess kind of kills the fun of talking to
E.T. until the end.
So maybe I can workshop that.
Put the interplanetary passport on your phone.
That's a great idea.
Sure, great.
The apps are big these days.
They have not converted those interplanetary passport cards to QR codes yet.
They're still rocking a barcode.
There we go.
Let's get it up to 2012 technology.
Yeah.
Also, a thing that bothers me is that they call him E.T.
His aliens call him.
His friends from the planet call him E.T., which is not his name.
I know his real name.
His real name is Zrek.
Z-R-E-K.
Because that is in the book.
Oh, that just rolls off the top.
Zrek.
So if we're going to be accurate, they should be like, hello, Zrek.
That's how they should be calling him.
I understand it'll confuse tourists, but let's be accurate.
Maybe you can slash a disclaimer with an asterisk as that is said, or pause the ride entirely,
unfurl a big sheet of information in the original, in the E.T. mythology.
E.T. is Zrek.
Obviously, they wouldn't call him E.T.
That's a name that Elliot made up, so that's why this is what it is.
And then the paper goes back up.
You continue with the ride.
Sure.
Yeah, that's fine.
Zrek is, I think, the name the Zodiac Killer signed some of his letters with.
Nice little reference.
Nice little Easter egg in that E.T. book to the Zodiac Killer.
He almost signed it Botanicus.
He was a flip of a coin.
I would install a few more Botanicus animatronics as well.
He has to have a little bit of a stronger presence.
Also, maybe make sort of a Force ghost, Star Wars ghost Botanicus during the ride, or the
first part of the ride, where he says, close call, you're almost there, or watch out, or
something like, have his presence be felt, because he's such a big, they pipe him up
to be so big, and then he's barely on the ride.
He barely does anything.
His big ghost is hovering above Dodger Stadium in the fake Los Angeles, visible in the spotlights.
This way.
I'm missing now.
Don't hit Chavez Ravine on your way out.
Yeah.
And then, also, tone down, because when they get to the Green Planet, it feels like they're
all the Munchkins in the Wizard of Oz.
It's a very Munchkin vibe.
Like, right this way.
Yes, you're welcome home.
You've arrived.
Pick a different thing.
It doesn't, I don't know why everyone would be so cheery.
And I think more E.T.'s.
Don't you want to see a ton of E.T.'s?
You want a ton of E.T.'s.
Not these little plant guys you never met.
The plant guys don't make any sense.
More E.T.'s and make them, one is a Mohawk or something.
One is like a, whatever the E.T. version of a Mohawk is.
If one had an electric guitar, like, who does the rock and roll E.T.?
He rips a quick solo.
And then you could do a thing where there's a new song every time you ride the ride.
You got a DJ one with a big dead mouse helmet.
Sure.
Let's make it relevant to the rave kids.
And you know what?
How about one girl one?
There.
One girl E.T.
Very token.
Let's be progressive here.
Token girl E.T.
Just blonde hair.
Which looks just like the E.T. from the closet.
Which is a photo op you can get after the ride.
Oh yeah.
Don't forget.
And then yeah, my last thing is for all these different characters and for Botanicus, as
Mr. Spielberg calls him, where's the merch?
Where's the Botanicus doll?
Like why isn't, like why are we not taking advantage?
Like the big part of theme parks is like marketing and selling some shit, moving merchandise.
You know what?
My favorite obscure characters, the Captain EO, Idy and Ody and Major Domo.
Major and Minor Domo.
And Hooter.
I have a little Hooter.
They do have dolls of these obscure things.
Why not ruffle through notes, ruffle through notes, Orbadon?
I want to take an Orbadon home.
Yeah, they should have more Orbadon merch.
I had that marketing worked on me as a kid so much.
I was like, look, it's the merch from the ride and you can't get this anywhere else,
you little fuck.
You better buy it now.
It's like, yeah, I better buy it now.
Where else would I fucking buy this?
Now the answer is eBay or Etsy.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, so.
Too many opportunities to share in the magic.
But I mean, when the ride goes away, it's hard to get that merch.
So like, you'll cherish that Botanicus doll for the next 30 years.
Who's the mushroom one, Orbadon?
Orbadon.
You get a big mushroom helmet.
Yes.
It doesn't have to just be a doll.
Becomes an heirloom.
Parents pass them, this is my Orbadon son and it's your Orbadon now.
I think like in the late 90s when kids were rocking the cat in the hat hat, kids are going
to be wearing that Orbadon hat at raves.
It'll be different colored Orbadon hats.
It's the new Devo energy dome.
Yeah.
For a new generation of kids who will get beat up as soon as they wear it in public.
So I mean, that's.
Orbadon helmets is the solution.
We all agree.
Keep it.
So implement, keep it and implement all of our solutions now, please.
You heard us, Universal Studios Big Wigs.
I got an in there, right?
Got a minimum wage job there.
They owe me.
Hey, start to get cranking on those Orbadon helmets, would you?
Yeah.
Send them an MP3 of this and.
And assume that they listen to it.
They might.
Folks, we'll be right back.
Folks we're back.
Here with a segment we're calling Souvenir Smackdown.
The three of us.
Souvenir Smackdown.
There.
That was a cue.
Souvenir.
Souvenir Smackdown.
All right.
We got all the morning radio.
The Zoo Crew stuff.
Folks, there's a large secondary market, I guess you'd call it, for theme park merch and
souvenirs on pretty much any website that sells stuff.
Amazon, eBay, Etsy.
And you can find vintage souvenirs, maps, tickets, anything you want you could find on these
websites.
And we, the three of us set out to each find a weird thing.
Yeah.
So we're going to find out who has found the weirdest piece of souvenir merchandise.
And then I guess we'll all vote on it.
I suppose so.
You might call this stuff Disneyana.
Yes.
That's that technical term.
Although some of it might not be from Disneyland.
So I don't know what kind of Anna it is.
It's the theme park Anna, I guess.
What is that?
Why is that word Disneyana?
I don't know.
I have no idea because it's not Anna.
It should be memorabilia, like Disney-belia.
Right.
Universal-belia.
Does it come from like antiquing?
Like maybe.
Like Americana?
Antiquing.
Is it Disney and Americana mashed up?
Could be.
Better name.
Burn down the name Disneyana for insurance money.
Tell us on Twitter if you know what, where did that come from?
Yeah.
So.
All right.
So who wants to go first?
I'll go.
Jason, you go first.
All right.
I got it.
Okay.
So I found, now we all know when you shop for collectibles, like collectible toys, you
want to keep it in the packaging so that it accrues value over time.
And it's in good shape when you keep it in the packaging.
With like toys and shit.
But what I found is a weird thing to keep in the packaging.
This is a, I don't know what year this is copyrighted.
This is a child's swim ring featuring the orange bird still in the packaging.
All right.
We'll have pictures of all of this on the, on all the social media stuff.
So this is an inflatable swim ring that you would wear around your waist featuring the
orange bird.
For those of you out there who don't know the orange bird, a character created by Walt
Disney Productions in the 1970s for the Florida Citrus Commission in exchange for that commission
sponsoring the Enchanted Tiki Room in Florida.
So and a character that went away for a long time and then became a huge hit in Japan.
So they brought him back.
Where would you see this character?
What's an example of the orange bird in the world?
You will see him in Florida at this, the place in Adventureland at Disney World where they
sell the citrus swirl, a combination of vanilla soft serve and orange icey.
And then you'll just see him in souvenir shops.
How would you describe the attitude of this character, this beloved in Japan character,
the orange bird?
He's sassy.
He's fun loving.
He has a head that looks like an orange and the rest of his body is either green or orange.
And he is no longer associated with the Florida Citrus Commission.
He's just back to being a Disney park exclusive character.
So he's a free agent.
He could advertise any citrus commission he wants.
That's true.
If your state is looking for a mascot.
So the eBay listing has ended.
They said it is a vintage 1970s, still in the packaging.
Guess how much money this child's inflatable swimming device sold for.
So this is like an inner tube, right?
Yeah, this is like a little inner tube you would put around your waist.
And it's from the 70s.
It's from the 70s.
Still in the packaging.
You wouldn't use it.
You could try though.
You could try, yeah.
Let me throw out a $200.
I think they're asking for $800.
Scott was closer.
It went for $133.62.
That's reasonable actually.
Yeah.
Horrible, although also the furthest character you don't really know and what is it and who
would be impressed by this?
Would this make you happy at home?
Would your spouse be impressed if you had this?
Also, it's not like an action figure or a little statue that you can see it in the box.
It is a folded up inflatable tube.
It's a Lesley's Pool Supply scrunched up in the box still.
You can't see the picture.
You could just kind of make out part of the word Florida.
Orrid.
I guess you would have to, if you wanted to display, you would have to try to blow it
up.
You have to open it.
Blow it up, yeah.
How long can an inner tube last for 45 years?
I don't know.
Did you purchase this product?
Is the purchaser of this listening?
If so, let us know.
Yeah, tweet at us.
What you want to do with it.
Why you bought it.
If you did and you've used it, just tweet us a photo of you in a lake with the thing
around you floating.
Because that would be great.
That would be very exciting.
Tweet at us at podcasttheride on Twitter.
Yes.
All right, Scott.
All right.
I will read mine with the same capitalization as the entry does.
Walt Disney.
Animal Kingdom.
Authentic leaves.
Tree of life.
Extremely rare prop.
What this is, and let me show you gentlemen without, I'm going to show you a picture of
two leaves.
This without showing you the price.
So the centerpiece of Animal Kingdom is a giant fake tree.
These are two leaves on the same little branch from the tree of life.
Let me read some facts about it.
This is the ultimate Disney collectible.
An actual branch with two leaves from the tree of life.
This branch with two leaves is from a bigger branch that was removed from the tree after
an incident in May 2012 in which the branch fell onto a public path during bark hours.
Public?
This seems like a private transgression.
Very special item and very rare.
This type of Disney souvenir has never been on the market.
The tree of life branch is about 25 inches long.
The first leaf is about 12 inches long and seven and a half inches wide.
The second leaf is about 12 inches long and seven and a half inches wide.
Just to clarify the difference between the first and second leaf.
Of course they are scratched after spending many years in the Florida weather.
Alright?
So deal with it.
Florida is rough as hurricanes.
They're scratched.
Alright?
Just buy them anyway.
Do not miss this opportunity.
What is the material?
What does it say it's made of?
I don't believe it says that.
I mean what are Disney trees made of?
I mean it's some rubber and whatever.
Plaster and rubber.
Plasticky.
Does it even say how they obtained this?
Did it fall off while they were at it?
It fell and I think probably whoever is selling this went and grabbed it and hauled it out
of the park.
Decided to make a nice pretty penny off of it.
Yeah and it implies to me, I think it says that it was part of a bigger branch.
This guy might have upwards of...
Oh he has the full branch.
Could have like 20 leaves.
He's selling it for parts.
Yeah.
Holding out.
Would you like to...
This is not sold.
There are four people watching.
One of them myself.
Would you like to guess the asking price for this item?
I'll say 200.
100 elite.
I was going to say 200 exactly.
Yeah.
The asking price is $29,000.
What?
No.
Come on.
Is that the buy it now price?
Let me see that.
I have to see that.
That is the buy it now price.
Oh okay.
There are no offers.
Maybe that's the buy it now.
People can set.
They're all handed around if you want to.
You can set.
That means they're setting it.
That doesn't mean if someone had put up that money, that means they would have been making
a commitment.
Can we make an offer right now?
Just like $10?
Yeah.
Maybe we should.
First we need to set up podcasttheride at eBay.com.
We're going to sell out of our merch.
Yeah.
No.
Let's do it and see.
Maybe we can end up with these.
$29,000.
We'll update you on a future episode.
Because I would imagine if somebody thinks this is worth $29,000 and they get an offer
for $10, they're going to be furious.
Did you not read the story?
This fell on a public path.
Oh my gosh.
Unprecedented in Disney history.
And yeah, they're beat up, but God shut up.
Don't bother me about that anymore.
Theme park enthusiasts angry about something?
I have never heard of such a thing.
The branch with tulis from Moogerv Branch after an incident in May 2012.
So there's a possibility that a person shimmied up the tree and ripped a branch off as well.
That's a good point.
There's a possibility this is illegally obtained.
We're trying to take the leaves back into our hands, democratize the leaves.
Or it fell on someone and someone saw it and they ran up and they're like, oh my God.
And they grabbed the branch before helping the other person.
This could be crucial evidence in the trial that could finally bring Disney down, bring
it to its knees.
And yet it was stolen, maybe hidden away by Disney themselves.
Maybe we're accessories to murder if we buy this item.
Disney does sell a lot of stuff to theme park.
To the Van Eten galleries where I've bought some Epcot signs, which I'm sure I'll talk
about on every episode.
There's a giant warehouse in Florida where you can just buy the sign from the hotel or
like a monorail door.
Well, the monorail door.
Yeah, I'm all about that.
We all, we would all really like a monorail door in our living room.
That's my $29,000 item.
Yeah, I would like the full people mover car.
Oh, sure.
Just like in your kitchen.
Which I've seen at this auction that I went to that I believe was set around $29,000 and
this is being asked for two leaves.
I'm going to the D, well, when this comes out, this may not make sense, D23, but they
always have a car.
You can always buy a car there for like $25,000 a people mover car.
Really?
Yeah, I hope so you'll hopefully ride one up to the next record.
Yeah, that'll become, the people mover car will become my real car.
I'll sell my current car.
I mean, I ride everywhere in just a sidecar.
That's a good point.
You just coast.
Okay, so here we go.
Here's mine.
This kind of doesn't fall.
I kind of moved out of the rules of the game a little bit, but this is so funny to me.
I had to do it.
I'll read the description and then I'll show you the picture because the picture is everything.
This Winnie the Pooh collectible Disneyland promotional art depicting Winnie the Pooh
with a park guest in front of Sleeping Beauty Castle.
This original full color illustration was created during the development of promotional
materials on behalf of the Disneyland Resort in Anaheim, California.
Now that all sounds pretty normal, right?
Sure.
Okay, but like, does this art look weird to anyone else?
Let me crane around.
Oh, fuck.
What the hell?
So what's going on here is that it's a drawing of Winnie the Pooh and a very attractive woman.
Yeah, real 70s hair.
Or she kind of reminds me of like, you know, she looks like a Jan Hooks.
She looks like a young Jan Hooks.
She looks like she just got engaged to a life-size Winnie the Pooh.
That is my point is that these two don't look like a tourist and a person in a costume.
These two look like lovers.
This is a little sexualized what we're looking at.
That was probably not the intention, but it's just, it's so weird because I imagine this
is probably why this never became like a big image they ever used for a lot of things.
But it definitely looks like Pooh and this human woman are having sex with each other
or about to have sex.
Her hand we can't see is in his back pocket.
Like that's what this is.
He doesn't have a back pocket though.
We can't see beneath the weight.
We can kind of see, but he could be wearing a half shirt and he has like bell bottoms
on.
He's got his arm around her in such, and again, this will be posted on the various social
medias.
He's got his arm around her in such an intimate way and she's kind of just like has her left
hand like resting on his breast, his like bosom, his peck, Winnie's peck.
It's a couple's photo.
It's a prom photo for sure.
Yeah.
It's just so bizarre.
There's not much more to it.
I will add, how much do you think they're asking for this?
Sorry, what's the context of it again?
Is this concept art?
It says it was concept art for a promotion.
It's possible this is just some perverts fan art and they're pretending that it was something
they were developing, the Disney company was developing.
And that if you buy the full thing, you get to see Winnie the Pooh's erect penis at the
bottom of the cutoff point.
Oh bother.
And it is the 70s Pooh, like he does look, it's not a much, so this is obviously like
old or-
The signature on the shirt.
The signature on the shirt is the old one.
This is like an ice storm couple.
This is the couple that was cut out of the ice storm.
Pooh's head is like resting too, like right on her bosom.
He's yeah, bosom and mouth are perfectly lined up.
He looks more lascivious than the normal Pooh as well.
He does a little something to him.
He looks a little bit more adult or human.
A little more sassy, a little more sexualized.
Like it's if the guy's, the woman's husband is taking the photo and he's like, check this
out, old man.
Look what I'm doing here.
Again, weird sexuality among Disney fans.
Who could imagine that?
All right, so what do we think?
In what quality do you get this item?
It is just, so here's what it looks like.
It's just, oh, did you see the thing?
No, I did not.
Okay, so it's kind of a big sketch.
Let's say $80.
Card stock?
$150.
$400.
And on the back it says, in handwritten it says, DL Co-op, feel like a kid, Pooh slash
guest slash castle.
$400, make an offer.
Should we offer, what would the offer be?
What would you pay for?
Oh, we can make the offer?
I think we set a podcast amount and it's always what it is.
$8.99 no matter what item.
Hey, the price is right.
We offer $8.99 for, yeah.
Let's start for sexual Pooh.
We got a budget.
That Pooh looks like he just, they just said like how was the wedding?
Like they just got married.
Yeah, yeah.
Pooh just said the joke like, well the wedding was great but I've been enjoying the honeymoon
a lot more.
And is honeymoon a pun?
Oh, yeah.
That's what I intended.
Let's say that.
All right, good, good.
Yeah, sure.
Very clever.
That's very clever.
Nice, cleverer than I am.
Who wins this war?
How do we decide this?
Yeah, how do we decide who?
I'll be honest.
I think Jason's is the least weird.
Yeah, I think it is too.
I think it's the least kind of the most pathetic.
What did you guys search?
What did you, I typed in like vintage Disney world.
I did all that stuff and then I just typed in Disneyland and then I set it to highest
price first and then just started scrolling down.
Yeah.
There's a lot of good, I mean, I'll save some of these for later but there's like for $450
you can get a Marie Osmond Disneyland 50th anniversary rose doll.
That's creepy.
I don't know what it is.
That's creepier than Neeti's friend with the tentacle hair.
I don't know who Rose is.
We don't have time to get into that.
We'll have to do a whole episode on Rose one of these days.
Is it between you and I?
I think it's between us.
So let's let Jason decide because I'm going to vote for myself.
The poo thing is weird.
I mean, there's a lot of erotic fan art.
There's a lot of erotic pop culture art online.
I think the Scots, the mysterious incident associated with Scots plus that $29,000 buy
it now.
It takes it into weird territory.
It takes it into a very strange territory.
Well, I agree, obviously.
I'm taking the whole package into consideration.
Yes, I agree.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Because yeah, okay.
I will accept defeat is what I'm saying.
Hooray.
I will lose.
Scott wins the first round.
Scott wins the souvenir.
Smackdown.
Yes.
And with that, we come to the first ending.
The first conclusion of the first podcast, The Ride.
We're closing up.
What's the theme park terminology?
The kiss goodnight.
That's what they call it.
That is what they call it at the end of the night.
They call it what Disney officially closes and they do a little light show at the castle.
Well, this is a good way to get no return listeners.
And now the kiss goodnight.
All right.
All three of us at once.
Never again.
That segment might not come back.
Sorry, kiss goodnight fans.
Hey, this was fun.
We're going to do it again.
And if you have any suggestions, anything you want to hear about, hear rambled about
for an hour in the world of theme parks, let us know.
Check out our social media handles at podcast, the ride on Twitter and Instagram.
And the email is podcast, the ride at gmail.com.
So if you have any ideas for shows, except wait, no colons, right?
Because in the title of the show, there'd be a colon, but we don't have the colons in
those.
Yeah, no colons.
No colons.
Great.
Okay.
Now that that's been settled, email us, tweet at us.
Thanks to Feral Audio and everybody here for helping us do this thing.
I'm Mike Carlson, you can find me at Fat Carlson on Twitter, P-H-A-T-C-A-R-L-S-O-N, hashtag
botanicus.
Hey, we didn't even talk about it.
That's a thing that everybody says at Mike.
If you go out with Mike in public, people say hashtag botanicus.
Well, I was waiting for the tease at the end because anyone who's listening to this knowing
about botanicus was like, what is he going to say anything about it?
Well, he the ultimate use of hashtag botanicus.
Yeah, I strung everybody out.
I strung everyone along.
At Scott Gardner, at Jason.
Oh, no, that was it.
Okay.
At Jason Sheridan on Twitter and Instagram.
At Scott Gardner.
Hashtag botanicus.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
We'll see you next time.
Good night.
Ferrell Audio.