Feral Audio.
Warning, the following podcast includes high octane Harrison Ford impressions, unadulterated adoration for the character Mutt Williams, and a pulse-pounding discussion of the Indiana Jones Adventure.
Strap in for Podcast the Ride.
Hello ladies and gentlemen and welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show about theme parks hosted by three childless men in their 30s. I'm Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
Hello.
And Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
We are part of the Feral Audio Network, home to Doughboys and many other great podcasts, and we are the one about theme parks, as I said.
Yes, we are.
It's been an exciting time in the world of theme parks lately. We're going to talk about the D23 Expo, which one of the three of us went to.
And our topic today is the Indiana Jones Adventure, aka Indiana Jones Temple of the Forbidden Eye, one of the great theme park rides of our time, of the time in which we've been alive.
Very excited.
So, yeah, welcome.
So, Mike, as I said, you just went to the D23 Expo, which for anybody listening who doesn't know it, it's the Comic Con of Disney, basically.
Yeah, it's three days, three wonderful days in Anaheim. It's right by Disneyland. It's at the Anaheim Convention Center.
And yeah, if you know what Comic Con is, a Comic Convention, it is that, but just exclusively Disney.
So, like, you're getting panels from Imagineers, you're getting, like, big stadium filling events where they bring out movie stars and showing Disney and Pixar movies.
And the, you know, the thing that I was most excited about is the Parks and Resort presentation, where they announce all the fun rides and things coming to the Disney parks in the next few years.
And resorts.
There are cool resorts coming up.
Yeah, there are different resorts. So it's crazy. So, yeah, so it's three days of that. And it's like, in addition to that, you're also going, like, table to table and seeing, like, people selling old merchandise.
So there's people, like, first of all, they'll have, like, old Fred McMurray Disney posters for movies that he made that you've never heard of.
He's the guy from The Absent-Minded Professor and My Three Sons.
Other films.
Yeah, there you go.
Double Indemnity is a very famous, not a Disney movie, but a famous movie he was in.
That famous Disney movie, Double Indemnity.
Well, Disney bought the theme park rights, but they did not.
They have not. You made it the Double Indemnity ride, but.
Or a live show or a firework show.
The Double Indemnity stunt show, I believe, is what they would have to do.
You have to throw a body off a train caboose.
Can we get a volunteer?
You could get a job as a Double Indemnity stunt double.
They had a big Fred McMurray picture, like, it was just a giant, like, it was probably, like, 10 feet by 10 feet picture of him.
And I go, what the hell?
And I walked over and it's like, oh, it's he's like one of the first Disney legends, which is a distinction they give a lot of different people, like, that have, like, made a difference in the Disney, you know, whether it's movies or theme parks.
And they shed his footprints and handprints on display.
OK. Oh, the Disney Legends ceremony is a thing that happened at this event.
Yes.
Oprah is a Disney legend now.
Because she has a movie coming out this year that Disney made.
And she was well, she was syndicated, but she was on ABC stations.
Is that part of it? Maybe.
I think that's right.
She was joined by who else?
Mark Hamill, Carrie Fisher, Stan the Man Lee and Jack Kirby, which is funny because now these these people, the Star Wars and Marvel have been bought by Disney.
So now they have to retroactively sort of be Disney legends because of their contributions to the IPs that Disney bought.
So they were also part of the ceremony.
They ride around in like a little weird parade.
So like there's little cars and like it's Mark Hamill having to wave to people inside the convention center inside and out.
Yes. I do not see them.
Not on to Catella Avenue.
They don't go into a main drag.
There are no no main drags for the parade.
The parade is mostly just on the sidewalk outside the convention center by the right by like the Sbarro's pizza.
Is where the cars drive by and like everyone waves.
Yeah. So that happens.
I mean, there's so much stuff they have.
The big thing was that they were showing off the model for Star Wars land, which is now called Star Wars Galaxy's Edge, which is not as good as Star Wars land as far as the name is concerned.
So, yeah. So to back up a little bit, Star Wars is coming to Disneyland and Disney World.
There's going to be a huge like is it 14 acre part?
14 acres. 14 acres.
Cars land is 12 acres.
This is 14 acres.
So there's 14 acres of like a dedicated Star Wars land, which has like it's going to have restaurants like a cantina.
It's going to have two giant crazy cool rides like the like cutting edge technology.
Droids walking about the land.
Characters wandering around accosting you.
Yeah. There's going to be like flash mob things and like yeah.
Like it seems like it seems like fun and then it also seems like man, if there's constant street performers like hassling you, you're like, OK, guys, can you sign up for an option in which you just do the ride like a regular person?
You don't have to.
I think spoken to.
No, there is not.
I'll stay out of it.
Well, they're in Florida. There's going to be the announced there's going to be a hotel in Florida, a Star Wars themed hotel, and there are no windows in it. It's all just like fake space.
So like when you look out your window, it just looks like it's space.
It looks it feels like you're like living in space for a couple days.
And like I think you have to it's like going to be expensive as shit.
And you're going to have to like take part in a whole thing where like you get a knock at the door like 8 a.m.
And he's like, come quick, pedo on.
We have to. And you're like, oh, my God, like you have to like.
Yeah, it's like these college no more times a thousand.
So also for families and humidity.
Yeah, it does. It seems fun.
And also like maybe like once you're there, you're like, oh, this is a big pain in the ass.
Like some college student knocking at your door at 8 a.m.
Being like, hey, we must go quickly. Boba Fett is on our trail.
And you're like, OK, hold on, man.
My wife hasn't even taken a shower yet.
OK, but another 45 minutes.
We will need our sustenance.
Keep in mind, there is an excellent, affordable buffet bar at the.
Yeah, yeah. But we brought those little cereal things, man.
We're just going to eat the cereal. Yeah, no, no, no.
Without seven choices of juice, you will not be able to withstand the IG eighty eight.
We'll be waiting for you by the steam trays of pancakes.
You know, I don't even like Star Wars land that much.
It's just not a busy season right now.
And there was deals for this hotel.
You guys paid for this, though.
You really should be playing along. Yeah, I don't know.
I just thought this would be like how that boardwalk hotel looks like an old timey boardwalk.
I just thought this would have like Han Solo boardwalk.
What is a boardwalk? What's a boardwalk?
These words do not exist in our world.
And then the college students just like, come on, fucking do just play along.
I'm getting eight dollars an hour to do this. I'm being secret shopped.
I have a body cam on me. If I don't do the skit, I get fired. Please.
If you like haunted houses, really intense haunted houses where they put a bag over your head and make you crawl around on the floor,
but always wish there could be a squid man knocking at your hotel room door.
This Star Wars hotel is for you.
I will say all the stuff we were talking about, I feel like is too much.
And then you said a squid man at the door. And I'm kind of sold on that.
If they do get it, if an alien is the one, if an Admiral Akbar brought you your room service, I do like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That is cool. Because there's a problem with your Visa card.
Do you have another one we can use for incidentals?
That's pretty good Akbar. Oh, thanks.
Would you like a USA Today?
It is an archive of Earth news from 2017, which is not this time. But if you're curious.
And it's a future news because you know the crawl. You've seen the crawl of the movies. It's the future.
There's a picture in the Star Wars land they had in the display of like a street vendor selling meat.
And it's an alien. And he looks a little similar to Unkar Plutt, the famous Force Awakens character, the portion quarter portions guy.
And he looks very similar. And I was thinking because as a kid, I always want I almost like wanted Mickey to be working at Disneyland.
I wanted all the characters to be doing the jobs like and this was I was like, wow, if this is this might be the first time when I will get a full character.
Selling me some meat, which is I think I was literally like, oh, that's great.
Like I would like to hand this, you know, again, poor college student in a full alien suit my card.
They swipe it and they hand me like, oh, this is meat from Alderaan.
And it's like, of course, you're like, well, what is it, though? I have like an allergy.
There's a hamburger like it's a normal beef. Yeah.
So I am excited about that part. It costs two hundred thirty nine Gleap Naps.
How much in Earth dollars is that we couldn't tell you?
We don't know. Get credit card statement later.
Fifty bucks. I'm interested in this because the food in the Star Wars movies always looks disgusting.
Yes. Like the food besides the blue milk, which I think we all want to drink that sweet, sweet blue milk.
Everything else is just like bowls of goo or bread that bubbles, bubbles up from nothing.
Well, they're doing. Yeah. I mean, they're doing the thing because in Avatar land, which opened in Florida a couple of months ago,
they're none of the food is called like a conventional like, you know, Earth food.
I mean, obviously it is all Earth food, but they're calling it other things or like a something pod or whatever.
So they're going to have to have the weird goop.
They have to make human normal food look like a bunch of goop or some of the thing that like Luke is eating on and Peru,
like whatever and Peru prepared will be eating.
So just put a bunch of eyeballs in it or just like some stray wookie fur on the rim of the plate.
I don't know that anyone ate wookie fur in the movies, but maybe. Yeah, maybe that's a delicacy.
Yeah, there's a bunch of weirdo creatures. One of them might like hair.
Hair might be the top delicacy. Sure. He's one of these dude ad guys.
I don't know Star Wars. I should stay out of all.
I'll skip the Star Wars land episode when it eventually occurred.
You may not know it, but in 2019, you'll be living it.
I guess I'll have to learn. I'll have no choice.
As far as the D23, though, they have there was a whole section like devoted to pirates.
And like I was very excited because two years ago at the convention, they had a big Imagineering Pavilion and it showed like it was just like the actual animatronics.
So you would see like stuff from Peter Pan. You would see stuff from Haunted Mansion.
And it was like the real stuff. And then this one, I was like, oh, pirates.
And I knew there was going to be like some movie stuff, which I was less enthused about.
It's like, look at Barbosa's coat from the first film.
I was like, yeah, yeah, OK, which I actually also snuck into this because I didn't want to wait in line.
Wow. Congrats. I actually stuck into a few things.
That's a behavior. Jack Sparrow would have been exactly.
Yeah, I felt like I would have made Will Turner proud.
Right. Oh, everyone's favorite character worldwide sensation, Will Turner.
But they did have some. So there was not enough, you know, rides.
There were some animatronics. They had the dog with a key in his mouth.
They had like one of the pirate robots with a frosty ale in his hand.
Most of it was like, here's the here's the sword that Jack Sparrow used to like whatever the day.
I guess Davy Jones like plunge through Davy Jones or whatever.
But they but I will say the cool thing was they had this is this is so funny.
This is the thing that I like the most. They had memos like from Imagineers to each other.
Like, here's what we want to do. And then there was an outline of the ride of the original Pirates of the Caribbean.
And it's like it looked whether it was real or not, it looked old.
So I was like, wow. And like you're imagining some short sleeve dress shirted old men like holding these pieces of paper and like passing it along and going, all right.
And then there's a scene where the dog's got a key in his mouth.
And like so I was very I have many pictures we can post that on all the social media.
I saw pictures of I don't know if it was that but something down there of like old documents.
And it said OK Walt on them like Walt had written in pencil OK and signed his name.
Yes. And they kept these like perfectly preserved him approving the right approving like yes.
Scene outlines or that sort of thing. Wow.
So if you were there with a child who was excited to see Barbosa's coat, you would have been like shut up.
Keep moving. We got memos to see. Yes.
I was very much excited more about the memos than any of the pirates movies, which I like some of the pirates movies.
But like you're not you're not a D23 for the movies.
You're there for the for the 50th anniversary of that ride, which is this year.
Right. Which you could you could go on the ride several feet away or you could read memos about the making of the ride.
But I've been on the ride so many times now I need to read.
You've been on the ride now. Experience the memos.
You need to know how long all the electrical cords that they bought for it were.
Look at some drawings. Remember that pirate that's right handed in the ride in the drawing.
That pirate is left handed. There is a cool there's a cool piece of art at the end of it.
There was an idea that as you were leaving the ride, you would look through a little peephole and there would be pirates behind it.
And the pirates would all look and see you because they were like plotting.
But that would never obviously came to fruition. But like they have art of like some some like abandoned things that they were going to do, which is really cool.
So, you know, you know, D23 was cool.
And then there's also a lot of like are there a lot of aftermarket like secondary markets that there's people selling like Disney paraphernalia.
Right. Like, oh, yes, like this was the sign in the park or this was a thing.
And I I've been at like smaller Disney fan conventions and there's there's some of that stuff.
But it's very interesting to think about, like, how did you get this?
Because there are some authorized auction houses that like sell pieces of like Disneyland, Disney World attractions.
And then there's also other people who are like, yeah, this is this is from the fucking park.
And it's clearly just like an eBay guy. Yeah.
And it's just like a trash can they bought from somewhere else.
Yeah. Yeah. It's really hard to verify that some of these things were like the real this is the real Tiki sign from nineteen seventy five.
It was the period where the Tiki sign didn't have the the font quite as big as it does now.
And it's like it's like got a picture, but you're not quite sure.
I mean, a lot of most of the places just have like old merch. Yeah.
You know, they had like a if you're a Captain EO fan, Fuzzball, the flying character, they had a Fuzzball gasp there.
Yeah. Scott is a big Fuzzball fan. Oh, boy.
And they had like an old the real it was it was not the real Fuzzball, but it was it was a piece of merch from who knows?
Twenty five years ago. Although did they bring them when they brought the ride back?
Maybe they had a new Fuzzball made. I think they had a they had a lot of made.
I don't think they had a new bag. So like you'll get stuff like that.
And then like it's interesting to see some of the old merchandise because they certainly did not have the likenesses of the characters down yet.
So it's like a Donald Duck hat. But Donald looked like he was in a fire or something like his beak just as very I mean, it's also, you know, sixty years old.
But it's just like he's he's Donald Duck, but he's like Nightmare Donald Duck.
And you were wearing on your hat before there were branding standards.
Damn. Yeah. Yeah. Hey, well, speaking of artifacts from the past.
Oh, what a very good. Yeah. What a transition. Oh, I thought so.
Oh, there's one guy who would always make sure to verify what he found because he broke into a temple and found it himself.
What am I talking about? You ask. Well, I could tell you or I could let a special guest tell the tale.
I'm here in front of one of the great archaeological discoveries of our time.
The mysterious Temple of the Forbidden Eye. Hello, Michael Eisner, head of the Walt Disney Company.
An unprecedented move. The Walt Disney Imagineers have brought piece by piece this incredible treasure to America.
You can now tour the Temple of the Forbidden Eye at Disneyland and Anaheim, California.
First of all, you choose to explore the temple. Be aware that some say evil and treacherous curse hangs over this ancient buildings.
Enter at your own risk. And I'm out of here. He does not react to the snake. That was the reaction to that was it.
It is an upsetting looking snake. That is that's the it is very upsetting.
Yes. And that's like an Academy Award level performance on the spectrum of Michael Eisner performances.
I'm making the presumption that anyone listens to who's listening to this knows about all these very stiff Michael Eisner intros to various specials, which are my favorite things ever.
Michael, he really thought he was the heir to Walt Disney. Michael Eisner, when he was the head of the company.
He's like, I'm going to I'm going to be in the TV, too. I'm going to be introducing stuff like what you still didn't know.
Mike, he didn't quite have the folksiness as old as Walt did.
I have to admit, I do not I do not really watch the program Bojack Horseman, of which he is a producer, but he doesn't introduce every episode of Bojack Horseman.
I wish he sounded like Michael Eisner when you play again.
So I was like, when you played that clip for the first time, I thought it was Trump for a second.
Really? Hello. Hello there. There's a rasp that I always thought was similar.
I see. This is the second episode now we've played an old man phoning in an introduction to an attraction.
You know, I don't know if it is a classic, if there isn't a very stiff, sleepy intro to it.
If you don't have like a real big money, if the ride is not being introduced to you, buy a billionaire.
Buy a billionaire. Is it worth my money? A sleepy billionaire. Forced to do this.
I was meetings all day surrounding this intro.
Hey, Indiana Jones and the Temple of the Forbidden Eye.
That's what we're talking about. Or the Indiana Jones Adventure.
It has something else in common with the last one we talked about, the ET Adventure.
Actually, a couple of things. It is a Steven Spielberg property made into a ride that is called an adventure,
in which, at least at one point, AT&T handed you little cards that did something for you in the line.
Do you remember that about this attraction?
I had not been on it. I was in it, excuse me, I didn't go on until my late 20s.
But I know of the, you're talking about the decoder cards.
This is something people might not know actually about the ride,
but the hieroglyphics that you see throughout it are a language that they sorted out.
They call them mauraglyphics because you were in the Temple of the God Mara.
So there is a language that makes sense. And it actually just looks like English if you squint.
It's like pretty English-esque. It's not some super-Klingon-y tough-to-decode thing.
But they'd hand you these little cards so that as you went along, you could decode the language as you went.
And none of it was profane or Disney, imagine you're trying to sneak something dirty in.
Because this ride has one of the longest lines ever. Maybe the longest? I should have looked that up.
It is half a mile long.
The line is?
The line is half a mile long. And it is very interesting, but the show building is so big
and so far back from where you enter, they had to build this giant long queue. And it is cool.
Because the space was occupied by the Jungle Cruise, so they had to figure out a way to weave you in this area
between the Jungle Cruise and Pirates of the Caribbean. That's kind of where you're going.
They built this show building on top of a portion of the old Eeyore parking lot.
And there is a little hidden Eeyore somewhere in this ancient temple that you can find.
I've always heard that. I've never seen it.
I know where it is because a guy showed it to me one night.
Which now that I said that, it sounds like he dropped his pants for me one night.
Want to see my donkey?
It was very late. It was close to park closing. We were waiting to go on the ride.
And some college student, fresh out of college student, he goes, hey, you want to see something cool?
And we said, of course, yes. And he took his flashlight and right before, it's the part where they're showing the old news reel
and the line, the queue. He's showing his flashlight to the very back of the thing and you can see it right back there.
But it's very hard to see because it's very dark in that room.
Yeah. The rare hidden Eeyore. There's a lot of hidden Mickey's. It's the only hidden Eeyore.
Well, what do we know about this ride? Are we describing the ride to people?
Scott, I wanted to ask you because you grew up in Southern California.
Did you ride this ride soon after it opened?
Because I know when it first opened, it was like three or four hour waits for this ride.
People loved it right out of the gate.
Yes. Yeah. And that entire temple was full. Now they kind of like hold people and you do most of the line outside
and then they send you into the long. You kind of walk straight through all the temple.
But it was like all the way out, I think when it opened, maybe all the way to Main Street
and then you would wind through Adventureland and Frontierland.
And it was like a three to four hour.
So you remember waiting that long?
Yeah, I did. Yeah. And there's no fast pass back then. I had to just do it.
I remember and my wife also grew up around here and she because that line was so crazy, she hated the ride initially.
It would have had to have been so incredible to make up for a four hour wait.
It ended up letting her down. But if you don't do a four hour wait, it's obviously one of the greats.
The first time I rode it would have been like 2006 when I was out here for college.
I didn't wait that I probably waited only like an hour, but I waited most of it in that that outside portion.
That's kind of a jungle. And in the middle of summer, that is kind of miserable.
Like you're very close to everyone. It is it is not.
There's a little bit of theming, but like nowhere near as much as when you get inside.
And it's just kind of rough. Let heat.
It is. Yeah, it can get really bad as far as heat. Let's let's back up and go to the story of the ride and then walk through it.
Because so so I learned a few things, honestly, I've been on it a ton of times, but I didn't notice a few things.
So so the story is that we're going into the Temple of the Forbidden Eye and we're supposed to be in India.
Although Michael Eisner in that video says that likely they constructed the temple in Disneyland.
Yeah, I just a little confusing that premise until that video that the Imagineers took it apart piece by piece and brought it here.
And I guess the did they pick up the curse along the way or did the curse just get retained from India to that making of TV special does not make a lot of sense.
OK, it's sort of narratively a lot of. Yeah, it's kind of all over the map.
So I think that might not be canon. I think the Michael Eisner.
So I think we just are in every Michael Eisner.
If if if Winnie the Pooh or Robin Hood meets Michael Eisner before the movie, that's part of the movie.
Michael Eisner exists in every single cinematic universe.
He is a character in the Disney. They could probably still use him.
That like like Disney still owns the character Michael Eisner.
Michael Eisner does not own Michael Eisner. Right.
The character Michael Eisner is still IP. The Disney Disney's ruthless.
Don't sign a contract with them.
So so the ride is where that's the Temple of the Forbidden Eye.
And Indiana Jones has found like parts of a map and he's located this this temple.
And the ride, the story goes that Sala, which is Jonathan Rice Davies, India's run out of money for his expedition.
And Sala, I did not know this until I started looking at Sala has been conducting tours of the temple to make money.
So to keep funding Indies research.
The reason that any tourist is allowed in there is because we're paying to keep Indies adventure going on.
And also maybe they'll find him. Like that's why I learned that about this, too.
The back door involves all of the main characters of Indiana Jones that are like in the movies a little or mentioned because like Abner Ravenwood is involved.
Marcus Brody is also Marcus Brody per the Wikipedia entry.
Marcus Brody has asked Sala to continue conducting the tours in the hope that they may locate Dr.
Jones and keep funding. Right.
So I think in the narrative of the ride, there was a time when Indy was just going through the temple and everything was fine and he was running tours safely.
And then something happened.
And for whatever reason now, Sala wants a bunch of tourists to take one of these ride vehicles, go into the temple and see if they can find Dr.
Jones, who's been lost for a week.
We're supposed to find Indiana Jones.
Yes, that's what we're trying to do.
So which they don't they could convey that by telling us.
Right, because we've all been out in a million times and we did not know that.
If we don't know this fact, then how could anyone?
So that's the story of the ride.
And what was Indiana Jones, was he after something in the temple or he just found the temple and liked it, wanted to hang out in it?
He's looking for what is it called?
The Jewel of Power.
Yeah, there you go.
Quote, Abner Ravenwood believed to be within an immense cavern beyond the Gapes of Doom.
Who's Abner Ravenwood?
Ravenwood was Indiana Jones's often mentioned but never seen mentor.
And he is the father of Marion, the character played by Karen Allen.
That's why they know each other through the dad.
So he hooks up with the daughter of his mentor, which is real fucked up.
Everyone's dream.
Let's be honest.
It's really messed up.
He shouldn't have done that.
It was the guy dead, though.
The guy was dead.
It was fine.
Well, they talked about putting him.
He was going to show up in the movies at some point and then it never happened.
I think he's long dead by Crystal Skull.
Well, sure.
And Marcus Brody is also long dead by Crystal Skull because he has that, Indy has that picture of him that he picks up and looks at at one point.
Or is that Sean Connery?
He looks up longingly at Sean Connery.
He looks at Sean Connery.
Maybe that's what I'm thinking of.
As we all should each morning to get some mojo for the day.
There's a statue in Crystal Skull, I think, of Brody in the middle.
This is the second Steven Spielberg movie with a character named Brody in it.
I'm just realizing.
Yeah, Brody from Jaws.
And then of course Brody in Mallrats.
In Mallrats.
Hey, all right.
Where's that ride?
Snoochy Boochies.
Smithland or View-Isc Universe.
View-Isc Uland.
A movie that ends at Universal Studios Florida.
Mallrats ends with Jason Lee's character getting married on the ride.
Right?
Although I think it's filmed in Hollywood.
Right.
They say it's in Florida.
Yeah.
Oh, View-Isc Universe.
That's maybe that's an episode.
You get to part of it's like the heavens open.
You get to go in the church where you get to obviously eat at movies.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
You get absolved of your sins.
That's what I'm trying to say.
So you get to like visit the convenience store and absolved of your sins by that smiling Jesus guy.
Let's make sure to mark this down.
Two episodes in we've gotten into a discussion about the View-Isc Universe.
So I feel like that's inevitable on any new podcast.
Tally number one.
Probably 20 or 30 times eventually.
Yeah.
We'll keep building that View-Isc Universe, the place, which of course is in Jersey.
Oh, man.
Oh, it's got a Jersey represent.
Hell, yeah.
Keep it at Gnome land.
Yeah.
So there is so as far as Indiana Jones ride, it is like an extensive back story with a lot of like a lot more moving parts than I even thought at the time because it was just I thought it was just like, oh, you're some tourists going through and oh, yeah, watch out for Indiana Jones.
There he is.
And then but no, no, there's like a whole thing.
So don't if you're listening to this, don't ever go on this ride again, just not knowing the full story.
You won't enjoy it.
You won't ever be able to just purely if you don't know about Brody's involvement.
Sure.
And despite despite all of that back story, there is one glaring omission from this ride.
Harrison Ford.
Ah, good point.
Yes, that is true.
Do we know why do we know why no Harrison?
I am not sure.
He was also not present for the grand opening.
Hmm.
Well, he was having a dispute with Disney.
Right.
Wasn't it over?
There was some sort of an advertising thing.
It was I feel like it's a similar situation where Robin Williams was like, I don't want using my voice to advertise.
And then something happened.
It makes sense that we get from poking around because this is if we ever meet a famous person or somebody who's been in a Disney ride, a question is like, hey, what's up with that?
They like treat you well.
Is it a good situation?
I'm not sure it is.
I don't know that you're like paid a fortune to do a voice or act in something that people that millions of people see every day.
Yeah.
I think Disney has a feeling of like you should be so lucky to be here.
And then it's also like the no guild covers theme park performances.
Sort of its own specific area.
Allow me to say that if I ever got to participate in a ride or do a voice or something in anything, I would pay them upwards of 10 grand for this.
Negative dollars is fine.
A lot of them.
We would all pay, I think, to just have like a speaking role in one of those pre-ride videos.
Oh, sure.
Look out.
I'm not behind you.
Anything.
Just one word.
So that I could bring uninterested relatives constantly and pointed out to them and have them say it's not you.
This hasn't worked great before, folks, but I'm sure it's going to go fine this time.
Yeah, that would be great.
You just casted yourself way up.
That's a very meaty role.
Yeah, that would be a starring role.
The most crucial piece of information in any ride.
No Indiana Jones, though you do get John Rhys Davies in the he does play Sala, although sometimes it's not his voice, but he does appear in it physically.
So you do have a representative from the movie.
He's the only one, right?
There's no.
Yeah.
There's a voiceover in that.
This is a side note.
There's a voiceover in that newsreel by a woman named Tress McNeil.
Oh, yeah.
Who is a very famous voiceover actor.
Voice of Babs Bunny and.
Docs from Animaniacs.
Lindsay Nagel on The Simpsons.
Yeah.
All like business ladies on The Simpsons.
She does a lot.
She's great.
A regular Simpsons reference too.
And she does a voice on this.
Right.
A lot of Tress McNeil references in a few seasons of The Simpsons.
And she does a voice on the ride.
Yeah.
So, yeah, we only see one character as far as in those early videos on the queue.
Maybe, you know, since I bring up John Rhys-Davies, it might be a good time to play a little pod
exclusive that I made.
We were referencing a special that was made promoting the opening of the ride.
I think it was just called The Making of Indiana Jones Ride.
As Jason was saying, it has a very confusing story and timeline where the temple is real
and John and Karen are trying to find Indy.
So, Indy is real, but it's Karen Allen, the actress, looking for him.
Playing Karen Allen.
Like, John Rhys-Davies shows up in the special as himself, but they also play the old timey
newsreel clip where he is Sala.
But Karen Allen is only ever Karen Allen.
That said, she, like her character Marion, is very thirsty for treasure.
Like, she keeps trying to leave and John Rhys-Davies.
Like, at one point he says, like, did I tell you about the treasure?
And she turns around and goes, like, treasure?
And at another point she's like, I've had enough.
I'm going to go.
And he goes, like, but what about the gifts?
And she goes, gifts?
Like, and that's extremely my shit because I love treats.
Like, I love presents.
I love treats.
Treasure.
And Karen Allen, a beautiful woman.
That's your dream girl.
Yeah.
Marion was a favorite character.
A pretty greedy lady.
That's very odd.
But yeah, they go on the ride and like there's a part where they're about to get on and then a ride vehicle returns and it's just full of skeletons.
Yeah.
And Karen asks John, are you like, is this supposed to happen?
Like, does anybody ever come out of this thing alive?
And he says, yes, one time.
I think last Thursday somebody came out alive.
There's a lot of crazy implications of danger in these theme park specials.
Yeah, that is crazy because like all the there a lot of these things it's like, well, you may not survive.
And it's like, there have been a couple incidents in parks where somebody hasn't survived.
Maybe we should joke about that.
Although usually on extremely innocuous things.
Yes, it's usually like a weird mundane.
The less dangerous the ride, the more likely you'll die on it.
But it's like a fun thing now.
It's like a fun secret.
Anyway, they go on the they go on the ride and the danger is real apparently.
And I just I found the way that John Rhys Davies screams to be really infectious.
So I made a pod exclusive super cut of John Rhys Davies.
Excellent screaming.
Oh, wow.
Enjoy.
Get this fuck out of here.
That at the end is not a scream.
It's him say what sounded to me.
I know it's not this, but it's it almost sounds like he's saying, oh, let's get the fuck out of here.
It does sound like that.
Yeah, it does.
It's kind of fading away.
So it's ambiguous.
I thought he said, ah, you get that's how you start the cars.
I really liked those screams.
I just like they're so like warbly and admittedly the screams of a larger gentleman.
And it really reminded me of the Orson Welles outtakes like, wow, the French.
Yeah.
Like like a cool fat guy. Excellent. Excellent screaming, John.
You've set a precedent now.
I think we have to have like a screaming super cut for a lot of different rides for people for reactions for pre shows and yeah.
Which you pro. All right.
So now we got to do that every time.
Now we got a segment caked in.
I did it to myself.
Are they actually on the ride at that point?
Like in that special, I because I watched it last night and it looks like they might be in a different vehicle.
Like it looks to me or it just might be in the station and it's rocking.
I think some of it is I think you're right.
They filmed it in a studio and they're just shaking a car around flashing lights on it.
Some of it I think is on the real thing, but maybe with stunt doubles with the indemnity doubles.
Also a lot more sparks like there's a lot more spark.
Yeah, they should shoot some serious pyro on the gang and make it look a lot scarier than it is in real life.
Let me say this, though.
This was a this ride did terrify me as a kid and the idea of it.
I remember in probably if that line was three hours long, first time I went on it, I think an hour of it.
I screamed.
I was like such a baby to where my dad was like, Jesus, like cool it, which I confirm my wife did, too.
I'm not the only one, but she was a young girl and I was a young boy.
So speaking of fear on this ride and Mike, you were also there for this.
Mike and I were on this ride when it broke down once.
Yes.
And the dream of any theme park goer to have be on a ride that breaks down.
That's yes.
And here is my recollection of it.
We broke down, the ride vehicle came to a stop directly next to the giant snake animatronic.
And the snake kept moving.
The snake kept opening its mouth.
The movement of the snake is that it kind of rears back a little bit and then goes like rears.
It goes towards you, towards the car.
I don't remember you being that scared.
Were you secretly scared while we were sitting there?
Well, I'm not super fond of snakes.
So I was just kind of a little like.
So you were having a panic attack and I didn't even realize it.
That was a little scary, but what really scared me was I was like, oh, we're going to get walked off this.
And then a cast member walked up to the car, right?
We were hoping because, yeah, as Scott was saying, a dream of a Disney fan is for a car to break down
and then you get to walk through the attraction because then you get to see like details that you would never see
because the lights come on and it's pretty incredible.
Or maybe get taken through some secret backstage park nobody else would get to see.
Which happened to me on Big Thunder Mountain Railroad once and was very neat.
This time what scared me is when the cast member walked up, I went, oh, she's a lot farther down than I thought I was.
Like, I never realized how far up you are on that ride.
All right. Well, that's a good point because the ride vehicle.
This was a big thing at the time that the Jeep itself is elevated up and you're kind of on a Star Wars type simulator ride
with a lot of hydraulic arms.
So it's it is a car that's moving around, but it's a hydraulic or it is a simulator on top of the.
So do you remember what happened, like how we got off it?
Yeah, well, they ran us just they with the lights on and the whole place lights on.
We just kind of slowly drove to the end of the thing with the work lights on and the ride still kind of like half jerking.
And some of the sound effects playing. Right. It was weird.
It was unnerving. And then we got to the thing and they're like, all right, we got to figure it out.
Do you guys want to go through again? And we're like, well, yeah, sure.
And that time it went fine. But like it was a very weird experience.
You got to see the lazy version of the Jones ride.
I am. I will say this. I I have no recollection of you having like a terror attack.
I don't think I don't think it was that bad. I was just more like, oh, God, I didn't realize we were this high up
because like I was like, oh, it's a car. You were just playing it, playing it cool.
You were playing it cool. You brush it off. You're a real hero.
You didn't want to freak out the kids on the car. No. Even though you yourself were dying inside.
Yeah, it was a car full of adults. Yeah.
No children. There are rarely any children on the rides when I go to Disney.
Yeah. Can we not be with him, please? That alone man.
What else about this ride? Going a lot, I guess.
Yeah. Well, going back to the queue, the queue is awesome.
Like there's some there's like a rock area and then there's a part where
which I don't think there's a lot. Well, there's a couple of maybe other queues like this.
But there are things that say do not touch in the queue, but they mean touch.
Like there's a room where there's a bamboo like pole keeping up the ceiling
and there are spikes coming through the ceiling. And the idea is that if you touch this,
all of a sudden the spike ceiling is going to come and murder everyone in the room.
Obviously, it doesn't it hasn't enough the capability to murder.
But if you touch that bamboo thing, you'll hear like rumbling and then you'll see that the spikes
will come down a little bit. Like these are like a bunch of cool interactive things
going on there. Do they all still work? I feel like they worked.
They worked Friday. I was on it Friday. Yeah. And the guy
touched it and we hadn't seen it work in a while because some of these effects go in and out of working
because there's so many of them. But it did work and I was like, oh, yeah, we haven't seen that in a while.
So, you know, periodically these things work. There's also the well. Yes. Like, yeah,
there's a guy. There's like a well with a bunch of ropes on it.
And if you like grab the rope or something, you will hear a voice
going like, hey, I'm down here. You also hear him fall.
Oh, OK. The idea is that you've, I guess, killed or really heard a guy
who is hanging onto a rope dropping into a well. So, you know,
that's another thing where it says do not touch. But then you quickly learn like you just grab the rope
and shake it. And then, yeah, you hear like, hey, what are you doing? Or you hear like, ah!
And then you get to cause a Chilean mine disaster
type of event. You get to really play God in that
scenario. I think probably narratively they have to be like, well, you know, he
wasn't that far from the ground or the water. But it just startled him.
That's why he screamed. He didn't break both arms
and his spine. But, yeah, let's be honest. You killed that guy.
Yep. Kids kill that guy hundreds of times a day. That man
dies hundreds of times a day at the hands of tourists. Maybe it's given a
real child practice in murder, in which they're able to
actually inflict later in their lives. Yeah, that sensitizes us.
It's dark. It's a dark riot, folks. Yeah, incredible line.
Probably one of the first rides where the line was really amazing
and engrossing before you even got there. The riot itself.
You know, I just wanted to point out, I don't have
any particular deep observation about this, but just when
you get on the right... Well, first of all, maybe a lot of people don't know that you are
given the choice of these three tunnels. Which one is riches, one's eternal
youth, and one's... See the future. See the future, yeah.
But that is in effect and it's always the same door and it's an illusion
that swings all of those doors around. So that's
cool. But I just like... In thinking about this ride, I was just
recalling how that moment where you're not supposed to look into
the eye of the god Mara, when you do, Mara gets angry,
which they just enhanced with these really cool projection effects in the last few years.
And then when you whip around the corner into that room that reveals
Indiana Jones at the door, like fending off all these evil spirits,
that whip around the corner, I would argue, is one of the most exciting
moments in any ride. And I think... I like it
because it shows that the car has personality. That was the thing
they pushed in a lot of the specials and everything around the time the ride came out.
The car will struggle and the car will recoil
as if you were scared of the snakes.
As opposed to Pirates of the Caribbean or Haunted Mansion or something where it's just an evenly moving
vehicle that isn't really doing anything or reacting. Like the fact
that the car has trouble with stuff and struggles, I think, is a really
neat innovation. And that's followed by, once you go
past Indy trying to keep the doors closed, you go
into a room with a giant
temple rockwork skull that's shooting
lasers at you. It is so exciting. And a fireball.
It's great. And the music cue is great. Yeah, that big
chorus hit that happens that reveals that.
You never get tired of it. It's cool every single time.
My girlfriend and I went on it Friday night and with this podcast, I always
would like to look for things that maybe we can make some fun of or light of.
And every time I go on the ride, I'm like, this is the fucking greatest ride. This is
so goddamn cool. Yeah, this one doesn't have the hokey-ness that you
can poke fun at so much. It is such a legitimate
incredible technical feat and probably the best thing Disney landed
done up until that point. There is a funny story because there was two years ago I went
to this event at Disney, which was the 20th anniversary of the ride, and Tony
Baxter, who is the lead Imagineer on this ride, who we'll probably talk about a lot,
was saying that for legal reasons,
Mara, because we were talking about the Mara, which is a big head statue or whatever
you would call it, and there's three different things they can promise you like
eternal life, earthly riches, or seeing the future. And legally, Disney,
you cannot promise people something on the ride, so they had to
put in the thing. Because what happens is they say, do not look into the eyes of the idol. And Mara
is huge, so it's almost impossible not to look at the eyes of this person. So legally,
they had to do that so it would
rescind the offer of earthly riches or eternal life or whatever
they were promising because one person, at least in the car, would look into Mara's eyes
and then legally, the offer would be off the table. Because Disney Legal would
be concerned that somebody would come back and be like, well, I went on the ride, and
I was offered a lot of money, which of course is dumb as shit, who would
do that. But that's a true thing that Disney Legal was like, well,
this is going to be a problem. So they had to add in the thing of don't look into Mara's eyes,
and then everything goes to shit. That's why that construct exists. That's pretty crazy.
Wow. So if you were on the eternal life
track and everyone agreed to not look,
then what? That's a good point. I mean, maybe there's a case
we could build here if we can get, what is it, there's 16,
how many people on the ride? 12 people on the ride? 12 people, yeah. 12 people can be on the ride. If we get 12 of us
together, we close our eyes, never look into Mara's eyes, and maybe document
it, maybe we have a case for a shitload of money
from Disney. Okay, so the three of us, and then
the first nine fans of this podcast, because, as
with most things, our significant others will not agree to participate in this.
So the first nine people to respond, let's all
get in the car, we'll get up to the front, 12 please, we'll all
look around like I'll sly because we know the plan. We're going to
bilk Disney out of eternal life. A class action lawsuit for eternal life.
And probably the result of that is like, one
front of the line pass. But even that's worth it, I think.
We gotta try to bilk them for something. We would like a lot of money, they'd be like, well we can have one front of the line pass, and we go, done.
Done! The end of the negotiations.
It was a pleasure facing off against you, Disney attorney.
They wouldn't even give us that.
So, well, okay, you said that there is not a lot that is hokey
about the ride, and easy to poke fun about the ride.
What are two? Well, let's hear what you're thinking.
Okay, so, the effects and stuff, by and large,
get bigger and bigger, crazier and crazier as this ride goes on.
But there are a couple spots where the vehicle needs
to turn around. And so the first one is a
dark room where the headlights are flickering, and you realize it's filled with
bugs on the walls. And that's pretty good. And then you go over the bridge, and that's
really cool. And they're shooting lasers at you. And then you go by the snakes,
and that's really cool. And then you go through a giant room of skulls, that's really cool.
And then you go to a black room, like a pitch black room,
that just has the projection of a branch with some rats running
across it. And that's where it loses steam for a beat there.
And I'm pretty sure it's just a spot where it's like, well the vehicle needs to turn and also
go downhill a little. So it can't just be a pure dark room. We gotta
do something in there. I agree that effects, thinly
projected rats dropping is a little... I didn't even know that's what it was until
like two years ago. I was just like, oh it's a spooky fog area.
It's ghost rats. And some people are very scared of rats
and mice and stuff. So maybe, I guess, kind of. I would not like
rats and mice. But there's not, this is a question I have,
is there an effect like in like Honey I Shrunk the Audience on the
ride where it's supposed to like brush your legs? Yes. There is. In Honey I Shrunk the
Audience, yeah. But not that, but I'm talking in the Indiana Jones card. Oh in this, no not in Indiana Jones.
Because that would make sense then if it was like you felt a brush against your leg on the ride.
I had wondered if they had had that effect at one point and then dropped it, but I don't believe it.
I hated that effect as a kid. I always hated that. Because there's rats. I scared the shit out of me.
And then it was a snake. Then it was a giant snake. I hated it. I remember like putting my legs up
for the only I shrunk the audience. I always do. Even if you know that
it's not real insects or rats, it's still just unpleasant to get like
wildly tased in the butt by a little buzzer in your
seat. It's horrible. I think they do that at Shrek. There's like stuff like, there's a, like it pokes you in the back
or something. I can see it legitimately like
damaging a nerve. I can't believe it hasn't happened. And Bugs Life. The Bugs Life movie.
Oh yeah, you get poked in the back too. You get poked by like stingers in the front of the chair.
Yeah, that's weird. These are not my favorite things at any of the parks.
Nor do I like that rats dropping. Say there aren't
rat droppings in it. But there are fake rats dropping on you. They should do a whole thing where
well maybe this is, we'll save that for later. What were you going to say, Scott? What were you going to say that?
Oh, in terms of hokeyness, this is off of the ride. But it's
about the promotion of the ride.
Do you guys recall or did you remember in your research
that to promote this ride, Disney staged an Indiana Jones Super Bowl
halftime show? I believe we have watched it.
I believe we have watched it. Have the three of us watched it together? Maybe.
Maybe. Maybe. Maybe. Several times. We might be repeating
life material here. That's fine. But I'd sort of forgotten about that until the other
night. I mean they threw so much at the wall promoting this thing. There were so many odd
specials and giant promotional budget. But that they did the Super Bowl
halftime show is, that's something for a theme park attraction.
And it's rough. It's not just rough. It's rough for
dinner theater. And this is the Super Bowl halftime show. This is before
the giant spectacle Super Bowl halftime show. This would have been like
1994 or so? Yeah. Or 95 potentially.
And it was post the Michael Jackson halftime show
which kind of defined the modern halftime show. Where now it's just a, it's a really good concert
that you get in the middle. Yeah. This is not that. No, no, no. It is not.
The halftime show is all kind of used to be more of a mess. Where there's a
zillion ideas all fighting each other. And here's this weird dance
part and then a singer you recognize but just for three minutes and then it turns into something
else. Disney had done a previous halftime show that's, it's a small
world themed but then the new kids on the block are in it for a second. Which I
would think, just give it, they're popular at the time. Just give them the whole time.
But there was all this like up with people bullshit. The Super Bowl
halftime shows were awful. I mean they're bad now sometimes but
it's a lot cleaner than it used to be. I just remember that Simpsons joke
where it was like, there was like a spaceship landing
on the aliens. The aliens coming out and like that's my idea of what the
halftime show used to be. It was like some. They kind of were, oh there was another Simpsons joke where
some up with people kind of. Was it Hooray for Everything? Yeah.
That was a different episode? And they sing Walk on the Wild Side by Lou Reed
but they don't realize it's an ironic. They just sing it as a face value cheery song.
So halftime shows were really bad. Disney had done a lot of them.
They did one for the Indiana Jones ride. It's really insane.
Indiana Jones and Marion, a non-Karen Allen, Karen Allen
skydive into the stadium. Which is legitimately impressive because
they had to, like a skydive takes I don't know how long, I mean a number of minutes.
So they had to like time it out. Like when the quarter ended it was like go!
And then they jumped and they did land in the correct spot
which is pretty impressive. And then it switches out for the stunt performers.
They got stunt performers who were from the Indiana Jones
stunt show at Disney World in Florida which we haven't talked about
yet. But it was like, what I like about this is
that sometimes the Super Bowl halftime show is Michael Jackson
the most famous man in the world. And then in this case it's some guy.
It's a stunt man. And he is the lead of
the show. And the idol they're trying to get is the
football, right? It is the Lombardi Trophy. Oh it's the trophy.
And for some reason it's not a lightweight version.
They're throwing around a real Super Bowl trophy. Oh my god.
I don't know if there's only one in the world. I don't know if it's like the Stanley Cup. But it's definitely
a heavy Lombardi Trophy. There's a really great article about this on Bleacher
Report you can look up. Which I think has the headline worst halftime show ever
question mark. Although spoiler, they determined it is not. If you haven't watched the Black
Eyed Peas I would say it might be that one. Oh yeah that was pretty great.
But yeah they say that it is a real Lombardi Trophy. There were a lot of problems.
The stage was serrated and there were a lot of little holes in it.
And the holes were exactly the size of Patti LaBelle's
high heels. So they had to change the whole stage because
Patti LaBelle almost tripped and fell. Patti LaBelle is in it.
Tony Bennett is in it. It's a very odd line up for 1995.
What is Tony Bennett singing it? I don't know what his first song is but at the end they all
sing Can You Feel the Love Tonight from the Lion King.
Disney did another big mess of a halftime show a couple years later with Phil Collins
doing Tarzan songs and Gloria Estefan. This one features
Miami Sound Machine without Gloria Estefan.
It's just the strangest line up ever. There's a really insane part
where Marion takes a torch and lights a guy on fire.
And it's not like a fire effect goes off under the guy and then he's on fire.
Marion takes the torch, touches it to the guy's robe and he
lights on fire. Which when you're asking is this a bad halftime show
I don't know. A guy got lit on fire like live between the
halves of a Super Bowl. That's pretty cool. Like what happens in it is cool
but when you put it all together it's just a big weird mess.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. A lot of ideas that don't really mix and why Tony Bennett
and really hokey acting and they just couldn't help that a lot of punches
miss. There's like the Batman style just many feet away
from the punch connecting. But it's interesting to watch.
I recommend looking it up. But here's the weird dark thing is that
they did pull it off and everybody felt really good afterwards and like maybe
stunt shows are what a lot of the halftime shows will be. Two years later they did one for the Blues
Brothers and while rehearsing it a stunt person
died. So stunts were dead forever at the Super Bowl halftime
show or else you might still see them to this day. Wow.
But yeah, this opened up the path too. But they, you know, at least they could say
that it was in the surface of a Blues Brothers. They died
in service of a Jim Belushi concert. Why were the Blues Brothers in the
mid 90s? Blues Brothers 2000 were coming out. Well, but not even
years later. It was two years after the fact and this was a rare
Blues Brothers lineup where it's three of them. It's not the
kid or the other guy. It's Akroyd, Jim Belushi
and John Goodman. It's the rare trifecta of Blues Brothers.
James Brown is in it. ZZ Top. That one is a big mess.
That one I would say, oh and it opens with a promotion for the
then new Fox News channel, which makes it extra
horrific. So I would rank that one below the Super, the
Indiana Jones one, which is at least fun. You know, in the original Blues Brothers
there is a, it's not John Goodman, but there is a third Blues Brother in
the movie and you don't really see it. It's called Cocaine. Like
Cocaine is the third Blues Brother that is in every scene
and driving all the action of a very odd movie
to watch many years later. Like I didn't see that until I was
in my mid-20s. It's kind of aggressive. It's almost a little like snuffy. It's very strange.
Because all the accidents are like real and scary and it led to
later the Twilight Zone accident
of like striving for realism in the film
stunts. Because there's just real broken glass and violence in that thing.
We're going to have all these links in the metadata and on all the
social media. So if you want to watch all of these nightmare half-time
shows. If you want to buy the book about the Twilight Zone film disaster
the Amazon link will be provided.
Talking about like all the promotion, this ride was promoted
a lot because it was very expensive. And
it was also part of the 40th anniversary of Disneyland, which is a big deal.
And I grew up on the East Coast. I grew up outside of Philadelphia.
And Mike you grew up in the Midwest outside of Chicago.
And I remember seeing the promotions
for this ride a lot. Like they weren't promoting it of like come to Disneyland
and see this. But it was, I remember that making of, I remember it being in
the holiday parades, which were very big in my house. Like we would
plan Christmas morning. It was like we'll get up, we'll unwrap presents, we'll watch the Disney Christmas
parade. If we sleep in we have the VCR set to record
it in case we miss it. And I remember it being a big part of those.
And Mike and I have talked about this before. We
just like as kids were like, man that looks really cool. Shame I'll never see it.
I'll never complete this impossible task
of traveling to California. There was a book we had.
This really shows how we were raised and what our view of
like how many world travelers we would not become.
Is that like, we had like a, I think it was cause we had stock. We have Disney stock
at the family. And yeah so in like 1994 I'm looking through like the, what's coming up
to the resorts. And there was a picture on the drawbridge I think there was a picture of.
You're talking about in the annual report. I got the annual reports too.
We have a couple of them still. He's such fucking nerd. These were big family things
for a while. That people would buy single shares of Disney stock or people would buy the like
commemorative annual report. And it was like keep saints
that people would have. And there was no internet at the time so it was a way to like look at real nice
photos of rides. Exactly. It was Indiana Jones. There I justified it.
It was Indiana Jones in Toontown. And I used to
look at those pictures and think wow that's so cool. I'll never go
there. There's no way I'll ever cause we go to Florida.
That's where we go. We go on a family vacation every three years to Florida. I'll never
leave Illinois otherwise. I'll never see New York. I'll never go out of the country.
I was raised to be very frightened of the world in California.
To not dream big. Something that ironically every
Disney parade and show encourages you to do. Dream your dreams.
The message was lost on me. Leave that for the other kids.
Yeah. You've told me stories of like you were 18
and going to like Largo and seeing John Bryan. And like I was
17 and 18. We didn't know a successful person. We didn't
know a person that lived anywhere. I was just literally like I don't
know what. I guess some people go out to California but you have to be
pretty special to do that I guess. You'll never see a man play a
guitar. Right. I was like you gotta be a Hollywood millionaire
to make that happen. I'm just here in Schaumburg. Yeah. I was like wow
big city folk. They got a lot of good stuff going on. I guess you know
what. There's a Portillo's hot dog. I'm gonna go hey maybe I'll get a large
cake shake tonight. Maybe one day I'll be I'll work at
the Portillo's and I'll put me in a commercial and then I'll be a big star
right here where it counts in Schaumburg. I'll get a five percent discount
on Italian beef at all my favorite restaurants. Don't tell me I
don't got dreams. I got big dreams. Hot dog dreams. It's like verbatim
what I was like. When I first came to California
I it was my first time flying alone. I would have been like 20
and it was my first time flying alone. It's my first time being on a flight longer
than two hours. I had been on one flight. Really? And since
I like from age you know zero to twenty two
one flight. Wow. Did you drive to Florida? Yes. Oh fuck.
Three times. Oh no no. How far is that? How far are we talking?
Oh it's. I mean it would take a day two days. It would take two days.
It's not uncommon from the Midwest or the Northeast that people just drive down there.
I've questioned my parents. I'd be like how much more money was it?
Yeah. What were we. I know we were like middle class but my god
we couldn't pay the extra twenty five dollars a person and fly.
But I. We would have saved a day. I should also say like once I got out here
for this like school college program.
The first or second full day I was out here. I went to Disney. I was like
going to Disneyland. Like I could care less
about like seeing Los Angeles one of the greatest cities in the world.
I mean I went. I think the first day I was here I went and saw like
Hollywood Boulevard and Grailmans and I'm like oh this is upsetting. The other main
thing you need to see. Yeah. And so I knocked that out in two days and like
Disneyland blew me away too because. Well and in
Disney's California Adventure you can see all the best things Los Angeles and
California have to offer. All in just a couple acres.
Yeah you covered it. Big dreamers here on the show.
All right. Yeah. Let's get out of the sad sack with Jason and I. Get back on the ride.
Should we talk about the Japanese version
of this ride. Oh yes. The one in Tokyo Disney is a little different from the ride.
It is called the Indiana Jones Adventure Temple of the Crystal
Skull. Was made a few years before the
movie Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull. And has
some very strange little differences. For
one Sala is not in the ride. The ride spiel is
done. The ride doesn't take place in India. It takes place
in Mexico. And I believe you're looking for the fountain of youth.
And Sala does not do the spiel does not do the safety thing.
It is a new character who is simply named Paco. But it is
portrayed by a Japanese actor who is speaking in Japanese.
Sure. So he is some blend that is neither
here nor there. Yeah. Also there is no Mara. It is
literally a giant glowing crystal skull. And then
throughout the ride there's just little differences. When you go into the big room with
the giant skull and the bridge you go over there is like a little
tornado going. There's a little steam tornado. Oh yeah.
Kind of this like otherworldly glow sort of thing. Yeah. Looks cool. Yeah. And then
after you they also have the dark room with the projection of
rats on a branch. But then they have a giant skull who blows
fire at you. Yeah. And their room where they shoot darts at you
is much cooler. Yes. Like a lot
less black paint and a lot more practical like effects. We should also
say that we have not been on this ride. We've just watched YouTube. We have
also never been on a flight outside of the country. So we've all we've watched
a lot of things to sort out. But we all watch this on YouTube so this is where we're getting this information.
We watch the video of the ride. Right. I mean that's an interesting point is
that you're right that if there's anything to be desired in the
current ride maybe that arrow room is
an area. I mean if you guys want to talk about our
system the plus it up. Let's do that
and then we'll talk about a few other indie things at different parks. Sure. So yeah we
have where they yeah we have a system where we say you know what
we would do with the ride if we were in charge and one choice is
keep it as is. Two would be to plus it up do something to it
and three would be to have it burned down in a mysterious fire
for insurance purposes. Yeah. So we'll go
around the room. We'll each say what we would do to the Indiana Jones Adventure. Temple of the
Forbidden Eye. Let's start with Jason. Sure.
OK. I mean I think I would definitely keep it like this is
hands down as close as you can get to objectively
one of the best rides there is.
And I never gave too much thought to like the last little bits
of the ride. I mean obviously the very end of the ride where the giant boulder comes
out and Indies hanging from a rope and then you come around the corner and
you see he's OK. Which interesting fact the ride vehicle
is not moving backwards. The ride vehicle can only move forwards like the
walls are moving backwards as the ball
is rolling towards you. I didn't know that. That's cool.
That part still scares me. Still scares me. To this day that boulder
flying I still go well this is the time it's going to happen and I'm going to get crushed. Yeah. Sorry.
Assuming it's heavy it could be an illusion. It's probably an illusion. It's probably
ride magic. So I never really gave much thought to
plusing it up. But then watching the ride through of the
Tokyo Disney One it did make me think about like yeah there is that one
dead spot where it's a black room with a projection of a branch full of rats.
And then the dart room which I think is really cool like the sound effects
and the air shooting at you like the darts. But like the
Tokyo Disney One which is in Disney Sea in
Tokyo just looks so much cooler. Like it's like there's a bunch of
little rock work. It's got this just Incan overlay
and this cool like crystal blue lighting effects.
That's pretty neat. Yeah. So that's my that would be my only thing. It's like
little touches like that. And in all fairness they have like just recently
even though they didn't have to they added some rear projection
effects in the early rooms of the ride.
Not rear projection. Whatever that projection map.
Yeah. Put a lot of nice sparkles on Mara's face in that room. It looks cool.
Yeah. So but yeah I think you keep it and
you really don't have to do much to it. I think it's great. Sure.
I as I was saying I think we have talked
about and you might have some points about this about that that arrow room is kind of the
Yes. That's the that's the spot where because it's towards the end of the ride too after you've seen so much
spectacular crap. And then there's a room where it's just flat and they're like
skeletons are painted on the wall as opposed to like real skeletons. It looks like
the club in Batman Forever or Robin
or whichever wherever Coolio is. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Where Coolio is in Batman
Forever. I think most people remember that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You know the Dayglow Club
which maybe is what it's called. Yeah.
My idea there I don't know if you have an idea regarding that
room as well but I you know I think
one thing that Disney's had a lot of success with in terms of plussing up
is adding more recent characters who people know
you know kids understand kids look at
Johnny Depp and C Jack Sparrow and pirates and hey it's for my
generation now. And I think if there's any let down in there I can only assume for
people younger than I it's that they are missing their favorite beloved
character Mutt Williams portrayed by Shia LaBeouf.
I'm sure by that point it get there's a little bit of a lull that Arrow Room is
only so exciting and people are probably thinking where is Mutt. So
my solution here is that those are no longer
arrows. Those are Mutt's famous switch blades.
Oh man. And he's whipping them past your head.
I don't know if it now I don't know. I'm on board for Mutt baby. Mike gave me a Mutt Williams action
figure for my birthday. Oh man. Oh you're a Mutt head. Oh boy.
Sign me up. Real Mutt hands. I was on board for that Mutt Williams
solo movie. A greaser who's good at sword fighting?
Wild. And good at like sliding around through
low corridors. So just so I'm clear I'm clear what
you're pitching me here. Towards the end is will there be Mutt animatronics?
Because like as it is now there's like multiple you know skeleton or
whatever people that are shooting you know darts at you. Will Mutt be
just painted on the wall or will there be like a Mutt two Mutt robot like one Mutt robot
running up and down throwing switch blades at the off. That's a good question. I mean
I just figure that effect could be easily amended to be a famous Mutt
switch blade whipping by your face. But then what does that require that there are
a lot of Mutt's. I imagine he has the ability to like ping it
back and forth on the wall. Oh okay. And make it go back
and forth. So maybe you still have those voodoo priest kind of guys.
And maybe it's a little like he interrupts the ride that we think we know. Like you're heading
into the arrow room and then Mutt's like okay not so fast huh.
And then he whips that knife back and forth and
they all get punctured right in the middle of the skull. He just wants to show you
a cool trick or he saves you or he just wants to show you a cool new knife trick. I think
he's saving you or maybe there's another little additional
sound effect and he is slicing the arrows in half
right as you're driving through. So right in front of your face right as the arrows
whiz by you. Also the switch blade is perfectly going back and forth
cutting them in half deflecting them and saving you. Huh. I mean
this is cool. I mean this is going to be an advanced animatronic technique because I would like to see
like if you could digitally show me that the knives cutting it in half
I think we'd be in business. Well maybe it's a I mean like the arrows
I think it would have to be an imaginary a sensory an auditory experience.
But right before you went in there I think Mutt would be
casually leaning up in the side of the road or like if you just be in the corner
you think it's just dark and there's nothing over there and then he leans out like
hey not so fast voodoo guys. Do you encounter Mutt's
skull a trick up his sleeve. Is he Barbarino from Welcome Back Hotter?
He is a he
in my shared universe theorizing he is the
father or grandfather of Barbarino.
Hey Wubba Balu Bop. Yeah he had that sweat he had the swag that
would eventually birth the sweat hogs. So the sweat hogs are ultimately a
tribute to Mutt. And then maybe you also
add him into the next room where Indiana Jones is hanging off the dangling off
in front of the boulder. Maybe he doesn't know what he's going to do and then old Mutt's like
hey I got you back me and my monkey pals and then he goes swinging by
I guess the monkeys these would also be the most
sophisticated animatronics in the world but I think it'd be worth it to have a bunch
of monkeys all together grab Indiana Jones take him to safety
and then you just crash into the boulder
and he isn't there to deflect it. So you die but Indy is safe.
That's my new ending. Okay I like the idea that in one of the
most urgent rides of all time both times you see Mutt he's just kind of leaning
he's like hey what up what are you doing? Up your nose with a rubber hose.
Sit on it. Which I guess is Potsies from Happy Days.
Ain't no big thing I got this I'm not like a control freak like my dad.
So okay we're going to plus it up with Mutt
you want to plus it up with Mutt. Plus it up Mutt it up. This universally
reviled character. Is he? I don't know
I think the youngster maybe it's like us old fogies
don't get the minions but I think maybe the kids are all big Mutt hounds just like
you. Mutt madness? I mean Jason calls himself a Mutt man.
Yeah. Just a dirty dog like Mutt.
If I could just get some of that Mutt strut. Oh man.
I could face the day. Mike?
I mean I don't have a suggestion as good as that but I do
as we said before a pretty almost perfect ride I would
I would put Indy on the ride a few more times honestly. Sure.
Cause you see Indy at the start he's holding the door trying to hold it closed and that's about it
and then you really only see him on the rope at the end and I feel like at least
we see Captain Jack like three times at the very least right? Three or four?
One might almost call it excessive. Oh well you sure?
Someone special guest recently had an extra appearance
by a not animatronic Captain Jack. Right. Oh yeah.
The real man. The real abusive man.
I'm saying too many dark things in this episode.
So I feel like there's opportunities to see Indy like
one instance like maybe like the hood of the car opens
and he's in there somehow like his head pokes out and he's like ah I got stuck in the car
I got stuck in the engine or there's a part where you're on that bridge
and he's in the big stone face and he's like
I'm in the mouth or something like I'm trapped in this mouth.
Maybe isn't you know I don't think I could write the next
film or be part of the creative of this franchise but isn't he he might he'd probably
be like oh this is good or right like oh I'm
in the mouth again. I'm glad about this. I'm in Mara's mouth.
Giant mouths. Why did it have to be giant
mouths? So like I think you know. He's a wry sarcastic
man. That's true or yeah like he could be I mean you could put
him anywhere. You could put him in the skeleton room. I'm getting
so old I belong in a museum. Yeah quips like
that. I guess that I'll be joining you soon brothers
he says to the skulls. Oh Indiana Jones
like okay with his mortality. Kathleen Kennedy
and the people of Lucasfilm call us. Call us. He's just
resigned to it. Oh boy. Oh brother.
That means an old crank right. Just like the real Harrison.
Then that brings me to my next point. Let's get that real Harrison
voice on the ride. Yeah. There's a TMZ
picture from a few years ago of him riding this ride with Calista and the kids.
He knows it exists. He's been there. He's gonna do another
Indiana Jones. While he's there get the sound guy to mic
him and get him to do 10 lines and let's record it so we can have the real
Harrison there. Especially because you know he's gonna have to do all this extra crap
on that set anyway like I'm Harrison Ford and you're watching a Yahoo
exclusive sneak peek of my new movie. Yes. So like if you're gonna
force feed all these horrible promos into his mouth do
something that the fans would really appreciate. Tell me that wasn't
big fun. Which like you're gonna have to get him to give like that energetic
performance that like. Part time. Part time. Hey. Oh if we could add part. Hey
Snatchatters. Check out my old Indiana Jones.
That. Okay you said that line. Indy at the
end. On Wikipedia it says like there's like eight things he can say
to you. Eight quips he can say. And the most two most upsetting
ones to me are don't tell me that wasn't big fun. Like it's not
a phrase. Yeah it's not a good phrase. And the other one was
you were good in there. You were very very good. And I don't
know why but I find that upsetting. That was the one clip
of the real Harrison Ford. You were good in there. You were very very good.
It might be maybe because it reminds me of it. Did you guys ever
see The Good Dinosaur? No. The Pixar movie. Yeah the Pixar movie.
It's pretty rough but
the tagline that is constantly repeated
throughout it I believe is
like the father dinosaur who eats shit and
dies pretty quickly says to the main character child dinosaur
like what is he oh god I can't remember it perfect
now but it's like you're me and more.
Or it's like you're me and so much more. It's something
where they like try to really make it like hit and it
did not and they say it so many times through the movie. It's the only movie
I've ever gone like should I leave? Like
I don't think I need to see the rest of this.
That reminds me of when the old dog in Homeward Bound
when he returns to his family the Hume Cronin voiceover
is like I'm home.
You're my boy. I'm back. You're my special boy.
It's a like real creepy old line. I have a real problem
with people saying boy that weirds me out.
Old grandfather love I think
I find to be a little creepy in this film. I just looked it up. The line is
you're me and more. So let's add this to
Harrison's reference. You're me and more.
He says by the broken boulder. I feel like you should get like 30 lines
for him to say at the end there too. Like really change it up. Make him holiday specific.
Like oh good thing we got out of there and Merry Christmas.
Good way to spend an Easter.
Happy Halloween. Like and really like make it specific.
Yeah I give thanks for that. Check out the
Disneyland Snapchat Discovery. The Snapchat
Stories channel. If you liked this ride be sure to subscribe
to our YouTube channel. Click here, here, or
here to subscribe. So we're keeping the ride as is.
Yeah keeping the ride. Adding some SEO marketing.
100%. Hey we'll be right back.
Alright we're back. And brace yourself because
right now we're gonna go to a dark secret
corner of the theme park world that most
people are not brave enough to venture into. It's an area people
don't talk about very often and it's called Confessionland.
Now in Confessionland a bunch of guys
tell unpopular opinions to each other. And then
we judge each other based on those opinions. We're going to confess
things that we as Mega Theme Park fans
have probably just shut up about. And we say
oh yeah we like this or we don't like that. But we actually have opinions that might
really rock the boat of theme park fandom. And this tone of
voice that we're using is making it seem a lot sleazier than it's
actually going to be. Get ready it's gonna be real dramatic.
Because it's probably gonna be not terribly eventful.
But I think we should keep in mind though this is something I would not say if I
met a bunch of like Disney fans in the park I would not lead
with this piece of this opinion. You're not gonna make friends
with these opinions. Because people in the park would be probably mad I think. So let's
go around the room and give our unpopular
opinion. Here in Confession.
We were just talking about which one would be called and that's both of them.
Alright look.
All things going off the rails. Okay I'll come into it.
My confession is I don't like the shows.
There it is. I don't. A big part of
theme parks is parades and shows
and fireworks. And I don't like any of it.
I think it's very rare that I enjoy any of the
like to me they are kind of a waste of time.
They only get in the way of the rides. I like that they exist because
they eat up people and prevent them from going on the rides and make the lines
shorter. But you know what I mean like all these Disney attractions.
So you're saying shows meaning you don't like the fireworks at the end of the night. You don't like most parades.
You don't like the Aladdin Stays show. You don't like Fantasmic. You don't like any of that.
I would I'd give it to Fantasmic. I'm fond of Fantasmic and I'm sure
we're gonna talk about it at some point. The show along the rivers of America
at the end of the day at Disneyland. But that one I'd bump up because
it's so spectacular. But like yeah I don't know a lot of them I find
to be sort of over underwhelming. You know it's
it's like the to me they like trade these things
out every year and they're all like just
different shades of the same thing. Like you know
the one year they'll put in a new thing and it's called like Wishes. A magical
celebration of dreams. And then they and then that's done. Wishes is closed.
We're opening dreams. Celebrate your magic
wishes. Like they're all so generic. Right now. Not really get to
anything. And it's all just you know it's the same songs over and over.
It's always gonna be a whole new world. It's always gonna be
now let it go. They've jammed
Let It Go in every corner of that park. I don't discount that children
enjoy these things. Families like going to them. But I sort of don't like World of Color.
I don't know. I don't I don't ever watch any of these things. Cause they have
I watched the fireworks on Friday. I believe it's called Remember Dreams Come True.
It's the name of the show. And the
sixtieth anniversary had this fireworks show that was very like you know you played the songs
from the party world or whatever and all that. And I like those songs
or whatever. And I was a bit underwhelmed. But the show they have now Remember Dreams Come True
has all of the theme park songs in it. So you've got Haunted
Mansion. You've got Tiki Room. And to dismiss
fireworks shows wholesale. I mean this show was
great. I had not seen it before. The fireworks go all the way around. I'm getting upset
now that I'm thinking about it. Okay. Well there we go. It's a great
show. Exactly the right kind of opinion for
Confession Lad.
Yeah I don't know. Look it's personal taste. I
admit that fireworks are very impressive.
I am not discounting the work of all the firework-ticians
out there. They do a great job. I don't know what it is. I find
standing and waiting for fireworks to be very unpleasant. Even something
like Phantasmic I don't like that you're jamming into some
you know little brick space and pretending it's a seat.
Or maybe you don't have a seat at all. A lot of this stuff is outside. And the
time of year can make it exponentially worse.
Especially oh god on the other coast in Orlando
like watching fireworks or watching the
like the Phantasmic in Orlando is at Hollywood Studios. It's in a giant
open amphitheater. It's insane. And it's
hot. It's 10 o'clock at night and it's
still 80 degrees and humid. Super humid. And it's
I definitely just fell asleep from exhaustion there
once. In all fairness I fell asleep a lot of places. That being said you beat me to it.
You've been in my apartment. You've fallen asleep at the weirdest times in the weirdest
like we watching something exciting. You turn your eyes are closed like my grandfather
or something. Like you fall asleep everywhere. In college I fell asleep
in class once with a pen in my mouth. Wait wait wait wait. Like a pen
like you were like. Like I was chewing on a pen and I fell asleep with it
like hanging out of my mouth. Like sitting up like a horse. Yeah I was sitting in like a giant lecture
hall and I had both feet up on the seat in front of me and I
fell asleep with a pen hanging out of my mouth. A little fact about me I've never fallen asleep
in a public place ever. Oh. I'm too scared to.
Well I've made up for it. For you. You fall asleep in a lot of public places.
The average of the room is high still thanks to Jason. Thanks to me.
I want to fall asleep when I go to see these
shows. I don't need to hear about wishes and dreams and journeys
anymore. I don't even really like the Epcot one.
Which I admit is very impressive. Oh illuminations. Illuminations. Oh wow.
The thing with the globe opens up. It's a beautiful moment.
But what is it? It's like a bunch of children being projected.
Oh yeah. I mean. I don't. There's a lot of. They're all too generic. I want
some more specific points and theories in these shows. I also
I don't think I'm that into the trend of projecting the stuff onto the buildings.
There's a thing that a lot of the Disney shows are doing these days where
like we took the castle and we turned it into Iron Man's house.
And it still juts out like a castle.
But I don't know. I feel like it's a trick. I feel like that effect
must be kind of cheap to do because they're doing it everywhere.
It's very new and trendy. It's very much like the thing at the moment.
Yeah. Yeah. But like a Spago kind of restaurant
that's going to have its peak and then it'll
be done. Well drones will be the new thing. I'm pretty excited for the
So maybe drones will bring you back to being into all these shows. I think so. A bunch of coordinated
drones. Do you know there's drone racing? Have you seen drone racing? No. Oh boy.
Like on Deep ESPN there's drone racing. Oh wow. It's like very very
excited. They book out an entire stadium and they leave the stadium empty and drones
like weave through the tight corridors. It's very cool.
So I think you're right. Give me some drones and then I'm back in. You got me back.
I'm back in the crowd of hundreds of thousands of people
watching the fireworks. Jason, what
was the segment called again? Confession Land? Confession Land.
What's your next Confession Land?
Okay. Well we're all Southern California based. The three
of us. We live in Los Angeles. Yes correct. So one
of the parks we end up in a lot is Disney's California Adventure.
And you know they did that billion dollar, multi-billion dollar
over redo of it a few years ago.
Mike and I went opening weekend. We were there opening weekend
for it. And you know I love
all the new stuff they add it. I think it's great. It's a much better
park. But every now and then man I miss that old
California Adventure. What? What really? Yeah
because I in all fairness I did not see it
like I saw it in 2006. So it was like there
some holes in the rowboat had been plugged at that point.
Like they had thrown Bugs Life in there for kids. They had thrown Tower
of Terror in there for everyone else. But I just like the fact
that you because Disneyland to me has always
felt like there's so much stuff.
And when the first few years of going like I really wanted to see a lot
and see like the limited stuff and the stuff that they didn't have in Florida
and the like little hidden secrets that like I would read about
online. And then when I needed a break I just go over to
California Adventure where there was no lines and there's like not that many people.
And you just walk around and you could knock it all out in like two and a half
hours. So it was I found it very relaxing. You felt it was like a
waiting room for Disneyland. Yeah kind of. It's
relaxing to me in a way that like
Walt Disney World is very overwhelming. Right?
Like if you go there and you spend a few days there like even if you try
to like well maybe I'll just go to the pool for a little while. Like my instinct is
go like but I should be out there. I should be at one of these parks.
I should be doing something. But I feel a similar way about like
Universal Orlando where if you stay on site you can walk
to everything. The parks aren't open very late.
If you stay at some of the hotels you get an express pass and you can kind of just walk on
to a lot of stuff. So you knock it out very quickly and it's kind
of relaxing. And as I get older I do like
relaxing a little at these places where when I was younger. This is
crazy. This doesn't explain to me why you like like a big
postcard that came to life or like the Whoopi
Goldberg movie about the history of California. I never saw that. I never did watch
that. I never watched it either. I never watched it. It was always there and I didn't watch it. It was always there. I don't know why I
never watched it. Well if you like being asleep then that's
the perfect spot for it. You would rather have a shittier park if it meant that you were like less
comfortable. No. I just sometimes like when you're
crushed like when you're in the queue for Cars Land or like
when it's really crowded in this park I do long for the days when it's like
well there used to be like no one here. But you know what was there
was a parking lot. Like it doesn't it replaced nothing.
It's not like there was some cool ride that just nobody knew about. Oh well that
yeah. But I didn't know it then either. I also did not know the
first gen. There's also a part of me that wishes I could have seen like
the superstar limo where you race through Hollywood and terrifying
puppet people talk to you and the ABC
soap opera cafe. Like I wish I had seen the first generation
catastrophe Disney California Adventure. See it yes.
But you didn't want to be there. Now it's this lush the Buena Vista Street
the great restaurant. That's one of my favorite places. Oh yeah. No it's
great. It's much better now. But every now and then I do kind of like
I kind of miss when this was. But name one thing you liked
that they took out. I like the ice cream parlor that was inside
of a train car. Yeah that's pretty
good. But you can get the same ice cream they have.
All the pun based signs like Burbank ice cream.
You still have photos of them. You can read them. This reminds you of some like garbage Jersey
shore shit you like visited as a kid. You watch your mouth.
You were used to some trash and you want to feel like there's some trash down at Disney that's more
suited to you. I oh maybe. And also
you've told me like your family when you would go on trips would have days of decompressing
before you'd even step foot in the park. Like there was so much relaxing.
Well no after the park. I thought it was before. After you go go go. You told me there would be a
day after the flight to recover from the flight. Then there would be the trip.
Then there would be another day to recover before you got on another flight home.
No. We would deke. I mean we were kids. We didn't have
to. We would do it in the summer. So like we were off all summer. But
yeah after like five days of like sun up to sun down
like in the parks. Like yeah we would want to decompress
a little. You know if you want to take a nap go to your home. Leave the
cool feet park to us awake folks. Yeah.
I am amazed that this is a more unpopular opinion. I thought this wouldn't be
that controversial. No you're going to win I think. This segment will tear us apart.
We'll see what everyone thinks of mine. It's much better now. I'm glad we have it now. But every now and then
it's like man I remember when there was just a bunch of fucking tractors here.
Here's what I like is that we set this up in a way of like we're going to say these things that would make people
pretty mad. And then we are mad. Yeah we are now mad. We're moving what
works for you. I've also like clarified what I've met a lot.
Like yeah no it's much better now. I don't want it to come back.
But it was kind of funny to walk around. It was
it was kind of different. Go to the Santa Monica Pier. Yeah.
Mike confession. Mine might be the mildest now that I think about it.
I don't love I don't even really like Jungle Cruise.
Sure. Is that that's not unpopular. Maybe mine is the weakest
because it's like I kind of find it boring. I find the punny punny stuff
with the tour guides. I think that's lame.
I think that it's outdated. It feels you know it feels like there's not enough
robots on it. It's just I never go on it. I don't have an
urge to go on it. Well yeah I agree. I think that I think the joke
stuff. I mean yeah it's it's I know it's tradition it's been around forever.
I think you're right. It's the kind of thing like you know watch a video of it if you like it.
But maybe there's a way to make that ride better. I would I would gut it.
I would make it like I would make the shore much closer to
the boats. I would make like crazy robot animals like I would
make it serious. I would take all that jokey crap away. I think that's
sacrilege to a lot of people because it's you know putting day wall thing. But like
I never go on it. But it's one of the ones that everyone considers like a classic.
That line is is kind of murderous. It's a really boring one.
I think you may have presented the opinion we all agree with the most but anyone listening
would be furious. Oh oh oh oh oh oh. I very much like that
turn of the early 20th century explorer kind of aesthetic.
Sure. I like the radio. I like the old timey music. Sure. Playing
I like that adventurer sort of
stuff. I agree with that all of that. Yeah the puns can be a little
much. I am not a fan of when any when guests
speak along to stuff. And now I feel like a lot
of really die hard fans will like speak along with like
the backside of water. And that always kind of make makes me cringe.
But it may also just be like being in comedy
and seeing like more hokey or stuff.
It can be a little crazy comedy. Now that you're a comedy expert you feel.
Now that I am yes. Now that I am a. See comics
can't stand hearing somebody else do a joke because you wish you thought of it.
Yes. Which jungle cruise joke did you wish you thought of?
The backside of water is a beaut. Two of his hits. Two of his hits.
We all know it. We wish we wrote it. Ah son of a bitch.
Man that's a classic. I wish I thought of shooting that gun.
Sometimes I do like the gun. I like the gun on the ride.
I do like that the original concept was like we got to scare off that
hippo. Shoot it in the fucking face. Yeah I like
that. So I'm not saying you get rid of the name jungle cruise but like
I would gut the whole thing. I would reimagine it in a new way.
Well aren't there rumors. You might be getting that. Dwayne the Rock Johnson.
There was an Instagram to this effect. It's public. Yeah but I think that
very quickly Disney was like that's not happening. Like I feel like Rock has just ushered into rooms
and like he's like posted an Instagram of like yeah I'm making the new
jungle cruise ride. And then like he's ushered out and then people are like what was he talking about.
Like he might have misheard someone say something and he posted a big thing
about it. Because I don't think. But maybe I mean maybe if this movie. Because there is a jungle cruise movie
which is something they reiterated they were doing at D23.
And that is the rock. It is the rock. So that is happening. So maybe
if the ride, excuse me if the movie does very well
and it's a very exciting adventure they'll change it.
Chances are though they'll do this Jack Sparrow thing and like the rock will be on.
The robot rock will be on it now. Yeah. Now that you've talked about changing it I don't like
that change. I don't like that change either. I mean if it's a fully new badass
jungle cruise I guess then like a rock animatronic.
Jungle cruise reloaded. Jungle cruise lock and load.
Jungle cruise lock and load. The gun they shoot in the sky just gets a lot
bigger. That's how they change. Most of the ride is taken up by adding pieces
to the gun.
It won't be able to fit as many people in the boat because there's so many chambers. There's like a shoot out between
the rock and a rival jungle gang. Yeah.
So maybe in that instance. Two crews. Two crews. Two jungle crews.
Ooh jungle crews. Plan words.
Cruise and cruise. Oh yeah. Wait what's the plan words?
Like crew like a crew of guys C R E W
and then cruise jungle cruise. Ah I see. So you could go both ways. I mean it's not like
a crew. It just happens to be. Oh is that a leaf? Yeah I think it's a leaf.
I need you to be part of my jungle cruise.
So we'll change the name of the ride to jungle cruise C R E W
S and we'll at least preserve the name, the sound of the name but it'll be
a whole new imagined action adventure ride for the rock and
Kevin Hart or somebody. Will that make you happy Michael?
No. Maybe I'll shut up about the jungle cruise for once.
You don't like the old puns so you thought of a way better one to name
the ride. Oh that's a good point. I'll tell you what you know I'd like to see
maybe let's you know there's already water in that play. I want to see
old Mitch Buchanan from the Baywatch
team. Maybe he's on the jungle cruise. Sure.
An old shirtless Zac Efron with his 19 pack
his scary amount of abs. Is Hobbs the rock's
character's name from Fast and Furious? Yes. And Hobbs will be there. Hobbs
will also be there. Alright let's get out of it.
You survived podcast the ride. Thanks to Feral Audio and everybody we'll see you next
time guys. So long.
Feral Audio.