Feral Audio.
Warning. The following podcast contains stomach-churning stops at Red Rockets' Pizza Port,
a white-knuckle examination of theme park swingers,
and an absolutely definitive decision about which is better, Walt Disney World or Disneyland.
With the help of birthday slash doughboy, Mike Mitchell, strap in for the new episode of Podcast The Ride.
Hey everybody, welcome to Podcast The Ride, a theme park podcast where some nice older men
talk to each other about it. Is that the good? That was a bad one, right?
Did you like that phrase?
It was a little cumbersome. We're working on that catchphrase. Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
And Scott Gardner.
Hi, I'm here again as well.
Yeah, and today with us is our first guest episode. We're being joined by,
from Netflix's Love and Feral Audio's Doughboys, Mike Mitchell.
Hello everybody, thank you for having me. I'm the first guest, that's great.
You're the Will Ferrell or the Tom Hanks of...
We're starting off within this scale.
In the podcast world.
You are a regular Seth Rogen or Billy Crystal.
You're what's called a get, Mitch.
Oh my God.
Yeah, yeah, so thank you so much.
What the hell's happened to the world?
Lots of fracturing.
I also, we are recording this here at Feral Audio where you originally recorded the first
several years of Doughboys, which makes me feel like we are playing with Michael Jordan in,
wherever Michael Jordan played.
You're going to be back in the booth.
The United Center.
That's what you were looking for.
The United, it's like we're back in the famous United Center with the memorable name.
Okay, it's nice to be back here. I forgot what it was like in here. It's great. There's free drinks.
Yeah, that's it.
Number one.
I found where the snacks are.
Jason found half a muffin upstairs.
Somebody was like, yeah, somebody was like, we got muffins upstairs. And he like wandered
upstairs, which we're not allowed to do.
I didn't know there was a second floor. They told me go ahead.
I've never been upstairs. Wow, you're very comfortable here already.
When you're in pursuit of free snacks.
For sure.
You'll get comfortable. He's got the radar for it. So thank you. Yeah. Thank you for joining us.
Thank you, bro.
Very excited to be here. I love, hey, I love parks. Every park there is.
Any kind of park.
Any national park.
Central park.
Central park. Park and go, Carlson.
Like at the airport.
That's every type. That's every type of park.
It's cheaper than that airport parking that's right next to the airport.
Sure.
That is very, that's true. Yeah. Fuck, fuck that parking.
And I love parks with, hey, even with Confederate statues.
Oh my. Oh no.
Keep them up.
Important part of our history from like 30 years ago.
I like when they pull the one statue down and like it crumbled. Do you see how it like crumbled?
Yeah. There's news stories about that. A lot of them were put up in the 20s and 30s and were
very cheaply made. Like made in mass quantities to put up.
Yeah, good. Take them all down.
We've sort of not, we've alluded to it here and there and I'm sure we'll do the full episode
about it at some point, but we are coming up on like a new monument being erected at Disney World,
the Donald Trump robot in the hall of presence.
Wow.
It's impossible to avoid thinking about talking about, I mean, it's not what's foremost in most
people's minds these days, I guess, but I truly am wondering, is that show ready to go? Can they
turn it on at any minute or are they avoiding it because everything is getting so crazy?
They gotta be avoiding it. I think they're trying to, they're trying to punt.
Yeah.
They keep punting.
That could also be another, I know we've talked about mysterious fires for insurance money in the
past. That could be another victim.
Oh no, the ride, guys, the ride burned down.
This is going to take another year to fix.
Faulty Martin Van Buren started sparking up.
Now it's just about the first couple presidents.
I like that they don't want to put it, it seems like they don't want to put it up, right?
Yeah, they don't. I mean, cause it'll be fights. There'll be people fight,
cause some people will boo, some people will cheer, and then those people will fight.
I think that's, I would have be a legitimate concern.
Just put them up and not have them talk or something.
That's what they're saying. They might change the scripts only like Lincoln or Kennedy talks.
Which is how it was until Clinton, Clinton started doing the speeches and then
Clinton, Bush, Obama have all given speeches. Trump's, the rumor is Trump's White House,
if you can imagine, has been very difficult about scheduling a time for him to come do
the robot speech. But then they came out and said that wasn't true and vice had to retract something.
And like every, every thing, even within this innocent theme park world,
everything this administration touches is just like toxic.
So much drama. But like not every president speaks, right?
Like, uh, okay, then he doesn't have to talk.
He should just like peer over something and like give a little wave and then go back down.
Or be suddenly in the chair next to you.
It'd be like alien encounter with Donald Trump. Or he's like all around you.
Heavy breathing and farting and just stalking around.
Smells vaguely like McDonald's.
I would like that. If Trump's robot had McDonald's, I think that's funny.
And worth putting them up for.
Offers it to you, opens with bag opening technology. This robot is the most advanced.
It's not unprecedented. There used to be those McDonald's French fry carts in the parks.
They just sold McDonald's French fries.
That's where it used to be.
Yeah. In Disney World.
But only McDonald's, just the French fries.
Just the fries. It was just like a little snack cart that sold fries and soda.
Yeah.
That's so cool because they, like they, they, they, they, like those are the best fry.
That's the coolest thing that they do.
Yeah. They don't do that anymore.
No, they don't. It's over.
It was like a license thing.
Oh, it was a lot.
It was like a sponsorship thing.
Well, and they were testing the waters of do people want McDonald's in the theme parks?
And people did not. All of the dorky fans such as ourselves at probably ages 14 to 16 at the time
were all like this ruins the original vision.
But people love the Starbucks in the parks. Like the Starbucks in the parks are always packed.
Yeah.
Yeah. There's Starbucks in, in Disneyland or Disney World?
Every, every park, every Disney park.
Really?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
They, I don't like that.
They've themed it better though. They, like there was a place called the Market House on Main Street
and now there's a Starbucks in the Market House. So it's like a little, it's a little more hidden.
The logos are inside, but like.
It hasn't been egregious, I will say.
Yeah.
Yes. You can go to a regular and it just has like the basic sandwiches that you would have
at any Starbucks and you can use your app there. It's sort of weird. It does pull you out of
Disneyland a little bit.
Yeah. I don't, I don't like it for that reason, but I have a question for you and I'm not,
this is not like some doughboys cross potting or something.
For real, and if I'm stepping on anything, yell at me.
Sure.
But I just wanted to say that I like Pizza Port.
Oh.
We have, there's been no discussion of Pizza Port yet on the show.
No?
In Tomorrowland, you're talking about the Tomorrowland in Disneyland restaurant.
I actually like that. I like how the pizza is like theme park pizza and it's good to me.
I like Pizza Port.
I have a question. When was the last time you went there?
The last time I went there was about three, four weeks ago.
Oh, pretty recently.
You went to Pizza Port?
I went to Pizza Port.
Oh really? See, I thought that the, I used to like it and I feel like it took a dive into like
mass produced Chuck E. Cheese type pizza where I was disappointed.
To be fair, I have gone to Chuck E. Cheese recently and Pizza Port is a billion times better.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's not besmirch the fine folks who make pizzas at Pizza Port.
Huh, that's interesting.
That's controversial though, because I feel like Pizza Port is everyone's least favorite Disneyland
place.
I know. No, I feel like it's gotten that rap, but you know what, I haven't eaten that. I was
wondering what your guys favorite food is, because every time I go there, for me, the biggest thing
for me is just getting a Dole Whip and I'll always get a Dole Whip. And then besides that, I don't
care. I'll get like a Churro, but I don't have like any specific places I have to eat. I've never
eaten in like, what's the, is it like the Blue Bayou or something?
Yeah.
I've never eaten there.
We did it with Mike and I went on a double date.
Was it at Blue Bayou?
With our girlfriend wives and I was with each other.
Oh yeah, it wasn't you two with us.
Yeah. Though we recently, we several times in the last few weeks have been to Disneyland, just you
and I.
For a few hours.
For, yeah. Look, if it was all day, then it'd be weird, but just several hours since. It's perfectly
fine for two men to go to Disneyland on a Wednesday and eat Beauty and the Beast gray stuff
together. It's a beautiful thing.
On a Wednesday morning.
Do you know about the gray stuff, Mitch?
No, what is, what is Beauty and the Beast gray stuff?
You know, like from the song, have the gray stuff, it's delicious.
Oh yeah.
Don't believe me, ask the dishes. There's a Beauty and the Beast restaurant now and they have
a dessert called gray stuff.
Is it good?
It is good.
Yeah.
It's delicious.
Jason had it.
It's good. Yeah, it's very good.
Have I split the gray stuff with you as well?
Yes, we've split the gray stuff, Mike and I.
Jason and I have also been.
Tried a little sampling. We split the gray stuff and the rose lemon custard.
Mitch now wants to leave this dark den as quickly as possible.
This is like when like a girl finds out that like, like a group of girlfriends are talking
and they find out that they like all gone on a date with a guy. It's Carlson eating the
gray stuff with everybody.
Mike and I went down, the two of us one, why did we go down that one? Was it after Guardians
opened?
Does there have to be a why?
Yeah, we were down there to go on the first Guardians.
The first, okay.
One of the first weeks of the Guardians was, and then we split a bunch of food together.
We just lay in your same game down. How many side Disney pieces do you have?
Look, this same, I give a lot of the men the same run around.
There's guys all over town who have been on my four hour Disney date.
And yet when it's time to go to Disney World, who do you take? Your girlfriend.
Yeah.
Very unbelievable.
You got to do, when it's long, she doesn't even know about any of the men. So she, it's,
I have to, she's got to go on one of the long-term trips because she, I got to throw her off the scent.
Your web of deception knows no bounds.
What else Disney food wise? There is a lot of good stuff.
Do we just want to get into it or do we, did we want to talk about that exciting discovery?
Oh yeah.
Right before we came in here?
You need to talk about that at some point because I want to know what this big discovery is.
Yeah, sure. We don't always have like hot news off the presses, but we just discovered before
we came over here, there's, there's a, all right. So shout outs to a fellow and, and,
going back much deeper than us, Disney podcaster Len Testa.
This is a podcast that we listen to that is a very like, if you're a super, yeah, you know, Mitch.
Oh, Len, oh, Testa.
Just cracking a brew and listening to it.
Hot off the presses.
Our future dear friend or our future mortal enemy, Len Testa.
Stay out of my territory.
He does a podcast called the unofficial guide to Disney dish podcast where they like break down
like the history of rides. He does it with this guy named Jim Hill and they,
they get like way into it. So you learn about like the whole like splash mountain, the history of
how it was developed, who made it to what.
Honestly, it sounds like a better guest than me. I feel like you guys need to,
you gotta get someone in here who knows what they're talking about. I don't know anything.
Well, I think Len was in Florida.
But could Len be as, as funny as us? Can he give you the laughs?
He's probably funnier.
Most likely.
So, so if you listen to that podcast, like you are, it's like, it's a calling card for your like
theme, weird theme park nerd, dumb or whatever.
And we, Scott just discovered on Twitter that one of Len's followers is Anthony Scaramucci.
In the list of followers you may know it's like the two of us and Scaramucci.
Scaramucci.
Strangest little fact to see.
He follows a lot of people on Twitter, but we also saw a couple days ago that he was tweeting
from Diagon Alley at Universal Studios in Florida.
He was avoiding the theme parks.
So there's a chance, we're not sure is what we're saying.
Scaramucci might be one of us.
Now, I don't know if he is going, was he there alone or was he there with his kids?
Is he allowed to see his kids right now?
Oh, that's right.
Well, what's up with the kids at this point?
He's got that crazy divorce.
He's got a divorce.
Oh yeah.
But the kid is new.
He has a baby.
He probably didn't take the new baby.
Unless this is the first time he's seen the new baby.
For the listeners who might not know who Scaramucci is, he was for what?
Three days?
It was 10 days exactly.
Oh, he was 10.
Okay.
He was the head of communications in Donald Trump's White House.
Yeah.
And he famously gave like just a really insane interview
where he's talking about Steve Bannon wanting to suck his own dick.
I love the fact of him being like,
I want to ride the fucking splash mountain.
You got to go in the fucking splash mountain, baby.
It's fucking, it rules.
Yeah, that's very funny to me.
Does he live in, is he a Florida man or is he just visiting?
We don't know.
We just found this.
We got a fucking vacation home.
What the fuck, who fucking cares?
You don't need to know where I fucking live.
I'm a Disney vacation member.
Fuck you.
It's like a timeshare, but you go to Disney World every year.
It's terrific.
I feel like poor SNL missing out on a sport like Scaramucci.
Oh, Scaramucci.
10 day and then SNL even got to get, they, on the weekend update summer.
They still slid one in.
They slid a Scaramucci in, but I was like, hey, this big over the top Italian guy,
like, this is going to be great for them.
And then he's gone.
It's like the one voice any sketch comedian can do.
100%.
And he literally just does sound like a sketch character.
You don't have to change a thing.
Anybody in the cast could have done it, but it was dead center of the summer
and it can't be done now.
And it was done by a former cast member.
They still brought back, no one here can do an Italian voice.
Nobody here can say friggin with a lot of gusto.
It's got to be, we need a special ops.
Dan Aykroyd.
Well now, I mean, they're going to have to bring back Bill Hader
as Scaramucci to address this following Len Testa situation.
They're going to have to write a weekend update.
I really hope so.
Who in the cast would play Len?
Oh, it's got to be Moffat.
You know Moffat's got a killer Len up his sleeve.
So what we probably should do is start a campaign to get Scaramucci on the podcast.
Mm.
Right?
Yeah.
I think that would be great.
So right now we should declare Mr. Scaramucci here.
I'm going to make a plea to him.
You can win off of me, Scaramucci.
Please come on podcast the ride, whether you're a big theme park fan or not.
We would just like to hear your review of Diagon Alley, even if you are not a big fan.
If we could say, if the guests were like three comedians we know in a row
and then Diagon Alley with Anthony Scaramucci.
Great.
And we never discussed anything that's going on.
If we were utter cowards and didn't ask him about anything that's happening in the world.
We'll make a pledge.
We'll pledge to him.
We will not talk about any of the other stuff.
I can make that pledge.
Yeah.
It'd be much more awkward to get into it.
Although you'd be tempted to say, well, if Voldemort shares some common traits with
a certain president who is.
Hey, I can't talk about that, guys.
I can't talk about that.
Okay, sure.
Sorry, sir.
Don't yell at me again, please.
We just become sniveling dorks in the front of me.
We all just gnarled up and we all lose a foot of height and.
You're so cool.
You're so cool, Mooch.
Teach us the way.
Teach me how to say fuck with confidence, Mooch.
I feel like you bringing up like a, I hate when people are like Trump is like Voldemort.
I'm like, don't compare into like a fictional.
Yeah, it's bad.
It's bad.
It's real bad.
There's never, and it's never deep cuts.
It's always Voldemort and Gollum.
Yeah.
There's only a few characters, but he is just, all anybody's getting at is he's a villain.
He is like any villain.
Yeah, he's a bad guy.
He's a villain.
And he's like, he's more like Gaston or something if you had to give him like a villain.
He hates book smarts.
He wants to be able to stop reading, women to stop reading and pay attention to him.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's very true.
He doesn't have the brawn.
Although you could, if you did the same Gaston song, but about eating five dozen egg McMuffins.
He thinks he is like, yeah, it's like LeFou and Gaston combined or something like that.
But he changes his LeFou every week.
It's a new LeFou constantly.
Unless it's Stephen Miller.
That's why he just keeps hanging on.
He's the LeFou.
He is the, yeah, yeah.
He's the guy he can kick into like a pile of chickens or something.
But he'll always dust himself off and be right back with him.
Do you know that LeFou was my first big acting role for real?
Whoa.
Really?
I was LeFou in Beauty and the Beast in, God, how old was I?
This is in theater camp when I was after fifth grade or something.
Wow.
LeFou, my big role.
Was it like a Disney adaptation of it?
Kind of.
I mean, I think like, I sang like No One Fights Like Gaston.
I sang that song.
You did that song?
That's a huge song to get.
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
So I guess, yeah, I guess it was Disney.
How was your singing then and how is your singing now?
I don't think I know much about your musical abilities.
I think back then it was high pitched and now it's more high pitched.
Your testicles have gone up further.
My testicles have, yeah, ascended, I guess.
Testicles ascending.
Did you see the live action one and did you have notes for Josh Gad?
I didn't see the live action one.
I will see it.
I felt like that was such like a Netflix, you know, as a 34-year-old single man,
like going to see Beauty and the Beast is just a little tricky.
And you went and saw it at the El Capitan on Hollywood Boulevard, the Disney-owned
theater with a little pre-show and pushed your way through the crowd to make sure you
got that front row seat.
Got there first and then there's just like an island, there's empty seats all around you,
like two families avoiding them.
That is what I'm, that's what I'm afraid, I guess you could take like a date there or something,
but I don't, I just, I don't.
With a date to take, would you, would Beauty and the Beast be your choice?
Unless the date was interested in this specifically.
You know, here's, here's, here's how I feel about like the,
one, I'm not a fan of Frozen.
I did not like Frozen as a film.
And then I felt like, kind of like these Disney remakes.
I did think like the Jungle Book was impressive, but I, but there's, there's something that's
like a little cynical about these Disney remakes that I don't love or in like the
live action version.
Do you know what I mean?
I agree with that.
It's just kind of like, I don't know.
You're just remaking a movie.
Yes.
Making a movie again.
Here, eat the same slop that we know you like, you fucking.
That's why even like, even though I didn't like Frozen, I was like, oh, at least it's
like a new thing or whatever.
Yeah.
Sure, sure.
Although they will, they'll run that into the ground.
Oh, for sure.
There'll be a live action Frozen, I'm sure at some point.
The musical's coming soon on to Broadway.
Coming to Broadway.
Oh my God.
And Frozen 2 in a few years.
Now that's a real mechanism.
They can just start doing it.
There won't be any lag.
There will just be five different types of Frozen.
Although to be fair, when we were children, there were so many Ninja Turtle products at
the same time that there's animated and you can go see, and the movies and you can go
see them on the tour and the action.
They're all sort of like different types of turtles.
Very sloppy brand I've noted before in the Ninja Turtles.
The people who do, who did Frozen, they did Zootopia, right?
And they, haven't they, aren't they responsible?
They did Tangled, right?
They did Tangled.
Okay, Tangled.
And then I think they, did they not do Zootopia?
They may have.
I don't know.
I think the music people were Broadway people, right?
Like did they write the Book of Mormon music?
Once again, legitimate Disney fans who might be listening to this.
Don't get mad with us.
We don't know everything.
We're this type of Disney fan, I think, who knows, we know the parks really well and the
rest not so much, although same with Len Testa.
You remember he said that once?
Yes.
He offended a lot of people by saying he likes Disney movies at all.
He doesn't like the Disney movies.
He likes the parks exclusively.
Well, I feel like that group that may, which I should never say I don't like
anyone who's making movies or TV, I guess, because of where we live and it's stupid.
But I don't know if I specifically like like the Frozen,
because I didn't love Zootopia much either.
Okay.
But I thought it was, it was okay.
I just didn't, I didn't love it.
I like Pixar stuff more, I guess.
Sure.
I like Inside Out better than I like Frozen or Zootopia or whatever.
Yeah, yeah.
I think that Disney, the Disney not Pixar CGI movies have been sort of a sloppier affair,
although lately they've been, at least there's been
giant hits that have really resonated with people.
But yeah, but go overall, like your bolts and your...
Well, Bolt is like, I feel like Bolt is them getting out of the dirt.
They're like getting, like they're finally getting like movies that people want to see again.
Well, when they bought Pixar, like Lasseter became the head of Disney Animation too.
Yeah, so I think that part of...
So they put a lot of practices in place that they had in Pixar.
But they have had hit, Big Hero 6 was a hit.
They've had...
Yeah, Moana was a big hit.
Any of that you like?
We should talk about your, where you land with Disney.
You were LeFou, any other particular strong Disney connections or theme park connections or...
Disney...
What you like or...
Yeah, all right.
I went to, the first time I went to Disney, I was Disney World,
which I argue is the greater Disney Carlson.
And we're going to talk about it at the top of the show today, so we'll get there.
I think we forgot to say...
We said it at the top.
I went to, the first time I went, I was a child, like a toddler.
Two or three?
Yeah, two or three, somewhere around there.
So my parents took me and my sister, my older sister.
Okay.
And so I don't remember that experience.
And then the second time we went, I think I was in like second grade.
And we took like a camper, like we took like an RV with another fan, like my godparents.
Whoa, whoa.
And so we like, we went down, we drove down to Disney.
Did you stay at like one of the RV, the campsite kind of place?
We stayed at the Grand Floridian at that point.
Oh, okay.
Took the camper to the nice hotel.
Oh, you know what?
Was it not the Grand...
Oh no, I think it was the Grand Floridian.
I can't, I'm not going to remember all the places that we stayed.
That's the big like ornate hotel right by the Magic Kingdom, like right by the entrance.
It was brand new when we went.
Oh wow.
That would line up.
Would that mean I would be in like second-ish grade maybe somewhere?
Something like that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's where the Kokomo music video was filmed.
That's the most relevant fact to me.
And Hulk Hogan's Thunder and Paradise.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, yeah.
And then we went one more time when I was in fifth grade.
So quite a few, I mean like one, I didn't remember, but two that I clearly remembered.
And so this is the timeline of this will work out too, but it was the day,
like the day we were leaving, I remember they were testing Splash Mountain.
Whoa.
And we never got to ride it, like we left before it opened.
And so that was the first time, like so that was my experience with Disney in my childhood.
And then I didn't go again until my senior year of college.
When my family and my godparents family, we all went like with adults, we all, there were no kids.
We just all went as though when we went during Christmas time.
And I rode Splash Mountain for the first time after like whatever, however many years.
Over a decade.
Break, was it everything you dreamed of?
It is great.
I mean, I did love it and I would have been amazing as a child to do it,
but it still was an amazing experience.
And I felt like I was closing the book on it or something like that.
But also in that visit, when we went to, I think it was we were in Magic Kingdom,
my dad and I, because Splash Mountain is a Magic Kingdom, right?
Yeah.
And we, like it was during Christmas and they cut people off,
they wouldn't let any more people into the park.
And I remember walking down Main Street and like we came to a halt.
And like it was like, it was like we couldn't move on Main Street and it like freaked me out.
Like it was the most people I had ever been around in a theme park ever in my life.
It was like insanely packed.
They will like close theme parks entirely.
I remember going with my family and passing by a sign that said Magic Kingdom closed,
being like, dear god, that's insane.
It gets to that point.
It was so many, it was so many, it was so packed.
And like you just like, I remember I couldn't move on Main Street.
And I was like, oh, this fucking sucks.
And then we went and waited in line for like two hours or something to get on Splash Mountain.
That happened to me at Disneyland like two years ago,
like the week after Thanksgiving, family was out visiting.
And like a couple of us were walking down Main Street to exit and it just stopped.
Like the crowd control was all messed up.
And it's like there's people not moving in front of us.
There's people behind and people were starting to get mad.
And it's like, all right, we're just going to duck in the candy store
because it feels like a fight might break out.
There are days, this is the dark side of theme parks for sure.
There are days where you'd rather be anywhere else.
And when I worked at, when I was a tour guide at Universal Studios,
I remember like dead heat of summer, people like,
like the line for the stupid tram tour is like three hours long.
And like people are passing out.
There's like medics and heat strokes.
They can be such crazy miserable places if the conditions aren't right.
Yeah.
It was terrible.
But I mean, I still loved it.
I mean, like we were definitely a Disney family.
I feel like once I got to middle school and stuff,
like my parents were like, that's over with and they just kind of like,
didn't care about it.
But like, I had always, I always loved it.
When we went back and went to college, I was so happy to be back there.
And my parents, my mom has Disney points.
And so when I was out here, she's like, I got to like waste Disney points.
So like I have Disney points to burn.
And so like I remember I took a trip down to the Grand Californian,
Grand California or California, California, California.
And I rented a room and my cam for a bunch of people stayed in there.
And and that that that the Grand Californian is awesome.
It's an amazing hotel.
It's so it is such an amazing looking hotel.
And so I've and so I visited I've been to Disneyland, like
I've been out here for 12 years almost now.
And I've been to Disneyland probably like six times.
Five or six times.
It's a decent amount.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
But like for someone who, you know, isn't like,
like you guys, I guess, out of their minds, not like I found.
I saw the number of how many times I've been
because your annual pass keeps track of it.
Yeah.
And it is I don't know what it is right now because I haven't checked.
It's over 100.
Oh, my God.
Ten years.
That's crazy.
I'll be there probably on average like once a month.
If it gets to be more than that, then.
But we do these a couple hour little stints where you go and, you know,
like get a couple get a couple drinks and mess around for a bit
and don't feel like you got to fit everything in.
And yeah, yeah, yeah.
Those are super fun.
I feel like for I feel like like when I was so I just recently took
like I had friends from Quincy, my hometown, come and visit.
Oh, that's right.
And I we I took him to Disneyland.
So maybe it is more maybe it's like eight times, but it's not more than that.
But I and like I would like I can only imagine Carlson how good you are.
But they were like, wow, you're like you're like the Disney king
because I just like knew where to go just because I'd been there enough times
that I knew what to do.
Yeah.
And I also that day signed up for the path.
You talk about Max Pass.
The Max Pass.
Yeah, yeah.
That Carlson, you I think you were the one who said it on this text thread
that I'm in that you should get the Max Pass.
And and it was fucking awesome.
It was great.
It was it was so worth it because it was like ten dollars per person or something.
And you get to book all your Fast Passes like on the go on your phone.
You book all your Fast Passes on the path.
Like and so we would just basically be going to a ride
and then getting off and going to another.
Like I don't think we waited in a line for like a busy summer day.
It reminded me when I was a kid, when I went in like second grade,
there was a rainy day and it was like the most empty Disney had ever been.
But like Thunder Mountain was still open and we just rode it multiple.
Like we rode it multiple times.
Like they didn't care.
It was and that was like the best day in Disney ever.
It's like a child or whatever.
And then this day was like a close second.
Wow.
I mean, maybe even better because I wasn't a dumb child.
It was like I was an adult.
And all your buds are there.
The whole the whole gang.
Yeah, the whole the Quincy guys were there.
And we were and we were like I think the only line we waited in was the Buzz Lightyear.
And I was like, well, first we go and get a Fast Pass for this thing.
And then let's ride Buzz Lightyear.
That's how I always started off.
I get like a Fast Pass for Space Mountain or Star Tours.
One of the big ones.
And then yeah.
Yeah.
That is, I think, the theme park pro way to do it.
You really do forget that when you go with people who don't go all the fucking time,
that like people don't know what the lands are.
They don't know what anything is.
I think just knowing your surroundings is impressive to people.
Because we're so insane.
I think we take it for granted that people know everything to do.
Because most people go once or twice a year and they just like go on.
And a lot of people don't even use Fast Pass.
They don't even know what it is.
They think they have to pay for it.
It's a whole thing.
Like it's like no one.
They don't get it.
Those are normal people though.
They're right.
Yeah.
They're right to not know all this stuff.
I was going to say, I think that I like I am not like I love Disney.
But and also there's the besides of Disney, of course, I don't like.
But I love Disney and I've been there.
I feel like more than the average person will go in their life, which is like 12 times maybe.
So you guys have been like like 100 times more than I've been.
And what's the Disney World counts for everybody?
I mean, I'm from the West Coast and I've still been like six times, I believe.
I'm at five or six.
I would need a piece of paper.
Yeah, you've been.
I went because we were in the vacation club for a while.
So there was a stretch there when I was in like middle school where we went every year
for like four or five years in a row when I was a kid.
Yeah, because we went away like three or four years.
I once spent two weeks straight in Walt Disney World.
You motherfucker.
Yeah, in an apartment, in like a one bedroom apartment.
What was going on?
Oh, just your family?
That was what we it was like the the the vacation club points.
Is that what your mom had?
Is she in the vacation club?
Is that what the points are?
She always just calls them Disney points.
So that could be what it is.
But she uses so many of those points on like you don't have to go to Disney.
Like you can go to like like Jamaica or Ireland or something.
Yeah, yeah, it's probably what it is.
And so you get you buy so many points a year.
And then like that that that amount of points gets you like a week at Disney
in a one bedroom like hotel suite or like depending on your level,
two weeks in what's called like a studio suite,
which is like a bigger hotel room that also has a partial kitchen.
That's at least how it was in the late 90s when we did it.
And so you could bank points like if you didn't go one year,
you could just save those points and apply them
to get like a one bedroom suite or a two bedroom suite.
Or you just go and you stay at the studio and you stay for two weeks,
which I can only imagine like at a certain point,
I know my parents enjoyed it like they were super into it too.
But there was a certain point in that two weeks where it's like,
is this our life now?
Like, do we have to go back to reality?
Can we just live here?
Sure.
I was I was saying that I think to you, Carlson, recently,
maybe maybe it was you.
I've said it to a bunch of people,
but I was like I always like I feel like a big regret in my life is like,
oh, I would have liked out of college or in college to go work at Disney
and falling in love with a with a with a Disney cast member.
I mean, like someone who just does the rides,
like I'm like, oh, that seems like it would have been the like a magical life,
a simple.
Yeah, that is funny.
You bring that up because we we Mitch and I went to the same college.
That's true.
We went to Ithaca, Ithaca College, two years apart.
And when I was there, I went to like an info session about the Disney College program.
Did you ever go to that?
I didn't go.
I would have gone.
Would have been a whole other life.
You literally missed the meeting.
I missed it.
It came to you.
I won like a trivia question.
Like, I don't know what I got.
I got like a prize at that and I talked to them and I was like,
this would be really cool to do.
But they have very specific.
Their semesters are different than a lot of college semesters.
So it's like they want you to take a whole college semester and then like a month
from either end.
Yeah.
So it was either like you're on Disney time.
You're on Disney time.
So it's like a month of your summer break and a month and a full school semester.
And so like it probably would have put me back graduating and like.
But Jason, I think you both agree that being in Disney would have been more fun than Ithaca.
I think that's true.
I mean, I had a nice time.
I think it was great, but I mean, like it's a cold ice block.
Oh, yeah.
And then Disney is we'd be we'd be marrying those those
these Disney cast members, like we're saying.
So you have like an ideal what your would it be like a woman from the
Norway World Showcase?
But it would be a woman from the Norwegian.
And I would be in Beast costume with very little makeup.
Just as a cost saver, they should have hired you.
I would have married someone.
The pretzel stand.
Sure.
Would be a family of pretzel people.
Or just or a mini.
And then you ask to like, don't ever take your head off.
That's the only way this will work.
I need to believe you're the real mini.
Truly magical.
Well, well, we should get into it.
The grand debate Disney World versus Ithaca.
You raised a few points already.
Ithaca is so far at a.
Ithaca still has their own currency.
They got rid of Disney dollars.
Ithaca hours, I believe, are still in circulation.
So the currency category.
What were they?
What they were?
There were bonus bucks.
I remember.
Yeah.
You could buy like a shitty like not subway, but like a subway type place.
And there was a terrible sandwich direction.
That's right.
Yeah.
So the campus had its own like bonus box system.
They had its own currency.
And then downtown Ithaca, like the local downtown shops had,
you could get like one dollar is one Ithaca hour and like their own little currency.
I guess the idea was you keep money directly in the community.
We're going to provide a graph later of all of the various points, bucks, hours, credits,
all the all the means of currency that we've discussed.
When it snows so hard and the wind is so rough,
it feels like it's snowing horizontally at you.
You kind of need to come up with distractions, right?
Yes.
And these hippies came up with Ithaca, or whatever the hell they are.
Off brand sandwiches.
Yum.
Disney World, Disney World versus Disneyland.
This is something we know that you're you're passionate about
and you have strong views about, or maybe that's the entire view is Disney World is better.
Disney World is better than Disneyland.
And I think both of you don't like that statement, but I don't know how Jason feels.
But we're cracking our fists.
And here we go.
What did you surprise you?
We have strong opinions on everything.
Get your notes out, folks.
Here's how I feel.
And a bunch of Quincy friends felt the same way.
Disneyland is great.
Don't get me wrong.
It's great.
It's the original.
I know that this is going to come up in your stupid arguments.
I'll cross it out.
It's the it's the original like in Magic Kingdom, like the castle is smaller and shittier.
Look, it's made back in the day.
It's smaller and not as good.
I get that.
It's still a slanted view of our view.
Here's the biggest part for me is that when you're when you are in Disney World,
you are transported to a different place that feels like nothing else in the world.
Like it doesn't feel like you're in a theme park.
It feels like you are in a weird, different world.
That's why it's Disney World.
And it is more of a the Westworld, the like full immersive experience.
It feels like it feels like a Westworld for sure.
Disneyland, you can't ever you can you can always feel that you're in in Anaheim.
Like it just it feels like you're it feels like you can look over a wall and and feel like see Anaheim.
And it just it just it doesn't it doesn't feel like like if you go to the top of the Tower of Terror now,
the Guardians, whatever the fuck it is, Guardians of the Galaxy mission break.
If you go to the top of Mission Breakout.
It rolls off the tongue, very natural.
Another thing that gets me mad about Disney, but we don't have to get into that stuff today.
Oh, we will.
We should.
Like I'm like, oh, you look at Anaheim.
You can see Anaheim.
A place where literally there are KKK rallies.
Not to throw all of Anaheim under the bus, but that does that is true.
Luckily, there's no white supremacists in Florida.
No ride could give you Disneyland.
It doesn't even matter what you are.
We're all friends in Disney.
Mitch, what it's surprising to learn, there's a term for this.
This is what's called the Disney bubble.
Oh, yes.
Like you go into it.
You don't want to leave the Disney bubble.
I love the Disney bubble and the Disney bubble is I don't know if there is a bubble with Disney.
I mean, there is a little bit with Disneyland, but not as much.
It definitely pops when you're at the top of the.
It definitely pops when you're at the top of the Guardians of the Galaxy.
For sure.
You can see like, yeah, the the Carl's on Harbor, the Mimi's, the Mimi's restaurant.
Captain Kidd's $11 buffet.
Captain Kidd's the restaurant that ripped off the Red Robin logo.
They just like ganked or something.
The exact design.
We're calling you out, Captain Kidd.
On guard.
Medieval Times is right there.
I did like there's something about it that just feels like a little like.
Like like if it feels like not cheaper, that's like not the right word for it,
but like I guess that's all I can think of.
It's a little chintzier and there's like I feel like a California adventure
just feels like a Six Flags or something.
It just feels like a cheaper.
It just feels like it like it like it feels that way.
And and and go ahead, Scott.
Scott does look like he has some anger in his eyes when you say that.
I sure made a face.
I don't think that face was.
I think you all read it is harsher than it was.
I think you were trying to hide it and you were doing a bad job of it.
Oh, yeah, maybe my my non-poker face was showing you.
I saw literally all these times that you've been drinking in the
Carthay Circle in California Adventure flash between your eyes before your eyes.
And you went, God damn it.
You're taking the place where I hold court and you're throwing it down the drain.
Hey, you're right.
People are supposed to get mad.
Maybe they should get mad.
No, the California Adventure, I think when it opened was was a much cheaper park
with a lot of problems and that's they really did scrimp on it.
I think in the intervening years, like since Cars Land and this great
Carthay Circle restaurant they put in and Mission Breakout, people seem to like a lot.
And I think it's I think it has caught up big time.
And there are days where actually my wife right now is literally at California Adventure
only, not going to Disneyland.
Oh, wow.
We will definitely do days where we only do California Adventure.
It's got some good I mean, it's got Soarin and I like Soarin a lot.
The new Soarin is great.
Oh, I haven't done the new Soarin.
I haven't done the new Soarin and I haven't done Guardians of the Galaxy.
And I haven't I haven't really seen Cars Land, so I'm in trouble.
I mean, yeah, it's terrific.
Well, you're I mean, then you're correct, I think in the original.
Yeah, it was it was a worse park for sure.
And it was yeah, it was definitely here's what we can do for this budget.
And it wasn't as amazing and immersive as Disneyland, but I think it's caught up.
I are you avoiding Cars Land because of how much your Doughboy's co-host Nick Weiger
is horned up for Cars Land is how much he loves it.
There's a little bit of that that Nick likes Cars Land too much.
Nick also loves the Minions.
So have you been on that ride?
I have not been on Minion Mayhem and I don't really want to go on.
Oh, it's fun.
I think it's terrific.
I hate this ride.
That's really the ultimate bad universal screen ride.
Just lame.
It is all the same tricks, though.
I don't hate it, but it's the same bullshit 3D trick they use on every single ride.
I mean, I just want to.
I think they're endearing.
I think the little girls are.
I'm not saying I hate Minions.
I'm just saying after you've been on every.
Little girls, huh?
I'm in.
Paul Scheer the other day was saying that he loves the Transformers ride there.
And I think the Transformers ride is fun.
It is good.
And it is like a good mix of like 3D and like kind of a dark ride a little bit.
But I guess, right?
Like it is a 3D dark ride.
Yeah, kind of.
It's exactly the same as the Spider-Man ride in Florida, which is a better ride.
I think it's.
Oh, yeah.
I did.
I died the last time when I went in college.
I did that that Spider-Man ride was like new and it was and it was great and awesome.
I loved it.
Still.
Yeah.
The face you all saw me make about California Adventure.
I remember Scheer on the doughboys saying his favorite ride was the Transformers ride.
And I think I made that face in the car to myself.
No offense to he is he is a great man and Transformers is a is a great ride.
But at the greatest of all time, I was like, oh, give me I wish I was in there.
I wish I was in the studio to argue this point.
I feel like I like the mummy ride more than I like even the than I like even the
Transformers ride just because it's like a dark ride that's like kind of like a thrill ride.
Like I'd rather it be like in more so, I guess Transformers is too.
But anytime I'm looking at like the three, if it's a 3D ride, I'm always just like it
doesn't feel it doesn't feel the same.
You know, too many of these, there are too many screen rides.
I think the fan outcry about screen rides is starting to get back to Disney and Universal
and they're starting to correct course.
I think people.
Yeah, I think people know that they you know, you need to give people big physical experiences,
which is why Star Wars I think is going to be really exciting.
And well, for sure, there will be screen rides in Star Wars and Nintendo.
The Nintendo stuff coming up, I think it's going to have a lot of which is funny because
it's a video game, but they're going to make it practical.
Yeah, they are going to do practical.
The Mario Kart ride is supposed to be very big and practical and crazy.
That's insane.
Like you're going to go around.
The Mario Kart ride is practical.
Because there's also rumors, I did not sidetrack, it's too much rumors that
that you'll be able to throw weapons at people.
But like some people are arguing they're trying to do it with like 3D augmented reality.
And then some people are saying, no, you're not going to need glasses for it.
They're like trying to figure out ways.
That's exciting.
I don't know how, but yeah, they're they're trying to.
There's people on the message boards who don't think it's doable the way it is.
They think it's impossible the plans they have and they'll never pull it off like the
way they're envisioning it.
These message board skeptics, they shut their mouths.
Why don't you believe in these people who've given you so much entertainment?
Back to the park thing.
I believe as we were going down to Disney two weeks ago,
we decided California Adventure, right now at least, better than Epcot,
better than Hollywood Studios.
Wow.
And at least on par with Animal Kingdom.
I think so.
Yeah, that's an argument I have.
A mark against Florida right now is some of the big parks in Disney World have very much
lost their way.
Like they're doing so much work on Hollywood Studios.
Like there's hardly anything open at that park.
There's barely anything.
They just closed the Great Movie Ride.
I was just down there last week.
I was there the last day of the Great Movie Ride.
That sounds crazy to me.
Which I did not go for.
Like we already had a trip and it happened to fall.
I'm not that insane where I'm like, I had to go.
We have to go on the last day.
I got to say goodbye to robot Burt.
Mary Poppins Burt.
I want to see the Ripley animatronic one more time.
That weird Ripley alien.
Creepy Ripley.
The beautiful ladies of Footlight Parade.
Maybe a Mappy.
They're taking this right out.
Do you think that the Footlight Parade animatronics will be on eBay?
I bet you could.
You guys could buy something from the Great Movie Ride, I feel like.
Yeah.
They gotta be selling that after Burt's.
Just a nose of a Footlight.
I'm buying individual body parts of the Footlight ladies.
The Great Movie Ride is what made me daydream about meeting a cast member.
And what if I was the mobster that took over the Great Movie Ride train car?
No kidding.
But you would fall in love with the woman who was doing a tour of the movie?
Yeah, why not?
So there would be a whole thing, like you guys were working together,
but then you became lovers as well?
In my life, fan fiction, yes.
That's what would happen.
So there's a lot of fake theatrical tension beneath it all.
You're falling in love.
Which is funny because I watched a Great Movie Ride, whatever.
What do they call those?
Like a ride through video?
Ride through video.
And that ride, when the mobster takes over the ride, it's like,
all right, now I'm in charge.
And then sits silently and drives you around.
Takes the turns, calmly, makes all the stops still.
I feel like that ride could have, if that ride was faster,
I guess it would just be that awkward minute of being like,
I'm taking over.
And then he's like, I'm set to go.
You know what I mean?
I'm set to go.
And then if the ride was fast or something,
then it really actually would have been a much better ride.
Well, the gangster is greedy, but he believes in driving safety.
He doesn't want to hurt himself any more than he wants to hurt anyone else.
Oh, sorry.
I sent you guys this lately.
I found a blog talking about the great movie ride,
like the week it was closing, a lot of people were posting tributes
or their experiences with it.
And I found someone write a blog about the early plans for the ride.
For one thing, the original tour guide script was 40 to 60 pages long.
They did all of the talking.
Nothing was prerecorded.
The other thing was that the shirts they wore had a little rip off chest pocket.
And so when the gangster shows up to take over the thing,
he was going to shoot the tour guide and they would rip off the fake pocket
and have like a gut shot or a chest shot.
It would be like a little graphic of blood essentially to make it look like they were bleeding.
A blood and a bullet hole so that the gangster shot them.
And that was never put into production.
That was like cut before it was.
But like, wouldn't that have been crazy?
I had a thing I always wanted to do as a universal tour guide,
where I wanted to like get a friend of mine to be a plant in one of the tram cars.
And when we went through the Jaws attraction to have him like stand up
and have just a stump arm that is spurting blood as if Jaws bit him.
Which I realize now would have been instant firing.
Instant fire.
Yeah, that's oh, and to lose that job.
How could I have dealt with that?
That is a cool job.
You did my dream, but in universal, so it doesn't count.
Yeah, there is zero magic in you.
I like the universal parks, but there's no magic in these places.
But you could fall in love with, you know, Shrekette or whatever.
Or the perfect girl, Shrekette.
The woman who plays Lucille Ball.
Or generic 40s New York lady hanging out the window.
Or depressed like PA that you see on the actual lot when you drive.
That's always the funniest thing to me is that like you go through that actual lot
and there's just like Hollywood people like.
Carrying a big heavy pole.
So, so I'm all out of sorts now.
Oh, I got you. I was about to come back with Epcot was one of my favorites.
And I love the troll Norway ride.
And even if those rides are bad, yeah, the Maelstrom.
Yeah, I love all those rides.
I'll give you a world showcase is still very good,
even though they've replaced that with Frozen.
That's a Frozen right now.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry to break it to you.
That being said, I won on the Frozen ride and it is great.
And I don't like a Frozen that much, but it is very good.
Well, that ride is like what I remember of Maelstrom.
There's like a couple like you go down like a couple times.
Right. Yeah, you go backwards down a little waterfall and then you go forward down a waterfall.
It's fun.
So this is the same track.
It's all the same stuff.
Yeah.
They juiced it up.
So world showcase is still good, but where Epcot fails now is that they let future world just like
be the most depressing monument to the 1980 like decaying monument, the Odyssey.
Literally like ghettos of Epcot.
There's places.
It's so sad. It's so god damn sad.
Abandoned pavilions and like, yeah, they they a park that is based on like an optimistic future,
you have to keep updating and they they kind of didn't like that.
That's one of the negative things of Florida is that people don't go there as often as like Anaheim.
If you live in Southern California, you can pop down to Disneyland for like a day,
pop over to Universal for a day.
But like Florida, people go to like a few times in their life.
So they don't like refresh it that often.
So they they also closed the energy Ellen's energy adventure.
Do you remember this ride?
And it's 45 minutes long.
We'll do a full episode on it eventually.
There's 45 minutes long.
It's got Bill Nye.
It's got Ellen and Alex Trebek, Jamie Lee Curtis as another Jeopardy contestant.
Correct me if I'm wrong.
Was that like a very big like when you sit in it?
Yes.
It's like a very it's like a ton of people, right?
It's a movie theater.
Okay. Yes.
Yep.
Okay. Yeah.
Even slower than the movie.
Right.
Yeah, I hadn't been on it in 20 years and it was closing and oh my this thing is the biggest piece of shit.
It is not well at all like like movie.
Great movie.
Right.
I'm bummed that they closed it.
I think they should just put better stuff in.
Yeah.
But Ellen's energy adventure.
Get it out of here.
It's the most dated.
It's so weird that it's 2017 and it's still like.
That's a perfect example of what happened to Epcot where it's just like we just let this fucking movie this shitty dated movie play in here for 20 years.
With literally with an Ellen that predates everyone's conception of Ellen.
You know we all know Ellen from the talk show and this is Ellen from the sitcom pre coming out Ellen.
Right.
Like it is another Ellen that we don't even recognize anymore.
It's very bizarre.
And Alex Trebek with the mustache too.
Yeah, that's true.
These icons before the biggest change in their lives.
Michael Richards without a speaking role.
Wow.
Yeah like he's a caveman.
He doesn't say anything he's just a brief shot of he's like a caveman.
Also before his defining event.
I was gonna say you should never have said another thing.
Ellen Cleghorn with a line on this as well.
Damn.
So this is old this is an old thing and it's gone now.
It's going to be replaced by a Guardians of the Galaxy ride.
I'm not joking but it needs to be replaced.
Need it to be replaced.
People's the tributes I saw to that people seemed to like the design of the building.
Some tile art when you walked in and the scene where you go through like the old dinosaurs.
Like that's what people want it.
Maybe they'll keep the dinosaurs around somehow in the Guardians.
I think that there's a rumor they will but there's a there's a chance in five to ten years.
All these parks are going to be amazing again.
I think they're going to get them.
But right now.
I want to hear all the IP opinions.
It just doesn't it just doesn't fit in Epcot.
Like that's right.
Guardians of the Galaxy shouldn't be in Epcot center.
It's it's it's.
You're making the Disney fan argument actually a lot of people feel this way.
I don't because I don't care about Marvel or Guardians of the Galaxy or any of it.
But I'm pro anything that gets new attractions built.
I mean I like rides as much as anyone but like when I went my senior year of college
I was your sophomore year of college at Ithaca.
Just for everyone who's tracking the tracking.
I think how many points did you both have.
Well I was almost out of points.
I was almost out of there.
Yeah I went through those points pretty quickly.
We didn't really know each other that well in college.
No I feel like I had met you though a couple of times.
Once or twice.
You know I think I has the comedy scene has gotten much much better.
Yeah.
They have like improv and sketch and stuff which they did not really have when we were there.
I think there was like maybe there was one club that I when I graduated I was the president.
Yes that's which I which I which I knew you were I knew you were the president.
But even that club I remember I went to a meeting like I went to the one of those that
club one time when I was there like my freshman.
So this before you got there.
Yeah.
And I was like this is like like this is bad.
Like it was bad news at that point.
You probably turned it all around I'm sure.
I mean a little.
But also like a second club opened up like like more groups started coming.
What was this club?
I was it was like the Ithaca comedy club.
And we would put on sketch shows or like do do stand up shows and a little bit of short
form improv.
No one really did any long form long form.
There's so many college long form improv groups which always makes me laugh because it's like
well who is teaching the senior in the club is teaching the freshmen how to do long form.
Of course now they now if I'm not mistaken they have a course that actually lets you
at the end become a birthday boy.
There's 700 birthday boys now.
You add anyone with a who gets a minus or higher.
There are regional chapters of the birthday boys.
I should license.
I have a depressing thing to say about that and once I was going to say at the with the
comedy club wasn't it like in like that like when I first went to it was like in like a
little like dining area like like a cafe.
Yeah which they also cleaned up like mice after you left.
They really cleaned up a cafe.
That's a lot of Ithaca.
You cleaned everything up after I left.
You know what else happened after you left the tuition just kept going up and I'm sure
that was happening while you were there.
I was happening when I was there for sure and then like I went back like years later
I'm like it's much nicer like this I'm mad like you made it so much nicer than when I
was there which I guess is maybe an epic can relate to Epcot in some ways.
Yeah.
Thanks for tying that back.
Thank you.
Yeah refurbishment of the Ithaca.
My one story is that the birthday boys went to Ithaca and there was like like probably
like 40 to 50 people in the auditorium.
Right.
And they were I was talking to like my old professor who one didn't recognize me
and that she was talking about she was like yeah like a few months back funnier die had
come here and it was a Dave Franco and McLovin and like the lines were out the doors and
they chased them to their cars.
I was like fuck this fucking place.
Anyways I.
Yeah that's that you know that that's like IP being put somewhere it doesn't belong.
It's like an Epcot.
It's like an Epcot center.
When I was when I was when I was a senior college I we went to Epcot and I what is the
is it like the ride in the big ball.
Spaceship Earth.
So we presented by Siemens.
We I was like I want to do Spaceship Earth and we did it and I was with my my godmother
basically and she and she was like at and her son and like at the end of the ride they
both were like that like sucked.
Why did you take us in that.
But I liked I liked I like it also it did it did like it stalled and we were like on
it for like 15 extra minutes.
Oh sure.
And then we did the figment ride where he sings imagination or whatever and they were
also mad about that.
But I liked those like that in my mind is the is the type of thing you're supposed to see
at Epcot like I want like I feel like the world is strange now and that they were like
we can't even like imagine what the future will be like anymore.
So instead we'll put we'll give you Star Lord and like in my mind I'm like at least then
like the 80s they were like they were like like like they would be like Harumba or something
you know what I mean like like their idea of what the real conception some some ideas
at least and I'm just like sure like Star Lord and his in Groot that's not like what
the fuck is that.
Yeah well they're promising that these rides will not only have IP but will be you know
have the spirit of the spirit in them.
We'll see if it happens inventiveness and you would hate how they tied it in.
What is this thing.
Oh well Peter Quill had been to Epcot as a child.
Here's the thing.
Such garbage.
But here's the thing here's the thing which makes me maybe not hate it is there's rumors
that that ride then will be a best of Epcot ride.
Well I'm on board for that.
You will get like you will still get the dinosaur portion of the ride you will get like reference
Horizon references like this could be like just like cramming the characters in just
for like the kids for the kids to be like I want to go on the Guardians ride but it's
like full of old Epcot shit.
The second.
And it'll be a monument to Epcot.
The second Guardians movies come out and it is bad.
And like do we really care about like the the first Guardians movie.
I can't even remember what happened in that movie.
These are big hit movies.
People want to see that.
My mom likes Groot.
Yeah.
My mom.
That's the that's the that's the thing whether the movie like the like if a mom likes Groot
there it's going in the park.
But the way they're putting in a Friends from College ride.
High demand for the Netflix series.
I do agree with what you're saying Mitch that it is weird.
It's a little weird to see characters in there and it's crazy how like yeah when this park
opened it was so optimistic and like you know looking at a bleeding edge future and I do
think it's crazy that they haven't like just given one of the pavilions of like this is
the personal computing pavilion and Apple do what you want with it.
Like just Apple make a rock make us a thing.
Where do you want to go honey.
I want to go to the personal computing pavilion.
Personal computing.
Because that is something that's like.
I agree.
We need a better name.
We need a better name is all I'm saying.
I that's like the nerdy way.
I agree with what you're saying though.
I do I would prefer it was all new rides with new characters a different care like
figment was made up for the parks.
Figment is better than Star Lord in as far as characters go.
I like figment.
I mean I do like figment.
You'll get no argument here.
They need a new figment right.
Like whatever one that's stuck in the 90.
I am also with Scott in the sense that like whatever gets that place that does
like it's a graveyard right now.
If it'll be better.
We'll do it.
But how many how many how many Guardians of the Galaxy rides are going into Epcot.
Just one.
Yeah.
And it's replacing this Ellen ride that is a correct.
Which is but then also like God frozen is in there too.
But they're building.
No wars is coming new stars.
But what so what is what is is is it still Norway over there is that.
Yeah it's still it's all still but it's like.
Wait so frozen takes place in Norway.
I guess.
In theory.
Yeah.
Yeah that's a shady one.
There's a lot more.
They're fudging some stuff.
They're like Ratatouille ride is going to be in the France Pavilion.
It's all I.
You know what I'm fine.
That's OK.
That makes sense.
Ratatouille ride in France makes perfect sense.
Yeah but it's a screen ride.
It's a it's a it's a.
Transformers.
They said they may make it better.
Yeah.
Hopefully hopefully.
I went on it's not great.
All right.
In Paris.
Let's talk about a different topic.
Can I just quickly say how how dated the Simpsons ride already feels.
Yes I agree.
And it hasn't even been a decade since it's opened.
So the projection is bad.
It's like dark in there.
They didn't they didn't update it from the system from the Back to the Future system
which is 30 years or 25 years old.
So it's yeah it's it's hard to see.
Yes it's it's it's all the same tricks that they use in the Minions ride.
The Minions ride is maybe better than the Simpsons ride.
I feel like it's just going to be just like characters are better.
Better projector better screen I think.
It's just all going to feel dated soon.
But before you move on to the next subject why is Disney.
I keep bumping this.
Why is Disneyland better than Disney World.
Oh well that's what I say topic I didn't mean.
Okay.
We're doing just another like like so you're talking about how you know it's a world versus
it's a small place.
Yeah.
Because I was just there.
So when I went back four years ago I hadn't been in a decade.
Okay.
And my memory is similar to yours where it was like a magical place where around every bend
is could be what is this it's trees and then all of a sudden oh my god it's a whole theme park.
But when you go back as an adult you're like this is a big fucking swamp.
It's just a big swamp.
Yeah.
And most of the time you spend there is in swamp transit going from one hotel to one.
You're in a cold bus.
Now I do like how much space it is.
It's cool.
But so much of it is like you're waiting in line for a bus and you take a bus through some
swamp land to the theme park and it's like this isn't I don't know it is like you're like on the
bus and you're like that's nice when you get to park in that Mickey and Friends parking in Anaheim
and you go on one tram and there you are.
Yeah.
Both parks are right there.
But I will say to be fair there's a lot of boat rides that are very magical in Florida.
So you can take boats from like Epcot to Hollywood Studios you can take boat we took a boat from
Disney Springs to our hotel.
Lovely.
So that does have that and Monorail is great.
The Monorail.
Is great.
So I'm saying good and bad in Florida as far as like it being this giant spread out world.
Anaheim benefits from the fact that like everything is right there you can walk everywhere.
You can walk to the hotels you can walk between two parks you can walk to downtown Disney.
Small though.
That makes it small.
It's small.
But to the point that when Universal built out their Florida their Orlando parks like they
took that design like the two parks are next to each other the hotels and the city walk
are spread out you can still walk to everything and there's a boat system if it's just a little
too far to walk.
That's true all the other and all the other Disney parks Tokyo and Paris like the parks
are right next to each other.
Yeah.
They haven't done these other giant sprawling.
They don't have a state size piece of property.
I mean this will never happen again in the world that a company buys that much.
I was looking up the acreage Disneyland is about 50 which that seems too small but something
like 50 and Disney World is 144,000 acres which you'll never see that again one company
slowly buying up that amount of acreage.
That's so insane.
Wait so hold on besides that what else?
What does Disneyland got?
Let's hear it.
It's entirely about acreage.
I mean I should get yeah what's what's an argument I have.
You're right the castle's better.
Oh god.
Well I think this doesn't make it better necessarily but you're right about as you said yeah it's
the original.
They were able to update they were able to like address the problems that Disney World
had with Disney.
They didn't want it to get immediately surrounded by seedy shit and for there to be hotels
immediately on the border which is why there is so much space on the outside.
Or you know why Disney World is so massive.
But you know it's not their fault that you know they didn't want all that shit right
on the outside and I think Disney World benefits from coming at being able to address the mistakes
of Disneyland which I guess is an argument for Disney World being better.
But come on count them a break.
Because you're original.
Walt likes Disney World right like.
Well Walt originally bought that property to build a giant experimental city.
He was more interested in Epcot in Florida than he was in the Magic Kingdom.
He was more interested in like a futuristic cutting edge city with yeah a Disneyland park
next to it.
Which is the coolest thing of all.
Is that he wanted to make some weird.
I love that.
Yeah.
Central city.
But that was the first thing when he died they're like well we're not building that
giant experimental city anymore.
This giant experimental non-Jewish city.
Oh god.
I'm just like we'll just take a drop of your blood and before you come in we'll run a quick
scan on it.
No it's just to see what diseases you have.
It's not about genetic making.
No I think well also here's a big argument.
I Disneyland is better than the Magic Kingdom.
Yes I think you compare those two parts.
Okay.
Those are the same format of park and I think Disneyland is better.
It's better laid out.
It's like a better laid out park.
It's more with news with you don't have New Orleans Square and Critter Country and Toontown.
And then I guess they briefly had a Toontown.
But they had a minor Toontown.
Minor Toontown Fair.
There's more like distinct the lands are better more distinct like everything kind of bleeds
more in Florida.
Like all of a sudden the Speedway is right there but you're in Fantasyland and it's I
don't know you can just see it.
In Disneyland everything is kind of smaller so it makes it feel like you're going into
these little different areas like of the frontier or you know.
You're buying that right.
Right.
Oh no different little areas.
Well I guess I guess that that is fair that that Magic Kingdom doesn't have as many good
rides as Disneyland has in it right.
Like there's there's.
I don't think so and I think I think there's I think Space Mountain is pretty and arguably
better in Disneyland.
Space Mountain is better here.
Yes.
It's gotten a refresh more recently.
The Florida one is very rickety and it kind of hurts.
I think we got a better I would say we have a better pirates because we have the restaurant
we have the Blue Bayou which looks out which is superior.
Yeah.
Anaheim benefits from the Southern California weather too.
Like it doesn't rain as much like the first time I came to Disneyland I was like did they
just paint everything like everything looks so vivid and that summer I had just been in
Florida and it was one of those periods of time where they they kind of let the Florida
parks go to hell a little like there was a bunch of stuff that was broken and like the
paint was super faded because it rains there all the time.
Yeah and it's humid.
Yeah the humidity and people are coming from around the world for like long expensive
vacations so like they can't shut stuff down for as long as they can like out here.
By the way I went on the big red boat like like one of the first cruise.
Oh the cruise.
The cruise.
That is another way I got to Disney I forgot we did the big red boat.
You took it down there and docked wherever.
We took it down to Disney.
It was like we went down to Disney and I gotta say this the big red boat sucked.
It was early on and I've told this story before but I was in a jacuzzi I was like I don't know
so this must have been like when I was like in fourth or fifth grade and I was in a jacuzzi
and a log of shit floated up.
Were you alone in the jacuzzi?
There were other people there were other people there it was not my log of shit.
No no I said I don't even know what I was asking I was just saying like was it just like stuck
somewhere and then it floated up or somebody's shit while you were in there with them.
There were a couple people in there but I don't know if it was like one of them I had no idea
but also like I remember like the pools being like salty or something like or like like it was
very it was very it was very strange it was it was it was it was bad it was early on and bad and like
my godfather was like puking the entire time like I feel like cruise ships in the last like
even 20 years have gotten so so much better.
I think Disney took a much more hands-on role with them now.
Yeah because they were they just like sort of licensed that big red boat but it was pre them
actually building the boats themselves.
Okay that makes sense.
That being said I don't really want to go on these Disney but you guys have you done it?
I've never done it.
Does anybody want to do a Disney boat?
I think I cruised to Bermuda once on like Norwegian cruise line.
But you didn't do it at Disney.
Never a Disney one.
Okay I think you guys now have to do it now that we're doing this podcast.
Yeah that's true yeah well and it's all it's all write-offs baby that's what we're doing
that's the entire methodology here.
Unlike the Doughboys we can 100% be bought like Disney Universe will send us.
That's what it's all about.
We're looking.
We started this thing so we can get a free trip to Dollywood.
We want to go to Dollywood we want to cover yeah cover a new ride a new Christian themed ride.
I've been to Dollywood before.
Really?
I have yes yeah.
Good.
I dated someone who lived in Tennessee and we went to and I wow and we went to Dollywood.
And what do you think?
Dollywood is fun.
I bet it looks good.
It's like a big frontier land.
That's a great review.
There's like Dolly's like cabin that she grew up in and you see like how small it's funny how
much people like they love Dolly so much and it is like a funny weird thing where like
there there are like some like exciting like like kind of like thrill rides or whatever but like
it it feels it is like kind of closer cheaper to like it feels like Six Flags or something but like
specifically Dolly themed or whatever.
Yeah well I think every other if you're not operating from the Disney price point it's
always every other theme park is going to be a little like step down in terms of production
value and that doesn't mean they can't be charming and fun and I bet Dollywood's a real
charming.
It's a lot of fun.
It is.
Yeah.
Well look forward to going there for free.
Maybe good in between points for us and Scaramucci to meet.
Oh yeah.
He's an Easter and see you there.
We'll see you at the Margaritaville Hotel in Pigeon Forge, Tennessee.
What else?
Another knock against Florida is that it smells worse.
And I'm sorry but it does like a mix of humans or some humans the plastic.
It's a little there's a little nostalgia but also like it's just there's overwhelmingly weird smells
and all the rides.
We're constantly being blasted with air conditioning.
The air conditioning is crazy.
One I love that.
I do too.
And I love that smell because it's like a weird theme park smell.
Jack Allison used to say that my car smells like the E.T. ride.
Oh.
And I take pride in that because I mean like I love the weird like basement smelling.
I do like that smell too and I like the one the Anaheim smells are a little bit less strong
than the ones in Florida.
The Carousel of Progress smells so weird I don't know why.
That's great.
Take its name out of your mouth.
These are all great things.
To experience smells that are not readily available every day.
But because of the weather it smells like a comic convention everywhere because of the people not
putting on.
That doesn't turn you off though.
That's a good point.
I am fine with that.
So you're right you've destroyed that argument for me.
That Florida heat though that can get to you like that can drive people crazy if you're not taking
breaks and staying really hydrated.
Now my family we've gone so much we used to go in August because it's cheaper and we don't notice
like we don't know it's like yeah it's hot.
It's it was 90 degrees every day we were there for seven days.
Yeah.
And you there were like you go into the gift shop and there was I remember there's a mother
head in hands just like leaning up against the wall sitting down with no family around
and like it seemed like someone should go help her.
I don't know like like it's a real there's a madness that can set in.
Yes I think you're more likely to have a full mental breakdown in Disney World than Disneyland.
Probably.
Families who have made that Odyssey just just break.
That's it.
You see it happen.
I like humidity more than dry heat like sometimes at Disneyland and Anaheim like the sun is just so
blindingly strong.
Jason I agree with you.
I'm with you.
I like to sweat it out.
I like the humidity.
I like the humidity too.
Give me a little humidity.
Get some moistness going.
It's good.
When I first came to Southern California I thought like oh it's hot it'll be like Florida and I'm
just like why is everything so dry.
Why? Jason you and I are on the same page.
I have the same.
When I brought this up on Doughboys I remember at a comedy show you said that you thought it
would be Pelican weather out here which is what I did.
I thought it would be like that too but it's not.
It's not Pelican weather at all.
Pelican weather at all.
I don't even know this term.
I'm from here.
I've never heard it.
It's like scorpion weather.
The driest.
It's so dry and so like and like it is like the just the sort of sun that will like
will just like kill you like it like I'm like oh I would die like if it was a like 200 300
years ago or something before this is developed before California was really developed if I was
just here I'd die in a day or something like that.
And the same thing with Florida or anywhere.
Well where everyone's going to die everywhere and these conditions will both both
both scorpion and Pelican weather will get so much worse in the next.
But in Florida it starts raining.
You get the rain.
It's nice.
I like the rain.
I do like the rain.
Crowd control and we went on an expedition Everest in the rain.
Great.
We got pelted in the face with rain.
It felt it hurt a little bit but that was part of it.
That's awesome.
It was awesome.
I've been in terrifying Disney World rain though like just.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It was that level.
It was that level of bad.
My dad and I had to run three blocks and pouring rain in a lightning storm like through the
90s downtown Disney because the bus station was at like the far end and we're just like
running from like overhang to overhang as we're watching like lightning strikes in the
distance and it's like we just need to get on that bus.
And it's because I made him stay at the Adventures Club theater and restaurants until last call
because I put it to see every show.
That's a parent breaking story.
Parents break.
Oh yeah I would break I would drive my father crazy like I would I would that's one of the
things I did love about Florida that is so crazy looking back on is I be like oh we have
like 20 minutes until this fast pass goes on and I'm like well we can go on Pirates of
the Caribbean and he would just be like Jace that's on the other side of the park that's
half a mile away.
We have 20 minutes.
I'm like well if we run he's like I'm not going to run I'm on vacation.
It's 80 degrees.
Adults don't sprint for fun.
Hey I don't know what else haven't we hit.
I'll say a couple pro Florida things.
Obviously I love Florida too.
Yeah well the ultimate answer is I always would rather be at either of these than anywhere
else in the world.
That's true I agree with that.
It is better than reality world.
Real life.
This is horrible.
Yes.
Yeah so Florida the Tomorrowland in Florida is slightly better than the one out here and
I'll say this there are more robots in that Tomorrowland.
There are robots everywhere.
There's that what's the what's the guy.
The trash can.
There's a trash can.
There's a guy.
There's a guy who wanders around now right.
What's his name?
Robot.
He's new.
There's a man who's pretending to be a robot and he like wheels around on wheels and he
takes pictures of the people and he's a totally made up character which I like.
An original.
An original character.
They'll turn it into a movie.
I should look up his new.
As soon as anyone remembers his name it'll become a movie.
I love Tomorrowland in Florida like that as a kid when that they first redid Tomorrowland
in Florida to be like the future that we that never was like I loved it and I would just
ride the people mover over and over again and I love carousel of progress to this day
like that Robin Williams ride the timekeeper.
Timekeeper ride that was really fun.
You ever go on that.
I probably have have rode all these rides and I've ridden all what is the right word
road or ridden.
Ridden road.
I rode in.
I rode I rode I've rode in all these rides.
You've done roadening on the ride.
I've done I've done road in all these rides and I don't and I and I can't remember a lot
of them but I was just remembering that there's a brown Derby in Disney World.
Yeah.
And it's it has the which has I mean the original brown Derby is in Los Feliz.
It's a Chase Bank.
Basically it's mess hall.
Yeah it's it's mess hall and Chase Bank.
And that's where the first Cobb salad was.
So you get that in Disney and it's a great Cobb salad down there.
That is good.
I like that.
And then also I just I was just remembering like good food stuff when I was younger.
We went to some German place and then there was like a live show and they brought my dad
out of the audience and they put like Liederhosen on him and he had like conducted like the
orchestra MGM studios.
Maybe.
Yeah.
No no no no.
German beer hall.
Oh right right right.
Yeah the German beer beer hall.
Yeah.
Better food better clothes.
Sure.
Custom Liederhosen for your guests.
I found the I found the robot his name is I can.
And here's a photo of him.
That's cool.
I like I can take.
Yeah.
Yeah he takes photos with people so a lot more.
Yeah so we were talking about food.
I will say this Florida has a better downtown Disney.
Yeah.
Okay Disney Springs is what they call downtown Disney now.
And they've recently renovated it.
There's a new plant in Hollywood which I heard the food is horrible but I didn't eat there.
I ate at a place called the Boathouse which is right on the water.
Oh yeah.
You can drive like you have a man in a captain's uniform drive you in a corvette into the water.
One of those aqua cars.
It's an aqua car.
Oh you did that thing.
I didn't do it but we should have.
It was raining real bad.
Great.
Well.
Fantastic.
There's a place that I didn't go called Paddlefish which is a giant.
It's like looks like it's on the Mark Twain riverboat but it's just docked.
It's great I mean Disney Springs is great.
Doesn't Disney World also have Pleasure Island.
That's gone.
That's where.
Yeah.
This old replace it.
Okay.
Yeah they just that they have updated like every 10 years they sort of do a refresh and
put in new restaurants and like more like there's an Edison going down there.
The LA bar.
And Edison is going into Disney Springs in Florida.
So is Disney Springs basically like it is it is pleasure whatever.
Pleasure Island.
Yeah yeah yeah.
It's Pleasure Island.
Basically they took out all the old mannequins and tracks and all the Z named.
I never got to experience Pleasure Island.
I wonder how it was back in the day like.
I would.
I know.
Pleasure Island as an adult.
I went all the time.
Yeah we didn't go.
I went as a kid like it was a little weird as a kid to be walking around outside of like
what were essentially nightclubs.
Did you and another kid put on a trench coat and get on each other's shoulders.
No.
There was a few like that's where I first saw live comedy.
I think there was a place called the Comedy Warehouse.
Just people doing like short form games and I feel like some real professional comedian
like I think Paula Pell like that was the first place she did live comedy.
I think she sat like she would like sit on men's laps and be bawdy when she was like
18 and 19 and 20.
Like that was her job.
Disney World once had Paula Pell.
There's a real this check in this horny side of Disney World is funny to me.
I didn't I didn't get I didn't see it.
So that's where it got body and pleasure.
Went down at Pleasure Island.
I had a friend who worked at Epcot when she was like 18 and it was just like it sounds
like it was just a fuck around like a free for all.
Yeah.
So you take your Norway babe when she gets off work till we're old body Pleasure Island
and you start getting some ideas in her head.
That's where I was saying me and my dad were when a lightning storm was bringing out was
the Adventurers Club which was like a term middle century like explorers club and there
were different you'd go in the study and there was a show and you'd go in the library and
there was a show and there was all these bars and there was characters walking around and
animatronics on the wall that would talk to you.
And that was like my favorite thing in the world for years.
It's what my phone case is like I have a phone case for a long gone Disney attraction.
And here's a strike against Florida.
Not a lot of couples without kids in their 30s.
Way more in way more in Disneyland and in Florida because my girlfriend and I are there
and it's weird because in Florida they would constantly be like parties of two parties of
like looking for people in line that were just two people because that is a very rare thing.
Yeah my dad and I would get that all the time.
Yeah out here it's all parties of two it's all people in their 30s with no kids.
That's so funny.
It is it's a whole different there's everyone's got kids everyone is there.
Probably like six to seven kids.
A lot of kids it's like a mandatory vacation and then there's these just two like kids we saw we
met these English kids in line with their parents.
Oh fun.
And they're like this has happened to me a couple times out here too where you can see the kids
looking at us and trying to figure out how old we are because like we're not dressed like mom and dad
but you're older like the man has hair that's white like his side of his hair is white.
And yet a t-shirt with Mickey and sunglasses and a surfboard.
Mickey he's dressed like I am.
Now I don't want to go to Disney World.
Maybe Disneyland is better for this embarrassment factor that.
It's a better place Disneyland's better to go alone as we will sometimes.
Yeah yes so if you're an adult person without kids Disneyland is by far the better option.
And Mike you were you were looking for couples in Florida because you guys were looking to swing.
Yeah we were looking we were trying but it didn't everyone had kids and it was too much of a hassle
to put them away.
You're thinking people are in Florida they're loose they want to have a good time.
Where do you think you're making.
That we went from like like Disney like like oh Pleasure Island is crazy it's you right over to
like it's all family both sides of it.
If you were looking for people to swing with that Disney World where do you think you go.
Is it the planet Hollywood is it is it is it one of the World Showcase pavilions
or people getting loose on that sake in Japan.
I think it's a World Showcase because the World Showcase is a party the World Showcase is by far
the one thing I would trade a ton of stuff here for that.
The World Showcase is so big and awesome and there's there is like kind of a Vegas
vibe where every everyone's like specialty cocktails just some big slushy drink with
like a little vodka in it.
They try to act like it's like oh heart of Japan drink and it's like this is just a green
green margarita there's a red margarita in China.
Which Disney couple you think would be most likely to swing with you.
You mean the characters.
Yeah characters.
That's good that's a good question.
I mean maybe one of these princess couples because they don't seem like they you know like
Snow White and the prince and Cinderella and the prince I feel like I've barely met
and maybe that marriage starts and they get bored right away.
Yeah Timon and Pumbaa.
I think they're gay right.
Yeah I think so I think they are implied.
I don't know how they have sex there's no way for them to have sex with Timon getting lost
in one of his orifices.
Maybe that's a part of it.
Maybe he spends a day up in up in Pumbaa somewhere.
I have a thing in Florida's favor.
Your money goes a lot farther in Florida than in California like in general but especially
at the Disney parks I feel like.
Damn.
I think I think that there's a I mean the hotels in Disneyland like the Disneyland hotel
in the Grand Californian are very nice but they're very expensive because there's not
that many rooms so they kind of have to price it.
And they're so close that the value is so good in terms of like you can just crash right
in one of those hotels.
Yeah so I mean it's great to stay at them but like you can get a much nicer room in
Florida I feel like for much less there's a couple dozen hotels on the Florida property.
And in a hotel it says like sports on the outside or something.
Yeah.
There's a big basketball next to it.
You can get any price of hotel I guess on like in Disney World like on property from
the all stars and then like you Mike you stayed at.
Port Orleans Riverside.
Yeah.
And they I mean it's like a cheaper it's a mid range hotel.
It's a mid range but it's still pretty good.
Still pretty good.
And they turn a blind eye on swinging.
Don't look the other way.
They encourage it.
Can I also say that another plus for Florida is as a big guy in Florida much a bunch of
more fat people I feel I feel.
You blend in.
I know I feel I feel almost I feel almost a little small.
It's good.
California you got all these fit people and you know how it is.
I remember like the last time I was there I see like the sheer size of people on the
like the scooters and the wheelchair.
It's a lot of rascals in Florida.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Sizes you don't see every day in LA necessarily.
So it's a self-esteem builder.
That's nice.
Jason I like the idea of there's a lot of rascals not meaning like actual rascals.
There's a lot of rascals.
There's a lot of kids.
Yeah there's a lot of little rapscalli.
They're off the leash.
They're off the leash in Florida.
Disneyland.
Disney that's their world not ours.
That's their world.
Well are we getting to I don't think we have any structure about it end to this.
I don't know what do you think.
Do we change your mind.
I mean before before before I mean I guess the answer is I will never change my opinion
about Disney World being not as good as Disney.
I think I think Disney World is still better but you know what I agree with you.
I'd rather be at both places than anywhere else.
I think what we've learned yes is Disney Disney World and Disneyland tie in the battle against
reality which the cold reality that we will have to face as soon as we leave this studio.
Yeah we could go straight to my wife is there.
My wife's mother is there.
Is my past good.
I think my blackout dates are over at this point.
Right they better be.
If not you have to upgrade.
You guys go to Disney after this.
I will think you are all losers.
Officially only if that otherwise we're the coolest toughest dudes.
I was going to ask you guys but but before we signed off what your favorite
food was from Disney or restaurant because I because I went out I went I went on the
line for pizza which I don't even know if there is a pizza port in in in Disney World.
I don't believe so.
No but but I but I like I like how like kind of old and dumb pizza port is.
Yeah.
But what's your and I of course I love I love churros and I love what you call it
uh Dole Whips but what what what are your guys favorite food slash restaurant at Disney.
So if you can only get.
Carthay Circle for two different there's two Carthy Circle is the restaurant and bar in
California Adventure.
They have a very nice like expensive meal you can get for lunch or dinner.
They also though which is maybe my favorite place they have a lounge.
It's a lounge which with a nice bar and they make you a nice like Manhattan the
Carthy Manhattan with that circular ice.
You get like a little chicken sandwich you get a cocktail you get two hours in the middle
of the day it's a nice little cool loss sort of like mahogany.
It's a nice atmosphere study lounge kind of where is it again.
It's in California Adventure.
Okay you haven't been to this place right.
If you ever turn it around I swear that every time I bring anyone here everyone's like this
is the greatest this is the place.
Yeah yeah it's like everyone's favorite place in California Adventure.
All right gotta go.
It's great we're going after this.
Come on down.
Yeah you know 110 dollars to get in then a meal that's 100 dollars.
A 15 dollar cocktail.
If you want to park up though it's an extra 40.
Parking as well.
You can pay us for gas too that'd be nice thanks Mitch.
Overall even though there's a lot less choices in Disneyland I think Disneyland
usually has the more consistent food.
Florida has a lot of pizza and burgers and amazing amazing fine dining but like in terms of like
just kind of counter service food like California wins very easily.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
You gotta shout out those Mickey bars love that in either part.
Oh yeah.
Sure.
Mickey bars are great.
Yeah.
I like the Dreyer's ice cream just standard like a double scoop in a sprinkle cone.
That you can buy at the store.
You sort of got whispery with it which I think was the uh.
Hey we would love we would love to treat you guys to a double scoop.
It's like you want to come back to Port Orleans with us.
An ASMR section of the podcast where I just describe the food that I have.
I love it.
I have ASMR.
I get that.
Do you do it?
It's too much for me.
I can't my girlfriend likes it.
I don't I don't listen to like the podcast but anytime I have the ASMR feeling I'm like
ah that feels nice it's a very nice feeling for those I feel bad for those who don't get it.
It's nice.
Is there an there's not an ASMR podcast on Feral is there?
If so.
There will be soon.
Have us on to whisper about respectively theme parks and chain restaurants.
There used to be a really good fried green tomato sandwich at the hungry bear restaurant
in frontier and credit country.
Please don't watch videos on your phone in line for rides without headphones.
I'd like to enjoy the full themed experience.
I agree with that too.
They never should have taken Rex out.
There's a roast beef sandwich at Flo's in Cars Land that's just terrific.
I've had that.
That is good.
Yeah that's good.
That's probably up there.
Cars Land is good food too.
Cars Land is good food.
There's a nice cocktail in Cars Land you can get.
There's a place in the cove bar which has lobster nachos in California Adventure.
Very good.
Lobster nachos are great.
Great view.
But I always feel like Disney food is pretty good actually.
It's certainly gotten better over the last 10, 15.
That's something Universal Studios garbage in terms of food, the entire operation, either park.
Except for the fried chicken.
I used to like Doc Brown's fried chicken which is now...
I did too.
Yeah.
Well they use that the same recipe at Cletus's.
Yes.
They have the recipe.
Hey now that we could do.
That's closer.
Hey Cletus's.
Cletus's chicken.
It's on me Chad.
Sure.
Except I don't think any of us have Universal Picks.
I do.
I have one yeah.
That is a thing you could do on Doughboys is the Simpson's Fast Food Boulevard because
it is... there are multiple locations.
There's one in Florida and one in California.
So technically a franchise.
Jason sadly we've already... we have plans to do...
We've talked about this sadly we're gonna do...
That's a great idea.
We're gonna do Simpson's World.
It's pretty good.
Simpson's World.
Oh hey.
Yeah.
Hooray.
Okay.
So look forward to that.
Check the Doughboys out.
I'll give my final thoughts real quick.
It's quantity versus quality.
Disneyland more consistently delivers in every aspect.
Disney World there is so much you're gonna find so much good stuff.
It's just that it's not all...
It's a little bit more hit and miss when you're going to the parks or the restaurants.
That's my... that's the ultimate.
But I like that it makes room for weird off-brand rides.
Like you feel a pressure in Disneyland that the rides have to be kind of really clean
and perfect.
And I like that there was Ellen's Energy Adventure even though it's getting out of there.
I like weird stuff like the Maelstrom or the Mexico boat ride.
I like that you end up with these odd fringe rides that you'd never see at Disneyland
because there's so much space to just do whatever.
There should be more of it honestly.
Thank you Scott.
Well as I said I don't hate Disney World.
I like...
Yeah we love both of them.
Yeah yeah yeah.
It's a very arbitrary podcast topic to be honest.
I like that and I'll say I'll whisper it for ASMR.
Oh boy.
The Disney bubble.
Wait.
There we go.
I didn't really whisper.
Let's all just stay in the bubble guys.
That's what I'll say for my wrap-up is I agree with Mike about the quantity and quality.
But for Florida once you get onto that property, oh man a week in that Disney bubble,
five days in that Disney bubble, forget about the real world.
It's terrific.
Agreed.
Wonderful. I'll say Disneyland's better but Disney World will be better as soon as Trump shows up.
See you soon DJT.
On that note let's wrap the whole thing up and thank our guest Mike Mitchell.
Mike Mitchell, you survived podcast the ride.
It was a thrilling ride.
I would love to go down to California Adventure.
I get to see more of it.
So whenever you guys ever go down there I'll come with.
We got to do it.
It's a great hangout, a great spot.
Yeah yeah we'll show you a great time.
Right now let's go.
We'll see you in our car outside.
And hey join us and join podcast the ride the group on Facebook,
add podcast the ride on Instagram and Twitter.
Am I getting anything wrong?
Send any questions or comments you have to podcasttheride at gmail.com.
Yeah and everybody individually at fat Carlson on Twitter, at Jason Sheridan on Twitter,
yeah at Scott Garner on Twitter, Mike Mitchell anything to plug?
At bdayboysmitch on Twitter I guess.
And then listen to Doughboys, a fellow feral podcast.
A wonderful podcast.
Absolutely yeah thanks for leading the way and you know making feral what it is today.
We'll get some crossover coming soon I'm sure.
We'll get some Doughboys in podcast the ride crossover at some point.
Hey that's a nice invitation to get.
Isn't that exciting?
Absolutely.
Oh you get to go to your house meet your beautiful cats.
Oh yeah that's right yeah I love to meet the cats.
Hey everybody thanks so much for listening we'll see you next time.
Bye.
See ya.