Feral Audio.
Warning. Today's episode is the first one to require an actual warning.
We are not kidding. This one really goes places.
Beware hitchhiking gangsters on Podcast the Ride.
Hello ladies and gentlemen and welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast that's a thin excuse for three adults to use churros as tax write-offs.
There we go. Score already. My name is Scott Gardner and that guy you heard laughing was Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
And Mike Carlson is here.
Hello. I'm here too.
A softer laugh.
Yeah, yeah. I'm withholding with my laughter, I've been told.
You have been, yes. Multiple sources have told you this and I might agree with them.
Yeah.
I appreciate some support as we record future episodes of this Podcast the Ride.
So folks, today we're going to talk about the great movie ride, which it feels strange to say it is a dearly departed attraction from the former Disney MGM studios, today's Disney's Hollywood studios and tomorrow's Disney Hyperia, Disney's XL park.
Yeah, we should talk about that. There's a survey just went out because they're thinking about renaming this park, this Disney's Hollywood, it started out as Disney's MGM studios and it's been Disney's Hollywood studios for many years, but there's a list of ideas they've got and they're terrible.
Each one better than the last, I would say.
They were.
These names.
These were like tested on guests, they did a poll and to see what guests like the most. The one that was kind of the most in line with what things have been named in the past at movie theme parks was Disney's Cinemagic, I think was the name of, is that correct?
Yeah.
Yeah, no Disney's Hollywood Adventure, I feel like that was floating around as a rumor for a while that it was going to be called that.
Seems pretty clean and clear. Part of me is like just don't rename it, like what an incredible amount of work for them to do and rebranding and re-merchandising. Maybe they want to though, now they get new money from that new merch with the cool new logo.
I've got the names here, these are the potential names.
Disney Kaleidoscope Park.
What does that mean?
Yeah, I don't know. Kaleidoscope is just a mix of shapes and colors.
What else? What the park is becoming, just a mishmash of Star Wars and Marvel.
Disney Storyverse Park?
Which like, what is a...
That was a name by committee, if I've ever heard one.
Disney Hyperia Park?
Made up word.
Disney Beyond Park?
Nothing.
You know where you ride the rides about movies. Disney Beyond or Disney Hyperia, a play on a local street name around where we are recording this podcast. Bizarre.
Disney Cinemagic, Disney Legends Park.
Which really, if it's called Disney Legends, it should be like rides devoted to all of the Disney legends like Dick Van Dyke and Imagineer Tony Baxter.
And Whoopi Goldberg.
Fess Parker, a virtual Fess Parker winery. He's the guy who played Davy Crockett and now he makes great wine that you can enjoy at the...
We all know who Fess Parker is.
Is he still alive?
Not sure. I say he makes the wine. Probably he never made the wine. At some point he was alive and may not be alive today.
There's my favorite potential name Disney XL Park, because I'm a big boy and I like a big park.
You've described yourself as husky before.
I'm a husky man, husky lad.
I don't think you are though. Do you like in spirit you are? Like you have your jovial, you have...
Well, at the very least when I was a preteen, I definitely had some husky clothes.
I mean, husky is a size category for young boys in department stores.
Not the dog, the husky.
No, no, it just means fat little boys.
I'm so sorry.
This would be a place you as a child would have felt comfortable buying clothes that don't demean you.
Big boy, big adventures, big thrills.
That would be a good tagline, big boys, big adventures.
Yeah, that's true.
Meet the hosts. This is Jason Sheridan. He lives his life XL style.
One thing you got to know about Jason, he's an XL kind of guy. He excels in living XL.
It also reminds me of the Disney, not Disney, the McDonald's Mighty Kids Meal, which was another thing aimed at husky kids.
It's like a happy meal, but if you're a little more hungry...
Were you like, was only your local McDonald's testing that out like they knew?
Like this is one XL kid, he'll come in and try this thing.
I wish. No, I believe that was a national branding effort.
I really have no memory.
Mighty Kids Meal would be like a double cheeseburger, not a regular cheeseburger.
And it was just to fill that fucker up a little more.
And a toy you could eat, I guess.
A toy you could eat.
And what was the Disney Cinemagic?
Cinemagic. Oh, man.
So if you can imagine the Cinemagene...
It also sounds like Cinemagene.
Well, doesn't it have a weird sort of vaginal quality to it?
Cinemagene?
Like what is the...
There's some comedy thing where somebody calls something a vagene and it reminds...
A boar rat.
A vagina vagene.
So unless they're putting an opening of a boar rat.
Like Cinemagene, like a Frenchman.
Cinemagene. See all the most famous vaginas in film history.
Julianne Moore in Shortcuts. Is that correct?
There will be a Julianne Moore in Shortcuts animatronic.
Think back to your Mr. Skin days.
The Robert Altman movie based on Raymond Carver short story Shortcuts will have a new attraction at Disney's XL Tour.
For all fans of Julianne Moore's Another Regents.
I'm trying to agree with you, Scott. I think they should just keep it as Disney's Hollywood Studios.
Because even like in real life in modern day, like movie studios mostly exist in popular culture.
Like most movie studios, they just keep bulldozing the sound stages.
Because so much is shot on green screens.
Not that we're all, you know, for those listeners who don't know our body of work.
Sometimes we all do things for TV shows or something.
Can you like count on one hand the amount of times you've been at a real studio?
It's so rare. You're always in some odd sound stage warehouse off the two and some awful at the Highland Park crumbling facility.
Like the studios are kind of a fake thing anyway.
A little bit. And everything's shot in Atlanta, New Orleans.
Also my reasoning for why you should keep it just the same name is that except for us and like a thousand people, no one gives a shit.
No one cares. There's not a father that comes to Florida and it's like, well the theme of this park is unclear.
And the name doesn't really match the rides that I've been going on. This is very bothersome to me.
What productions are currently shooting here?
I don't see a sound stage anywhere. The famous hanger shape of a sound stage.
I don't see any teamsters or craft services anywhere.
This isn't like the movies at all. I didn't need a special pass to with my face on it.
I didn't need a drive on. Mike and I were recently at a working movie studio, Universal Studios Orlando.
Not together. We were not there together. We were both there within the last few weeks.
Separate trips. I'm so jealous. How did it go? What did you find?
Some stuff looks really good and some stuff does not.
You're talking about just Universal. Just Universal Orlando in general.
I had a very weird experience where I was down there and Orlando gets a lot of rain.
But the first few days I was there, it just rained so much like all the time.
And usually it's like hot and sunny in the morning and then thunderstorms roll in.
This was like waking up and there were thunderstorms.
I like that we're talking about Universal Orlando and the first thing you just talk about is the rain.
It was very weird for Orlando because I've gone to Orlando so much.
They were like, what's he going to talk about? The rides or the restaurants?
Jason, Florida's rainy, folks.
Let's cut to the chase. We want to hear about your naps.
Do you get some good naps soon?
Spider-Man still looks great.
Yes, it does. I agree.
Spider-Man still looks great. The E.T. adventure, Scott, you'll be happy to hear, was running great.
When I was there, it looked really good.
And compare some of the other attractions, like some of these screen based rides.
Universal has a lot of screen based rides and some of them are not aging well.
What's suffering right now?
I mean, the Terminator ride needs a new screen.
Oh, they still have Terminator.
Terminator is going away though. That's going away soon.
The thing with the screen rides is some of them may aging poorly, but it's mostly screen rides.
It's so depressing. It's the same crap. It's the same stupid trick every time to make you feel like you're going forward.
You get sprayed in the face with water at the same spot to me.
Like, oh, whoa, a guy just spills a soda on you from the Jimmy Fallon ride and like water hits you in the face.
I don't even want to talk about Jimmy Fallon ride.
Pleasurable sensation in the world getting water sprayed at you that you don't expect.
The Kong ride is a lot of screens with a great animatronic at the end.
Like the giant Kong animatronic looks awesome.
There's one robot on the new Kong ride and it is awesome, but the rest is just like the crappy Kong that's out here now.
The thing like and it's just the same stupid water where it's like, oh, weird bugs and she's shooting at the bugs and the bug like, oh, we got hit with water.
And like the bugs like blood is on you now, but it's just water.
Let's see what else?
I mean, the Harry Potter ride.
Fast and the Furious coming by the way.
Supposedly not a screen ride though.
Supposedly a real ride and not a screen ride.
Ah, wonderful.
I heard it here first.
I found a lot of the big roller coasters in University of Orlando.
I might just be getting too old for that.
I like had headaches walking off of them and they just redid.
Now we're getting back into the incredible Hulk.
This is stuff that Jason started talking about.
The headaches I had and the rain.
I used to I used to go on the Hulk like multiple times a day when I was there and I walked off this time going like, oh, I feel really bad.
I will say that I got a little headache on the Hulk as well.
OK, but it's that's a new track, too.
So maybe the track is faster or more aggressive somehow.
Something like that.
Nobody had a seizure like Mission Space style, which was killing people.
Right.
Several folks a few weeks.
The Hulk ride.
I do like that they've sort of changed the idea of it.
It's just sort of like, hey, you get in line, we're going to turn you into a Hulk.
It used to be like Banner had an experiment and like something was going wrong and then he was transforming.
But now it's like you get in line like here's what we're going to do.
We're going to turn you guys into a fucking Hulk and you're going to shoot out and it's going to be great.
And like it's totally a different like context.
That being said, you still it's like just a roller coaster.
There's no robots to bring it back to what we're talking about with this.
The studios re theming and everything.
I haven't been to Universal Studios proper in a while as opposed to Islands of Adventure.
Do you feel is it getting confused at all being that they have taken out?
There's no tram tour.
There's less behind the scenes.
There's a roller coaster where all the sound stages used to do.
Does it matter?
Is it?
It seems like it matters because that park I feel like they always got away with like this set is next to this set is next to this set because it's like it's like a movie.
It's always a back lot.
It's still the park doesn't make any sense.
So it's just a jumbled mess of like New York Street and there's the Blues Brothers.
But then Shrek is down the street in his own fairy tale theater.
And then it isn't like T2 3D is in like the Schwab's Pharmacy or something.
Yeah, it's a lot.
Islands of Adventure.
I mean, I my family has always really liked Islands of Adventure.
We always had a lot of nice times.
It really hasn't changed a lot, which is nice.
Like personally, I'm like, oh, it's nice that this is still here.
But also like it really hasn't changed a lot since 1999.
It's bizarre because of the comic strip area most specifically.
Like you still have like Beetle Bailey and Nancy and like just like Little Nemo, like comic strips that were too old for when I was little.
Like I don't know what the hell Little Nemo was.
But by Nancy, do you mean Kathy? Did I say no?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Nancy, Nancy. Nancy has like a big she has a big poofy like hair.
She looks like she looks kind of like Little Dot.
Remember Little Dot from the comics?
OK, she's not an older woman. She's not like a Hallmark card.
No, she's a little girl. No, no, that's what that very weird.
Oh, Mary Worth.
No, no, no, no, no. Hallmark card lady.
Oh, the cranky old lady. Yeah, I can't remember her name.
We should leave this to the podcast that assuredly exists or will soon exist about a Hallmark lady, the great heroines of comic strips.
I one thing I did really like was spending time.
And I know I made kind of clowned on it in the stunt show episode.
But like I enjoyed being in the Lost Continent and when I saw the Sinbad show this time, like there was a lot less jokes and a lot more fighting.
Like I feel like there was a lot more.
Did they give what's his name? Poon Jab?
They gave Kabob. Kabob was Kabob. Sinbad's.
If you didn't hear the stunt show episode, go back and learn about Sinbad.
Sinbad. Voyage of the Lost Beyonds.
I don't know the subtitle of the stunt show. Something like that.
Everyone else was doing a lot more like intensive like fight choreography.
So I was like I was impressed by that. Also packed.
The Sinbad show was packed and the like, you know, kind of weird Poseidon walkthrough adventure was like packed.
But not a lot of crowds. This is great.
It's cool. It's almost 20 years into the game.
The classics are still hard at Islands of Adventure.
But not so at Disney's Hollywood Studios.
Exactly. And it's this is a park.
Disney's Hollywood Studios is a park that has had its troubles lately that it's in transition.
A lot of the original opening day attractions have been let go or turned into some awkward iteration.
Like when there was an American Idol attraction and now that's gone.
And so we are we have bid adieu to the great movie ride.
But that but we are going to resuscitate it today, bring it back to life on this episode.
But why should I tell the tale?
Why not leave it to some TV station from Tampa from 1989?
One of the most entertaining of all Disney MGM Studios theme park attractions is the great movie ride inside the Chinese theater.
It was the first idea that surfaced from the original concept team to take guests through the most golden moments in film history and actually put them in the middle of the scenes.
Of course, the first obstacle was deciding which of all the moments are most golden.
Tough work for the Imagineers. Which moment is the most golden?
They had to move. They probably had a big board up moving from golden to silver to bronze.
And if you were bronze, you're out of the ride. Only the most golden moments.
Should we talk about the rumors about this park? Like how this park got started?
The park in general?
The story about how Universal Orlando, like, you know, they were in development for a few years of building in Orlando and brought in like the heads of other studios to see if they were interested in getting in on the park somehow.
And at the time, Michael Iser was the head of Paramount and essentially saw the model for Universal Studios Florida.
And then when he became the head of Disney a few years later, was like, we should build a movie studio.
No kidding. Really. He kept that in his pocket, which is similar to how it's rumored that Katzenberg saw the early development of A Bug's Life and sort of brought that over to DreamWorks.
He like caught it in a meeting and then just kind of kept it in the pocket, smuggled it out of the building.
This is all allegedly. Please don't sue us, Rich Wellford.
Please still be on the podcast, Michael Iser. Our ultimate guest, we were just saying.
Today, anyone with a BoJack connection who might be listening, please hook us up.
I know you probably party with him all the time and we want to party with him, too.
I've read that he just wanted people to be like, well, we could go to Universal Studios, but like if we have our own Universal Studios, they won't go to Universal Studios.
So just make it here. What does make Universal Studios here? That was his idea when he like said yes to this park.
So like that's the whole point is like the movies are at Disney and it's it for sure is the park did take a lot of elements from the original Universal Studios here in Hollywood.
There was a tram tour initially, which that's gone now.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Where you went through a thing called Catastrophe Canyon, which we can cover at some point sort of equivalent to earthquake.
One of these like experiences where your tram shakes in this fire and water. Yeah. When the park first opened, it was very odd.
There was the Great Movie Ride and like an hour and a half, two hour back lot tour.
And that was it. Mm hmm. Which is sort of that in Universal Studios history.
That is kind of how that park was where like there weren't all the individual rides.
The your day at Universal Studios was you did the tour and that's like a four or five hour experience.
And and in fact, the Great Movie Ride is kind of a remnant of that era because it is a very, very long.
It was like a 20 to 30 minute ride. Yeah. I'm like there.
Do we know the time probably like 20 minutes around 20 minutes, 24 minutes or so.
Seemingly like in that more Universal Studios tradition now, I feel like we're in an era of extremely fast rides like three minutes, three minutes.
Yeah. But I don't know. I kind of miss that era of like saying and I like it on Pirates of the Caribbean or Haunted Mansion or some of those classic attractions.
You're sitting on this thing for a very long time and clothes like both the Ellen's Energy Adventure and Great Movie Ride closed on the same day.
Both like moving theater rides, both like 20 minute, 22 minutes, 22 minutes.
Ellen's Energy is 45 minutes. Is it really? And it feels like it felt like it when I rode it.
Extremely long, slow moving rides, the opposite of thrills.
There is not a thrill to be found on this ride. But that was part of the chart.
You can just say something that you can go on if you were a wimpy little kid like me.
You knew nothing would scare you until the alien popped out.
And I but I just like sink down into the seats and close my eyes. I did not like that alien.
No, I was scared. Yeah. Did we all saw I sobbed on the ride.
My mom said my sister and I were sobbing when the alien came.
So no one else sobbed. OK, no one else was sobbing.
I cried in those parks a lot. So I did it. So the alien was the only thing that made me cry.
I feel like probably the universal earthquake probably freaked me out, especially because as a child of Los Angeles, I lived under the shadow of real earthquakes.
Sure. But so so let's well, it's kind of talk talk you through the attraction.
Are we missing any other well, I mean, it was the opening day.
This was like an opening day attraction. Original attraction first 1989.
Wow. And it was the last because now it's gone.
But it was the last opening day attraction that was still there.
That's crazy. I really like the centerpiece of the park, especially because it was in the Chinese theater, which is the what's that Disney term weenie.
Do you know that that like the big thing at the center of the main street that takes you down like it's the Magic Kingdom or the Epcot ball,
the spaceship Earth and Epcot and in that park, it is the the Chinese theater.
But yes, yeah, the primary symbol of the park that's leading you.
The thing that's on the T-shirt. Yes, that's a better thing to say.
Also, that phrase weenie is extremely irritating. I don't even know if I've ever heard weenie.
Maybe I'm making it up. I don't know. It's somewhere in theme park lore.
That's funny you say that because I when I watch a ride through the great movie ride today and I, for whatever reason in my mind,
had convinced myself that the ride goes in chronological order of the history of the movies.
And it pretty quickly does not like the early scenes are very like the early days of movies.
But then it just jumps around. Oh, because you're into Mary Poppins very quickly.
Well, let's see. Let's talk you through it. The line is a lot of fun.
You get to see real props from some of the movies you're going to go into like the Mary Poppins carousel horses.
The first thing I noticed when you're walking around there is that it's nicer than the actual Chinese theater.
The outside from living in Los Angeles outside much cleaner.
There's no like guys walking around in superhero costume like I was like, well, this is what it should look like.
This is the one out here should look like this. It's much less sticky.
Elmos. Yeah, yeah. It is very much an idealized version of Hollywood.
Yeah, yeah, which is great. The Hollywood of our dreams that has really long ago got.
I mean, when it was this ride was closing, I feel like there was a lot of tributes and like blog posts
written about like this is how when I was a kid, I got interested in classic movies.
And I know for me, like that was a big this was a big thing.
Like this made me I went and like hunted down the movies that show up in this ride.
So you've seen you like I've seen Footlight Parade three times in the last five years.
I have a lot of thought a life you live in Excel.
But I was a weird 12 year old who had a VHS copy of singing in the rain and I would just watch it over and over to tapes.
Right. Is that a tape might be it is long.
But between the Gene Kelly animatronic and the ride.
And then there was like a photo op in in the park where you could with a lamppost with an umbrella on it and rain would come down.
And I'm like this chubby 12 year old kid going like I want to be like Gene Kelly.
I can't fit under the umbrella. I'm still getting wet.
My sides are damp.
But I love that cue like looking at that like montage of the of the trailers the original trailers of these movies.
Well, that's right. Yeah. Because in the ride you go into what 12 to 14 different movies and on the way in in the Chinese theater where the big theater screen would be you watch all of the original trailers, which is fun.
And that was probably an early me realizing that trailers were not always the way they are.
Yeah. Today, like the fact that trailers used to have those crazy like spectacular.
Yeah.
Amazing.
I love our time over and like the number of dancer over 200 dancers.
Yeah.
Could you imagine if trailers were still like that?
And it's like the one to not miss the emoji movie coming to your local movie palace.
It would be better, honestly.
Over 500 different emojis represented in full technicolor.
Next summer prepare yourselves as the minions go to summer camp.
Sounds like a little bit like D'Ampardo.
And with your host the minions.
That's the episode.
I mean, that's yeah.
They'll get to it one.
Hopefully season 40 whatever we're heading into.
Yeah, that'll be there.
But we will Facebook group minions host, please start the campaign.
Now that that those trailers like that giant screen showing those trailers in like the last couple years of the ride operating.
That's the first place you see Robert Osborne, right?
Like Robert Osborne.
Yeah.
God rest his soul.
So they did like a couple years ago.
A couple years ago, they like the movie.
Right.
The classic movies.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Sponsored the ride.
And then they added Robert Osborne, the now deceased host of that channel.
And he just like there's a lot of him now or there was a lot of him explaining the movies and like his narration is all over the ride.
So like he does so much of the heavy lifting with the ride as far as like explaining what's going on.
Did he like take away some of what the guides were supposed to do?
Yes.
This is the thing that irked me when I got my job as a tour guide at Universal Studios in 2006 was so much of the fun stuff was given over to Whoopi Goldberg.
And now Billy Bush.
And now Jimmy Fallon.
That's correct.
In fact, the most infuriating thing for me was that Billy Bush now, you know, Trump related philanderer.
I guess he's not.
But yeah, you know, he's been exiled from television.
That creep got to say, we'll see you in the movies.
And I didn't get to say it.
I'm still.
You had gotten to say it and then they changed it or just started working there one summer prior.
I would have gotten to say the classic line, we'll see you in the movies, which is why I now do now.
That's my common goodbye.
If I'm hanging out with people at a bar or something, I see you in the movies.
I don't say I love you to my wife.
I say, see you in the movies.
It's an important phrase to me.
As you go to sleep at night praying you wake up in the morning or not.
I hope so.
Yeah, we're scared of us.
All right.
Well, hopefully see in the movies.
Anyway, where were we?
Robert Osborne.
You're in the queue.
Yeah, so he's taken over a lot of like information on the ride now.
Honestly, the update is a little it was a little too much, a little too much.
Not salvage the ride, did not was not enough of a hip updates to make them keep it in the park.
I don't know if it was like the first off, I have to say Turner Classic Movies rules.
Like it's great that there's just a channel that shows like uncut classic movies that are very well curated.
And there's no commercials or minimal commerce, just commercials for other movies.
No dumb original series.
No, but yeah, I mean, I didn't ride it with Robert Osborne in there.
But from what I saw, yeah, it seemed like a lot.
And some and like a elderly man dryly discussing movie facts.
It was not the like boost of energy.
Yeah, I don't think that I don't know.
Yeah, I can't imagine that they were like, well, we know it'll bring more kids in is that this old man will tell them about a 1930s movie.
Like this will really reignite the children.
I think it probably came down to like, you know, they needed a sponsor and Turner Classic Movies gave this ride a few more years of life.
Right. Like it was probably a practical concern.
And I would like a pure sponsorship money issue.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, but the thing that maintained throughout the entire history was that you entered this wonderful room with this big, bright marquee.
And you got onto a big, big cardboard box looking vehicle that moved very, very slowly.
And you were whisked away by your guide, a flat speaking 18 year old wearing an usher vest.
Well, hooray for Hollywood played, which as a kid just got me so excited.
I loved it.
It was a little movie.
I was so excited.
Take it away, CB, they say at the start.
Like, oh, Ben and Cecil B. DeMille says like action or someone.
Oh, yeah. They call action on the ride.
You start moving.
And I'm glad they never changed that.
They never like updated directors on that.
It was a take it away, Gareth Edwards.
No one would have been.
Take it away, Colin Trevorrow.
Wait, maybe don't actually scratch that Colin.
So then you go through under the marquee, essentially into a movie and you go into you start off with the Golden Age of musical movies, which yeah, we mentioned Footlight Parade.
There's a giant like statue of all the dancers and beauties and Footlight Parade.
There's a ton of them.
There's like a ton of like there's like 30.
Yeah.
And then there's like projections from like, I think other Busby Berkeley movies.
So a few years ago, I got a copy of Footlight Parade and watched it.
And it is an insane movie.
It stars James Cagney.
And it is like two and a half hours long, I think.
And it is about a theater company who like back in the day, giant movie palaces would have like musical numbers in between like the different movies and stuff.
And you would see like a fully produced Broadway number.
And this theater company is like in danger of going under.
So like the whole movie is them trying to figure out what they're going to do, what they're going to do.
And then the solution is they have to perform three different giant musical numbers at three different theaters in one town in one night.
And the movie ends with three giant set pieces back to back, including the last song in the movie, a song called Shanghai Lil, which is insanely racist in a huge number of ways.
But it's the it's the moment when James Cagney finally has a number like he is an amazing like song and dance man.
And he doesn't sing and dance the whole movie.
And then the last number he tumbles into like he accidentally falls into doing this number and like his character like nails it.
But it includes Ruby Keeler playing an Asian character named Shanghai Lil and any number of other racial stereo.
Let me ask you this question. What from the because the the scene in the ride, which number is that from?
Is that the racist number? No, that's if you haven't been on the ride or you don't recall, it's like a kind of a tiered cake that a lot of dancers are.
It's a lot of ladies on a giant cake on. Yeah.
And and like the spectacle of these footlight parade and 42nd Street.
It's also kind of like like this shows up in a lot of Busby Berkeley movies with like just like a few dozen dancers doing an amazing choreographed number.
And that's really what the ride is pulling from.
But like, yeah, really glosses over some of the racial stereotypes.
And there's also a giant sequence where they make a big picture of FDR in the movie, like a bunch of men in sailor outfits like hold up signs.
And like there's a lot of like our boys in uniform stuff.
Well, that sounds good. Yeah.
Yeah. In the past, there was no good movie.
I don't think they're like jaws.
It's amazing to witness and think about they were doing it all practically.
But yeah, in terms of like, oh, this says not exactly held up.
So tourists every day from 1989 until several weeks ago were being whisked into this film.
Footlight parade featuring a song called Shanghai Will.
And then and then you see a Gene Kelly animatron.
And then it goes right to singing in the rain, which was another child.
That's a giant jump in film history.
Yes. Yeah.
Because seeing the rain, oddly enough, is essentially a jukebox musical.
Most of those songs appeared in other lesser remembered MGM musicals.
And then like they were brought back for singing in the rain like 15, 20 or like our own personal Robert Oz.
I am. Yeah.
Comforting old man. Yeah.
Telling us about the old films.
Would it surprise you to find out I played Robert Osborne once in a show at the UCB theater?
It would not. OK.
Did how long was the standing ovation?
Longer than the show.
Two and a half hours. The length of Footlight Parade.
This has been your musical history.
Well, then you go into one of the other great film musicals, Mary Poppins,
which is the first I believe for the only representation of Mary Poppins in the theme.
Which is crazy.
That's what I had that thought, too, because there's an old there's a video online that everyone should look at where Tony Baxter is showing.
Tony Baxter, one of the most famous imagineers, he had a whole book that he made a Mary Poppins ride in sketches.
That's really incredible. That would have been an amazing dark ride.
And it was like kind of his way into Disney.
But yeah, for this to be the only Mary Poppins like Mary Poppins should be a ride.
It's weird that like this is the only thing we've got was a couple like and now it's gone.
I think they're going to put some like here's my fear is they're going to put like Emily Bunt and Lin-Manuel animatronics in the British World Showcase in Epcot.
They're talking about putting they're going to put something in there. Poppins thing when the sequel.
Yeah, when the new one comes out and it's like, don't please, please just put the old characters in like or, you know, how about this?
Let's do the attraction based on saving Mr. Banks in Disneyland.
So there's a you go through a ride in Disneyland where you watch Tom Hanks Walt Disney take Mary L. Travers through through Disneyland.
So you're in Disneyland. You're in 60s Disneyland in this Disneyland ride.
And Walt is a folksy southern man like Tom Hanks.
Hello, Mrs. Travers. Good to see you, Mrs. Travers. Why come on in?
There's a five minute scene where you just see a very tired Walt listening to the entirety of Feed the Birds like thinking about his life, the weight of the world on his shoulders.
I have to build this experimental city.
Cancer infected his brain to the point of the city is got the city.
Build this ski lodge in the mountains.
I've got to build this city of tomorrow.
Seriously, that voice is screwing my ass.
That voice is so weird. A trip through Walt Disney's collapsing mind.
There's another we're going to do a lot of ride pitches over the course of these episodes.
And there's one. But so here's at this point is where the ride gets really exciting because you're you board with two different ride vehicles.
And at this point, they split off.
One keeps going into the old west and another goes into sort of like a like an old New York world.
And at this point, the guide who we have been with is gets caught in a shootout and he gets replaced basically by either an old cowboy or a 1940s guy.
Oh, God. Hey, what do we got here?
Is this a podcast? So somebody's just broken into the studio.
Who are you? See, oh, God.
OK, OK. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hi, Jack.
And this podcast, the ride.
Excuse me. How did you know we were here?
How did you find us? Bugsie. Bugsie Malone.
And I'm going to take over this podcast.
Oh, God. Please. Hang on.
Hey, hey, please. Wait.
You know, I mean, I mean, business.
No, he's got a Tommy gun.
For those of you who cannot see what's happening and most of you cannot, a pinstripe suit wearing 40s gangster has broken into the studio.
He has a Tommy gun.
He's safe. What's that over there?
Is that a red on air podcast light?
I hate red on air podcast lights.
We shot out our red on air podcast light.
There's no way to know whether we're on the air or not now.
No more red on air podcast light.
Please. You've already robbed us of the most precious experience of hosting a podcast.
What is your what are you trying to do here? Mugsie.
Hey, now, mind your P's and Q's. OK.
OK. Are you minding them?
I'm minding them.
You're minding the P's.
I'm minding the P's and the Q's.
The Q's.
Yes.
And put your valuables in my mouth.
Oh, God.
What counts as a valuable?
I want to suck on them. Yeah.
Give me them jewels.
Here, take this aux cord.
It's not connected to a microphone here.
Folks, again, it appears a 1940s gangster has hijacked our podcast.
I might take this podcast a ride for a little ride myself.
No, no, no. Please.
There's no way of knowing what this monster has in mind.
Mind them.
OK, OK. Wait, wait.
Which are the Ness's? Which letters?
The P's and the Q's.
The P's, the Q's. I'm so sorry.
All right.
Let's take this podcast a ride to another zone here.
Oh, no. He's in control. Mugsie's in control now.
That's right. That's your name, right?
No, no, no. Mugsie?
It's Bugsie.
Bugsie.
It's funny in the ride, it's Mugsie.
No, but now it's Bugsie.
OK, here it's Bugsie.
Bugsie.
Why don't you buzz off?
Oh, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, Scott, come on.
I'm sorry. I don't mean to be a hero.
I'm not a hero.
I'm a coward.
I'm crying just like I did when I was a child on this ride.
I'm going to put some money in Bugsie's mouth
and let him suck on it.
OK, that's calm him down.
Bugsie is now eating money.
Hey, let's go.
We've got to get out of here.
I'm unwanted.
I'll be sent to Sing Sing if I don't get out of here.
I'll be sent to a thousand years in Sing Sing.
Let's get out of here.
Guys, Jason Mike, we could be accomplices if we aren't careful.
OK, let's just try to lay low as we keep explaining
the history of the great movie.
Is that OK if we just keep doing?
There's a James Cagney animatronic,
public enemy James Cagney, not Footlight Prey James Cagney.
Which is kind of interesting.
He's a good friend of mine.
You know him?
Oh, yeah.
We gangsta all the way back to the roaring 20s.
Have you been on heists together?
Is that what you're saying?
That's right.
We were sent to Sing Sing before.
Oh, OK.
Did you help him bust out and that's how he can be on the ride?
Yeah, I busted out of Sing Sing.
Oh, OK.
Well, I guess thank you because James Cagney animatronics really good.
Yeah, it's good.
It's a good robot.
Thanks, Bugsie.
There's also in this section here, I looked up in the names of the other gangsters,
our brains, legs and weasel.
Are you familiar with these three?
These are also your comrades.
You're talking about my gang.
My gang of thieves.
We busted out of Sing Sing together.
So brains, legs and weasel, they were all in Sing Sing with you and James Cagney.
Yeah, yeah, we busted out, you see.
High tailed it out of there to Shanghai ourselves this year.
Podcast.
Did you hide in a laundry truck?
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
We jumped right into it.
Tell you how it happens.
Was there too.
You know what?
I'm going to say I don't I don't believe your story.
I don't.
Scott, Scott, you're telling the truth.
Do you believe this?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, that's what I taught.
Oh, God.
That's what I know.
You know, that may sound like just a wave file of a Tommy gun.
But if you were here in person, he is absolutely demolished the studio.
This isn't even we're new here.
This is going to mess it up for all the other Feral podcast.
Joe boys are going to come in here and they're they're not going to have Sonic Clarity anymore.
Yeah, I stole all the animal Lisa puppets from this year.
You got to give those animal Lisa puppets back.
I might get a I might get a bucket to on the black market from these animal Lisa puppets.
No, no, no, don't.
And do not take your eyes off of that Rick and Morty autographed poster.
Maybe I'll put my eyes on it.
No, no, no, no, no.
Now my hands did not sign that for it to be stolen.
Now my mouth.
Oh, no, it's putting it in his mouth.
This gangster and his disgusting oral fixation here.
Put some of my rate, my rings that I wear on my fingers in your mouth.
Yeah.
You don't touch all this priceless memorabilia.
Oh, my wedding ring is room.
Gold teeth at Sing Sing.
Oh, God, you're a truly vile man.
Wait, wait, wait.
What?
Where are we now?
Well, now we can't just anymore, folks.
No, we are, of course, looking at the man with no name, a Clint Eastwood standing outside of a saloon atop his great horse.
Do you know about it?
Now, do you I know, you know, Jimmy Cagney, but do you know John Wayne?
I've never been here before.
This guy doesn't look so tough.
Well, he's the most he's the toughest, roughest, rudest, tunest cowboy in all of cinema.
Show some respect.
The toughest World War Two draft dodger there was John Wayne.
Where are we right now?
Are we in Joyze?
I've never seen these these horses and these these cantinas.
What are we in?
Joyze?
A lot has changed in the world in the time that you were trapped in Sing Sing.
You don't know about the gold rush.
A lot of a lot has happened.
Well, maybe I can get myself a few Ben Franklin's while I'm here.
Oh, no, no, no, no money at that point.
Put them in my mouth.
No, he's right.
Oh, my God.
You folks, you should really not have to watch a man put money and tools and artifacts in his mouth.
That picture of the guy with all the billiard balls in his mouth like this gangsters mouth.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing like that photo.
Nothing like that.
No, no, no, you don't look silly.
You look very cool with those puffed out cheeks.
You have minded those peas and cubes.
I will continue to mind them.
I will go back to mining them.
OK, OK.
All right.
And cues in mind.
Let's just try to look over there.
A different cowboy from a different Western era Clint Eastwood.
Oh, yeah.
Well, yeah, I notice this guy, Clint Eastwood.
There's also this guy, Ethan, from a film that I like called The Soy Cheese.
Oh, so are you a film fan?
Oh, I love the movies.
Oh, what are some of your favorites?
Ten Thousand Years and Sing Sing.
That one doesn't have a lot of mass appeal.
It might only relate to folks like you.
Was that your sentence?
Ten thousand years?
I got ten thousand years.
How many did you serve?
Poof, poof, poof.
Not even a week.
Oh, wow.
That's how fast I busted at an age.
Geez, you got the land of media.
That's crazy.
You know what?
I'm starting to think maybe this guy's not so bad to have around.
He's a smart guy.
He's a real character.
Just like all of us.
What did you get set up the river for?
Hey, I got set for putting jewels in my mouth.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
I would.
I think it's against the law around where I'm from.
It's a sanitary concern.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
I also I also like going on the great movie ride.
Oh, wow.
So that's exactly what we're talking about.
It's a shame it's gone.
Huh?
I think Mickey and Minnie's runaway railroad might be a good attraction,
whether they're the ride that's taking its place.
Hey, the only Mickey and Minnie's I know.
I savin' ten thousand years in Sing Sing.
No.
All right.
Well, I know if there's one thing, you know, maybe you might enjoy a mouse or two,
but I know you don't like a rat.
Hey, the last thing Bugsy Malone wants to see is a rat.
Are you a rat?
No.
Jason, tell him you're not a rat.
I'm not a rat.
Snitches get stitches.
How about a stool pigeon?
Are you a stool pigeon?
No, no, no, I swear.
I'm no stool pigeon.
Mike, are you a stool pigeon?
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I'm just trying to call the police real quick.
I'm suddenly worried that you're on the way to the cops.
What's all that mumbling over there?
Some studio stuff, just like disturbances on the mic, feedback.
And you don't know how we're playing.
We're getting radio signals from a different place.
All right, all right.
Well, keep minding your P's and Q's and nobody will get hoiced.
Where does this podcast or I go to next?
Well, the next part of the attraction is the this is probably the scariest part of the attraction,
even more scary than having a tommy gun pointed at your head.
This is where you go into the spaceship Nostromo from the from the 1979 film Alien.
Space ship. What the what with us?
What's a spaceship?
Oh, well, so that's a new thing.
Since the 40s, when you're from, we've opened up a whole new part of the universe
that we can go to above the earth.
It's called space. And to get up there, we use space ships,
the highly advanced technological cars, the car that takes you to the stars.
Wow. The moon. The moon.
Sure. Yeah. The moon.
The man has walked on the moon. Hey, maybe that man saw my old lady
because I sent her there last night.
Oh, no. Bugsy.
You can't wait. We should remember it was acceptable in his time, but it's not today.
No, especially not when we're talking about Alien starring Sigourney Weaver.
Ripley, one of the strongest heroines in cinematic history.
I don't know if you know this. Women star in movies today.
That's a new development since your time as well.
Sigourney Weaver, I'd like to challenge you to a boxing match.
No, no. She'd clean your whistle, Bugsy.
She'd clean your clock. Yeah.
You mind your P's and Q's. You're talking about that kind of thing.
Oh, all right. And even this alien is a lady, too.
Oh, no. Hey, Scott, I think that alien up there likes you.
You don't say, huh? Why don't you give her a big smooch?
Oh, ew, no. That's disgusting.
Oh, I basically want to barf. Don't say that.
Why don't you smooch both of her mouths, the inside one and the outside one?
I will not. I'm married one mouth at a time for me.
That acid blood could really choose through some bars at Sing Sing.
All right, Jason will kiss the alien, but Scott doesn't have to.
And there is a full sized alien alien here in Farallon Studios.
He can constantly peeking through the ceiling like in the ride.
It's unnerving. Nobody noticed it until Bugsy showed up.
Jason, come on, kiss the alien, get it over with.
Do it for all of us. Be a man.
Yeah. Yeah.
Why don't you put your tongue in it?
For those of you who can't see, the gangster has put his Tommy gun down.
He's quite aroused.
And maybe this is my chance to get the drop on him.
Just grab.
No, no, no, no, no. OK, OK, OK.
I'm sorry. Go back to watching Jason kiss the alien with a multiple mass.
Take the inner mouth with your two hands.
This is really nice.
Hold that inside alien mouth.
How do you know how it's done immediately?
Put the whole inner mouth in your mouth.
Why did it take us all the way up to its outer mouth so that the outer mouth can give your face a little kiss when you go down the inner.
Yeah, Jason is just using you for positive euphoric right now.
He's kissing the alien's tiny mouth.
So right. Yeah.
All right. Well, that was a good one of our ho again.
Love is very helpful.
He's helped one of our hosts discover who he really is and what he's into.
It's good for both of us.
I you guys go ahead for the tour here and get to know them.
Oh, all right. Jason is going to go up into the rafters with the alien.
All right. And an alien.
That's pretty woke.
Hey, I would say fucking an alien is the wokest thing you could do.
Oh, yeah, I guess he's right.
I mean, whatever that word means.
All right.
Extra is an extra terrestrial sexual, I guess.
Yeah, an extra terrestrial like I like the sound of that.
OK, now. So let's leave Jason behind.
Hopefully we'll catch up with him at some point.
But now we're now we're heading into the the Indiana Jones experience.
Do you know about it? He's from your time.
You ever bump into him? Hey, yeah, I knew a guy named Indiana Jones.
Yeah, he fixed the races over in the Indianapolis 500 for me.
Oh, so we made great all those sacks of money and dollars.
So he would fix horse races and then you would win money.
Same guy who did the white socks.
Yeah, I'm in the fixing thing to see you ever run into a guy named Williams.
Williams. Oh, my. Yeah, that guy.
He's a real greaser. Yeah, he is. He's a real greaser.
Yeah, we would have fights with him and his greaser gang.
Oh, geez. So you had to watch out for his for switch blades.
Yeah, yeah, we would we would put point switch blades at each other.
My gang versus my Williams gang.
But sometimes his switch blade was a comb and he would just comb his hair back.
And I thought that was pretty smart. Yeah, that sounds exactly like Mott Williams.
I thought it was a switch blade. You for sure have dealt with the real Williams.
It was a switch blade, but it was a comb and he used it. The comb is greasy, greaser hair back.
Now, I don't suppose your weapon is secretly a comb as well.
Oh, you mean this? Clearly, it's not. It's not. It's a real Tommy gun.
If anything more must by the bullets.
Bugsie doesn't like to get too familiar with the with the common folk that he's robbing cointely.
All right. Well, let's keep a comfortable distance.
All right. So tell me about this Indiana Jones guy. OK, so so this is this is interesting because this is the first
appearance of Indiana Jones in the theme parks predates the Indiana Jones ride.
It is a couple of rooms which are pretty impressive rooms, obviously littered with snakes and the first Indiana Jones animatronic,
which is like carrying the the arc out of these like lifting up this this big golden thing with the with John Reese.
Did someone say gold? Yeah.
Well, that room on that attraction does have a lot of gold, a lot of a lot of a lot of valuables in it.
But we've already given you all of ours.
I've given you all my money, all my rings on my finger.
Like there's so what do you want. Why do you need more?
Hey, hey, Bugsie likes to make as much dough as possible, you know, before he makes a pizza made out of jewels.
He's got to get the dough.
I mean, look, looking around this recording studio, there's not much value left to you.
I mean, except maybe for that that ruby that magically powers our mixing board.
Yeah. Yeah. There's a whole.
Yeah. Look, I think you should not look at that, even looking at that magical ruby that's really big and like it's illuminated and it's been here for a long time.
Right. Red. A magical type of magical chunk of ice.
I really think you shouldn't go. You shouldn't do it. Stop. Oh, do not touch that.
Well, that. Oh, for people who cannot hear or cannot see what's happening, the pinstripe suit wearing 40s gangsters now been joined by a new hooded man, a man in a cloak.
Hey, stand back. I'm trying to get this here ravioli chunk of ice and get put my lips on it.
This ruby is cursed. All who have tried have perished. That's why Farrell got such a great rate on this building's rent.
So that makes a lot of sense around the ruby. I see you better.
You better listen to it. It seems like he knows what he's talking about.
He doesn't care about a quiz. Oh, God. Doesn't scare Bugsy Malone.
Oh, he's walking over to it. I guess he's going to take a look at the idea, man.
Put my lips on it. I don't care about a quiz. Oh, he's puckering up. Oh, boy. Oh. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, my God.
The power briefly flashed on and off here at Farrell and and and the 40s gangster has just turned into an ashen pile of rubble.
a coal black skeleton.
And that's the magic of podcasts.
Whoa, Jason.
It was me all along.
You were in the cloak.
The guy was you?
Yeah.
I thought you were busy kissing that alien.
Working his double innocence.
I made love to the alien, and then I ran back in here
through a cloak on and hid by the cursed ruby that
haunts and powers feral audio.
Wow.
Oh my god.
This, I have to say, I mean, I don't know how well you guys
remember the other episodes that we've recorded,
but it seems like we just talked about rides.
And today seems very high in terms of magical content.
A lot of crazy stuff is happening.
A lot of surprise to me.
I thought we would just dryly walk through the ride
like we normally do.
But today, yeah.
And air our grievances about changes to the park.
Maybe drop some mild profanities.
But instead, all these, but the most special guests of all
have showed up.
Hold on.
I'm going to go try to pry my rings and money out
of this dead man's mouth.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, OK.
Don't touch the ruby.
You work on that, please.
Here, I got it.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
OK, great.
Here's your stuff, too.
Oh, thanks.
And let's give back that oxcord and all those.
Where'd all the hundreds come from?
Those all yours?
I guess you keep those.
Ah, right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't want to touch them.
Old money bag, Carlson.
A little finder's fee for me.
Full of saliva that, I bet all the saliva surrounding
all the jewels in his mouth helped him get electrocuted.
Yeah, it probably works a lot of sense.
And probably as a conductor.
Makes a lot of sense.
Anyway, then there's a Tarzan room.
Yeah, so then you go into the Tarzan.
Yeah, there's a cool Tarzan room.
Johnny Weissmuller and Maureen O'Sullivan.
It is crazy that there was a ride for 30 years, 20-plus years,
featuring a Johnny Weissmuller animatronic.
Yeah, if you want, you could go to the parks.
Kids could see Anna and Elsa and Johnny Weissmuller.
Johnny Weissmuller.
The magic of Disney World.
I was thinking, it's weird that they didn't just
theme it to the cartoon Tarzan.
Like when Disney's Tarzan came out,
it would have been such a simple thing
to switch it to the cartoon.
That seems like a thing they would do.
Put a Disney store level kind of dummy up.
Just a mask.
Just a cartoon mask on the same thing.
And be like, it's Disney's Tarzan.
And no one would have given a shit.
Or Brendan Fraser's George of the Jungle.
Oh, sure.
Disney property.
A lot of 90s properties could have filled in.
The whole problem with the ride is that they did not
keep updating the films.
You can only assume that in the original conception
of the great movie ride, it was like, oh,
and we'll update it once every five years.
But they didn't particularly do it.
Yeah.
But a cool room when I was going through.
One of the better rooms, honestly.
Jungle room, he flies back and forth on the,
he does the yell, the famous yell.
We all know it.
There also could have been a Mighty Joe Young
with Charlize Theron.
Yeah.
I didn't know she was in that.
I don't know if I ever saw that.
She was, I just heard her on a Bill Simmons podcast,
and he brought that up.
And she was like, let's keep moving.
She did not activate and talk about George of the Jungle.
Anyway, yeah, so they missed a lot of opportunities.
Or the new Tarzan, Kellan Lutz Tarzan.
There's been a lot of Tarzans they could have updated with.
But they stayed in the past, and we stayed in the past,
with the Casablanca scene.
That was another movie, a 12-year-old me
hunted down at the video store.
And I feel like I did not understand
a lot of the context of it.
I remember watching that a bunch when I was younger.
And Casablanca to a little kid in 1996 doesn't really sink in.
You mean the Nazi stuff?
Yeah.
I don't think I knew about World War II a little,
but I didn't know about Vichy France and that sort of thing.
And the bit at the end where they throw the Vichy water
in the trash can and the song plays.
See, I don't remember all this stuff.
If that 40s gangster were still around,
he probably could share his film buffalos.
He knows.
That's right around his era.
That's right around the same time.
So he probably saw that movie and maybe lived the same time.
So it's possible.
Is that also the plane?
Wasn't there a rumor that that is really the plane
from Casablanca?
I don't mean to interrupt, Jason, but right behind you,
oh my god, the smoking, ashy skeleton of the gangster.
I'm back.
His bones are chattering.
He's doing a graveyard dance.
I'm back.
This is not canon.
So as you were saying, Jason, that is the actual plane
from Casablanca.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
That they use in the movie ride.
How about that?
Yeah.
Stick him up.
He still is, but now it's firing bones
instead of bullets.
OK.
Clinkity clinkity.
This is a lot like Walt Disney's the skeleton dance.
Did you see that?
You're a movie buff.
That would have been our new release.
No.
Oh, OK.
Well, I can't see them all.
And they don't, not too many movie screenings
in Sing Sing, I'd imagine.
Hey, well, glad you're back.
Glad you could join us.
And I'm glad that your soul somehow survived
in that ashen rubble of a skeleton
that you now pile into the body.
All my old gang members up there.
Oh, it was Bugsy and Mugsy.
Squint and Beans.
Squint and Beans were all up there.
What about Brains, Legs and Weasel?
Brains and Legs.
Oh, it was wonderful.
All my old gangster friends, we were reunited.
But then did God send you back here
because of your unfinished business?
They wanted me to set the record straight
on the Casablanca plane.
Wow.
OK.
So it was the real plane.
Although, was it?
That's actually, do we know if that was the real plane
on the ride or not?
Half of it.
Bugsy says.
Message straight from God.
So God sent you back to give us that message
and only that message.
No, Bogie himself sent me back.
Oh.
Bogie himself.
OK.
A cinephile's dream you've experienced.
Wow.
And I fenced with Douglas Fairbanks Jr. as well.
Whoa.
I can't believe it.
I don't mean to pimp you out for your entire heaven
experience, but you didn't by chance swing on a vine
with Johnny Weissmuller.
Oh, did I?
Wow.
Because even two minutes up there was an eternity.
Hey, while we're talking about Casablanca,
that famous scene in Casablanca actually
shot indoors on a soundstage right here in Burbank
at Warner Brothers Studios.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Another Robert Osborne style.
Another Robert Osborne.
Did you see Robert Osborne up there?
How's he doing up in heaven?
Hey, Robert, he's not doing too good, actually.
What?
You can't do bad in heaven?
Oh, what a horrible revelation.
What?
Very sick.
Oh my god.
He's very sick.
He's sick.
He's not walking around introducing things
to his heart's delight?
No.
No, it's really sad to watch him.
You know, he's getting all his facts wrong.
He's very sick.
He's going to go to the next one.
The next what?
They're sending him down to hell?
Purgatory or hell?
Next level of heaven?
There's another one.
Is he going to other heaven?
That's what you don't know.
There's other ones.
Oh.
There's multiple heavens?
Is he being punished?
Or is God unhappy with his incorrect movie facts?
So he's being cast away?
Well, he couldn't save the ride.
He's got one strike against him.
Oh, God was a big fan of the great movie ride.
Of course he was.
God loves the classics.
Yeah.
You know, God's a good man.
He would like such a great ride.
God's no man.
God's a woman.
We all know that.
Of course.
Hey, all right.
Well, you know, now we're heading towards the finale.
Slap God in the mouth.
Hey.
Come on.
OK.
That's the worst.
That's crazy.
How would you even be able to do that?
You can't fight God.
Dude, Bungie got sent back here because you're going down
to meet the man downstairs.
I think you're on the way back to hell.
You're on the way back to hell.
I'm going to go to the other level.
There's another level?
There's another level.
The levels go both ways.
There's about three of them.
So there's multiple areas just like Disney World.
Heaven's kind of like Disney World,
where there's multiple parks.
And you get around via a boat.
Yes.
You were sent down in a boat.
What a very fun leap.
It's pretty nice to know that.
Yeah.
Just so you know.
Yeah, OK.
Well, now we're heading to the Wizard of Oz
with the witch, which is a really great animatronic
character, one of the best, I think,
in the history of the parks.
A lot of points of mobility.
Yeah.
And those creepy munchkin animatronics always
kind of creeped me out as a kid in that too.
Because they talk to you and they sing along
and they ask where you're going.
They make eye contact with you in a strange way.
Yeah.
Bugsie, are there short people in Heaven?
Oh, what do you think Heaven is?
It's not going to exclude the little freaks in the world.
They love you.
Bugsie.
Wait.
No.
In his language, that's nice.
On his spectrum, that's an inclusive statement.
All right.
Let me tell you.
Everyone gets a cloud.
Everyone gets their own cloud.
I had a pinstriped cloud.
Wow.
Really?
And the munchkins have little tiny clouds.
They don't need to be as big.
That's how it works.
As a shorter man, I'm happy to hear
this, that I'll have an appropriate size cloud.
You'll get a little cloud.
You won't feel bad for hogging cloud space.
Yeah.
But I bet Manute Bowl or which one of the tall basketball
players has passed away, George Mirachan.
Oh, they have the biggest clouds.
They must be eye-bogglingly big.
Is that where the Lakitu from Mario Kart?
Is that where the idea came from,
the character in the Mario games where it had a cloud?
Oh, yeah.
Did you see any little creatures tossing shells out
from a cloud?
No.
But that is where they got the idea.
Oh, OK.
Cool.
That makes a lot of sense.
So whoever designed Lakitu must have died and gone to heaven,
come back with that notion.
Yeah.
And now that all the munchkins are dead,
they all have their little tiny munchkin clouds up there.
They're all dead now.
They're all there.
They're still singing.
They're singing their songs.
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah.
That is nice.
Well, yeah.
You're giving us some hope for the future.
I hope we all, as one day, will all.
In heaven, they sing, follow the yellow brick cloud.
Oh.
See how they changed that?
Yeah.
That's very charming.
Because clouds are the street in heaven.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm still concerned that you can be sick in heaven,
and that's bothering me.
Yeah.
I'm concerned about Robert Osborn.
Judy Garland, too.
She's a little sick.
Sick?
Didn't she live a hard enough life on Earth?
Yeah.
She's been sucking too much munchkin come up there.
I mean, whoops.
Oh, Bugsy.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
That's now you've fucked it too far.
Hey, you know all the bugs.
Bugsy man.
This is way too far.
No, no, no, no.
I'm kidding.
That's just his nature.
What do you spell?
We've been right telling out of Wizard of Oz town
before we hear more of this.
Maybe you guys catch the rumor that it seemed unclear
some sources very confidently said Liza Minnelli is
the voice of Judy Garland in the Wizard of Oz sequence,
but that did not seem confirmed.
I don't know if that's true.
I have never seen that, so that's interesting.
I don't know if that's true or not.
I feel like that's a fact all us little freak kids would
have known for sure as children, as children interested
in Judy Garland and Liza Minnelli.
I feel like if that were true, we would have known that.
So I'm going to say no.
I think that's a false rumor.
So if Judy, if Liza Minnelli was dead, I could have told you.
That's true.
She's not that sure.
That's why I don't.
You didn't see her.
She hasn't climbed upon the boat to heaven yet.
The rules of Bugsy are now that I only
know about things from heaven.
So that's the new thing that happens with Bugsy.
Well, at least you're not haunted by your less than a week
in Sing Sing anymore.
No, no, no.
That's so far in the past.
Now I'm a messenger from beyond the gold.
But not of anything profound of just sort of odd trivia
from heaven about how celebrities do it.
The sort of mundane life of heaven.
Yeah, you're not spreading the word of the gospel
or the word of Christ.
If he threatened to smack God, so I
don't think he's a religious man.
Yeah, I guess not.
Although you believe in God.
Same for AMC's preacher, right guys?
AMC's preacher.
Now that you're back on earth, you can get caught up
on AMC's preacher.
Start binge watching.
Oh, I can't wait to binge watch the Ozarks.
That's what I was waiting for when I was in heaven.
Better than heaven, they say.
That's what all the critics have been saying.
So I'm glad you get to do it.
So you make it now.
The great movie ride finishes and we get to the movie
at the end of the ride where you get to experience all,
you get to binge watch really all of cinematic history
in one sitting, several glorious minutes
in which you see, you know, what's in that?
Those, what I remember is that that movie at the end,
the montage of all the great films that it was high.
It was very oddly heavy in like 80s Bette Midler movies.
Yeah, Bette Midler shows up a few times.
Which they were really pushing Bette Midler in the 80s
at Disney World in general.
Like there was a heavy Bette Midler presence
and she was like at the opening and everything.
I just, have you ever seen any of those like big business,
the like touchstone movies of the 80s?
I, for some reason, Good Morning Vietnam
is highly featured in this montage.
That's a great point.
Good Morning Vietnam.
They like give a lot of real estate.
I have never seen that movie,
but that scene is like burned into my brain
from riding that ride so much as a kid.
Also the cut from like Al Jolson going,
"'You ain't heard nothing yet' to a shot from Showboat."
And like the music.
I'm really glad that Disney and Michael Eisner
would put in Al Jolson.
Al Jolson and Showboat.
You can't ignore it.
But then in a more recent edit.
It's part of our history.
Yeah, we have to acknowledge it and move on.
In a more recent edit, they took out Showboat,
but put in, is it Laurence Olivier from Marathon Man
going, is it safe?
Laurence Olivier.
Oh of course.
The old Nazi going like, is it safe?
Yeah, the old death camp.
Yeah, the old torture.
The person who's about to pull his teeth out
and looking for the diamonds that he stole from the Jews
during the Holocaust.
Yeah.
Really?
Yeah, your film buffery is, I'm glad you came back.
It's a part of that movie.
Although a big shot of Woody Allen in that movie.
I forget from Take the Money and Run, maybe.
I don't know.
Because they have to represent like comedy in general.
So you see Buster Keaton and Woody Allen
and like Robin Williams or like Pat.
They were like, they made it when they were
plugging its Pat, so just all the Disney movies.
I was trying to watch it today and see what
sexual maniacs were in it besides like Woody Allen.
Like I was trying to see, there's a shot of Johnny Depp,
there's a shot of, I was trying to see like
if they had removed anyone.
There wasn't like, there's no like Jefferson Davis film
that they included.
There's a decent chance they had to get rid
of the great movie ride, cause there's a problematic element
in every movie.
Well yeah.
In the great movie ride.
So it's just easier to replace it with Mickey Mouse.
Footlight Parade, as we've experienced today,
Bugsy, the 40's gangster who's visited us
has shown us his very problematic views from the past.
So this might all indicate why they needed to
take the ride out.
Maybe it was archaic, maybe there were offensive
viewpoints within it.
And also maybe licensing a couple dozen movie properties
from other studios started to add up over the 30 years.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They did lose the MGM license.
You know, we do a thing where when we've reviewed rides
in the past, we've used our system of keep it,
what were the choices?
Keep it, toss it up, mysterious fire for the insurance money.
Burn it down for insurance money.
Now the choice has been made for us,
the ride basically was burn down.
Burn down for a 20.
But if there was a way to salvage the great movie ride,
do you guys have, and Bugsy I include you in this,
is there a, yes you're welcome.
Was there a way, is there a way
they could have salvaged this ride?
More Bugsy, that's what I think.
So your suggestion is maybe turn a lot of the other scenes
into a 40s gangster scenes, or at least put the animatronic
James Cagney maybe in like the Wizard of Oz scene as well
and make that a through line.
Like you pop up in one of the munchkin windows,
maybe you go bother Glinda the Good Witch.
Yeah, Bugsy Bones, which is my new name.
Oh, because I'm a skeleton.
Oh, right.
Bugsy Bones' great movie adventure.
Now that's something I would pay to see.
A cursed skeleton from the 40s who's been to heaven.
That's right.
And it's on his way to hell.
Where the great movie ride is now in hell
and Bugsy's on his way to hell.
Me and Al Jolson and John Wilkes Booth
take you around the great,
great adventure of acting and film history.
Yeah, I like the sound of that.
With brief touches of offensive opinions,
but not so much, it certainly is not any sort of
demented history lesson.
Right, right.
It's just what you think.
A manageable amount of offensive opinions, I think.
Also, all the old great studio heads,
the Warner Brothers and Thalberg and Mayer,
and they're probably definitely in hell.
They did horrible things.
They probably laundered money through you.
That's probably one of the many things you went to.
Yeah, I've taken care of Irving Thalberg.
I've gotten a kickback from the Warner Brothers.
Yeah.
The budget overage of D.W. Griffith's intolerance
was slid to you, Bugsy.
Please, intolerance.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
That man couldn't tolerate a thing.
Not a thing, huh?
Not a thing.
You know, you are, you know,
you've proven yourself such a cinephile,
you've proven yourself such an important part
of the great movie ride experience,
it's too bad that you can't now leave your hand prints
or your bone prints, as it were,
in the cement outside the Chinese theater.
I know, it would stick in my bony,
bone fingers would fall off and stick to the cement.
Or here's an idea,
it might prevent your finger flexibility in the future,
but maybe cement is a good way to cover up those fingers
and give you a full hand again.
And you have like cement hands
and you could punch, or no.
No, no, we don't want him to punch.
I'm so sorry, I haven't suggested that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, don't do it, don't do that.
The only cement I'm familiar with are cement shoes.
Oh, no, no, no.
You guys keep choking around with your little ride opinions,
I might have to fit you all for a pair of cement shoes yourself.
Wait a minute, so I thought we were friends now,
we bonded over movies and you're still mad at us,
you're still threatening us?
I'm going to toss you in the river and drown you faster than
than the Robert Wagner drowned Natalie Wood.
She told me in heaven, by the way.
Once again.
That it was him, that it was him.
Again, it's part of our history.
You have to acknowledge it.
She really does mean it.
Probably what happened.
Jesus.
Allegedly.
It was a weird story we never found out about.
It was Catalina Island is haunted by that forever.
I know the real Casablanca Plane is in the great movie, right?
The real Robert Wagner boat isn't in there somewhere, too.
No, that was on the backlot tour after they closed it down.
Oh, that was like teetering above catastrophe.
Yeah, and it got left out in the rain with the spectra magic
floats and the rocket rods.
So it got destroyed.
It just rusted away too bad.
Well, that's why we have to preserve our history and not let it rust away.
All that remains is the horrible memories left in Christopher Walken's brain.
Another another theme park ride idea.
A journey into Christopher Walken's brain.
Well, I mean, that pretty much takes us through the
history of the great movie ride and how wonderful to get to
encounter one of the characters from the ride.
Bugsy, thank you so much for being here.
A pleasure. Absolutely.
Is there anything is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, got a new book.
Bugsy got a bone to pick coming out about two weeks.
So, well, yeah, doing some other things.
Very clever. Did you think of that?
Or did you have like a ghostwriter thought of some of the jokes for you?
I know. No, no.
Well, I have to say, when I was in heaven, I did meet one ghostwriter,
Tennessee Williams.
Oh, how's he doing?
He was a see, because he's dead.
Well, yeah.
Why did you go to him over Trumbo?
Trumbo saw who he saw, Mike.
So sorry. I just want to know about the because he was dead.
He I consider him a ghostwriter is what I'm saying.
Oh, I see. Yeah, yeah.
I get it. I get it. I'm sorry. Yeah.
Is he like, did you get to experience he written like dozens of new plays
up in heaven that only you got to read?
Yeah. Cat on a hot tin cloud. Wow.
Oh, that's a heaven exclusive.
You're not going to hear it here on Earth, folks.
It's like he's kind of resting on his laurels there and going over old material,
to be honest. Wouldn't you?
Let me ask you this. Yeah, I guess I would.
Is he sick as well? No. Oh, good.
Oh, thank God.
Some people are something we've learned.
Some people are well in heaven.
Some people are struggling.
So they the struggle never ends.
Ain't that right, Bugsy?
That's right. The struggle is real.
Hashtag Bugsy.
So hashtag bugs, if you want to see Bugsy back on the show
for potentially an un unrelated ride.
I know you only appear in one ride, but if you ever.
Well, what could Bugsy talk about?
If you want to come back and talk about horizons or they never built
Dick Tracy's Crime Stoppers. Oh, that's great.
Yes. Yeah, that's another guy.
Dick Tracy. Oh, yeah.
Wait, let's not parallel. OK.
When I think of Dick Tracy, my trigger finger gets a little tight.
OK. None of us are Dick Tracy's not here.
Yeah, yeah. We hate him. Take care, everyone.
Hey, thanks for being here.
You've survived Podcast the Ride.
And as they say in Hollywood, that's a wrap.
We'll see you in the movies.
Follow us on Twitter at Podcast the Ride.
Email us at Podcast the Ride at Gmail dot com.
Once again, we are Podcast the Ride.
The podcast is called Podcast the Ride.
Thanks for being here, folks. See you in the movies.