Feral Audio.
Warning, today's podcast may include extreme amounts of oil industry propaganda, thrilling
live descriptions of comic book panels you can't see, and multiple references to Disney
Parks and Resorts head Bob Chapek.
All this and twisting turning discussion of Epcot Center's Universe of Energy.
Wrap in and enjoy Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the only theme park podcast with very mild profanity.
And many other fine podcasts.
Sorry about that everybody.
I'm scanning my head right now and there's four Disney parks so that doesn't work.
So we're on to the second one.
Blue who's a little bird who's their mailman and then they have a friend named Gela Tony who's an Italian painter cat
Yeah, and then there's another character who's a rabbit that I'm forgetting
We're gonna do a whole episode on Duffy at a certain point, but yeah, we are
Whatever week that is Scott gets the flu this flu season
A lineage of Duffy the Disney bear feel free like parents going out of town
You guys do whatever you want. We just tank the podcast by talking about the stuffed animal universe
That is Duffy the seven and a half hour edition is entirely Duffy
Well, yeah, that's that's
Well one bit of dry arcania and we're talking about another one today the the universe of energy one of the
original Epcot attractions from 1982
Shifted gears in 1996 and became Ellen's energy adventure and is about to shift gears again
and become the
potentially a Guardians of the Galaxy
Attraction that's the overall what we're looking at possibly the most insidious of the original Epcot future
world
Yeah, well and for what reason?
For the sponsorship of Exxon like the the
How much fossil fuel industry talking points this ride is I mean for the time I get they they do talk in the original
ride a lot about like
Hydro power and solar power and with power they pay some good lip service to future things that they will lobby against
Yeah, it's basically what happens also like with this opening in 82 like Exxon was already doing
Research on climate change and like had pretty much figured out like all of the major oil companies had pretty much figured out the climate
Change was real. Yes, and I read 1978 they knew and this thing opens in 1982
so they knew and then they sponsored this right till
2004 and yeah, even on the second version of it. There's stuff like oh, isn't it fun to drill like drilling is fun
There is there is a part in the remake and we'll get into it with with Ellen and Bill Nye where Ellen says
Why don't we just make everything solar and Bill Nye says hang on?
Ellen Jesus today's like most one of the most prominent climate change activists Bill Nye the science guy
Like to what was that? I said we'll get into him later. Oh boy. Oh the gloves are off in this episode
Is there a way for this one of anything? We've talked about feels like a ride that
Potentially listeners might not know is there what's like the quickest way to explain?
So it's an opening day. It's an opening day action for Epcot Center. It's a moving theater
it's like you get into these cars that that essentially make a
theater and then they
Move like through dioramas and then they shift into like individual cars
They shift into a line and kind of come back to the theater
Set up at the end of the and in the middle you you go through this like kingdom of the dinosaurs
So if you have vague recollection of a Disney World trip
Yeah, you went through a dinosaur world that then might be what that's probably the only thing you remember is the dinosaur robots
And if you said all right, like if you looked at old Epcot Center maps
There'd maybe be a little cartoon dinosaur poking up out of the roof for the thing which was like the encouragement
for for kids to come in because they were not necessarily thrilled by discussion of turbines and
You know shale and said an 80s 70s 80s easy listening music that like
Tracked the ride that stuff is good though
And checking it out that's actually the best but it's my favorite part of the ride from re-examining it today
There's multiple there's still like energy like I feel like we should do a mystery science theater sort of thing
We're just throughout the ride. We just start off thinking energy. I
Have I downloaded like there's three different versions, right?
There are three different songs and they're all tremendous and we will get maybe I guess I'll play them
There's an opening at the opening day
Ceremonies a bunch of people come out dressed in all white and do a choreographed number and sing one of the songs
It's incredible cuz like Exxon employees and like CEO or whatever get up there and they speak about this and enjoy the ride
And then like a bunch of people in white jumpsuits and like a very like ABBA ask
Yeah, like dance medley start doing the song like a 70s variety show breaks out around like very stiff suit
Giant like butterfly wing type. Yeah. Yeah, it's a little bit more spare than that
They don't have a lot of production but but it is in that realm that isn't the in this area
This is an area by the way that I imagine you guys have watched a lot of these two like as theme park nerds
We were versed in the area of ride opening ceremonies and there's a lot of like really grainy bad
videos of these things on YouTube like here's like the
awkward little ceremony where like Mickey Mouse hands the keys to Star Wars to Star Tours over to
C3po and the Darth Vader tries to interrupt it, but then all the characters
I don't know ask him to leave and he does
There's a lot of great a little like there's a really good one for back to the future
The ride there's a very awkward opening ceremony for Guardians of the Galaxy mission breakout
Yeah, that's still certainly yeah still doing these like bad like awkward things
We're like there's you're like, oh is the collector gonna come on then?
It's just it is Benicio del Toro, but he's not in his costume and he's like, well you expecting someone and then everyone's kind of confused
Yeah, you're expecting collector Benicio del Toro and you got like three Heineken's deep
Toro like his other project wandered on stage
No one's quite sure what to do and then head of parks and resorts
Bob Chapick is up there and he's not the greatest speaker in the world
Yeah
They set up a story that like you are now in the story of the ride and then some executives talk to you
And then you get back into the story of the ride characters from Guardians of the Galaxy come out speak to you introduce
resorts head Bob Chapack and then and like all of the care all the real actors who played the characters next two
Iterations of the characters. These things are always so confusing
You never see like we're the deepest of nerds and we only sort of know about these
Like it's it's hard to tell it's not like they go viral
You know what? I mean, like you gotta see what happened at the opening of
Luigi's flying tires
Local contest winners thrill is Bob Chapack takes the stage
I went oh I saw a really sad one for the opening of
So the reopening of soak city, which is the nuts very far
Oh, right theme park and there was a very stiff little ceremony where like the mayor of Buena Park shakes hands with us with the snoopy
Walk around character and then you know a tiny amount of confetti goes off and
Snoopy gives as big of a thumbs up as he can and his constricted suit. I'm a fan of these
I know I watch all we should have we should review them all on a future of it
Well, I also really like and I don't know if they still I don't think they do these much anymore
But it was like a big thing on ABC in the Disney Channel in the 90s of like a special about the ride
We talked about the Indiana Jones one on that episode and like the Tower of Terror one with Kirk Cameron is also
something to watch
Living Seas with John Ritter
Yeah, they used to have enough like promotional budget to do an individual special for every single ride that opened
I'm sure they'll do one for Star Wars land, too. They'll probably be like an ABC special
Yeah, they did get Harrison Ford to introduce like footage of it at whatever whatever special that was
Oh, yeah, there's like a Disneyland thing on like ABC and we watched it and it was live from the Kodak theater
Whatever that's called now
You should enjoy the whole new galaxy opens of delight and fun
What will await you up in the galaxy's edge?
Assuming I do not perish in a flight in the near future. I look forward to look out for replicants
Oh fuck wrong
wrong project
Wrong project. God damn it. Callista I need the copy
Why does Callista have the copy?
She was just helping out. She was just like got roped into helping. Print it in a bigger font next time damn it
I don't want to look at it on the iPad. I like a paper copy
So I learned my dialogue for witness and it's how I'm gonna do this
I think this is the second time we've done a riff on Harrison Ford's voice
I think we did it in the Indiana Jones ride to where he was announcing the holidays
The old Harrison we love him. So yeah, the ride video is something to watch for for the open
I mean the opening video
Energy. Oh, here's what I'm gonna say about this ride in general. This is the first time we're
Doing the research for the attractions that we talked about has felt like work
This was so arduous because there's two rides both of them
45 minutes long so long like a feature film to watch
These videos if you put them together it'd be about the length of this podcast
Yeah, I'll accept with like much more giant holes of silence
it's like the slowest narrator and then like a
15 minute little slow jaunt through dinosaur world with no dialogue no music
These things are such slogs both versions. Yeah, I think though the the
Attraction itself is like a great illustration of the evolution from like the original vision of Epcot to the
90sification of Disney to like the possible future of like an IP based Epcot. Mm-hmm
Yeah, it follows kind of the arc that some of the other pavilions have had world of motion into test track and journey into
Imagination like the Eric Idle journey into imagination like I feel like some of the stuff that Disney did in the 90s
They're like well, we got to make this contemporary and they weren't
Thinking a lot about the fact that it could be there for 20 years
Like well it starts Epcot starts out in a lot more of a dry like this
Especially more than anything is like a film strip you're watching in school
Like this is just a video that's supposed to explain something to you and then there's some robots and then they explain more things to you
So like they were realizing in the 90s like this is dry as shit. Like this is like, yeah
This is this is homework to watch
Let's just throw a care a person people love and then that'll make everything like that'll make the medicine go down easier
And what network are we thinking about acquiring?
And who is their top star Tim Allen?
We've already like used every favor from him every
Who is number two or three or four?
It would have been great if they got like Richard Karn or something to do. That's true
That would have been like Richard Karns energy adventure and then
2017 it was still there credit where it's due Ellen and Bill Nye are both in like culturally relevant
Yeah, they're still around so as Alex Trebek as is Alex Trebek who appears in the second
Why is it probably that it lasted so long?
It's cuz the kid those people are still people that people know well
There was enough time for Bill Nye the science guy to completely disappear from
relevance like because I remember going in the mid 2000s and
Thinking like do people have any idea who this is and now he is back with a Netflix series and
Constantly in the news and yeah. Yeah, he had enough time to disappear and come back. He was just in
Academia for a while. He was like the distinguished visiting professor at Cornell when I went to Ithaca
My mom is a teacher and got to meet him at a conference or something and she like it she lost her mind
Oh my eating a beetle for when you're a teacher mom my elementary school like fourth grade teacher like loved Bill Nye
We would watch Bill Nye stuff. She loves science. She loved teaching kids science and we'd watch Bill Nye like every other day. So like
1996 like yeah, sure. He should be in the right kids loved him and a very popular Disney
Product. Yeah, that's right Disney produce. He's currently suing them
like
Profits like profit sharing it he missed out on
More of a Beakman kid
Beakman more it was more funny at a rodent sidekick. Yeah, Beakman was definitely sassier. Yeah, he was sassier
So yeah, anyway, I found Beakman like sort of caustic and unpleasant and he was certainly caustic broad costumes the wardrobe
Yeah, cool it guys. I mean, I'll be honest. I have not revisited Beakman in many years. Yeah
We'll catch up. I'm sure there is elsewhere on feral. There's a Beakman's world
Podcast we'll listen to that before we discuss Beakman's world
Me on whoever does that one it is crazy looking at this ride and seeing like
This hasn't necessarily aged super well
But then like looking at stuff from around the same time like Tower of Terror or Indiana Jones
So it's like these are still both terrific
and I don't know if that was just a team working on them or like that they were totally original creations or like
Well, because you well it because the the 96 redo has to like use the bones of the 80s. That's true
so but it is what this brings up a point of like all
The rides you almost all the original rides in Disney World and Disneyland
I can see where people were like this is gonna be fun
Maybe a little informative and like kids and adults are gonna like this
Yeah, and it does kind of boggle my mind that they put this in Epcot and we're like, yeah, this is great
This like holds up to all the other stuff we've got in the other park
like I get what they were going for but it's like
Wow, what a 45 minutes and most of it's just a film strip. I understand like big screens
I guess you the big screens are bigger they were thinking I loved spaceship Earth and I love
Like the seed where all the like fruit carts ran into each other
There's comedy there's like a audio animatronic comedy
Yeah, yeah, so I guess they were trying to with the with the update like trying to put some like, you know personality into the ride
But then if you don't if you don't know the history of it
If you don't know that it's like Ellen invading a pre-existing ride that was kind of dry like imagine the tourists
last year going into this seeing a
20-year-old
20 years out of date version of Ellen who takes you into a world of dinosaurs
It just doesn't like you need the context even understand what you were looking at and why you're going on
We I went on it three days before it closed forever. Yeah, and
People there was a man next to us an older man who fell asleep
During it Lindsay my girlfriend started nodding off in the middle of it
I mean, it's you know, it's hot out there and but still like it's such a boring
Experience it's hard to imagine anybody
like truly feeling great about this about this ride and like
Like what person walks out of it beaming?
and also, I found clips last night of
Both Ellen and Bill Nye in the recent past talking a little shit about it
Like like Bill Nye makes he doesn't like explicitly insult it
But he says and why is this a great ride air conditioning and then Ellen?
referred to the rides and removal she actually talked about it on her show and kind of was
side-snarking about it like she did like a hashtag
Educational as she's making little and she did a bit asking for animatronic back like yeah clothes
Which I think is a funny bit like can I have it now that you're done with it?
Can I just have it like I think that's a funny the truth is it's gonna be repurposed for Star Wars land
I like that was into a they just like put like a first-order
Uniform on it and then like put sunglasses over
You don't know that many robots that quickly Garner Holt just can't churn out that many animatronics and that's small of a time
So first order officer Ellen
Will make the command Ellen the death trooper
If you just kind of melt that skin and stretch it around enough you can turn it into an akbar fairly sure
She could be a Mon Cal Mari one of the Mon Cal Mari race sure I
I want I started to watch like because there's there's a good amount of ride through videos of the Ellen version
and
There is not a lot of footage out there of the original version
So I have to give a shout out to Martin's vids Martin's video
I found Martin's vid as well Martin God bless you
Mari you are like Martin makes these
Martin is this guy who makes these like hour-long tribute videos to some rides that are still open a lot of rides that have
closed and he finds like
footage and concept art and like opening day stuff and gets like source audio and makes these like
Ride through I don't even know what to call it documentaries because they're like really well done
They're really well researched and edited and some behind-the-scenes
Footage and in this case an overhead of how this this ride works
Which is like I actually I found that very fascinating watching the flow of it because you enter a giant theater
Which splits off into eight different cars which all slowly move around this entire building and sort of a sort of a hover fashion
I mean it was like this crazy ballet watching those cars move around in this overhead
It's it's a technical Marvel this ride if not a for sure. Yeah, Marvel
Yeah, it's I found this video too and there's some pretty good
Footage of the actual original ride
Yes, and he like crowds. He does all this stuff for free. Like he doesn't charge for it
he like crowd sources all of this stuff and then cuts it together and like a
Coherent narrative and like yeah talks about it. Yeah the history a lot in the opening of it and so watch that
There's a journey into imagination one like there's all of these ones and they're like that's good
This is like we're all half researched and we're just goofing around
We have no visuals to show you yeah, we're gonna do we're gonna do a lot of descriptions
but yeah, it's kind of this thing where if you if you could just see it and sort of a
It's kind of a moving you just have to see it
But people weren't taking full VHS camcorders to tape a 45 minute ride through
I remember my mom me like making my mom like tape like I don't know
Mr. Toad or something on our video camera so we could watch it at home like as like
We would take these giant video cameras down and I feel like barely use them and barely watch what we shot when we were down
There but this ride is 45 minutes long. So people just weren't taping it. You need a SLP to fit that
I was gonna say tapes tapes weren't that big you'd have to switch tapes in the middle of that's right. Yeah
The so the basic the basic like way the ride is is like the first
Part of it is like the history of energy and how you know, yeah energy and oil and dinosaurs
Then you see the dinosaurs and then what's the future of energy?
right, it's like
Petroleum
Yeah, and I'm like just some even something like so a journey through inner space, which was a ride in Disneyland
The idea was like you're going to be shrunk down and you're gonna go see what's happening in an actual molecule
So and what is this is just like here's we're gonna show you
I guess there's sort of they might say well you go back in time, right?
We take you back to the days of the dinosaurs. Here's the dinosaurs while they were living before they
Turned into bone and muck under the earth
But it also doesn't really work because like it's about energy and now it's just some dinosaurs
I'm like, I'm really vague on what even energy if watching to entire ride through shouldn't I?
Understand the basic concept of energy. I don't think I do I think I know either
I know dinosaurs died and they became oil. Am I wrong? Yes, that's right. That's right. Okay, that is right
But what shouldn't we see the dinosaurs melted down on the ride?
Shouldn't they like all like a comet hit or something? We see like the melt and decompose and then turn into
Raiders you want to see?
A live version of that footage of the Fox
Decomposing and being eaten by maggots. Yes, you want that to somehow happen in audit you want like a living
a
Dinosaur that can like puff up and then slowly deflate and turn to bone. Yes, that actually that would be an incredible
It's like you would see you know
What happens over hundreds and thousands of years and it would actually make sense because really also these dinosaurs are just repurposed from two other
Like other rye like they were at the World's Fair and then they were at the World's Fair ones are still out here
Like I think they just copied the according to Max's vid
I'm pretty sure that some of them Martin Martin
Whatever the man's name
Sorry, so sorry that some of them were from that from the World's Fair
I guess my most interesting thing I thought was that like from the very beginning
there was always going to be like a solar energy based pavilion and
Surprise surprise
The Epcot plan changed because exons like we'd like to sponsor that but we have some other forms of energy
We'd like to talk about in addition to solar energy. Is that the history?
That's I think that's what I said in the video. There were solar panels though on and there there has always been solar panels
And it's powered like a little bit harshly unclear how much it actually powers. It's possible
It's just for which we I would like to talk about in a second the VIP lounge. That's also in this ride
The VIP lounge it just looks like a lobby of a Holiday Inn a 1985 holiday
I guess we may sir and I guess we'll die
Well, we'll do a quick jaunt here over to the VIP lounge
So all of these different rides in future world have a VIP lounge for their corporate sponsors
Yeah, and this one has one that was for the exxon
It's like you were an exxon employee and you came to Epcot you were allowed into this lounge
But as you pointed out the only perk of being an exxon executive my yeah
That reminds me of like a childhood friend growing up
Her mom works for FedEx and FedEx sponsored space Mountain for a while and I feel like there was either
Was there a lounge in space mountain?
But I feel like maybe they got front of the line payout. They got some sort of perk for space Mountain
And FedEx there used to be a FedEx diorama as you left space Mountain the like
astronauts
By the exit we used to be delivering FedEx
Yes
Corporate I feel like they don't is this maybe why there's so much IP going on in the parks because I feel like corporate
Sponsorships going to happen as much these days. I would yeah that would make sense
I feel like there's less and less Siemens just said no that they're not gonna keep sponsoring spaceship Earth. Oh really?
AT&T does not sponsor Indian Jones anymore, correct? I don't think so
I think I think probably that signage that's sort of going away. I guess test track is still
Ford
right
No, it's it's Chevrolet Chevrolet. I think yeah, yeah
Honda sponsors Autopia
Because are they added awesome. Oh, they added awesome. Oh and the bird is the bird called like Birdo
Bird is named Bird. Oh, yeah
You're gonna be Autopia and bird always from Mario to oh, okay Birdo is the egg-shooting
Our engineer is nodding along. Yes, that is Birdo
Oh if that were if you could avoid Birdo's mouth eggs in the Nintendo World's coming Universal Studios
That would be
Or painful or bad a bad idea. Yeah, there's a I found a website that says who can get into each different
Pavilion and or we to be excuse me VIP lounge. So for the Exxon lounge
The lounge used to be available only to Exxon employees
But then some of them are available to like the employee of the company that sponsors and like make-a-wish kids
And then some of them are still lounges and then some of them have been converted into just like offices
There's also a few lounges scattered about like every now and then it changes
It's like are you a chase Sapphire member? Are you an American Express card holder?
There's a vacation club lounge on the top floor of Journey into Imagination now. Hmm. What's in there?
It's the old image works into the old. Oh really? Yeah, but I don't think it's really working
I think it's mostly just outlets to charge your phone and couches
That's
Something high demand it. Yeah, you need that the GE for horizons
They used to have this like kind of secret thing here
We should put a link to this on the website, which would just be like if you're a GE employee this way. Yes
We're looking at the old GE logo and then three arrows all in 70s beige
Well, give that to you to ogle on your own time. Yeah. Yeah, I know you're dying to see it
It's funny how Epcot was when it first opened was a mix of these beautiful vibrant colors
But then also some of that 70s beige baby scattered here and there which I love
I mean this yeah entrance to the universe of energy as this awesome sort of
Gold and red tile tile mural. Yeah. Yeah, I'd also like to say aesthetically
I thought when when I was watching the ride through I thought from the beginning
I was gonna love it
Like I'd been under rating it this whole time because at the very beginning the Exxon tiger
Runs right at you and on five screens, by the way
It's the widest wide screen you ever seen a tiger runs right at you. It's really cool and scary
And I think he's got kind of like 80s
Old analog video effect trails behind him and then the title universe of energy flies at you and it is like
70s Superman it is such a cool
Opening title it might be like why I love old analog
Video effects so much. I probably like saw this when I was seven and it like freaked the hell out of me
So it's a step. There's some aesthetically amazing stuff early motion graphics stuff. That is pretty cool in the original ride
Yeah, and and that and then some of the music which I guess let's figure like do you were you listening any of these tracks?
Yeah, yeah. All right. There's a couple different ones here. I
Mean, this is great. This is but like this is everything you want
from a theme park
Yeah, this is up my alley
There's gonna be a 10 minute here where I just play things off my phone
It's sort of a R.E.S. Speedwagon roll with the changes here we go
Universe of energy
See you glow
Well, that's a
Song's music were so goddamn earnest in the 70s and 80s
And then can you play the one where the guy makes it sound like he wants to fuck energy?
Yeah, that's this one. This is called energy. You make the world go round
And this is a little more melancholy. There's also some that video
We were watching there's a melancholy acoustic version of it that I could not find
Like sticks is lady
Forms in the faces nature taking its course
Oh, it's a different time folks a different time lady energy
Oh
Carpenters I'm tearing up
I
Found an instrument we won't play that there's an instrumental of just that first song like it's real. Those are great
Those songs are great. Yeah
That song would be a wonderful song for like the first dance at your wedding if you were named
If there was a woman named energy one of the pot and we'll get to it at the end
But one of the positives I think is if you're doing a Guardians of the Galaxy, which is very much like retro
We playlist stuff. I think those songs got to come back
I think there's a decent I think so and put those songs back in and they were fit real well in the in the ride
Was there a rumor that the ride could be like a historical journey through old Epcot attractions?
Did I imagine that I think we've talked about that before? Yeah, it's
We're getting ahead of ourselves. But yeah
Supposedly, they're keeping the building the same they they're ripping everything inside out
But I don't know they're keeping the building the same which means maybe or maybe not ripping everything out
Maybe they're keeping the dinosaurs
But the idea of which a lot of people roll their eyes at is that Peter Quill visited?
Epcot Peter Quill, of course the famous Guardians of the Galaxy character Star-Lord for those of you have not seen the film
Is that he the not narrative of the ride is that he went to Epcot as a child
So that's it seems to indicate that the ride is gonna be very self-referential to Epcot Center itself
So there is people are speculating there's an opportunity to
Fit all the Epcot nostalgia from the 80s that you could possibly want in this ride
Which could either be really terrible or very fun because you get to like hear those songs again
You get to put like Horizons robots in the right like you could put everything in there and then the rest of the park just
Turns into IP potentially because potentially segment featured too great these days. Yeah
But does that I like that would the typical audience going we want a Guardians of the Galaxy, right?
I have any idea what I think going on if you get some Guardians animatronics in there and you make the ride go fast
Sure. Yeah. Yeah, I think it's just got a spin around in a circle. So people get a little dizzy
You hear a talking raccoon and then they can throw treats for weirdos like us
We're in the universe energy. We got to get out of here. What is this robot a drag purple dragon?
Get out of the way young Peter Quill. We got to get out. I gotta get old Peter Quill out of here
That's the other thing every every other Epcot thing was like three to five minutes long
And this was 45 minutes long like world of motion space of birth body wars. Everything was pretty quick
Like and in watching the ride throughs of these I like I stopped paying attention for massive stretches of time
That's one thing you can guarantee the Guardians of the Galaxy ride that replaces it will be like a tenth of the running time of the original
Oh, yeah, I would think so unless they really want to stay true to the spirit
Save the galaxy making a better world for me
There you go
That's probably that would be going to the top of the charts
So while we're still talking about the original one
Can we talk about the promotional Mickey and goofy explore the universe of energy comic book?
Yes, of course. I this I so we were trying to piece this together
Yeah, what because I think I had this growing up too and you said it was because they would hand this out
Outside the ride. Yes, they would give you this comic book like either at the
front of the ride or at the exit and I I
Still have a copy somewhere like this is probably the first comic book I owned like as a kid at like three or four years old
And it is pure propaganda
There's a cover where the Mickey and goofy are just pointing at the ride
Universe of energy presented by Exxon. It just says that on the front of the comic which oh, that's wait
I remember that the the famous that's why I know the Exxon Tiger. Oh
It's a bath from this comic. Yeah. Yeah, yeah Exxon Tigers walking down the road there
I liked this comic book a lot as a kid because before there was the internet there weren't a lot of ways to like
You know have a piece of Disney World in your home
It's why those the stockholder annual reports that I think of you as a kid
So I like it to look at like a really beautiful picture of the theme parks
it was this
Comic is cool because it has like animated depictions of the ride
But you beyond that it has a lot of weird scary oil
There's a crossword puzzle
Which has a little picture of Mickey and goofy doing a crossword puzzle and the crossword puzzle is on a big oil barrel
Like so bonkers to look at now stuff of dick Cheney's wet dreams
I would just look at this again and again as a kid probably before I could read would just like look at the pictures
And yeah
I I felt it a nice way to connect with the park in addition to our monthly Disney magazine the very dry
Yeah
Disney magazine yet, I don't know that we have Disney news
We got that and Disney adventures when I was yes, so you are the most we're not susceptible to propaganda anyway
So this oil thing so I mean the whole thing is like Mickey and goofy go through the
ride and
Mickey gives a lot of talking points about energy and then goofy
Goofy says like vaudeville jokes like goofy makes jokes
And I just wrote a note at a certain point that says goofy is a fucking menace in this
We're not taking our energy crisis seriously some sample dial with pieces of dialogue. Do you want to do?
Mickey what do you want to do? I can't do a great goofy. I can do pretty decent Mickey. I'll do goofy then all right
I'm ready for you. I'm mostly good my goofy is mostly just me saying gorsh
Okay, so Mickey starts here. No, I think goofy okay great
permafrost what's that gorsh?
It's a permanently frozen layer of ice and soil that can be thousands of feet deep
Wow, I bet no one is to worry about ice cream melting here yuck
So that's that's when like about halfway through this comic when I lost my well, there's also like
they're talking about how gas prices are going up and
goofy says
gosh, Mick that
Scares me a lot like yeah, this is your soil is getting scarce
Yeah, goofy, but it will help if we can find new sources of oil in our own country
This comic acknowledges the 70s gas crisis about like we can't
Great and we can always buy oil from foreign countries too. They're writing a camel riding in this panel
Sometimes we can't depend on other countries since 1973 our foreign oil supplies, but cut off
And it also did it out the the website I found this all scanned on scanned it in reverse order
So you're gonna be back together back together also you're passing by a very crucial panel
Yeah, so there is a panel where Mickey explains how Mickey and like a perca
pointing up to a map a map of Alaska that shows how oil goes from
Prudence Bay in northern Alaska to Valdez in southern Alaska
And you might remember Valdez from the being the site of the Exxon Valdez oil spill
only four years after this fun kids comic
There should be
Without issue or spillage to Valdez
There's no panel where Gooby's like why are you talking about all this stuff?
What? What got into you?
Oh yeah, here we go
There are they also talk about other forms of energy
There there sure are there's nuclear power in the future it can provide endless energy
Like this is right around three mile island, too. I think right
We love nuclear energy
CEO Rex Tillerson is doing a great job
So yeah, it's truly perverse this whole thing is perverse
It's very perverse
I mean look the drawings are great
They are do we know who did the art here?
I don't know it's funny
That's a whole interesting thing in Disney's history of like the Mickey and Donald and goofy like comics which
were popular in America because all the stuff with those guys are reasonably popular but in Europe like
They're huge like the Carl Banks and the Don Rosa stuff is like huge and are like
Which is why DuckTales has this like extra cult to it beyond the show
Like adventure, adventure story
Yeah, so but like a lot of those guys at the height of their creative peak were not like really given the credit
They they were due until like, you know many years later and they were forced to slave away on oil industry
propaganda
Yeah, I don't think this comic has any credits in it. It's like well no one wanted everyone knew what they were doing
As with branded entertainment, you don't want your name on it
Walt Disney Productions and a branch called Walt Disney Educational Media Company
Oh boy
Walt Disney Educational Media Company can be bought
Elsewhere in this comic also Mickey says makes a point of saying how coal will be around for a long time
And there's a general
Sentiment that runs through this comic as well as both iterations of the ride, which is solar power is a great idea
It's it'll be awesome. Once it's cheaper. That's what it's pushing like. Yeah someday we'll get to solar energy, but it's just
Yeah, you know
Look, it's cross-breed
Also wind is mentioned in the ride
But they didn't draw it in the comic and you'd think like giant windmills would be a nice little page of the comic
But like nope
Who cares?
That's for our children's children children to worry about
How are we gonna what if there's no wind it doesn't work?
What is this Holland fuck off
When you I did not I don't recall having this comic as a kid
I mean, I'm sure I went on this I have no memory also of going on this as a kid because it's obviously why would I remember
It yeah, but after you read this as a kid. Did you suddenly have an urge to pump gas?
Like help mom pump gas or something I remember
Only at Exxon
Only as long as it was at Exxon
We were a Sonoco family so we
We liked we were mobile we'd always go to mobile which eventually was obviously Exxon mobile
Yeah, mobile got a spin at sponsoring our favorite attraction the universe of energy
Well, you know, I guess well unless well anything else on the original iteration of the of the ride because while we're talking about the great
comedic possibilities that come from the combination of jokes and oil
Disney finally in the 90s went full-on comedy and transformed this dry ride the universe of energy into Ellen's energy adventure
Although it was originally called Ellen's energy crisis on the
Yeah, weird right? Jesus!
And then it was changed almost instantly like the day it opened they changed it with no explanation
Yeah, they were finally like a little honest about what was happening and then no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's an adventure
It's fun. I do like energy goof about I feel like some some evil scientists was there opening day and he was like
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, we got to change this. This is real. This is right. There is a new adventure
Too real, too real
No, not crisis. It's fun
Ellen's prescient verbiage
This opened in 96 and then the episode of her TV show that
Where her character comes out of the closet and shortly after she had come out of the closet happened in 97
Mm-hmm. Just a few months after and this was I think I was maybe talking about this when we had Mike Mitchell here the
One of the weird things about this ride. It is like
It is an Ellen who is several Ellens ago
It was before coming out of the closet which if you can name anything about the show Ellen besides her coming out of the closet
I'm very impressed. I like that is like the primary thing that happened on that show and this ride is like
Whatever Ellen was in the early 90s
It is pre talk show. It's pre dancing. It's pre Oscar selfie
Like none of the things we like she's changed her look entirely
Yeah, it's it's an Ellen that is like unrecognizable to the
the public at large
Yeah, it's it's it is a weird time capsule
If for that really like when I saw when I was there in August like I was watching this and it is like
You are there you are in 1996. There's no then there's no this has to be at this time
This is not timeless at all. Like no she the clothes she's wearing. It's kind of this like 90s wide
Butterfly collar that makes her look like one of the Roxbury guys
She is the third
Oh, yeah, she's got like a suit on at one point and then she's got the like
khakis red shirt like open blue Oxford like which I believe is what the animatronic is
Yeah, yeah, yeah, which so we've alluded to that this like mostly this was like
They replaced all of the movies in the ride
But you still go through the dinosaur kingdom just like you did in the previous edition
But with one big change there is an animatronic Ellen fighting a big snake monster
One of the strangest tableaus anywhere in Disney World and it was there and I mean, it's still there probably
But like up until this year you could have seen 90s Ellen fighting a snake monster. Although that like
I think they have trouble
I think they have to really pay attention with like the presidents when they make the decisions
For the Hall of Presidents, but like other modern celebrities
I feel like they've always struggled with and this Ellen is not particularly Ellen esque this robot
I wrote down that she looks kind of like Dr. Zayas
Sort of big like blonde mop and like white pants and a big tunic shirt
Celebrities they had the best
Luck with in the late 80s early 90s in terms of animatronics were like Humphrey Bogart and James Cagney because their faces are a little fucked up
Already so it's easier to mull when the robot melts a little bit. It's a dad's character. Yeah, like an attractive woman done via audio animatronics
Is there like like they did the witch in the great movie ride?
Judy Garland looks pretty good. Yeah, yeah Garland Ingrid Bergman. I guess both fair reasons. The Sigourney Weiner weaver. Did I call her Sigourney Weiner?
They messed up the robot. That's if you dress a dachshund like Ripley for Halloween. It's a Sigourney Weiner. And it's a viral sensation
Sigourney Weiner would get the dachshund would get invited on Ellen. I'm burning all over the place.
You just gave it away. You blew all the viral dough. Sigourney Weiner would be more popular than this podcast and like anything any of us ever do
10 million likes. Finally have something worth mentioning on our gravestone. Is she a dachshund dressed like Ripley from Alien?
Owner of Sigourney Weiner. Is Sigourney Weiner on fucking Dancing with the Stars this season with like Sean Spicer and Anthony Zapato Jr.
Fuck that guy. Man South Park said some really rude stuff about Sigourney Weiner. Whatever it's part of the zeitgeist I understand. Oh yeah.
They take on all. They take on all so nobody's safe. They're libertarians. Not Caitlyn Jenner and not Sigourney Weiner.
We may be burying the lead in terms of famous people in this ride because we mentioned Alex Trebek shows up. Also Jamie Lee Curtis as Judy.
Yeah the most maybe the biggest actress in this. Yeah major actress for Disney. But doing that thing where it's like a bunch of people are themselves and then one famous actor is playing a character which always kind of like drives me nuts.
Ellen's friend Judy who Ellen is watching Jeopardy and she gets bitter about it because her old college snooty friend Judy appears and knows everything about energy just because she's a scientist.
Yeah I don't know why she's so like Judy didn't do anything that bad. Like Judy just happens to be very smart. Yeah she certainly carries herself in a manner I understand you might be annoyed a little bit but Ellen didn't study science.
Ellen didn't study science. She didn't strike me as being like a villainous know at all. Not even a little bit. No she looks composed.
Ellen comes off very petty is what I'm saying. Yeah. And like yeah of course she knows. And she's watching her friend on Jeopardy from like the nicest apartment you've ever seen.
What's described as a New York loft that is just beautiful. It's a real winner of New York property. Like what do you have to be mad about Ellen?
Yeah this show establishes a universe where Ellen lives in this giant New York loft. Her and Bill Nye are neighbors. Her favorite show is Jeopardy and also Bill Nye comes over to borrow a bunch of stuff for an experiment.
I need some aluminum foil. And a candle and string and it's like wait he's a scientist but he's not prepared for his latest experiment.
There's some logic flaws. There's some logic flaws.
Well and they point out like he just walks in the door and then a separate Ellen pops up outside of the narrative to say you know how in New York everybody leaves their doors open.
Like why do you have to. You're deconstructing the thing you made that we're watching. Yeah.
There's a lot. I think that there's this could also this ride could also be just called like Ellen's adventure asides like Ellen's constant asides.
She takes a phone call during it and then hangs up on the person she's talking to.
Just like Bill Nye is like you know this is when the universe was birthed and she's like must have been a big delivery room. It's just like constant asides.
There's a side. Someday our oil supply might run out but Ellen's quips never will.
There's a very strange bit in this like after you go through the dinosaur scenes you go into a totally black room with a radio antenna and there's like a bit that's like morning drive time news radio.
But it's about the destruction and extinction of dinosaurs and Bill Nye chimes in every now and then. But what it really is it's a pitch black room that they didn't have to dress like it's a set they didn't have to build like all they needed was just this black room and this one graphic like this one like fake neon projection that's like a radio broadcast tower.
And you're listening to Chris Berman and I believe another ESPN anchor.
Is that right? Yeah it is a tie in to the other recently acquired Disney property ESPN.
Yeah this is a theme about like Disney animation there was kind of a golden age in the late 80s early 90s and then it gave way to this very unpleasant messy time.
And that's that's true in the movies and I think it's true in the parks and there was a lot of bad shit in the late 90s early 2000s where they're trying to jam ABC stuff. This is one of them obviously this weird hamfisted Ellen thing like all that when they tried to do when there was the soap opera bistro where you can take on the sets of your favorite soaps.
There was the live who wants to be a millionaire experience. That's right ABC mashup with the parks was such a boring disaster.
I found out something interesting recently the old stunt show at Hollywood Studios the lights camera or lights motor action.
Yeah. Which was a pretty cool show to like doing live car stunts and stuff that was originally pitched as a James Bond stunt show and the licensing didn't work out.
I think this came up on I think I'm probably stealing this from Jim Mills show. I feel like it's where I heard it. But it's like that would have been awesome if there was a full James Bond stunt show.
But they probably still would have bulldozed it to build Star Wars. Yeah I think at this point.
Huh. Crazy.
No they'd rather stick with properties like grace under fire and private practice stuff that's in house already.
The Louie Anderson sitcom. Oh yeah. Is that an ABC. Maybe.
Also don't forget that truly one of the biggest in the deepest dregs of attractions sounds dangerous with Drew Carey.
Oh yeah. Of course. They would cut your hair in the dark.
You sit in a dark room with headphones on and you feel like you're getting your hair cut.
That's all I remember about it. It's like maybe there were bees and then you got your hair cut.
Yeah there were two like good headphone gags they could pull off. Bees and haircut.
Which is why there was a brief time where if you went on the great moments with Mr. Lincoln attraction you'd put on headphones and pretend that you were Abraham Lincoln getting your hair cut.
Is that true. Yeah. What the fuck.
For only like a couple years. Really. Here Mr. Lincoln have a seat.
We'll transform the I will pan the audio around I'd imagine and post on this so you'll feel like you're getting your hair cut.
That's insanely messed up because back then getting a shaver a haircut was like taking someone's like taking your own life at risk because like if you got a cut and it got infected like you might just die from a haircut or a shave.
Yeah I mean they also did dental work too.
If Lincoln hadn't been shot he eventually would have gotten infected by a haircut.
A dirty haircut scissor.
A razor would have sliced his neck. He was going to have it at some point. John Wilkes Booth was just doing the hobbyist.
How many people died of dirty haircuts.
I don't know.
Was that an epidemic.
Tenth of the population every year.
Walter passed away this summer.
He had a bad haircut.
Dearest Juliana I'm afraid I will perish soon.
There's a CGI flyover in this ride too that has not that didn't age well.
What's what's up with that.
It's either before or after the dinosaurs. It's like soaring over a prehistoric world and it's very like Sega Saturn level 3D graphics.
That said there's one really I there's a great joke that I think it's a solid joke in in one of the Jeopardy sequences where like Jamie Lee Curtis is explaining to Alex Trebek like yeah Ellen used to be my college roommate.
Our nickname for her was stupid Ellen.
I think it's like a pretty funny non joke like like yeah I don't know. I'm amazed that made it in.
Yeah that's kind of nicely like clever in its non cleverness.
Yeah. Well so I mean the like not that you need to know the whole plot but basically Bill Nye comes over while Ellen is watching Jeopardy.
Then she has a dream sequence where she imagines being on Jeopardy and missing all of the questions that are all about energy.
Then she goes to see the dinosaurs and goes to see how solar power is not ready yet and that enables her to come back and win Jeopardy at the end.
Yes. That's what it takes 45 minutes to tell.
That's how it was pitched probably.
So I think it's a song with Jeopardy. I know Alex Trebek will probably let us in the studio.
Also we have not mentioned the fact that Michael Richards appears.
No lines. No lines.
Is he Einstein? He's a caveman.
Oh he's a caveman. There's also a wordless Einstein in the Jeopardy sequence.
And Ellen Cleghorn SNL cast member Ellen Cleghorn has a line. She's like a PA or a producer on Jeopardy at the end.
Oh. What really? I watched it.
Yes she's got one line.
Weird. Two Ellen's energy adventures.
But here's another thing about this ride. You're watching.
The first two or three minutes of it are just Ellen talking at you doing energy themed stand up.
And it is bombing. It is eating shit.
And Ellen is funny. I like Ellen.
Watching her be saddled with this bad material that has been dying every day for two decades at Disney World.
There is not a laugh in the entire thing if you watch any of the ride throughs of it until Michael Richards shows up.
Does kind of a half-assed Kramer getting burnt by the first discovery of fire.
And the audience loses it. Finally a laugh. 25 minutes into the whole thing.
Whoever's awake laughs.
Hopefully woke up others who are still asleep.
Yeah I think it goes to show that comedy in theme parks is tough.
Even if a line is funny once it will probably not be funny dozens of times.
And something as basic and simple as Kramer getting electrocuted is all you can do I think comedically in a theme park.
It's hard to because you have to pitch. You have to hit from 8 to 80.
You have to try and hit all demographics.
And lots of people who do not speak English.
There are people from all over the world at these parks.
So you can't really be doing flippant little jokes about 90's coffee shops.
Regional stuff.
I did watch one of the other Martin vids of the ride through for Alien encounter.
Which is one of my favorites.
I want to do that at some point.
But he had the original audio and when the alien breaks out of its container you can hear Disney put in some wild sound of stuff tourists would say.
That you think your fellow audience members are yelling out but it's clearly on the track.
And the alien explodes out of the thing and it's horrifying looking.
And someone goes what is that my mother in law?
That looks worse than your meatloaf honey.
That's another 96, 95 attraction I feel like.
I wonder if there were joke writers on staff for Imagineering.
Just your show show writers.
They're retired. They come into Imagineering one day a week to say mother in law jokes.
That's where all of the 3's company writers went.
All the Ropers writers was the only place they could get work for a while.
Energy themed jokes.
So when you're watching this or when I was watching it earlier it is again for as far as propaganda.
They're having so much fun talking about oil and offshore drilling.
And they're like did you know that one of these facilities that offshore drills is as tall as a building?
Like a skyscraper?
It's like wow can you believe it?
Goofy in the comic and Ellen in the ride fall into the same role about like oh what about this?
Could we do this? And Mickey and Bill die fall into the role of like calm the fuck down.
We can do it a little but not a lot yet please.
Okay? How many times do I have to tell you?
Look you're not a serious person Ellen slash Mickey.
Don't leave it to the experts okay?
Side note, Bill Nye when he's on these shows now arguing about climate change he's not doing a good job.
I don't know a lot about climate change.
I think he's eviscerating his opponents. I think he's devastating them. I think he's eviscerating them.
You're saying what headlines say and then I watch the clip and I go no that is not what just happened.
I say whatever Buzzfeed tells me to say.
Tucker Carlson just talked circles around him and embarrassed him. And I was like no this isn't helping.
If those two go up against each other the only way to know who wins is if one of their bow ties starts spinning.
And their head shoots up like a rock em suck em robot.
Both characters get a scientist on that actually has a master's degree in something. The guy's got like a bachelor's degree in engineering or something.
Come on why is he? He's an entertainer.
Yeah I haven't seen enough of them to know but he convinced many groups of tourists on the daily at Disney World to not invest in solar energy.
No I know. That alone should disqualify him. I'm surprised nobody brought that up on one of these Fox News shows.
Would have been a good gotcha. Yeah yeah.
We're saying though that like people like there's not a lot of last people aren't really like die hards for this ride.
But I started watching like one of the videos of like the final ride through of this ride and people were like talking along with the dialogue.
And that's when I went like oh nope like I can see if I was there. I'm sure I would have probably got like caught up in the fun.
Although the last ride of this I think was a walk off right. Like it stopped in the dinosaur.
The last ride ever of this ride broke down. Broke down. And the audience had to walk off of it.
But they let people like you know what you're here just take pictures don't touch anything but you can take pictures with the dinosaurs like take your time.
Like the cast members were also like you know into it too. Yeah.
And also no one cares what happens. So no one. There was not ultimately a final conclusion to the Jeopardy saga.
Yeah and I don't think anyone cared. I don't think that the audience was clamoring for the ride.
Could have broken every time. Like the search for energy. The story goes on.
There's no true conclusion.
There's no there's no last modern scene where it's like the answer is disgusting lithium ion batteries that will be in everything and never biodegrade.
Well so this this tale has come to an end.
Ellen's energy adventure due to be replaced by Guardians of the Galaxy.
A lot of fans don't dig this. This is people feel like this is a big betrayal of the Epcot Center model that to put IP intellectual property from the Disney movies into Epcot betrays the original vision of the park.
I don't care because this could be a good new ride maybe with old Epcot stuff.
I don't know. Do we. Is there anything to that. We are losing the educational component of Epcot. Does it matter.
No. Yeah no. I don't think so. I think the problem is this people will be mad at us for saying that.
But if you're certainly if I listen to other podcasts the party line is yes. Yes. But this is against the vision. And I like I love I I love Epcot so much. I love it.
Yes. They're wearing an Epcot shirt right now. Right now. I bought the Epcot prop at an auction. I've used the font and the aesthetic and a bunch of things I've done. I still am like as long as some of that aesthetic and vibe is around like take all the rides out like we need new better.
We need new better. We need new better rides. Yeah. The thing is like if they had kept up the original mission of Epcot like to make a futuristic like bleeding edge looking to the future park like sure I think I'd be more upset but you have to be constantly updating it.
You have to constantly be racing the future to do that. And at a certain point they're like well the 90s are here and it's not going to get much better than virtual reality and your phones might get cool soon.
Like that's at a certain point they were just like this is very calm anyway even if we don't just constantly keep updating.
There's no acknowledgement of like really recently future stuff like if you could if there was like a Hyperloop attraction or something like you go to Mars there's a self-driving car.
If you like this so there's so many like exciting near future things going on and none of it is represented in the park. Yes because we're talking about like touch screen phones maybe will happen one day.
So at this point if you're not going to keep up the future thing there's no exhibit about like public utilities start transit transferring electricity wirelessly like you don't need power lines anymore.
Like that's a thing that people talk about. Is that right. And I didn't know that. I think it's kind of hypothetical but like the next iPhones you can charge on a little mat.
You don't have to plug it in. So like that's a baby step towards that very easy to convey piece of technology as opposed to 45 minutes of rambling about energy.
That leaves me more confused about what energy is but also like do what like do what the ride the best rides do like pirates or Haunted Mansion or the original figment like give us a robot.
Give us a character that we like in a robot that's new. Give us some personality on the thing and like make a fun dark ride and the thing could last for 50 years. Yes.
Like if you're just presenting it like that like this like yeah this thing's going to have to go. Like this is so dry like people will people do will not miss this ride even like the test.
Like the last time I rode the test track update that like it's kind of like blue and looks like Tron and like you know it looks like the obstacles are like generated out of the computer out of nowhere.
Like I thought that was cool. Like that looks pretty good. Sure. I do think it's crazy though because I saw pictures from like the food and wine festival is going on in Epcot right now and it's like oh yeah.
The wonders of life pavilion is there and they just closed it like this just they didn't bulldoze it's all there and like they cleared out most of the stuff and they just kind of use it as like event space.
But it's like that whole pavilion did they shut that down after like 9 11 when attendance was like really low.
Is that when that happened. But it's like body world. I loved body world as a kid. I love the thing where you were like the brain of a 10 year old and like a Cranium Command.
Well that had characters. That's my point. Characters and personality. Body world was a thrill ride. Body world was like a Star Tours kind of simulator.
Like a great character Elizabeth Shoe the microbiologist. Oh yeah. Directed by Leonard Nimoy. Leonard Nimoy. Yeah. Remember that one at some point too.
But like you use care like fine use the Disney characters and yeah keep some of the idea of Epcot. But like yeah like that's better than what we have now. Jesus.
Like I was there in future world and it is bleak. It is a bleak situation. Just like our future.
The world is a disaster. Yeah another total disaster. Infrastructure falling apart. It's all laid to waste.
I mean if we were doing our scale of would you have plus it up would you. What was it again. Plus it up. We always forget this stupid scale.
Keep it as it is. Plus it up. Burn it down for the insurance money. I'm going to burn it down for the insurance money and build a whole new thing.
Like I'm a little worried that they're not destroying the building quite frankly. I think that's a thing. I think people like the rainbow colored building and I think people like the mural.
That's what people seem to be more sad about. The dinosaurs, the mural and the building.
At the very least build a giant like show building behind it to give us more room to give us some thrills baby. Let's let's get some fun because now as it is there's not that much room in there to kind of make a fun.
It could be a cool like slow moving dark ride which maybe that's what it'll be.
Well if that thing is the facade that that amazing entrance because I love that. I'd be sad if that went. I love that old Epcot architecture.
Sure. Yeah you open that up into a much bigger show building. Right now it's just two theaters and a tiny space for robots. So I would say like the only reason you would want to blow it up is just so we get more room for robots. More robots.
More robots you think? They have the rocket. People want robots. People want less screens more robots. The rocket animatronic is one of the best. Oh it's terrific. Yeah.
So I assume they'll make a duplicate of him a couple of him I'm hoping for this ride. Robotic versions of all the bands on the Guardians soundtrack. Robotic raspberries.
10cc in robot form. Oh man if Raga Raccoon could meet the singing animals from singing food from Kitchen Cabaret. That would be terrific. Oh wow yeah that would be great.
He'd probably eat him. He probably would. Look out peach boys.
There should also be a reference for no one. This whole show is a reference for no one. Oh pretty much yeah.
Hey if you get most of what we're talking about tweet at us and say I get it. You don't have to say whether you like it or not. Just let us know. I get it. I get it alright. Yeah carry on. Keep rambling fellas.
Anything else? Yeah I just I like the idea of the Guardians ride. I like it that this will be our little hopefully like our little place for nostalgia and then the rest of them just give us some new cool rides that just loosely tie into imagination or loosely tie into these original ideas.
And I think like you know keep up the because Epcot has like good merch like all the design stuff all the original Pavilion logo like they really have made an effort to bring back that kind of merch the last few years. Yeah.
People like that aesthetic. You keep some of that aesthetic around and add some bigger better rides and I think we're I think we're good. I think so. Do we all agree it's a I mean hopefully what they're doing to some extent is burning the ride down. Yeah that's what I'm hoping.
For we all want it burned. Dark fresh. Cool. Alright well we'll be right back.
Alright we're back with more Podcast the Ride and today we're going to introduce a brand new segment that we like to call animatronic of the month.
You know folks the entire theme park industry runs on the backs of unsung mechanical heroes the audio animatronics audio animatronics are forced to thanklessly perform the same tasks over and over again every day for absolutely no pay as opposed to the human
workforce at theme parks who perform the same tasks over and over every day for something kind of resembling pay.
The point is the theme parks would crumble without audio animatronics and today we'd like to shine a light on a random underappreciated robot somewhere in the theme park world.
What lucky animatronic will be the animatronic of the month. We're all going to highlight a different animatronic and then you all will get to decide who is animatronic of the month.
So so here we go with with my selection.
My animatronic hails from Pirates of the Caribbean. He's a fellow I like to call striped shirt pirate trying to get the key back from the dog.
Since 1967 striped shirt pirate has led an unglamorous life squatting in a dank cell begging to a high status canine.
His daily duties include whistling turning his head slightly and dangling a rope in his hands.
Never once in the history of the attraction has this robot glitched out lassoed a park guest and yanked them back into the water.
His bulbous cheeks suggest a white dizzy Gillespie and his striped shirt is timeless enough to be found either on a pirate schooner or at a modern J crew.
Since he can never escape his seaside jail today we salute this audio animatronic with a hearty.
I messed it up. I didn't quite get that whistle at trying to do the pirate whistle. Wait here I'll do it without the music.
There we go. Yeah that's the whistle that the pirate does in the ride. That's what I was trying to do.
Okay that's my that's my robot.
Fellas do you have your own robot selection. Yeah I'll go ahead. Great.
My animatronic hails from Splash Mountain at Disneyland and I'd like to give a hearty well done to the man sized dog sitting in a spinning robot.
Buddy not only are you large as hell you also sit perfectly still as that robot spins forever and ever.
And sure sometimes I get a bit of a sinister vibe from you. Maybe it was from the time I rode the ride and the robot wasn't spinning.
So you were just sitting there in the darkest part of the ride totally motionless.
And the fact that you're the size of the man is a little upsetting.
Or maybe it's like you remind me of the man in a dog costume from that one shot in the shining.
But whatever it is that robot spinning at a cartoonishly fast speed brings me back to the more innocent peaceful place I was.
That is the Splash Mountain Holler. So keep up the good work.
Man sized dogs sitting in a spinning robot in Splash Mountain.
Thank you. Thank you Jason. Beautiful.
Ready. I'm ready. Yes.
Sure. Ringo stars Sheila E and Max Weinberg are great drummers.
But what are they missing. The answer is the
answer is quite simple. They are not robots and they are also not stereotypical Italian pizza chefs.
My nominee checks all of those boxes. He is Pasquale P. Pieplate.
Drummer in Munch's Make-Believe Band. The band that performs at your nearest Chuck E. Cheese.
Whether he's making the sauce or providing a steady back beat. This mustachioed man always delivers.
You haven't lived until you've heard him play the skins on one of Chuck E. Cheese's famous songs.
Like the Bon Jovi parody of Wanted Dead or Alive titled Wanted Big Pizza Pie.
Or the parody of Aerosmith's Jamie Got a Gun titled Kids Are Having Fun.
Also Pasquale is an aspiring comedian. Aren't we all?
I salute you Pasquale P. Pieplate. My nominee for animatronic of the month.
This time I'll fade it out gently. Ah that was a relaxing little segment.
I hope you found it as such too. So we've had three nominees here. Let's recap.
We have Striped Shirt Pirate trying to get the key back from the dog.
We've got a man sized dog sitting in a spinning rowboat from Splash Mountain.
And Pasquale P. Pieplate. The drummer for Munch's Make-Believe Band at a Chuck E. Cheese restaurant near you.
The last name was news to me. I'm excited to know it.
Pieplate yeah. Born into a certain lifestyle with the last name Pieplate.
Background for it. Pasquale was discovered in the kitchen. He was drumming on the pieplates.
And Munch found him back there and then decided to put him in the band because he had such a great rhythmic.
He joined later like Joe Walsh joined the Eagles.
Not until Pasquale joined did it become a super group.
You know I feel like I have my winner in mind already but I don't want to tilt you the listener.
So here's how this is going to work. Go to our Twitter which is at podcast the ride.
We will set up a poll and you will determine who is the animatronic of the month.
Unless of course we forget to do any of this by the time this episode comes out.
Yeah so and if we do forget please yell at us on Twitter and we'll put it up.
And then we'll really know someone is listening to the show.
You forgot the poll. What else am I supposed to do with my day.
I was going to weigh all these options through with my significant other.
We nearly broke up in the argument that ensued trying to come to consensus.
Not realizing we could both vote individually.
No it's the road it should be the rowboat dog not the dog near the boat.
No the pirate is like ubiquitous it's a classic thing.
But the other one represents the old south.
What is this really about. What is this really about.
I haven't been happy in years. Oh there it is. There it is.
If you're interested in animatronics it's the only thing keeping us together and it always has been.
If our podcast was the catalyst for your breakup please let us know on Twitter.
Another thing to tweet us about.
Hey where else can people get a hold of us about things of this nature.
Oh you can email questions comments concerns at podcasttheride at gmail.com.
You sure can. So check out the poll. We'll post pictures of these robots so you remember who they are.
And hey follow us check us out individually at Scott Gardner on Twitter at Jason Sheridan and at Fat Carlson P-H-A-T-C-A-R-L-S-O-N.
The only one who did a thing that wasn't just his name.
So with that you have survived podcast the ride and we'll see you next time.
See ya. Bye.