Feral Audio.
Warning, the following podcasts may contain the shocking history of the boysenberry, a
thrilling journey into a right-wing freedom center, and a rip roaring discussion of Knott's
Berry Farm with guest Ryan Perez.
Trap in for Podcast the Ride.
Hello and welcome to Podcast the Ride, the podcast about theme parks hosted by three men
who once counted audio animatronics as their only friends.
Joining me today is Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
And the great Mike Carlson.
Oh great.
Wow.
He got a great arbitrarily change you a great and not Jason.
That's nice.
I thought they did make me feel like good.
Also, and as all the greats, that was the Larry King movie on my part.
You know call anyone great, like great Joey Budafuco.
It would be anyone he was talking to.
The great Will.I.Am.
The one and only Pol Pot is here.
He was being nice.
We'll trade it out.
I'll call you great next time and I'll call Carlson dirt.
Hey, we're a part of Feral Audio, home to Doughboys, Beyond Yacht Rock and many other
great podcasts.
Check out Feral Audio at feralaudio.com.
How's everybody doing guys?
What's going on?
Good.
I don't know.
Everything's fine.
No recent developments?
Anybody's dying to get off their chests in the world of theme parks or otherwise?
No.
I mean I just ate a big tuna sandwich and it's sitting weird with me, but other than
that everything's fine.
You've got a real roller coaster ride in your stomach.
Yeah.
It was like a big bread bowl basically and then there was tuna in it, but it was called
a sandwich, but it was weird and I ate all of the bread.
I ate every single piece of bread and it's bad right now.
It was good bread.
It was good Italian bread.
Oh, we all ate.
I was pretending we didn't eat.
I was keeping that secret.
No, but we all just ate together.
That's true.
So, well, we don't want to sell out the restaurant, but start poking around the Burbank area.
If you're in the Burbank area, see if you can guess what was the place.
I had a thing I wanted to address real quick because I'm not 100% sure when you will be
listening to this episode listeners.
As we recorded, it's early October.
It's the start of the Halloween season and I feel like we should mention a lot of theme
parks go all out with the haunts, Halloween Horror Nights at Universal, not Scary Farm.
We are three men who do not like to be scared, right?
Yeah, we don't do the haunts, do we?
We're not haunt people.
I think this might be true of our guest as well if I know him.
Our guest is-
He doesn't like a good spook.
Our guest is Ryan Perez.
He's a great writer and actor.
The great Ryan Perez.
He's great.
Let me ask, do you like to be spooked, Ryan?
This is a very odd way to-
Yeah, we didn't really build you up.
We gave you no credits.
Who is this guy?
Yes, I mean immediately I'm a pussy before anything.
First you know him as a pussy.
No other achievements.
Do I like the spooks or not?
I don't really love these, what are they, not scary farm Halloween Horror Night kind
of things.
Like teens jumping out at you to be, yeah.
No, I've only been to one which was the Queen Mary.
I think they still do it.
They would retrofit their boat to be a haunted boat and then on the grounds of the Queen
Mary they would have various horror mazes and things.
I found the whole thing very stressful.
It's very cheap.
It's a very cheap thrill.
I don't care for it.
Anybody can jump out from behind a thing and scare you.
It is pretty true and hiring a teenager at minimum wage is probably literally cheaper
than building an animatronic or some kind of machine to blast smoke or fog at you.
The thing that's weird to me is that people love it.
It's beloved.
This is the most popular time for all of these things is people go there just to get a teenager
to jump at them.
But they also want to be part of the twisted mazes going to the world of Guillermo del
Toro.
It does seem like those Universal Studios, I don't go to them really, but they are supposedly
good experiences for horror film nerds.
I don't think it's like they aren't like chintzy sellout-y experiences.
They make a good set.
They make the set look very authentic to whatever the IP is.
They have a shining maze this year that looks great.
That's an interesting idea.
I think they should do a mother, a Darren Aronofsky's mother horror house where the
whole thing is a metaphor for the destruction of our planet.
Is that what it is?
And the patriarchy's religious control.
Scarier than any scar-ector.
We live in a constant horror maze.
We live in a horror maze.
It's a horror maze about me and how I use my girlfriends and throw them away after they've
given me all the artistic validation I need.
Is it a very personal statement on Mr. Aronofsky's part?
It's the darkest part of his psyche?
It's a very personal...
This movie, I should just have a podcast just talking about mother.
I'll talk to these Feral Audio guys after that and see if I can have just one podcast.
It's called Exclaimin' About Mother.
Every week I have a different person talking about mother.
Mother has many different kinds of themes in it.
An environmentalist theme, a sort of religious allegory, and a statement about artistic inspiration.
And they're all pretentious, all three of them.
One mild theme.
Universal this year also has one maze called the Horrors of Blumhouse, which is the production
company that makes horror movies.
So it's got me.
So it's like a get out move.
Their company is a codified Pixar.
You get a little of the purge, you get a little sinister, and a little bit of Happy Death
Day.
What?
The upcoming Happy Death Day.
Oh, so it's a tease for the movie Happy Death Day.
But no get out.
That's their big hit.
I don't think they could do a get out now.
Little touchy.
It's a bit...
Oh, I want a sunken place ride.
That would be great.
Jordan Peele went in and pitched the ride and then somebody clinked on a glass and his
ideas were not even...
I guess they'll be in all right now.
Never mind, it was a dumb idea.
There is an actual discussion on the Horror Nights Twitter account of someone going, why
didn't you make a get out house?
And did they respond to that?
They did.
One of the Universal creative people were like, I need you.
All right, I'm going to try to be very nice about this.
I need you to think about what that movie was about and then think about why we didn't
do that.
That we couldn't do a house based on a...
Who is the person responding?
This doesn't sound like the official PR account of Universal Studios.
It was one of the creative people.
I don't know who exactly, but they were just like, we could not.
The movie is a Rachel...
We can't do that.
We're glad you enjoyed the movie, but we could not make a haunted house.
That would be very inappropriate.
Well, can we send the get out gang on a new adventure where they're running away from
more conventional villains like skeletons and goblins?
Get out meets Freddy.
This time goblins were trying to sell me as a modern slave.
Let me ask this, are all the mazes in one Blum house?
Is there a Blum house?
I don't know the answer to that.
Okay, probably not.
So it's probably, the Blum house is not a real house is what I guess what I'm asking.
I hope it's like, because at the Disney studios in Florida, you can go into a recreation of
the Pixar campus.
It looks like the Emeryville campus of Pixar.
So if they made it look like whatever the production bungalow is of Blumhouse honoring
the famous Blumhouse headquarters.
Just like a harried intern answering phones.
Palettes of Diet Coke everywhere.
Are you here for the haunting?
Okay, well, just have a seat.
You get to take a general at one house.
The scary thing and then they tell you they'll call you and they don't.
The real world is full of horrors.
Blum house doesn't like your pitch.
I'm so sorry.
The on tap cold brew machine is not working today.
I'm sorry.
Well, Mike, you had some business with the horrors of singer songwriters.
That was a good Byron Allen transition.
So Mike, I understand you've got some complaints about what you've heard lately.
So your father used to give you a whooping, right?
No, it was the one where he was like, so John, I understand you're getting older.
I said that to John Lovitz, I think.
I understand you have some observations about the difference between men and women.
For anyone who doesn't know, there's a show called Comics Unleashed hosted by a man named
Byron Allen and it's just they end up stealing their material and that's the way he transitions.
If you like your comics leashed, do not tune in.
Comics Unleashed also, you'll just be watching it like I was watching it the other night
and like Robert Schiml, like a dead comics will just show up on him.
There'll be four dead comedians.
These guys have any great Geraldo.
Mitch Hedberg, you have a story about coupons.
Any young men.
I guess he's alive. I thought he was dead.
You had a soft shoe to do, is that correct?
Hey, Mort Sahl, what's in the newspaper today?
Anyway, enough about Byron Allen.
So, yeah, so my buddy and I were at California Adventure and we're at the line.
So Cars Land is a land dedicated to the successful franchise of Cars,
where the Cars talk in case you have not seen these.
It's Mater and Lightning McQueen and kids like it.
We all probably agree we like Cars Land better than we like the movies.
Cars Land is wonderful. The movies are fine.
So in line for the big ride called Radiator Springs Racer,
they play old timey music, rock and roll country stuff.
And it's not it's like real old. It's not like new old stuff.
It's really old stuff.
Yeah, but sounds like a little bit.
Everyone's in like a little box. The recordings are all bad.
And the one song which I've heard before in pieces,
we were sitting there and we heard it and we were singing the chorus of it.
And then we looked and we found the whole song.
And it's a song by Bob Wills and the Texas Playboys and it's called Roly Poly.
And I'll play here.
You can hear it sounds old.
And it's I can't believe this was I think this was like a popular song.
I think it's a banger.
Alright, so here.
We'll get after the piano comes out. Oh, wait, there's a whole intro.
Now we're all up and dancing.
We can't focus on some point you got.
Oh, no, the fiddles coming in.
I really planned poorly for this.
Trash can full of stones they're going to rotate.
The
the
long as he can chew it.
It's OK.
He can eat an apple pie and never even bat an eye.
He likes everything from soup to hay.
Roly poly daddy's little daddy.
All right, so
that should give you an idea of what the song the song is.
Best I can tell is about a man admiring his son is chubby son.
And the chorus is the roly poly daddy's little fatty.
But he's going to be a man someday.
And it's just like talking about how much his son is eating.
While he's doing chores on a farm.
Not a bus going on a biscuit, hungry every minute.
Roy, he can eat an apple pie and never bat an eye.
And then the second verse is like scrambled eggs for breakfast bread and jelly 20 times a day.
I mean, it's it's weird.
I mean, it's a man who wrote like a pop song about his son overeating.
But it's not a fat shaming song.
No, he's admiring it. Yeah. Yeah.
I think without this song, without Mike Huckabee's father writing him this song,
he wouldn't have achieved the success that he has in life.
That wouldn't be a shock if it was like, oh, did you know that was written about Mike Huckabee?
I'd be like, oh, yeah. Oh, of course. OK.
And then Huckabee got to sing it to his two large sons.
Yeah. Right. Right. He got to clang it on the bass.
Fox and Friends or whatever the hell show he plays.
I learned to jam. I jammed on. Oh, he plays on a Huckabee.
Oh, my text. Oh, yeah.
Don't yank that cord out. I had it muted. I forgot.
It's the Bob Willis and the Playboys estate.
They're shutting us down.
When somebody plays one of my songs, a little fat angel gets his wings.
Good luck carrying little fatty around.
Those wings are going to work overtime.
I don't think I'd ever heard Daddy's Little Fatty in like a pop culture reference.
There's like one Adventure Time or something.
I think Ice King calls one of the penguins Daddy's Little Fatty at one point.
Yeah, I don't know if that's an expression, but we were listening to it because most of the songs are just about
most of those songs in the line are just either about like rock and rollin or driving a car.
And then there's this one we were like, what the hell is this?
Is it mostly country music in Cars Land or is it tough?
Well, it's outside in Cars Land, I think it's more rock and roll, 50s rock and roll.
And then when you're in the line for Radiator Springs, it's more like country, old time country or like standard type music.
I think it goes a little bit even. It's like older music in line for Radiator Springs.
But it's very specifically chosen and they really went after what they do.
I guess really pay attention because there must be some maybe some other weird songs,
weird old timey songs that are playing in that line.
Women should stay in their place.
They're like, all right, get on the car, get on the ride.
And you're like, what was that? No, no, no.
Don't worry about that.
You don't have enough time to register.
Sending a subliminal message from the 40s to get me to re-adhere to traditional value.
Hey, well, from one song, one cool jam to another, I'm going to transition us into today's topic with a spirited song.
Take you back to 1986. And here we go.
Can I leave? Can I do it?
For the discussion.
The door is locked from the outside.
And the man who's easily frightened, who wanted to talk about the place from which that song came.
There's a YouTube channel. You can find several employee morale building music videos such as that was my favorite.
We love the farm. There's also a what I like about knots.
So check those out anyway.
Hey, today we're loving the farm here with Ryan Perez, who you know, you have some some particular childhood affection right around.
You're probably going there. It all went away.
You love it.
I take it back.
You might admit you could be potentially in this video somewhere.
You could have been at the park and unaware.
That's true.
1986. You might be on the merry-go-round.
I'm looking at right now.
You're on an ostrich going by.
Yeah. So you grew up.
Because you grew up in Orange County and wait in Laguna, Laguna, Nogale or Laguna.
Yes. Yeah.
So you're the well near Disneyland, but also very near near the Knott's Berry farm.
Yeah. What's your what's your what's your relationship with with knots?
Well, that's I've always liked because it's kind of number two.
Like in this, I guess it's maybe it might be number three, actually, I think, by universal in Southern California, actually, because Magic Mountain, I think, is also more.
So Knott's is coming in at four.
Actually, that's might be the worst part in the country, with the exception of like Action Park or whatever.
Or people.
Traction.
But it has like such a huge.
I'm just so in my heart, it's number one.
I really like Knott's more than any other.
And growing up, so much of that of my memories of this of Knott's and really all these Southern California parks have to do with my parents and my mom in particular lived out here.
She's originally from South Carolina, but moved out here in 10 and lived in Anaheim.
And so she has these memories of Disneyland as a young woman and going there when it was sort of when you didn't have to pay and you would buy tickets to individual rides and everything.
So she has those memories.
Her and my dad would go see bands at Disneyland.
This is like in an era when jazz bands and big band Count Basie and Woody Herman and these kinds of Duke Ellington would play there.
Yeah, they got really legitimate.
And there's no admission.
I didn't think about that.
So they used it just as a bandstand.
Yeah, at the Carnation Plaza.
And so so much of growing up.
These are the kind of stories that I would hear about like, yeah, Disneyland used to be.
We just go there and dance.
You know, it was not like you can still actually there's a place for it still.
It's a tiny place where like old people go and some young people to swing dance at Disneyland at night.
Yeah, they tried to move it to downtown Disney.
And I think it happens there sometimes, too.
But then they eventually brought it back to the park.
There's a little area.
There's a little area out of the way where they let you swing dance.
Anyway, and yeah, that's I mean, it's still I guess it's still sort of in the heritage of the park.
And then my mom was also a she was a hostess at a restaurant called Shake Harry, which used to be an orange or in Santa Ana.
And it was sort of one of Southern California, really one of Orange County's like only five star restaurants, a very high quality restaurant.
And there was a lot of celebrities that would come in.
John Wayne and Lucille Ball and Walter Knott would come in as well.
And so she sort of had that, you know, time waiting on Walter Knott.
And then of all places in the world, when my parents got married in 1970, they got married at the Church of Reflections at Knott's Berry Farm,
which is a little chapel that sits inside of the park.
And if you go there, it's still there. People still get married there to this day.
But the park was very different back then.
It was sort of like in the four wedding photos that my parents have.
One of them is them in the Church of Reflections getting married and then one of them is feeding chickens.
It was like, oh, well, it's a fun place to get married.
You go to the chapel and then you feed the chickens and then we'll go home.
Like it was that kind of situation. I don't even know if they had rides. I think they probably had a ride or two.
They were maybe starting to around then.
But they also, yeah, they didn't have an admission for a very long time.
And it sort of came out of this tradition of like it was like a like a roadside stop.
They really started as a farm and they added this restaurant and started adding this like old west calico ghost town kind of stuff
just to give people something to do while they waited for the endless line.
Like this chicken dinner restaurant, the line would build up for three, four hours and let's give people something to do.
And so it really like very organically became a theme park and not really a premeditated.
And it still shows to this day that it's sort of this weird mishmash of like, oh, then this grew and then we did this and this.
And it's sort of all over the place, but it still has all this old stuff.
So it's a very like interesting like time capsule.
Yeah, the old west vibe is still very much there.
And back when I was going to it, mostly in like the early 90s as a as a, you know, whatever, middle school kid or whatever,
we would take a middle school trip and that would be the graduation trip.
Also, not had like a crazy deal in maybe 1994 or 95 where it was like fifteen dollars a person after three or four p.m.
So like during the summer, we would go multiple times.
My family would go multiple times. And so much more so than Disneyland.
That was the place to go.
And then also it wasn't a particularly popular park.
So you could just get on the log ride or whatever and ride it over and over and over again.
And I mean, there were just no lines for anything.
And so in a way, it felt like having your own little park or whatever at certain times of day.
You would go there like on a late August day and and, you know, have the park to yourself almost.
It's still pretty affordable compared to other.
It is like I think the tickets vary price wise by season.
But like if we went down tomorrow, I think it's like forty five dollars to get it.
And it's one of those were like you give us 80 bucks.
You can come in whenever you want for a year. Oh, yeah.
Like whatever you want. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like because it's they want they want people there.
Yeah. Which I think is nice.
It is an unfortunate thing about Disneyland that it's getting more and more and more expensive.
And now there's add ons to get you like more better access to the rides.
It really is becoming, you know, yeah, it's so insane for a giant family to go to Disneyland.
So for there to be like a fun local place that is not bank breaking, I think is cool.
And it's unique in the history of theme parks and that like both Disney and Universal were made by movie companies, you know,
made by movie companies featuring their properties.
And this, like you said, Scott, was a roadside attraction that just grew and grew and kind of evolved into a park.
And has never really retained any kind of property other than peanuts, which has that association with.
But that I think is because of Cedar. It's owned by the Cedar Fair Company now, which runs Cedar Fair and in Pennsylvania,
Dorney Park and a bunch of other parks around the country.
And I think a lot of those parks have the the peanuts characters.
But I think peanuts were first. They now have under that general license.
The peanuts also it was a Camp Snoopy is the peanuts area.
And it used to be Camp Snoopy in the middle of the Mall of America as well.
I'm not sure how affiliated those things were, but two big two Camp Snoopy locations in odd places.
I've been I mean, we went Scott Ryan and we were there once and we saw.
This is the last time I was there. This is about three years ago.
OK, because it was there was an ice show. It was a peanuts ice show.
Snoopy on ice. Yes, Snoopy on ice.
One of my greatest memories is Snoopy at the very end dancing to Opa Gangnam style.
That's like my platonic ideal for entertainment.
Yeah, this was very disappointing because I had never seen Snoopy on ice.
And I thought, oh, it'll be a you'll go see Snoopy on ice and it'll be Vince Guraldi music.
And it'll sort of have the like it'll be like an ice show that has the sweet feeling of a Christmas special.
It was the most obnoxious thing I've ever seen.
I believe one of the routines was set to the Sugar Ray cover of Abracadabra.
And then there was like maybe a weird Al song or like was Eated in there or something or there was a food.
There was a whole kitchen section. But it was just like humans.
Snoopy was the only one who was a character. He was the only one on ice.
Just local talented ice dancers.
And like we were sitting in the front row and we were getting hit by like just the spray, the ice spray in the face.
Did you ever see did you ever go to a park that had Star Trek on ice?
What? That was in. What the hell?
Kings Dominion, another Cedar Faroe Park now was one of the Paramount branded parks in the 90s.
And a lot of these regional parks, for whatever reason, yeah, they tend to have ice shows, I guess, because they're cheaper than stunt shows.
To make you just need some ice skaters. What was the narrative of that?
I cannot remember, but there was definitely. Oh, that's well, that makes a lot of sense.
I think they played this music. They played the Star Trek music like like you would think,
like you thought with the Vince Garaldi music would play with Snoopy.
This was like the next generation. Next generation was on at the time.
Oh, there's probably a video of this. We got to do a whole thing on this.
What were the characters? Were the characters like Picard was Picard on ice?
I think it was like generic crew members and then maybe some cling.
I think there were two Klingons did like a mating ice skating ice.
I don't think I'm making this up.
We'll come back to this. We'll come back to this.
That's what like people outside the thing said when they looked at the marquee. Klingons ice skating.
Now this I got to see. Yeah. God, that does sound really awful and great.
The other thing that Nats has right now that's like an IP is Elvira is doing a Halloween show.
I saw that. She's been doing it for many years.
Last year, I believe. Little kids out there. Is this the last year?
I think maybe. We know you love Elvira.
You're clamoring for more Elvira. Every I don't know.
My little niece, 10 years old, she says, I want Elvira.
Where do we go to see Elvira? I go, there's a place. That's Mary Farm.
Where do we see her do what Elvira does? You know, Elvira's act.
Yes, this it's like an old cabaret act essentially.
I haven't seen it in a long time. She tells jokes, I think.
I think it's like the Bill and Ted Halloween special.
The thing they did at Universal. Are they still doing it in Florida? Is that right?
This is the last year of the one in Florida.
All these special Halloween shows are ending.
I can't be the real actress that plays Elvira. It is.
Yes. So she does shows. Yes, she does like five shows in a week.
She like lives in Buena Park for the Halloween season.
It's like a cabaret residency.
It's interesting at Halloween that there's an exclusive place you can see Elvira.
I like it. All kidding aside about Elvira, it's pretty cool that Elvira's down in Buena Park for a month.
That's great that she just has a residency for a month. That's terrific.
Now that you know it's not a regional Elvira.
So weird knockoff Elvira on all the cedar points. There's a different young girl playing Elvira.
No, that wouldn't be fun. You would see right through that.
The real cleavage. I don't know anything about Elvira. That seems to be a big...
Elvira was, that was her thing. She was sexy. She was sort of a sexy vampire. I think Vampira sued her.
Yeah, yeah. She stole Vampira's gimmick supposedly.
Are you the Groundlings? Yeah, she is. Because she's in, the actress is in, what's her name?
Cassandra Peterson, I believe. She's in Pee-wee's Big Adventure.
That's right.
And there's a moment, my memory of Elvira, I might be wrong about this, but it was like
as a little kid staying up to watch Saturday Night Live, sometimes it would be, my two memories,
it would be like preempted because of wrestling, which was a bummer,
which because I was not a wrestling watcher, and also preempted because Elvira would sometimes come on.
I feel like, you'd be like, what's Elvira doing?
I saw, I think up until a couple years ago, she had a show still out at midnight on NBC or whatever channel,
and it would just be like Mystery Science Theater, but maybe a tenth of the jokes.
And I literally mean to say, she would play a minute of the movie, and it would be like a Wolfman,
and a little circle would appear, and Elvira, and she'd be like, this looks like my last ex-boyfriend.
And then the circle would close, and then it would be a minute, and then another minute,
and then she would come back in with another joke.
Oh, she would host a movie.
She would host basically like a bad movie.
Like a Ghoulardy or a Joe Bob movie.
Yeah, so it was the same kind of horror movie host gimmick, but it seemed like there was,
they just probably had like 30 of them, and they would just put these in different movies,
and they were the most generic, because she was literally like, my ex-boyfriend, huh?
And like rolled her eyes.
And it could be any weird looking thing or guy.
I don't know that that's true, but it felt like it.
It felt like they were so not specific to whatever I was watching.
The production value sure is hokey of what's going on behind you.
Yeah, whoa.
What generic comments to comment on an old movie?
That's like a reverse dream on.
That's like if you put dream on in a thing that made it go backward,
it would be watching an old movie with contemporary comments that don't apply to it necessarily.
I figured it out.
Wait, what channel was Dream On on?
Was HBO Dream On?
Yeah, that was HBO.
So this would be on OVH.
Oh, you got to watch a Dream On.
That's when Dream On is one of those HBO shows that like HBO Go or Now has disavowed.
What was it?
I don't think it's in the collection of old shows that you can pull up on HBO.
But I mean, what happened on?
I thought I knew what it was, but I can't picture it now.
Dream On?
Oh.
Dream On was about a guy who, hell, it was Brian Ben-Ben was the guy.
And the idea was that as a kid, he'd watched all this old television.
And so as he's going through his daily life, dating and troubles at work or whatever,
it would cut to clips from old TV shows to punctuate what was going on.
So he's in bed with a woman and he's having a hard time getting the bra off or whatever.
And then it would cut to an old movie where a guy's trying to defuse a bomb or something.
And that was how the show worked.
Could it be a rights issue?
Oh, probably. That's true. Yeah, that's true.
Oh, maybe.
Do they have like their old horny shows and stuff?
Like the Real Sex, do they have all those or whatever?
I think they have like one or two Real Sexes, but not the entire collection of Real Sex.
Also maybe a rights issue.
That's true.
Real Sex is so funny because it was like Real Sex 57.
Let's just make it a series.
Why are we doing Real Sex 1 million bajillion, gajillion?
Yeah, they have to keep three numbers.
Like Chicago albums.
Roman numerals.
I'm jumping around and order things a little bit here, but this kind of dovetails into...
I found a YouTube oddity of a weird cable show that seemed to be a cable show that was on,
but it could have been like a presentation and there were just clips from it.
It was just cut up into parts.
But there was a show called Dinosaurs that was hosted by Gary Owen from Laugh-In.
Is that right? That's who Gary Owen is?
He was the announcer.
But there was a show about dinosaurs where they explored the modern fascination with dinosaurs
and went to weird road stop places that have dinosaurs, like the place on the way to Palm Springs.
And there was a...so I found a clip of Gary Owen and the other host going on this ride,
Kingdom of the Dinosaurs, which is a dark ride, a sadly departed dark ride that Nutsberry Farm used to have.
And you can watch it. It's not an edited segment of him on the ride.
It is just raw footage pointed at the host and you don't really see what's around him too much.
And you can hear the director in the other car giving ideas of lines and things for him to say.
So you'll hear some mumbled thing and then Gary Owen will repeat it back,
such as they pass by like a big lava flow, something that looks real hot.
And Gary Owen says, I'll have my filet medium rare, please.
Oh, that's a line.
That's good.
And then later they pass by a particular animal and Gary Owen says,
Oh, look at the saber toothed executive.
This sounds like whatever director was feeding him lines.
This sounds like Scott Gardner's dream job.
Sounds like everything you're mentioning this because you want to see if there's a contemporary example of this.
So if any aspiring sizzle reel creators out there are...
There's an 80 year old announcer that you can feed lines to.
Like, oh, looks like my mother-in-law.
Wait, yeah, lines about theme parks through a voice that I can do very readily.
I rode Kingdom of the Dinosaurs a bunch because it was one of those rides with no line.
If you went to the park in like 1994, no line.
And I had my little sister Carly at the time, she was four or five years old,
loved dinosaurs and so we would jump on that ride.
And it was a good ride.
Can I ask, was it a slow moving ride?
Yes.
Someone who grew up in Orange County and used to go to knots a lot told me once
that there is a ride at knots that teenagers would go on to make out like a tunnel of love kind of ride.
And I think it might be the dinosaurs ride because it was dark and slow.
I've heard about teenagers making out before.
I don't know about this.
I don't know about teenagers.
It was definitely slow enough.
Every ride at Knotsbury Farm is slow.
The Calico Mountain thing is slow.
The log ride is slow.
I can't think of one that's not slow.
The train, which by the way gets robbed.
Have you been on the train during a robbery?
You know, I haven't actually.
I forgot that they did that.
Oh, it's great.
I think this is in many ways, I think the train at Knots is better than the train at Disneyland.
A robbery.
There's a robbery.
They should brand it to be like an assassination of Jesse James by the Calico Mountain Ford ride.
I saw a video of that too that had a great theme park joke where one of the cowboys is pointing out people on the ride.
Like, yeah, I know all these people.
There's Billy Sue, there's Billy Joe, and there's Billy Goat.
Sorry sir, I didn't mean to.
Good, clean fun.
I like jokes like this.
I feel like everyone laughed a little earnestly at that, right?
Yeah.
Good for that cowboy.
There's a lot, like with Knots it does feel like, because they do like a whole old west town, there's a lot even more like characters.
People in character.
You'll talk to the sheriff in front of the jail.
There'll be a guy in a rocking chair that'll razz you as you walk by.
There's a little more interactivity than there is at Disney, I feel like.
One of the great Knots attractions is, and I believe it's still there, but this was a family tradition growing up, is there is a jail cell with a wooden carved character in it who's called Sad Eye Joe.
And you can go up to the, my parents knew the trick where you can go up and talk to the guy that does the voice beforehand and give him information.
And so we went, I remember one time going with my little sister and my mom goes back there and gives him information and then through the little thing he says, hey, how you doing, Carly?
How's your brother Ryan?
And how's first grade?
I heard that you're here for da da da da.
And it blows the kid's mind because Sad Eye Joe knows everything about the kid.
It's like one of the great, I mean, imagine being a little kid and that happens.
It's terrific.
Yeah, you wouldn't be able to put it together.
That's really magical.
It's like a Santa Claus type experience.
How did they know?
That's pretty neat.
There's a wooden character who is no longer at Knots that I found in one of those, if you go to Barnes and Noble, there's like a sepia tinted book that tells you about the history of a local area.
Oh, the historic images of the world of America.
And I found one for Knots Berry Farm and they had a local character who I can only assume they have retired who is Wing Li, the Chinese laundry man.
Oh, no.
He had a sign on his laundry display that says, no, no Tiki, no Shirtie.
No Shirtie.
I thought the phrase was no Tiki, no laundry.
That's the phrase I've heard.
This was Tiki and Shirtie with double E's.
So bad on you for that one, Knots.
Although I have also seen some touting of the fact that they do acknowledge the role of Chinese Americans in building the railroad.
Like they like there are Chinese robots on those rides on the on the mine.
I guess that's good.
I think I saw a site that claimed that that was good.
So I will go along with that and say that it's good.
There is also Knots is also home to dioramas, right?
Of all the missions in California.
Am I imagining?
I can't remember that.
I feel like I heard they started putting those back in.
Full disclosure, I have never been to Knots Berry Farm.
Oh, my God.
I want to go down there.
And this is all just making me even more excited to see all this.
You would really love it.
And I you'll never come back.
I love chicken dinners.
Knots also where they originally grew boysenberries.
They're famous for that.
Yeah.
Well, we should talk about the man who started it all.
The man, the myth, the legend.
And it's not your mom's friend.
Did you get anything out of it?
Like what's do we know about the guy?
Oh, no.
They came into the restaurant with his wife and they were all very courteous.
Cordelia.
The lovely Cordelia.
Who cooked all the chicken dinners herself.
She really is to blame.
She's not the right word.
She should get the credit.
There you go.
The positive word for for kicking off the whole thing, because it really was though they had a successful farm, it was the chicken dinners that caused this influx of people to come in and ultimately grew the place into a theme park.
And she's still like through the 70s.
If you went and got a boysenberry pie there, it was very possible that Mrs. Knots made it herself.
Wow.
That would be amazing to get a Mrs.
Knots one that she touched with her hands.
She says Knots touched this pie.
I didn't really.
I don't think she signed it in some way.
If she could like kind of autograph the crust.
She had a signature way that she would decorate the crust perhaps.
Mrs. K.
So I didn't know this, but Walter Knots teamed up early on in his farming career with Rudolf Boysen and they created the boysenberry.
Oh boy.
That wasn't a thing that existed.
I heard this other version of it where that's kind of clunky or more confusing where a guy is he like he knew of this guy Rudolf Boysen, who was the head of parks in Anaheim and said, I heard you tried to make a berry and it didn't really work out for you.
And he said, oh, I just got a couple of vines of it left here.
You take them, see if you have any luck.
And then it flourished for some reason at Knots, which that seems like I'm worried that that's a cover for like he stole the berry.
Yeah, that seems like he stole the berry.
If that's what that's what did you I mean mine is just some Wikipedia.
Mine is probably a website that got it from Wikipedia.
Sure.
We're all just using the same barely sourced material.
We need you guys need to go like talk to the farmers.
You get out there in the field and get actual information.
The definitive berry theft.
Who made the expose.
Let me throw another one in too, which is that it's possible that Boysen originally got it from a guy named John Lubin and that he called them Lubinberries.
And that and whatever. Maybe this was just a chain of lies on Wikipedia or wherever I saw it.
But that Lubin might have taken it from Luther Burbank, who is the founder of Burbank founded the very city we're in right now.
So there's a lot of weird stuff going on with the history of the boys and bearing.
Oh, my Lord.
Yeah. Yeah. Huh.
Not clear. I like this kind of old timey fight, though.
Like, you know, if we were all fighting one day about like, no, it's the Carlson Berry.
No, Jason stole the Carlson Berry from him.
You'll never prove that old boy.
The Sheridan Berry.
It just sounds better to the ear.
We've given the public what they want.
Nobody nobody would buy a Carlson Berry barf.
We should all wish that we could be so successful to have a berry.
And to have a tangible skill such as cross breeding berries to get.
What is that? How do you do that to begin with?
That's a very good question.
Yeah. I don't know.
When you go to wineries and you start with they start explaining how they make the wine and you get bored immediately.
Just want the wine samples.
Yeah. Coppola does it.
He's out there.
Does he explain it to you?
I'm making grapes.
I got the best grace.
Sophia, come try these grapes.
I don't want to direct movies anymore.
No, I just want to play with grapes.
I was thinking about putting a red grape and a white grape together.
It came out gray. Who would have thought anyway?
Walt are not famously friends with Walt Disney.
They would visit each other's parks and steal each other's ideas.
It's unclear if they were like because some people say they're friends.
There's a lot of misinformation I feel like some people are like, we don't know if they were like really friends.
They were like competitors, but I don't know if they were truly like friends.
But the one thing is clear. They certainly stole ideas from each other.
And like the log flume ride at not clearly influenced then Splash Mountain later, which isn't Walt's creation.
But the mine train through Nature's Wonderland and Disneyland.
Walt stole that right away from the Calico.
That predated, I think.
I think Calico mine ride has not happened until the 60s.
But the big thing, I could be wrong about this, but I think the big thing that influenced Walt Disney was the like hidden lines.
There's the story where that ride, the Calico mine ride that Walt Disney got on it because he thought there was no line.
And then he got it in and the line was hidden in the rock work instead of just sitting out in like a boring kind of back and forth queue, like which is all Disneyland had.
Sure.
So the idea of like the line is also part of the theming.
Walt's definitely was influenced by all these the nicer by by Nuts.
Yeah, and you're getting like you're you're looking at some cool stuff and it's air conditioned and the idea of a lot of the line is indoors as opposed to.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then you're not. Yeah, you're not sitting out in the sun.
And it's more inviting if you if you see a if you see a ride with a three hour line outside, you know, you might skip it.
But if you don't know how long it is, it's all hidden.
Scott is indeed correct.
Hey, about the mines.
All right. Let's not credit it.
What else though in this back and forth?
Oh, I think, well, one thing I discovered in the history of it that, yeah, it didn't it was just an open gate park until 1968 when there was a bunch of vandalism.
So they had to build a wall to keep people out of the park.
And only then did they charge admission, which I'm not sure when Disneyland became an admission park.
They held on to the ticket booklets for a while and used them in Florida, too, because I remember my dad talking about having when they went down to Orlando in the 70s, they they were still using the ticket booklets.
OK. Yeah.
But anyway, it does seem like they bounced back and forth in terms of like figuring out how the modern theme park works.
One thing on those ticket booklets. Are you talking about that?
You said in Orlando or?
Yeah, Disneyland and Disney World. They used to you would.
The ticket book and the tickets.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah. My parents would use that phrase, e-ticket ride.
One time years ago when the movie Waterworld came out, I saw at the premiere, they interviewed James Kahn.
And he walked out and said, they said, what did you think of Waterworld, James Kahn?
And he says, oh, it's great. It's an e-ticket ride.
He said that phrase. Did he think of that before? Did someone ask him to say it?
I think that was how he described a really fun ride was that's you.
That's how you would describe a thrilling experience.
That was the vernacular at the time.
This is 1995.
Yeah, this is 1995, the vernacular.
Yes. But it was an old man who had gone to Disney World.
And theme park enthusiasts still refer to like, you know, the big marquee ride, your Space Mountain Haunted Mansion.
Oh, so that's still in the.
I mean, like kids don't maybe know that.
Kids don't.
But like, yeah, the inside Imagineering and then weirdos that do podcasts certainly know, well, this is more of a d-ticket than an e, you know.
The thrill, the robots aren't quite as good on this ride as they would be on an e-ticket.
Or to know what they would have charged.
Only the head moves on this, not the arms.
Those new Star Wars rides could be f-tickets. It could go bigger than anything we've seen before.
They are saying they want these to be f-tickets, these Star Wars.
They've used that phrase, they want to go beyond e.
With the big ride through on this.
Probably not the best thing that the letter after e is a big old f, though.
You mean because f is failing or.
F grade is good.
It's like bad.
Shut up, man.
They mean good now?
More on Walter Knott from his obituary in the New York Times from 1981, which the headline is very funny.
It's Walter Knott of Knott's Berry Farm is dead.
Like that's what they wrote.
Blunter time.
Like, OK, like not like kindly old man passes away.
It's like, no, he's dead.
Jam jars across America emptied to half full in respect.
Was he preserved in any form?
Save it for Mr. Owens's special.
Was he preserved?
He was described as a trim and spunky man.
And personify this is weird, the personify the spunky.
Hey, a wily idea.
I got a new jam idea too.
Can I write obituary?
This spunky man deceased.
I don't know what this somebody maybe somebody knows where this comes from.
Personify the rags dash torches, which obviously is rags to riches, but I don't know the spelling.
Rags dash toriches.
Spelling rags to riches like this as one word rags to riches rags to riches.
Is that from something?
This is just a poorly written piece of shit.
I don't know what any of it means.
James Kahn coined that term.
He was a very conservative man.
He was more politically active than Disney, right?
Yes.
So he has the full Independence Hall, which is in Knott's Berry Farm, which is still there.
But also he financed a lot of conservative endeavors, which is probably very bad.
He gave out pamphlets in Knott's Berry Farm potentially about conservative ideals.
Yes.
And the can-can dancers of the Calico Saloon would often spout anti-communist propaganda.
So yeah, he had a freedom center in the park, he called it, and it produced pamphlets and film strips,
extolling free enterprise and self-sufficiency and deploring big government and taxes.
So do you have any recollection?
As a child, do you remember going to the freedom center?
Now that's an e-ticket, baby.
That's another e-ticket for enterprise.
I don't remember this at all.
He died in 81, so maybe as soon as he was dead they shut the freedom center down.
Get the freedom center out of here.
No, I don't remember any political memories.
Of course, Mr. Knott, we will keep the freedom center alive and burning bright.
It's funny to think about now, because I feel like people who don't live in California,
when you talk about California in terms of national politics, it's always like, oh, it's a blue state, it's a blue state.
But there's a huge conservative streak.
Orange County gave us Richard Nixon, and Richard Nixon and Ronald Reagan were both California politicians
before becoming president, and Orange County sells a lot of very conservative pockets.
Yeah, when I was a kid growing up, I lived in the most conservative congressional district in the entire country.
Wow.
It was the most conservative district?
I believe so.
In the mid-'90s, it was.
I remember hearing that in school and thinking, oh, shit.
Now it's the chillest conservative county.
It's the most relaxed.
They say that Walter Knott and Carl Karcher.
Carl Karcher also came into my mom's restaurant.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
A different, not his own.
And Walt Disney.
These guys always came into the Shae Carey.
That's wild.
We haven't previewed this, and it's only 49 seconds.
I found a clip from the Freedom Center.
Whoa.
It's Clip Currency of Orange County Archives.
It's from 1964.
Okay.
So who knows?
We'll see what this is.
I think that if we are ever going to eliminate poverty in America, it will have to be done
through the free enterprise system and certainly not by government.
That was Walter Knott, owner of Knott's Berry Farm, a family entertainment center near Los Angeles.
Last year, nearly two million dinners were served here with Walter's wife, Cordelia, in charge of the kitchen.
The farm is a huge playland, and Walter Knott makes sure that his employees share in the profit.
He also puts his ideas into action in other ways.
For instance, he has established, in a re-appilitated farmhouse, the Freedom Center, a passion in a one-man program to
to bulwark certain of our liberties, which he believes are being eroded by authoritarian ideologies of the right and left.
Wow. That does not beat around the bush either.
authoritarian ideology
You'd be a kid sitting there listening to that in the Freedom Center.
It is funny how nowadays people talk about, oh, the Trump administration has destroyed decorum and that sort of thing.
But back then, you would be hearing that about, our boy is shipping off to Vietnam.
And it's just like these insidious things would be presented with wholesome Leave-It-to-Beaver background music.
I mean, even the Iraq War, that was a thing where it was like, well, everyone is very composed.
All the politicians are very composed and professional, but they still sold this crazy war.
Well, look, a spoonful of sugar helps the medicine go down.
Yeah, that's true. I mean, you get that Freedom Center.
Now, what you're saying is you like it now, Jason.
I mean, I'm a crass. I'm a crass man.
Jason shared it as on the record for saying he likes it now.
He likes Trump better.
This is now the second episode in a row where this business goes up.
Trump tells it like it is. He doesn't underscore things with some old filmstrip soundtrack.
Yeah, some old Land of Chocolate Homer Simpson music to play while he's saying something horrible.
Trump doesn't need full sentences to get his idea across.
Every day he becomes more presidential.
In fact, I think we should bring back that Freedom Center.
Bulldoze that restored Calico Mine train.
I think Trump would have gotten bored midway through the clip you just played.
He would have drifted off and started tweeting.
Or just pulled out his emergency McDonald's bag.
Oh, sorry, I couldn't hear it.
Man, so there you go. That's the history.
The history of nuts.
But you know what? They got less conservative as time went on because in the 80s they opened two hot dance clubs for teenagers.
One called Studio K and the other one called Cloud Nine.
You could go see all the hottest DJs from K-Rock. Richard Blade would be there.
This is on the premises of...
Richard Blade?
Yeah, I forget who that was.
I don't know who that is.
I saw him in a little pamphlet about Studio K.
That's another little back and forth Disneyland arms war which I'm sure, well, I hope to God we talk about in a later episode
because Disneyland opened the teen nightclub Videopolis.
So they both had competing teen dance clubs.
Now what happened to these clubs? How come they don't...
I believe there was a stabbing at one or like one...
Was there an incident at one of them?
Or maybe in the parking lot like an altercation or something.
I think it was at the parking lot during Videopolis, yeah.
When teens dance they start getting rowdy and they get violent and horny I guess.
And that's probably why they had to close down Kingdom of the Dinosaurs.
They got pregnant on the ride and people were just getting too horny on the damn ride.
There was a custody battle between the mother, the father and the dinosaurs.
Technically I caused this.
That was a T-Rex target.
That baby is property of the Knot family.
So when you, Ryan, when you were a kid though you never like saw the dance club and were like, let me in.
Never saw the dance club but an average Knot thing would be we would, it was a relatively easy park to sneak food into.
And so that was another, you'd either eat at the chicken restaurant or if it was on a sort of a more money saving day
you could sneak like a bunch of sandwiches into the park and ride on.
There was a parachute ride or a sky drop ride that was very scary.
Yeah, no longer there I don't think.
Yeah, no longer.
So many of these things are now gone.
Yeah.
There was the mine ride of course.
There was the Bigfoot Rapids ride where you would get soaked and then go into the, where is it that we went?
Oh, the mystery lodge.
The mystery lodge.
Yeah, that's what I was going to say.
That's the first, that was the thing you were.
Do you know about this, Jason?
Scott was most excited I think to show me the mystery lodge.
I did not know what it was.
Life could not have been less exciting.
Again, we're doing the, she might have just not done it.
No patience for dull, dull shows.
She's like, I would rather look at this grass than go into the mystery lodge.
She can sit quietly and I think she did.
Is it like Twin Peaks is Black Lodge?
Is it like a place where everything is weird?
No, I wish.
No, no, no.
Maybe it is though.
Am I prepared to explain mystery lodge?
I think you have to, at least give a brief explanation.
It's a thing that was at like a Vancouver World's Fair Expo kind of thing and they just moved its lock, stock and barrel.
Lock and stock, I'm not sure there's a barrel in this ride, that'd be too exciting.
But it was like, it's a slightly multimedia show where a wise old Indian tells tales of...
He tells a tale about a raven that pretends to be an owl.
Oh, the raven doing a trickster.
And also, before you go in, they admonish you very heavily, like show respect to this thing.
This is like Native American history and show...
They would be mad at me if I did the voice.
Well, actually a lot of people would probably be mad.
Yeah, we're gonna get problems online.
But yes, it's like this is very serious history and then you walk in and it's an animatronic.
Native American.
Well, you know what it is? It's like a performer who doesn't actually...
Is it a performer or is it a geek?
He performs to a lip sync track and he wears an old Indian mask over his face to make him look like an old man.
And he's like hunched over. It's kind of a magic show that he's interacting with a projected bird like the Haunted Mansion ghost.
It's like a screen. There's a screen in between that looks like it's just a mirror, but the mirror is actually a projection.
So that is a real man.
Oh my God, I thought it was a robot.
I thought it was a very sophisticated robot.
It should be underselling the show.
That would be one of the greatest robots of all time.
Well, I don't think so.
Notts has restored a lot of their classic rides in recent years and uses Garner Holt, the same animatronic manufacturer that Disney uses to repair and build them.
Yeah, the Mine Ride has better animatronics.
I was told, because I hadn't didn't go like eight years ago, the Mine Ride, which is you go through this mine and you see a bunch of robots like working in horrible conditions
in a mine breathing in, you know, getting black lungs.
Conservative values.
Yeah, conservative values. But they got that Asian one.
So everything's all right.
But I was told, and I didn't see this, that like if you went on that ride eight or nine years ago, all of the characters were melting.
All the skin was like melting off of them.
And before the restoration happened, it was a nightmare ride of like all these men's faces were falling off.
And then they went in and did a full scale like, you know, cleaning up the whole thing, which they did a great job.
And here's the thing to congratulate Notts on the recent past. Really great job restoring that ride.
Did they restore also the Calico Mine Ride or was that just the Mine Ride and the Log?
Yeah, both of them have gotten recent.
They're both great and really fun, unique experiences and good reasons to go there.
I also just went to they I just checked out the the Chicken Dinner Restaurant, which they have recently remodeled.
And now it's like a cool gastropub kind of place.
Cordelia's restaurant.
No, they didn't. It's like still homey. I mean, it's like as cool.
That sounds like a bummer.
It's as cool as like an Applebee's would be.
That sucks.
You dig it, though, I think.
Really?
Yeah, it doesn't feel like it's the same week as we went anymore.
Weren't you telling me there was a TGI Fridays in the park?
It's across the street. Yeah, there's a TGI Fridays, but it's on site.
That's another great thing about Notts.
There's an on site TGI Fridays that you don't have to pay admission to get to.
Please show respect to the Mystery Lodge.
And if y'all are hungry, there's a TGI Fridays.
Jack Daniel's chicken strips always in fashion.
Was Mrs. Notts, was the we went to a breakfast buffet there like a couple of years ago.
Was that the same room or is that different?
That had mimosas and the breakfast buffet at Mrs. Notts.
No, they've redone it since then, but it's nice.
It looks like a new, it looks like a frontier land type.
That's kind of a bummer to me, though, because going in that one room,
it felt like you could be in the middle of like Alabama in 1940, which is scary,
but also like it does feel timeless.
I liked it. I'm now very reticent to revisit the chicken restaurant.
But I'd be the first to say that I'm bummed that they redid it.
I think you'd like it if you walked in.
There's like a bar in there now.
And the food is still what it was.
You get a ton of food for, you get this giant chicken dinner plate for like $16.
With like the giant bowl of rhubarb.
There's a lot of people in there, especially older couples, that are just in there for dinner.
They're not even, they wouldn't even think about going into the park or Soak City
or any of that stuff. They're just in there to have dinner and go back home.
Is it free to just park and go to the restaurant? Like it's just like a restaurant.
I think you can.
And here's the thing I'd like to say, because I've done this several times,
highly recommend it. If you don't want to pay the Knott's Berry Farm admission,
just go down to Buena Park and check out all the stuff that is free in the Knott's Berry Farm area.
There's the chicken dinner restaurant, although you pay for that, obviously.
But then there's like lots of oddball little shops.
You can go hang out in the Knott's Hotel, which has a...
Oh yeah, they have an outside hotel.
They've got, yeah, and they've got a, there's a fun little restaurant in there called Amber Waves.
You can go get a nice beer at Amber Waves.
Is that the hotel where you can pay a fee and Snoopy will tuck you in?
Yes, we learned this from Doug Jones, our friend who will be on the show soon, I'm sure.
Yeah, you can have Snoopy come tuck your kid in, or presumably...
Or you.
Yeah, Snoopy will walk into the room.
It's up to the person playing Snoopy.
Snoopy tucked me in. It was great. It was the best day of my life.
Doug Jones.
I'm not sure if that was a man, like somebody who was too into Snoopy tucking him in.
So you could just call downstairs, like Snoopy please.
$50 later, college student likes up some stairs because he can't fit in the elevator.
Kiss my forehead, Snoopy.
Opens that door to a handful of swingers and eyes wide shut, Basks.
Hello, Snoopy. Welcome to the party, Snoopy.
The general Knott's area, and also down there, these are unrelated to Knott's, but you can go down there,
you can go to Medieval Times, you can go to the Pirates Dinner Adventure.
We should cover all of these things at some point.
There's a weird McDonald's that used to have a simulator ride in it, and it no longer does,
and yet it's still labeled on the outside McThriller.
Oh yeah.
Well, this McDonald's that we went to, incredible, has that...
A big model train.
Yeah. This is a whole McDonald's that have novelties within them.
There aren't enough left. In Dallas, I tried to go to a McDonald's that had chandeliers,
and we had to explain to the Lyft driver, where are you going?
Well, we're going to a McDonald's, but it's like a weird McDonald's,
and then we got there and it was just a normal McDonald's.
They had taken out the weird stuff.
But yeah, it's a sadly endangered animal, the weird McDonald's.
But they got one of those down there.
A really crazy, creepy mall that has a photo studio for fetuses,
which several malls do. I don't know if you see...
Ultrasound photography.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, that's... What? In Buena Park Mall?
In the Buena Park Mall, yeah, me and old Bug Mane went down there,
and the first thing we saw when we went up the escalator was Ultrasound photo studio,
and it was lots of heart-shaped frames with little fetuses inside.
Buena Park is a real bazaar. I highly recommend.
Go have a free day in Buena Park. So bazaar.
Your other dream job would be taking an announcer through an abandoned mall.
There's plenty of them right now in America.
Why am I not pitching a true TV on this subject?
Scott, the mall guy.
As you describe Buena Park, it's crazy to think about...
Not Sperry Farm, I don't know how many years ago, but it was up for sale,
and Disney was considering buying it, and they briefly were trying to figure out,
can we run the monorail from Anaheim Way to Park,
which not that far considering how long monorail tracks they have in Florida,
but they control all of the land under it in Florida.
They would have had to run an above-ground monorail through neighborhoods,
so it was pretty much impossible.
Wow, that would be incredible though.
Imagine it moving at hyperloop speed.
It would be there before you know it.
Disneyland in two knots in 2.4 seconds.
You might burst ventricles in your heart.
But you get there fast. You'd be fine.
Yeah. Oh, well, seriously, the weird thing to go back to something you mentioned earlier,
the Church of Reflections that your parents were married in,
they actually moved that. It was inside the theme park,
which I guess when they got married, it would have been...
Do they have to pay admission to get married?
No, I think the park was free at the time,
and I think the whole cost of renting the church was like $150.
Oh my God. Wow.
So, yeah, very cheap thing.
But then going back as a teenager, the church was like under a roller coaster.
It might have been under the Boomerang roller coaster or whatever it was.
It was the first roller coaster I ever rode on when I was like eight years old.
A roller coaster going over the church.
And I remember making the sort of...
At the time, I thought it was a very cool writerly analogy of like,
this is where my parents got married, and their marriage was a roller coaster too.
One day I'll like put that in something.
Have you put it in something?
No.
In the great novel.
That's much better than if the church is just next to a parking lot or planes.
But now they've moved it.
Yeah, now it's across the street.
Also in the weird free area you can explore,
there's a full perfect replica of Independence Hall that is so perfect,
it was used in the film National Treasure.
It was like that much of a double for the real Independence Hall.
Oh, that's right. Yeah.
And then you can go from that to visit the Church of Reflection
and reflect on the spot where Ryan's parents were married.
But weirdly they moved it across the street.
And here's an odd fact, I don't know if you know about the Church of Reflections,
but there used to be a thing called the Transfiguration.
It was a painting of Christ, and he looks sad and forlorn,
and his eyes are closed, but if you shine a blacklight on it, his eyes open up.
I don't know about that.
There is a magic blacklight, a college dorm Jesus painting.
Oh, boy.
Gee whiz.
I want one for over my bed.
Some might say that blacklight could be described as poisonberry colored.
Oh, boy.
On that we're sort of coming back around to the station.
Incident free, no robbery.
If we missed anything big about another,
there's so much to talk about with the entire park, but that's, yeah.
I think we're recommending it.
Yeah, yeah.
If you're living in LA or if you're coming here.
Is that how this show works?
Can you just shit on an entire park?
Could you be like, California Adventure? No.
You know, we haven't reviewed an entire park yet,
so we don't really know our system necessarily.
I don't know if we have a different one.
What we've been doing for rides is a system which is keep it as is,
plus it up, or burn it to the ground for insurance money.
And now do you land on one of those four knots Berry Park?
What was the first one?
Keep it as is.
Don't change a single thing about.
I think probably keep as is at the moment.
And they have they also also I do think you could probably review
individual rides at Knott's Berry Farm because they do have some pretty
distinctive rides right now.
They have Pony Express, which you sit on like a horse.
The roller coaster you sit on like a horse.
They have a silver bullet, which is a pretty good roller coaster.
They have some pretty good roller coasters.
And some a couple of important.
I believe the first roller coaster where you went upside down was at Knott's Berry.
I think the corkscrew.
Well, corkscrew Montezuma's Revenge is a famous roller coaster there.
That is the first ride that had like a launch mechanism as opposed to you just
like climb up.
You climb up a hill on like a hook on the track.
It was the first ride that launched you the way like, you know, like a Hyperloop from
the zero to six.
Is that that green coaster?
I went on a green coaster there last time and it hurt my head so bad.
That might have been the boomerang before they got rid of it.
Did they just get rid of it?
How many years ago was it?
Two years.
Well, I don't know.
Some of them, they really tried to be a coaster park in the night with like very minimal theming.
And then eventually they're like, man, we're going to take some of these down and.
Yeah, that is that is probably an issue with it.
That was our complaint talking earlier is that they sort of added all of the roller
coasters kind of willy nilly.
And it doesn't like the theming from place to place doesn't make a lot of sense.
And there's an area called the Roaring Twenties.
And then that's just full of a bunch of neon roller coasters.
And they don't do the best job of like cohesion in the place.
And I'm glad they've taken out a couple of.
Yeah, it's a little bit right now.
The old west stuff is I mean, this is three years ago.
It's coexisting with the roller coaster stuff, the kind of tackier roller coaster stuff.
And so there's really like some of that old west stuff, I think, is still genuinely old
west stuff taken from old west towns.
And there's like a bottle house.
I think there's like a bottle house where you read the plaque, it's like this lady like
built the bottle house out of her alcoholic husband's beer bottles.
And you're like, oh, this is very dark stuff.
But then that's sort of next to, you know, whatever, you know, a scary drop.
Yeah, yeah.
I think you're right that there are individual rides worth reviewing because we didn't even
touch upon a newer ride where steampunk octopus.
Yes, are destroying the park.
Right. And you have to shoot them.
We went on this ride a couple years ago.
You're in Knott's Berry Farm in a lagoon and this is a giant robot octopus.
So you have to shoot lasers at.
Yeah, it's a steampunk like a wild, wild west.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, yeah.
Giant spider in that giant octopus in this.
We have.
My opinion is certainly plus it up.
I like all the old stuff.
I don't like a lot of the non-themed roller coasters.
Like the thing I was talking about is the boomerang that green that's gone now.
But like I want, you know, terrible ride, by the way, a terrible ride.
But like a shitty roller coaster, a shitty roller coaster that really like I remember
there was a part where because it goes like backwards and I like clang my neck against
them. I felt like a crack in my neck and I was like, oh, shit, like I'm hurt.
Yeah, I think I just heard I went on it like eight years old.
I think I almost fainted. Yeah, it's terrible.
But rides that hurt you.
I'll say this.
The roller coaster should be themed better.
It's called the boomerang.
You know, put it put at least the queue, the line in a in a enclosed space.
Give me a Australian man robot.
Make it like he's throwing or something.
We've got to get the whatever.
Like the kangaroos are coming.
We've got to get away from them or whatever.
Give me something like that.
Yeah. Give me a little theme.
A little theme after Baz Luhrmann's Australia.
Great, great idea.
Let's I don't care if they're IPs.
I don't care if they're original.
I just think there's too many rides in this place that just have a generic kind of six flags roller coaster name.
And then give me some robots.
Give me some story.
That's what I like.
I like it mixed with the thrills.
So I love all the old stuff.
I love the chicken dinner.
I'm going to love this new fancy downtown L.A. chicken restaurant vibe you're talking about.
Is it like the hot chicken?
I keep forgetting.
Old Buzzy Miller.
What was his name?
Buzzy Miller.
The ghost of Cordelia.
How dare you speak ill of my precious roller coaster.
So yeah, yeah.
Because it because that's now just feels like it's half fun.
Old park, half six flags from the 90s.
It's caught in a bit of an identity crisis and clearly that's why I like those remodels of the Calico Mine Ride and the log ride.
It's that's getting you back to the the old timey charm and fun.
I think you're never going to compete in the thrill area.
So yeah, I like that it's a bit of historic landmark a little bit.
They should play into that more.
They should really play into it like, you know, every couple of years in Hollywood, they're like a Western will come out and be a hit.
People will be like the Westerns back open range or whatever was a hit.
And they should not really embrace that as like where the old West where Westworld or, you know, whatever the Western property is.
If they took I guess it's an all IP and everything.
But I feel like people would come in just for the old West experience.
So they have an old West show there.
That's a lot of fun.
Yeah, fun.
Yeah, I know they're doing more.
We haven't seen it. They're doing more with like interactive like you go on a journey now in the old West town where you have like this an adventure and you get your and your part of it.
There's a whole thing going on, which we have not tried.
If not wants to bring us down, we'd love to try it.
If they're listening, I'll withhold judgment until I get to see it myself.
Sure.
Jason hasn't even been.
Let's get Jason to not make it happen.
It happened.
We sort of insulted a lot of things as we went and now we're demanding things.
This is the most anyone's ever talked about.
Not very long.
This is the longest conversation about the Farfetch'd ever recorded and also ever.
Even the employees there talk about how their kids are doing more than they talk about.
Hey, well, not you're welcome.
I guess with that, we're heading back to the station.
Choo-choo, we're back in the station.
That's what you say when you when you land back at the Choo-choo.
Choo-choo.
And we're home.
Hey, Ryan, thanks so much for being here and sharing your not memories.
It's been a roller coaster of a conversation.
Cool, man. Cool.
That's a pretty neat analogy.
I feel like I thought of it.
And then you'd like to plug or say closing thoughts here.
I don't really have any closing thoughts.
Thanks for having me on.
And I don't know, to plug, I would maybe I do like this idea about you going to malls.
That's more of a pitch to you.
Sure.
We will take it upstairs to Starbirds.
Okay, great.
And take it general.
Yes, we immediately lost our exclusivity.
Look, I'm fine with that.
And some of those malls have like weird like have been retaken by nature and these weird swamps.
Yeah.
Yeah. No, thanks for seeing the idea I should have been doing all along.
Well, that's the next project.
This is the last episode of podcast.
I'm thrilled.
Thank you guys for having me on podcast the ride.
And I hope you guys are all driving safe.
I like to say that now.
Watch the road.
Laugh, laugh, love, but watch the road.
And enjoy the rest of your day.
And you all enjoy your day.
Mike, Jason, any closing?
Well, wait, go to podcast.
Contact us at podcast the ride on Twitter or the podcast the ride at what?
At Gmail?
Is that right?
I always forget it.
And or our personal Twitter's and you can find that we don't need to say them.
They're all linked on our show Twitter account.
This is some kind of dating thing for you guys.
Well, for Jason.
For me.
If there's any Jason single and if anyone likes all this bullshit, like tweet at him.
You know he's in.
If this gets you going, like tweet at Jason.
Please don't murder me with an oversized turkey leg.
But you're into someone lately beating you with a turkey leg.
Oh, yeah, not be around all day long.
Is that part of the new restaurant?
That's part of the hotel service.
Oh boy.
Snoopy will beat the shit out of you.
Civilization is crumbling.
Thank you, Snoopy.
Hit the button weird stuff on the not's phone.
Hey, folks.
Thanks.
Thank you so much.
You've survived.
I guess the ride.
We'll see you next time.
Goodbye.
That be rusty trails.