Warning, today's podcast may include surprise appearances by the Capitol critters and fish
police, fanciful fun-alysis of ad hoc cadaver surgery in hotel ballrooms, and a roundup of
theme park news, including the Donald Trump robot and Disney's purchase of Fox.
Stay seated and refrain from protests.
This is Podcast the Ride.
Hello everyone, welcome to Podcast the Ride, the podcast about theme parks hosted by three
men who have had fewer sexual partners than there are Disney theme parks.
Correct me if the numbers are wrong.
No, they're not.
Jack's with me.
I'm not adding a lot to that pile, but there's also a lot of Disney theme parks, and are
you counting water parks?
We can discuss all of it.
We'll cross-check numbers later.
Anyway, hey, I'm joined by Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
And Mike.
I said hi to Jason's name.
Sorry, I was really counting numbers in my head.
They're very low, so I was really thrown off.
Can you guess at home?
Let us know.
Hey, well, this is that we've released new episodes in 2018.
This is the first one that we're recording in 2018.
And also, we've tended to do a lot of episodes that are recorded well before they come out.
And this is the first one where we're putting it out the week of, and we felt this was very
necessary because theme park news has been just bonkers lately.
There's so much to catch up on.
And the beginnings of January have just been absolutely bat shit, and we wanted to tell
you all about it.
And not necessarily good news.
Yeah, in fact, a lot of it not.
But it's definitely happened.
Yeah.
Hey, I mean, among other things, this is only tangentially theme park news, but our podcast
network fell apart.
There's one thing that happened on Christmas Day.
Yeah, that was great to deal with over the holidays.
A lot of fun.
We had a blast, you know, because going indie is, you know, there's just a real thrill to
getting back into the into the grime and the muck and, you know, being freed up, I think
has been a real pleasure for all of us and a fun thing to deal with.
I think we're a bunch of podcast cowboys now.
And that's the way I'm looking at it.
You know, just going from town to town.
We'll record anywhere.
We're doing this in my living room.
There's a dog floating around.
You may hear him on the track.
I don't know.
I want to wander in here and bark at me.
Yes, we got your letters.
And finally, we now have what you've all been clamoring for.
More talk about the logistics of recording a podcast, baby.
Yeah.
So we're talking more referencing trucks that go by sirens outside, humming and construction
work at nearby apartment complexes.
We're bringing you all of that new for 2018.
Finally, we get to do all the technical stuff that we spent months trying to get with a
network to avoid having to do.
Yeah.
So I guess we're saying, look, hey, if you have a network out there, hey, let us know.
I mean, we're listening to any network.
If you have a theme park specific network, there could be one that we don't even know
about that wants to take us and put us under your delightful wing.
Is your wing warm?
Let us in.
Hey, but our RIP Ferrell Audio and thanks for the snacks.
Yeah, I sure did eat a lot of free snacks that I may not have supposed to have eaten.
Too late.
Never stopped before.
Can't sue you now.
They don't exist.
Hey, but anyway, but yeah, that among other things, just a crazy couple of weeks.
I don't even need to tell you about most of these stories.
I'm sure you know about most of them.
We're talking about the outbreak of Legionnaires disease at Disneyland.
Two coolant towers had to be shut down to prevent the Legionnaires outbreak.
I don't think they're not sure it came from Disneyland, but they're pretty sure.
So like people just are getting sick in Anaheim and then they traced it back and they're
like all these people with Legionnaires disease all went to Disneyland and they had to clean
out two towers.
And then, you know, Scott and I were there yesterday and so far I haven't contracted
Legionnaires disease.
I don't know what the symptoms are, but if being in a great mood and feeling fine are
the symptoms, then I got them.
Jason, do you know what Legionnaires symptoms are?
I don't know the symptoms, no.
I think it's probably fever and shortness of breath.
It's the same symptoms as every other disease.
You get a fever and you feel like crap.
Coughing.
Yeah, cough.
Wasn't there, there was several years ago, this is very old news, but there was an outbreak
that started from a kid who had not been vaxxed.
That was measles?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
It was a small child, yeah, that had not been vaccinated and went in fantasy land.
And if your kid had not been vaccinated or you, you could go to Disneyland, touch the
wheel at the teacups and get measles.
Boy, wonderful.
It's a very touchy park in general.
Yeah, there is.
Everything that kids do is like have fun, jump around it, touch it.
Touch all the levers and buttons and do that.
It's right in the middle of a state where people have some sometimes kooky ideas on
child rearing.
Anyway, Jenny McCarthy, great job.
This year's Rockin' Eve.
Thanks for ringing it in.
Fine work as always.
Blood on your hands.
I will not allow the innocent Disney company to take the blame.
It's all Jenny.
What else happened?
There was also a blackout at Disneyland that took out most of, took out all of Toontown,
a lot of fantasy land, left people stranded on it's a small world for a number of hours.
Also notable, it happened on the day both teams playing in the Rose Bowl were there.
Oh, didn't know that.
Yeah.
And in addition to like, wasn't it the 26th?
It was Christmas week, it was a big crowd day already.
And then there was another thing going on and then the blackout happened.
People had to walk off, right?
Yeah, I think there was some walk-offs, some rides, sure.
Have we talked on the show yet about walk-offs and what a sort of a treasured thing it is?
What a valued, yeah, if you get stuck in an attraction and then possibly the hope of seeing
some backdoor weird alleyway part of the attraction that people don't otherwise get to see, that's
pretty exciting.
Like that, like if it was a walk-off and you were on pirates, the dream would be like you'd
have to get off the boat in the town.
Yeah.
Like that would be a dream to get to go up close and see the horrible pirates.
Yeah, to like pass right by one, get to plant a kiss on one of them or something.
Yeah.
I'm sure that's not allowed, but.
But you, but all bets are off when things close.
Yeah, anything where you'd have to like, you know, straddle water or like, you know, do
some death-defying jump.
Absolutely.
Yeah, that'd be.
So the blackout was bad, but it was good for those folks that probably got to walk through
a few of the attractions.
Ah, yes.
If it happened to you and you're listening, let us know.
Tell us your tale.
Share any photos.
Share any kisses you planted on robots.
Tell us all the sultry details.
That treat is like the opposite of what happened to me when I went to Another Park in like
mid-December and a woman kept holding up her giant dumb ass phone to try to take a picture
during the ride, Space Mountain, a pitch black ride, trying to get pictures and a pitch black
ride.
And I'm scared to death.
Like, I'm going to get a concussion when that giant Android phone flies out of her hand
and right up my head.
And then as we pulled back into the station, she went, wow, it sure was dark in there.
Like a cartoon character.
You would have been like Fabio and the bird, but a phone would have been a phone.
Oh man, that fucking bird.
It would have bloodied your nose.
It's been a lot, yeah, just lodged straight into your head, just a corner wedged in there.
And then we still do the podcast with you, but it makes very little sense.
Yeah.
That said.
That was, I did not wait at all.
I walked right onto Space Mountain because I used the single riders line at the Space
Mountain Disneyland.
Another piece of news.
Another news story.
Oh boy.
News.
That I, are they still doing it?
Are they not?
Was that a test?
I forgot to check.
We didn't even go on Space Mountain.
It was very ad hoc when I was there.
A lot of folding signs and like back, back, went through a back alleyway I hadn't seen
before.
Oh yeah, there you go.
Splash Mountain 2 is like that where it was not intended.
They don't have a special single rider.
You just kind of go through the exit and then they just plop you next to somebody.
So yeah, another exciting thing that happened while we were gone.
Changes.
They're shutting down.
We, Mike and I went yesterday to bid farewell to Paradise Pier at California Adventure,
which is set to become Pixar Pier, which I'm sure will change everything.
You'll hear all of the earth-shattering details here on the show.
Yeah, what actually happens there?
The California Screamin' turns into the Incredicoaster.
They put some stuff, it looks like they're going to put like some characters on it.
So like you'll go through a tube and Mrs. Incredible is stretching.
So like there'll be something, but it's the exact same ride.
There's going to be no change to what you're feeling.
But like there'll be a few nice, there'll be nice paint.
You know, there'll be new paint.
They're going to make the Cove Bar into something like Frozone's Bar.
We came up with a good, yesterday we came up with a good re-theming for the Cove Bar,
which is over on Paradise Pier.
Theme it to the up, no up, Jesus.
Theme it to Wally's Captain.
Oh, so it's a glutton place?
Yeah, so we assume he likes to drink.
So like the Captain from Wally's Bar.
Voiced by Jeff Garland, the fat Wally guy with the little bones with the most authority,
who I assume probably loves to eat and have a good time.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, so just big old food trays you just dip your head into.
We need to get the Wally stuff into the park finally, because people want to see a giant
trash pile that a robot collects.
But this is a better version of it, so that was our blue-skying yesterday.
Sorry, by the way, Jason wasn't there because his past is not good enough.
I don't have the Saturdays, okay?
I'm not throwing money around left and right like these two, you know.
You can check out more frugal theme park texts on my upcoming podcast on our own network.
Yeah, Theme Parks on a Budget, the frugal rider.
I like this.
I want this.
This is our Patreon side project.
It's an exclusive.
I'm totally into the frugal rider.
Only go to the parks on a Tuesday morning.
I mean, it does rule.
That's what I did.
I got down there at like eight in the morning on a Tuesday in December.
You did do a Tuesday morning, right?
Yeah, Tuesday or Wednesday morning.
Did you hitchhike your way down there?
No, that would have been more pleasant than driving in that morning rush hour traffic.
But I wish.
I did ride like six rides by 10 in the morning.
That's the one time when people go like, when is it not crowded?
And it's like before 10 a.m. is pretty much your only guaranteed thing anymore.
I think this would be really an ultimate tip.
And one, I don't encourage anyone to try, especially not yourself.
But you could.
The real way to save money would be to get somebody to fly a helicopter over the park
and then try to sneakily skydive down into the park.
And you're skipping that admission altogether.
Maybe see if you can land in the lake that might be a shallow lake, though.
Oh, yeah, yeah, that's true.
Depending on how high you're coming down from.
I think top of Matterhorn I would go with.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And then you and then you're coming down and people think you're one of those mountain
climbers.
That's right.
People think, oh, the mountain climbers back, but he's got a American Apparel sweatshirt
on.
Surely this is what would happen and not like as soon as you're within a thousand feet,
you get shot down by Disney snipers.
Well, somebody I don't know.
Give it a shot.
See if you can.
Yeah, somebody tried airdrop into Disneyland.
Well, it's not just in Disney.
Changes afoot everywhere.
The Johnny Rockets at Universal City Walk is closing.
I would heartbreaking news that I'm sure you're already really.
No, it's not actually.
It's closing for a few weeks.
Is it not?
It is a it's closing for a few weeks for a refurbish.
It is a refurbishment closing.
OK, OK, I see.
We saw different news stories on the theme park Twitter.
I think they updated.
What was the account?
Was it Inside Universal?
Inside Universal for catching that there were walls around it and then correcting that it
was just being refurbished.
OK, thank God.
Because this is no folks, if you haven't been up there, if you're not Los Angeles natives,
this is no ordinary Johnny Rockets, why it's one point five times the size.
It's a sprawling campus.
It used to be a daily grill.
All right.
Here's the way that they reported.
So Inside Universal, which is a Twitter account that follows the universal news exclusively
that the three of us all follow and know people personally that we know people recently.
So I guess we're kind of I'm sure they were jumping on the back of their scoop.
Yeah.
So they tweeted Johnny Rockets at Universal City Walk.
Hollywood has closed.
And that was and they put a put a article up about it.
And then an hour later, Inside Universal has learned that the closure of Johnny Rockets
is for refurbishment.
The restaurant should open in a month.
OK.
Oh, thank God.
They retracted their story.
What a start that gave me.
They have been closing a lot at the city walk in Hollywood and replacing it with either
like fast casual stuff like, you know, your smash burger, your ludo chicken or like slightly
nicer stuff.
I think at some point he's coming.
But they still have a sock store.
They still have a story and a stock market.
Socks.
Yeah.
And a store where you can buy the same garbage that you could buy in Hollywood Boulevard
like there's Hollywood that say best teacher.
Yeah.
So I think myself and upcoming guest John Daly had a had a pitch at the similar also
defunct company CISO, RIP, Feral and CISO.
And we went to City Walk before Angus.
They were near they were nearby each other.
And we went to that store and bought shirts that say I heart Hollywood.
Oh, yeah.
Properly decorated for our pitch.
They were the shirts were met with a lot of forced grins.
And our show was not picked up.
But if it had been, we still wouldn't be making it because CISO is dead.
So hey, thanks.
Store.
Yeah.
Upstart Crow is the name of I was just going through my receipts for tax purposes.
That shirt was a business write off for a meeting.
So I now know it was the Upstart Crow.
Thank you for helping the pitch.
Yeah, you're helping keep them in business basically.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
I'm legitimizing it and I encourage everyone to go there.
So yeah.
Oh, you know what else you can get there are like what you can buy license drivers licenses
for like movie stars or Elvis Presley or Marilyn Monroe, Dr. Evil.
And there's a bizarre like some of them like there's a space for occupation.
And in the case of Dr. Evil, it's like mad genius, but in the case of Beyonce, it's like
single ladies.
Like it's there's no consistency to what the occupations are.
So I will try the Upstart Crow for that.
My memory is that half of it is also just Betty Boop merchandise.
Is that wrong?
Yeah, that's a lot of Betty Boop merchandise.
I mean, a lot of those generic Hollywood souvenir stores are Betty Boop and James Dean and Marilyn.
Maybe the easiest license to get possibly that might just be floating out there.
Well, but so there are lots lots of stories.
But there's another tiny one that we should probably fit a little bit of time of the podcast
to talk about, which is the arrival of Donald J. Trump into the Hall of Presidents.
Are we doing that one first?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Are we doing the?
Why I just don't want the well, we can we can hit the cadavers as well.
Which order?
I think let's do cadavers.
Let's talk cadavers.
OK, OK.
Trump teaser, but cadavers.
I want to take the lead on this.
OK, OK.
So this is one that I feel like a lot of theme park news sites did not pick up on.
But Scott.
Oh, yes, I was aware of this because of Matt Wyatt, a friend of the podcast.
Thank you, Matt.
I sent sent this to Scott.
And this is part of a Reuter series called The Body Trade Cashing in on the Dead.
And I have some of it in front of me.
The summary of this this series, this is part six cadavers in the ballroom.
Doctors practice their craft in America's favorite hotels.
Big names in hospitality have a little known sideline.
They rent space to physicians who drain on cadavers and body parts.
There is scant regulation and some public health specialists warm up of biosafety risks.
So this is the opening of the article.
And I think you'll quickly see why we're talking about it.
Just outside the operating theater, the organizers of a medical conference wore Minnie Mouse
ears.
Inside, as doctors practiced on three cadavers, blood from one of the human specimens seeped
through a layer of wrapping.
I guess we should have had a wording before that.
They leak a lab technician set of the bodies.
This session.
So mouse ears, blood leaking already.
Yeah.
The sessions held last month attended by a Reuters reporter weren't at a hospital or
medical school.
They were part of a so-called cadaver lab.
It was one of scores of such events over the past six years that have been held at a hotel
or its convention center.
And now here it comes.
In this case, doctors practice nerve root blocks and other procedures on cadavers in
one of the Grand Harbor Ballroom salons at Disney's Yacht and Beach Club Resort Convention
Center.
That's right.
There's the twist.
A cadaver lab at the beautiful Yacht and Beach Club Resort.
Yes.
Which if you haven't been down to Disney World is kind of the, what do you, it's sort of
the New England themed, very, very picture, picturesque.
One of my favorite hotels that I stayed at when I was a kid.
Very upscale and.
Yeah.
A deluxe resort.
In fact, it is classified as and the ballrooms were also just conventions and weddings are
held are also being used to take actual dead bodies and do tests and practice operations
on them.
Online Disney refers to ballroom, their ballrooms at this particular place as regal and resplendent.
And offered no comment on this cadaver lab story.
And so what's crazy to me is this resort just got like a top to bottom refurbishment and
this is already, and it was already like one of the most expensive properties in Orlando.
And knowing that just feet away from your room or just like bone pieces going flying.
Yeah.
That was part of this article is that whatever, whatever tests and operations are being done,
they do like put down plastic and sanitize the room to some extent.
But also.
Yeah.
But also just, you know, surgeries are pretty wild and little bone pieces can go flying
up and hit the ceiling.
And one of the concerns in the article was for people who think that this is, you know,
it's basically like not these events are not really under the purview of health code regulations.
Health code.
Also like any convention, people forget to shut doors.
So I think the reporter was like, I was standing outside in the hallway, which was a public
access hallway and I could see a corpse.
Like this is crazy.
Disney doesn't need this money from cadaver labs.
Like there's so many hotels in Orlando and there's so much convention space.
And also this is a very weird part of like these bodies come from like after they, you
know, Oregon donors or if you donate your body to science and after they're done with
it, they're like, well, does someone else want to turn with this body?
Like you end up going to Disney World for the phrase body brokers was used in this article.
Yeah.
So you go to a body broker and you get a body for whatever you want.
Oh my God.
There's a horrifying thing.
I think in the same article that said the writer's reporter witnessed one participant
who was operating on this dead body because this is what it's for.
They're trying to learn how to operate on or test out new like medical devices that
are for sale or one of the people that was operating like, you know, just had a hand,
a hands full of blood and he was trying to wash and there's no sink in a lot of these
places you have to go to the bathroom and he had to go arms outstretched out into the
hallway like covered in whatever.
I mean, I don't know his blood still, it depending on how old the cadaver is.
I don't know what that would happen to blood after a while, but there's gotta be some
liquid.
There's gotta be still some liquid in these bodies and they have to be kept fresh.
So yeah, you could be walking through with your family and there's a young medical student
just dripping with like goo.
A kid who was like, you know, the snow white ride was too scary for me.
I don't want to go on that again.
Oh, that's OK, honey.
You don't have to quit.
Get me to a bathroom.
I need to I need to be sanitized.
Blood dripping off guys as he walks by goofy and yacht captain attire.
Yeah, the other features of this hotel are a big pool area with a water slide that comes
out of a ship wreck called Storm Along Bay and a snack stand called Beaches and Cream.
Hugely popular.
Both of these things hugely popular among Disney loyalists.
Steps away.
Blood and bone exposed.
I imagine that it's like you're eating at Beaches and Cream and just think of the scene
in the Ghost and Ghostbusters two when they come from the sewer covered in goo and they
interrupt Bill Murray, who's eating there and they're getting goo over all these rich,
fancy people.
That's exactly what happens at Beaches and Cream when you're trying to eat one of the
kitchen sink floats, which is there like fifty dollar giant mess of ice cream.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, you can only assume also with the New England theming that someone there speaks
in that tycoon.
Oh, well, my heavens, I never.
This for five hundred dollars a night.
Yeah, I really didn't say else of the fact that see the so just to give the body brokers
credit, the bodies in this operation are screened for HIV and hepatitis.
But there's certain things that you can't really pre-track like tuberculosis.
So there could be tuberculosis filled bones flying around this room.
And also, as the article points out, you know, like a little a little piece of bone ends
up in a carpet that they didn't put plastic down on.
And then in two days, there's a wedding there and there's a one year old crawling around
on the floor who's like, you know, nobody's nobody has eyes on and is like, you know,
he's like licking the carpet or something.
I'm describing a very grim scene.
This is why this article was written.
It's why people are concerned.
And yeah, and it's it's I don't know.
I mean, it's another just insane branch of health care in our country.
It's just another insane dark side story to how America deals with health stuff.
But like, it's crazy to me that like Disney, I mean, they must have known when they're
booking these events, like they would have to know someone's going to someone's going
to find out about this at some point.
But like, I really haven't seen much uproar about it.
So we might be helping break this.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
In our world.
But reading the Reuters website all the time.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not too constantly on Reuters just once in a while.
And yeah, the maybe though Disney, maybe the body brokers have a little situation, a little
backdoor situation with Disney and maybe there's maybe Disney has needs for before dead bodies.
Maybe like maybe you're like, you know, that's the correct amount of weight to test roller
coasters with or I don't know.
No other way to do that.
Yeah.
How else could you wait sewing together?
And couldn't do the same job.
No, no, no.
Well, look, you'd have to like stack them up and make you have to make sand arms and
legs.
Who knows if that's complicated.
Why not just go straight to the source?
And I think they need the bodies because they need to refresh the skeletons on the Pirates
of the Caribbean every once in a while.
So what other way are they going to get those?
There's no way to make a fake skeleton.
It's expensive and expensive.
Yeah, you can.
But it's like five hundred thousand dollars for a fake skeleton.
Michael, that sounds like mere Tom Fulary to me.
No.
I'm being very highly serious.
Well, this I think there is there is one recent audio animatronic that very well that very
likely may be a reanimated corpse, which is the new animatronic of Donald J. Trump in
the Hall of Presidents.
Yeah, here we go.
Here we go.
Disney World.
Now that we got the cadavers out of the way, we can we can we can get on to this.
Cut to the chase.
I mean, look, this is a this is a story that's been out there a bunch already.
If you're listening to this podcast, I can only assume that you've seen photos, perhaps
a number of photos of the of the glorious Trump bot.
But anyway, it was they they snuck it in very just under the white, maybe thinking that
you slide it into the holiday season and people don't really pay attention.
People's trips are pre booked and families are there and they don't attract a lot of
trouble.
I was I was just always I was wondering if this was ever going to open.
I can't believe it did in 2017.
And suddenly one day it happened and we dropped everything and we had a little emergency session
of what to tweet about it.
Our own tweet store.
It was our little The Post style.
All right.
What do we do?
Roll your sleeves up, gentlemen.
But it's there.
Trump's Trump's there and he's making his speeches and waving his hands around every day.
Ugliest Donald John Trump, as he says, Donald John Trump.
By the way, and I think people mentioned something like this, but I don't know.
I haven't seen anyone say his name is Don John, the same as Joseph Gordon Levitt's character
in the movie Don John, where he's like, I like to eat things by women.
Whatever my cars, my phone.
I like lifted weights and I like porno.
And that's Don John.
But that's the same name.
I don't know.
He's Donald Trump is Don John.
I know.
Yeah.
You never hear the John.
Yeah, it's only it's only Jay.
And he says it on the ride or on the on during the show.
Yeah.
Donald John Trump.
So, I mean, a lot of people have seen the the the character and it's, you know, we don't
we only have audio here to do.
It's hard to describe, but he's it's it's it's grotesque, certainly.
Coolish.
In credit.
It were me.
I'd be incredibly insulted.
I mean, it looks it technically it's a good life.
Another generation of lifelike animatronics, but it really, really makes him look like
shit.
Yeah.
The only speech he gives is probably the most coherent speech Donald Trump has ever given,
probably because it wasn't written by one of the fucking white supremacist speechwriters
he has on stand.
It wasn't written off the top of his dome.
It wasn't just coming off his dome.
Yeah.
Imagine yours wrote like a pretty safe spiel about America.
Oh, Jason, let me correct you.
Steve Bannon didn't really have anything to do with the presidency.
That's that's come.
Oh, is that what we're going with?
No, no, no.
He was a he was a coffee boy.
Basically, he was an overblown.
He was he was there.
He was in the room.
I think he was just fetching people snacks.
So just to correct your oh, you're right.
I think I forgot.
So he is sloppy.
Yeah, obviously.
I think he was probably going to get people coffees and that's why he's now he's sloppy.
Steve.
Yeah, God.
Yeah.
The speech.
It's I mean, I don't not to just read it.
I'm trying to remember.
I mean, the part the part that I noted and have written down is specifically the line
being American is to be an optimist.
Yes, that's what I was going to say, too.
Yeah, because I don't think he's ever he's he is not an optimistic man.
No, no.
At the I put that side by side to another prewritten speech of a rare prewritten speech
of his, which is from his inauguration address, rusted out factories scattered like tombstones
across the landscape of our nation.
Though I guess that's him describing the past and the optimist saying no more.
And I after the last year, yeah, no more of those factories.
He scrubbed them all up.
Rust be gone.
That was apparently a thing revealed in that.
What is that book that everyone's going nuts on?
The fury of fire and fury just released.
Yeah.
That inauguration address was supposed to be like a rousing victory cry.
But because like Trump is such a grumpy gust and he looked so unhappy, it like he came
out as like just a just a horrifying like, oh, well, and it was the weather was the weather
was the people.
No one was there.
That too.
No one was watching.
But people seemed like they were lining up for this.
All the presidents and why not?
Why not watch?
Watch the train wreck.
Why not check it out?
Oh, yeah.
I mean, well, the day that it broke on Twitter was very excited.
We did all just have to drop everything.
We were texting each other and refreshing Twitter every two minutes.
And like because imagine being in the park when that happens.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's happening with no announcement.
We can be the first in this audience.
Yeah, for sure.
Friend of the podcast, Bugsy Malone, Bugsy the gangster, as he is canonically known on
our podcast.
I'd call him a friend.
The way he threatened us.
So easy on Bugs.
I loved his skeleton dance, his graveyard dance.
But he's a skeleton now.
So Bugsy Bones was there, presumably for a cadaver operation.
Checking on some of his buddies from Sing Sing.
I know him.
I was in Sing Sing with him.
He was there.
He happened to be there on a pre-books trip like a week out and like a lot of a lot of
Manga hats, he said, a lot of folks very excited to go represent and check out their guy.
And he alerted me to two things.
I mean, you can everybody can watch video of the attraction if you haven't already.
It's this odd, stiff speech that is pretty nothing other than the fact that it's not
in line with how he talks otherwise.
But this I would not know without Bugsy that when he when they in the roll call, when they
get to Abraham Lincoln, he does this odd.
He like gestures to Lincoln, who's sitting pretty close to him with kind of this attitude
of like, huh, pretty good, huh?
There he is.
Hey, I ain't heard a lot of these other folks.
I don't know about no John Tyler, but hey, Lincoln, pretty good.
Abraham Lincoln classic best class act winner.
But there's another thing that I haven't seen written up anywhere, which is almost odder
than the than the gesture to Lincoln.
And I'll just I'm going to turn the laptop and show you guys look up a video.
If you look up like close up Trump and watch his watch what Trump is doing for the entire
roll call, because if you don't know in the Hall of Presidents, they say the name of every
president, right robots of all of them.
And right around the middle, they get to I'm at a backtrack right around the middle.
They get to Teddy Roosevelt and just watch the video of this.
Look what he does during Teddy Roosevelt.
He kind of holds up his hand and starts counting or like he puts his fiddle with fingers.
I notice this too.
I have this I have this written down.
He has his middle finger and his thumb and he like rubs them kind of together.
And it's this real odd.
He only does it once.
The only robot does it once.
And I don't know if that's a thing Trump does.
I'm confused by it.
I don't.
It's not I'd be concerned if it were something.
It's I was concerned it was going to be the OK sign.
You know how the alt right has adopted to be like, you know, OK, simple.
But it's not some dog whistle something.
No, I don't.
I can't imagine them putting that in there.
Like that's horrifying.
But it's not.
It looks like more like he's rubbing like when you know, like hey, you owe me money.
Like when a mobster like rubs their fingers together, they're the money.
It feels like there are a few other in addition to this subtle digs at him.
Obviously, just the way he looks.
But also like we were looking at close up like video of of the other presidents who
all have an odd look on their face and do like kind of slightly roll their eyes once
in a while while he's talking.
Yeah.
And we went back and my girlfriend and Lindsey, we went back and we looked at like the Obama
one and they don't seem to be moving their eyes at all when Obama was speaking.
So there feels like there's some subtle stuff.
Also I noticed when watching that same video, Trump looks away when the other like so they'll
announce a president and everybody looks to all the robots look to the right.
Trump will look to the left.
Trump will look a different direction like and look like an idiot because they're all
looking at one president except for him who kind of looks or like kind of looks bored
or like looks over.
He's like kind of just staring into the distance.
Yeah.
He's not really focused on anything.
And yeah, you can watch every single president goes hard right to hard left and only he's
just staring at.
I yeah, I think he's I think he's bored.
There's he's very he does a very odd like thumbs up gesture.
That is so funny.
If you haven't watched this whole video at the very end when the music soars, his little
like his little hands and this like tiny gesture where he's just like giving the thumbs up
like this barely has his thumbs up from his stomach.
Like there's probably like six inches from his thumbs to his stomach.
And it's so funny.
I mean, it's it's funny to think they captured his dumbass long tie and his stupid open jacket
that his jacket is just always open.
It's never buttoned like he never talks like this and he never dresses like this.
And I've never seen him in anything other than the like I'm sure he wears other ties,
but I only know like big bright red long, long.
Yeah, usually.
And they dressed him up a bit.
He's I don't know.
He's still one of the the dumber looking ones on the stage, despite people being in like
patterned wigs and frilly collars and 18 hundreds clothes.
Disney really, you know, with this attraction, like this is one of the ones that it's like,
you probably can't ever close it like they painted themselves into a corner by like,
yeah, we have to add the current president.
And then like in the 90s, it's like, and now the current president has to talk.
And like there's all these like artifacts in the lobby.
Like they couldn't demolish this building because they would have to protect all these
artifacts and then they'd have to destroy all these robots of like American heroes.
Although that said, if you look at them cumulatively, it is a real hodgepodge of like rapists, sociopaths,
outright racists, genocide committers, drone drone strike enthusiasts like all the presidents
is full of vassals, full of horrible assholes.
They don't maybe they wouldn't deny that, though, it's not as if they're say these
are the 45 greatest men that ever know that.
Yeah, that's true.
But it's certainly.
Yeah.
When you think about who's in there and what they've done, it's like, oh, there's Andrew
Jackson, the butcher.
Yeah, there he is.
And he's looking at Trump, but he's like rolling his eyes and you're like, hey, don't roll
your eyes, Andrew Jackson.
Who do you think of the 45 presidents and then let's just take like 45 random pirates
from Pirates of the Caribbean who have done worse things?
We don't know.
We'd have to make up the backstory of the pirates.
But right.
I mean, cumulatively, when you have the arm, the might of the United States military at
your hand.
Yeah.
And all Jack Sparrow's got is a bottle of rum.
And that and they also a lot of the pirates seem nice.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's they are Disney by the pirates are disney by the presidents.
You cannot know no matter how much you wash away, you can't wash away those sins.
I think it's possible somebody might buy one of those brides at that auction and just like
take them out to some nice.
Oh, yeah, they're very nice.
Those guys are too goofy looking to have to too bad intentions.
They couldn't dream of course.
Of course, those pirates are just nice guys.
They burned down the city.
Sure.
When it comes down to it, they just want to goof around.
There are Caribbean town carnage rusted out, rusted out restaurants.
And if they did, if they get rid of all the presidents, which I think they if they want
to do it, they have to get rid of it like in the in an election year, probably like
at the end of a president's tenure.
So no one accuses them of being bipartisan or saying, well, you're getting anyone's running.
That's well.
Yeah.
I think that's a good thing, though, maybe unless there's like a crazier guy than Trump.
If they if by some bizarre stretch of the imagination, Trump is impeached and Pence
gets in there, I could see them going, all right, you know what?
If this is the way the president sees going to be, we're going to have to be changing
these out every year and a half.
Then maybe we don't do this anymore.
Also, if they have a replacement ready, they're like, you can't tear down the hall of presidents.
Well, see X-Men's mansion now.
OK, well, does it destroy it?
Left can agree on that.
We want to go to the danger room.
You just put masks on all the existing ones.
Millard, Bill, Maher, and yeah, damn it.
Yeah, got to get straight in there.
Oh, man, that would be great if it was just a show showing all the X-Men like all of the
X-Men.
We're getting ahead of ourselves.
We should do this in the last second.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll save the hall of X-Men.
The last thing about the Trump thing, a hearty jeers to that one idiot who protested it,
to that one idiot who already in the lamest way possible stood up when Trump started talking
and started yelling, lock him up.
And it's like you see the picture of this guy and he's like the biggest dipshit looking
white dude.
Boho, bohemian looking white dude.
And then when reporters asked him, like, what do you say to the criticisms of like you kind
of ruined a lot of people's fucking vacation or what like ruined people's days like these
people should check their privilege, said the man who paid money to go to Disney World
and yell, lock him up.
He even I found a bigger interview and it's even one step beyond, which is that he went
he was already going there with his family.
Yeah.
And he says, you know, because, hey, I couldn't afford it.
My son, are you kidding?
I could.
So he's being taken there by his family.
Family.
And he says he's on a parent paid Disney World vacation yelling about, check your privilege.
Exactly.
And like there's there's there were probably people in that room who like saved up for
years or maybe this is the one time they got to go.
Maybe there was like a family reunion.
And it's like, come on, dude, you're not changing.
And it's like, shut up.
Like fair go protest.
There's plenty of real things to go protest and go protest the president for real.
Where he go nonprofits.
But it's like, come on, man.
Like most people are taking a nap during this ride.
You probably just startled a lot of sleepy dads and like kids and stuff.
I feel like this whole time I've kind of been looking forward to maybe protests happening
in that thing.
And then it happened and I didn't like it.
It's like the way it went down version of it.
I don't know what you can do other than like hop on stage and try to steal the robot.
Like other than just trying to disrupt the show.
I've said it several times, but I know that there's big old turkey legs right next to
the Hall of Presidents.
I remember them specifically in the Liberty Square area and just nailing it real hard
in the face.
Yeah, I mean, that would be that would be fun.
Like that's true.
There are funny ways to do this.
I mean, you feel a lot of nice imagineers put a lot of time, but I think even they would
have to go, oh, that was really funny that you cleanly took the head off of the Trump
robot with a turkey leg.
They'd have to admire it.
Yeah, they would have to go.
Well, I get it.
Like, but aren't there rumors that there's security in these shows as well?
Oh, maybe they have been.
They have plainclothes security officers in the.
Well, there are spikes that we know there's like not like hard pointed spikes, but they
did add like a layer flourishes or little.
They almost look like Fleur de Lis, but they look like they're made out of fucking balls.
So yeah, I don't think those are really dissuading anybody.
They built a wall.
They had to fill the wall.
All right.
I mean, there's a thousand things to say about this, but the other thing they seem to be
doing to try to quell the potential outbursts is that they don't really provide a point
for the booing to happen.
I mean, this protester found one.
He just started yelling, lock him up.
But as opposed to I've watched now just to make sure I watch a video of the previous
presidents who all actually gave speeches, Clinton, W. Bush and Obama.
And for sure, in all of the previous iterations, they say, ladies and gentlemen, the current
president of the United States blank.
And I watched one of George W. Bush from 2009 where he gets a rocket surplus.
People are like, George W. Bush.
Yeah, it's like it's huge for him.
But they don't.
So so they kind of downplay that by having nine.
Yeah, yeah.
Like I said, January, like when he was getting right before watching the video of like his
last appearance before they closed, right.
Sending him out, I'm not sure.
But so they sort of don't give you a boo point, which they've never done in a previous
iteration of the ride.
And they they kind of get around it by having Washington make a little speech, which he
also did for Obama.
And then Trump says his own name as part of saying his own oath of office.
It's like, and now we go to the present.
That's all that's all the narrator says.
It doesn't they don't announce the president, which they weirdly all they also did for Obama.
But then they also said Morgan Freeman, who hightailed the fuck out of this riot as soon
as Trump appeared, he says, ladies and gentlemen, Barack Hussein Obama and Hussein in it.
And I'm sure there were booze for no bomb.
There were.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
That's why they've been worried about this thing is that they're ever since the president
started talking, and especially with Bush and Obama, people have been like actively
cheering or booing.
Yeah, but no one knows President Baby Man broke our brains so much.
No one knew how people would react to him because everything is chaos now.
Everything is insane.
So like looting our dear theme parks.
Yeah, looting our Dean.
But you know, this is this.
We're all going to forget he's in there soon enough.
I mean, like, you know what?
I'll say they did a good job.
The fact there's only been that one protest, I think that will just swayed other people
from doing it.
Yeah, nothing else made you out.
We didn't see anything else major.
The real quick to go quick.
I also think that the only one of the only presidents Trump looks at is Nixon when they
announced Nixon.
I think I think we can look at it again.
Look at it again.
He looks at Nixon.
The other thing also, they they make a big this has never been in a previous iteration,
but they they very specifically point out in the narration that it's really it's more
about the idea of a president.
They say this several times.
Oh, goody.
Once again, we place our trust in the idea of a president.
This also after a lot of at the very beginning, they mentioned Walt Disney a lot, which I
think is a way to say shut up nerd, settle down.
Walt wanted this.
Yeah, that's in the lobby, too.
There's like a corner.
There's like here's James K. Polk's vest and here's Lincoln's hat.
And here's a corner about Walt Disney.
Our 47th president, my president.
Geez.
Oh, yeah.
I think invoking him is this way like he would have wanted that he loved American history.
Even if it's not a guy you love, don't you?
He belongs here.
Right, guys.
He has to be here.
This was Nixon when it opened.
What do you want?
Yeah.
Here's we'll show you a video of Nixon dedicating the monorail with Walt.
They were buddies.
You're going to complain now.
Yeah, he was a he loved piece of shit.
Conservative politicians.
What are you going to do?
He was Walt Disney.
He'd be so happy about all this.
Yeah.
Not like Iger turning his back on leaving the counts, the special.
Oh, the special business council.
Business council.
Does he want to run?
What would Walt?
No, that's all the councils are disbanded by this.
No more.
By the way, also, another real quick thing, although we can't let's talk for 45 more minutes.
There's a ton to say here.
But the I was I got curious if there was any real if there were any Google results for
Donald Trump Disneyland before 2015, like before he was literally in the park.
Right.
Is there any association between Trump and Disney?
And I found two things.
One to speak of the heads of Disney, Michael Eisner in actually when Trump started campaigning,
Michael Eisner said Trump expresses what a lot of people have in their unconscious, nightmarish
thoughts.
I don't think that style of insulting people, everybody you can insult should be representing
our country.
Michael Eisner, hard against hard against Donald Trump, although he also made his company
made a giant deal with Sinclair broadcasting the right wing fake local news syndicate that
John Oliver's railed against.
So Eisner talks to talk.
Maybe doesn't walk the walk.
But the but the other I think I then I broaden the search to just Donald Trump theme park.
And here's here's a fact that I never heard.
There's something called Steeplechase Park, which is a part of Coney Island.
Oh, sure.
I'm one of three zones of Coney Island.
And in 1965, this area, this beloved seaside amusement park was bought and torn down by
Fred Trump.
There it is.
Wow.
Pretty crazy.
Old man, Fred Trump shutting down the guy arrested at a KKK rally.
Is that right?
In Brooklyn?
Was he?
Yeah, I feel like there's there's some weirdness in the family.
If we get if we.
Oh, there's some weirdness in the family.
I feel like there's a little bit.
And he hate I bet.
I mean, for sure, he hated fun.
Yeah, he hated fun.
He was like Art Carney from the Christmas special.
He was a cartoonish old man who only liked business.
He liked the day's business and he liked the Klu Klux Klan.
He was another character.
So many characters have been based on Donald Trump in cinematic history.
Maybe Art Carney's character from the Disney.
Gramps Gramps was probably based on old Fred Trump.
Yeah, I think that's probably right.
Oh, an old man who destroyed an amusement park.
He's a literal Scooby Doo.
Yeah, really.
And the and the end he ended up then like the zoning for the area didn't let them put
up housing developments, which is what he wanted to do.
So they just he sold it back to the city for a frustrated state three years later, having
torn down all the fun.
Wow.
Yeah.
Crazy, right?
So we hate the Trump's hate theme parks.
Yeah.
And look what they've done since we're here.
Now we're all mad and talking about our little escapist theme park podcast has now become
all politicized because of the because of the Trump family again.
But why don't we segue into something lighter?
Absolutely possible anti trust media media company marriages.
Yeah.
So our validation of all media.
Our final story that we have to talk about is, yes, we is a horrible thing, probably
for everyone involved.
Media news, everything.
The merger between Fox and Disney or I guess Disney's buying Fox.
What do they want to call it?
It's not really a merger.
I guess buying their assets of 21st century Fox, which is like the creative wing of the
Fox company.
Fox News, Fox, the broadcasting channel is not going with them.
Yeah, no.
Some of the shows are.
So the way television movies get made is insane to look at from two normal people.
And it's kind of complicated to explain.
But there are studios, there's channels, there's production companies, there's.
Yeah.
And confusingly, Fox, the studio is not necessarily affiliated with Fox, the channel.
Right.
Very confusing.
I've learned some of these things, by the way, because I have a project in the works
that now I believe because of this deal is owned by Disney.
So I'd like to say I'm all for it.
I don't know what you guys are talking about.
Thank you, Disney, my beloved new overlord.
Well, if you get a free pass out of it, of course, it's good.
Sure.
No matter.
You don't want to ask for that?
Renegotiate now.
If you don't give me what I want, maybe I'll speak ill of this whole thing on my podcast.
You don't want that, do you?
So Mike, so what are some of the things Disney would get out of this deal?
Well, I mean, I know when everyone's really speculating.
So I don't really know exactly what everything is perfectly, but they're going to get like
Avatar, they're going to get Alien, the Alien franchise.
They're going to get Simpsons.
They're going to get Family Guy.
They're going to get Die Hard.
They're going to get like a ton of like back catalog of TV show and movies because it's
very confusing because sometimes you look at the Wikipedia and it says like this was co-produced
by two studios.
So I'm not exactly sure everything, but I think most of the things I just mentioned,
they're going to get like full control over.
And of course, the big thing and probably the big reason they wanted to do this was
all the Marvel characters from Fox get to finally come home to Disney.
We're talking X-Men.
We're talking Fantastic Four.
And we're talking Deadpool.
And we're talking Deadpool, folks.
Talking motherfucking ass Deadpool.
Yeah, he's irreverent.
The merc with the mouth is finally back home at the House of Ideas.
Everyone's favorite, like everyone's fifth favorite 90s character that is somehow like
a giant star now is, yeah, he's coming home to Disney.
Which and so the big question is, does this does the Disney ownership affect, I can't
like, will it affect how these properties are released or do they have to be more family
friendly or anything?
I can't imagine they will.
Well, Bob Iger was asked about Deadpool.
Some reporter was like very concerned.
Like, is Deadpool going to go away now?
We're going to get more Deadpool.
He's going to get to say bad, naughty words.
And Bob Iger is like, yes, Deadpool will still have his wit and his irreverency.
Our rated still.
I think there's still room for our rated.
We don't allow a sides to camera here at the Disney Corporation.
No more, no more comments.
He's going to be in.
Yeah.
He can't say like, what is this Rosie O'Donnell over here?
Like one of his famous quips where he he's like for some reason in 1997.
Oh, Rosie.
He can't do.
He can't do a bunch of jumps and flips to third eye blind semi charmed life.
Yeah.
It's going to have to change a little bit, but it remains to be seen because because
they have a whole Marvel apparatus that makes look and Jason and I are big Marvel boys as
we've said on the show before.
We were kids.
Yeah, we were kids.
Um, uh, and they make now they make three movies.
This is made three Marvel movies a year and they vary from like, you know, oh, good to
okay.
And we'll see what happens.
We don't know if Deadpool, it will throw things off because no one has said the, no one said
fuck in Marvel yet.
So when will Deadpool come in and say that and will it just upset everything?
Well, and it'll be the new, uh, uh, now I can't go.
What was the first talkie line?
Um, it's not, I was going to say here's looking at you kid.
That is no hard incorrect.
Heard nothing.
You ain't heard nothing yet.
It'll be a you ain't heard nothing yet moment.
The first time fuck is said in a Marvel Disney.
Hey, fuck off Robert Downey Jr. and he'll say his real name and then people will, I
don't know.
I have a feeling it's going to be separate.
I feel like it's going to be a thing and then maybe he like winks at the camera or maybe
in like 10 years when there's another like mega Avengers crossover movie, Deadpool shows
up for a couple of minutes.
I think they're separate, but I think X-Men and Fantastic Four movies go back to one.
I think they relaunch.
I think they burn off this dark Phoenix one.
Well, they got a lot of movie that what's weird about this is like when you buy a movie
studio, they have a year or two worth of movies.
So they have like three X-Men movies, they have Deadpool two already shot and made.
Yeah, so that has to come out via Disney.
New Mutants.
This deal is also going to take like a year to fully, I think, process.
I think Trump's already like, hey, great.
This is this sounds good to me.
Like he doesn't see a problem with only Disney owning everything.
Is there any chance it gets shot down by your right?
Probably under the Republican government.
But yeah, for it shouldn't.
There's no it should know.
I mean, it's bad for like, yeah, the monopoly like media corporation monopolies.
It's a bad thing.
And is it happening because the the Murdoch children are fail sons and daughters?
I would like to fucking idiots.
That's what I assumed.
It's like Murdoch is going to die one day and doesn't trust any of his children with
this stuff.
I'm just going to parrot what I heard a fellow podcaster, Jim Hill, say on his podcast is
that they're concerned that like content is the is the thing that's going to move, you
know, whatever streaming service you have.
And they were looking ahead and they're like, we're going to lose to Disney.
We may as well cut our losses now and make 60 billion dollars.
And because that's how much like the deal.
It's like a 60 billion dollar deal.
They're going to keep their news network.
They're going to still keep their organizations of evil.
Those are going to happen.
Apparently does not go anywhere.
And a lot doesn't.
Yeah.
They're going to keep that there.
And this is a weird thing, too, with modern family is a Fox owned show, but it airs on
ABC.
So then Disney gets control of modern family and gets all their residual money and all
that shit.
Disney gets control of Avatar, which they have had to license for the parks.
And now they will save all this licensing money because they'll own it outright.
And they will put out the Avatar films.
If they are.
I think this is like Trump and his fake news award show that he's like stalling on because
he doesn't know how to actually do it.
I'm worried that there is no Avatar to there will never be an Avatar to does the Disney
thing, but the heat on him to actually put his money where his mouth like he hasn't shot
a single inch of film or anything.
And he's just like in a submarine going, I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
God, oh, God, oh, God.
I got to show up at his house shows up.
I think he shows up.
Oh, hey, man, was that today?
I think I girl show up underwater in a sub is another submarine.
Oh, another open hail him.
He didn't make it like they were hitting Mickey or.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, no, that shape.
It's no.
It looks like the Nemo sub from Disneyland.
That's Bob Iger sub.
Oh, yeah.
He's like, surrender the film.
Surrender the outline.
The unobtaining.
What are the kids doing?
Why are there kids in Avatar now?
Tell us when will we see the mighty Akron again?
Yeah.
Mighty Banshee.
They saw us.
We want to see them.
Yeah, there's going to be a lot of that going on.
Iger having to shake people down for the movies they promised years ago.
Yeah.
Twenty eight dresses will finally get 28 dresses.
Now, do you guys know I was reading about movies?
20th century, 21st century Fox's release.
Marley and me and Brideswords, both Brides Bride Wars, Bride Wars released on the same
day.
Isn't that interesting?
I thought that was interesting.
I suppose.
I guess.
They're kind of cutting in on the same market, aren't they?
A dog movie and a wedding movie?
Yeah.
Bride Wars is raunchy though.
Yeah, I guess it was a little raunchy.
I think they're going to get like 24.
They're going to get that franchise.
Oh, right.
So you're going to see I think all these we're going to get diehards for we were probably
already going to get diehards for the rest of our lives.
We're going to get everything.
Everything's coming back already.
And now Disney is the king of doing everything again over and over again.
I would like to put Mike and my name in the hat to write a big, loud, dumb 90s X-Men movie
with characters with giant guns and lots of patches and bright colors and lots of explosions
because I think that's what those X-Men movies are missing.
Yeah, I think that they need the outfit.
I mean, a big thing with me is the outfits.
Yeah, you got to have the outfits.
Well, that's that squealing that rock guitar that.
Oh, man.
Yes.
And you bring the theme back.
You bring the theme back from the 90s cartoon.
You like make put the orchestra behind it.
It's all melodrama.
Every character is screaming like melodrama soap opera melodrama lines about their powers
and there's love triangles.
Jubilee's got a giant yellow trench coat.
Yeah.
This sounds much better.
It sounds like a lot of fun.
Then the joyless black leather costumes that they've been stuck in the in their singer
verse made for so long directed by international sex criminals.
I wonder how he's doing in international waters.
Maybe he might.
His submarine is going to bump with Cameron one of these days.
These guys are in submarines.
Kevin's spacey submarine is one place I'm safe.
The bottom of the ocean.
Yeah.
Also, Fantastic Four was so odd and joyless in the last round, but you've also seen Fantastic
Four iterations that are so bright and colorful that they seem kind of silly.
But like I would argue that that's not the problem with those movies being bright.
No, no, no.
Probably.
There was a way to do bright, but nobody I think anybody knows that everybody's doing
this like this this Nolan ripoff.
I guess Guardians is a good example of a bright, fun movie that doesn't feel stupid.
And like Thor Ragnarok has a ton of color.
It's just a lot of Jack Kirby design and color.
And like the least like that's that's another reason why I like the Marvel movies is because
they're not like your joyless affairs.
Yeah.
The Incredibles is essentially a great Fantastic Four movie.
Like a lot of that.
I mean, the family elements and even in some of the hours they ripped off all the powers.
Yeah, they just stole it.
It's exactly the Fantastic Four.
That's what you would do with that movie.
Pretty much.
So they have to just do that again.
So the Incredibles and the Fantas are in the same family.
Meet now.
Yes.
I actually if it was CGI, Incredibles and live versus live action.
Yeah.
I think it'll I think everything is collapsing, too, even though these companies are getting
bigger and bigger.
I think everything is collapsing.
No one knows.
Like we're bringing back the office on NBC.
Like barely been gone two years later.
The office is back and everything's like they're good.
They wanted to bring 30 rock anything that and 30 rock they're trying to bring back maybe.
And like that wasn't even a hit at the time, but it was a bigger hit than what they're
making now.
Everyone's desperate.
The walls like all these networks are going to collapse.
But I think that that'll probably happen with movies.
And you'll see like stuff like that.
The last gasp of entertainment will be throwing like Fantastic Four, Incredibles, Star Wars
meets the Deadpool.
Like it'll just be this disastrous, gross crossover stuff, which, you know, will be
that does sound fun.
But like, you know, just occurred to me, the entire Simpsons Family Guy crossover series.
This will happen.
They did.
They've done little crossovers and they did the big episode.
I think we're about seven years away from an entire new show where they just reset the
rules and they all live there.
They're next door neighbors.
They just merge everything.
Doesn't that seem?
Yeah, I mean, you probably should edit that out because it's a good idea that you could
pitch and they'd be like, yes, of course.
You can show run it.
And I'm just given four billion dollars immediately.
And you have to get it.
And Matt, don't get a cut.
But you have to do it.
You'll have to.
Seth will still do the voices.
Yeah, yeah.
And I'll have to meet him and say, say, sorry, you didn't get a cut.
But hey, thanks for coming in.
We got a hundred dollar check for you.
Man, that Peter voice so funny, dude.
We did see in your contract we will get you crooning.
You will.
Lie to Rose.
I'm home again.
We'll get that in there.
Seth can now perform on the on the Disney holiday specials more and more readily.
He starts going down Main Street like Regis Philbin used to do, but he's doing the Peter
voice or the quagmire voice.
Oh, God.
This is this episode, by the way, a lot of references to our own continuity.
We're declaring it.
Yeah, we can we can make insight.
We can make references to our old episodes.
Sure we can.
Seth McFarlane, I saw he commented on this because he was like he's like, it's fine.
Who cares?
Like he doesn't.
But also he was called by Bob Iger.
Like, oh, he had to.
He got a call.
Wow.
As did I believe Ryan Murphy because my Murphy has so many shows, Fox shows and also FX is
part of this as well.
Like they'll get Disney will get American Horror Story and like whatever else is on.
So like Ryan Murphy got a call, McFarlane got a call of like, hey, you know, just checking
in.
We're going to buy you and it doesn't matter if you're all right with it.
But you know, fuck you.
So to bring it back to to our fate.
So what does this mean for the parks?
Oh, well, and this is I'm going to probably I just listened to this Jim Hill podcast.
So by the way, the plug Jim Hill for shout out to our boys, the OGs Jim and Len, Len
Testa, they do a podcast called the Disney Dish Podcast.
And so I did my Disney Dish podcast hosted by Lentesta featuring Jim Hill.
It's a long title.
It's a very long.
It's not as long as Guardians of the Galaxy.
And the logo is in for some reason.
Yes, it's the touring for plans, touring plans.
It's touring plans.
Unofficial.
That'd be my only comment, guys, is decide the name.
But otherwise, we listen to it all the time.
Yeah.
So yeah, and also if like listen to that podcast, if you want people that really know what they're
talking about, like we're we're half.
Yeah.
Casual conjecture.
Yeah, yeah.
Also, non shout out to that one iTunes reviewer who said we don't do enough research.
Oh, that's right.
We saved it.
We didn't comment on it on the Twitter or anything.
We got a three star review ruined our perfect record way to give us a lot of stink coming
into 2018.
We had five stars for every review and then this guy gave us three and was like, these
guys are funny, but man, they are inaccurate.
Yeah.
And we're just here to say we will never do more research.
This is the amount you're going to get.
All right.
This is about it's part of the spirit that makes that makes the fans come back again
and again that and the inside references to things we've done before.
Ain't that right?
Bugsy bones.
Anyway.
So back to back to so the park.
So he was saying Jim Hill was saying that he thinks that right now the Imagineers or
according to his sources, because he is like, we are yet to have sources on this show.
We don't know people in the inside, but he apparently has these sources and they say
that, you know, there was a chance that they were going to build a big Marvel and in California
adventure right by that Guardians of the Galaxy ride.
But now he's saying there's a chance they may slow it down and build an entire Marvel
park.
So he might just do a full sized thing with all the properties at once, put them all in
the same place.
Because right now there's only so much room in California adventure and you know, you're
going to get a few things, but you're not going to get all of it because now they have
access to all of it.
Now you can make the X-Men's mansion.
Now you can make the Baxter building, the famous skyscraper that the Fantastic Four
live in.
Like you can do all of it and hey, maybe we wait.
Maybe we maybe we'd use that Toy Story lot and just do all Marvel.
Maybe that's the step.
So it's there's that's what it could mean for the parks.
But in the short term, yeah, maybe Cyclops shows up.
Maybe you can shake Cyclops's hand and California adventure in front of award wieners in front
of the hot dog store.
You can meet the apes, Caesar and the Coba.
Yeah, I think I'm wrong on that name.
I know Caesar is doctor.
I have not seen any of the new apes, which I hear they're very good.
Is Dr. Zayas in them?
No.
But they will own he's going to get that's right, because they're like prequels.
Yeah.
So like Dr. Zayas comes in later by the time.
Well, then by the end of the first original.
Yeah, they're they're they're they're now at a point where they're going to go build
their society and probably Dr. Zayas will be part of the but there's no young Zayas
either like his grandfather.
Not unless somebody we've not unless a little baby ape we've met already is a burgeoning
Zayas.
I think that's a big I think they should have had a young Zayas.
Well, now they can have in the parks, they can have a walk around Zayas.
There's so many they can have the old one.
They could have a young old.
Yeah, they could have the Charlton Heston era Zayas.
Yeah, they are multiple, multiple fantastic force.
You could go to Mr. Magorium's Wonder Emporium.
Well, that's that evergreen comedy reference Mr. Magorium's Wonder Emporium.
Unless we had anything else maybe to speculate that leads us into this next segment.
Because did anyone else have any thoughts before we do it?
All right, we're going to do it.
So here we go.
We are going to now build a Fox land, a Fox theme park.
Now I've decided maybe we leave the Marvel characters out because they all belong in
their own thing.
But using all the Fox properties, we're going to sort of just sketch out what we think blue
sky is what they call it.
What they could legally do.
Legally now.
Yeah, Disney could do with all these properties that they're buying and it's going to be
called Fox land.
I think we all agree on that.
It's nice and simple, simple, love it.
I was thinking, where does this thing go?
And my first thought was they, Iger should call Rupert Murdoch up and say, look, we want
that Fox lot over in Century City.
It's about 56 acres.
It's a little smaller than Disneyland, but that's perfect.
I think for the spirit of Fox.
Yeah.
OK, does everyone agree with that?
That's where it all is where it all began.
I think you demolish all the sound stages where the famous movies were.
There's this fave over that one giant steamroller rolls over and everybody's kicked off.
Bye bye, modern family set.
You move somewhere else.
Bye bye, Simpson's office.
This is writers go to hell.
Go find another place.
Go to the Disney lot.
Everyone go to the Disney lot.
We're building a theme park, a Fox theme park.
And I think you got to walk.
So when you walk into a theme park, that's Fox.
It's got to have the big famous 20th Century Fox logo with the spotlights up on the top.
Yeah.
That's what I was thinking.
That's the castle.
The big attraction that leads you down 21st Century Avenue.
And I think that you light that thing up, you got those spotlights going and you're
playing the fanfare.
Brum, bum, brum, bum.
Maybe at least once an hour, you light it up like the small world clock or maybe once
every 15 minutes or maybe just all day, all the time.
Live band is what I have a marching band playing the 21st Century Fox theme.
Uh huh.
I think that you have to go live band.
Yeah, that's a Disney Disney type thing.
You could trade them out in shifts, just kind of in way.
All right.
Now the drum bone players leave and we slide in the next shift and you do you do eight
hours of straight horn playing straight drumming because there's been people in the played
with the title like in their movies.
They sometimes do a different type of theme or if it's a futuristic theme, it's like an
EDM Fox theme or something.
I don't know that's real, but I assume Don John probably if it were if that was Fox.
Wait, is Don John Fox?
I don't know.
I can look up Don John in there.
Oh, fingers crossed.
There's a very funny on YouTube, like somebody doing it.
That theme is a recorder, just like in the 20th century hard to control recorder, the
20th century Fox theme or the Don John theme.
Oh, not Don John.
Oh, OK.
The general Fox theme.
Don John is not Fox.
All right.
You're out.
You're out of Fox.
So there won't be a walk around Don John.
OK, OK.
But we have the giant the logo.
That's yeah, that's yeah, we can all agree.
That's a simple that's a that's a gimme.
Yeah.
In now I'm thinking like we can start with like land ideas or ride ideas.
Do you have Jason?
You have one?
Well, I've got some legitimate stuff and then I've got some goofy bullshit.
So well, to be fair, Jason, this is all goofy bullshit.
Yeah, that's podcast.
Everything we're doing here.
OK, well, here's here's a deep.
Well, here's like a real nerd answer is that we could finally get the very original iteration
of Alien Encounter.
Yeah, sure.
This this didn't come up earlier, but Stitch's Great Escape, the Disney World Ride has like
officially closed now.
And you know, that was built on the bones of the Alien Encounter ride, legitimately
the scariest ride Disney ever built, which in a very early version was supposed to be
the aliens from Alien.
I forget what is what are those things called?
They have a name.
Oh, the xenomorph.
Yeah.
So you were supposed to it was supposed to be an alien teleported in and it was supposed
to be like a xenomorph.
So like that is 20th Century Fox.
So we could get a Prometheus or aliens like themed ride or walk through or show or something.
This is good because this is this sex into an idea I have.
I think there should be a whole sort of space land at because there's we have lost also
Lost in Space is a property that they have to and they're going to do a new series on
that.
So I think this alien ride would be perfect.
You put a fun sort of Lost in Space ride.
And then because I'm a thoughtful person when it comes to corporation and synergy, I think
you put in a new ride based on the TV show, the Orville.
So and what the thing about the Orville ride is you're riding and you're going, well, is
this supposed to be funny?
Is this supposed to be a serious ride?
And it sort of straddles the line between you're riding it and it's fun and it kind
of looks good, but not good.
And you're like, it's just you're not sure.
So you're done with the ride and you're like, oh, I kind of like that.
And you just you're scratching your head.
And it's a different type of an experience that you're getting when you ride on this
ride and of course, it's innovative.
It's innovative in that respect.
So I think that's a good idea.
I think that would be a whole space section.
Nice.
Titan A.E. perfect.
I had Titan A.E.
Great.
We can throw all of that in there.
Do you know more about Titan A.E. than I do?
I certainly don't.
We're going to teach the world.
We're going to revitalize the franchise.
No, I remember I don't think I saw it on theaters.
I think I saw it on videotape, but I remember liking it.
We can merge the Titan A.E. characters and the Treasure Planet characters finally.
Well, well, here's my idea.
Speaking of Titan A.E., Titan A.E. comes up on one of mine.
It's called Fox's Cartoon Street.
OK, go ahead.
Because like Mickey's Toontown, all of your favorite Fox cartoon characters live with
each other.
You know, so all of your favorites from The Simpsons and Family Guy and Titan A.E. live
on the same street.
And who's that?
Why it's the gang from Ice Age at the zoo.
And who's visiting them today on a class field trip?
Why it's young Alan Gregory, the child genius.
Of course.
Yes.
Hello, Alan.
And will the fish police are keeping an eye on everything?
The fish police are keeping an eye on everything.
I think that's great.
I think people are going to love that.
You know, you know, I want to see in there the Gracie Films silhouette.
Shushing everybody.
That's great.
And I would, if I may, I think we should also see the Capitol Critters there.
Also on the box.
Sure.
Yeah.
And the Airdine ABC, I believe, but owned by Fox.
So will Capitol Critters, capital famous 90s under one political satire cartoon all under
one glorious roof and simulate a different kind of cartoon.
And this I am legitimately think would think I legitimately think would be cool.
They own.
They made the Fantastic Mr. Fox movie.
And I really like that movie.
I think it's got a really cool look.
And that I feel like would be a great dark ride or walk through attraction.
Yeah, that would be fun.
I'm looking at mine and they're all goofy bullshit.
So look like the famous superstar television at Disney's Hollywood studio where you would
get to be part of the TV show.
I think that it's fun.
That's fun to see your mom up there and she's doing fun stuff.
So I think you take maybe some talk shows that Fox owns and you put those up.
I'm talking Magic Hour.
I'm talking the Chevy Chase talk show.
I'm talking we get actually Magic Johnson and Chevy Chase to do shifts in the park,
interviewing your mom or your dad about what's going on.
How are the kids behaving?
How hot is it out here?
Although Culver City, it's actually not that hot because it's kind of close to the ocean.
So maybe the answer will be it's fine.
The temperature is fine.
Both of them basketball involved in both of those shows.
They could probably use the same set, Magic Johnson, an actual basketball player, whereas
Chevy Chase would come out and do a take a shot at the beginning of every episode so
they could just leave that up for either of them.
Chevy missed very often.
Also, we also just like the I want to see the full recreation of that set with the fish
tank behind him.
Keep that basketball away from that fish tank.
That's a potential spillage.
How's the vacation going, Grandpa?
Like Chevy would say.
Then yeah, I think this would be great.
I think you could sell a VHS copy of the appearance after for everyone if they wanted it.
Not even DVD.
Nope.
VHS.
Me and Chevy.
I mean, I'll run through my other ideas here real quick.
I think that they have guides at Disneyland.
If you're rich, you'll have a guide.
I think that all the guides should be dressed like Mr. Belvedere.
I think they should be helping you and finding things you want.
I think that's a good idea.
I think that, let's see, here we go.
Okay, this is actually my favorite idea is a whole, let me backtrack.
Fox owns MTM Enterprises, which is Mary Tyler Moore's production company.
So when Disney buys this, I'm assuming they now own all of these shows.
And there's a lot of shows here.
And I have some ideas for them like, for instance, New Heart.
New Heart was a show by starring Bob Newhart where he owned a bed and breakfast and there
was a whole host of weird characters.
That's the hotel.
Oh, wow.
New Heart is the hotel you stay at and then there's the people, the famous wacky characters
that come in.
I think that you can, when you go into this Mary Tyler Moore land, which I'm going to
call it, you're greeted by the cartoon cat Mimsy, which is the famous title card for
MTM.
I'm alienating anyone who's under 50 right now.
Instead of it's not a lion in the logo, it's a cat.
Actually in fact, here's my pitch for this area, Disney MTM Studios.
I think that's great.
Sue Ann from Mary Tyler Moore, you'll eat at her restaurant.
You'll learn newspaper making from Lou Grant.
And there'll be a Mary Tyler Moore e-ticket where it's like an omnimover ride where you
go through the streets of Minneapolis, aboard a news van trying to break stories.
You could do a parachute ride that shoots you up real fast where you're on a giant Mary
Tyler Moore hat.
She's throwing you up in the air.
That's great.
That's all ages.
This omnimover one, you have to be like 14 to ride.
Okay.
So there is now.
I've got a bit of a saucy one that we might have to put an age gap on or an age limit
on.
Oh, go ahead.
We all know Mike and Dave from Mike and Dave Need Wedding Dates.
Yes, of course.
Right?
Yeah.
Well now Mike and Dave need your help.
That's right.
You are the wedding date in this new 4D gross out simulator adventure.
That's good.
I like that.
You got a ride component.
You're jumping on mopeds with those goops.
Oh man, you kidding me?
Yeah.
You know, you could maybe do an entire sectioned off area that is 18 and up, which is where
Deadpool can live, but more importantly.
Deadpool is everywhere.
There's walk around Deadpool's everywhere in my mind.
Well he can be like he's, there's him in a space suit and him as a cowboy.
Oh perfect.
There's just multiple, you know Deadpool will be in every land.
You just don't know where.
He can be in Mouse Ears over in regular Disneyland.
But I think you take the, maybe you call this area Fox XXX with all three X's.
Oh yeah.
This is the 18 and over area and this could be the home of an area that I want to see
which is Silk Stocking Square.
The famous Crime Time and Prime Time started on CBS and moved over to USA.
You know, a 90's crime show is very sultry and very sexy.
Fox I'm unclear on it.
It looks like they only produced the season six through eight.
So you would have to pick up just the characters from season six.
So late period.
Yeah, yeah.
Towards the end.
We're talking like 96 to 99.
So you would have to center on detectives Tom Ryan and Cassandra St. John.
But that gives you a lot of great plots to work with and I think maybe you could do kind
of a live show, there was a Dick Tracy show in the 90's at Disneyland.
You could do a thing like that.
Maybe not quite a stunt show because I don't know that USA could afford a lot of stunts
by that point in the run of Silk Stockings.
You could watch Tom and Cassie solve mysteries live on stage and you could slide out different
formative episodes of Silk Stockings.
I'd love to see a live experience based on their episode where somebody is committing
murders based on who he meets in a chat room.
That episode of course called Call Me at Murder.com.
So let's see the stunt show off of that.
Also another one called Do You Believe in Magic where Tom and Cassie's only clue in
a murder case is a ventriloquist dummy.
So that lends itself pretty perfectly to a theme park environment.
So yeah, a lot of sexy fun waiting in Silk Stockings Square.
Hey and buy your gal some lingerie and some garters while you're over there.
Some steamy 90's goods.
Sure.
Vox has always been very salacious.
But I think we shouldn't forget the company's rich history.
I mean they have been releasing movies since the 30's.
And so I know I said we could bring something back earlier but I think this is just too
perfect.
And we were talking about stuff going away and coming back too quickly.
I think you've got to bring back the great movie ride just exploring the history of Fox
all the way from early classics like Red Heads on Parade and Steamboat Round the Bend to
Oscar nominated Golden Age films like Heaven Can Wait and the Oxbow Incident.
All the way to your favorite movies of today like Why Him and the Murder on the Orient
Express.
And let's not forget all your favorite Fox produced TV shows like Ally McBeal and Judging
Amy and the current hit Sleepy Hollow.
They're on the movie ride?
They're all on the movie ride too.
This is a good catch all to fit them all on.
I agree.
And the ride culminates in an incredible climax featuring a very accurate and very graphic
rendition of the crucifixion from the Passion of the Cross.
Is that them?
Is that Fox?
They get Christ.
Fox has Christ.
And the whole ride is hosted by your good friend Deadpool.
He's not letting anybody get out of there scuffery.
The only thing I would say I have one improvement is if you could put a show scene on there
from the hit Fox show Drexel's class starring Dabney Coleman.
I mean we might have to dial back the perfect.
Wait was it Boston Comet?
I forget.
Oh yeah.
There's still a 90s thing.
But you know we were sort of roughing out an idea yesterday that I think could fit within
this.
Oh yeah.
Which is that with these purchases we now have between Disney and Fox a myriad of Samuel
L. Jackson characters and films.
So I think that this iteration of the great movie ride should have the hall of SLJ.
You can pass through the hall of SLJ where you can meet I mean remind me of Nick Fury
and Frozone from the Incredibles.
He's Mace Windu which Lucasfilm's owned by Disney so you can get Mason there.
Put out by Fox and now totally owned by.
You have his character from Die Hard 3 whose name is available on Wikipedia for you to
look up at home.
Oh Zeus Carver.
Oh yeah.
Of course.
And imagine passing by every within the company's ownership Samuel L. Jackson character.
Yeah I mean that's great.
I think all of them badger you as you.
I'll tell you those are the only guys who are going to be able to put Deadpool in his
place.
Yeah Deadpool is like oh I'm cutting out of this part of the ride.
I'll see you guys at the end.
But you know this might get a little heavy the history of an esteemed movie studio and
that's why I think next to it should be something a little lighter a little area called parody
land because Fox put out both Meet the Sparks and Vampires Suck.
Oh no.
You can see some of the hilarious skewerings of the pop culture of what was that the mid
2000s early 2000s.
The Seltzer the Seltzer Friedberg franchise of quickly pumped out parody films.
Yes that one.
Great.
Are you watching the movies.
We're live.
Oh there's a land.
You're maybe they could be it could be a land that is parodying existing Disney.
That's good.
Oh yeah.
Uh huh.
Meet the land meet the theme park land.
It's like here's the actually how about a great movie ride that's like the highlights
of all of the Disney the main Disney attractions.
But you know you say you're going through the room the room with Madame Leota and the
crystal ball in the haunted mansion but inside is Snooki.
Oh boy.
That wouldn't be the first Snooki reference in a theme park.
Snooki famously appeared in the Disney California Adventure Aladdin show.
I mean the.
Oh right.
Yeah now we're getting back to that.
So yeah that's not our way to get topical reference.
That's not without.
Yeah without precedent.
Back in the same park.
You know you're there's sort of a Star Tours kind of section but your pilot is Borat.
Oh yeah they do own Borat.
And you know but but the parody films also that's that's the fun of those movies.
It'll just cut to Borat not even a parody of it.
Just here's Austin Powers.
Here's Borat.
So I think that's all fair game now within Paris.
So really in parody land.
Yeah you can have every character ever because you can hear whatever you want outside apparently
land while you could get your pictures with the monument men and then inside parody land
the monuments men Jason.
Oh excuse me the monuments multiple monuments there's a there's a sharp sharp witted takedown
of the monuments men in parody land.
Wow yeah both.
So you can yeah real Borat and then fake fake just off enough different mustache widths
so that they get sued.
Borat.
Wow.
I love it.
That's great.
I mean the only the only last thing I have is that I want there to be a live show based
on Kelsey Grammer presents the sketch show from seven or eight years ago with with local
improvisers headed by one Jason Sheridan.
Oh boy.
Oh really.
Yeah.
Oh wow.
I mean the show he was not on the show.
I wasn't on the show.
He's in the theme park version of the show.
Oh I see.
Oh OK.
I thought we had wait that show was a while back.
It would be funny if you didn't know Jason was the star of Kelsey Grammer presents.
Oh Kelsey Grammer was the sketch show when I was like 20.
And as far as I know as far as the world knows about Kelsey Grammer's the sketch show.
Yeah you know I'll put in one more which is a you know a more hallowed Fox television
franchise.
There's going to be an area called Mash Mountain and it's kind of a kind of a camp Snoopy.
It's actually I think it's with all of the vehicles famously used in Mash you can have
it's you can have a lot of fun little little kids rides but the kids can also learn about
the horrors of the Korean War.
Hawkeye's helicopters radars racers Trapper John's tanks maybe a merry go round.
It's all scalpels and different surgical instruments and you can form your own conclusion about
whether that's a war we should have been in or not.
I think that's to use another reference to our old show much like your Christmas pitch
for the submarine ride where Santa's the North Pole's been destroyed as a way to teach children
about global warming.
I think this is great.
I think kids are going to learn a lot from it.
I want more lessons and I think that the property the IP mash really lends itself to that.
This is yeah I think this more adults issue oriented park is the is the way of the future.
Kids will learn about parody and skewering at an earlier age and and about about war
and there's there's there's a lot of possibilities here.
So come to Fox land which is right off Avenue of the Stars which is the street in call and
it's in an incredibly inconvenient location.
It is and if you've ever been there they try to make you park at a parking garage.
It's 25 minutes.
That's a little inside baseball but I've had to walk literally a half hour from a parking
garage to get to the lot.
It's insane.
But so they're all ready.
It sounds like Disneyland already.
That's a good point.
It's really just add a tram or a gondola and then we're good.
Yeah Foxland's right.
I think we just I think we gave them enough information to get started on it now and I'm
going to leave here and immediately make some calls and get the Simpsons Meet Family Guy
series going.
So we're willing to invest.
I'll toss in a little toss in like a billion or so to start it off of my personal funds
and then I think we'll have Foxland up and running in no time.
I think we're all getting on the phone with our teams after this right.
Yeah.
The ball moves started start triangulating.
It's it's it's time.
We're and then and of course because we thought of it there will be statues of the three of
us in front of the Fox logo like Walden Mickey the statue in Disneyland but it's all three
of us holding hands.
Yeah and microphones and also trying to find the person in the middle is getting the most
screwed because he's got a because yeah well he has a cordless headset mic on.
Oh great.
Perfect.
So we can solve problems so quickly in no time.
So hey we'll see you in Foxland.
You survived podcast the ride.
Hey so now so now what happens.
Follow us on it's all the same.
Hey I heard nothing.
Nothing really.
Follow us on Twitter.
You will notice no different.
We're trying to do a little more on Instagram post videos of weird stuff that we're talking
about.
We're trying to do this on iTunes but only say nice things and say give us five stars.
We don't want any like criticism at all.
Don't you very sensitive.
We call our little review zone Avenue of the five stars.
No no threes no threes.
Cast the ride at Gmail dot com.
We've gotten some really nice emails.
We have to talk about those in a future date.
Yeah.
Future episode ideas throw away.
I think we are.
Thanks.
Anybody on Twitter said let's talk about Stitch's great escape.
I think that one's probably coming up soon.
Yeah.
And happy happy 2018.
If you have any complaints about anything from this episode now we're kind of doing it on
our own.
Let us know.
You're our boss.
So shoot us an email.
Hey this is great.
This is fun.
Yeah.
And thank you all so much for listening as we roll into this new year.
We it means a lot.
We appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
Buckaroos.
And we'll see you next time.
Bye.