Warning, the following podcast is about extra-terrorrestrial alien encounter.
The scariest ride Disney ever built.
Be on the lookout for Tim Curry, Kathy Najimy, Ray J, and Cato Kaelin.
And keep your ears peeled for multiple hair-raising mentions of the beloved character Spinlock.
Seize the future on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast where three men reminisce about what
good little boys they were.
My name is Michael Carlson, I'm joined as always with Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
I'm really fumbling, this is the third time I've done the intro.
And Scott Gardner.
And hi.
You powered through it, you got there, and now we're off and running.
Today we're going to talk about Alien Encounter, which has a subtitle of extra-terrorrestrial,
is that right Jason?
That's right.
It's a super, in all caps, estrile alien encounter, but also it's one of those, there's like a
slash in it, like the universe of energy, where, because since 2003 it has been Stitch's
great escape.
Although maybe not for much longer.
People wrote us on Twitter and encouraged this as a topic because we thought it might
be closing, but Disney says it's maybe not closing.
Disney says it's coming back, yeah.
Was it 2003 or 2004?
2004, I guess the 2003 to 2004 was the changeover period.
Oh, okay.
So they did all of the alterations on the ride.
They put a beard on the one robot that they couldn't otherwise replace.
We'll get to all that.
Yeah, we'll get to all that.
But Scott, you had some stuff before, right?
Oh yeah, well I wanted to take a little of your time to talk about a local Los Angeles
attraction.
It's not in a theme park, but it's accessible to anyone who's strolling Hollywood Boulevard,
and it's a place called Hologram USA.
Now this is a place, shout out to Jason Walliner who turned me on to this place.
You gentlemen have not been here, but have I told you anything about it?
No, I don't know anything about it.
From scratch, Hologram USA.
I think the actual, like extraterrestrial, it's got a more specific title.
If you look at the marquee on Hollywood Boulevard, it says FilmOn.tv Hologram USA Theater.
Oh boy.
And it's been really big under that Billie Holiday Hologram show.
This used to be, I think, like a laser show theater?
Is that right?
Or a laserium kind of thing?
Oh, it could be the laserium.
I'm not sure.
And maybe a porno theater before that.
I was looking up the site, and I think there's a few weird little seedy theaters on Hollywood
Boulevard.
This particular one I think may have been a church right before its conversion into
a hologram, into the Church of Holograms, the Holy Temple of Holograms.
Was it a porno theater before it was a church?
I think it did some time as a porno.
If you're on Hollywood Boulevard, anything new.
You were a porno theater at a certain point.
You were a porno theater, and before that, a newsreel theater that very quickly slid
into pornos at a certain point.
And before that, a place where Charlie Chaplin used to live.
This is an observation.
Yeah.
I'll credit our friend Ryan Perez for this, that we were at some bar where he's like,
they told us Charlie Chaplin used to live here.
And he's like, if I go to one more goddamn place where Charlie Chaplin once lived, I
think everywhere in Hollywood.
I've been to a house that claimed that Charlie Chaplin lived there, yeah.
Worson Wells.
Worson Wells, I feel like also had a similar thing, because Worson Wells was crashing a
lot later in life.
And I feel like, oh, Worson Wells lived here.
I feel like I've also heard multiple houses of like, Worson Wells died here.
And it's like, this is the third one I've heard about that he died in.
They were, they all moved around a lot.
Charlie Chaplin and Worson Wells, the original Pete Holmes.
It did a lot of crashing.
Yeah, it's so weird.
Is it that these people, is it a lie to get people into your place and give it prestige?
Or is it a, is it just people who heard of urban legend?
I think it's a, yeah, it's a game of telephone.
Maybe.
Well, not telephone, I guess, because the names change.
It doesn't change.
So I've heard, I've heard Liz Taylor.
Whispers down the lane, whispers down the line, whatever you call it.
Right.
My friend lives in Liz Taylor's old house.
He lives in the attic.
And it's just a, it's a, the whole house is just a big dump where a bunch of dudes live.
Although I think they recently moved.
That's a whole nother podcast, but yeah, there's a giant house where like seven people live
in, but it used to at one point be the wonderful Liz Taylor house.
Just her, not her and seven other actresses.
She didn't live with seven other dudes.
Seven other dudes, dirty dudes.
No, it was just seven frat guys.
Lived with Liz Taylor.
She married all of them at once.
Her seventh husband was seven guys.
Yeah.
Okay, so anyway, whatever this once was today is the thriving film on.tv hologram USA theater.
And so this has been up for like a year or so on Hollywood Boulevard.
If you've, if you live in Los Angeles, you may have passed by this marquee that says
Billy hologram, Billy hologram.
That's why she was chosen was the proximity of her name to hologram.
Billy holiday hologram show.
And if you watch the ads for it, it advertises itself as being from the makers of the Tupac
hologram.
So that adds it some, some prestige and some pedigree.
But when you go into this place, well, first of all, several things I bought an E ticket.
This is an event that you're, the, your minimum of new hologram show that you're getting is,
is, uh, is an hour of material.
That's how it's presented.
You get an hour long hologram show and that is supposed to be $30 through some trickery
and means I got to do it for free.
But the, but then you go in and they try to like, they don't have the technology to scan
your ticket correctly.
Like the E scan doesn't work, which gets you very excited for the hologram technology waiting
just behind.
Uh, another weird red flag at this place.
They have a CBD oil popcorn.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, CB.
Okay.
Uh, I don't know about this Jason lit up.
Yeah.
So CBD oil is the, uh, non psychoactive, uh, part of marijuana THC.
CBD oil, uh, uh, widely like apple cider vinegar, uh, uh, people say has a lot of positive health
benefits as an anti-inflammatory as a sleep aid, uh, unprepared statement from you.
Uh, yeah, this is, I've been reading it.
Well, I have a CBD vape and it does, it is great for sleeping.
And it, it, it actually like when my shoulder has hurt before it's like helped, helped with
that.
I have that shoulder, like, uh, that shoulder, elbow ache we all do from holding our phones
all the time.
Oh yeah.
That's just stress injury.
Well, here we get, well, we're in the Jason wheelhouse.
So, so my, so they're selling CBD pop because the other thing about CBD oil, like up into
a certain point, you could buy a pretty weak version of it at like whole foods.
Like you could buy it as like an herbal.
I went to some hipster restaurant that had CBD oil cocktails, which, uh, I gotta say,
they've cost about as much as the hologram show and did absolutely nothing to me whatsoever.
Yeah.
The other thing is like CBD oil, if you buy it, like if you have a medicinal marijuana
cart or I guess a recreational, anyone can get it now.
It is more expensive.
I don't know if it's more expensive.
Are you lobbying for the CBD industry?
I've never heard you high on CBD right now.
I'll take freebies of any listeners.
I've never heard you speak so eloquently about anything.
It's a current interest.
Oh wow.
Well, the theaters got you covered.
CBD oil popcorn, which I'm sure works and is not just a bizarre scam that this place
is pulling.
Anyway, so the, the, just to get into the meat of it, you walk in and there is a, uh,
there's just shows happening all day.
First of all, so you get an hour's worth of hologram material, but also you could just,
it's open from noon to 10 PM.
So if you were a Hollywood Boulevard homeless person and you could get together $30 or probably
just go into the lobby, talk to the two stoners behind the registers, say, look over there
and then just go and sneak into the theater the other way.
You could, you've got a place to sleep for 10 solid hours in very comfortable chairs.
Did they not make you leave after the show?
No, you could stay in the hologram theater as long as you want.
Okay.
You start at 10, you start at noon and you're in all day.
Uh, so there's just a constantly going loop of hologram attractions and also hologram
trailers, which is very exciting to see.
But the main show that you come in and watch is a Billy hologram, Billy holiday.
Keep doing that.
Billy holiday hologram show.
Uh, and you can immediately tell that this is not the same thing as the Tupac hologram.
It is not a Tupac's face melded onto a, a realistic, uh, living body.
It's you, they just got an actress to play Billy holiday and she just performs.
It's like watching a still shot of a concert filmed over black, uh, and, and just projected
life size in front of you.
It's like watching a concert video with no cuts is basically what you do.
So and she does lip sync the real Billy holiday songs, the recordings of them.
So you're watching a live concert of pre-recorded Billy holidays.
So he's not by real Billy holiday at all.
It's just some actress and also like, but sometimes there are magical elements.
Like when she'll start a song, her band will magically appear in a puff of smoke.
But there's another part where just a like modern white guy roadie comes in and gives
her a mic stand and then walks away.
And I can't tell if that was a joke of some kind or just like a way to poke through the
magic or if it was just carelessness.
Um, it's, it's one of the strangest things I've ever seen.
Uh, but I actually wasn't there for the Billy holiday hologram show.
I was there for something else called, uh, let me make sure I get the title right.
Ray J and Kato's sexy Hollywood freak show.
Oh good.
What?
It was a show co-hosted by Ray J who I believe was in the Kim Kardashian sex tape.
Uh, also on a show called for the love of Ray J and then, uh, Kato Kaelin, uh, the America's
most famous, uh, house gas eventful crashing that ever occurred.
He took the mantle from Orson Welles.
Yeah.
Um, so yeah, I don't know why these guys, we kept questioning what, where do they know
each other from?
Why are they friends?
Um, they come out and they're wearing sparkly spangled costumes.
Uh, and they do a lot of talking over each other material, the comedic crux of which
is calling each other gay.
Like Oh, more like gay J, you know, more like Gato Galen.
Do they really say gay J?
Yeah.
Wait, wait, and this is called, they call him gay J.
This is hollig filmed holograms doing.
Yeah.
It's something that is, it is life-sized, but just projected.
And by the way, just this illusion, uh, it does nothing for you.
Nobody would walk in and go, wow.
It's you're just watching.
Like the way these things work, it's an illusion called pepper's ghost, uh, where there's,
it's very simple where something's projected from down on the floor and then via angled
glass.
It looks like it's, there's kind of a ghostly effect on it.
And, and this is in a lot of Disney rides.
It's basically how they do, uh, there was a, in the rock and roller coaster or they're
using it in the, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh, the fast and furious attraction at universal has this very stiff part where a bunch of
like people, really well lit party goers all dance in one place.
You can tell they're very careful to not move from the one spot they're on.
Uh, so anyway, this is a thing that would be like a part of a separate Disney attraction.
It would just be like one thing in the line of a Disney ride, but they're masquerading
it as its own event and you're supposed to pay $30 for it.
You're supposed to pay like a third of a day at Disneyland to go watch.
And then, and then what's the thing gets going?
It's like after this, this, uh, like unlistenable clap trap between Ray J and Kato, then you're
watching, uh, then it's like, uh, it is a literal freak show where guys are banging
nails into their nose and there's like, uh, there's burlesque stuff.
There's sexy girls in forties lingerie spinning around on a, uh, like a carousel horse with
a bunch of dangly things coming down.
It's like, it's very lame Hollywood Boulevard kind of, uh, uh, yeah, like the, the freaks
and kooks and, uh, uh, like, Ooh, it's a little bit of Randy.
Um, but there's this stuff like, like the, the screen is split into three thirds and
like, here's a guy banging nails into his nose.
Here's a guy, here's a sword swallower and here's a sexy lady just dancing around and
those things don't, uh, interact with each other whatsoever.
There's just like three unrelated freak shows all going at the same time.
Um, it's, it's, it's one of the, one of the odd, Oh, on the website, they describe it
as having featuring many of Los Angeles is best alternative performers.
They miss, but they drop a lot of letters from all.
Um, and, and then it's just, and then it's, uh, it's over in 17 minutes after you've paid
$30 for 17 minutes of content and then it loops.
Uh, yeah.
And then you see the sleaze again.
Yeah.
If you stayed in there, you would get to watch it at least 10 times in a row.
Wow.
Watched it all day.
The big story with this thing is that it was, it's concocted by a Greek billionaire named
Alki David and, uh, Alki seems to be a very litigious man.
So I don't want, I want to be careful with what I say about him.
I want to really, really carefully say that, uh, he is very hot and cool and, uh, very
cut.
He clearly works out a lot and I think he's in, he runs a perfectly legitimate business.
Uh, that being said, uh, other people do not feel this way.
He's been sued many times.
He's currently, he basically like bought the, he did not do the Tupac hologram.
He bought the technology after the fact so that now he can claim he's the owner of the
Tupac hologram.
No, he had nothing to do with it, but he's gone out of his way.
He's sued people who try to do holograms.
He sued Fox after Matt Groening appeared with a hologram Homer at Comic-Con.
Wow.
He had something.
Uh, meanwhile he's getting sued by other people.
He was sued by a company called Roy's boys, which is literally the sons of Roy Orbison
who asked him to come up with a hologram of Roy Orbison.
And from the sounds of the synopsis of the lawsuit, he just didn't do it.
They would call and just like, uh, hang on, give me six months.
They check in again.
This is like the dark side of fame right here.
Like this is, this is something else.
The dark side is screwing over Roy's boys.
I mean, this is like, uh, Scott.
Buying the, buying the rights to the ghosts of dead celebrities.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
And either do it poorly or not at all.
Uh, Scott, I don't think I told, when you said you want to talk about this, uh, I decided
to say this for the podcast.
Uh, my experience recently with hologram USA almost simultaneously as you were, you posted
like some pictures or some video clips from there, uh, uh, you know, over the holidays.
And I was back visiting family in Pennsylvania and New Jersey.
And uh, there was a night, I don't know if it was the same night, but it was around the
time you had gone to this.
Uh, I was watching, I think it was like one of those affiliates that's different in every
city, like my network TV.
So it's like my Cincinnati, my Philadelphia, my Los Angeles.
Oh, sure.
Sure.
Uh, uh, I think they were playing like two of the Daniel Craig Bond movies back to back
every commercial break I saw there was a commercial for a hologram USA on Hollywood Boulevard.
No kidding.
I went back at home back in Jersey and I don't see, I have cable in LA.
I don't see commercials for it and I live a mile and a half, two miles from it.
But I saw a commercial every commercial break and I remember the puff of smoke guy.
The big band appear behind the big band appear.
The best was when they did a time lapse of them building a stage for the hologram, but
because there is nothing on stage, it looks like they just time lapse the construction
of an empty state.
They took, they took black and made it more black.
They put 10 layers of black paint, but they, they showed it so many times.
Oh, I'm glad you, between clips of quantum in between quantum of solids segments.
Weird.
Uh, if you Google Alki David harass, there are many pages of results right away.
Oh boy.
It's a good sign.
Again, allegedly I'm not saying anything.
I'm just talking about your brother.
We love he's also an actor.
Oh yes.
I'm looking it up on a Wikipedia.
He's directed a bunch of films and he's in all of the films as well.
And he'll be next to a more famous actor and they will present him right after as if you
know him.
So in the trailer it's like Judd Nelson, Alki David, they very confidently say, you know
Alki, you all know that.
The last thing he was in was Bob Thunder internet assassin and he played Mr. Network.
Scott is Dr. Modem is this a fever dream you had that you create?
You became a Tulpa.
It became an idea that became real.
It became like a person.
I'm starting to wonder that.
Yeah.
It had a very, uh, it also like it's, it smelled weird in the place.
Like paint was recently put in.
So maybe there was a, maybe there's a paint huffing aspect to this.
Maybe I just, was it the popcorn?
I think I took that CBD oil popcorn, watered into somewhere else.
Did they also have regular popcorn?
Was that an option?
No, just yeah.
Okay, just CBD oil.
So if you took a kid in there and you were paying attention.
You're gonna have to get real mellow.
You should not take a kid on Hollywood Boulevard.
Well, you shouldn't take a kid.
Yeah, not at all.
I don't think you should take a kid anywhere near anything Alki David is doing.
I think he could be a good guest though on the show.
I think maybe we should try.
Yeah.
Alki, if you're listening, please.
If you're listening to the definitely not a special cut of the episode that we sent
you that deleted a lot of materials.
Yeah, yeah.
If you're listening to the regular audio that we have sent you, please come on.
Hook us up.
Hook Jason up with some CBD oil popcorn.
Oh boy.
Oh yeah.
Let's have a real chill conversation about your armada of holograms and your upcoming
hologram shows, including soul legend, Jackie Wilson also played by some actor you've never
heard of and the real not say not a deceased person, not CGI and not an actor.
The real John Lovitz will soon be doing the first ever hologram comedy show.
Hologram comedy show.
He's taking a break from his residency.
He currently has a two man residency in Vegas with Dana Carvey.
And he's under lifetime contract at the laugh factory on sunset.
So he's gotten himself in a lot of messes and another one now is the hologram show.
Maybe the hologram is a way to ensure that he can perhaps fake his own death, but not
have to get sued by the laugh factory.
I think he's probably just trying to get back to to try it.
It's tie it back into our normal subject matter.
He's trying to get back to the John Lovitz comedy club, the former city walk.
Yeah.
Hollywood.
Okay.
He's just trying to get the gang back together, get the John Lovitz comedy club reopened,
at the Kevin Smith podcast lounge in there.
Was it named after Kevin Smith?
Yeah, there was the Kevin Smith.
Was the Smod Castle?
No, the Smod Castle used to be on Santa Monica Boulevard.
Right.
By where we used to do improv shows.
By where we used to do improv.
It was a black box theater where people used to do improv and take classes.
And then it became the Smod Castle.
And now it's back to being a black box theater where people do improv.
Boy, the commonality of all this, if anyone listening is not already in Hollywood and
or in Los Angeles.
We're sorry.
Come on out.
Come and say, look what you're missing.
You're missing the Smod Castle.
You're missing Hologram USA.
If you move here and don't immediately find a place to live, I'm telling you, Hologram
USA, you could probably hide in the rafters for a couple of months.
You can crash there for a while.
Yes.
You can crash at Liz Taylor's house.
Live where Elizabeth Taylor and Orson Welles and Pete Holmes all lived once.
So there you go.
Hologram USA.
Check it out.
Uh, yeah, it gets five hologram stars from me.
Scott Gartner.
Great.
That's great.
You can quote that, Alki.
All right.
We'll be right back.
Welcome back to podcast the ride.
We are now going to talk about an attraction that I have to confess I've never been on
because I was too scared.
What?
Alien encounter.
This is a revelation here.
Let me tell this quick story.
Uh, I saw, I was reading Disney adventure magazine.
We were going to Disney world.
It was a big trip.
I was very excited about it and I was reading about alien encounter and I kept talking about
it.
I kept telling my mom alien encounter is coming, but it's not going to be open when we're there
because it said, you know, opening whatever July.
I don't remember when it all right.
Uh, and I was very excited about it.
So we got down to Disney world.
We were at tomorrow land and my mom went, the ride is open.
This is crazy.
It was soft opening and my face dropped and I said, I, I, I don't want to go on it.
And I didn't.
Am I, my dad and my little sister did go on it.
I didn't, I sat outside and was just a little coward.
I was too scared to go on it.
It's a shame that I carry with me to this day and I'm revealing it on the show right
now because I am the polar opposite of this.
This is an all timer for me.
No, I know.
And I've never told, I've never, I've known you for almost 10 years now.
I've never told you that I didn't go on any of the other multiple times.
I'm ashamed of myself when I would go like this, this as a, as a kid, like when I was
like what, like 10 to 14 and we would go down like tomorrow, like that was my home base
because alien encounter, uh, the people mover and carousel of progress I could, and space
mountain, uh, before it started to beat the shit out of me.
Uh, I would just, just, I could be there just for hours, for hours.
And I would like run back there.
My family would be like, uh, we're going to go back to the hotel.
And it's like, all right, I'll be back in a few hours.
The park closing in 15 minutes, but I can knock out one more of these.
Like you're forget, Hey, I want to make sure we don't, uh, forget.
Let's give a shout out to the visionarium.
We got the timekeeper and the vision.
I love the timekeeper too.
I love the timekeeper and I was sad when that went away.
Yeah.
Like tomorrow, the redo of tomorrow land, which came 94.
Was that like tomorrow?
Land 94 and sunny eclipse.
Don't forget.
Well, sunny eclipse.
We all can agree on there was so much for anyone who doesn't know.
Yeah.
They redid tomorrow land in 1994 at Disney world and added a lot of mythology.
They made it a land that all, it all connected.
The people, right.
It was no longer called the people mover.
It was called the tomorrow land transit transit authority.
It was like the bus that took you around to the different places like the tomorrow land
convention center, which is where alien encounter takes place.
They would, they justified every, why am I, why was I excited about this?
I loved it.
I, that's right.
Into a municipality.
I, I, I got a new phone and it, for whatever reason didn't transfer over.
But my ringtone is, uh, the old man going now arriving rocket tower Plaza.
Oh, rocket tower Plaza.
That's right.
And it's just, and it's this old guy.
I forget the actor's name, but he, he was the voice of a lot of Disney rides for a while.
At some point they switched it out and it was like a young surfer dude.
And the last time I wrote it, like a few years ago, I was just so mad that they got rid of
this old man talking about all the different public transit.
Your favorite character, an old man.
I loved it.
But like alien encounter, I, it was so great.
I'm sorry.
It scared the hell out of me.
It scared.
I wish I went on it.
I wish I had the courage.
I would go on it now.
Every year I had to re-psych myself up.
But like,
Ritz, you were scared.
Oh, I was scared.
Yeah.
No, I was scared little boy, but I just like, I was a coward.
I was just a coward.
I couldn't, and no one like forced me.
My mom should have gone, go on it.
Somebody should have said something.
Yeah.
I also, I, same thing.
I haven't been on it either.
I'm not, I don't feel tormented about it.
I feel fine.
I've made peace with the, um, me being a little and scared.
Um, uh, I don't know.
I also, here's something I realized when I was looking at the timeline of the attraction.
Um, I realized that, so there was, uh, the, the, this attraction opened and it was, it
was too, too scary originally.
Yes.
Too scary.
And it closed for six months to make it a little less scary.
A little less scary.
It was still horrifying.
Yeah.
I don't think they, they undid that.
And I feel like Michael Eisner too, was like, people are like, this is too scary.
And he's like, I think we can make some minor story tweaks.
And honestly, I don't think it's scary enough.
That's always the rumor.
He wanted to punish people more, but apparently the, the version, the, the kind of testing
out version, the beta version of alien encounter was only open for six weeks.
And I realized I was there in six weeks.
So I could have been, I might've been there too.
I might've been there too.
There was, it would have been like Christmas, 1994.
No, I wasn't.
And then it officially, the grand opening was in the summer of 95.
I was there before that opening.
It was soft over for like on and off for like six months.
It seemed like it was one of those.
I think when attractions are retooled, they don't get away with it in the same way that
movies do.
When you hear that a movie is having a lot of trouble and reshoots that could indicate
that it's a big mess and it's having a lot of problems, but it can come back full force
and be better than ever.
But I feel like if a theme park attraction is trouble, it almost never gets over that.
There's like, there's just an asterisk with it, like the rocket rods, another space.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
You know, they had to work out the kink of it killing people.
Yeah.
They had to stop that, which it hasn't done that in a while, but like there's never a
line.
No one really cares about it.
Like it was just a heart.
It was a harbinger of things to come.
All kind of in sort of the same era, roughly like 90s, early 2000s.
Yeah.
A lot of like Disney's attempts at scare attractions and thrill attractions have had a lot of trouble
in the recent past.
I mean, I think this is easily the scariest, like big budget, like big two Disney and Universal
theme park ride that they ever made.
And for me, like I really don't like to be scared that much, but this was like the exception
because like, did you guys watch a ride through of it?
Yeah, but you can't YouTube ride through.
Yeah.
Shout out once again to Martin's vids who has a pretty good recreation of, you know,
has the source audio and has like a recreation of the pre-show and the ride itself.
It's a dark, not only is it scary, it's like very cynical.
Like it's a very dark ride.
There's a lot of dark jokes.
Tim Curry is like a very mean robot, a very mean animatronic who like tortures a very
cute animatronic, Skippy.
Like I can't stress enough, this watching the ride through of this is similar to me of like
watching classic Simpsons episodes where it's like, I may not remember it like every joke
in it, but it's just like, I am remember it, remember a lot of it like in my bones, like
subconsciously.
Wow.
And like this is your favorite ride of this ride.
It's probably my favorite ride.
This in the, the adventurers club, like this of like built into the DNA of my personal
interests.
And you're sitting here with two wieners who wouldn't ride it.
Should we leave you?
Do you want to just, we'll just go outside for a while.
Don't take the dog for a walk.
I was pretty busy leading up to this recording and it's probably for the best because I feel
like I would have gotten obsessed reading about this.
You would have been our first four hours, like going through a real emotional journey.
You would have bullied the two of us when we were little.
Probably would have.
Cause another thing I liked about the ride was Stan.
Well, for one thing it emptied in into a gift shop.
I believe it's still there.
The merchant of Venus, uh, which in the day used to sell alien encounter merch, which
was all, I also was very into like, I have a lot of the merch.
I thought it was a very cool design.
What merch do you just with the logo or was there like a plush?
Uh, Oh, I have, uh, still in the box action figures, uh, one in, in, and the packaging
is the tube is the teleportation.
And so one is the monster.
And then the other is a set of Skippy sir, the robot, and then fried Skippy.
Uh, and I had no idea these existed.
I would, I would like these actually, though I would have to, if I had them and displayed
them in my home, I'd have to like write out a note that said, uh, this is from an attraction
that was too scary for me to ever ever.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm not a true fan of this.
The sign out front, uh, uh, the sign out front with the alien that says alien encounter and
like sort of a weird, I don't know, metal thing, uh, which is also next to the sign
that says excess tech, which is the fictional company in it.
I have both like lapel pins of the alien encounter logo.
I have a t-shirt of the excess tech logo that Mike and I, like we ordered up and Scott too.
Uh, uh, Disney puts out these throwback shirts every now and then.
And we, they're called, they're, they're a line of shirts called yester years.
Yeah.
And sometimes we'll pull our orders.
So we save money on the ship.
Uh, sometimes it's like I to get one free.
And so we split the costs and, uh, uh, yeah.
And I, as soon as this line came out, we're like, oh, that, that Disney shopping village
one looks cool.
I'm like, order me the excess tech one now.
Uh, uh, a real chairman clench.
Uh, yeah, it was a real, we should maybe back up.
I was going to say the basics of the, because like, my wife didn't know.
I mean, I'm going to need to lay down.
Let's yeah.
Jason's overheating between the marijuana oil and the popcorn and alien encounter.
Jason may have 108 temperature right now and we may have to rush them to the hospital because
there's steam venting from his ears.
So the, so the, yeah, the origin of this ride is that they were trying to do an alien ride,
the movie alien or aliens.
Uh, they were going to do something like that.
Michael Eisen wanted to do like a scarier ride.
You were going to Disneyland originally, right?
And it was, yeah, it was going to be a Disneyland as well.
Yes.
From alien and the company behind it, like Waylon, you Tony from the movies, the company
behind it was going to be the fake company getting you into this ride.
Okay.
Gotcha.
And then do we know, do we know what the plot would have been?
Like you're, you're in the, you're in the ship.
So it's like, it is the plot of the movie.
Like the alien gets loose in the shit.
Testing something and a xenomorph gets in or something like that.
And then that everyone's, uh, uh, the policy used to be that Disney rides had to be based
on P P G or G movies.
Uh, now the pirates of the Caribbean movies are PG 13, uh, uh, you know, movies.
So that's, that's an exception.
They shattered it a little, uh, they did use the rights for alien to put into the great
movie ride.
Yes.
That sequence.
But, but it was, I think the subject of a lot of, uh, infighting within the Imagineering
organization.
By the way, this whole thing, uh, apparently started because, uh, Michael Eisner, when
he took over the Walt Disney company, he took his son, Breck, uh, on the, uh, for a tour
of Disneyland and he came out of it going like, it's lame.
There's nothing cool here.
There's no right here.
So he wanted to do a ride that would impress his son.
So he, and he was, I think, uh, no way.
No, Michael Eisner was parent that before.
So he, uh, uh, nevermind.
Uh, I thought maybe he had previous relationship with the aliens franchise, but he just wanted
to bring that property into the, yeah.
Uh, a lot of just a side note about Breck, uh, Michael Eisner's son.
I do believe that like Breck has a lot to do with decisions Michael made overall.
So like, if you like the approval of splash mountain and stuff, I think Breck has a lot
to do with that.
So we can thank Breck for some of the best attractions for going, dad, I want this ride.
This is a cool ride dad.
So like, I think, uh, kudos to Breck is what I'm saying.
Star tour splash mountain, a lot of more thrilling stuff.
Some of those early nineties, uh, late eighties rides.
He came up with the Indiana Jones Mara language.
She did like the, uh, did diagrams explaining how the rocket rods would work.
Uh, centrifuges, his, let's get Breck guys there on the show too.
In addition, did he become a director?
Is he a director?
That's a good question.
I have no idea.
I feel like there's a director Eisner, but I will have to look at that.
We'll look that up later.
Anyway, sure.
That being said, the three star review we do mostly do research.
Yeah.
I'm planning on doing a lot of Breck guys and your material.
I'll have it next time.
I'll never get over it.
Can he really review us and be like, they didn't know anything about Breck Eisner.
He probably, if he re-reviews this, he'll probably say I was attacked personally by
the podcast.
Well, we're, we're also treading the line too with this ride because there is a lot
of speculation online of like, you know, there was some imagineers that, uh, you know, really
want it to, um, you know, they just stuck with it because after the alien idea was scrapped,
like people kept pursuing, like we should do something with this alien idea, even if
it's not that movie.
And then they brought in George Lucas to like, you know, consult on or give them advice of
how to do this.
Um, but who, according to the Jim Hill synopsis of events, he kind of checked out once he
was given a producer credit, he was not terribly involved.
Uh, he was not a prequels level of involved in the creation of alien.
Right.
And if you, if you are not in the entertainment industry, you know, sometimes the title of
consultant or producer, that can mean like people are very hands on and are very responsible
for stuff where it can mean they would pop by for an hour a couple of times and, uh,
collect money.
Yeah.
And then collect, uh, a year's worth of middle-class, uh, uh, income, an average middle-class income
for a couple, a couple hours.
Grab more money than you make in a year to send a couple emails.
That's Hollywood baby.
So, so yeah.
So when that stuff kind of all fell by the wayside, the imagineers then had to make their
own like mythos with their own characters.
So they created all these different things.
They created this fake company that would be the basis for the ride, which is called
excess tech.
Is that?
Yeah.
It's like XS and there's a lot of jokes of like, if something, something is only worth
doing with two excess.
So like this is with XS, it shouldn't be done.
And this is like a Halliburton type company that has like, it's dangerous.
Like they're really trying to give you the jokes, but they're trying to be like, this
is corporate overreach.
This is corporate, uh, corporation is the bad guy gone mad.
Yeah.
Like Jen and Jurassic park where like you're trying to make a comment on human beings,
uh,
But within a theme park, corporations within Disney land and universal studios.
They're odd.
Uh, uh, yeah.
So, and so the basic premise of it is that this company excess tech is giving a demonstration
in the tomorrow land, interplanetary convention center,
Convention center, public transit systems.
I loved all this stuff.
Yes.
Of our night land 94.
I think the aesthetic too, that sort of like future that never happened aesthetic, like
every time I've been down there the last few years, I'm like, as long as the lights are
on, as long as the, like the purple and green neon and stuff, it's like, this still looks
pretty good.
Like I think it still looks good because it's, they leaned into like, yeah, this future never
happened.
So I did tomorrow land in Disney, in Disney world in 1994 and in Disney land in 1998.
And I think most people would agree the 94 Disney world was much more successful.
Oh, for sure.
Uh, then the 98 tomorrow land tomorrow.
And I really kind of looks like she's Disneyland nerds.
Tomorrow land is sad and you w I walked by it on Saturday with my girlfriend and I just,
I went, I made that noise because there's just things I looked at this tomorrow where
tomorrow the, uh, the people mover would load in and it's empty and it's not moving.
And it's just sad.
It's very sad to see our tomorrow land right now.
And it won't be fixed for many years is also the problem.
There's so many, it's what makes me, uh, it's why I don't like some of these things like
Pixar peer, because why are we doing that when we could be improving picks our tomorrow
land, which tomorrow land in the, uh, as yeah, your, your love of Disney world tomorrow land
probably equal to my love of Disneyland tomorrow land growing up.
It was where all the best attract, it's where it's, it's star tours.
It's kept in EO still a lot of great attractions.
Yeah.
It's crazy how rough that land looks with like how many e-tickets and d-tickets are like
concentrated.
Yeah, I know.
Just like overloaded with so many strollers.
It's just, it's a lot of scrolling with like the strollers reproduce when they like strollers
get together with other strollers and breed and make new strollers while they're sitting
there.
So they've recreated like a smaller scale version of tomorrow land 94 out here.
Like again, I think it would still look good as it stands.
Like what was going to happen was a massive plan called tomorrow land 20, 55, uh, which
would have seen alien encounter reproduced in Anaheim as well as, uh, there was going
to be a flying saucer in the carousel of progress, like a new flying saucers, which was an original
opening day.
It was Plekdu's fantastic intergalactic review.
What I mean, I don't know a lot about, but I love that title.
I would have loved to have seen the, they, if you go to Disneyland today, it is for a
long time now, it's been the star Wars launch Bay, which is where you go meet Chewbacca
and there's some fun little things in there, but it's like massive real estate in tomorrow
land that you could do a pretty major show in.
And there has not been a, like a, a reasonable, uh, you know, well done attraction since America
Singh's closed.
Yeah, I don't think there's been a circle vision thing in there.
I think they were talking about putting the timekeeper in there.
There were, I think they were talking about putting the timekeepers somewhere out here
too.
The alien encounter was supposed to go where the pizza port is right now.
Oh my God.
So the pizza port, which is regularly everyone's, our past guest, uh, Mike Mitchell loves pizza
port.
Um, but he's the only person I've ever heard say that a pizza port, I think is like everyone's
least favorite restaurant.
It's a cafeteria now that he's not here.
Yeah.
That us, we're not afraid of bully Mike Mitchell, uh, had given us a blowback on pizza port.
No, it's like, uh, yeah, I think the graphic design in there is miserable.
It smells like a cafeteria.
It smells like a Chuck E cheese.
Yeah.
It's very Chuck E cheese.
Yes.
Uh, but yet without robots, the thing that was the salvation of all, all they have to
do is plug Sony eclipse in there and we go, well, it smells like a Chuck E cheese and
it's the graphic design is terrible, but there's a fucking robot playing piano and alien robot
singer.
And we'd all be like, well, it's pretty good.
Yeah.
And then they do have a salad.
I like there.
Okay.
I was, I get a decent, they can get a decent salad there.
If you scrub back on the podcast, like about a minute or two, I'm about to say they have
a decent salad.
I swear.
So go back and listen.
I'm about and then someone talks and I go, well, why do I have to fucking talk about
a salad?
I think you're making this up.
I think you're front and no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just going to go back and listen to this.
I am trying to kiss up to Jason, but that is a thought.
I had my friend is scared of alien encounter and he doesn't even know about that cool salad.
I don't even podcast canceled.
And the thing that happened with tomorrow.
Land 2055 is that.
Uh, fuckin' uh, Disney, Disney, Paris was such a financial, uh, fuck up for a while.
I hate to, I hate to get off the top cause we keep getting off topic here, but that
happens all the time and that drives me nuts because there's certain things like
when Shanghai Disney was being built and it was going over budget then all of a
sudden there was garbage everywhere in Disneyland they had cut staff and like
garbage is overflowing from bathrooms and they had like yeah this is what
happens when other countries Disney parks start to go to shit or something
gets behind schedule is that we in Disneyland who have been supporting the
park for years we suffer because of it and it's upsetting and it's not fair but
then it swings the other way where it's like you know there hadn't been a new
attraction for a while and then you get a big new thing like Guardians of the
Galaxy and they're like two billion dollars infused into Anaheim over like
ten years yeah but that was 20 years after a new attraction and still not a
new attraction that's still a repurposed skin I don't want to put all this on just
Disney parks in other countries because that makes this a Trumpian well it's not
the other countries are dragging down our you know that's it's not the other
countries fault it is the Disney corporation that's true well the worst
they were the worst Disney parks probably are Disneyland Paris and I
haven't been to Hong Kong I could say it seems like kind of I think it's just a
smaller scale more money but I think they're they're they're sprucing it up
but also Disney's Disney World budget problems from things like the wristbands
the man yes the magic that's true too yes loan a lot of money something like
that Disney World it does some program that burns a lot of money and suddenly
we're cutting things from Star Wars land out here Disneyland which is doing great
hometown pride taking the fall for Disney World's mistakes they yes very
recently they had to cut a ride from Star Wars land there was gonna be you're
gonna like ride on the back of these beasts of burden the band there was a
bantha right a bantha yeah sure I'll assume I think it's a bantha but yeah
that because of Disney World Disney World didn't have the money to do that
so Disneyland lost it we would have had one more attraction a big cool creature
attraction that would have made it's crazy yeah yeah yeah this stuff suffer I
say what's the political version it's like it's like state funds versus
federal right oh yeah we need to like separate I agree well they've they've
recently I think separated because before there was a policy that Disney
World had control over decision-making for an or an I'm just crazy which is
crazy but I think they've stopped that now which is good I also think Disneyland
should just break off from the company and be its own thing like it should
totally be separate it should have its own budget so we can get regular new
rides and it doesn't have to be like oh well the Pirates of the Caribbean bombed
you guys aren't gonna get a new Tomorrowland until 2030 and their budget
should be 150 billion dollars a year yes that's I think it should be a public
service I think we should nationalize Disney World and Disneyland and that
just just like we should nationalize the internet as a public service and also
Amazon we're getting to the point where we're Amazon just needs to be a public
service that's true to be the path to get that to drilling in Disneyland yeah
that's a good way into the matter or no if you start going this way so I also
think I'd like to say I'm a little self-conscious I feel like this is one
of those where we're just like talking about our nerd issues yeah we definitely
are so apologies but look that's we've yeah apologize in episode one this was
gonna happen we're just we're gonna get all we're talking about our stuff you
know hey this one's one for us but people have told us they enjoy the
sincerity and I'm gonna tell you I mean there's very I I there's very few things
I'm this sincere about like alien account yeah I mean it's just yeah from
the pre-show through the ride I just love it take us through it explain the
the the attraction to us but I think the bells are the very fundamental basics of
it it's like a it ends up being a theater show in the same place where there
used to be an attraction called mission to Mars and before that flight to the
moon rocket to the moon yeah I think mission tomorrow well what what was there
when Disney World opened I think they did it was mission to Mars yeah a little
while and it was a but it was a circular theater with a bunch of seats that were
all surrounding a porthole where you could watch a rocket take off and you
could and you would land on on the moon or Mars depending on which iteration it
was so they took this same circular theater setting and they put a big tube
in the middle and created this experience where an alien teleports into
yeah into the theater and then using a technology that that they were very keen
on at the time binaural audio which is like very sophisticated sort of a lot
going on left to right speakers that combined with you know with like water
and and I guess I don't know the harnesses the harnesses that you're
strapped into would like push down on you as if the the alien was walking
across your shoulders as if it was walking through the aisle it was very it
was cool it was cool and people would scream every time also if you weren't
sitting up straight if you were slouching when those harnesses came down
it would really push down on you like it could be a tight fit I saw a complaint
about the new iteration about stitches great escape but which uses the same
harnesses but there was a Yelp review where somebody said if you were a mother
reaching out for your child you would not be able to reach them another reason
if I could for mommy why am I going on this ride I think it's pretty easy to
grab someone's hand but if you wanted to put your hand across maybe not uh-huh
and it's not a good place to make out you know it's not a good push your arm
around somebody strapped in you were strapped in strapping also if you start
to freak out you're fucked I'm sure there was an emergency release but they
I would have freaked out you and I Mike you and I could have both been in
institutions for most that's a good point if we have gone on this ride I'm glad
we didn't probably a good thing this ride takes place in total darkness I
told one of the first episodes I told the story of going on this really shitty
UFO ride that was in the dark where I thought like we were going into space
and I almost had a meltdown so yeah this would have sent me although I was old
too what was this 95 when did this open yeah 95 95 I was 11 that wasn't five but
this is probably one where it's okay to be scared because uh adults were scared
too yeah adults were scared too this so many of the jokes in this ride are about
how the employees of this fictional company these aliens don't give a shit
if you die like there's so many of me like it's a lot of the characters are
mean like there's a lot of dark there I mean what's interesting about it and I'm
trying to think of there's an equivalent other than like in Jen for Jurassic Park
is that the bad guys are all the people that are talking to you and entrolling
like all the yeah all of the aliens and that robot are bad guys they're hurting
people right yeah except Skippy I mean yes Skippy is good he is a good alien
but he gets hurt and they ate that robot at the start hurts him and he fucked the
robot hurts him a lot like he's constantly fucking with him honestly
like as a kid I thought that was like I love the dark jokes that like the Tim
Curry animatronic where he just like just him wasn't Phil Hartman the voice
to Phil Hartman was originally a voice and he was goofier and then they're
like no that this guy's got to be a darker yeah they had to make the pre
show scarier so that you weren't thrown by how scary the actual show was so for
those six weeks and now I wish I really wish I had done it but for six weeks
there was a Phil Hartman right animatronic yeah he was a different
character named Tom 2000 later Tim Curry became sir and then Phil Hartman
would not appear in the park again until enchanted Tiki Room under new management
right in which he plays one half of the bird agent team William and Morris oh
boy that is it right we will get to Tiki Room under that's another one 45 minutes
of complaints on another one where a beloved attraction becomes something
mystifying in the 90s or 2000s many of those and we covered this already with
Ellen's energy adventure yeah there's yeah you will find this is a common
umbrella topic for these episodes the bad 90s or 2000s reboot so just to hit
the big beats of this ride so you walk into like yeah what is a fictional
space age convention center lobby and and there's a video you know explaining
the history of this excess tech company and they're demonstrating this new
technology and this is also green aliens bunch of green aliens the makeup looks
really good on these aliens and they should say this is a star studded the
film stuff looks a little cheap like the actual quality of it sort of video but
there's like name actors underneath all that makeup there sure are the first
actor you'd see it's not her voice oddly enough but the actor playing it is Tyra
Banks under makeup and she's the one explaining the history of the company
and then you see the head of the company chairman LC clench played by Jeffrey
Jones we've not been able to avoid controversial figures because the world
is the world is horrible the reason why we'll come back around to that when we
come to the ride closing not Jeffrey Jones
Jeffrey Joe's of course had a child pornography no I know worse than that oh
yeah I think there's a taking photo taking photos in a shed it's the guy
he's the principal from Ferris to Rooney yeah very sad that he did bad things he
was so he was so great in many 80s and 90s films Howard the Duck he's in a lot
of stuff he still worked out he still worked after to which anyway insane
German clench yeah he played German clench and then the two alien scientists
dr. Femis is played by Kathy Najee me Najee me this is how I can tell you love
this right you said dr. Femis without any like attitude or any that just very
earn it and the dr. Femis and then of course the the instigator the one who
makes everything go wrong spin lock no trade by the great Kevin Pollock
Kevin Pollock we need to get we need to get Kevin on the show to talk about
spin lock on the show to talk about took his fedora off to portray we're all in
luck so after they tell you a little bit about the history of the ride you go to
like a second pre-show area with sir the simulated intelligence robotics that is
portrayed by Tim Curry the great Tim Curry and then he has like two
teleportation tubes there with an adorable animatronic named Skippy an
adorable alien who they would sell lots of stuffed animals of and he demonstrates
the technology and takes the light in torturing Skippy by using this
technology on him and teleports him from one tube to another tube where he's all
like fried like a loony tune after they've been shot with a cannon I have
I have a skippy toy as well from Park Stars oh yeah yeah yeah sorry I should
have been added early toys huh I would like us what is it what's coming politics
character name in luck I would love a spin lock toy oh you have a spin lock no
there weren't any alien action figures sucks I wish dr. famous the Kathy and
Jimmy character wears this very odd like plastic or tin looking dress like I
would like to have the full I'd like to have her weird shiny space dress it's
like a space dress but the design is kind of like when there is a nurse in
Downton Abbey when there was a matron lead nurse said they're wearing like a
tent yeah yeah yeah but it's in space so blue hey if you don't know the ride that
we were talking if we have not I have not convinced you to look up a ride
through of it yeah check out dr. famous's space dress so after Tim Curry
fucks around with Skippy for a while and then the thing is he teleports Skippy
Skippy gets fried and then he's like the best thing is like you can pause the
teleportation so then Skippy is disappears and he's just in the air he's
just kind of like hovering between like Mike TV and Willy Wonka yeah like Mike
TV that's perfect yeah and then there is footage of dr.
famous and spin lock telling you what's about to happen that one of you is gonna
get transported to their planet and then chairman clench bursts in and he says no
I'm going to transport to them and they're like alright alright dude what
is interesting is that that's supposed to be the better scenario but if you
think about it transporting Jeffrey Jones into a room full of children is a
lot less scary or a lot more scary excuse me than transporting the alien
who are all locked in place who are a lot in place cannot reach them uh-huh
yeah that's I think here's another maybe you and I just both had a bad feeling
about Jeffrey Jones already in 1984 maybe that's so maybe we're just the
universe is sending us a signal I mean signal you didn't get Jason even if you
saw a clip of the pre-show you would know that chairman clench you know did
not get to the head of this company ethically you don't make that many
space dollars being an ethical businessman there's weird implications of
what else excess tech did yeah yeah so they one of the things that their
company does is like planet planetary restructuring which implies like blowing
up yeah and it's I think yeah there's a whole list I should have written it down
but yeah there's a whole list of of terrible things that this company is up
to a little Easter egg there is like a receipt or invoice from excess tech in
the collector's office in Guardians of the Galaxy oh yeah like they so the
Tyvon collection did business yeah they did business there's a bill like
there's a car there is there is some real great little Easter eggs in that
Guardians ride for Disney fans collection of this of Vinicio del Toro
and there's a lot of yeah and believe it or not the collector's a big Disney
Parks fan yeah so he's got figment in one of his little cases anyway so then
you're loaded yeah you're loaded into this theater and you're strapped in
these harnesses like come down all at once like very slowly lower into this
theater full of people and you know the film starts to play I think maybe it's
in the room where like the film is like all right we're gonna transport one of
you that's yes that's where it's explained the chairman clench we will
not be transported but chairman clenched chairman clenched will be a very odd part of the ride where he says no I if only one of you
came I could only meet one of you but instead I can shake each hand I don't
know what he's after this whole I don't know the drama of chairman clench wants
to meet us yeah they don't really set that up of like why he's so hell-bent I
mean he's very much like a politician who's like I want to roll up my sleeves
and go to a diner and shake some hands it's very weird it's unexplained but so
what so you know it's dr. Femis is trying to reconfigure the machine for
this this change and then spin lock goes like no fuck it just do it we gotta do
it spin lock messes everything up oh it's his fault and and because a planet
gets between the teleportation signal they transport clench to another planet
and then he they're like oh we got to get him out of there we got to get him
out we got to get into earth and they're like well there's this life form looks
about right he's just just do it it's him it's him and then they transport him
into a teleportation tube and that's when you realize like I think the wrong
alien yeah there's a joke where it's like us since when does clench have wings and
it's like it is a monster it is a monster scary shit yeah scary shit
mm-hmm it's usually partially obscured by like fog a lot of the time which just
makes it even more frightening does it appear in the tube kind of like
screaming and writhing around oh it sure does breaks out okay yeah and then it's
they it the glass like they do a cool effect like a lot of the fear in this
ride comes from like classic like theatrical effects like playing the
audio from different angles a lot of smoke and mirrors type of stuff and then
like the tube is empty and the power goes out and so like the the implication
being the alien this monster alien is crawling around the room mm-hmm and they
had to know the fact that he has wings is one of the things that they had to
change when they shut it down because that was like a lost story point they
had to show that the alien has wings to let you know how it's flapping around
and flying from one part of the theater to the other oh this was like this was
one of the things that a lot of people like the problems that this ride had and
the story issues kind of stemmed from that they wanted to do a the movie alien
yeah that's an alien that you've seen that you understand you don't need the
backstory because you're coming in aware of the franchise and a lot of the
issues this ride had is that they had to like reverse engineer and tell you all
this stuff about excess tech and since when does it have wings they had to
explain the alien to you in a way they wouldn't have had to with the the
xenomorph okay that this again this sounds like a note that is parodied in
Hollywood movies a lot of just like well this character's at his house and then
he's having lunch with his boss what happens in between like how do we how
does he get to the restaurant it's like who gives a shit like the alien can
climb I just solved it I fixed it the alien can climb the xenomorph has like
limbs like long limbs that like can make him climb her climb but this also like
this alien like the the model of it's like got like a dozen legs and it's got
giant claws and it's got wings like okay it can get around the theater's not that
big another important thing to note in terms of theme park exposition is that
nobody is paying attention whatsoever only psycho little kids who are gonna
start a podcast 20 years later are no no any have heard the words excess tech or
dr. femis or any yeah so it is fun to imagine ears just remember no one is
paying attention it is funny because you would how many people have done like
this thing was open for how many years eight years just under ten years if you
were to give a test to every dad who went on this ride do you recognize this
logo the excess tech logo what is the percentage of dads who would know what
that is is it oh very low two percent the main logo of the ride it's a no I
know that I'm just saying if you were to give all this iconography and all these
different things in the backstory and like would a dad ever remember anything
would he remember spin lock show my photo of spin lock
dad is so weirdo my dad my dad went on it I don't know if I go hey dad you know
who spin lock is he would not know what I mean I remember seeing this face right
right after I saw my son weeping openly in public that was another one of my
favorite activities with this ride is standing in the gift shop which was full
of stuff I bought or wanted to buy and watching people exit and I would just
watch people crying scared children leave this ride and I remember my family
like my me and my mom talked to like some of the employees once we're like
hey do a lot of people come out really scared of that ride and they're like all
day all day long all day every day yeah they got constant complaints complaints
from people because they didn't know how scary this thing was and their child
would be traumatized it was I mean it just made it that much better like
there's never been like a better yeah I mean it's scary it's just such an odd
thing to have it in Disney then that's what adds to it I mean Halloween Horror
Nights has nothing on this right you know what you're getting into there this
is like it's a fucking convention center it is a great misdirect because you're in
Disney and Tomorrowland and it's so bright and cheery and then right off of
the hub yeah it's right there you're looking at the castle and then you're
about to get eaten yeah it's I think it's pretty great that story is crazy to
me it was effective that for as much as we you know we had we're like we were
too scared to go on it it really did like mess kids up I am curious if like
if people if there was like legitimate psychological I'm sure people I mean I
got it I got a thing so pretty amazing and I like I just like that it was like
a bold thing I like that they do something very different yeah yeah and
they'd ever done before it's like yeah noticeably different than any other
attraction this the next big thing that happens in the ride they send a
maintenance person in and so there's like this is again another smoke and
mirrors trick where it's like someone is in the rafters above the theater and
there's like a dangle a light that moves so it looks like a flashlight walking
around and they go to repair it and then they they they he has like a night vision
camera on that he's wearing and like on the one screen you once he plugs it back
in you see what he sees and it's the monster and the monster eats him
multiple people die in this ride like this guy dies horrifically he is
screaming you there they drop droplets of water on you as if it's his blood
they use the droplets of water to be the breaking glass too like when the monster
breaks out you they spray water at you so it feels like you got sprayed with
like little shards of glass like it's it's really wild and then did you still
like when you do you remember specifically like first time second time
third time like do you were you able to brace yourself how bad was it the first
I think every trip the first time I would be scared because I would forget
stuff and then after the rerides I would just like I just liked all the beats of
the ride I also like like to laugh at everyone who hadn't been on I like to
scream I remember talking to people like I've been on this before and they're
like no and I'm like this is it's great let me have great let me ask you this
did you have a secret fantasy that you would get eaten I mean oh maybe I mean
I've always longed for death sweet touch that's what I mean long to touch the edge
no I know so I was wondering if you were like this is the time it happened this
is the time it happens I feel like there is and I can't remember if I read that
there's like one broken seat there's always one broken seat with like an
excess cover on it hmm I forget but like there they left a lot of the excess I
mean they reused a lot of the stuff for stitch we haven't even gotten to the
stitch I know as well and so then eventually the power comes back on they
lure the alien back into the tube this is at the very end when you get the
fullest view of him and he's the alien is screaming they're flashing lights
everywhere there's there's he's leaning through the broken glass and then they
slide the tube up and I think they're like they don't even try to teleport
him out of there they just like full power he's gonna explode and then he
like explodes oh which gets me to another thing he explodes right as the
tube starts to close and they do spray the water again so like you got the
like you got a water and you got alien parts and there's also some piped in
dialogue and from as if it's audience members saying it and at that point like
when you first see the alien there's a very faint cry of someone goes like oh
what is this my mother-in-law and then at the very end when the alien explodes
someone goes oh my mouth was open like this is these weird wow these comedy
guys it's a real like theater actor man my mouth was open yes a real hammy joke
and then like you're tourist I forget what the closing lines but like Dr.
Femis and spin lock come on the screen they do not address the fact that
Chairman clench is stranded on a strange planet and probably dead he's
probably dead or injured depending on the atmosphere yeah depending that or
not they say like and at that point they're not even sorry they're like well
the future you know you got a break some eggs to get to the future like there I
forget what the line is probably another play on excess and then the lights come
up and do you believe having survived what is essentially a traumatic
experience you try to walk out with your knees shaking with your knees shaking
yes yeah if you can manage to not faint and on your steps to the gift shop I
mean besides like yeah I mean I saw some kids coming off crying but most people
were like laughing going off you know most people were like wow that was crazy
like that was great and you know better and like a better area that was more
appropriate for it I think it would have been a big hit like if it was in a
universal park or something I think because because this is a beloved
attraction actually like yeah as much as this thing got because it you know gets
ripped on for being scary it's just because people weren't expecting it and
kids are expecting a fun much more pleasant experience at Disney long lines
like once all that our land stuff like that Tomorrowland everything was pretty
popular there except carousel progress which is slow and for old people and I
still love it and the people mover which never stops running so there's rarely a
line because you just walk into the car so I agree oh boy I've been
transported to 94 tomorrow I loved it there so eventually this ride but
eventually they're like this is people are complaining too much and they I mean
I don't know what the hourly capacity of it was either I'm not sure if it was
huge it always had long lines but they they did close it in 2003 mm-hmm and why
is the quiz because why well there's yeah there's two schools of thought it's
a mix that it was like too scary and then also like it didn't help that a
child bluster was one of the main characters and a villain a sinister
villain leering at you I'm guessing it had mores to do because you can redo a
video you can refill that you can refill you get who's a villain at the time who
was like a character actor who was evil who should have in 2003
oh Billy zane that's a little late that's a little late yeah I mean Nick
Cage would have been a get surely an a-lister probably want to put all that
maybe he's a big Disney Parks fan who should have been clench if you could
reclass recast clash right now would be a mocap that man now clench yeah oh it
would all be mocap and it would all be a simulator and yeah yeah yeah the mess it
up yeah what was gonna say I think that like this is an area too now they've
talked about putting like a virtual reality Wreck-It Ralph mm-hmm thing in
that because it's a small area so so yeah it's a small theater I mean and
it's it's like the it's built into the infrastructure of other stuff like the
people mover track and multiple gift shops so like they kind of can't totally
destroy it they just keep reusing this theater they keep trying to figure out
how to reuse the infrastructure yeah yeah it's so it's lit it's limited in
what they can do with it well which is why they closed the ride and gave it
this overhaul this was an under an underwhelming over underwhelming over
that would that is called stitches great escape and if you had to synopsize this
ride it would be everything we just described but with stitch and it's
wacky Tim Kurt the Tim Curry robot has a police uniform and a beard now it's nice
and he's nice and the projections on the screen or the the film segments are all
animated you know I oh and and instead of the alien dripping his slime on you
stitch burps a chili dog smell in your face yeah that is the main headline when you a lot of
different theme park websites and listen Pica a lot of theme park media has
declared this the worst attraction in all of Disney World and but the really
the the crux of the argument is always stitch burps chili dog not like it's not
fun it's not pleasant it's not I mean you listen to the audience they're all
just like like stick I mean I guess it's I'm it makes sense like why I mean
stitch Leo at stitch was like a pretty big hit right and it's like the one
thing that's like survived from that era of Disney animation that people like
yeah the treasure planet era the home on the home yeah Lilo and Stitch is the one
thing I think people actually do have affection for I do find it a very
endearing yeah it's cute but this is they very much were like alright let's take
out the family stuff and the ohana means family family means no one gets left
behind let's get rid of all that yes let's get the alien scientists who
torture him but but not like torture like the old alien scientists do torture
people no no it's like I'll admit this I've never been on this one either I have
not I think I've been and I guess I've been using world yeah it's just you're
too it's just too much stuff to do in Disney World both times I've gone in the
last ten years it's like well I'm gonna go gonna go on Stitch's great escape or
go on Space Mountain or go over animal kingdom like I would imagine your
girlfriend similar to my wife who has does not have the pain tolerance that I
do I need to experience every horrible attraction she could love she would love
to never again go on journey into imagination or sit through the I mean
this isn't a bad attraction yeah American Adventure I remember oh just
staring daggers that the American Adventure rules like the American
Adventure so but also again this is the the climax of the show is Mark Twain and
and Franklin and shaking hands poorly shaking hands it's great I don't I'm not
gonna blame my wife here I'll say that no no it's not I didn't go on and there
was that nothing to do with Lindsay I just we were like under the gun to get
other stuff done it does feel I mean it's very melancholy for me when I've
written it's been very because the old ride meant so much to me and I was like
smile like a friend I used to recognize but it's so much is gone similar same
harnesses I so much of it they barely changed and the other thing is the time
key I used to love the timekeeper too I didn't ride that as much because it was
just a movie and it was a little long I have never written the Monsters Inc
last year I don't even know what it is and just because I'm like no absolutely
not to I think pretty dynamic interesting new attractions not based on
in other intellectual property alien encounter and the timekeeper which will
cover at some point I am sure but the these were replaced by these I think yeah
these these very lame quick you know like shove them in kind of attractions
based on the only popular movies Disney had at the time yeah right that that
Monsters Inc thing seems so I guess they are for little children this is what I'm
forgetting yeah but people like them the other thing is what I've read in stitch
kids still kind of cry and scream because it's still pitch black a lot of
the time and weird noise and it's invasive yeah I mean we touching you
we'll do honey I shrunk the audience which I did do and I scared the shit out
of me as a little kid yeah I was so scared like those snakes I don't even
like Shrek 4d when they poke you in the back when I don't like poke in the back
do people like this to people like it's tough to be a bug when like the bugs all
crawl yeah I hate anything like this it's I'm not scared of it yeah it's so
people like you're being molested by these people like being scared some
people like being scared and that's what's what's different about the three
of us is that most theme park people not most I shouldn't say but a lot of theme
park is a big contingent now of Halloween Horror Nights people that like
this they like being touched by college students and masks they like like
constantly going ah like I don't like that I got six minute haunted house the
old house of horrors at Universal I had a headache after it I was so like stop
stop yelling at me college students I got a I have a story I'll save for
another day on that but yeah I friends maybe go through that once and it sucked
and then I got the biggest fuck you at the end of it and yeah I would have
saved that for another yeah yeah we're really over freaks who were taken over
yeah our nice cute attractions get out of there you're a bad element and yeah
look at least tallow at least Universal shoves them into the night the unruly
nighttime we're nice these people these weirdos out of my daytime parks yeah
we're nice boys want a pleasant experience yeah nice park or at the very
least if you're gonna make it scary spend a lot of money on it and get some
character actors in there yeah yeah more yeah more indelible characters like
we're just Tim Curry just get put Tim Curry in there you know big influence
for me Tim Curry sure yeah the also it's just this isn't about this right but I'm
in my the fact that the monsters ink laugh floor was a ride where you can text
in a joke and then they'll tell a joke you text what an unpleasant I might as
well say it now because I'd love to not do an episode about the monsters ink
laugh I think if we're doing it we're doing this in three years I think we'll
will have already gotten to monsters ink lab floor scraping the bottom of the
barrel will be we'll be doing that on the roof of one of our apart that'll be
our like the Beatles that'll be our last episode as long as you think Lord we're
doing on a roof for a crowd you know you know that it's been rough our
relations our personal relationships afraid and yeah people gather down while
they're doing it one more time Jason's got some cool new girlfriend
dressed like dr. famous we don't like to dress this way I didn't tell her it was
alright you was dressed this way when we met she's sitting in the corner for
recording and healthy together I think this is probably an attraction where we
should do the thing that we often forget to do which is plus it up keep it as is
yeah burn to the ground for insurance money because that it's a big question I
don't know what you do the rumor is like you said that this record Ralph
attraction is coming in although there's sort of a rumored issue with that is
that there's a really amazing Super Mario Kart attraction on the way they
don't want to look like shit that because this would be in the rumor is
it's a ride based on sugar rush the go-kart yes game that they play a race
game that is in wreck at Ralph so is that sort of is that does that end up
being a lesser version of what probably yes well also like those VR sets of
parks are experimenting with putting on people not only is it time-consuming to
put them on people and secure them the technology out paces in event
innovation out paces like people's expectations so like if it looks good for
six months it's gonna look like shit in a year yeah you know and also people can
do it from their home people can buy VR for their home so you got to compete
with that right yeah I think I always think that stuff is weird like shove the
idea that I mean I think some fun rides came out of Disney wanting to do video
games in the parks I like Buzz Lightyear Astro Blasters and I really like Midway
mania but I think you there's still think you can't go nuts with that I did
not like the Knott's Berry Farm video game right Oh journey to the iron reef
that was yeah that's bad that's that's a headache inducing ride sure so yeah
this video game stuff I don't know in the VR I don't know I'm really not sure
what you do here but I bet this the idea has occurred to you guys as well that
with the Disney Fox merger well we talked about it on the last show they
could do the original version on the astromo with a xenomorph and I'm all
for it yeah if we're doing the scale like I would say bulldoze the one in
Tomorrowland build the original version but let's get crazy with it so plus it
up like have people in there always that are plants maybe that get like sucked
out of their seats and or like bloodied up or like have half the audience kind
of like like have part of have part of the things move so like the seats go
met like people go missing so like lights go back on and maybe the person
next to you is gone dad is gone have the Prometheus the weird Prometheus God
creatures oh in there have and then of course I mean fold spin lock into the
Wayland Yutani mythology yes everything is alien but also spin lock and Dr.
females are there and make Ridley Scott do another one of these alien movies but
spin lock is in it and he's interacting with fast benders what David is that the
character the robot character so yeah put David on the ride to David is out
the eyes like obviously get talking to you before the ride and then like spin
lock like knocks him over like gets him wet because he's a robot and that's bad
and like he starts the short circuit or something you have a little levity
before the horror yeah Paul riser goes in Ripley goes in I think alive yeah live
actors that was what I thought like a live that's Lee yes see two 3d that'd be
fun yeah there's a lot of stuff you could do I think and I think the grand
finale you do it like the I don't know why they didn't do this this would have
been good in the original the alien encounter like in the movies you blow
the alien out of an airlock and you got fans blasts that's great like that that's
so that's a cool effect yeah yeah big whirlwind of wind a whirl of wind yeah
I'm very well spoken this would be great right and I think you know obviously
it's tough like you know to set the mythology and you know well I think we
need to change it from Phil Hartman to Tim Curry so that we know that it's a
scary ride and so that kids are why don't you put up a big red sign say no
says no kids there was this attraction maybe too scary and
intense for young children but people so rarely they made it look like one of the
like more bored like one of the like we legally have to put on this like fine
print ride they say that about everything but not every ride yeah little
Mike's and Scott's Peter pants yeah and so I mean business here some cast
members would be like you know what this is right it's like you know this super
scary right and others would be like hi welcome to access tech come to our
presentation and hey welcome back Jason welcome back you small little butter
ball you weird weird little butterball your I heart for future mr. femis did
you get tired of riding the people mover for an hour because if it's not
busy at night they'll just let you sit on it they'll let you stay on it hey
there's a hack yeah that's that's that's not a people mover hack but a
Tomorrowland Transit Authority hack yeah that's another one too where it's like I
mean it's great it's still there I love that it's still there but last time I
was there I was like could I rip an mp3 of the old people mover narration and
listen to it through headphones so I don't have to hear this teen like I
could queue it up and have my own little experience and then my old character
actors give me this old man and then when you ride stitches ride you can put
on hurt by Johnny Cash during the ride oh yeah or just spin lock I just yell
spin locks lines during you cosplay is spin lock too at most conventions yeah
conventions day jobs whatever have what have you when stitch comes out you yell
lock him up check your privilege stitch riders so I think we have agreed it's
somewhere between yeah plus it up somewhere else but it's a head it was
ahead of its time because I don't even think at this like horror nights wasn't
a big thing in the mid 90s I think it was just they were starting but it was
now it's a hole it's a phenomenon it's the most popular thing that Universal
does people want to piss in their pants that's not not us but people want it so
they this would they were really kind of forward-thinking in a lot of ways yeah
maybe just set up a different land entirely called this and Trump robot can
go and piss land to also dark dark humor like again like dark humor usually like a
little bit of it and ride it's fun and different it makes it stand out with
dark mother-in-law jokes nothing darker than that that's that's the the seed of
my getting into comedy was like this dark humor and then the hammy nonsense
of the Adventurers Club and it's just never gone away and so I remain
incredibly niche and unmarketable so so when you're on Marin when you're on WTF
and he asks you who your guys are you're gonna say spin lock you a sure guy
you're sir kind of guy the Colonel puppets and the giant idol from the
Adventurers Club oh yeah and he's gonna go like yeah you know you and I aren't
so different you are I heard so different you ever do heroin no mark oh
boy well look forward to that episode coming up yeah of WTF and we'll be right
back all right welcome back we now are presenting our second edition of our now
recurring segment animatronic of the month and before we get going with that
I want to congratulate the last winner of animatronic of the month striped
shirt pirate trying to get the key back from the dog from Pirates of the
Caribbean thank you so much congratulations to you I hope you
animatronic have felt some increased pride while doing your repetitive work
over the last month two months I don't remember when we did this last but feels
like forever ago but hey striped striped shirt pirates where does a badge of
honor on your on your striped shirt and but now it's time to yank the badge away
from you and give it to another deserving animatronic who does such
excellent work every day in a Disney park somewhere on the globe Mike I think
you're first hello my pick for animatronic of the month is uncle Orville
the drunk man drying out in a bathtub on the carousel of progress move over Bobby
Moynihan this is the original drunk uncle uncle Orville you're great because
of your meld blank voiced out of tune singing your weird uncle Sam costume and
also being a very rare thing at Disney World a naked robot it's a thrill being
able to see a naked relative of that character John up close so today I
salute you uncle Orville I hope you do as your brother John asks stop being a
leech and start looking for a job so what are we determined here in the theme
of the episode where Jason is a lot more active and agitated than usual you just
you convulsed when that began well Scott I guess my animatronic of the month is
an example that we should probably talk to each other before doing this segment
because my choice is also old uncle Orville tell us about him oh he as Mike
said is a lazy man who spends all of his time in a bathtub specifically wearing a
giant uncle Sam he is the permanent houseguest of John and his family and
he miraculously invented a system that John calls air cooling which in this
case is a giant ice cube sitting in front of a fan and so this lazy idiot
somehow invented air conditioning to make his time engaging in the sin of
sloth that much more pleasant lazy lazing around enjoying cool air why those are
two of my favorite pastimes so I'm also throwing it my hat into the rig for
uncle orville so god bless you uncle orville you're also my pick for
animatronic of the month wow this could be a race yeah well I was that well I
think we could do the vote we could do the vote a couple ways it could we could
put on the Twitter where you cast your votes Mike's uncle Orville and Jason's
uncle Orville but maybe here's where we really form a little difference would
you like to declare different years or decades well let's I'll say this
uncle Orville did change he used to be cousin Orville in the original and he
didn't have the uncle Sam costume on for a while oh so we both talked about the
uncle Sam costume so honestly we cannot we have to do the same we have to do
this all right because he shows up at the in the last segment of carousel of
progress but it's just a toilet flushing as if to imply uncle Orville now is
also a houseguest but just takes long shits all right well since I'm not
taking that one since it's just a shit sound effect and not not a fully built
robot why so it'll be it'll be my choice versus your two and I have a feeling one
of yours is gonna win because mine I might is a little bit more of a of a
point I'm making is this the best animatronic I don't know but I think it
might be the most put upon I'm talking about from the 3d movie it's tough to be
a bug at the villainous animatronic hopper hopper is already hated and booed
by children in two different theme parks plus he's straight out of Pixar's fourth
worst film according to kid film critic lights camera Jackson not to mention
he's typically most of the year stuck lifeless in the rafters of his own
theater while Disney changes out the tough to be a bug theater to show
trailers for things like I don't know their live-action reboot of chicken
little but the worst burden that animatronic hopper faces is that he is
cursed with a voice that most people assume is Kevin Spacey it is not and
never was Kevin Spacey in both the attraction and the video game hopper is
voiced by Pixar director Andrew Stanton Stanton is a two-time Academy Award
winner the man behind Finding Nemo Wally and two episodes of stranger things
there is almost no animatronic with a higher pedigree of voice talent and yet
everyone assumes hopper that you are voiced by a creep so today I raise a
glass of bug juice to hopper and his Oscar-winning non harassing voice it's
tough to be a bug but it's extra tough to be animatronic hopper Wow Wow great
choices all around isn't it a shame that because I think that you heard to me
that people think that they're getting yelled at by an animatronic Kevin Spacey
and yet it is not him and the voice in the movie he is the voice in the movie
not on the right of the rider the game the grass the grasshopper we're all
making a lot of assumptions that we've assumed that you remember who hopper was
we assume certainly that you know who John is for to the memorably named
protagonist progress throughout the years on his journey and he's also
another another character that is exactly like Jason yeah a kindly old man
in a rocking chair with a thick sweater who's eternal I do like the I like the
idea that we there are hundreds if not thousands of robots and the second time
we did this Jason and I picked the same character he's the seven about the same
thing the seventh most prominent robot on that ride this 45 presidents alone
hundreds of pirates right hundred nine hundred ninety nine ghosts you manage to
choose a large man in a bathtub it makes a lot of sense yeah somehow
psychologically attracted to this large this this man in bathtub okay well so go
to our Twitter go to at podcasts the right on Twitter and cast your vote for
animatronic of the month is it orville orville or hopper hey well so enjoy that
the results will get back to you whenever we remember to do this again and
you've survived podcast the ride thanks for listening what do we oh Twitter
podcast the right at Twitter at Instagram podcast the right at gmail if
you want to send us an email yeah we love getting your your tweets and your
your your comments on Instagram and your emails episode ideas because it saves us
a couple of texts yeah yeah and review our oh yeah review on iTunes especially
since we're you know the boys are off the leash we're independent now so tell a
friend tell friends tell friends give them this disease yeah help build up
podcast the ride audio our new audio podcast network podcast network the
right podcast that well that's right that's the name of our new podcast
network podcast network the ride so please support podcast network the ride
and if you want to donate to us personally write us on Twitter and we'll
give you our addresses and you can send a check so yeah for some ice check
couple of coins or bucks in an envelope alright thanks so much everybody we'll
catch you next time see ya bye