Warning, today's podcast clocks in at more than two hours and it's about a parking garage.
It's the Mickey and Friends parking structure with Nick Weiger on Podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast the ride a theme park podcast hosted by three members of an unsuccessful barbershop quartet
Joining me as always Jason Sheridan. Hi and Scott Gardner. Hey, that's right
And that that real mean diss was written by our guests today
You know him as a writer from comedy bang bang and at midnight and from the podcast doughboys ladies and gentlemen, it's Nick Weiger
Friends, that's why I'm known as the successor to the roast master general
When Jeff Ross hangs it up, I'll be assuming his mantle wearing his
General leasimo outfit whatever whatever. Yeah, he's got angley custom. Yeah
Yeah, you'll eventually grow to be able to fit into it perfectly
After the race after after the war a real a real thrill to be here guys really really enjoying here
Thanks so much, yeah, I don't know why we had you on
second of your we've had Mitch on right already and I don't know why we didn't have the like
informed person with a lot of
Theme park opinions. I don't know why you weren't first. Yeah. Well, I think you really though
Like I understood that you wanted to hear from Mitch on the episode. He was on
discussing
Disney world in Florida versus Disneyland out here in California. I understand you wanted to get his trenchant insights like
Disneyland's bad
Disney world so much better. So he pointed out that Disneyland is small. Yeah
There's more of it
we've also like
Like like we've we've all talked about
Theme park issues with you guys and you bring up writing park stuff on this on the show sometimes and I feel like you're your
opinions kind of I
don't know they they fall in line with how you guys are on the show where Mitch is this like a
kind of
populist
Distrusting immediately like he hates IP
Right in with him hating the new but the IP if the IP was when he was a kid, it's fine
That's what yeah
As to fall within that sweet spot of like having come having come out between like 1980 and like
1997 and if like it's in that range if it's in the those two the final two decades of the 20th century
It's good
Outside of that. It's bad
Yeah, I don't know like like and I don't want to just turn this into a proxy, you know sort of
Doughboy spat without my co-host here, but I do I do think that I do think that it's
It's interesting the resistance I get it but but some I noticed there's some sort of some resistance towards you know
the big one I feel like recently is
Tower of terror retrofitting that tower terror terror out here in LA retrofitting that as the Guardians of the Galaxy ride
and you know I get some hostility towards that because you have like this want this version that
exists that you're familiar with and
Then it gets replaced by this thing that was just like basically because it was a popular movie that came out in the past
ten years
But I mean, I think like if you actually take it on its merits the Guardians of the Galaxy, right is good, right?
Like it's really fun. It is a good ride really well received that animatronic is yeah one of the best animatronics in a long time
It's really good
And then Mitch just hates it without ever having been on it
Like he just he says it's bad and then if someone else has like written it and says it's bad
He's like they're right and if someone's like that's actually pretty good
He's like what are you talking about like it's it's maddening to have a discussion with them
Well, that's a weird one because like Tony longtime
Imagineer Tony Baxter who like helped build both tower of terrors is like yeah the the California adventure one was
Okay, but he was like totally fine with them redoing it because it's missing like the main
Well, I was gonna say and funny enough
We're pretty sure we we met him right after he rode the Guardians of the Galaxy ride for the first time
Yes, right Wow all three of us all three of us. This is before the podcast
This is like this is early last year
We were walking between Disneyland and Disney were excuse me just California Adventure
And we saw Tony Baxter and I was looking at my phone and Scott goes. Oh my god
It's Tony Baxter which most mild mannered you can you can all kind of our code when we all met like oh
We're all theme park fans apparently you know so and you start talking about Tony Baxter right away
He's one of the like code with that's like one of your ways in if you really end it
He's like he got it star tours. He did Indiana Jones. He did figment in Florida
Okay, he's done it so my Disney in Paris on her mountain big Thunder Mountain like this is a major heavyweight in the Imagineering
Akinda maybe this probably isn't perfect, but a kind of like a Steven Spielberg
It's kind of like oh this guy's had this degree of influence on his field. Yeah, I mean
Yeah
Similar to that Mike that you would like recognize it a deep comic book artist on site
Which a lot of people who've even read his work wouldn't like know what he looks like we know the iconic right only Baxter mustache
Yeah, so he had just ridden the ride
And we were walking me like oh excuse me
We're big fans of you and he like he's like well
Did you did you ride it and he pointed at the point of it and I was like yeah
And he's like give it the big thumbs up oh there you go and like not and obviously he wasn't gonna be like oh
Fucking IP man like right in rocket raccoon right still
Was my opinion to because the version in Florida is a little taller
But also there's a sequence in Florida that they never replicated anywhere else where the elevator leaves the elevator shaft and pushes forward
It's unbelievable through a giant recreation of the Twilight Zone opening credits. Oh my god
Cool. Yeah, and such a letdown when you go on this one, and it doesn't have that yeah
Oh, I didn't even know about that. Yeah, it was taller
It's not is it taller. Maybe a little bit
It'll talk to you and the whole line is you walk up and there's a whole like there's all this like greens like shrubs
And like it's really sets the mood very well
And now like at the end to like there's a there's a show scene at the end when you come down
And there's like the puppet from Twilight Zone at the end and like there's a whole little room as you're like pulling back
That's not in this version. This one just like pops you in gets you up and down and it sucks compared comparatively
It's still a good fun ride that I write but it's when you're like comparing it to that. Geez. This is that's crazy
This is the hill that Mitch is dying
Lesser did even like the Twilight Zone the Tower of Terror to begin with or is it just the idea the awful notion that the new
Guardians because they are new that they're in the theme park. Well, that's what it is
Like no one cares about these characters and then like some people say that a message boards too when it's like that the numbers
Really tell you otherwise. Yeah, it's not true at all. These are very popular kids like these movies a lot
Well, I'm like Florida there, you know, yeah, they're taking these characters
Nobody cares about and and you know get kicking out, you know, Ellen and Bill Nye
Yeah, I don't know it's it's an odd I yeah, I'm off I
There's a lot of I don't I don't even like Marvel movies
I'm not even sure where I land on the new Star Wars movies, but like in the parks all bets are off
Yeah, we're all pretty
Yeah, we're all pretty progressive when it comes to like changes right park. I feel like you know, we're we're not conservative
We're not stodgy conservatives
well for me it's like and I appreciate that perspective because you guys very easily could be you know cranks and it would still sort of
I mean, there's a world where you guys are theme park cranks and you don't want anything to change
But I think like
For me the big the big factor in towards what Scott was saying because I'm not someone who sees every Marvel movie and the
Ones I see are generally like like, you know, check out Ant-Man and like alright, you know
Yeah, that got the job done. Like I don't I don't have like a I'm not I'm gonna say static
Reaction to seeing Thanos or whatever like I don't care that much
But I understand these movies are you know important to some people and I also
For me the big proof of concept for this sort of theming can result in a great
Park attraction is Cars Land. Yes my favorites and the Cars movies are not great like they're fine
I think I don't think I'd go any higher than fine
Would you go all the way into like bad terrible? Are you mad at him? No, they don't suck
They're just like they're but you know, I'm not gonna go full lights camera Jackson and say that's Pixar at its best
There they're fine they're probably
Towards the the the low end of Pixar's output. They're like they're not that great. They're not the good dinosaur, but they're not great
Not so they open the land yeah, the good dinosaur land could be fine. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, so so yeah, I mean like you put more Marvel shit in this the park
I don't care if that's what triggers great new attractions
And I agree I think I think you'd be really impressed to find somebody who doesn't like Cars Land that right?
It's an incredible addition and
Yes, just some of the most the best like immersive theming and rock work and gives you that route 66 vibe
And yeah, you can like a vibe from a movie without liking the sure. Yeah, absolutely
Yeah, the aesthetic is great for a theme park. It just really really works
Well for something that you're going to inhabit
I had one thing on Tower Tower of Terror real quick the the because I've only been on the LA version now
I'm very excited to try the Florida version to see this this extra
Leg that Jason mentioned, but so do they do they still in its most recent?
Because I can't remember the last time I wrote it before it got converted
They still have a moment where like a bellhop would give a little orientation in the lobby
They sort of like a lobby or there was a point where a bellhop would sort of give a little speech of like
You know like welcome to the Tower of Terror
This is a this is a tower of mystery and grandeur where any like there was like a little live-action
Huh, I don't I don't recall that this so maybe this was something because I this this would have been early a visit
In the very early 2000s, right observe this but I think they they later took it out
Because it was a moment. I remember that really took me out of the Disney
Experience because the performer was so awful
Like it was this woman who was had been cast as a bellhop and she was supposed to talk about this spooky corridor
Where you know?
Whatever where the rules of science do not apply and where you might meet an untimely end
but she's delivering it like like
This is the Tower of Terror
That's really tipping a lot of what's about to happen
And she was really like it was just it was just the worst like most stilted delivery to the point where I was like
How did you get this job? Like why are you here?
Why aren't you a cashier over at the like next to the a bugs life like stage show?
Like why is why is this your job in Disney parks? Yeah. Yeah, that's very odd because the cast member interaction
I associate with Tower of Terror is like once they make sure you're buckled in and the door is closing
Like the I think they kind of give them the freedom to have some fun with it
Oh, like sometimes they'll go like your rooms are ready sleep
well
or like some people some people get really in character other people would just be like enjoy your stay, you know, like
And and not really do a big thing about it
But the ones who are really into it like really would go into it like Haunted Mansion
It's a good area. Yeah fun and get somebody with a lot of personality
How do you end up with this flat person but you get a lot of duds
Yeah, you do get a lot of duds on Haunted Mansion
You get a lot of duds at Tower of Terror where people just kind of brush
I mean this sounds like it's just like she was reaching and didn't get it
Yeah, she yeah, she was she was trying but she didn't have the chops to pull it off. Yeah. Yeah the the other thing the
Speaking of the the bellhop who has a little bit of creative liberty the last time I rode the actual Tower of Terror
As with my wife and
the
So like you finish the ride and the doors open at the end and our bellhop attendant had like was crouched down
And then so when the doors opened he jumped up and went ah and gave us like an extra scare and everyone loved it
That's great. Yeah
I've had that happen. I think once and yes, it's delightful
It's great when you get because I do think at these parks you get
Like there's an extra you can get an extra bit of magic by the cast member doing something fun and like that
There was a time when the stormtrooper I'll never forget. It was a guy dressed as a stormtrooper
I felt like a guy grabbed my arm aggressively. I turned around
It was a stormtrooper in line of star tours Wow
and then like there was a kid there and he was trying to cut the line and he like
Booted the kid like softly with his foot to get him out of like out of the line
I it's we all like we're delight would delight it. It's crazy how that does that is such a big deal
Right having like a college student try a little bit
That sort of
Well, like that's that is a big big deal. And yeah, you can really it can really bring it down when there's not doing it
There's this great in thing. I recommend to anybody going to Las Vegas where there's a there's in the M&M store on the strip
There is a 3d movie that was made only for that specific location with the like the the
90s
CGI
Red and yellow the I don't know. I never met the guy. All right does exist
From the Christmas ads but they let you there's a little like adventure of them in Las Vegas in a 3d movie and the the in
to get into it is like a you're in an M&M's laboratory and
At the beginning a really nonplussed high school student in an ill-fitting lab coats
It's like welcome to the M&M's laboratory. I am the professor
I've been twice now here at least but the two is that extra or is that free? That's just free
Strip especially. Oh my god. Oh man get a couple drinks and wander into the M&M's
3d movie it's like packed every time but I still feel like I was shocked when I ran into what do you mean?
There's a 3d movie up here and then like, you know bad stilted interaction with like red
What are you doing red get out of there red? It's it's it's something else
So he's acting against the pre-recorded film for a little bit
There's some like machine that they get sucked into and then you move into their adventure like oh
I think I think I think one of them loses their M and that's the plot
And then but then the solution at the end ends up being all the minis who all like form giant objects together
I'll have the fish and finding Nemo like they all work as nanobots
And rescue the M from some scary factory check it out
Three years we're just gonna dissect the M&M
Well, that's well we should talk a little more about your theme park history you're right now your Southern, California native
What'd you what'd you like growing up? Yeah, so from Lakewood, California
Which is a suburb of Long Beach, California a little better known and that's the city in which I went to middle school in high school
And we had the the orchestras and bands I played in at school
Charles Evans Hughes middle school in Long Beach and Long Beach Polytechnic High School would sometimes make
trips to Disneyland to play in the
What is it? What is that? The the
Carnation Plaza, is that what it's called?
Is that now become part of this little fantasy land
Is that what they call that now
But are like kind of outside the cast
Yeah, it used to be associated with the Carnation company and and you would go would be near where they they sell the ice cream and we
do a little orchestra show or
When I was in marching band boy, you know what?
I guess I don't remember ever actually marching but we must have what at why else would we be there?
So we must have done we must have been involved in a parade in some capacity
but so like yeah, I made a lot of outside of just just going a lot with my
Family because we were close by and it you know, it was like a 25 minute drive and it was it was
You know probably about an annual thing
I probably I'd go an additional time most years just for some band trip and we'd also go to
Six Flags Magic Mountain, but that was usually just like a fun thing a fun activity for the band
So big yeah, right, but I but pretty early on, you know, like it at age 12
I was in the backstage and I was seeing you know
I remember seeing Merlin smoking a cigarette and I was just like wow, this is really
This is crazy to see behind the scenes at Disneyland at an age where I'm young enough where I don't you know, I
Understand that this is like a show but I'm also like not quite an adult where I you know
Fully grasp until I see it that oh, these are just people kind of doing a job, you know
Yeah, sure. Um, and yeah, I mean and so it's so a lot of trips there. I was very very like you guys
I was very scared of
Unlike you guys I grew out of it
Yeah, I also grew out of it at some point and I will pretty much ride anything all right
Standing up thing because I've ridden some standing up roller coasters and they are not made for men of a five one
They either hurt my shoulders or my dick
But it's a yeah, I do remember I went to Disney World when I was a kid kind of all over the place here
But when I was like even though we went to Disneyland a lot
We got we did take a family trip to Disney World when when I was eight where I remember crying on
Their big thunder mountain equivalent they have a big thunder mountain there, right?
Yeah, big thunder. Yeah, yeah that we're crying on their big thunder and that that kind of scared me off of thrill rides for a bit
And then I got back on that horse eventually I think due to peer pressure
Yeah at Six Flags Magic Mountain some classmates cajoling me got me to ride Colossus a wooden coaster there
At age 11 or 12 and from that point on I've enjoyed the role. I've enjoyed the coasters. Mm-hmm
and then a lot of time spent at
Probably the the the amusement park I've been to the most it might honestly be Disneyland at this point
But but at some point in my life, I just racked up so many trips to Wild Rivers, which is now closed theme park
Raging Waters is the other big Southern California water park
And that was the one that's in Bill and Ted's excellent adventure. They go down the slide with Napoleon
that's the one in San Dimas, California and
But Wild Rivers was like the one in Irvine and I went did you ever go there Scott? No, I do not
I'm trying to think that's where is that where the Irvine Meadows is? Yeah. Yeah, and there was also like a safari park
Yeah, there was yeah that that there was there weren't I don't know if they were of the same ownership
But it was the same general area and so I went there a lot for just one just day camps like Cub Scout day camp or just
Like, you know
Whatever those those camps are that they that parents drop off their kids during the summer just so they don't have to take care
Of them
I was in like I was in those like constantly like school would end and then it was like in a day camp for the entire summer
Just to get out of my parents way. I guess actually they were probably working is what it was
They were they had jobs to go to and this was a functional daycare
But not always at Wild Rivers not always at Wild Rivers, but it was like a very frequent trip like oh we're taking this
This is a cheap, you know, whatever like it costs eight dollars per kid to get him in
And I remember we'd pack lunches to go there
We'd have a sack lunch that we'd eat and then we just ride we just go on water slides all day
So you didn't there wasn't some educational onus you know, you could just run around. No. Yeah, pretty much
I mean, I remember being hurted a little bit
But beyond that it was just a way to keep kids occupied for you know, you know six to eight hours
Everybody in the in the the unified shirts. Were you all some like some particular monkey?
We must have been yeah, we must have been we must have had whatever that camp shirt what what the hell
I can't even remember the name of the camp down
But yeah, we must have we must have had something like that
and
Yeah, honestly, like I don't remember that this is a this is a little bit of a of a tangent
But you know something of a doughy kid
But I don't remember there being a big shirt on swimming contingent at that point
There was still like I because I do remember being shirtless there and feeling a little embarrassed
But yeah, that's tough. Right you said like wait or like middle school. This was younger than that
This was this was this was as a preteen
This is when we went to Wild Rivers, but I had a weird that this is a thing
I'm just remembering I told for whatever reason I guess I thought it would be a funny story to tell my parents
But I made up a baseless lie about this kid Matt
There's this ride at Wild Rivers called the Python which is this this like kind of crazy
waterslide
wasn't I think the craziest one was a Cobra and the Python was like the Cobra jr and
So I told my parents that this kid Matt
like he loved the Python and he wouldn't stop writing the Python and
All day he'd ride the Python and then just run back up the stairs and write it again on a continuous loop and
They thought it was so funny, I think they told Matt's parents about it
And then I thought back on it was like why did I come up with that?
And why did that why would that resonate as like a good story? I have no idea when this began
I was worried you were gonna say that Matt was a lifeguard or something who touched you inappropriate
No, it wasn't even that was the thing it was like a total white lie
It was just like why like this is a harmless thing
But also completely untrue like why did I say maybe there was an element of truth
Maybe he said it was his favorite ride at some point and exaggerated. I don't even remember it
But yeah, it's weird. My actual childhood was just doing that for real
Like that was the reality my parents lived right there was some
Right. I can't remember what it was now, but I just remember there was one night if it was
If it was a waterslide connected to like a big
Themed hotel pool or if it was something in it would have had to have been something in Florida where my brother and I would just
Get off and our parents were just like, you know on a bench close by or something
Because they didn't really want to ride it or they had written it enough and we would just do the like we're going again
and just go again
because every now and then like
The Florida parks like if you stay at the Disney hotels like hotel guests get an extra
Either hour or so in the morning or hour and so at night. That's amazing and then it's like
Really empty like the whole park, right?
And I'm sure it was something like that and I can't remember what it was now
I yeah, I stayed at the the Disneyland hotel and they have this really cool
Waterside that's like kind of looks like the old-school monorail
Setup, but with a waterslide inside it and I I did it over and over you could not get me out of there
But then I had to go because my wife said we had to go because the wedding we were going to was in
20 minutes. This was five years ago and I was at the wedding with very wet hair
I don't know why I didn't then use a hair dryer to fix this right? She's still mad about that one
I used to David love for
Such a slobber your wedding
I did that same thing two years ago did not have a wedding to go to did not it just
Throw that slide a bunch because no one else was there lucky you have adults
Three of us all have I have a still my I
We there was it was very late at the park and I was there with my mom and sister and they were gonna let us
Ride start tours because no one was in line and they were gonna just let us do it
My sister got sick like on the second time and I was so mad at her because we had to get off like so
Like I think there's something common here that we would all ride these things for infinity
We would all we were worried your story about about the Python we would all we're all guys that would ride the Python forever
Yeah, it's plausible that that that's like it's like I didn't it didn't even need to be made up because I probably there
Probably just another kid. I could have just said that about I don't know
I don't know where it came from it also
Integra people have been listening to this podcast a little bit a big common thing seems to be trying to break the record on
these rides
I did this 18 times I
Yeah, my friend Perry was touting his Dudley do right rip saw falls record I couldn't tell you the accuracy
They probably tell kids every day. You just broke the record
The records are not being kept right so and if it's next to water, it's impossible to keep the records
so
Well, I mean my my favorite like family story of like redoing stuff a bunch and I may have told I can't remember
I told this before on the show
I do want to make my dad call in and tell it because he tells it a very long a longer version a very funny way
There used to be like this
Immersive comedy club in Pleasure Island in Florida
Which was like a district of nightclubs Disney had in the early to mid 90s
And there was a place called the adventurers club, okay, which was like themed to a
Early 20th century like explorers club and rice there was loosely scripted
Mostly improvised like should there be a different show in the library and then in the study and then in the bar and there was
a giant animatronic
like totem that would talk to people and there was a night where I made my dad get up and
Do the bit with the totem because they gave you a pin they gave you an adventure club pin that you couldn't buy and I'm like
You gotta get me that
But then we came out like as it was closing and it wasn't a place I could go to alone like because it's an it was
Like at a certain point they're like you have to have a parent with you here
It is a nightclub district and we came out and there was like an electrical storm going
And the bus stopped back to the hotel was like two and a half blocks away. Oh, yeah
So we're running through like thunderstorms is like terrifying like they is going above us and just like walking
Walk back into the hotel and they're just laughing at us in the lobby
I like the people working the front desk that pin is a potential conductor of lightning. Yes
You have it still yeah, absolutely. Yeah. Oh, yeah wonderful bring it on the show
Yeah refer to it for being yeah, I clink it around on the mic the the summer that reminds me the summer
We went to Disney World
My family went to was Disney World and it was just like I had never really I mean it rains out at Disneyland
But it's not like I guess as common as it is in Florida
And so there was like a torrential downpour and so we had we basically were in a situation where we had to get
Ponchos and I remember I was very excited to get a
Dick Tracy rain slicker
It is famous. There was one. Yeah, the Warren Beatty Dick Tracy movie was in theaters and
It was like a you know, like like his like his famous yellow raincoat
except it was in poncho form and then it had Dick Tracy written on the back and his silhouette and
I was so excited to wear it and I wore it like, you know
The for the all the rain that was going on and then when it was back to school time
I still had this Dick Tracy poncho, but it was like Dick Tracy wasn't cool anymore
And so I remember wearing this Dick Tracy poncho while it was raining but just leaning
Against a tree so no one would see the Dick Tracy logo on the back
They just thought I was wearing a plain yellow poncho. It's like a giant logo with him looking at the watch. Yeah
There would have been there would have been a pretty tiny window and Dick Tracy was cool
Yeah, yeah, no cuz I remember when the McDonald's promotion was going on that was fun that was fun
Yeah, and but that was it. I once the McDonald's promotion was over. I feel like no one cared any
That was either the first or second movie. I saw in theaters Wow trace it really no one which is kind of horrific
So there's some weird stuff in that movie lips manless getting the bath is so yeah
they have so they this this guy and they've all got grotesque makeup, which is horrifying in and of itself, but
Lips manless is killed very early on and the way they kill him is he's like he's very scared
He's like not the bath big boy. Not the bat
Like he's like very afraid of dying and then they just cover him with cement
This is what's called the bath. I like they put him in a crate and they cover him with cement
Alive and then they throw him into a river and it's just like very early on in the in the movie and it's super grim
It's like something that would be in like, you know, Donnie Brosco. It's just it's it's very I'm pretty sure I then like
Made my action figures take the bath
Incorporated that into my child like fun play with play dough with like play dough or sand or something
So Nick, yes, we're doing theme parks like we're two were three guys who when we were kids we were like
Dreaming of them. Did you have like kind of an obsession with them?
Or was it just some fun thing you did once in a while? I would say more towards the ladder
It wasn't a thing I was thinking about all the time. I certainly had some some great
Memories and some great days spent there
But maybe because I went with some frequency that the man I got kind of got numb to the magic a little bit
Right. It wasn't a thing. I was I was constantly daydreaming about
Right. So just a regular
Attachments a regular kid. I think I was more I was more interested in video games and sure then than than theme parks
That's by the way the normal reaction
Human reaction to be like, oh that's fun to go to once in a while
As opposed to me or you guys who would see the stock report come in and there was a picture of all the balloons on
Main Street and I used to just sit there dreaming about owning a bunch of balloons
Like those did the Mickey year balloons like it's so vivid in my mind of like wow, they're all the different colors
Will I get to see Disney afternoon Avenue a second time while it's open?
Yeah, yeah god pretty pretty fixed. What do I what's your what's your deal these days? Do you do it often?
Yeah, I mean I went to Disneyland last year
With some co-workers after a job that it ended and that was kind of just like a fun work thing
But you know, I definitely like the adult theme park experience. I think adult theme park experience has gotten better
Especially I think with there's more
There are more grown-up beverages, you know, like there's more like nice places to get a drink
Not just like cheap beer if you if you're into alcohol and and also I feel like
I
Don't know. I feel like this is just because the attractions have gotten better. It's like you can still you like
Like the you know, you can still have the nostalgic appreciation for the these old ones that you went to as a kid
You're Pirates of the Caribbean's and your Matterhorns and what-have-you but like that like the new attractions coming in and being sleeker
It's like it's something that you can go and still be kind of impressed by
You know, you don't have to just be a kid to be wowed by something
You still can kind of like we're talking about with Guardians of the Galaxy
You still see this these the new tech that's being shown off there and be like, oh, this is pretty cool
That's a lot of it for me and why I don't really care what the IP or characters like it like matter what it's a display
Of some insane often like military grade technology that when would you like?
Why would you get to experience this? Yeah as a civilian that's that's kind of like that sort of true throughout, right?
Like I mean certainly like flight simulators comes from the that came out of military technology
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, like some area 51 right our tours probably out of simulator technology
It's just like the same. It's just like simulating and then of course mission space in Epcot
Which is literally simulating going into space, which is why it killed a couple people
Going into space is very hard on your body. That's not a thing you should be doing
You should not eat a cinnamon roll underneath
Drink a big sugary coffee drink and then experience a few G forces not spaceship Earth mission space
No, no, I said you're eating. Oh, I see. I see beforehand you get right
I thought you were saying that your experience on spaceship Bruce was it was so intense
That it was too much for you
I had a pre and post I had one beforehand to ready myself and then one to reward myself for doing
Quick sign. Oh, you can take food and drink on spaceship Earth because I did it last time I was there
That's crazy
Like I had like a bag of something like nuts and like a water and no one stopped me
So you could like throw a big beer on to the Steve Jobs esque figure
Yes in his garage. Yeah, you could ruin the Sistine Chapel
Oh
It helps it with ice really
Easy, so well so of everything of everything in the theme park world
You sent us a list of stuff to talk about and few options
Yeah, we went through it and considered it and of all the things for some reason we landed on we really wanted to talk about
The Mickey and Friends parking structure. I love it at the very least because it's a very funny episode
Like I can only like I'm just imagining people's reactions of looking at their phone on a Friday morning
I was like, oh, there's a new app. What the hell?
This boring man wants to discuss a boring topic I guess that's on brand the ball road carpool
Yeah, it's it's pretty elemental
Yeah, when I been thinking about in the last couple days was this
Was it was it kind of a dare or was it or do you do you do you have a lot of stuff to
Say about the Mickey honestly, like I'm not sure how much I have to say like I mean
I think we could probably find it did you know discuss anything at like this this podcast is all about you know, yeah
Yeah mining minutiae
Stringing that thread. Yeah, I can so, you know, but honestly, this is a thing
My wife Natalie and I when we go to
Disneyland together and you know, sometimes you'll get the Mickey and Friends parking structure and other times
You'll get some other lot like the woody lot or something some just like adjunct lot
But we're always like there's always like an extra thrill when we get that Mickey and Friends parking structure and it's thing
We've talked about because she you know design is something that she is
very conscious of and it's a thing that I'm I'm aware of and I used to ostensibly be a
Designer of working working in the video game industry. So it's just such a a great
Functional I'm using the word design again
But design is a great functional design and and and it's just so efficient and I feel like it's like the beginning of
In the same way that I mentioned raging waters earlier and like when you park it raging waters is my memory of it
It's like a dirt lot. It's like so janky. It's like yeah, it's like the
sloppiest
Beginning of what's supposed to be a day of suspension of belief or just like a day of fun and
Windy and sharp hills and weird turns exactly. I went up there
Yeah
And then you get on like an an
Unair-conditioned bus like just said like a decommissioned school bus and that's what's taking you to the park proper
Like that's their tram system
Like it's really really janky and then that's that's your end of day too. Like after you've had a day of fun
That's how you're going home that so you you're in your you're beginning and end
It's being bookended by this kind of like a clumsy
Experience and I think the opposite is true with the Mickey and Friends parking structure because you're going in there
It's a breeze you're being guided like basically
Directly to a space because of the cone system and the you know, they've got an abundance of attendance
They've got so many attendance working there showing you exactly it feels like you're getting valet while you're driving yourself
It's like they're guiding you to exactly where you're supposed to park. It's a perfect use of every space is occupied
It's not like there's a you're gonna drive by a bunch of empty spaces and and you know
It's all being used and then there's the escalators that go this to me is what puts it over the top
There's escalators that go directly from your level to the ground
Yeah
You don't have to go like down a flaw a few flights to some other levels of the parking structure that you'd have no reason
Like if you parked on level four
There's no reason you'd ever have to go to level two
You've gotten there's nothing for you there. You want to go from four to the ground. They have a direct path
And and to me that's very elegant in terms of getting in and out at the end of the day
Damn, yeah, really?
You're run down by the level. We're blown away by that. Yeah about this. Yeah, and I absolutely agree. It's
Yeah, you know, you know, you don't really find and by the way just to totally
In case you don't know this is the major parking structure at the we're talking about a parking garage
But not just any part garage for a time and it may still be this was the biggest parking garage in America
Like this part garage built in 2000 deal with the I will tell you that
No longer it is no longer to look at these notes
It is okay
The largest parking garage in the United States now is at the SeaTac airport in Seattle and no
Wow spaces out ranking the Mickey and Friends parking structure. I want to say that full name every time. Yeah
Like Guardians of the Galaxy mission breakout
Mickey and Friends parking structure has 10,000 spaces the biggest in the world is the West Edmonton Mall in Canada
20,000 Wow
double imagine a structure double the that's crazy
Yes, it requires such imagination. Not even the Imagineers could dream it
But everybody at the time it opened though the biggest parking
Yeah, right an interesting jumping off point to just talk about how Disney handles transportation in general
Sure, let let's go Jason and I did we were talking about this Jason and I are not from Southern, California
So we never got to experience the original Disneyland parking lot, which is famously just a parking lot in it's where California Adventure is now
Yeah, it's just a parking lot in front of the theme park and you would park and walk up like what let's ask you guys Scott
California boys, you got to tell us what was it like I
Remember it being and Scott I'm interested in your thoughts
I remember being a gigantic surface lot just like a huge like just basically parking as far as the eye could see I remember
It being similar to what would occur if you angry about that
But what you would what you would encounter at outside like for me just I remember going to angels games and Dodgers games
The same sort of thing just like the giant like ballpark
surface lot and then certainly like the characters
Which is an element they've retained it at you know
I basically I think at every theme park parking structure and then it's certainly a thing in the Mickey and Friends
Parking structure, but there they it's actually color-coded and then tied directly to the escalators. So it's it's like even more clear
It's even harder to mess up
But the but yeah, it's just giant surface lot and then you know
You'd be parked next to dopey or whatever and that would be your guide
You'd have to remember that to find your car at the end of the day
I remember being easy to get like lost like it was just like a little too big and sprawling
I don't know what's your memory then those characters were very small
Like you have to squint probably to be able to tell which dwarf it was or whatever
Is that pongo or is that?
So did they have like I have so many questions about what it was like
So was it like because in the new Mickey and Friends parking structure, they have they'll have like a whole level
That's Daisy. Yes, and they'll have like a number and letter that corresponds with so be like Daisy 2d
And that's like a section of the parking lot. Yeah, and you'll remember there
Did they have these numbers and letters to correspond or was it just like that joke on the Simpsons where we're in the itchy lot?
Yeah, just the character and you have to remember like that's could be like one of a thousand spaces
Yeah, I don't remember specifically enough, but I don't think it was as
Crystal clear as it is with the Mickey and Friends parking structure
I remember it just being the character and then you just you know
You'd be there be goofy and then you just kind of know you were generally in the periphery of goofy
You're kind of in his territory. But like that. Yeah the Mickey and Friends
Structure so they even go to the level where on the receipt
They have the they have like a guide printed on it
Yeah, you like and if you have a you have a writing implement in your car
You can circle. Yeah, you can circle the G and you can circle the 7 and so, you know exactly where you are on whichever
Characters level you're at it's pretty great. I fun little game of bingo. Yeah
I had never realized because I like those escalators and I always use the escalators
Elevator buttons in the garage elevator have the characters on yeah
So if you just remember if you don't remember what level you number you're on, I just go like, oh right. We're at goofy
Yeah, let me shut it out real quick to six mini five Donald for goofy three Mickey to Daisy one
I think nothing one is just no one is Chippendale. Oh
God I took the time to make a list and I screwed up the list according to the elevator buttons
Is this Daisy's highest profile like attraction in the park?
I does she get any any anything bigger than this house in Toontown?
Yeah, it's sort of a facade though you can't go into it
I don't think it's like Minnie's house where there's a little like area actually to go in
It's just sort of a painted flat. Maybe right as Daisy's house. Does she just live it's or is it like a floor in Donald's boat?
Like under the she's on the starboard. Yeah
I'm not even sure if Daisy is fleshed out and like the classic Carl
Banks or Carl Banks Carl Barks. What was the name the cartoonist?
There's a series of Donald and uncle Scrooge comics that are like worldwide beloved and it's like
If Daisy
Poorly flesh. Yeah
Much more so and looking real bad these days next to Minnie who this week received a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame
Congrats many. Congratulations to many Katy Perry was there in Minnie s. Cogarb
Saluting her and welcoming her. I guess a million dollars by the Disney Corporation
Where Minnie's dress and show up with Bob Iger? That's a little fun for dad though, right? Oh, yeah
There's two the two sexiest women he knows
Minnie and Katy Perry. I just saw her live
Two three days ago. Yeah, I went to Vegas to see her specifically and
Instead of the instead of anything instead of talking about something sexy that happened
I'm gonna say how she played basketball against a dad in the audience like a giant arcade style
Basketball game with a big inflatable ball and the dad one must have been a thrill for the
And if we really gave me the taste to I went straight into the New York New York casino
Past all of the casino games straight to the arcade
I had to play some hoops myself
It was great though
I don't know if this Katy Perry tour is still going or if she's done her LA dates or what Katy Perry a lot of fun
Yeah, and we enter not in the mini dress
It was Karl Barks I looked at us, okay, don't get mad at me what about yeah, yeah, you're correct that
Daisy's pretty that's a pretty big representation. Yeah, I'm pretty underrepresented
Utilized it should be like stitch instead of Daisy
But I think they I think they're I have to think just because the the psychology of this is
So thoroughly thought out that I think they they must be a reason why they I think they want to justify the color pink
I think they're like, oh we want this to be the pink
I'll make this the Daisy level right the color coding is very very clear
It might even be to the degree where it accommodates the colorblind like it might just fall into that red green spectrum
Sure, I don't know so like yeah, maybe not
Isn't there a thing in the 80 like there's a very specific set of rules of like the central six or the means that like
Characters you mean yeah that like Mickey Minnie Pluto goofy
Donald Daisy like there there are very there were and I think it loosened up and now I'm sure it's but then Chippendale
Are on this too. So yeah, that's true. They got enough floors become primary because yeah as of the 40s and 50s
They were just like pests bothering Donald right suddenly there among the primary
Best of friends with the whole game. I would think Pooh Bear would you would go with over the Chippendale, right?
Yeah, he's much more prominent in the part somewhere. There's no is there a poop
There's no put this Toy Story lot ease or there was
And there's a Pinocchio. Now why is Pinocchio one of the primary ones? Yeah. Hmm. I don't work a variation
Oh, there you go. There probably is something to all that
I'm sure if you looked into it. Yeah, yeah, I think in the old in the original lot they were I think they chose characters
They tried to have all 26 letters of the alphabet
But there are I think are no characters of X Y & Z. Although I thought of Zorro right away, but other than that
It's I think I think they tried to represent a through through W and they were sort of organized alphabetically
Oh, so there's some info for you salivate over that old school
Parking lot information one of my favorite anecdotes about the original parking lot at Disneyland is is and I forget who the two
of this is credited to but like
when
California Adventure first open and they were doing like cast member previews and
Imagineering previews and stuff for family like two longtime Imagineers were like walking out afterwards and the one goes
So what did you think and the other goes? Well, I liked it better when it was a parking lot
Which is such a devastating
Going on like a brand new park, right? Yeah. Yeah
Well, so that that's the whole history of it is that up until the mid 90s
You could park in the spring lot that was right next to Disneyland
You're essentially at the ticket booths and at the train station
Right away and you could see that from your car
That area that was taken out to build California Adventure so that there was like a just a short walk between the two
Right. Yeah, there was Disney has bought up odd areas of land all over that Anaheim campus
But it makes more it made the most sense to have the two parks next to each other and even now it's a question if
They ever did a third where would that go when how would you connect with every monorail?
Would there be yeah, everyone says it's the Toy Story parking lot, which is a little little ways away
It's the one that's zone yield for a park for a new park. Oh, wow. Yeah, that's like a little bus ride
It's right by the Anaheim Convention Center
this is a
Question that they're running into at the Universal Orlando
Resort because that resort was designed very much like Disneyland where it's like the original Universal Studios Park
had a second park built like right next to it like essentially like a block and a half walk and
now that and they
Gradually built hotels and a city walk there and now they keep adding hotels and they have a huge plot of land down the road
But like at the time when they're like we're gonna buy this Florida property and try to compete with Walt Disney World
They're like they didn't want to build and sustain a massive
Transportation infrastructure like Disney World did so they made a design closer
Actually to Disneyland where it's like the two parks are next to each other and people can walk there
Or they have a handful of boats and you could take a boat from the hotel
To the two parks, but now that they want to expand and build a third park
It's like farther away, so they're gonna have to start having I don't know buses
Is there a creative way to do it like it's pretty cool that Universal now has the the the Harry Potter
Harry Potter in Islands of Adventure and Diagon Alley in
Universal and the train can take you to both right?
There's some ride that maybe somewhere in the Marvel Universe
potentially there's a rainbow bridge you could walk on or there's a you know,
What else Tony Stark has some new?
Tony Sager Reed Richards is
Hop on to onto the shield supercarrier that takes you over
The carrier yeah, yeah, it's just like not clothes just the Hulk's bridge
It's very green
I will say that speaking of
The two points that I thought of while you're talking Jason and one about Universal
So I want to I had fairly close a couple years ago
fairly proximal Disneyland trip followed by a
Universal Studios a Hollywood trip and
the difference between the Mickey and Friends parking structure the elegance of that and the
Jurassic parking that they have there
It's like it's night and day even though it's but it functionally as a little parking structure
The Jurassic parking has all the pitfalls that exist in you know
Like like a poorly designed like mall parking structure or ballpark parking structure where you've got all these these these different levels
You got a cycle through endlessly you got a hunt for a space a little bit
Where you park like the iconography is not super clear in terms of which which air you know, like
Like was I in J6 was I in L1 like one, you know, you can't quite
Parse it perfectly and even if you write it down or take a picture of the pillar you parked by
It's still a little bit of an ordeal to find your space and then walking through it
You got to walk through a lot of other cars like that that if you've got a family if you're pushing a stroller like that's
A little bit of a hazard. You've got other people looking for parking and maybe making abrupt turns
Trying to snag a space and you got it. You got a family in tow. You don't necessarily have those same sort of
Black marks that you're dealing with if you're in the Mickey and Friends and also too
So, you know Universal is different because you're walking right into the park
It's like it's like right butted up against Universal City Walk, basically
So you're basically just in the same way that you would walk into downtown Disney and then be in the Disneyland proper
Like you're right that you're right butted up against it. There's a there's a tram ride for the Mickey and Friends structure
But it's a nice tram ride. It's very pleasant
And it's kind of like a gentle sort of I feel like when the kids that are on there
They're building anticipation a little bit. They're like getting excited because they're like, oh my god
This is like the ride that's taking us to Disneyland. This is akin to the the helicopter that's taking us into Jurassic Park
a little small thrill that's that's that that tells of
Bigger thrills to be had in the future. Sure. You get a look you get a ride right away, right?
Yeah, that is a thing to talk about I think that I think that tram is very pleasant
I like the look of that thing they get it
That's a that's a that's a neat shiny classic car vibe the white with the red stripes and yes
That's very appealing. I'm gonna I don't want to I don't want this to turn into a fight. Oh boy
But I'm gonna say I like the Universal parking garage
You're right about everything but what's interesting about Universal parking garage is like you don't know where you're parking on on occasion
You just walk out and you're right where you wanted to be and on occasion
It's a 10 or 15 minute walk, right?
So like on occasion I park and I go where are we and I go down an escalator and I'm like
Oh, we're right here at the margaritaville at City Walkers
I'm like we're right here on sometimes so like there's sort of a fun chaos that I find
It's like sometimes you have to get an elevator that's themed a curious George there
That's the whole level or that's the whole parking structure, but then you get to kind of walk have a nice city walk walk
Which I honestly and this is the controversy this is where the controversy will come in
I kind of like walking through City Walk better than I like riding on that tram to Disneyland
which maybe this I should save this for later when we were gonna say controversial things, but
The tram I find I don't think is it's the the though
What happens what happens you leave the tram from the parking structure and it's like what five minutes to get to?
Downtown Disney basically right in front of their world of Disney, which is a giant store
I don't think it's themed well enough. I don't I can see through the fence
I can see the buildings the show buildings for Pirates of the Caribbean or Indiana Jones fair
I can see right through it and honestly it starts to trip off by going
Oh, yeah, Pirates of the Caribbean is in that big on like
People are having
For me Jason I'm saying for me
All right, I agree that dad on the trip of the California isn't going all that show buildings really ruining the magic
But you get magic built up when you walk past the sock market a little bit a little bit that giant
Gaudy King Kong sign that all feels like I'm already in this nonsense
Cosmetics yeah when I was first out here in LA and I had an internship on the Universal backlot and I
Go up and eat it city where they were there was like dollar taco night at a what is that?
She rubio there used to be a row. Yeah, it's fish tacos that a dollar fish tacos on Tuesday nights
Tuesday night CityWalk in the fall looks like the world ended and someone left the lights on
like to just eat a giant plate of fish tacos and like
Watch weird watch music videos on the giant CityWalk screen and every now and then there would be an interstitial ad for just like
And it's just a logo and so I whispering CityWalk it's just like yeah
This feels real like end of the world this feels a real apocalyptic people hate on CityWalk
We're going to do at least one episode on CityWalk eventually
Oh, yeah, not a couple parts because there's so many different places there. I do love CityWalk
so that's that's sort of I'm biased to get toward it and especially because the
Hollywood CityWalk and the Orlando CityWalk may as well be different planets
Really differently because the one is catering to like locals going out for the night and the other is catering to like people in town for
Vacation so one got tricked. Yeah
If you're a local who goes to CityWalk a lot you're a weirdo like us
Yeah, but one definitely feels more like a mall and the other feels more like
People who are hammered right?
I would say and and I like CityWalk and I also like downtown Disney, which I think is maybe not as
It doesn't feel even though it is it doesn't feel as crassly commercial as as as Universal CityWalk
It doesn't feel like there's as much like stores just selling like like dog shit like just trying to like, you know
Just selling whatever there's like a sock stores
Is that still there? Yes, I believe
There's like a popcorn store, there's just so many so many stores
Right just right garbage just chintzy garbage and and and I feel like at the at
Downtown Disney's there's not that same effect here
Here's what I would say it just to just return to what you're talking about with the tram earlier Carlson
I think you make a very valid point in terms of entering the park. However, the thing I would say is
It's very nice at the end of the day
And and it's sort of like especially I feel like if your parents and you got some kids who are maybe wound up all day
And now they're crashing it just gives you a moment to decompress that tram ride
It's like that tram ride back is like, okay
This is the day is over the day is done
and I feel like if you're if you're you're tugging your kids through
Universal CityWalk trying to make your way to trying to figure out what level you parked at at Jurassic Parking and you know
You still got that chaos basically until you got them in the car and you're like shut up, you know
And it's like that that's the energy that's carrying you out at the end of this day versus like like oh, this is our
This is like the end of Lord of the Rings where Frodo is getting on
To the little boat and he's going to like sail off into the distance
Like that's the equivalent of the the tram ride towards the the Mickey and Friends parking structure
Except like Frodo's competing for space with like 700 other
Yes, that was gonna be I agree with you that ride can be very pleasant
But a ride itself, right the right itself
But the lead-up is kind of a nightmare because there's a million people there to queue up a little bit and I mean as most people
I don't have kids
We don't have kids. None of us have kids
They're not even coming soon like
These are four men whose bloodlines are going to end
Not as fun as a theme park
But oftentimes we'll just walk from Disneyland to the Mickey and Friends parking structure
I didn't know you can do that
Like I've done this at least ten times because sometimes even though you're dog you're dead tired
You go well 15 minutes or I stand in front of I don't even know maybe it's 15 minutes for this tram
Let's just walk so you walk through downtown Disney you walk all the way and then you see this glorious parking structure in the distance
And you're going on these days. I almost find that that's even maybe a more
Visually interesting walk sometimes than it is to go on the tram
But you have to pop the Disney bubble to do it
You have to essentially go into Anaheim streets a little bit
But there's also Disney streets to like it's all
Kind of only Disney owns the streets. I think because they're the Disney
I don't think the Disney like street signs
Yeah, I guess so
But it is like you're crossing streets and I wonder now cuz they they have moved security to like right next to the Mickey and Friends
Parking which is better. Yes, they move the metal detectors like right at the bottom
And where you yeah where you look yeah, right? Yeah
Yeah, and I used to be by like the world of Disney
it used to be by like the ticket booths and everything which was was very jarring would lead to traffic jams and
Honestly, I think it's better having it at there or on the other side of the property right the Esplanade like just yeah
Knock it out if it's unpleasant and it sucks, but it's part of the world we live in now
So like yeah, just bang it out and just get through it. Yes
I also don't I'm now I'm being real negative and this is not I did not go into this
No, it's a thing. I'm gonna like take you to task or anything. It just these are my feelings
I will say so now Bill Maher
New rule
Mickey and Friends blows
I
Do here I'll say some good nice things about Mickey and Friends
There is a an exit on the five which is the freeway you're on you generally take to go to Disneyland
It's the specific Disneyland exit. So you go in the left lane, especially you have to think you have to be a carpool to be in
it
And you go off on a kind of a left exit on the freeway and you go sort of on this
Like specifically made for Disneyland bridge kind of thing and then they redirect you like it's an express lane
To get to Mickey and Friends. Yeah, and I love it and that feels like a ride to me that feels like my first ride
Zooming over the side streets
Yeah at the end of the day they flip it. Yes, and that goes the other way
So you leave your Mickey and Friends you again feel like you're going on one last ride
And then you go right under the five and you're back to the real world one of the last times I went
I was I was riding out of there with my with my roof down and the fireworks are going off
Car yeah
That's that's your Frodo sometimes you can catch the fireworks from the tram, too
I mean
I like the trans just cuz I like the modes of transit at Disney Mike always makes fun because like
Anytime we've been at the park together. We're trying to figure out what to ride or stuff as long waits
I'm always the first to go like well
Maybe we should amble on over to the Mark Twain River Boats
Just ride the train for the rest of our lives, but you
Not only does he do you like the train you like the Casey jr. Train, which I do like Casey jr. Train
I've written all I think I have only written that ride with you
Yes, I made you ride the Casey jr. Train and once or twice we were in like the cage
Car like it's a very tall man and I'm crouched into this thing
Sitting on the caboose part just happy as a clam
Employees are like there's plenty of room in there on the other side for kids and a family
Like no no no let the adults have the cage to themselves
They must always be a little concerned when adults without children get on Casey jr. Oh, yeah, no, it's gotta be a flag
No, it's like they've got a flag and it's like going on a little spaceship outside a market or something
It's tiny we shouldn't go on it. No, it's great. The storybook boats are great, too. I do like those
Yeah, I like the speaking of transportation guy. I do remember going on trips to
To Disneyland as I mentioned this earlier when we were doing this for for orchestras kids
And I remember my buddy John Civi had found out I think through a previous family trip that there was a so the arcades in
The starcade I think is the big one, but the arcades that are at Disneyland
This was when Mortal Kombat was was first in arcades and they had turned the blood off
The Disneyland ones but he had found out that there was an arcade in the Disneyland hotel that had Mortal Kombat with the blood
Awesome. So on this school trip, we took the monorail over to the Disneyland Hotel
this is before Disney downtown Disney I think even existed there was just it just went to the hotel and
Not being guests there. We like went into the lobby had a little
Lunch at whatever the monorail cafe was and then we went over and just was good. It was pretty good
Yeah, that's a first place. I had a vanilla Coke
Yeah, right. Yeah
And then we went and we played we played full blood full fatality Mortal Kombat for most of this trip
There's a hack. Yeah
Anytime travelers. Yeah
I
Sorry, oh no, I was gonna say I mean I I did that last time I was there
I not not to there but I love eating at the hotel like it's such an easy pleasant experience
at the hotels usually especially at the quick service like restaurants like in off hours or like lunchtime because people don't
Unless you're staying there like a lot of people don't know like yeah, there's a really nice like one
Whitewater snacks at the Grand Californian is like in the very back
Yeah, it's just so quiet and they pump in the sound effect like it's it's up against California Adventure
So they're pumping in like very pleasant folk music and sound effects and what do they have?
Is that like a hot dog and burger stand? What is it? It's like nachos
Flatbread pizzas. Okay and burgers. Yeah, they rotate it
Say what Tango row a terrace at the Disneyland Hotel also very good
Unusually empty the park lunch spots usually very crowded the hotel lunch spots much less so
Yeah, I love them. Even those downtown Disney spots are often very very crowded
Yeah, that's good to know that the hotel itself has some the the Grand Californian too or just this just the Disneyland Hotel
All all three of the hotels that I've never been inside Paradise beer now
They say that but oh, they all have restaurants of different like levels a little junkier
But they have like they that's where the like the good like character breakfast
Oh, yeah for kids
Yeah
You can find like there's like little slick the steakhouse in the Disneyland Hotel if you go to the bar
Especially later you can get a lot of the menu there. Oh, not usually that crowded Napa Rose
Well, it's probably one of the best restaurants at a
Disneyland period you can get the full menu at the bar
Natalie and I went to Napa Rose and got the the chef's I know this thing
We got the chef's tasting menu ones
Whatever you have like reserve it and you like sit at the counter and then they're they like prepare all the courses for you
And you can like it you can watch them kind of make it and they have wine pairings and everything
And it was a delightful anniversary dinner. Yeah
Also you did a club 33 once I've been to club 33 one time
I I was I so used to write for this TV show called at midnight that was hosted by Chris Hardwick
Chris is a very
Was a very generous boss and as part of his
Like as part of it is gratitude towards the writing staff
He used his leverage as I think it whatever membership he has club 33 to get us all in to club 33 for a meal
And so I had a lunch there and it was have you guys ever been inside? I've never been I did one time
Yeah, shout out to David love. Thanks for getting us in. Yeah, it was it was it was
Picturesque in there is very very like it just an amazing
Exactly what you expect us to be like that felt like this real secret society and and you know a cabinet with this
Ultra-expensive top-shelf liquor that you could buy by the bottle
But the the thing and this this might be more for for us than than for your listeners and unless they they happen to know him
But like this this was like a random day in the summer and we were going to club 33 for lunch and
Randomly I ran into our friend Doug Jones was just there
He was hanging out at club 33 and I just like oh, this is perfectly appropriate
This is this guy. Yeah, I've seen parks so much. Of course. We just be here. Yeah
Yeah, it was it felt like such a random confluence to just run into a guy
I know it at this exclusive club within this theme park. You thought it would only be like Archdukes, right?
Yeah
See you have Pepsi or something
It is like a thing you would expect like like kind of the and maybe this was kind of the lunchtime crowd
but you expect people to be wearing, you know, sharp suits and and
You know cocktail dresses, but then it's just like a dad wearing Birkenstocks and cargo shorts, you know
How was the food? I don't really remember this. I remember being like this is my thing also with Carthe Circus
I really like the food of Carthe Circus. I don't like there's nothing like it's just a very nice restaurant
There's not a lot in terms of like some story about the shoe. Am I wrong? I like it's great obviously very good
Yeah, I would say not mind-blowing not like I had like fried chicken and it's not like oh, this is the best fried chicken
I've ever had but like this is very good. And you know, certainly there's a gigantic markup on it
This cost like $30 or something
It's absurd but it's a year you're paying for the atmosphere and the exclusivity and the fact that you can get alcohol inside
Disneyland and those weird toilets. There's like weird old like
Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I remember that I think they also had mouthwash in the bathroom, which was nice
Oh, that's very fancy
I was just reading a story about one of the first female imagineers and she looked at the plans for Club 33 and she had to
Tell Walt she goes this bathroom for the women is too small
And he said you're right and they doubled it
Yeah, they got a like literally like a one woman could not fit in. Yes. I think so. Yeah
I think she was also saying female beauty was so
Yes, I think that's what she was she would know literally she I think she she said something in an un-pc way about women of size
Would not be able to get in the bathroom
So they they doubled this so they took apart away of the kitchen and then right Walt is like 85 pounds
Whatever weight he made Lillian stay at
That's the weight women should be isn't there a story about a woman who is an astronaut like the
Sally Ride and they were sending her in the space and they were like will a hundred tampons be enough, right?
They just had no sense
That feels like that's like a
A few years from now when they've they've run out of
Saving mr. Bank stories. It feels like they're gonna make a hidden figure style movie about this first female imagineer that has to be in the
Pike, right? Yeah
I mean a lot I was reading I was very interesting because she was talking about how it was like no one listened to her
Like just go to straight 12. She's very she said Walt was very nice
Okay, a lot of the imagineers were just dicks who wouldn't who would ignore things
She said she designed a lot of the Haunted Mansion. Well getting her name. Her last name is Norris
I really should look that up if he won if Walt wants to talk to a woman. He'll draw one
Still love drawing all the time I look up her name
I do think right now though while people are listening to this they're gonna go
When are they gonna go back to the parking garage? Yeah guys stop talking about we didn't want engineers and we didn't want a tangent
Anywhere in this thing. Let's get back on track. So
Well now this is actually the opposite of the parking garage
but I think this parking garage is is especially indicative of
Southern California car culture because like I mean all of the Disney parks have some sort of parking option
Sure, Florida if you're going to the Magic Kingdom you have to park across the lake from it and take the boat or Monorail over
To the Magic Kingdom
The other resort of parks in Florida all have parking lots in front of or next to it at the international parks
There's a much bigger emphasis on like public transit. Yeah, I do I do wish there was because I'm someone who I
Love, you know, like when I'll go I'm an NBA fan and we'll go
Go see the Lakers play in downtown and Staples Center for more we live in Santa Monica
I'll take the train and and it's it's great. It's great to not have to worry about parking
I would love it. This was this was a few years ago
I think when Obama's infrastructure plan was being floated and they used it as like a talking point to be like like
You know, he wants to build a high-speed rail between
LA and Disneyland and it's like it's like well that would that makes it that would be amazing
Because it's a huge tourist destination people fly into LA they would 100% make use of and locals would 100% make use of like
That makes a lot of sense. But as a talking point, it's something that you can
Bat down but yeah, I wish there was a better. I wish there was a train option
I wish you could take you you didn't have to drive there
but because you have to drive I think the the bikini friends parking structure is is
You know as as good as it can be basically. Yeah in Disney Paris. I was reading in
Disneyland Paris there is a major like regional hub like a two-minute walk from the park for the train
Tokyo Disney a train station. Yeah, and it's and it's like not the weird thing not too Disney-ified
It's like just barely off the property just like a couple steps away. And so there's just like
Train station weirdos. It's like it's wow
Not a magical Disney train station and that being like I think it's like 20 minutes outside of Paris and that you're like in the
Magic of Paris and then you're just in some weird European suburban dirty train station
Yeah, really that I mean I we haven't talked about Disneyland Paris a ton on here
But I like I found it sort of odd and janky and sketchy and that train station arrival was part of it because you're thinking
Disney and train. Oh, it's gonna be a med
It's gonna be like an old Victorian train station
Then it's just like lockers and people sleeping on the ground and it sucked
What you would like sounds like what the Tokyo experience is where like they have a monorail there that goes around the whole property
But you have to buy a pass for it
And it's like I believe technically part of the transit system in Tokyo so you can buy a monthly pass or use like a subway
Ticket to ride the monorail even though it's on private property and operated by the Oriental Land Company who runs Tokyo Disney
Hmm. That's awesome. But it takes you right it like what you need to get around Tokyo already what takes you
I think you can use that pass or at least buy like a monthly Disney pass if you work there and it's got stops at
all the hotels and like the partner hotels and then there's like the
Entrance to the property right by the way Oriental Land Company sounds like ominous. That sounds like a
relic of a
colonialism like it was established by the Netherlands in like the
1500s and had its own Navy it does but I believe it was established by the Japanese government
Co-run the Disney Park
Autonomy in the way, and they put a Tokyo Disneyland
Yeah, they dumped a ton of money is which is why I suppose like to I which we have not been yet
Tokyo Disney Sea which is like this was like the greatest theme park in the world
I thought I've heard this so much money from that Oriental Land Company. Yeah Wow
Hearing it in English in America. It is a weird. It's got a weird
Right
Like my grandparents say that word where it's like, oh, I know you don't mean this maliciously
But we don't really say that anymore. Sure, but it sounds like the third Reich development
Yeah, something
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna tie a couple things together here you mentioned Tokyo Disney Sea
if you I'm gonna talk a little bit about the sort of the history and why the
Friends parking structure exists
Do you guys know sort of the anything about like the weird bidding wars between Long Beach and Anaheim that took place? Oh, no
No, I don't think I do. So okay. So
All right, and interrupt me with the jokes or something
Podcast with interruptions. I've never heard of such a thing. I demand it
Okay, so mid 1980s Michael Eisner takes over the Disney Company
He wants Disneyland to be more like Disney World where there's multiple parks and multiple hotels
But he immediately gets acquainted with there is not a lot of land in
Anaheim and they don't own any hotels at that point like but in the mid 80s Disney did not own the Disneyland Hotel
It was built by a friend of Walt's named Jack rather and Walt was just so desperate to get a hotel
Opened there that he said like whatever you want
Well cut you a great deal and Walt's leased the land to the guy for 99 years
It's yours for an and you can use the name Disneyland and no other hotels in this area can use the word Disney
So this guy Jack rather has this cake deal
They've made the monorail go right up to that hotel
But Disney was not pocketing any of that hotel room money
So major like lack of income for Disney for many many years Eisner's like done break it get him out of here
They did basically a hostile takeover of the rather corporation. They just bought up the entire thing Wow similar to the way that they just bought
Fox where it's like
Well, if you won't give us X-Men then we'll like we'll just buy the whole thing. So they they took over
rather
So now they only Disneyland Hotel, but in the rather corporation also owns the Queen Mary
so
That gives them ownership of this big like plot of land on the Long Beach Harbor and now
They've got this bargaining chip. They say to the city of Anaheim
We would love to build a second park here
But we really need is a parking structure and we want you to build it and Anaheim's like that's bullshit
Oh, that's really stupid. Well, if you don't want to do it, we could always just go over to Long Beach
We already own the Queen Mary, right? They've developed plans at this point for something called Port Disney. It's very similar to Disney Sea
Yeah, like Disney Sea I remember this this is a thing growing up in the Long Beach area
I remember reading about the ongoing
Port Disney
You know it would end up being a debacle and never happening in the the local paper the press telegram
There's a lot of updates about the about this ongoing thing
And I remember there there was a point where it was like it looked like we're gonna get a new Disney Park like right
Like, you know, very very close by yeah, how close would that have been for you?
That's true
I mean it would have been like a 15-minute drive for us for my child at home
Right there right by my high school. I mean it could have gone anytime I wanted. Wow. Yeah
Yeah, and like right. Yeah, if you've been if you've been to Long Beach, yeah, I would have connected all of this stuff together
There's a big mall there called the Pike and there's all these hotels and stuff and like it all would have been this massive
Disney campus and they were also gonna build like over the harbor
They were gonna reclaim land and build it on the ocean Wow the Sierra Club
protested it and had a big like
Yeah, really tried to get it to not happen and somebody a guy from the Sierra Club issued a really lofty statement about like the hubris
of man to build above the sea
That's funny cuz the joke I make is is when
Eisner
opens
the Grand Californian and California Adventure as he did it with the hubris of a bad God like
Californians come to this park themed to California
Made a miniature cow. There's no need to do the rest of California
so anyway, like they and
They've got options now in Anaheim and Long Beach and Eisner issues this this odd
Statement about like well, it's just we'll go with whatever city wants us more and that caused Anaheim to cave and they said yeah
All right
We'll build you at the time the idea was three different parking structures the the city of Anaheim would build them
Give Disney like just this tiny lease and that is what happens. So the Mickey and Friends was built by the city of Anaheim
The city of Anaheim gets no money for that. I think they get it. They get it like a dollar a year, right?
It's like some token amount. Oh, yeah, yeah something like it's like bear like legal minimum, right?
Yes, he has had Anaheim by the balls
Forever and there recently has been a big yeah about like a non Disney what mayor was installed sort of an anti
Within the Anaheim City Council, there are people who are there councilmen who were kind of bought by Disney and right who are not
It's a very like Congress NRA
situation like Disney hasn't had there hasn't been any tax on tickets for years and years and years and then some people finally were
Like that's fucked up. Right like when you see there are parts of Anaheim that are in terrible shape
This is like blocks away from Anaheim. They're like, yeah
Really like really lower in terry is in the city could use that money and what they were talking about was like a single dollar of
Entertainment tax right on every Disneyland ticket and Disney freaked out this cannot happen
and also
So there was an LA Times article kind of revealing a lot of this information and sort of the the odd
relationship between Anaheim and and Disneyland and
Disney was so displeased with this article that they told the LA Times fine. You can't review our movies anymore
I remember this yeah happened a few months ago. That was all
Essentially related to like the parking situation
Right. Yeah, and also and this now we're really getting into the driest of dry territory
There was another parking garage. They wanted to build. Yeah, the Eastern Gateway project
Yes, which is a whole thing and they had a whole design for it
And there was a bridge that was gonna take you over like, you know, those right like Captain Cook's is like a restaurant
There's like a desert Denny's right there. Yeah
Harbor Boulevard, it was gonna be a bridge that was gonna take you from the
New parking garage right into Disney and
They were like, well, you can't do this because this is gonna block off all the businesses
Yeah, those businesses would have been I mean, yeah, but those businesses are kind of leeches like let's be oh, yeah
Yeah, I mean why they're there to begin. Yeah, the Mimis cafe right there is just leeching off of Disney's, you know
I mean, I mean to see me me's go. Yeah, I like the rest of it. Yeah. Yeah, that's a good
Captain kid's buffet though what you mentioned that what that place is like dog shit
Reviewed is the worst restaurant in Orange County and they're leeching off the logo of red Robin. It's
Yeah
Yeah, they were gonna build essentially a second Mickey and Friends parking structure
and so people coming from the north would park at Mickey and Friends people coming from the south would park at this other one and
He could not get through Anaheim City Council. They would not get it through
so now part of the situation being as
To in the in the mid-90s when they could say we're gonna bail and go to Long Beach instead they can't do that now
They can't exactly say we're gonna go right right Star Wars land somewhere else, right?
So Disney sort of doesn't have the bargaining chip like they had in the night at this point people listening to the podcaster like talk
about the restaurants again
Jesus Christ talk about that lady whose name you
Tanya Tanya Norris
I know I know
Needed more parking spots for years. Yes, they certainly need them before Star Wars
Oh, yeah, and we got a disaster brewing. I would love to break this story to Nick if he doesn't know
They are building a new
Parking structure Wow right by Mickey and Friends about the same size. Am I correct?
I there's essentially duplicating or duplicating Mickey and Friends
6000 is about six thousand. Okay. Yeah. Okay, so it's a little
Now and maybe one day they'll get that Eastern Gateway parking garage. So that's a little present for you
That there'll be another
Well-designed parking structure coming soon efficient. Yeah, so they're building the parking structure because Star Wars land is coming, right?
And what's also gonna happen is they're building a giant hotel over downtown Disney. So you're losing ESPN zone
You're losing rainforest cafe and the movie theater and the Earl of Sandwich
And this is all just this massive
Construction project that they're like fast-tracking. Yeah, there's a lot of acreage though those oh, yeah
Yeah for rest or those three restaurants in that movie theater
They'll be retail and restaurant space underneath the hotel
Okay, as people are coming in and I'm sure like Earl of Sandwich will be back in there
There could be a small weird ESPN zone in the hotel. We don't know they're talking about stuff like that
It's possible like with especially like with a beloved restaurant like the rainforest cafe. Yeah, let's
We've talked about this for either Sheridan's love the rainforest
It's certainly pretty fine. Like I went with a friend a friend's 21st birthday. We went to that rainforest cafe
This was back in college. So that was that was a real hoot right spent a 21st birthday there
yeah, what she wanted to go to she wanted this was this was my friend's girlfriend and
she was also my friend and and a group of
Friends and wanted to go to Disneyland for 21st birthday and then for dinner went to the rainforest cafe
It worked out nicely. Oh, yeah, I got in high school. I got way too high in there
Oh boy, and I just sat silently freaked out by animatronic monkeys
Didn't say a word to my dinner guest and friend and that kind of informs my my marijuana experience to this day
I think that was the last time I went to a rainforest cafe
I'm thinking thinking back and I this was that that 21st birthday and I
Remembered that the I got a Caesar salad because I just like eating garbage all day at Disneyland my stomach hurt
So I got something very and it was like a very weak like not good salad. Yeah, their foods not great, right?
No, it's terrible. No, they like fun fruity fun fruity drinks and like fun appetizers
That's my yeah, it's like eating the blue bayou. It's like yeah, it's the experience
I drove down alone a couple years ago to see Dick Van Dyke in a parade
And
That's a true story no one would go with me
It was his bird 90th birthday and I was like, well, what am I gonna get the fucking chance to see this old man again?
And he was in a parade like waving. It was like two seconds
And then I parked it downtown Disney and to get validation. Yeah, I was like well
I'll get it to go order at the rainforest cafe and I went up to the bar
I ordered like a cheeseburger and then got it parking validated because I wasn't gonna be I wasn't gonna be a bad boy
And get the part like lie and say oh, I just came from the restaurant validate
I've been a bad boy a few times you have well in the past. They're a lot more strict nowadays
Although I didn't out I've been a bad I've been a bad boy in regards to using the movie theater to park for free
Oh, right cheat. I said earlier where you buy a ticket you get it validated then you cancel the ticket on fandango
This this is no what would dick van dyke say if you heard of this nefarious behavior?
This is the way this is the way that isn't the way Burt would behave. It's the way that mean old banker
He also that's true. Oh boy. That's a good point. He liked bird not like the banker
Well, look, I the movie theater is going away. So I won't have the opportunity to be this bad look
They're pressed for parking. Okay. Yeah, this keeps coming up. So I had the cheeseburger long story short
I had the cheeseburger and it was just the worst it was so bad
Like how was it could it be this bad? You got to go? Yes
You drove it back to LA and then a layer no, no, no, I ate it while I drove
I'm very good at driving and eating. Yes. I have a whole system down
I can do it on the freeway if I have to
But I think I had eaten most of it by the time I even got to the freeway and it just how did they how is it?
This bad. Yeah, it shouldn't be this bad. How could it be? So yeah
The only reason anyone would ever eat it is to sit next to like a firm that's alive
Yeah, the feeling is the whole point
It's like getting a Chuck E Cheese pizza delivered
Just want the food. All right, we could do it was the to-go box like a big clam or something
Styrofoam box
It was a styrofoam box from islands because they don't do to-go orders and to go to a store to borrow
Some weirdo
I want to say many of your stories could probably end with long story short. I ate the cheeseburger
Yeah in the car I drove or begin with I was driving to a parade by myself
Yeah, I
Just wanted to return to this new this this duplicate Mickey and Friends this Mickey and Friends
Sequel lot real quick, but I'm very excited about this this new structure franchise to expand right?
I
Want to make a prediction?
Which is I don't think they're going to use the blank and friends designation for the name of this new lot, right?
because I think it's going to be too confusing to guests and I think because they have
Some other properties under their umbrella now
They are going to make use of that in their parking
Nomenclature and this will be the Avengers lot
One for level two black widow level and so on Wow, yeah
It's just writes itself seven levels. It's associated with their own Avengers member
I think that's a very good prediction and it's very likely
I think there's also a chance that they go with avatar and it's
It's the banshee it's unobtainium for level three or it's so I think it could be
Each child each of the child avatar children
You know, I have friends who've listened to the podcast regularly and they they took some time to ask me
What is your guys deal with avatar? Do you like it?
Do you not like you failed to convey right right? What is your talk about it?
Yeah, we've talked about it in like seven different episodes. I you know, I just brought it up again
The Chronicles of Jake Sully and the Navi people here's here's what happened
This is this should not be a thing we get into at the end of a podcast
But I will get into it a little bit
What happens with me is I get fascinated by something that I think I don't like and I I obsess on it
I make a lot of jokes
I'm like very dry with it and then after a while I like it it happened with Jimmy Buffett
Yeah, it happened with Duffy the Disney bear sure from Tokyo Disney Sea and it's like I make enough jokes about something and then one day
I wake up and I like it. So I guess I like avatar
Yeah, I guess I like it but it's fun to say the mighty Akron in like a very dry
I think we're referring to the fact that even though
This is the highest grossing movie of all time or one of them and there's these
Mega-budget sequels that have been coming for a decade and there's old theme park about it now
That these things that nobody could just tell you the mighty Akron
You're right, right
It's like yeah really hold on to that fact to even remember it right or that or that the thing is the Hallelujah Mountains
Like quote a line from Avatar it's not there isn't something that comes to the tip of your tongue, right?
No, everyone's seen this movie. It's my feeling about the Star Wars prequels
Which I know you guys have talked about always a ton about the start Star Wars, but it's like the three movies are bad
There's so many bad choices, but I've seen them now so many times. It means so many jokes. I like them
Yeah, I like them. I like them. Yeah, I like but I don't like them in this weird way that a lot of people are like
Well, they're good. They're actually really good. Right? I mean that's crazy, but I do like them
I like Dexter Jekster. I like waddo. I like the podracers. I like I need to know all the names sure team
Toppa Gaileys is a name I know
That most people don't know and I but I like him. I don't know much about him, but I like team Toppa Gaileys
What what is he with it? We keep it quick, but what is he?
Yeah, he's one of the podracers do you know the names of the two-headed the Greg proofs and oh, I'm yeah
Yeah, what's that character's name? I can't think hmm. I don't remember
I did at one point somebody is shouting at the podcast right I tune in and Weiger was on it and nobody knew
The one pull I have is what tambor. Oh, yeah, what?
Senator lot Dodd is one
Of Christa lot
Oh
God George Lucas took to a Democrat Senate senator and a Republican senator
They're lions of the Senate. Yeah, it is a kiss. That's one of the senators
I think he's like the same races new gun rate Wall Street shill Christopher Dodd
Commemorated in a Star Wars film I
Looked this up a second ago while you were talking Carlson about avatar because this this is a thing
That we saw Taruk the first flight. Yes, Cirque du Soleil
Inspired by Avatar, which was pretty entertaining. This is sickening. Yeah, say how much money we spent it was too much
What's like a hundred and fifty dollars?
Money, I don't know what we were thinking. I
Seats just good seats. They weren't mind-blowing. They were good seats
Did you know they bring you up and interact with you and bend you around or something? No, they did. Oh, yeah
Not really. I mean, it's a pretty good show
It was just like it was gibberish like trying to get the story of the Taruk and because there's a narrator explaining everything
That's happening. You watch all that you're still not quite clear on what's going on
Wait explain where this lands in the in the world of Avatar in the kingdom of Avatar. It's the it's it's it takes place on the
Avatar planet and it's just it's just a purely Navi story
Yeah, what is the is to root the Avatar planet? No Taruk is the legendary?
Wyvern they have to fly
Yeah, but like to Rook is then I'm trying to remember because they're the Banshee is in it
But to Rook is like a bigger version
Again who's like a harbinger of of death and and by the end of it spoiler alert the young Navi who has yet yet to prove
himself has
Taken control of the mighty to Rook and he rides him into battle and that's respect of his drive
It's still a spoiler if you like stop paying attention during this
So this is reminding me and Mike you may have been with me because it's happened
Comic-con a few years ago, but we came out of the place we were staying and maybe I was with someone else and
like a van pulled up and parked and
Like a passenger van and a bunch of people got out half in Navi clothes
And oh, yeah people who were gonna be handing out flyers
And they just seemed miserable like they were all like had coffee cups and like half in their costumes half in their street clothes
All right, let's get ready for the day
Yeah, so I found that it's increasingly the name of the
The Greg Brooks character. I have no idea even how to pronounce this food food and bead
They were called but collectively they're called food is in bead and no do
That's the name of the character in the prequel to the announcers
The two guys that are announcing the pod race that's considered cannon yes, yeah, this is from
Cannon tab of wookie pedia not under the legends tab. Okay, these are all
This is like the these references are like the last remaining cars at the end of the night in the Mickey
One of the thing I'll say this about Mickey and friends real quick that I like I and this sort of contradicts what I was
Saying before I do like now that you can sort of see Star Wars land from the parking garage
Because you can see how big it is how expansive it is when it let me be clear once it opens
I don't want to see it. I want it to be covered completely
Right now while it's under construction
I love and I make my girlfriend do it every time I go
Let's go to a higher level so we can get a better view of it and we go up the stairs and I take a look
And I just like breathe it in for you know a couple minutes
And I and I and I annoy her probably by saying I go I think that's the where the queue is gonna be for the
Millennium Falcon ride and I think over there is where the the toy Darien toy shop will be like I've done this with you a
Couple times, but sometimes I'll be with my wife, and I will say well Mike's not here
So we don't have to go look at the Star Wars construction
We could skip the stop this time
But it I admittedly it is very it's been good
That's like the best vantage point to watch yes the growth of that thing which has been incredible over the last year
So that's another good thing I like about Mickey and friends right great views hey great views of all the new landscaping
They did at Frontierland. You know all the plates making they did to blend the two areas
Landscaping placemaking city planning yeah the old Star Wars senators. We're hitting all your favorites
There's what's interesting also?
They do a very good job especially earlier in the day when you're coming into Disneyland about having all those like people on staff
Directing you to spaces and telling you where to go
I have come in later in the day
And that's an interesting thing and a weird thing only annual passholders do where you go
I'm gonna go down at nine o'clock sure I'm gonna hit the park then and it's a little more lawless
And it's a little interesting that way you can kind of go a little different routes
There's you know you can you can sort of try to park closer and no one's telling you where to go
so it's an interesting and it's it's it can be it can be very rewarding or
It can be a big pain in the ass because you go all the way around the parking garage trying to find a close spot
And there's nothing and then you got to go all the way back so it can there can be big rewards
But you also it can be very hard trying to find a spot at the end of that especially when it's later in the night
That's what I like about the at the end
That's that's that's an interesting thing to know about going later in the day if I ever were to do that but
What I do like about it early on is that they're making those decisions for you
What can yes stressful moment hunting for parking in a large?
Cavernous structure ends up being something where you're just being guided directly where to go and all you have to do is follow the leader
I think it's interesting to like sometimes if you're if they're directing you to the roof of the structure
That is a very good thing and sometimes. It's very bad like it seems like they load
Based on like whatever algorithm they had that tells them to load from the bottom up that day or top down that day or skip
a level like
Whatever system they had for crowd projections or like how they should fill it out
I'd like to point out also that they I agree that I think the flow in the place is great
And you rarely end up you don't really end up in a traffic jam at the end of the day which is your aim for?
Disneyland but apparently when it was
developed
Michael Eisner really specifically took credit for the flow of it
He said he like made a point of saying it's this new thing speed parking and I actually personally
Figured out how it would he did sort of?
Shaking credit and apparently for the first couple months it did not work and they had to redraw it
Oh, so whatever I did or did not lay out did not work as well as today
Well when he's on the podcast will get will give me a hard questioning about it an hour about just the parking
contributions
Well, well, what do we think? Yeah, do the regular?
the structure the so we so what we do obviously with
The rides as we say do we want to keep it as is do we want to plus it up or do we want to?
Burn it down for insurance money. So I'm thinking we do the same scale to do our same choices for this
I have thoughts. I'm sure you guys do too. I'll make sure that I do by the time your thoughts. Okay, great
Jason do you want to start or do you want me? Oh sure. No, I'll go ahead. I say I do like this parking structure
I say plus it up. What's are obviously doing they're building another parking structure
Go even further because I put a put a
Monterey Alcafe type restaurant. Oh, what are these parking structure?
I would love like if I want a quick bite to eat at the beginning or end of the day that would be a
Real treat right? I would like that a lot. What type of food? Oh
I would think you would want to go broad
I think you would want like either like some some sweet maybe some simple ice cream selection some sandwiches or burgers and like
Personal pizzas like personal pizzas are always agreeable. That seems excessive
Structure I think that would be great. I
Think I
Cheese or pepperoni sir like something simple. Sure where they don't have to customize it too much
Bring for us cafe burgers without the cafe. Yeah, rainforest mini
I I think maybe you could I you know
I would say maybe like a coffee kiosk or just even just a guy with coffee
Or some waters could probably clean up there. Yeah, yeah, that's a good idea especially in a hot day
I honestly I'm just gonna vote for keep it as is. I think it's very functional. I think it does its job
I think what you're talking about the exit also speaks to in the same way
They have escalators going directly to the levels
They have a direct exit from each level that you could you could go in your car
You don't have to circle around and and let other cars merge in which is pretty efficient. I think it works
Well, I think it's it's a model for what theme park parking structures should be and I'm glad they're replicating it with a second one
So is so yeah, I vote keep it as is. Okay. Wow. That is a good answer. I have
I would say plus it up and this is a silly idea
But if you can give me a little more Disney magic in the actual parking garage
Like for instance say you're walking down and like maybe every 30th parking space
They have like Doc Hudson from cars parked there
Oh, that would be fun. Just something like that
Like a little you don't even have to notice it every time
Maybe there's only one of the Disney's cars parked on a level each time and you got to go find them or something
Which I guess now that I'm thinking about it means you're like
Running around looking for lightning McQueen, right might not be a good idea, but I think it's fun. I think it's good
I think yeah, you do just little things like that
I don't want I will say this when I was a kid
I always kind of wanted the characters to be working at the parks
So once in a while Goofy's in the ticket booth when you drive up you hand him your annual pass
He fumbles around with it. Maybe hands you back a piece of bread or something from the thing the bread
He was eating bread in this scenario
But something like I want a little more if you give me a little more magic at the start and then on that as far as
When you're taking the tram, let's get that fence has got to go that fence has got to be I can't I don't want to see
Through it. I want some I don't want to see the big building. I want to be
Transported to a magical place and I would like a lot of theming to happen on that little journey. So plus it up. Okay, I
think
Having the levels named after the characters is good
But I think that the Disney lexicon is so deep at this point, especially with all of their recent mergers
What if every single parking space?
Has its own character
And you start stretching and it's every it's all 101 Dalmatians, right it's every
999 happy haunts. It's
you know
every
like every every every extra in the Avengers were pointed like you have to like zoom in to
Like somebody getting blown up in some see you like zoom into like a little pixelated head every pod racer including team topa galey
Every student quadrenneros is in there every every padawan every student from Xavier's Institute
Mm-hmm. All right, they're getting the X-men. Yeah, so I think they great specific characters
Who are the only place that they are in Canon is in these spaces Ludwig von Drake's great nephew that kind of yeah
Yeah, it can be a great source of future ideas
characters from shows that were
Greenlit to pilot by ABC and ultimately not picked up
the character Dave Chappelle played on the show
No, it wasn't called friends. He and Jim Brewer were on a really like vaguely titled
It may have been called neighbors or something like that get Jim Brewer the neighbor on one of those parking spaces
So deep and it's a way to honor the vast Disney ABC ESPN ESPN anchors that
Yeah
Is that Chris Berman is that one of them? Yeah, there's a rich eyes in there's a rich eyes in space
This this is fun. You get a deed there
You would be so bizarre if you got the same one twice, right every every every visit difference. There you go
It's very exciting. Yeah, that's a great idea. All right
So yeah, I think there's our there's our take on the Mickey and Friends parking strike
But if you want a sequel start demanding it now and we're happy to do so
Or maybe we wait until
Until the Avengers lot is open. Yeah, I think that's that's we've got our sequel already scheduled for us. Yeah. Yeah much like Marvel itself
We've got it penciled in for
One a year
Hey, well while we're here, let's do a quick thing at the end
There's a segment that we we've only done once before and I don't remember how we did it before but I believe it may have
involved a scary whisper which was
Confession land and what this segment is that's very committed to is it what this segment is is we
confess
deeply held theme park it world secrets things things that we believe that we think may be
Unpopular that we've been afraid to come out of the closet with but here we're in a safe space
And we think you we are with you listeners as well. So we're gonna share some unpopular theme park opinions. Sure
Mike, would you like to go first? Sure. I'll go first
I think this would get me tart and feathered if I said it outside of the place that I'm gonna talk about
Sleeping Beauty cast or she's yeah Sleeping Beauty Castle at Disneyland
Is too small
Wow, and it's sacrilegious. I know to say this because it was the first park. It's an icon of Disneyland
But what they're doing now in Hong Kong Disneyland is they're taking a very similar castle and they're plussing it up
They're making it bigger. They're making it a little more
Impressive. Mm-hmm. Let's do it here. I don't know. Let's do it in Disneyland
I think you know, I don't want it
I don't want you to demolish it make a totally different looking castle, but let's make some towers that are taller
Let's let's do something fun. Like let's we don't have to be a
Frozen in time, you know, we're taking this idea. Let's let's make it a little tall
It doesn't have to be giant doesn't have to be like the Cinderella castle in Florida. I just think let's let's fuck around with it
Yeah, I think that's fair
Do we all I don't know. Yeah, there's another what's everyone's feeling on that's me about that
I think it'd be a bummer to see it like closed for that's true time
And I don't like there's been bad things messing with those castles like when the Disney World one was a birthday cake
Well Jason, I love the birthday
The unpopular opinion hate the birthday cake
I watched a lot of old Disney specials on YouTube and stuff and I'm disappointed when it's a birthday cake one Nick
Do you know that I saw no what is it?
Cinderella castle and Walt Disney World into a big pink birthday cake. What was the occasion the 25th anniversary of Disney World?
Oh, wow. Okay. So this was this was how recent was this?
96 oh, okay. Wow that Disney World is that yeah, we're coming up on the 50th anniversary of Disney World Wow
Oh man, that is gaudy and tacky
Well little Jason little Mike loved it
Melting away like like that cake
Little Jason was a chubby boy. I don't know little Michaels excuse. Oh
So you were imagining eating the I was just see I was just floating towards the castle off the ground
Quick the 25th anniversary is over. We need someone to eat
A typical Jason dream. Can you do it little boy? I I will serve
This is a little bit of a tangent but on the Sleeping Beauty's castle up front a few years ago
I shot this commercial with a guy
With an actor and an older actor and he was telling me that his previous job
like he just worked a job as the major Domo in character at Sleeping Beauty's castle and
And but the for the occasion the event it was was that Lars Ulrich the drummer from Metallica his
he had a set it up where he was going to propose to his
His then is his girlfriend then fiancee
At Sleeping Beauty castle but have it be this big like in character thing and it's just like I would like I would
Specific that it was a Lars Ulrich blew my mind because it was like the least metal thing I could imagine
Yeah, because his girlfriend must have loved Disney
It was been like she was wanting to be a princess or something like that
But just the fact that he was going to these lengths to entertain Wow this the the guy behind, you know
Ride the lightning that that was yeah was ultimately where his life ended up
Like a lineup of characters and this guy was one of them
Yeah
He was he was like the I don't major to I think it's like an attendant like like they had they were like in the carriage
Like they wrote the carriage up after hours or something like that
And he was like he was like like like like you like you know your highness or whatever just sort of doted on them
And then he had a proposal to her at the storybook castle at Disneyland. It's very very bizarre
Oh, I have been thrown because major Domo is a yes. That's what I have to neo and I thought he was playing
That I pointed at Scott like oh my god, what's
Neo yeah, because I was starting to do the math of wait is Lars Ulrich a big captain
Yeah, no I think I think this was I think this is a character and I think this has some sort of royal
It's like a royal title of some sort like a royal attendant. I see. Yeah, we don't know the real time
We just know that's a character
Like the Disneyland thing
Wow, okay, well, I don't know not a big disagreement there. Yeah, I'll make it a cake. That's all right
Yeah, don't turn it. Okay. I'll be honest wouldn't mind if it was a cake
But okay, all right
I'll go okay
Nick I was thinking about you being on the show you host a very popular food podcast and this actually came up in conversation
you know how many bars and and place there are to get a drink at Disneyland a California Adventure and
I like those places and always had good food and drinks and good service
But like we're talking about the tram ride getting you into the park
I think Disney's got a
Totally revamp how they get people in and out of those bars because some of these places
They run like any bar in LA where you just if it's too crowded
You just show up and wait until a seat opens up or like the Cove Bar at California Adventure
Which is currently closed. It's being redone
Just has like a queue
it just has a line like a ride and and like a line people wait in until a table opens up and
That's fine. If I'm going to J's bar in Silver Lake, California or
On Ventura beautiful
Beautiful Studio City, California, but I expect a little more panache from Disneyland like there are like tiny
restaurants that that that will text you when your tables ready and I
Need to make
buzzers this so in the world of these magic bands to get you on the rides way in advance
How is there not a better system especially in a place like sorry where we can say
I'm gonna say this doesn't sound like a confession you're making this just sounds like a good idea
Everyone would agree with I just think I think it's a so it's it's a hole
It's it's a source especially like Trader Sam's like
Controversial opinion to have this is just a good idea you
Trouble coming up with I think they need to
Make the bars a little better in terms of getting you in there, and I'm surprised they haven't done it so far
This isn't good idea land
We like your idea, but I'm coming in soft cuz I
The first time we did this I said sometimes I miss the original California adventure and everyone
All right, but that was not see now that you just walk up to stuff cuz there were no lines, right?
I want a little of that ease no one was queued up to do the tour of the mission tortilla factory
Yeah, I was the king of that place. That's what I would do where I would just go again
Mine's a little more Disney
Classicist and I don't know if I don't know how you guys will feel I I don't like the dole whips
I
Had my first
With you and Lindsay and I know I I didn't dig it and maybe I do it again
Maybe I need to remind myself
But I don't know I found it to be sort of like weird and watery and Shincy and after all the build-up
I just didn't it was not the like grand perfectly crafted magical dessert that I might have imagined
I find it like that the the sort of
Therapy
Watery thing that the McDonald's soft serve comes in it feels like like what like canned peaches
Sit in it's like just the goo
It feels very I don't know it feels very can't fit
I think if you like I think if you crunch the number they charge like like
450 for that thing I think production costs of each dole whip have got to be seven cents no more
Yeah, it's pure profit right you got the float or the regular one just the regular one the regular one, okay?
I think that's right. Uh-huh all right, but you responded sharply to that. Yeah, I mean those are I love the dole whip that for me
That's the light when I go to Disneyland. That's a sweet treat
I've got my eye on and then I got it. I got to try that at some point when I'm over in it
I'm turning off Twitter notifications the day this comes out
Scott's about to get his ass ripped out
Everyone ends up just being mad at Sheridan for proposing having a more sensible view
We like the chaos
Nick you know if you get a dole whip at the Disneyland Hotel you can pay an extra markup in the poor shot of rum on it for you
Whoa, yeah, okay?
I'm into that you could so you can go play bloody mortal combat
and get hammered on rum dole whip
Which which bar is this in the it's like the coffee house. Oh the coffee
It's like yeah, just a quick little window at the Disneyland Hotel
You gotta come down with you got a roll with us down there
You know I 100% could that idea of making that boozy I think that's the only way you can improve that thing
Yeah, yeah, give it give it another shot Scott. I probably should you know what else
I think I think that the like the weight is so crazy and the fact that there is such
Look that is a congested area already in Adventureland like to me when I hit
when I'm heading into Adventureland trying to get an Indiana Jones fast pass or something and it is just
Packed to the brim with strollers
And then you run into that line that is super long and that bathroom is really credit
That's the exact zone where I think oh, maybe we shouldn't have come today
Really crazy sure so I think I'm associating it also with the with the crowd
Yeah, and and maybe just over hype
I think it was presented as you know they have these these these pineapple things, but I don't know it's like
I think Disneyland is like incredible restaurants at this point. I really like Napa Rose really like heart they circle
So if you see a list that's like but the number one is still the soft sir
I just don't I think it's a little over built up right yeah, yeah, it's not transcendent, but it's
As an adult I noticed the artificial taste now right but then after a while you go well the artificial taste is good right
And then it just whatever takes over. You're also you do you love the sugary bullshit. Oh, yeah, I am a
Yes, I have when we were somebody asked just on Twitter what our favorite beer it up caught was and I drank
No beer in Epcot
I just drank colorful drinks that look like those Vegas those slushy Vegas booze drinks
So like it would be like the rising Sun in Japan
And it was just like a red cherry drink that you would get like it's just a slushy with with a little booze in it
So yeah, no I like artificial bullshit. Yep. Yeah
My turn yeah, okay, all right
I got I got I got to I'll give the first one quick because I don't think it's going to be as controversial though
Some people might be upset another food one
Big
Turkey legs take a hike. I don't like no big turkey legs. I think they're gross and I think they're I
Feel like you're gonna get sick when you eat them
And I feel like I don't like what like it feels perverse to see these people just walking around these big hunks of meat
Like these kids with these giant hunks of meat these that are as big as their thighs and then as you bite into it
It's like there's like mid-rare turkey like just a little bit
They're never thoroughly cooked and it's just got to be the cheapest meat like what you're talking about with the markup for the
Dole Whip, I think it's the same sort of thing
I think they're getting those things for like ten cents a pound and and they're selling them for for a huge markup and it's
Pure profit, but I think they're disgusting you see some weird colors in those things. You really do
Pinks and purple right very unsettling. Yeah, it's like it's it's like subway meat, but it's like on a bone. It's really gross
It's really low grade meat Jason's been oddly quiet during
I
Castle cake giant turkey legs
I think we I think people forget they're meant to be shared in terms of the size
Wow, some of that color and though are you sharing it? Right? I don't get it that much. I mean, I think it's
It's not one of my go-tos anymore
But at a certain point it was oh, yeah around 11 or 12. Yeah, I put one of those babies away
I think I think they're I think they're for kids but also but maybe kids should be eating them
I would pay a hundred dollars for a photo of you at 11 with a giant
I can't see
I I've never had one. Yeah, I don't had one
I think a turkey leg can be good if you get like that the leg at a Thanksgiving dinner
That can be you know, you get a well a well-cooked turkey, but I just the theme park for right
I would stay away from but yeah, I was just gonna say I think this is not that controversial here
But I do think like that is a big thing with a lot of people. There's a shirt. There's a new shirt
I just saw that it's like turkey
It says turkey leg and you can get it Disney now
So it's so popular that they listed on the in the thing where you list like the all the Jackson 5
Like Michael and Tito and germaine. Yeah
Yeah, like churro and turkey leg as well
Maybe multiple sure
With like churro and Mickey ice cream bar and yeah
So so it's like a thing as much as we don't care
I do think that like it pulled well enough in like surveys of like would you wear a shirt that?
Probably talked about eating a giant turkey leg and people like yeah, I'm sure there are people who love it
I do remember on a fairly recent visit to Disneyland
I saw like a like a 30 something dude wearing like a nightmare before Christmas hoodie and then a Jack Sparrow like Mickey hat
With like the dreadlocks and then it carrying a big turkey leg and he was having more fun than I'd ever had it
Yeah, like a big shit, right?
But but so that's that's my one opinion
But my other one that I think will be a lot more controversial and I think will may even make me a priya
to listen podcast
Not into fireworks. Oh
I think they're I think they create a
Their necks up to look at it to gawk it at things or maybe if they don't have an ideal
Angle in addition to all people just just staking out various places to sit and stand and watch it
I don't like that
there's like that they've created that as a profit center for the park that like you can buy like a
Good seats to watch like the world of color or you can buy like a little picnic basket to watch it
I I to me it's like that's that's not what's fun about a theme park is is finding some place to sit and look at
I just like I want to like go on attractions and I don't like that
It's positioned as this big thing at the end of the day and I think it just kind of
To me it disrupts the park way too much the fact that this event exists
So just to be clear when you say fireworks world of showcase or world of world color. Jesus Christ
We've been recording for what feels like four hours now talking about the garage
I've supplied you guys with your longest dullest episode
World yeah, so world of color does not have does it have fireworks like you're saying any sort of show outdoors
Oh a firework sort of thing. No, no, I know I'm just saying so you said you didn't like fireworks
I'm just your blanket saying sort of any of the live shows and like fantastic doesn't really have fireworks
But it has like pyro effects
I may I may have been conflating them all under the sort of the sort of nighttime night time spectacular
Yeah, I think the whole nighttime spectacular thing. I'm not really into I understand there for families
I understand there for kids
but I just see so much of the park getting roped off when they're going to happen and I and I just feel like there's
such a disruption and
And I like I'd like to I'm fine with stumbling upon them
Like I'm fine if fireworks are just happening, but I'd like it being a big to do. I'm just not into it
Hmm. I'll say one in and when we did this before was like just shows and parade
Yeah, and I forget if I threw fireworks into there, but I yeah, I definitely agree, but I you know what?
I'm glad they
They had the bad thing is that they create a bottlenecks and bad credit flow
Good thing is it eats up a lot of people and that's a good time to hit rides, right?
You can get on Space Mountain sure if you plan accordingly last time we were there
We were I don't know what I fell asleep at the wheel as far as planning
But we kept running into shows and parades and it was very frustrating
So I get that concern but I will say if the shower parade is right the Disney magic
I mean if we saw the Main Street Electrical Parade when it came back
Tremendous, I mean, it's so great to see that. There's a certain I don't forget what the fireworks show is now
But there is one that there's one that was like during the 60th
Celebrated like all the movies and that one's like fine, but then there's one that like is just about the theme parks
So like sitting with everybody watching fireworks
But then playing like Haunted Mansion and Pirates of the Caribbean and then like having these new projections they have on the castle
I mean, it's a it's a magical time
Come on. Yeah, so good selling. Yeah, it's like an uncle guilting us
Has Mc but then that takes the boats out of Commission for the night and right in the Mark Twain around at night
And that's I think that's a missed opportunity for that giant body water at California Adventure
They never put any boats on that add some real kinetic energy to that part of the park. That's a good idea. Yeah
And you don't like the Mark Twain repurposed when all the characters are on it later too cuz that takes you out of the illusion that
It's just from the turn of the century. I think it's a little disrespectful. I
Think they're having a little too much fun for my taste
We've got streamers down guys. We've talked about it
I think before on this but Jason has a certificate because he drove the Mark Twain. Oh, yeah
I got the captain the Mark Twain one time. That's fun. Yeah his birthday. It was great talking. It was my birthday years ago
Yeah, when you were a child, yeah, you just like you were really you want to talk about a pig and shit
Yeah, I got a side of guest book there's a guest book up there oh man, yeah
Yeah, that's pretty great only way to improve it as if the Mark Twain was made a cake
We need you to drive it and eat it when you're
That is going to 100% your his dream tonight, oh, yeah, he falls asleep
I don't think we're at the point where we have listeners who would do fan art yet
I don't think anybody's that committed. I think the free time you call it right calling the shot now
There's somebody will drive and ask for this. I want artwork of Jason driving the cake mark 20
My first request to the audience if there is one
Maybe a bit ambitious to start with I'll say if you want to put in all of the phantasmic characters
No, no, I'm not having that oh wait, yeah, no wait, that's against her it's here that alright it'll add time anyway
Have you listened to nothing?
Do you understand my whims or not?
Yeah, all right fan art. It's time. I'm calling. I like that
Podcast arc where it doesn't like naturally happen. Oh, right. Somebody did a drawing of me. I'm like, yeah arts now
Here's what it is get to work. I
Think that's right. I think that's good
We haven't been aggressive about anything else in our lives and this time now it's time for that now it's time to demand
Alright well on that note Nick wager you survived podcast the ride. Thank you so much for being here. It was a blast
Yeah, thank you so much. Yeah, three and a half hours
Avatar land weights worth
Anything you'd like to plug or direct people to
If they made it hey, you know check out doughboys the podcast about chain restaurants
We have new episodes every Thursday host it with my friend and previous guest of podcast the ride Mike Mitchell
So give that a listen if you like if you like
Hearing two men talk about food. I had a very funny realization earlier
Which is if people listen to this but have not listened to doughboys yet
They will spend a few minutes at the top of the show going who is this guy Mitch? They're really ragging on
The assumption that we know all his opinions at the same time I guess he was on our show
Yeah, I guess that's true. Yeah, but I also find it
I feel like probably a ton of our audience has to be doughboys fans already and and rightfully so and thanks for
Yeah, thanks. Thanks for doing a little merger here. Of course. My pleasure is a blessed
Hey, you can please
Rate us and then subscribe on iTunes and give us comments and reviews
Podcast the ride on Twitter and Instagram
any anything else for this and
Let's get that fan. Let's get the fan art
I mean if we could have multiple people doing different art from different perspective like everyone can bring their own art style to it
I think that would be great
Maybe split up where somebody does just like the black and white and somebody else fills in the color, right?
There's a way to ease the burden. I think I'll also throw this in cotton candy smoke poofs coming
Yeah of the boat. Oh
Also, can we have on the dock waiting for the boats arrival a Scott Gardner enjoying a dual whip
Thought bubble I was wrong
I'm eating this and my own shit and
Meanwhile there is on in a canoe is Mike Carlson with the thought bubble
Imagining the old cake castle that he missed so much
This is getting very elaborate
It'll be worth it when someone to lose. We're gonna need to pay a commission soon enough
We'll talk payment later. Yeah, I know I don't know we said all the things so yeah, just hey, thanks for listening