Calling all teams. Today, a musical kaleidoscope of sight and sound. Neon light sticks, fast dancing, surplus 1984 Olympics equipment, and bodacious sets from Swedish Eagle and DJ White Rabbit. We're going to the top. It's Videopolis on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a show hosted by three guys who believe people should not be judged by the color of their skin, but by their high score on Buzz Lightyear's astroblasters.
I'm galactic hero Scott Gairdner. I'm joined by space scout Mike Carlson. Greetings. And cosmic commando Jason Sheridan.
Hi, where does that rank on the chart?
I gave myself the highest one, which is really selfish of me.
Oh, you came up with that joke?
None of them are the last. Yeah, that's my reward for thinking of the joke. And none of them are the lowest. The lowest is sort of if you just don't shoot at all.
And you guys, you shot and you did well. Although those names probably don't reflect our actual scores. I'm terrible at astroblasters.
I always get the same thing. It's always in like the 200,000 range or 300,000 range.
Yeah, my brother is amazing at it.
Well, you have to know the secrets.
Yeah, you got to know the colors.
Do we know the secrets, Scott?
I think I just found one that I got 100,000 in one shot and I feel great about it.
I think it's the blue ones, right?
No, Jason.
Or the purple ones?
No, Jason, no. There are unpainted, unlit targets on Buzz Lightyear's astroblasters.
Oh, I don't have time for this.
You have to know where to look.
Okay.
And then you shoot, like when you go in that dark tunnel, there's a secret one against the wall.
So hopefully the car gets, the best case scenario is the car gets stuck right there and you shoot it for like five minutes.
But that thing will give you so many extra points.
Yeah, I'm very good at Men in Black Alien Attack getting the 100,000 bonus by pressing the self-destruct button.
Oh yeah, I've heard of this. Do you know also about the Midway Mania secret?
No.
No, what is that?
There's tons of them. I can't even, I should have said secrets plural.
There's tons of them and we cannot waste our audience's time anymore.
No, we can't. We've got a lot.
But there are tons of them and you have to look for little things and it shoots out and it changes the whole complexion of the characters on the ride. It's crazy.
Yes, look it up.
They're not even in the ride. You have to have an app. You have to start firing on the app before you even get on site.
You stay up all night until you land at DCA.
Alright, but yes, look, there's a lot to get to because we have a great guest today.
There's so much to describe you. You're a raconteur. You're an actor and a writer and a DJ and a drunk history narrator and a video remixer.
But most of all, you're a big theme park nerd like us and we're happy to welcome Doug Jones to the show.
Hi.
Hi, Doug. Welcome.
Thank you for that introduction.
Absolutely.
You guys wrote an introduction for yourselves, so can I write one for myself right now?
It's only fair. I am a 38-year-old who likes to live life to the max.
Several X's in max, I would assume.
Thank you.
Doug, you said that so loud we have to recalibrate or record your booming voice.
I, uh, lashing through.
Should I keep the microphone like...
Far away from me.
Yeah, we're going to put it on a boom pole and then into a C-stand.
I'm so excited to be here. It's going to be really hard for me not to be projecting loudly into the mic for the next five hours.
Which hopefully will be edited down to two.
If we can. If we manage to do it.
In all seriousness, move it back closer. You're making me nervous now.
Might not be picked up at all.
Alright, well, yeah, we're here. There's so much that we could talk about with you, Doug.
But we're here specifically to talk about a topic I've been looking forward to for a while, which is Vidiopolis.
And Vidiopolis, if you don't know, was an 80's teen dance club that was open in the late 80's at Disneyland up near It's a Small World.
And there's a ton of issues that this thing brings up, especially the fact that Disneyland, to Disneyland's dismay,
Vidiopolis really opened up a Pandora's box of rowdy youth culture entering the park for the first time.
And some of these negative elements remain to this day.
And there's a story that people have asked us on Twitter to talk about a little bit.
I forget how much on the show we've talked about the Disneyland gangs.
But there are, well, you wouldn't necessarily call them gangs.
Social clubs, Scott. Please, social clubs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. But there is the thought recently in a lawsuit alleging that some of the social clubs have engaged in more gang-like activity.
There was a story in the LA Times, I'll just read their synopsis of it, that the head of one of these clubs,
oh, but by the way, if you're at Disneyland, keep an eye out for big roving groups of social club members who wear vests with patches all over them.
And sort of a Sons of Anarchy fashion. That's how you describe it, right?
Yeah, many of them look like their favorite songs probably have the phrase,
a-wop-bop, a-loo-bop, a-wop-bam-boo in them. A lot of rockabilly looks.
Greasers.
Like the patches, though, instead of having maybe like a skull or a motorcycle, it'll have Jack Skellington on it or Captain Hook or, you know.
Like Tinkerbell with tattoos or something.
Or Darby O'Gill and the little people. And they got cuts, but they're cuts. They got leather or denim vests.
Motorcycle gang calls them cuts.
Oh, okay. I thought you were saying the word cucks.
Oh, no, no.
The recently relevant term cucks, and I was like, that's a bold statement. I wouldn't mess with these guys and call them that.
Yeah, I wouldn't at all do that.
I think just the hippest, coolest guy on the podcast has just shown us up as far as slang goes once again.
He's thirsty for slang.
Yeah, I love slang and Sons of Anarchy lingo and all that stuff.
So anyway, what is occurring is that, okay, so the head of one, according to the LA Times,
the head of one of these clubs has accused another of using gangster-like tactics to collect protection money for a charity fundraiser at the park.
So there's a lawsuit now, and forgive me, I forget the sides, I forget who's who in this story,
but the lawsuit is between the Main Street Fire Station 55 social club and the White Rabbits social club.
And the flames of this feud have been lit by podcasts like this one apparently, and I don't seek to add fuel to this fire.
In fact, all I want to happen is for all of these social clubs to just get along and make peace.
And that's relevant to us as well, because all three of us, the hosts of the show, are all in Disneyland social clubs. Isn't that right?
Different clubs.
Yeah, we are in different clubs, and yet we put our differences aside to come together to do this podcast.
And that's why we want to just encourage peace between everybody.
If you guys want to talk about your groups.
Well, I'll go first. I'm not the head of the group, but I would say I'm sort of the vice mayor kind of a thing.
We kind of have a whole hierarchy to it, but I can't get into that.
Or I couldn't, I could, but it would take too much time.
But anyway, as a very prominent member of the Disneyland social club, Eeyore's Reason to Live,
I want to say that these social clubs are not about anger or violence.
They're about getting together with some good buddies, wearing some thick denim, some of the thickest denim that you can find,
and growing a big beard as bushy and as black as it possibly can be, and just loving the park, having an adult libation or two,
and just enjoying the time without having kids and enjoying it with your other adult friends.
We can all agree. Sorry, I was getting a little emotional here at the end.
I, of course, you know, I am, yeah, I started my social club. I founded my club.
And I've been a subject of controversy in the community.
Of course, I founded a group called the Uncle Urville's Controversial from the start,
because in lieu of leather or denim vests, we all wore terry cloth bathrobes with the sleeves cut off.
Also controversial was Carousel of Progress has not been an attraction at Disneyland in quite some time.
I was then exiled from the group in a coup orchestrated by Mike Carlson,
much like he tried to snake me on our animatronic of the month poll.
This is before he found it, helped found Ur's Reason to Live.
My current group that I started is known as the Jake Sully's.
Again, controversial, as Avatar is not a Disney property.
It is merely licensed for the World of Avatar section of Animal Kingdom,
land that does not even feature Jake Sully, but I like to think I was future looking, future forecasting, some might say,
because that 20th Century Fox merger goes through.
It's gonna be big for the group.
It's gonna be big, big for the group.
Yeah, well look, you guys have personal beef and yet you've been able to put it aside,
and why can't the White Rabbits, the Main Street Fire Station,
I've, you know, probably the listeners already know if you've explored certain corners of the park,
that I run the gang that hangs out at the very top of Tarzan's treehouse.
We're a Tarzan-themed gang and we call ourselves the Edgar Rice Burrosers.
And, you know, look, I'm not saying we don't resort to some shady stuff to maintain our territory.
You know, yes, we've, you know, people are messing with us.
We have had to threaten to use baseball bats to play Phil Collins drum fills on people's kneecaps.
But, you know, it doesn't mean we're actually, you know, we're just trying to maintain the territory.
It doesn't mean we're actually gonna commit any violent acts.
And overall, we're interested in working in a spirit of harmony, you know,
and we're keeping up the motto of two worlds, one family.
Yeah, and you guys also do public service, too.
You stand at the treehouse and tell people whether they want to know it or not.
That, like, look, over there, that little teacup and teapot look like Chip and Mrs. Potts from Beauty and the Beast.
Like, all day long, you'll tell them that little bit of trivia.
Yeah, we're happy to help.
I think this is, I think we're all headed for, like, a really great, really great breakthrough here as far as, like, talking peace and stuff.
I do want to just remind everyone, stay the fuck out of Critter Country, okay?
Whoa.
Stay the fuck out of Critter Country if you're gonna, you know, bring the whole gang there.
You can come in singles and maybe pairs, but as far as the whole gang, stay the fuck out of Critter Country.
Why, because it's your territory?
Yeah, Eeyore's reason to live, Critter Country. That's where our brother Eeyore is.
The Hundred Acre Way, you're not wanting to lose any acreage in the Hundred Acre Way.
Yeah, we always have a person or two in line to meet Eeyore at all times.
So if any of our brothers or sisters want to get in line to take a photo with Eeyore.
The council has talked to you about this. You can't go around making this proclamation. You know that.
I respect the wishes and territory. I don't want to rile anything up.
I'd encourage you to, let's all try to avoid profanity if we can.
I'm sorry.
Because they are family parks even if none of us have families.
My parents listen to this podcast, so they're...
Is that right?
They don't want to hear words like that.
Oh boy, okay.
Oh boy.
Well, so there's one rule we all need to adhere to in these social clubs, which is keep the profanity light.
I find myself having to censor myself when I'm at Disneyland because of the amount of children that are around.
Do you guys also watch The Lip when you're...
Because I'm one of those people that like, I forget where I am.
You're excited to be there.
I'm excited. Like when you started recording the podcast, I was talking way too loud.
I would do the same thing if I'm in line and I, you know, dropping F bombs and maybe S bombs.
And then I quickly realized, oh, I'm at Disneyland. I've got to...
It's easy to forget.
Yeah, try to keep it clean.
Try to keep it clean.
Yeah.
I never have a problem.
Because you're a good boy.
Because I'm a very good boy. I will say I scold my girlfriend all the time about that.
She's got the pirate mouth.
She'll throw the F word around.
And I'll say, shh, there's like a child behind us.
And also like, you're not in these walls, not between these walls.
We shouldn't be saying those words.
I also, anytime I'm at any park, I assume that there's microphones everywhere.
That I'm being, everything I say is being recorded.
Yeah, there have to be.
That's fair.
So besides the swearing, I don't want to talk anything about my personal life that might get somehow entered into their system.
I know it's a silly thing to...
I mean, I think it's a silly thing to be used as wallah in a film or something.
I mean, you guys talked about that there's like plainclothes security guards everywhere.
Like, I'm saying like, oh, let's go back to the car and get the drugs.
Well, that was a very...
They will follow you to your car.
And make sure that you don'tԽ come back in.
A very funny story a few years ago, that two people were in line for going through security,
and were like talking about the edibles they had on them.
And a plainclothes security was around them.
And the picture published with the story was like, you could see the plainclothes guy talking to the uniform security guy.
Once they had taken the massage.
And they just said like, hey, you can't let you in today.
You're not banned or anything.
But like, take it off property today.
But the plainclothes guy was wearing the goofiest Star Wars dad shirt.
They give him like XL.
And he's like, oh, I'm just a normal tourist.
Cargo shorts.
Tim Burton mad hatter, like frizzy red hair.
Yeah, so it's just him writing up a report on the little, you know, filled out notepad.
A porg backpack.
Which I just saw for the first time at the park yesterday.
And they look ridiculous.
It's like the Yoda I was explaining to the person I was with.
That the Yoda, the Wookiee backpacks are like a shrunken down Wookiee.
So it looks weird.
But the porg backpacks are like oversized, like way bigger than a porg should be.
And that also looks weird.
I don't like either of them.
It should be like a clutch.
It should be a porg clutch for like ladies.
Like a tiny little bag.
And when you open it, it screams.
Like the porg.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Yeah, they're kind of a, they're a little shrill.
I think I was expecting the porgs to be cuter.
And they kind of just scream and make a fuss.
I love them.
I understand why they have them wearing them.
Because that's the last, a person with a porg backpack is the last person I expect to tackle me.
As soon as I exit the park.
Yeah, that's a good, but anybody could have weapons and like fold out batons in their porg backpacks.
You gotta be careful.
As always, we're talking about a place that we love that uses North Korean-esque tactics to spy on people.
And prevent illicit substances from entering.
But you know what, they're running a private business.
Yeah, it's private property.
And they, look, the parks are great.
Doug, you're a huge parks fan.
I think we met for that reason.
Yes, our very first conversation, I believe.
Yeah, yeah, I think there were some tells in some of my videos that let you know that I was a theme park guy.
And then you told me about your excellent videos.
I don't want to get the names wrong, but the Mouseketeers Escape from Splash Mountain.
And the Golden Girls Return to Space Mountain.
I could be mixing up Witches Going Where.
Yes, that's about right.
Okay, something like that.
But you make these wonderful mini movies that are remixed out of Disneyland specials, some of our favorite things.
Which, these things you've done have delighted me over the years.
Oh, thank you.
Highly recommended to our listeners.
Dante Fontana is your name as a remixer and DJ, correct?
Yes, for EverythingisTerrible.com.
Right, right, right. Okay, yeah.
And you've put so much wonderful Disney madness out into the world.
Thanks, and there's so much out there that's not on YouTube.
Like, you guys have no idea.
Like, there's so many reasons why your YouTube channel can get shut down.
Especially if you're a person who likes to upload Disney clips.
So, the reason for the DVDs is to not have to worry about that.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You send people these DVDs in the mail.
And they're sourced from mostly video cassettes that either I taped off television or a soccer mom on the internet that I traded with taped off television.
And, yeah, I amassed over 200 live Disney TV specials from the 70s, 80s, and 90s.
Oh my god.
To make these things.
There are, and there's so many more.
Jeez.
Truly insane. And you're getting VHSs that have commercial breaks and everything. You're getting it as it aired.
Oh yeah.
Oh, all kinds of Kissimmee Saint Cloud commercials, right?
For sure.
Yeah.
For real.
My childhood favorite. The target with arrows being shot at it.
Of like, here's Universal Studios, here's Disney World, and here's Kissimmee Saint Cloud.
Right?
Perfectly illustrated the proximity.
That's exactly why you need to get into the heart of the action down there in Kissimmee.
Yeah, okay. But so you're a big Disney archivist, a big Disney fan.
You also, if we could pimp you out for a specific tale, you're also a fan of something we haven't talked about a lot on the show, but the world of the Chuck E. Cheese animatronics slash the Rock-A-Fire explosion.
The showbiz pizza.
For sure.
Yes.
I think also something we talked about the first time that we spoke, and you've got kind of a history at this point with the Rock-A-Fire explosion.
Yeah, I grew up going to Chuck E. Cheese and I had no idea about the Rock-A-Fire explosion. I don't know if there was a showbiz pizza in Southern California or not.
Maybe not.
Because if you don't know the full story of it, yeah, Chuck E. Cheese, all the Chuck E. Cheese's were kind of, there was a merger of two franchises or it was, what's that creepy term? Like concept solidification?
Yeah, it's something that still goes on today where they just do a cheap redressing. So the Chuck E. Cheese Munch's band was cheaply, quickly, and thoughtlessly redressed. I mean, sorry. The Rock-A-Fire explosion was quickly and cheaply redressed as Munch's band.
The current Chuck E. Cheese band.
Current?
Yeah, well, I guess the current band is becoming no band at all.
I hear that there's only like one left in the United, in Northern California.
Is that right? Have they all been?
Well, they all, the band's been gone for a while. If you ever stepped inside a Chuck E. Cheese, which I don't recommend, it's awful.
We are half a mile from one right now.
We should all go.
There's no doubt that all four of us have gone into Chuck E. Cheese alone without children. Am I correct? Can I assume this?
I don't know that I've been in alone.
I went the day after my senior prom with all my friends and dates and stuff because we were not getting a beach house or something afterwards.
And it was for sure, like all the signs said, must be over 18 or have kids to get in. And we just walked right in. No one gave a shit.
We had money to spend. We were hanging out for a while. We didn't cause mischief. We were all good boys and girls.
Not as weird as a mid thirties gentleman.
I feel like for the last 10 years, it's just, they got rid of the band and it's just been one animatronic Chuck E. Cheese doing a radio show.
Yes.
Every kid's dream is to watch someone do a radio show.
The Eric Bogosian version of Chuck E. Cheese.
Let me get really confusing here. I know that the radio station version of Chuck E. Cheese's is called Studio C.
And we later, probably soon, we'll be talking about something called Studio K.
Yes please.
So let me just delineate. Let's get the studios straight in your head. C is the Chuck E. Cheese version.
But anyway, the original band, which is a lot more loved and fondly remembered, is the Rock-A-Fire Explosion, which was at Showbiz Pizza.
Not in California, mostly, where we both grew up.
But so you've gotten to interact with the actual Rock-A-Fire Explosion.
There's a movie, also I should just point out, there's a movie that talks about there's only a few of these robot shows left.
People have preserved them.
There's three full shows in this country.
Right.
And I was so moved by the documentary. I'd never heard of the Rock-A-Fire Explosion before.
But as a Disney nerd, as a theme park, animatronic, obsessed guy my whole life, it really spoke to me.
And I had to see the show.
It's very country bears-esque. In the look of it, at least.
That's when I saw the documentary the first time it struck me.
I did grow up with the country bear jamboree.
Or somebody at the park yesterday.
Actually, one of the country bear walk-around characters was at California Adventure in front of the Grizzly Bear Rapids.
And I heard a mom... shaking my head.
Excuse me.
I heard a mom tell her daughter,
Oh, look, it's one of the grizzly bears.
And I just sank my head in disgust.
I was like, yes, there is one of the grizzly bears from the attraction, the Grizzly Bear Jamboree.
Excuse me, I have to go in the men's room and throw up.
I'll be back.
It's like someone who needs to listen to this podcast and learn a thing or two.
Yeah. No, I grew up with the country bear jamboree.
And it's so much similar, which I believe is also three stages.
One main stage and then two side stages.
So I had a trip planned to New Orleans.
And I rented a car and basically skipped New Orleans and went on this trip to Mississippi.
To a rural, Sandy Hook, Mississippi, which is in the middle of nowhere.
And found one of the guys who was the subject of Damon Breland.
And he was, I reached out to him via email.
And he was very nice to let me drop by and watch about three hours worth of shows with him.
I offered him money because I don't want to waste this guy's time.
It probably cost, he probably spends a lot of money maintaining this.
And he has the full show.
He has the full show.
You know, some people have pieces of the show that they bought on eBay.
There's only three full shows that are running.
The guy in the documentary who drinks Mountain Dew.
That guy.
Who only drinks Mountain Dew.
Yeah, who has it in a shack in his backyard.
Oh, you did not meet that guy.
No, I did not meet that guy.
Yeah, I met the guy who has the tattoos on his arm.
Oh, right. Okay.
And then the third guy who has the show is Aaron Fechter.
Who I reached out to and almost went to on my most recent trip to Orlando three months ago.
He really, really wanted to host me.
But he unfortunately, he said he had a timeline.
He's like, email me in the morning and I'll see if I can squeeze you in.
And he couldn't.
So, yeah.
Is he hosting people constantly? Is that what he does?
Yeah, he has began opening tours to the public for the first time.
He is the creator.
Yeah, yeah.
Of the Rock of Fire explosion.
Look up, if you're listening to this podcast, look up this documentary.
This documentary is phenomenal.
It's fascinating.
It's as good as King of Kong.
I associated it with the King of Kong.
It's not the same filmmaker, but it came out around the same time.
And both of those documentaries just like blew my mind.
So, yeah.
All he wanted in return, I offered him money.
And all he wanted in return was for me to bring him a pizza.
A cheese pizza.
That's all he wanted.
How amazing is that?
I think you were saying that the nearest pizza place was like 30 minutes plus or more.
An hour away.
Much to my surprise, I did not know that.
And I felt so bad.
I showed up like two hours late.
And people who know me know that I'm never late for anything.
I went on this wild goose chase.
What was the pizza place?
Do you remember?
Was it a local place?
Yeah, it was like a Domino's.
But the closest Domino's was an hour.
This was in the middle of nowhere.
And he had taken like a gas station and converted it into a showbiz.
I mean, it wasn't just the rocket fire explosion.
He had like original showbiz tables.
He had original showbiz like kiddie rides.
Like he had decked it out.
This guy, unlike us, has children.
But I have a feeling that it's like mostly for him.
He probably hosts one or two birthday parties a year.
He confides...
I don't want to make fun of the guy because he's just like us.
Very nice.
To make fun of him would be to make fun of me or any of you guys.
Look at him walking in the mirror.
He confided in me that he has on a couple of occasions slept on the stage.
Which I would do like that's when I got my Reebok.
The day I got my Reebok pumps, like when that just came out, I slept in them.
How is that any different?
That's really funny.
But the show is beautiful.
Seeing it for the...
I mean, seeing the documentary is one thing.
To see it in person was just...
I wept.
It was so...
Now I get it.
Now I get why people are so obsessed with it.
The music's good.
The jokes are funny.
It's so effective and it's so much better than Chuck E. Cheese.
And now I really understand.
The first show that he programmed...
And by the way, this is all...
Now I know it's all running off of Windows 95.
He took me into the back room and it's running off like an old PC.
With all the weird hydraulic pumps.
And these guys teach themselves how to...
This show takes maintenance.
So he's constantly having to fix the hydraulic pumps.
And hydraulic fluid.
You have to acquire industrial fluids.
And there's so many little details.
There's a frog on a lily pad on the stage.
And Nat pops its head up and down.
So if one thing's broken...
I saw him as we were watching the shows.
As the shows were running and they were singing and chatting.
He was going and making little adjustments.
Wow. Geez, really?
Is he one of the people who's...
Because there's been a few music videos where artists have worked with the owners of the Rockafire Explosion
to make them sing their songs.
Is he one of those that has customized it?
No, that's Aaron. That's Aaron Fechter.
That's the factory that once housed 200 employees.
It's now just him. He's the sole employee.
They talk about this in the documentary.
The only reason why he's still there is just these little freelance projects where people...
There's a big band that did it.
I can't remember if it was MGMT or something.
I feel like maybe Norrels Barkley has...
Yeah, there.
I'm probably mixing them up.
I believe the Rockafire Explosion makes a cameo in the Key and Peele movie.
Which I have not seen, but I hear that they...
Keanu?
Yeah, Keanu. They wake up and they're being held hostage in a room that has the Rockafire Explosion.
Whoa. So that would have been...
Not the one you went to, but made by the owner in Ortega.
Yeah, I think he's the one who actually represents...
When the characters do cameos.
They do publicity. He's their manager now.
It's worth mentioning that Rockafire Explosion was the inspiration for the horror video game.
Five Nights at Freddy's, right?
Five Nights at Freddy's.
More so than Chuck E. Cheese.
Are you so into it that you know the names of the characters?
I do now.
This is a thing I should know.
Because I know Chuck E. Cheese characters.
Can you list just for my enjoyment?
Fats Domino is the terrifying gorilla that is at the front and center playing the keyboard.
Clearly, when you see the purple monster munch in Chuck E. Cheese, he's clearly a remoded version of Fats Domino.
Crudely remodeled, much like Tower of Terror is crudely remodeled to be Guardians of the Galaxy.
Oh, sure. Indeed.
Shots fired.
Sorry. I've been wanting to get that out for a week since on record.
If it's not clear 30 minutes in, all our guests on past shows have been wonderful.
Doug is definitely the one who has the same disease we do.
Aren't these the same strain of it?
Yeah, slight variances, but ultimately the same overall virus.
So Fats Domino is one.
Yeah, back to the robots.
Sorry, Mike.
Beach Bear is on the stage right.
And he's got a bird that he holds.
And what I did not know until I actually saw the show in person is that the bird, his pet bird, also sings and interacts and talks.
So it's like a bonus character that I did not know about.
So it requires his own separate maintenance.
Yeah. And the first show we watched, which, gosh, I can't remember. I believe the word magic was in the title of every song.
It was like the songs were so well themed. There was a Beatles, an all Beatles set. The shows are 15 minutes long.
So there's an all Beatles show. The first show we watched was all songs with the word magic in the title.
Wow. Pilot's magic, ELO's strange magic.
Yeah. And the bird that Beach Bear holds took the lead verse on the first song. And I was like, what?
You sing?
I was like, no way. I was like, that bird sings? And then Damon looked at me and he's like, yeah, the bird sings.
I thought you knew that. I thought you were one of me. He didn't realize that I'd never seen the show before.
Like, is the sky blue?
Reaching under the counter for a real shotgun.
There's Rolf de Wolf.
Rolf de Wolf?
Rolf de Wolf. Yeah. Earl Schmurl.
There's Loony Bird, who I was just speaking of.
That's the little bird.
The little bird. Yeah.
Good singer.
Duke LaRue, who's the drummer.
I know Duke. Yes, I knew that one. I knew Duke.
Mitzi Mozzarella is the female cheerleader character who became redressed as...
The bird?
As Helen? Or as Pasquale? Or no?
As the other one?
The female character.
Helen. Yeah.
Helen is the bird.
Helen is the weirdest, most common name. Everyone else has a fun name and then it's just Helen.
Very plain.
Jasper T. Jowls, Pasquale, and Helen.
Boy, we are certainly... there's a little preview of the ultimate, the seven hour Chuck E. Cheese.
R. Lawrence of Arabia will be about the Rock of Fire Explosion and the Munch's Miggly Band.
Well, hey, look, you know what? We're talking tunes. We're talking music.
We're talking great music, very retro music and boy, if you want to hear some great stuff, you'd probably want to time travel back to Vidiopolis at Disneyland.
It opened in 1985 and finally a place where teens can hang out and get rad at Disneyland.
Doug, in many cases we are pulling our... we conversationally present information that is ripped out of articles that we quickly read before recording the podcast.
In this case, you literally did write the article about Vidiopolis for dangerous minds.
Yes, and I have to... just like Rock of Fire Explosion, this is not something I grew up with. This is something that I happened upon a year or two ago.
I had found... I guess it first came under my radar when I found a Disneyland special called Disneyland Summer Vacation Party from 1986.
A two hour special hosted by Mindy Cohen from Facts of Life, Kim Fields, also from Facts of Life, Scott Valentine, who you guys might know from the Splash Mountain rap.
Oh, hey, is this a zip? I performed the rap on an episode that's coming at some point.
Really? I sure did. I look forward to that. It was a blast.
He was also Nick Moore, Justin Bateman's boyfriend from Family Ties.
Wow.
And Malcolm Jamal Warner. So they're at Vidiopolis and they split up like Mindy Cohen and Kim Fields go off looking for cute guys.
And then Scott Valentine and Malcolm Jamal Warner go out looking for girls to talk to.
And then meanwhile, while we go looking for girls, here's a live performance from Culture Club.
Or Miami Sound Machine.
This is the special that was used for one of the Everything is Terrible videos, right?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
So I cut. There's there's there's it's a it's a super serious dance party.
It's it's it's it's 1986 and and it's it's it's in the characters are out dancing with the yeah with the club goers.
And and so I cut out I took the two hour special and just only edited together the characters dancing with the guests.
And it's like stars are from the original special like you know, I added this.
I added the special effects. I love the stars. So it's like it turns out to be a 15 minutes of nothing but characters characters like like like the queen of hearts dancing with a bunch of guys are like there's there's a there's a scene where a Miami Sand Machine is playing the song Bad Boys and like the big bad wolf gets like pushed in the middle of circle and starts breaking saying it's just like if you're ever sad or you want to cheer up, just just watch this video.
It's truly something I took some screengrads from it because I watched it. It was fascinating. The two of the country bears are dancing at one point and then both Brea Rabbit or Bear Fox and Bear Bear.
And there is a long. Yeah. Yeah. Bear Fox really shaking his bottom.
This is what I call serious sweaty dancing, which is something that I miss. You don't see as much in that if you go to a Hollywood nightclub, you're not your chances are you're probably not going to see dancing like this anymore.
It's going to be more like, you know, casual casual type of music.
Sure. You're not seeing like serious pop lockers. No, you're looking for skill and timing. A lost art. Unfortunately.
Yeah. So I was showing this montage at the Ace Hotel where I do a monthly projecting and DJing and my friend Daniel Paul, who's a Los Angeles architectural historian.
Oh, boy. I have to talk to this gentleman. Oh, my God. He's he's he's I've met him recently and he's one of the most fascinating people I've ever met in my life.
Wow. He just his knowledge is incredible. So he looked at it. He's like, oh, wow, video op. And I said, what? And he said, oh, the dance club at Disneyland in the 80s. I used to go when I was in high school.
And that's I my jaw dropped and I was like, well, but God, the way that and this I kind of there wasn't that much. There's not enough information on the Internet.
So I just started and that's how me writing the article came about. No kidding. I have to tell that there's a story here. I have to tell it.
Now, if you if your appetite is not already wet by the general notion of the 80s teen dance club in Disneyland, just I think it's I think it's crucial to set the tone that we hear a little bit of the videopolis theme song.
This to me, if you're not in already, this song, I think tells you everything is really something you need to know. And here we go.
Oh, right.
This show.
To the music so high.
Going to the top.
The.
Oh, boy. So I got to say, I'm sure there's more iconic 80s songs, but this song, which has been stuck in my head for days since like starting to research this episode, is like the perfect Disney distillation of 1980s pop music.
Yeah, I know that this isn't true, but it seems like that song influenced everything Scott Gairdner has made in entertainment.
Scott, all of this is so much in your wheelhouse.
You know, I didn't know I didn't know videopolis like you. I was a late comer, but I remember it existing.
I remember probably the first time I went to Disneyland in 1988. I probably passed by the dance party in progress.
But I'm three, so I can't go in there. But I know that we talked with Anthony Geo about baby brain.
I know my baby brain locked into like the distant neon so hard and the logo just like if you're listening to this, please pull up some logos.
Right now, I'm looking at the 45 of that song, which is like, you know, that that sort of 80s squiggle writing with a big like slash under it and a big purple triangle.
And if you are familiar with Moonbeam City, the show that I did, like for sure that is me just like, well, I got to clear out the attic of the old baby brain stuff.
Yeah, I like I know that videopolis had a lot to do with my like locking into neon and triangles and and, you know, Janet Jackson music.
Here's the thing I like about that song is that it's very much the perfect kind of pop music single nonsense.
Like the words kind of mean nothing like they may as well be singing to do Ron Ron.
Yeah. Go into the top video.
Go into the top video. I've just been singing to myself for days.
You're gonna see what I mean.
In that scene.
Ellie Greenwich, Phil Spector, Brill Building, Fashion.
There's a lot of American bandstand comparisons to videopolis because there was a TV show broadcast from there.
As well. Yes. Yeah. But I also want to say about the song.
I'm a I'm a big liner notes junkie. I want to know every musician who played on everything wrote wrote everything.
And I was this like this song is on discogs.com which kind of compiles liner notes and all you get on it is unknown generic male singer.
There is no one bothered to write down who sang the videopolis song which is so disappointing.
If anyone out there knows for some reason anybody like it's your dad or something, please let us know.
Let's give him a credit.
It was probably the guy who wrote it.
And it sounds like he like this is a demo. This is the song that I wrote.
And you could when you find a big name singer to sing it. Let me know.
I can't wait to send you the track like no, we'll just use what you sent us.
This is fine. We don't want to we don't want to pay Bolton or whatever to do it.
We don't know the writer either. No, none of it's none of it.
None of it. Thank you for gifting that song to us.
That song I think really sets the tone and set the tone for my life.
The thing that I didn't know until recently, there is a wonderful video on YouTube that shows you 50 minutes of what it was like to be at videopolis.
Somebody just like showing one of their nights out with their friends.
A raw unedited like one hour home video of videopolis from from like start to finish.
It's just wonderful. You couldn't fake if you like set out with the art decorators to like create a perfect sort of snippet of 80s culture.
It's so so perfect. But I didn't know that they they played the song at the beginning of every night, apparently.
Yes. That's when you knew Videopolis was up and running and was when they played the themes. It's a club with a theme song. It's wonderful.
If they were to have like if you were to look at all the people wearing the 80s clothes and the music and everything going on in the hairstyle.
If they were to show like the art director of the Goldbergs, they would be like, this is too much. This looks too much.
This is too fake 80s. This isn't really how the 80s were. But like it's there. It's just this is a this isn't even a promotional video on YouTube.
It's just like someone's home movie. Yeah, it was crazy. It's the it's unbelievable how much everyone was the 80s.
The dance floor accommodated accommodated 3000 guests.
That's wild. Yeah, that we should say this is where the place now if you're if you've been to Disneyland, it's where they do the show Mickey and the Magical Map.
That's right. Which is a family friendly little show. Fantasyland Theater. Right. Which was it was strategically placed.
They want to put it at a place that was like a way that it wouldn't interfere with the families. It was in the corner of the park.
This is before Toontown. So there's no real reason to be all the way up in that corner, which is probably why I miss it because I was going to the park during this time.
I would have been between the ages of like six and eleven, I think. But but it was kept separate for for for a reason.
It was it was the back room of Disneyland. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And the the fantasy the Fantasyland train station for four years became the Videopolis train station.
So the party could actually start, I guess, when you enter the park and get on the train. Yeah.
I have a picture here and it is very like cool looking. Oh, yeah. They full on changed the like station and it looks very I don't know what the style, but it is crazy to change the train station.
I can't even I'm not sure I can like look at all of these this imagery and function. I'm like I might go into an epileptic fit the more of these things we see.
A little bottle of smelling salts and a a mint jewel up close by.
Should he get the vapors? Much like an eye on me, guys. Much like when we talk about couches with Jason's.
When we talk about neon and 80s stuff with Scott. Yeah. They're both prone to too much excitement.
And for Mike, it's a Chicago style Italian beef sandwich. I got to have my beef.
You got it. I should also say, if you're listening to this and have never been to Disneyland, but something your head goes like this sounds familiar.
I have been to Disney World a lot. Videopolis East was an opening day club at Pleasure Island.
No kidding. Even less documentation on that. You can find virtually nothing on that.
Pretty much. No, I mentioned in the past our the much liked among us Funkland series.
I was watching their two parts on Pleasure Island and they mentioned it opened as the Disneyland was closing.
Yeah. In 1989. It should be mentioned that both of these were Michael Eisner projects.
Old Mikey Eisner.
The Videopolis at Disneyland was the very first attraction to be completed under Michael Eisner.
Wow. His first order of business was TTT.
The thing he rushed out like Trump's immigration ban.
Eisner ordered a cool teen dance club and he needed it done in his first. Well, not his first hundred day, but like a presidential order.
It was done in 100 days. They rushed this thing out. They call it the 100 day miracle.
How much did it cost? Like 3 million?
3 million dollars.
A lot of it repurposed media equipment, projectors and screens and stuff from the 84 Los Angeles Olympics that they got on cheap like at surplus prices.
I've also seen it reported, although this might be a Wikipedia fact that is wrong, but I've also seen it reported that some of it came from the US festival.
Steve Wozniak's San Bernardino concerts in the early 80s, which I recommend any videos of those legit amazing incredible bands, incredible performances.
I think after the current Olympics, maybe we should look around and see if we can get our own Videopolis going. Get some cheap discounted TVs.
You mean from Seoul?
Yeah, yeah. We'll go to Seoul.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, we'll go to Seoul and buy all the leftover TVs.
Hey, you want to go to Tokyo soon?
Yeah, stop over in Seoul.
Stop by Seoul.
I think I don't have any concerns about stealing things from Korea. I think that's a totally fine thing to do.
When they find out what we're doing with it, they'll be happy.
I think it's time to start talking about Michael Eisner's cool complex. He, I think, was very concerned with getting cool stuff into the parks.
He was influenced by his son Breck, who thought Disneyland was lame, and he wanted to jam some cool stuff in there.
And let me say...
Jam cool stuff he did.
He really did. Well, and think about this. What a recipe for disaster it is to try to get rock music and MTV culture into your theme park.
You know, think about any time today, there's a corporate impression of what the teen's like. It's usually a disaster.
But if you think about it, look at this list.
Alien Encounter, which we all agree we really like. Splash Mountain.
Yacht and Beach Club Resort.
The Beach Club, yeah, yeah, yeah. Hey, The Swan and The Dolphin. Nothing cooler than those places.
No, but I, there's, as you look into Vidiopolis, I think Vidiopolis was legit.
I don't think it was even, like, a lame corporate impression of a teen dance club. I think it was pretty cool.
They did not mess around. They had lasers shooting everywhere.
Video crews taping people dancing and projecting them on screen. So you would be, there would be music videos playing on, you know, hundreds and hundreds of TV screens.
And then you yourself would be projected on the biggest screen of all with, like, 80s effects, like, superimposed over you while you're dancing.
Man, you're the star.
That long video, that's the home movie, basically, like, it shows how it starts. So, like, there's an appearance on the video screen by K-Rock DJ Swedish Eagle.
That's right, yeah.
Which, that was news to me as far as that gentleman. I didn't, I was not.
He's still, he's on XM Radio channel 33, first wave.
Yeah.
That's great.
And he announces a bunch of 80s specific prizes, like Tower Record gift certificate and tickets to Oingo Boingo.
And a GM car.
A limousine that will take you to the concert.
That you're, yeah, you get prizes at this place.
I mean, no one gets prizes at Disneyland.
No, not since the 35th anniversary in the prize machine.
Oh, let's not forget the year of a million dreams.
Okay, okay.
Let's not forget the gift giver 5,000.
Oh, that's what I'm thinking.
Every park wins, excuse me, every guest wins a prize upon entering the park.
Wow.
I did, I should retract my statement because in 2014, Lindsay and I went and went to this special 59th anniversary celebration.
We got a bunch of prizes.
We got a paperweight, a little diamond paperweight, and we got fast passes to every ride.
Wow.
That's insane.
I got free mouse ears once during the year of a million dreams.
Like, I have year of a million dreams mouse ears.
Alright, so I take it back.
Disney gives free stuff all the time.
Not in a while, though.
Maybe more to APs, annual pass holders.
And I went, Mike, when we went to watch the Oscars at the venue where the great moments with Mr. Lincoln show happens.
They show, they put the Oscars on in the Lincoln Theater.
The Jimmy Kimmel hosted Oscars last year.
I don't know.
This might have been new, I don't know.
But we watched Justin Timberlake's opening and Jimmy Kimmel's monologue.
You should go to that.
And I won the raffle.
My seat was called after lots of empty seats were called because there were lots of empty seats.
What did you win?
I won the Guardians 2 mixtape.
No, you won the Guardians TV show soundtrack.
The cartoon soundtrack.
Wow, that's a very specific prize.
I felt bad because I, you know.
People were excited.
People were very jealous and shot me dirty looks, I think.
There was some tension with the weirdos watching the Oscars.
Speaking of soundtracks, Doug, I want to, from your Dangerous Minds article.
This was a highlight for me.
Every night, Videopolis would play two tribes by Frankie Goes to Hollywood during the fireworks show.
Which took place right above the dance floor.
Which, that is great.
That's awesome, isn't it?
It's awesome.
That's such an 80s sentence.
Spectacular view of the fire.
Because there was so little information on the internet when I was writing this article,
I believe I picked up that tidbit from a YouTube comment.
Which I don't want to give away all my secrets, but YouTube.
You guys troll message boards.
I troll YouTube comments.
Because if you keep scrolling, you'll find some really, really helpful little tidbits like that.
My trend of being the slang boy.
We lurk at these. We don't troll them.
We're not going like, you idiot.
We're quietly lurking and observing.
Firing shots is trolling.
My deepest apologies.
I found a blog where somebody was describing that,
okay, well first of all, because Videopolis is at the top end of the park,
which is where the fireworks still are shot off from.
So you're essentially right under the fireworks as they're going off.
And I saw a blog that described it as sort of a little scary in a way.
That everything's trembling around you and ashes are falling on you.
It was very intense to be right.
They closed Toontown because they don't want people to be right under the fireworks.
But back in Videopolis days, kids are breathing ash.
I've still gotten some ash at certain parks if I'm too close to the fireworks.
Going to a kid at Disneyland in the 80s,
I don't remember them shutting off all of Fantasyland while the fire...
I feel like that's a newer thing.
Because now you can't even walk through certain areas of the park
while the fireworks are going on.
If you're not interested in seeing the fireworks, it's such a nuisance.
It's like you get trapped and you can't go anywhere.
Oh yeah, they got to split parts of Main Street up and whatever.
Yeah, it does get a little annoying around that time.
I guess also in the super legal world that we're in now,
probably they have to block off areas.
But not then. Kids are high on firework fumes.
Also, here's the other thing I want to say.
Frankie Goes to Hollywood, Two Tribes.
I've never heard of that song. I didn't know that song.
Really?
I didn't actually. Do you guys?
I was going to say, a lot of this music...
I was born in 1985, so shortly after Videopolis.
So a lot of this music, my context for it,
and I do like a lot of the New Wave 80 stuff,
was either commercials for compilations on TV in high school.
And then a big thing, and I'm sure a lot of our millennial listeners will agree,
the Grand Theft Auto Vice City soundtrack.
The multi-disc soundtrack of 80s...
That's how I learned about 80s pop music.
Just playing back 80s for hours.
Yeah, and Two Tribes is in there.
Oh, gotcha.
What I think is cool is that you might expect the Disney opening in 80s nightclub
that you'd get the biggest top 40 kind of songs,
but they played deep cuts from what I could tell.
They played really cool, legit...
Yeah, it was not all hits.
I feel like if today they said,
we're doing 80s night at Disneyland,
you would hear Girls Just Want to Have Fun,
you'd hear Relax, you'd hear The Top Top Sub.
But this place had taste, I think.
It's interesting because they've done...
And this is another episode,
but they did a show called The Mad Tea Party at Disney's California Adventure.
I was hoping we could get into that.
You knew we would get there.
Once we're done talking about Videopolis.
Because I'm sure we all have...
This is something that we've all been to,
and probably have a lot to say about.
I certainly do.
Right before The Mad Tea Party, actually,
they had a different show that was called Glow, I believe.
Let's start, if you want to...
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I have the chronological order.
You do the chronological, yeah.
It started... This all came about...
It's similar to the Disneyland story in 1985,
where Eisner's like, we need to get...
In the late 2000s, they realized that California Adventure was like a bust.
No one likes this park.
We need to do something drastic.
And some genius realized,
oh yeah, we sell alcohol, let's do something there.
And Glowfest was the first experiment in doing something like this.
This was in 2010.
And this Glowfest coincided with the debut of World of Color.
Well, wait, wasn't it Tron Legacy themed?
That came later.
Excuse me, that was 2011.
No, that came out by the end of the year,
because Glowfest was... People didn't like it.
They hired a third party to make it,
and people were like, this isn't very Disney.
This is too adult-oriented.
It was not successful.
By the end of the year, Electronica was up and running,
which was the word Tron, all caps,
to promote the movie Tron Legacy.
Which I thought looked cool.
I remember being at the park.
It was awesome.
There was a lot of Clockwork Orange-style furniture outside everywhere.
A lot of that blue...
The whole Hollywoodland section of the park was projection mapping
to make it look like the Tron grid.
They had Tron characters throwing Frisbees at you.
They had a stage show called Laser Man.
There was an arcade.
There was a replica of Flynn's arcade.
They even recreated the facade of the building perfectly
with the neon sign that said Flynn's.
It looked really good.
The Tron game right in the back with a glow on it calling out to you
as in the first film.
It was the perfect time for people like us to have an annual pass
because I went to that thing every other weekend.
It was so cool.
It was not overwhelmingly crowded usually,
like for a tea party.
It was a pretty low-key, underappreciated thing
because such a big change to California Adventure came right after it.
I did think Electronica was a pretty neat idea.
It was.
Every time I'd go to Electronica,
it was when the whole first section of the park was completely under construction.
So you were walking down a tunnel of construction to get to Electronica.
And there was alcohol was flowing.
They had the glow-hito.
Oh, I remember the glow-hito.
They had the digittini.
For those who didn't drink alcohol, they had the laser light lemonade.
And then the Muppet Vision 3D Theater was showing a sneak preview of Tron Legacy.
With lasers in the theater and the glow of the ships or whatever
would be reflected with lights and there'd be smoke machines.
It was like a 4DX experience of Tron Legacy,
which made you think Tron Legacy would be great.
And it looked great.
Everything was so well done from top to bottom.
And then you wonder how you have all these kids and young adults
and teenagers and there's alcohol.
How are you going to monitor this?
And they had so much security.
To drink you had to have a wristband.
And if one of your friends took a sip from your drink,
they would just swoop in like a hawk.
And it was very, very well monitored to make sure that you didn't have any underage drinking.
And I loved it. I miss it.
It was cool. I remember it and it was cool.
But then the next thing is the Mad Tea Party, right?
And the Mad Tea Party, I will say I do love it in a very similar Jimmy Buffett style way.
I'd always want to go there.
But it is what you think of Disney doing something, trying to do something cool.
It is a Disney attempt at being cool and hip.
And of course it's kind of lame. It's pretty lame.
I remember.
That is what you think Disney when they think cool.
Mike and I were at the Mad Tea Party once we both went to the Tea Party.
We went there many times.
We went there many times because any time we were there, Mike's like,
well, we got to swing by the Mad Tea Party.
I would say we got to get mad.
We got to get mad.
And he would say it like you were running an errand.
It's like, oh, I got to stop by Target. Oh, we should swing by Lowe's.
He'd go like, yeah, well, we got to stop by the Mad Tea Party.
And I remember the one time it was a Friday night we went down.
It's like, oh, yeah, let's get some Mad Hitos or whatever the drinks were.
That's correct. I have that here in my notes.
And we mostly did get the cool glowing ice cubes,
which I'm still finding plastic glowing ice cubes among my junk drawer stuff.
And I just remember I could see in through the back of the stand.
And I'm like, they're pouring these out of like milk jugs,
like a gallon of, if you imagine a plastic gallon of milk.
They had premixed mojitos in those that they were just pouring over ice.
Mad Hitos.
The other drinks were croquette tinis and a mad Long Island ice tea.
Those croquette tinis would have a delicious chicken croquette floating right in the hole.
I think there was probably croquet tinis.
Good point.
The Queen. The Evil Queen.
I see. There was not a pronunciation guide.
People love the Mad Tea Party.
I remember getting my hair cut in at a, what is it called?
What's the Rock and Roll Barbershop chain?
Floyd's?
Floyd's. Yeah.
Oh, so Rock and Roll.
That's the coolest barbershop in town.
I had a hairdresser there once and she had a tiny Mad Hatter hat on.
And I asked, oh, is that from Disneyland?
Have you been to the Mad Tea Party?
And she went, I bought an annual pass to go to the Mad Tea Party.
I go every weekend.
Whoa.
That's how seriously the Mad Hatter hat became the new Cat in the Hat.
People were wearing them to nightclubs outside of Disneyland.
It was a rare case of Disneyland fashion sticking outside.
Oh my goodness.
And became too popular for its own good.
They eventually had to shut it down because it became too rowdy.
Really?
Much like Videopolis.
An oddly similar arc.
So you guys might not, the final piece of information to that story is 2015.
As you may or may not remember,
Mad Tea Party closed and became, very briefly and very unsuccessfully,
Freeze the Night, a family dance party inspired by the Disney animated film Frozen.
Freeze the Night.
I don't remember that.
I remember that.
It was a big letdown.
Now they kind of play music over there in that section, but it's not the same.
It's not fun.
Why do you want to freeze the night?
That's not an exciting, that's not a mission statement.
Like going to the top.
Have you seen kids dance?
They don't really know what they're doing.
It's embarrassing.
For a five year old, the definition of dancing is usually just jumping up and down.
Come on.
Doing something you wouldn't usually do.
Right.
The only way you can screw up is by just walking casually.
Right. What a joke.
Don't even try kids.
When they announced that summer, so Disneyland last year had a promotion called the Summer of Heroes
to introduce the Guardians of the Galaxy.
And they were like in a Guardians dance party.
And I got kind of excited because whether you think the movies are good or bad or whatever,
the music is pretty good in it.
So you could get some fun songs.
And I was like, oh, they're going to put a cool 70s, 80s dance party over there.
It's not what happened.
They just put some like 22 year old dressed as a Chris Pratt character with a boombox
and they play like 30 seconds of ELO.
And I was like, what? That's a waste.
Put it over by the spot where you used to do cool parties.
I'm hoping that because they did after freeze the night was a disaster.
They brought Mad Tea Party back for like one hot minute before it went away.
I'm hoping that there's a sequel to Tron Legacy that they bring back Electronica.
That's my hope. That's my hope in my dreams.
Here's some blue sky for you.
If they do turn that corner of the park into some Marvel stuff as speculated
and they get the X-Men back.
Oh, Dazzler dance party.
Dazzler themed dance party is would be something.
Dazzler's Videopolis.
Sure, you can combine.
Dazzler wore roller skates and she was like a singer and like a disco singer.
She was a pop singer who was a mutant who had like light powers.
I think that's only going to happen if we get the Dazzler trilogy of films.
So if that happens then.
But we have yet to see Dazzler in the movies.
Man, I like, I don't know.
These are all movies I don't see or like.
But I want them all to happen just so I can get some cool like.
Yeah.
These Tron, like we're talking about a Tron with Jared Leto.
That sounds like.
That sounds apocalyptically bad.
A movie grown in a lab.
Like a movie Tron.
To make Scott Gerner the angriest.
But please, if we get that and then we get the Tron coaster in California
or we get the electronica back.
I'm all for Jared, do whatever you want.
Just don't play any of his music.
Is it safe to say that the Tron dance party and Videopolis are the two coolest things
Disney's ever done?
Disneyland specifically.
Disneyland, yeah I would say so.
That's a pretty good bet to say I would think.
Because Disney as a whole is, I think the nice thing about Disney is that it's not trying to be cool.
So when it actually has hit two things that, you know, four of us think are very cool.
A Tron dance party.
They've actually sort of done something impressive.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I don't know.
The fact that people found this club to be legit is pretty impressive to me.
For my childhood at Disneyland, the two story Starrcade when it had all the games you could ever want.
Starrcade is kind of gone finally.
Yeah, it's sad. It got reduced to like eight to ten games and then the rest of the area merchandise only on the first.
That second story has been vacant for like 25 years.
It is crazy how these corners of this, like the happiest place on earth, this hugely popular theme park.
No matter how much money or how well the parks are doing, there's always going to be corners that just kind of like...
Or big empty spaces that are just storing boxes of Stitch t-shirts.
How is that possible? It's like the most valuable real estate in the world and how do you end up with just an attic?
Yeah, it's crazy. I hope you've heard that we've been just being so upset about what's happening at Tomorrowland at Disneyland.
That's another part of that is just Starrcade being empty.
Yeah, it's pathetic. I don't like the H.D. Wells-Jules Verne makeover.
It's barely there.
It's like they had something that they're trying to do and then they even abandoned that and now it's...
The Tomorrowland in Tokyo is perfect. It's the time capsule. It's the Tomorrowland we remember from like 1983.
That version. Nothing will ever be cooler than that.
Honestly, what I've seen of the building that the Tron coaster is in in Shanghai and will be coming to Orlando in a few years...
Again, the look of Tron Legacy I think still looks really good. So just cover the Anaheim Tomorrowland in glowing neon colors.
Yes, that will always be the future.
The future ever... Well, it's not really a current future. The future is always lasers. When will you learn it, Disney? It doesn't change.
Even at the opening Olympics. The opening Olympic ceremonies in Korea just happened a day or so ago.
There was visualization of what a future Korean cities could look like and a lot of that was glowing blue.
It looked amazing. We were at the soft opening of Splitsville in downtown Disney watching the opening ceremonies of the Winter Olympics on the TV with the sound off.
Wait, is it just soft opening? I didn't even realize it was that far along.
It was in the bowling alley of downtown Disney. How is it? What did you think?
It was fun.
Great. Well, it's another place to get beer at Disneyland so I'm happy as long as it satisfies that.
Full bar. They'll make any drink you want.
Wonderful. While we're jumping around Tomorrowlands, I'd like to say that the name Vidiopolis, in addition to Pleasure Island, also made it to Disneyland Paris.
Good point.
Which has the Discoveryland, the Jules Verne overlay. I got to go to Vidiopolis Paris and I was curious if it felt anything like the 90s Disneyland Vidiopolis.
But in fact, it's kind of a cafeteria and all of the seats and the risers people go and take food over there.
So I ate my lunch at Disneyland Paris at Vidiopolis and there was a stage which had a bunch of big thunder kind of rock work.
Like big jutting out rock pieces. And I was like, I wonder what show we're getting today.
And the show we got was the stage being empty and all four monitors quietly playing clips of Star Wars Rebels.
Which is kind of a nice little synopsis of Disneyland Paris in general and our Disneyland Paris experience as I sat and watched quiet clips of a cartoon while eating the worst burger I've had in my life.
Very strange. I think they did want Vidiopolis Paris to be a teen club a la Disneyland but it was apparently cancelled due to lack of interest from the public.
There you go.
So they never played music there but they did do a show which you can look up on YouTube. A show called Rock Shock.
And I would describe this, they did this in 1995 and I would describe the show aesthetically as being done by people who thought that the in sync pop era was too tasteful.
It's a real nightmare. And the description of Rock Shock on Wikipedia, it featured a gang of teenagers journeying in the footsteps of Jules Verne to the beat of rock music.
It was a relative success. Which is maybe, I'm not sure I agree with even that praise, the opening, it's a 20 minute show you can watch on YouTube.
I'll happily watch any weird Disney live show. This thing, it starts with Mickey being brought out in like a little space rover and then trying to plant a flag in the ground and then failing.
And he eventually gives up and takes the flag back with him on the space rover and then a bunch of teens flop around for 15 minutes and there are no characters. Doesn't feel remotely like Disney in any way.
So mixed reviews from me on Vidiopolis Paris.
Well speaking of teens flopping around with no direction, watch this transition. Ken, let's talk about some of the clips we have seen of the Vidiopolis TV shows.
Absolutely, sure. Yeah, so they made a syndicated television show a la American Bandstand or Soul Train using the name Vidiopolis.
And I also thought it was funny, they did not just use the name Vidiopolis but they took another part of the live experience of Vidiopolis, the Snack Bar Yums with a Z.
Which was right next to Vidiopolis which offered pizza, ice cream and nachos.
Oh man, the best foods!
I'm sorry you can't go to Yums today. But there was a part in the middle of when it got to the interview section of the Vidiopolis show, a big sign that says Yums came down and a bunch of teens all sat at tables and talked to that day's guest.
Which would have included, I believe guests on the Vidiopolis show included Debbie Gibson, New Kids on the Block and in the one that's the most on YouTube, Pebbles.
Yes, 80's singer Pebbles. What are the Pebbles hits?
Mercedes Boy, Girlfriend, which is a wonderful jam.
And the interviews are so awkward and stilted. First of all the host of the show, this guy Randy Hamilton, who is like a local actor.
The squarest square I've ever seen.
So square, like late 30's hanging out with teenagers.
Yeah, he's too old, why is he hosting the show?
Yeah, way too old to be hosting that show.
And there's a strange thing with him where he comes out and introduces the show and hosts it, but then when you go to Yums he's on a TV monitor, even though you've established that he's on the main set of the show.
Well video conferencing was amazing back then. It was the idea that you could talk to a television was incredible.
Even your visage through time and space.
That was so funny, the opening credits of the episode. There's a lot of clips of online just hearing the announcer go, with special guest Pebbles and your host Randy Hamilton.
And out comes a guy in the palest khakis I've ever seen wearing a quilt, like the bougiest.
A big thick sweater.
Yeah, Martha's Vineyard attire.
He was just yachting.
Yeah, he was yachting. Another Michael Eisner obsession. Michael Eisner wanted cool stuff.
And he loved his childhood summers in New England.
So he wanted to reflect that in the host of Videopolis.
Yeah.
Yeah, so it's an odd show. Pebbles is real dour. She's kind of, she's not wannabe interviewed.
She's very like Prince in her answers, I felt. Like when Prince was in an interview he didn't want to be in and he would just be like, I guess so.
I did like in the interview when Randy Hamilton asked her, who are your guys? In sort of a proto Mark Maron, hey who are your guys? Hey Pebbles, are we good?
Pebbles said Bill Hicks.
There's a Randy Hamilton, I wrote down a quote that Randy says too, just with this like unknown young dancer. And he says this, I don't know if you guys saw this, I'm sure you did.
He goes, ever since show business started, audiences love to see new unknown talent get a chance at stardom.
Stardom. He mispronounces the word or he's like being funny. I don't know. So he says, yeah.
And then he goes, now being the swell guy that I am, he's like, I'm going to send this kid up and then he's going to become a big star or whatever. And then like a kid dances.
It's bizarre. And they, it's like, he either makes them, I mean, he makes a mistake. He called, he says stardom stardom, and then he like quickly corrects himself. I don't know why they didn't do another take of it.
Or he was being funny and like saying stardom and like thinking like, Oh, this is a bad, I don't know.
Speaking of cumbersome transitions, they try to set up a song at one point in one of these episodes. And he, and his line was, after two people have been together for a while, people start to take each other for granted.
And everyone is clearly distressed and confused. And I believe it was to set up a Janet Jackson song. Like there's, there's like 30 seconds of weird banter and he was trying to get them to setting up this Janet Jackson song. They were all going to dance.
Why didn't they get Scott Valentine, the splash mountain rap guy or better yet, Mark Price, AKA the guy who did all the splash mountain promotional, you know, like, uh, well he was Skippy from, I believe growing pains, but the, oh, yes.
I did like, uh, it's, uh, uh, Hamilton does a good job introducing the start of the clip. I watched like, uh, uh, the boy, this, uh, you know, there's, there's an interstellar phenomenon known as a Sonic boom. And that's exactly what this song is doing on the charts.
This is Westworld with Sonic boom boy.
Song I'd never heard of, but I enjoyed highlighted different odd Randy Hamilton line.
Randy Hamilton is creepy too. He's like, there's that clip where he's trying to like, get like one of the kids on the show to dance with pebbles. Yeah. And he's like, uh, pebbles. Uh, there's a, this guy's got a question for you. And then she's like, what?
And then the kid doesn't ask the question and he goes, uh, weren't you saying you wanted to dance with pebbles? And then, and then he's like, yeah, oh, would you dance? He goes, uh, pebbles, uh, he's asking if you guys can go to the dance floor together. And then she's like, yeah, that'd be fine.
Yeah, that sounds nice. Okay. We'll do that.
When a disembodied man on a TV tells you what to do, I guess you got to do it.
Um, it's weird. He's very weird. He comes off so poorly.
He makes you feel so uncomfortable, much like your dad would like if you were at a cool place and your dad was there.
Like dad, please go away.
Just ask the girl out, Tommy.
Randy Hamilton should not have introduced himself as the host. He should have said, I'm the chaperone for tonight. I'll be keeping an eye on you guys.
If my dad hosted a dance night at videopolis and declared at the top, well, we're gonna have a lot of fun. Won't be playing any of that damn rap though. I'll tell you that much.
Who's the girl you like, son? I'll ask her for you. Where is she? Oh yeah. Hey, Tiffany, get over here. My son's got a question for you.
My wiener son's being a wiener.
Did you do a little pity make out with him? Come on. Yeah, be nice. Make him into a man.
The creepiest host that we've talked about maybe since the Jurassic Park guy who was the first man accused of gerbaling, who hosted the Jurassic Park opening special.
There's one to look up. Go back to our Jurassic Park episode for a determination of gerbaling.
I may have to go back to that episode. Okay, yeah, now I remember. Okay, yeah.
Anyway, well, there's a whole big, before there was a TV show, there had to be the dance party, but before there was the Disneyland dance party, there's a whole other wrinkle in this saga.
The other thing that's interesting about this genre is that Eisner, in addition to wanting to make the park cool, he also wanted to siphon business away from Knott's Berry Farm.
Because Videopolis opens in a rush job in the summer of 1985, partially because in the summer of 1984, Knott's is doing gangbusters business with two dance clubs, one called Cloud 9 and one called Studio K.
So we're huge. Like the first all-ages dance clubs anywhere. Really? Yeah, they had huge DJs like Richard Blade from K-Rock. They're attracting 2,000 teenagers and young adults a night.
Oh my god. So, of course, Michael is like, we need to get on this ASAP.
And Knott's also kind of pioneered a different kind of ticketing specifically to appeal to youngsters. I think there was a special pass you could get. If you paid $8, you'd go in after 6 o'clock.
You don't get the full day at the park, but to encourage people to go to... And Disney did the same thing. But with a much pricier deal.
You could get a summer pass. Summer's night's pass. Summer's night's pass. And you got a Videopolis membership card for it. How cool is that?
You could go every night for the summer after 5pm. This would cost you $40.
Wait a minute, the entire summer... The entire summer... This pass being pricey. Oh my god. It wasn't every night.
No, no. You paid $40 and then for the rest of the summer you could come after 5pm. To all of Disneyland. Not just to Videopolis.
If you told me for a summer now, this is going to be a pass. You get into Disneyland past 5 o'clock. And maybe you don't get to do all the rides, but you get to dance to Janet Jackson.
Nobody would ever see me again. I'd have to get an apartment in Brea just to be nearby. The summer's blown. I'm gone.
This was common practice in Florida too. You could buy half day passes for the parks to get in because they wanted to get people in the parks. Now they want people out of the parks.
This is how they started attracting the wrong element which ultimately led to Videopolis' demise. It was gone by the late 80's because of gang wars in the parking lot.
Wasn't there also a stage in Tomorrowland where local bands would play?
Yeah, they still have that. It's now the Star Wars Jedi Academy and for a brief time in the 2000's it was called Club Buzz. Meaning Buzz Lightyear.
But I think in the 80's people would buy this pass and hang out there too. Or maybe it was the 90's they had a similar teen pass.
I definitely remember cool stuff happening at that Tomorrowland stage. It's so cool the way it rises out of the ground.
And I believe that was maybe the 90's. Someone who grew up here was telling me about that and that also had some violence and then they shut it down. But kids were just hanging out there in lieu of the mall.
It's like, well we could go to the mall or we could just go hang out at Disneyland.
I wasted my youth.
My friend Ska Bad in the mid 90's opened up for No Doubt at the Tomorrowland stage on grad night.
Even back in the old days they would have cool bands. They would have up and coming bands.
Which they probably stole from Magic Mountain. Magic Mountain in the 70's had huge huge bands and Disneyland probably wanted to get on that. Disneyland stole everything from other people.
They kind of wait for other people to test the waters and once they get it working they have an example and they take it.
I learned from the defunct Land series on Videoopolis. The local attitude was that the rich kids went to Videoopolis and everyone else went to Studio K.
A little wilder, a little more fun it seems like.
That is what it sounds like. Disney did have to be a little more... they had to censor the music. There's certain songs, certain videos they aren't playing.
But it sounds like it was a little more all bets are off at Studio K. Studio K does sound a little more legit to me.
And also to go back to No Doubt there is a quote when Gwen Stefani was promoting her 2004, her first solo album she said,
The goal was to make a record that had that feeling I got when I'd go dancing at Studio K at Knott's Berry Farm. You don't feel that anymore.
Which is the album, I like some of that album. It's got Hollaback Girl, it's got Cool which is a good song.
There's like other, Bubble Pop Electric is a good song. So mission accomplished Gwen.
If you were making a period piece of that era, you open up on a shot with Hollaback Girl playing, you're immediately taken back to that time period.
When there is a 2000s coming of age film or show, yes the trailer will have Hollaback Girl.
The Videoopolis, it seems kind of odd that they would do something like this or even they would do it at Knott's.
But Disneyland has had a history of having people come at night and dance.
That actually is a date night at Disneyland. It's a song that was made and it was attracting couples to come and dance.
Is the song called that?
Yeah it's on this Disney competition and it's like, hey everybody it's a something something orchestra get ready to dance.
And it's like, Date Night at Disneyland. It's an old timey song and it's very fun.
But it's like this is a tradition and they've actually just been doing the new version of it every year.
I guess they haven't really done it in a while, but they still have people go and do a weird swing dance over in front of the castle once in a while.
That's always it. This isn't the first time they did dancing a bit at Disneyland.
My mother grew up in Southern California and she'd go as a teenager every weekend.
I think there was a cover band that they would go specifically to see perform at Disneyland and dance.
And then try to hang out with them after the gig and go on rides with them.
Disneyland and Knots has always been a cool way to date.
I would go to Magic Mountain when I was in high school and we would try to meet girls.
Before Tinder and dating apps it was like, this is how you did it.
And I still prefer this way.
I still go to Disneyland looking for hookups. Not true.
But they spell it all out in the special Disneyland Summer Vacation Party.
That two hour special, the whole storyline is about trying to meet cute girls and guys.
Right. I guess that is just on the opening day, Walt said, this is a place for all to come.
And also for hot young singles to meet and hook up.
And where families can have fun together and where the ages of consent get fuzzy.
Scott, you were surprised by the date night at Disneyland single.
But nowadays you just make a Twitter account or an Instagram account to promote something.
Back in the day someone would just cut a single as advertising.
That's when they would just be like, alright, I'm opening a hamburger restaurant.
Hire those kids down the street to cut a single. Call it like hamburger Mary.
Sorry, I was right. It's Let's Dance at Disneyland. I'll play a second of it for you.
It's date night at Disneyland with the Elliott Brothers and the Disneyland Date Nighters. Let's dance!
Let's dance at Disneyland. Date nights are late nights at Disneyland.
We're rolling to the park once one AM. Friday and Saturday nights.
That's your original videopolis. Wow.
It was recorded on Friday. It's always been cool.
Press it on Saturday. Sell it at Woolworths on Monday.
Watch the tickets skyrocket next Friday.
Rowdy, horny teens have been coming since the 50s.
Amorous young people.
It does seem like Disneyland has always had it. I think maybe less so now.
I feel like if you see Disney band now, they're more likely to be kind of handpicked.
They feel like it's sort of a more corporate entertainment.
But it does feel like in the first 40 years of Disneyland's existence.
Somebody fact check me on any of this, but I feel like I've picked up from various sources.
Bands that played at Disneyland before they were famous include the Beach Boys, the Jackson 5, the Osmonds, all the coolest bands.
The Carpenters. Bands that went on to be big legit bands. It was a legit place to start and get their name out there.
Jackson 5's first gig in Southern California. Golden Horseshoe.
What?
Not true. Sorry.
I like that so much. I wanted it to be true.
Sorry. Sorry.
Wally Bo doing the teeth spitting gag for a young Michael.
Also, I didn't realize they would have legit bands play at Grad Night at Disneyland in the 80s.
Where they would deploy the high school graduation event at Disneyland.
And now that's a month long event. So it would be impossible to book incredible bands for every night of that.
But it was more limited in the 80s. And I was seeing people shout out on a message.
I was lurking and I found people saying, who played at your Grad Night? Expose and Zap. Crazy legit.
And my favorite one was that Cheap Trick performed on Tom Sawyer Island where Fantasmic now takes place.
Cheap Trick playing over the river. How cool is that?
That is awesome. This is not quite as cool, but I think for New Year's two years ago, Big Bad Voodoo Daddy played in New Orleans Square.
And that's not a joke.
So they still have hot young bands.
That sounds too crazy to be true.
No, no, believe it.
Now they've kind of shifted. I mean, Epcot every year has free bands play during one of the festivals.
The Food and Wine Festival. I believe it's called Eat to the Beat.
Eat to the Beat. Yeah.
And then...
Lineups are crazy amazing. Like I was there three months ago and they have this schedule.
And it's like the Pointer Sisters. Like huge names.
The Naked Ladies.
Rick Springfield maybe.
And then Universal always in Orlando does a big Mardi Gras thing.
And they always have free bands and theirs tend to be pretty good too.
Like Jason Derulo is doing it this year and it's just included in your park admission.
Our list of who we have considered cool bands at this point is so...
Really spanned.
All over the map.
Robin Thicke and Jefferson Starship.
And all the coolest bands.
Two of the four Boys to Men.
The Mormon Tabernacle Choir.
Wally Bogue's Daughter.
Anyway, I want to shout out specifically the band that you were most likely to see at Vitiopolis on a Disneyland Summer.
That played a half hour of cover tunes every night.
Of course, everybody at home say with me, Donna McDaniel and network.
We all know Donna McDaniel riding high from the success of her film Hollywood Hot Tubs.
Have you seen Hollywood Hot Tubs?
It seems like something you would have run into.
Yes. I have a video somewhere in my garage as well as the sequel Hollywood Hot Tubs 2.
Hollywood Hot Tubs 2.
Teaching, it's a name. Like teaching Donna or something.
Anyway, she would play...
And I found an article that was a little complaining in the LA Times about like...
I don't know about this unsavory lyrics and this element.
They're singing songs and they clearly quote the lyrics of Jungle Love.
That's presented as the trashiest song.
Funny enough in that video, Pebble says she's going on tour with Morris Day.
Oh, hey.
Morris Day ever hit the Disneyland circuit?
Oh, that's an interesting question.
He still could.
I think that's possible.
New Year's Eve with Morris Day in New Orleans Square.
Sounds like a blast.
I'd like to see DeBarge perform at the Tomorrowland Terrace.
That would be amazing.
If they're still around.
They are. They performed...
Really?
They were making those rounds this past summer.
Oh, no kidding.
Because I feel like the scoop on DeBarge is always like...
Well, one of them was passed out under the freeway.
They've had some serious...
If you want to get the full scoop, I recommend the DeBarge episode of Unsung,
which is an amazing TV show I'll throw out there.
Kind of like the BBC-produced version of Behind the Music.
Ah, gotcha.
But focusing on the type of R&B and 80s one-hit wonders
that were never popular enough to get their own episode of Behind the Music.
They'll cover it.
Shouldn't be overlooked. Like the Whispers, wonderful band.
The Whispers, yeah.
Zzap, which is an amazing heartbreaking story.
Oh, okay.
Did the vocoder tube get caught down his throat?
Oh, boy, it did it, unfortunately.
He was murdered. I found that out today.
That's horrible.
Jesus.
Sorry.
I just ruined your podcast. Sorry.
From the heights of Grad Night in 1989 to the lows of being murdered.
I didn't have a spot to bring this up earlier.
In researching for this episode, I found a videopolis.
I don't know if this is authentic merchandise from the time
or if it's a throwback pin, but it's a Disney lapel pin
featuring one of my favorite versions of Mickey, 80s Mickey.
Oh, yeah, I know.
This is casual 80s Mickey, not businessman Mickey.
Hell, yeah.
And he's looking real sleazy, this 80s Mickey.
He's ready for a night out at videopolis.
Pomped collar, half-down eyelids, sly look into the side.
Yeah, I know.
Hands in pockets. There's a lot of tells about this guy.
Maybe if he's in the corner of videopolis, don't go up to him.
The rival camp.
The rival rich kid camp.
Yeah, yeah.
That's another interesting thing because a couple summers ago,
they introduced a version of Mickey at the parks called Hipster Mickey.
Oh, God, I've seen this.
Yeah, and he's got glasses on and he's very nonplussed
and he's looking at a phone and he's got a backpack on.
And every time...
Wait, this is at the parks?
Yeah, it's on the parks.
You've never seen Hipster Mickey?
No, no, no, no.
Yeah, he's on merchandise and stuff.
It's at the Wonderland Gallery.
I'm sure you've seen him.
He's not yet a walk-around character.
Thank God I'd smack that phone out of his hands.
Look me in the eye, Mickey.
I want to get a picture with the Mickey who won't stop fucking with his iPhone
and reading a Tao Lin novel.
Shout out to Brooklyn literary scene piece of shit, Tao Lin.
I don't know.
The current Mickey's fun and nice and all,
but I don't know where he stands on Pod Save America.
Is he a fan or not?
Hipster Mickey's much more of a Chapo trap house listener, I think.
Does he like Cum Town?
I think you're just putting your socialist beliefs on this Hipster Mickey.
You're projecting the socialist Mickey you want.
There is no way that Hipster Mickey did not pledge to the Sanders campaign.
Hipster Mickey definitely donated to the Sanders campaign.
I don't know about that.
He feels more like a hashtag resistance kind of guy to me.
I'll be honest.
He was more of a centrist.
A mainstream Democrat.
He was a mainstream Democrat.
Anyway, so Hipster Mickey, when we all saw it on shirts and stuff,
we all went, oh, this sucks.
And it felt like a new thing.
Like, oh, look what they're doing with Mickey now.
But obviously with this videopolis thing,
I think if you were walking around then and you were, you know,
a grumpy person in their thirties, you'd go, oh, oh, gross.
Look what they're doing on Mickey now.
Like, and now it feels again, this is,
I guess now we're learning that this is all just cyclical.
Everything happens over and over and over again.
And it feels like a new thing.
So, you know, good point.
Thank you.
I'm trying to make a point about the Skywalker family.
Yeah.
These same things repeat.
Except that they cut off the Skywalker family in these new movies and it's
not about the Skywalker family anymore, but that's a different story.
We have to mention the Totally Minnie, which was a huge thing.
Yes, that's true.
It was the new cool Minnie that they were selling around that same time.
There was a TV special called Totally Minnie starring Suzanne Somers,
which I highly recommend.
I watched that together.
Maybe not Jason.
I don't think you were there, but did we?
Yeah, I think we had a wild weekend with a drunken viewing of the...
Just the boys watching Totally Minnie.
Oh, gosh.
This podcast has just entered evidence in a courtroom.
Jason, here's Minnie.
Here's what Minnie looked like.
Welcome back to haunted.
Yeah, Minnie was also susceptible to the 80s fashions, of course.
But I think that 80s Minnie is cooler than 80s Mickey.
Yeah, for sure.
And 80s Minnie kind of...
I feel like current hipsters still look like 80s Minnie.
We'll tweet out this photo, see if you agree.
But I feel like it reminds me of the recent Cardi B performance
of Finesse on the Grammys.
I might not know Cardi B's style other than when she was retro with Bruno Mars.
80s women's fashions are a lot more fun and come back around.
They feel like a lot more than 80s men's Wall Street or Ralph Lauren polo wear,
which is exhausting.
80s men's wear is exhausting.
Like the hard, hard, slicked back hair, which you only see make a comeback
with the Trump children.
They're such...
It never went away for them.
They're still living their...
They're living their father's youth.
The 80s never stopped.
They're yuppies from birth.
What have we missed?
Well, I guess we're getting towards the end.
So the sad demise of Vidiopolis.
Well, you know, one thing before we get to the end.
So there was kind of the step one of controversy,
which is the same-sex dancing.
Before Vidiopolis opened, there was that Tomorrowland rise-up stage,
as we talked about.
And in the early 80s, two young gentlemen were dancing with each other there
and were asked to stop by a security guard.
They ignored him, started again, then they were asked to leave the park.
They sued Disneyland.
Sorry, according to the defunctland video,
they described it as homosexual fast dancing.
Jesus.
This is a long way...
Again, we phrase this place.
We love that they spy on people.
They use phrases like homosexual fast dancing.
It's a very gay-friendly park.
There's a long time before gay days.
And it switches in the course of this controversy
because they ban homosexual dancing.
But then it goes back and forth.
It's in court.
And then Disney's trying to pretend that that's not really why we're banning it.
Very confusing.
Then they said, according to the...
I can't say the word defunctland, apparently.
They didn't want two women to dance because it would have excited the men too much.
So they were trying to do some weird work around to say,
no, that's not why. We're not anti-gay or anything.
Whereas, as all this is happening,
then Studio K and Cloud 9 opened to Knotts,
which according to my research, very gay-friendly from the beginning.
Legitimately a place where gay teenagers in Orange County could feel comfortable
and not get hassled and a lot of the DJs were gay.
So, seemingly, Knotts was way ahead of it and cooler way before Disney was.
Yeah, so then eventually in the defunctland thing,
it shows a newspaper article that says,
Gays Can Dance at Disneyland.
That wasn't their ad campaign.
Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
Randy Hamilton announced it on the show.
Gays Can Dance in Disneyland.
Okay.
That's what you kids are into.
Look, I'll look the other way. I won't be there.
It's not my thing, but whatever.
That other DJ we mentioned being on the screen at...
Swedish Eagle?
Yes, Swedish Eagle.
Also dressed very similar to Randy Hamilton.
E-G-I-L, by the way.
Oh, weird.
Yeah, I know. It's weird.
Very confusing.
But anyway, so by the time Videopolis opened in summer of 1871,
in 1885, they were cool about it.
They did, like, yeah, they had switched their policy, which is great.
But then, but they, but different issues arose at the play, at Videopolis.
I'm not, I'm actually not as familiar with this.
There were, there was an incident in the parking lot.
Like, like they, like there were gang affiliations.
Several, supposedly several high profile gang related incidents
in the old Disneyland parking lot.
Which you did Mickey and Friends.
You have to do a whole episode about the old.
Yeah, yeah, we'll get to that. Don't worry.
But, yeah, one involved, like, a 15 year old kid being stabbed to death.
It was horrible.
So that quickly went away.
It is, it is interesting, as you mentioned, Jason,
that this is around the same time that Pleasure Island opened.
So I kind of feel like maybe Eisner took what,
the lessons that he had learned from Videopolis
and brought it to Orlando.
Well, Pleasure Island, I remember being at Pleasure Island a lot as a kid.
Like every trip we would go at least once or twice.
And it was, I, again, I never saw Videopolis,
but like Pleasure Island was like secure, pretty secure
and like pretty tame walking around outside the clubs.
It was not all ages like Videopolis was, correct?
No, everything, well, a lot of it was.
Ease was of all ages.
Most of the venues were 21 and over, correct?
At certain times, like I remember going to the comedy warehouse
like in middle school and also to,
I talked a lot on the show about going to the Adventurers Club.
I could not go alone, obviously.
I had to have an adult with me.
But then there were certain ones, like I think, was mannequins the one?
There were some of them where it was like, no kids.
Like this is an actual nightclub.
But I never felt weird walking around Pleasure Island.
It was always pretty safe and sanitized.
If the Adventurers Club were still open, you could and would go there alone.
Yes, I would just not be in Hollywood.
I would just work there.
You would be a performer.
I would live there in the building and also work there.
Was there, is there a character that you could have,
I'm not familiar with the Adventurers Club,
but if you had to pick a role to play.
I, there was, there was definitely an old man
and there was definitely a jolly scientist
that I probably could have played in my chubbier phases.
So if you were auditioning, you could say,
I also have a take on the jolly scientist?
Or if, I believe the general was an animatronic or a puppet of some kind.
So not open to casting?
Probably not.
But that would be ideal.
That's too bad.
If you promised to stay there all the time and stand real still,
maybe they would have hired you and replaced the robot.
For sure.
Just to not, just to lose those hydraulic oil fees.
Yes, I cost much less than hydraulic oil.
Your oil, your normal oil is cheaper than hydraulic oil.
Yeah, yeah. I'm a canola boy myself.
Okay, so with gang activity and, you know, issues concerning Disney,
they shut the place down, but obviously they kept the infrastructure of it
and still that initial base of videopolis they built
is the Fantasyland Theater.
It was a Beauty and the Beast show for many years
and the spirit of Pocahontas with a talking grandmother willow,
a very impressive puppet.
One of my favorite things as a young child,
the Plain Crazy show as part of the Disneyland afternoon avenue promotion,
you know, with some great, I put it on last night,
a killer song between Fat Cat and Don Karnage.
It was great to pair up a couple of the great villains.
But anyway, I said that weird, but I meant it.
I am like, yeah, it's really good. It was cool to see them.
But so, yeah, that place is still there
and they've done a good job of folding it into Fantasyland,
but you know, you can't help but miss what once was
and Disney's legit entry into cool youth culture.
Yeah.
I think they did a good job. I don't know.
I think it does sound like some people either you get a spectrum,
some people say not as cool as the Knotts Clubs,
not as permissive as the Knotts Clubs,
but other people seems like had a lot of great summers hanging out at videopolis.
We need to find some older us's that were there.
So let's maybe in the audience at this point,
there are a few older us's and they could tell us what it was like,
like what was the cool, like what was the scene like,
what would you go to both?
Did you get much out of your friend who,
like were there any weird details that he told you about the place?
No, unfortunately I didn't press him at the time.
I had no idea what I was about to stumble onto.
It was just something that was casually mentioned.
I've enjoyed watching the video photo montages on YouTube that people have made.
Some people have saved like a hundred photos from the videopolis years
and have uploaded them to YouTube in the form of a slideshow with like 80s music.
And I find that quite delightful to watch.
That and the one hour unedited Take It to the Top video that's on YouTube
do make you feel like you were there as much as possible.
And you posted as part of your article from that long unedited video,
you posted like a set list of some of what was played at a random rate.
A sample playlist, yeah.
Which as we said had some great stuff.
You heard Pleasure Principle and David Bowie, Time Will Crawl and Depeche Mode.
It's a cool list. Yeah, I don't know, legit stuff.
I feel like they were actually letting these DJs play what they wanted
as opposed to a DJ White Rabbit who probably had to have anything he wanted to play,
had to probably be approved in their gold boxes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a real clear channel situation.
I feel like this is probably one of the best examples of a thing we've talked about before
where we do think about these parks as like an escape from the real world,
but they definitely exist in the context of their times.
Just like the parks now exist in our current craft cocktail brew pub hell that we live in.
I don't know why I said it like that. I like it.
What's wrong with the craft cocktail?
It is a little exhausting.
As long as the thing I want to keep out of the parks is politics.
As long as there aren't town halls being held at the fake town hall.
Like Mr. Knotts used to have.
Yeah, yeah, I don't want any pamphlets.
Bring back the Freedom Center. That's what I say.
But I would like to say also, you were very cool to put at that playlist
to transcribe what you'd hear at a night of videobolus.
I looked at a bunch of other comments and message board posts
to see the kind of thing that they played at videopolis.
I made a playlist on Spotify that's almost two hours long.
That is what you might hear.
Hopefully two hours that take you into the world of videopolis
and we'll tweet that out when the episode comes out.
That's a little gift from me to you, the podcast, the ride fan.
Go disappear mentally into videopolis for a little while,
as I would like to forever.
A lot of good stuff that we will have to combine our notes
and tweet out for this one, because the pictures
and the marketing material is really cool.
It can't be described by words.
Yeah, it cannot.
Not really. We can't explain just how creepy Mickey looks in this pan.
And the wonderful Everything is Terrible videos
that you are responsible for.
Thank you.
Absolutely, yeah. We'll definitely tweet that out.
And hey, well, I don't know, with all that being said,
I think Doug Jones, you survived podcast the ride.
Awesome.
Thanks so much for being here.
Any closing thoughts or anything you'd like to promote
or make people aware of?
Everything is Terrible on tour now,
the great Satan tour coming to a city to you.
You're the first guest with a tour to promote.
That's so exciting.
Drunk History season five, it's back in Better Than Ever.
Oh, yeah, you were in episode two,
and you told a tale that Bob Odenkirk acts out.
The tale of who?
WC Minor, the murderer who wrote the Oxford English Dictionary.
Oh, right.
No, but he was actually a good guy.
You'll see when you watch it.
It's a great tale, very well and drunkenly told by you.
Thank you.
Yeah, please check out, look up Dante Fontana
and everything you've done in the Disneyland remix world.
You've made me aware of so much of the crazy, weird pop culture collisions
that have happened at the parks.
You've made me aware of a lot of cool stuff.
That Pablo Cruz thing that I talked about for a while
on the Pablo Cruz playing Worlds Away.
I was in Reno, Nevada, like two years ago
and just wandering through the casinos,
and it was like, tomorrow night, 10 p.m., Pablo Cruz.
They are still doing their thing.
And Reno looks like Videopolis.
That's a locked in time kind of place.
Thanks for not changing.
Thanks for maybe not having the option to change, Reno.
Much appreciated.
Well, fellas, closing thoughts.
We didn't rank the thing.
I just want Videopolis sounds.
The only thought I had is if you work in Disney,
and I don't know if it would be Imagineering or Events or something,
that Hollywood lot is open.
Why is there not just a bunch of Videopolis retro nights at this point?
I mean, it's just all you're doing is you want to suck money out of people like us,
and you've been doing it so well, let's suck even more money out of us.
Let's do the Videopolis nights.
Because they do these ticketed events now, which are crazy, and you go,
well, why would I do that with the annual pass?
But if it was Videopolis, how much?
I want to say, I mean, my actual answer is like $70.
It's not an incredible, I should say, all the money in the world.
I could tell you, I just invested $150 in a reservation for the Saved By the Bell.
Oh, the max.
Saved By the Max, which won't happen until
the end of 2018.
That's the recreated restaurant?
Is that also going in next to a Mendocino Farms, right?
I feel like I walked by the build. Is it in West Hollywood?
It is in West Hollywood.
I think it's next to the Boiling Crab.
Yeah, it's next to the Target.
So then you're right.
That's weird.
So that's where the max is.
I think it's in between a BevMo and a Mendocino Farms sandwiches.
Hey, maybe the rent was cheap there. That was the best they could do.
Yeah, noted cheap rent spot West Hollywood.
So yeah, Disney's listening. We will spend our hard-earned money on something like that.
And looking down the line, I'm telling you, Dazzlers Videopolis.
If we get those X-Men sorted out, it's right there in front of you.
It's really good. I don't, look, I can't start thinking too far ahead,
but the idea of like somehow off of the podcast,
you Jason being brought in to consult on Dazzlers Videopolis.
I mean, if you go back to her first appearance and the Hellfire Club is trying to interrupt it,
and then the X-Men and Dazzlers stop them, and now it's,
now let's get back to the tunes.
I mean, it's right to itself.
Wait, so there's like stories unfolding between the songs and your vision?
Like maybe instead of some DJ who's married?
This might get cut, you know, as we start to look at budgets.
Like the Hellfire Club and their goons invading.
You mean like Sebastian Shaw will interrupt the dance party?
Because Dazzlers first appearance was in the Hellfire Club Phoenix stories.
Yes, of course.
So yeah, but she was a cosmic singing superstar.
Eventually, yeah. Well, no, that's Lila Chaney.
What?
Lila Chaney was the inner-factor.
Dazzler wasn't a singer?
No, Dazzler was a singer, but on Earth. This is too complicated.
You guys, you're speaking Japanese to me.
I don't know what's being said, but I like the sound of it.
And whatever it all means, get it all into the park is what I say.
If you want to hear all about us arguing about Dazzler, tune into the after show.
Yeah, tune into the after show.
We're going to end up with a dense network at some point.
On Podcast Network the Ride.
Podcast Network the Ride.
I've been seeing more and more Powerline World Tour t-shirts at Disneyland lately.
I did just see one two days ago.
So why not do that? He could come back.
That's good too.
He would fit right in.
Boy, you start with the Videopolis song, you close with Powerline.
Eye to Eye.
That's a, oh man.
That really works.
They play that at some club at Disneyland. Everybody loses their minds.
Is there anything else? Are there any other cool Disney songs?
If those are considered cool.
Eye to Eye is a cool song.
Like if you get an EDM guy to remix some Annette Funicello songs.
There is to have that.
There's a techno version of I Can't Do The Sum from Babes in Toyland.
Yeah, I want to hear that.
Where's that remix? Where's that plussed up Monkey's Uncle with the Beach Boys, Annette Funicello?
What's this? DJ Khaled has remixed, yeah, Monkey's Uncle?
Featuring Mike Love.
Oh yeah, he's still around. He's there. His vocals are heavily auto-tuned as it is.
They would never do that because they would have to cut him in on the hat sales.
Well, look, we're throwing a lot of great ideas out there.
And they're there for the taking. We will not get upset if you use our ideas. We will just be delighted.
As long as we get to participate in them and enjoy them and waste our money experiencing them.
So yes, all that. And if you can help us achieve these dreams, then tweet at us at Podcast The Ride.
Hit us up on Instagram at Podcast The Ride. Email us at PodcastTheRide at Gmail.com.
Yeah, if you're an Imagineer and you want to go off the record, just DM or email and be like,
here's what's going on and here's what I'm going to try to give Videopolis back.
And we'll work some sort of shadow campaign with you to get this thing back.
DMs are open, folks. DMs are open on the show account.
And for me. And all my personal account.
For dating purposes. Well, we have a chance here to create the place to take dates and then you get to go there.
I'm thinking several steps ahead.
That's great.
Well, hey everybody, this was a blast. Thanks for going to the top with us. I think we made it rock here on Podcastopolis.
Thanks everybody. See you next time.
Thank you. Bye.