Warning, today's episode features the ominous rise of a powerful political regime, terrifying
Vietnam-esque flashbacks involving Ernest P. Worrell, and four white guys nervously
tiptoeing around a weird old racist movie.
Anthony Gio takes the plunge on Splash Mountain.
How do you do?
It's Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the amusement park podcast hosted by three men who've been
collectively soaked in at least 100 gallons of dirty theme park water.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
And Scott Gairdner.
Hey, I got splashed the other day at Universal very unpleasantly at The Simpsons ride.
It felt like just a literal slap in the face made out of water.
It was gross.
Still reeling and I hope there's no boils on my cheek that you can see and I haven't
noticed.
There's enough chlorine in that, I'm sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It doesn't matter.
It's dirty, but it's free of germs, I think.
It's a specified kind of dirty they created.
Yes, and today we're joined by a very special guest.
You know him from Pop TV's Return of the Mac and as a writer on People of Earth, it's Anthony
Gio, ladies and gentlemen.
Hey, guys.
I gotta say, before we even get started, I am so honored to be here.
I'm a big fan of the podcast.
I think it's great.
Thank you.
It's the only, I have a short commute right now and it's the only one I make time.
Oh, thank you so much.
So just like in, at, our typical episodes have been like two and a half hours lately,
so you're getting through them in like five weeks since.
Yeah, I've listened to the preview so far.
Sure.
Well, hey, eat shit this American life.
Get down.
Get down in one car at least.
Well, we're very happy to have you.
We're excited because this is a great topic.
It's a weird topic.
We're talking Splash Mountain.
Yeah.
So, yeah, there's a ton to talk about there.
Before though, before we start, I do want to get your sort of viewpoint on this and
I have a few ideas.
It starts sort of with a sad story and the mayor of Main Street in Orlando, there is
a position basically for cast members where someone is actually the mayor of Disney World
or Disneyland.
Right, right.
My girlfriend, Lindsay, and I found this out a couple of years ago.
We went to, I think it was like the 59th anniversary and they have all the characters come out.
It's a big celebration.
And then all of a sudden this man in a top hat comes out and they go, introducing the
mayor of Disneyland.
And we were like, the mayor of Disneyland?
Right.
Like we were very surprised to see that this is a position.
Is he the guy that, I was there in 2012 at Disney World, is he the guy that welcomes
Casey Jr. and opens the park or is that a different position?
That might be right.
I actually don't know all of his duties as mayor.
But it seems like that would be a position.
But the sad news is that the man who played the mayor, who was the mayor, Christopher
George Weaver, passed away in December.
Of Disney World?
Of Disney World.
So I had not seen this gentleman.
I saw a different gentleman and I'm not sure his name.
The Disneyland mayor.
Yeah.
But the thing that I thought, Lindsay and I thought when we saw the Disneyland mayor
was, wouldn't it be perfect in a few years time if our very own Jason Sheridan could
become a Disneyland mayor?
The Disneyland mayor.
I mean, I'm open to Orlando as well, but since he lives in Los Angeles, I, yeah, I can't
think of someone better.
As long as he can stay awake, he can have the job.
Like, hey, look, there's multiple apartments in the park.
So if I cannot stay awake, take a little power nap, have a cup of coffee.
I'm right back in it.
Oh yeah.
You'd probably live up in Walt's old apartment above the fire station.
Yeah, the old apartment and a nice summer in the dream suite.
Which is now just the dining room.
So I guess I just put a pillow on a long dining room table.
Wouldn't be the first time you did that.
Hey, all right.
Jason, you would have this like astronomical, uh, ascension into this amazing position and
then you would be embroiled in some sort of, you'd be like indicted for like stealing churros
or something like something would happen where like you, yeah, yeah, like they would just
like come down to this like huge controversy.
I've slowly been making a chef's Oscars, a famous famous potatoes with peppers and onions
have less and less peppers selling them off to another party.
And a massive pepper smuggling scandal.
Laundering peppers.
Laundering breakfast peppers.
What would you say, Jason, what would you do?
Like, I'm guessing there are like a list of like type of things that the mayor does do.
It sounds like there's some ceremonial type duties.
I think that's what I probably, that was right.
I mean, I think it's a position where he's in the park a lot.
Probably an opening.
Yeah.
Every morning I think.
Uh huh.
And Casey jr comes at least on big day, especially important days.
Yeah.
So what would you know?
Casey jr is a fantasy land.
Yeah.
Casey railroad.
Oh, I'm thinking Casey jr too.
I bet he like, oh, I'll be checking.
Well, that'll be Jason's thing.
Cause that's Jason's favorite train at Disney.
So no, probably hitting like the Casey jr each morning with a bottle of champagne.
Oh yeah.
That's the only alcohol in the park outside club 33 is when I just am constantly dedicating,
rededicating stuff by my own volition.
Why isn't he throwing a bottle of champagne and get some work towing in the middle of
the afternoon.
Yeah.
Hey, who's up for a dedication?
You kid, you look like you could smash a bottle or two.
You know, I have to say, I think my, uh, well first off I would wear a sash at all times
like mayor Quimby.
That's a given, right?
Just one at least one.
Let's up the gaze.
Sashes just on your arms, wrists, legs, sashes, top hat with its own sash.
Uh, you know, I think I want to be a mayor of the people, you know, I think I'd be inspired
by the, the Jeremy Corbyn campaign for the many, not the field.
Okay.
Wait a minute here.
So I would like to make some socialist mayor of the first democratic socialist of America,
mayor of Disneyland.
Uh, you know, the millennial voters I think will get behind me and I would like to make
radical changes.
One, the Mark Twain runs at night so everyone could enjoy riverboat ride after fantastic
to the vehicles of main street.
Never stop running.
They stop, they stop when it gets as the crowds get more in the day, no more.
We got to figure out a crowd solution so we can keep the Omni bus going.
And today 1130 at night, everybody's leaving from fireworks and the, that thing's got a
thicker bus through still going.
They go during the fireworks.
We figure we need to find a new place to send off fireworks from so that we can keep attractions
open during fireworks so we can experience them from a new viewpoint.
These are the sorts of radical positions that will be in my platform.
I mean, this is, I mean, I, I ambush Jason with this, but he has all this stuff ready
to go.
This is so serious.
He is, he has all of these viewpoints already.
He'll be the first socialist mayor of Disneyland.
I'll go one more.
I got more.
Okay.
Uh, the Gibson girl ice cream parlor.
Either we need to up the quality of that ice grids, delicious ice cream, but I think we
could do better.
It's the happiest place on earth or if not more varieties of Edie's dryers ice cream
available for purchase.
You know, that kind of, uh, I'll say I, you have my vote if we can get dryers.
I feel like I can, it takes me out of it sometimes.
I almost want them just to lie to me and be like, this is made here.
I, there are certain parts of the park where I see like, Oh, dryers.
Like, you know, that's the, the, the frostiest one at Albertson that like no one picks your
outsourcing instead of using a Disneyland local.
Yeah.
Want more jobs on site, more jobs on site, more flavors in mouth.
I will taste as many flare.
I will say I will not rest until I tasted all of the treats.
Uh, universal students, Hollywood just up their game.
They have all these crazy saucer flavors now, expensive milkshakes with like, you know,
sauce and donuts.
Voodoo don't need to strike back.
We need to strike back.
Also ballast point brewery.
You're on notice.
You're opening soon, but you're, you're very expensive at grocery stores.
I better not see that sort of thing in downtown Disney.
And it better be flavors like pina colada beer and cotton candy beer.
I want sweet treats.
I'm okay with that.
They're actually one of the brewers that do fruit beers reasonably well.
All right, so we're off to a good start, but we're on you ballast point.
This is the most awake I've seen him.
You're literally reclined on a couch next to a puppy.
With a dog at my feet.
It's like the carousel of progress.
This is like John and the carousel of progress.
But if I had a day bed.
Well you're in dry uncle Orville mode is what you're in.
Yeah.
Shout out to recent animatronic of the month winner, uncle Orville.
Uncle Orville won.
We had lovely fan art of me.
Kat to make the Mark Twain.
Oh boy.
Yeah, you're riding high.
You're kicking back, enjoying the fruits of your success.
Yeah.
So what you want to do as mayor.
So when the scandal goes down, Jason, well I'll assume churros, but you know, it could
be maybe the bell peppers.
And special counsel Tony Baxter indicts you.
What is that going to maybe do to your feelings towards your great land?
Would you be willing to talk to him though?
You'd be willing to sit down with him?
Have a conversation?
You know, I would, well first off I'll default to my team of attorneys.
And then I would probably.
Goofy and Clarabelle.
Jason's in better shape than any mayor of Disneyland has been, says Dr. Cogsworth.
The fittest mayor of all time.
And that is just in.
Jason Demine Spinlock is nothing but an aide that had nothing to do with his counsel.
And then yeah, I would much like in the Iran Contra, other people took the fall to shield
Reagan.
I would, yes, Spinlock is going down.
The timekeeper, unfortunately though he's been enjoying his retirement.
Sorry timekeeper.
You're doing some time.
The Disneyland marching band refused to perform at your inauguration ceremony.
You got three doors down.
Joy Villa is there plenty though.
She is there constantly in a different Main Street USA garish dress.
You can call me Sheridan.
Customized song for you.
This is a very exciting idea.
So we're just, maybe we'll throw it to the listeners.
Like Jason for maybe we do a hashtag.
Is it Jason for mayor or Jason for Disneyland?
What Mr. Mayor, what would you think?
You have a preference?
Yeah.
I mean I like, I think Jason for Disneyland.
Jason for with a number four.
Yeah.
Jason for Disneyland.
Okay.
Is probably pretty distinctive.
Yeah.
Mayor need to factor in?
Mayor Jason for, I don't know.
It's gotta be simple.
Well, yeah.
Well, I mean Jason for Disneyland mayor, I guess.
Well it be because it goes beyond just being mayor.
It's Jason for all of Disneyland.
Oh yeah.
I give to all.
That's you representing.
Yeah.
Jason for mayor DLR, Disneyland Resort.
Okay.
Yeah.
Jason for DLR.
Jason, because you're Disneyland first.
You're going to be the one to put Disneyland first.
Just to be clear, whatever we land on, people are just tweeting this?
That's it.
And that's the exact, that's how it's going to have to happen.
Yeah.
No one is tagged.
In another way, like if you went to Disneyland and put a letter into the box, if there's
a box at city hall, maybe we need to go and step.
Maybe there's needs to be an in-person campaign.
And this doesn't have to be tomorrow.
This doesn't have to be in five years.
I'm talking in 20 years.
Oh yeah.
Right.
When you look like a mayor for sure.
Like you'll look like a mayor.
Yeah.
Movements don't happen overnight.
This is a long game, you know?
So I would like a written agreement from Disneyland that you will be installed as mayor or at
least a fair election will happen.
Yeah.
In a Conan J. Tonight Show-esque situation in five years when the current mayor steps
down as number one mayor.
He's agreed to it.
Yeah, yeah.
And he'll do the handover, no problem.
There'll be no funny business.
Nine months, it'll still be Jason.
Don't worry.
Yeah.
And I want same day registration.
I want open elections, same day party change.
You know?
Sure.
I also, another agenda I want to put on your radar, I think you should try to bring the
Olympics to Disneyland.
Disneyland Olympics 2036.
That's an excellent, and it's, we know from Olympics coming to any city, it's great for
the economy.
It's great for quality of life.
Right.
And long-term wellbeing.
Breathing.
It helps the air pollution.
And Disneyland could use a new swimming arena and ropes.
Absolutely.
And if there's one thing Disneyland could use more of, it's money.
And we've seen already with the Disneyland, when they had the circus early nineties that
they're able to put in different acts.
There was a promotion, what do you like 91 or 92, somewhere around there, right?
Where they had circus performers doing circus acts just in the middle of Disneyland.
Did you go Scott during that time?
No, I missed that.
Okay.
I think there was like, there was a state fair theme for a little while, like one summer.
And then I think there was also a more extreme circus, like with the motorcycles in the cage
on Main Street.
Oh yeah, I think so.
And then some of the older Imagineers were like, we can't do this.
So you're telling me a real nitro circus.
Yes, something along a nitro circus X game sort of line.
Weirdest hour, you were reminding us via Twitter about the Disneyland Pogs promotion.
Maybe this is your chance to start in another Pogs too.
Oh, this is the time to bring back a Pog Wild and Rollerblade Crazy.
That's the spring break promotion at Disney World in the mid 90s.
This is a perfect thing for you to campaign on.
When Jason is mayor, there will be, we will go Pog Crazy again.
We have forgotten, we have forgotten our past.
We have forgotten just how wild Pogs are and how crazy Rollerblades are.
So much so that Scott, Disneyland expert, thought it was Pog Crazy, not Pog Wild.
We all don't remember our heritage.
Yeah, it's time to change that.
There's so much, and I think we can build up a lot of platforms.
Sure.
A new, new deal for Main Street.
Great.
How do we, can we all sort of pick a role within, I think you as the first, I think
you're the Bannon of, oh yeah, you're the, you're the, I'm going to be, you're my buddy,
Steve Bannon.
He's the smartest man and I'm the smartest man too.
Masterminded his way out of Breitbart, just like he wanted, just like the plan was.
He's a Machiavellian genius.
I will be much the same.
Five dimensional chess for Mike.
And maybe when Jason gets installed, people will be like, oh my God, it's a coup.
These guys know what they're doing.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
So Mike's chief of staff slash body man.
What else do we need?
I mean, I can be a Kellyanne Conway.
I can be out there sort of, you know, on the, on the morning shows on, I'll be on the hotel
TVs reminding everyone what a great job you're doing.
Sure.
In press guy, communications guy, right?
Telling people to buy your clothing brands to buy your, your varieties of wine, polos,
the shirt and Tommy Bahama.
That's too expensive.
No outlet Tommy Bahama.
Tommy Bahama at the Nordstrom.
Jason Bahama.
They're beautiful shirts.
Tommy's younger brother.
Perfect quality for half the price.
And then that voice is that sort of a Conway.
I'm trying to do a little bit of a generic smarmy woman, but kind of Conway.
I thought you were trying to do the Coke boy, the son of one of the Coke boy.
Do you know that guy?
One of the brothers adult son has like a very garish clothing line.
It's like Hawaiian to say these kinds of things.
But like I, this is what I think.
He looks insane.
Like his, yeah, his, he looks like a fake person.
Like he's like a cabbage man and the shirt and every shirt has like three or at least
different patterns on it.
It'll be like a Hawaiian shirt, but then a Helm's tooth collar and the cuffs are a different
color.
It's what like rich people think fun attire is.
It's at all.
It's not tasteful like normal Hawaiian shirts.
No.
Or like my many mayoral sashes will be.
Yeah.
You'll have the palm tree or two on this.
Are you kidding?
Yeah.
It'll still, it's so not tasteful.
It'll be the new taste.
I don't know if it's too early to call for more fan art, but.
Oh yeah.
No, no, no.
Where are the podcasts that demands it?
I think that if we're asking for more fan art, I think it's Jason in a mayoral outfit, which
I picture like, like a big like top hat, like, like, I guess like was wall double cobble
pot from the Batman Returns, a Turkey leg at the podium in front of the train.
Instead of, it's a press conference with many microphones, but instead they're all Turkey
legs that you fit in, you take with you and eat when conferences over.
Maybe a chimichanga.
I really legitimately liked the chimichangas.
That's a great snack.
You can get to walk around with.
Uh, Anthony, where do you want to factor into this campaign or if you had to say a Trump
equivalent, Trump equivalent, cause I'm just a guest from any master for many Kevin.
No, but I think you're, you were here for the Rob Lowe kind of liaison sort of like
you are my voice on the Hill.
Rob Lowe is a part of the Trump administration.
No, no.
I mean it West Wing turns West Wing.
You get caught having sex at the DNC.
I was going to say, cause I'm a guest, like I was like maybe just fitting.
I'd be like a Michael Flynn.
I'm in and I'm out.
I'm like, a scared mooch.
Papadopoulos maybe?
A Papadopoulos.
If Ursula had done a 10th of the things, if I'd done a 10th of the things Ursula has done,
I'd be in some sea jail today.
So let's see.
Uh, man, well since I'm here just from the inception, I feel like, oh yeah, maybe I could
take a role of, um, uh, you know what I'd love to be?
I love to be when Jason's got to take his frequent naps.
I want to be the Stephen Miller that steps out and just maybe, maybe speaks on his behalf.
I think you are, I think you are my, the guy I send and when they, when you walk into the
California adventure city, they're like, oh shit.
Like, right.
When you show up at the Disneyland hotel, like, oh, business is going down.
Business is going down.
A fitted suit, a giant ass forehead and I'm walking in and I'm coming in and all of my
decisions are clearly, uh, catalyzed by grudges I held in high school.
Oh yeah.
No more, Walt's policy of Disney executives picking up their own trash.
Why should we do that?
When there's janitors to pick up the trash floor.
You're not picking up trash like Walt, Jason.
You're uh, no, you're above the peons.
So maybe if we bring it back to the hashtag, uh, I'd love for people to, I would love to
see as a fan, the drawings that come in, but I love maybe if we could check in on the hashtag
at some point, see like what do people want to see from Jason as an ideal candidate?
Well, yeah, transparency is important.
I mean, they are the people I work for them.
Yes.
You know, now Jason, will you open up your Wells Fargo account for all of us to see all
of your statements and whatnot?
Yeah.
Your credit cards, your, your bank account, your checking and your savings.
Uh, my domestic accounts.
Sure.
Fortunately, most of my money's overseas or at the Caymans.
I just can't get access to that.
Disney's private Cay as part of the, they're buried in a castaway Cay private Island.
It's a little bit buried at Aulani, but mostly it's in castaway Cay.
Yeah.
There is some gold, uh, there's some bullion buried.
Just in case things start to go south.
This all ends with you living on a cruise in international waters, a Disney cruise where
you can't be touched.
Weird how like the Disney magic docs like once a week, but the Disney dream never comes
into a domestic waters.
That's all about here.
I am a, and there's, it's maritime law.
I can do what I want and you have two dinners at the buffet and you have experience piloting
the Mark Twain so you can easily drive the dream.
Yeah.
If something, if there is a mutiny, I can take control.
I can lock myself in the break and take control of the ship.
Uh, all right, well there's a lot of plans.
There's a hidden Mickey Mickey at the cyanide capsule in my hollowed out molar.
He's gone catatonic.
Um, well look, if you're going to, if you are going to be successfully elected, you
need to start playing to all the districts.
And one of the areas that you will have jurisdiction over of course is critter country.
Absolutely.
So let's turn that.
Are you blue or you red?
I don't know what color, if you want to represent a color, what, what color do you want to,
uh, critter country to light up on your electoral map?
Oh, uh, well you're a socialist, so you're left leaning.
So I guess red.
Yeah.
See if you can get a small rose somewhere in those drawings too to represent our people
power.
Traditionally though, critter country is gone red.
So it shouldn't be a problem.
So that's the American definition of red in politics.
But to be honest, it's red, it red with the rose and it's, it's, it's my hand shaking
a bear paw to show, but if you guys, I don't want to cooperation, I don't want to get into
it, but if you've actually in like I'm saying actually looked at a map of critter country,
the gerrymandering of this place, it is insanity.
The hungry bear is like, like sides of the hungry bear top floor and bottom floor, separate
parts of district districts and the star Wars land is just going to keep, keep ruining it
further because there's a whole now trail.
That's where the money is.
They're going to start lobbying as soon as possible.
Well sounds like I've got a lot of work on my hands cleaning up this mess.
Hashtag Jason for DLR.
It just rolls off the tongue, Michael.
Great, great.
We'll see how it goes.
But hey, let's, well let's, let's start playing into your critter country constituents and
talk about splash mountain a little bit.
Here we go.
Uh, yeah.
So geo, you picked splash mountain.
Uh, what were you thinking?
Well, uh, I mean I might be wrong.
I'll be happy to hear from you guys, but like splash mountain to me, it feels like, and
this could be like me having been tainted from my childhood experience.
I feel it's like one of the big biggest rides.
Like I feel like it's like when you think of amusement parks, like splash mountain is,
is one of the, one of the big ones.
Um, but so I, uh, not to like weigh this down too much with a personal story.
When I first went to Disney world in 1994, uh, the geo family packed up their arrow star.
Uh, I think it did not have air conditioning.
Uh, and we made our way down to Florida.
Um, I was so excited, preemptively aware of and excited for a splash mountain because
I think they did a big TV special opening for it.
I would imagine like there was so much coverage, so much coverage cause they had spent so much
money on it.
I've come to learn.
And this was when they had like the ABC relationship big to like, like they like, I feel like Disney
around this way in our childhoods did like 12 specials a year.
Yes.
Burning through special money.
Every sitcom family on, on TGIF went to yes.
Without exception, without exception.
Pretty much dinosaurs, but right.
But excuse.
I mean they should have some equivalents.
Yeah.
I remember, uh, so just getting very excited for it.
I remember the special was about, uh, like the water wasn't running and they had a figure,
find some sort of magic to get the water run and I fucking ate it up.
I loved it.
I was like, I want to go to this magical place.
So we ended up getting down there and um, I had like voiced this to my fan, my dad.
He was like, all right, yeah, we'll head right to it.
Uh, and so we go to it.
And it was the type of vacation where we had one day in the magic kingdom.
Um, and then, you know, maybe at the time obviously Epcot was there, animal kingdom
was not there yet.
So like it was established like we have one day and we get to the ride and it's broken
down and it's out of order.
And I took it hard.
Like I was, I was just like a little kid and I, I just remember being like, well, like
I think I was just in denial.
I like went through the states of it.
I was like, well, no, it's not.
Uh, that signs temporary.
You know, like, well I'll wait around.
And like clearly my sister who's a little older than me, like she was still a kid.
She was like, what the fuck are we doing?
Let's move.
Like I want to go see stuff as well.
And I was like, oh no, no, this isn't happening.
And so I didn't ride it and I ha I didn't go back to Disney world until 2012.
Whoa.
So six, what, six plus?
Yeah.
So eight, you know, we're like 18 years later.
Uh, my family did our next Disney world trip cause my sister has children now and it, uh,
it was like a really big moment where like I got in line and like I took it in and there,
I will say like for a lot of great Disney rides do this, but, uh, the, uh, splash mountain
feels like it's a long ride.
Like it feels like an experience.
And like, I, I, this, I mean this doesn't like quite make sense, but like it feels like
you're getting your money's worth.
Like you don't pay obviously, but like you feel like you're really, uh, you're like settling
into this weird little story.
And I loved it and I love the smell of like the summer, like in like the outdoor air hitting
like that sweet chlorinated water that like may be the end of Scott as we've heard from
the couple of days from now.
And so it was oddly like obviously excited, but oddly, uh, it kind of snuck up on me emotionally
when I rode a splash mountain.
Well, interesting.
When I finally wrote it.
Were you wet by the end?
Were the, was, were you wet from tears?
I, you know, I, I, you know, honestly there was, you come out of the place sucks, so no
one can really say.
But you know, I surely probably did.
Had you not ridden at Disneyland?
No.
I've only been to Disneyland once and um, there, this was, so this is like kind of the
selfish part of the story.
I uh, I think I had the opportunity to maybe ride it at Disneyland.
I was like, no, it's gotta be, cause I knew there was a Disney world trip on the horizon.
Oh yeah.
You had to be that one.
Yeah.
So man, when you were little, did you like, cause you said the ride was closed in hindsight.
Was the ride for sure closed the whole day or was it just cause like the family wanted
to keep moving and you never returned?
Like do you remember if there was a full confirmation of this is shut down today or perhaps it was
shut down for half the day, you guys didn't return and you could have maybe ridden it.
That sounds totally possible.
I think we had, we had to keep moving and I think I was the kind of kid, uh, it sounds
like a, like my current company, a real wiener of a kid who uh, like wouldn't have spoken
up.
I don't know if he did feel like he wanted to like maybe go and check on it like, ah,
no, my fate is sealed.
Uh, this is the equivalent of it.
Like watching it like be demolished in slow motion.
Uh, you're watching it get blown up.
Big wrecking balls.
Right.
It's done.
It was really all hands on deck in terms of promoting splash mountain.
Splash mountain was so ubiquitous.
If you grew up in the nineties to the point where I feel like splash mountain in the same
way space mountain is in pop culture is almost used as a standard for the term theme parks
or like like in a monologue joke, they might just go like splash mountain.
Like when they mean like theme park.
Right.
It's become like, and it is a great, it's like an e-ticket attraction.
It is like a big attract.
That's like a premium, right?
Yeah.
That's like a high, high level.
They really sealed that mountain thing.
Like it may, I think it wasn't as much of a, you didn't talk about the Disneyland mountains
because the third always seals or that would be the third in Florida space mountain, big
thunder and then Disneyland with Matterhorn.
Yeah.
And Matterhorn.
Right.
But yeah, there's been other mountains that have not come to fruition.
They decided not to call Everest like Everest mountain.
Oh, it's not though.
It's just called expedition.
Not star Wars man.
But there's been a high low mountain, the Kylo Mon will be coming soon.
Buzzing Woody's toy mountains.
We're clamoring for it.
Yeah.
I mean mountains are cool.
Mountains are universally recognized as cool.
I like like the rides that feel very escapists.
Like I think you get that with pirate, like the immersive darker ride, I guess.
Right.
Like there's something also in that I would, I mean this is probably easily accessible,
but like it is such a like there's, where are you when you're up in that little fiber
last mountain?
Like it is like a pretty winding, interesting path.
Is it behind it's base?
It's sort of, I know Disneyland better than Disney world, but it's like the Disney world
one kind of the, the train runs through the mountain.
So some of the ride has to be like, like it straddles both sides of the, of the berm quote
unquote the big like Disneyland.
Disneyland.
Yeah.
So you get a little bit of a peak of what's going on or like on the other side.
No, no, you don't have the train or no, the train you do.
Oh, in the, oh, inside the train.
You're saying you can see the last show, the scene, the riverboat, you can see the animals
on the riverboat, which is a great way to, if the lines too long, it's splash mountain.
You can see a little of that big end show scene and you got to ride the train.
What could be better?
Or if you don't go on flume attractions, this is one way.
Oh, here we go.
Scott does not go on splash mountain.
Yeah.
This is the third one of these.
Uh, what do you mean?
Have you been ever?
I did one time.
So there was like, I had a little run in like a middle school, high school where a friend
or girl peer pressure would make me inspired by band Margera and his boys.
You got, you got that.
I'm Scott Garner and this is the splash mountain.
You're crazy.
How are you even going to do that?
I can make sure I'm seated in the ride vehicle.
I keep my arms and legs inside all.
Yeah, I, uh, yeah, I don't know.
I probably could, you know, in looking at it, I was realizing it probably doesn't make
sense that I don't do it because I have done the knots Berry farm.
Yes.
Uh, the, uh, what does that, uh, recall?
Am I not coming up with that?
It's another flume.
Yeah.
Is it called, it's not Calico mountains.
That's the mine cart.
Um, the knots flume ride, but the, but I think it's a, it's a similar amount of drop.
I think the, uh, splash mountain might be steeper, more angled and it's also visually
much more impressive looking than the one at knots.
So it looks taller, scarier.
And like when I was a kid, I felt like from looking at it, even though it's clearly not
a 90 degree drive, it looked, it felt like that to me from looking at it and I was like,
Oh my God, you fall straight down.
But really when you're on it, even though it's fast, like it's, you can, well, and they
sell the splash with like, um, water jets to like water up.
And when you're a kid, your brain isn't fused.
Like everything's just two dots and a mouth.
Like you can't, you still have like baby brain.
This is now that I'm about to say it, it's going to sound like I'm trying to really insult
Scott, but it's not what I'm trying to do.
The only ride that's of like an e-ticket that my mom will go on still is splash mountain.
She won't go on Indy cause she says jostles are too much.
She won't go on space mountain for the same reason.
But she's like, I'll do splash mountain.
No problem.
Well, I think it's different.
It's a different because I don't like, I don't like the flume dress and I don't like the,
I don't like the quick launches.
So I don't go on a mummy.
I don't go on California screaming soon where the credit coast credit coast.
Did you, uh, is it like a, um, a feeling thing or just like a, like a, those give me the
most sort of like a little, uh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Just like that kind of like a little like adrenaline or dropping your heart or whatever.
Yeah.
Um, yeah, I dunno.
It's a feeling in my heart.
I don't like, I've proposed according to evolution though.
You're right.
And we're wrong.
We should be seeking out like the feeling of a lion eating our ears in the night or
whatever.
You shouldn't be doing the thing everybody finds fun that millions of people line up
every day to do.
No, I'm right.
I'm trying to say it.
I appreciate it.
I know I'm wrong.
I also probably could do it.
I proposed to you at this, with the wedding, you were, if you recall this, that perhaps
we do a series, maybe we check in every week building up to your return to splash mountain.
Yeah.
We check in, how are you feeling about it?
And then we bring a recorder into the park, get a before, maybe during, depending on if
we have water.
This is Mike's a wrestling, you know, interest, uh, showing my building up a story line weeks
in advance.
You gotta build an angle.
And then you pay it all pay per view pay.
That's right.
And we'll put it behind, we'll put the episode where Scott goes on splash mountain buying
a paywall $10.
I'll make it worth your while.
So you're saying that I, that you want me to, uh, that there, we would do maybe like
a half hour special in which we find out what it's like for me to brave splash mountain.
And I try to become a, I'll use the proper term splashtranaut.
That's what you're proposing.
I think that's a great idea.
Because this, what I am describing has precedent in the way a very vivid memory from my childhood,
1989 earnest goes to splash mountains, a half hour Disney channel special.
Have you guys all seen it?
You've seen pieces of it.
I've not watched the whole thing.
I vaguely remember it.
And this could be something like that.
Like also part of my memories are like, Oh, I looked, I looked it up like in college or
stuff, but like, yeah, it was, it was just a commercial, right?
Yeah.
What big half hour commercial that's like definitely more odd and off brand than I've
seen a very, very many Disney specials.
If I haven't established that by this point and it's like, it's, it's a lot more, it's,
it's very odd.
It's focused on the one ride.
A lot of it is filmed by Jim Varney and his team because if you know that he like, he
like self produced all of that stuff, every earnest thing you've ever seen, whether it
was for an ad for Cerritos, auto square or the wraparounds for his show, Hey Vern, it's
earnest.
So I'm missing that in, I'm probably getting the state wrong, but you know, Tennessee or
wherever you live.
So, so a lot, so it doesn't, most of the specials are not filmed at Disneyland.
It's him like prepping.
So he said he, it's, they referred to Vern's daredevil Institute, which I guess is where
I have to go or to make, it's actually perfect to do my sequel.
Oh yeah.
This guy goes to splash map because not only did the, this, not only did the ride freak
me out and not only did the special probably contribute to me being afraid of the ride,
I was afraid of the special itself.
I watched this when I was, I probably three, four years old.
I'm not sure exactly, but it, in my memory, earnest's trip down the drop was like a terrifying
Lynchian nightmare.
Like I wish I could show you like distort what I had in my baby brain because it's,
you know, it all builds up to him doing it and he's kind of like, yeah, piece of cake.
And he puts his feet up on the log and he says, wish I brought a book, which I think
is actually funny.
And then, and then he finally goes and there's a news, there's news reporters covering all
of this.
And he said, and the news reporter says, squeamish viewers may want to turn away at this point.
And then he goes down the drop and he's super terrified.
Does a big old earnest scream.
And I just wish I could like transplant what's in my brain to you guys because in my mind,
the drop sequence itself was like 10 minutes long and just like the most fright, like mother
esque existential nightmare experience.
And I remember that there were strobe effects and I remember it like electrified him.
It like affected his hair and made his hair shoot up.
And if you watch this and we'll, we should post the link and we're posted the clip to
our Instagram or whatever.
But if you find what I finally as an adult saw this again, it's 10 seconds long.
He goes like, ah, his hair shoots up and that is it.
But my baby brain just like morphed it into terrifying Guillermo del Toro nightmares for
many, many years.
I just, I, you guys have to see how, especially the hair thing, it's literally like strobing
on and off.
He has a wig in one and hope not a wig in the other.
But to me, like what's the most terrifying horror film of all time?
Ernest goes to splash.
Um, you're saying that's in your brain still really?
Yeah, I think it impacts me.
Yeah.
This has become my, my therapy session.
I still, when I stare up at that ride, I see earnest and his strobe nightmare.
Uh, and I do also remember, um, the first time I went to Disneyland or any theme park,
I think I was like three or four years old and they were still building splash mountain
or they were still running tests and it wasn't open yet.
And so at that age, I am the smallest that I've ever been at Disneyland.
I am very small and this building is very tall.
And I remember staring up just like the shadowy building at night, scaring the shit out of
me.
It seems to just giant towered above me.
Uh, so maybe, maybe I have, maybe there's more mental tied up in here than I, then I
realized it sounds like stories of trauma.
Tied into a splash.
Yeah.
And now here's the rest.
I take another hour.
By the way, the knots ride is the timber mountain log, timber mountain log ride, which opened
first I believe.
Yeah.
Opened well before splash mountain.
Okay.
Um, and I think when they were like considering some sort of water ride, like some imagineers
like poo pooed a log flume like log flumes, I think we're getting popular, but people,
but they seem like, Oh, how will we tell a story?
Right?
How would we get animatronics?
How we get carriages in there?
It seems too simplistic for Disneyland.
But timber mountain itself, if you haven't been on that ride and knots, it is, it is
full of animatronics and recently refurbished and it's sort of like a sets the precedent
for splash mountain for sure.
And it's a, it's similarly structured where there's many drops through it all building
up to the, uh, the final climax and the things get like spooky on the way up to the top.
This is the minutia we tune in.
Yeah.
So it's ever mountain.
It was a big influence.
So I know like the early blues records influencing rock and roll.
What are the animatronics at knots?
I've never been like, is it Snoopy based or no, it's a bunch of like gruff construction
workers.
Like miners and like, you know, like, you know, people getting coal dust in their lungs.
Uh, it's a lot of like, just like working people.
And like, I mean the calico mine rides, that's the one that has a ton of people just working
in the cold shit.
Right?
Yeah.
I guess that's where you get coal lung here.
The timber bound is where you get sawdust.
Yeah.
These are all like lumberjack kind of guys that are chopping down trees and sawing things
miserably.
They are.
So just a bunch of gruff, grizzled assholes.
They're less in the Disney style of like kind of like pirates of the Caribbean where they're
big cartoonish.
They're more like people.
So when we went on these rides, it very much feels like you're just like looking at these
people with incredibly hard lives, especially the mine ride.
It's like you're going through and there's like 15 people like, and it's not a fun seven
dwarf style like pickaxe and hand hitting the rocks.
It's just like men who have no other option.
One of them slips you a note that says, please, we're real.
Get us out of here.
My campaign will not forget the hardworking animatronics.
They'll all have benefits.
I'll settle for you as mayor of knots.
No longer mayor of knots might be more attainable.
Good first step.
Good thing on the resume.
Yeah.
Well here, we'll call you mayor of podcast ride.
That's done.
So you have mayoral experience already.
There we go.
Uh, here's your inauguration ceremony.
I'll bring my glass of water on your leg.
It's wet and covered with glass.
All right.
We have inaugurated you and uh, yeah, you're, you're the experienced mayor already.
So we, we have to touch on a, the weird topic, which is where this bride comes from.
What is this?
46 movies, song of the South.
Yeah.
So we'll, we'll touch on it as four white dudes can.
It's very strange.
First of all, I'll say this.
It's very strange that in the eighties they decided to build this thing.
There were plenty of other movies.
There were plenty of other things they could have used to make a giant flume ride.
Cause there's nothing about when you're inside there.
Like I'll be honest, the characters I don't really care too much about.
They're like the rabbit, very rabbit.
Like they're kind of ill-defined qualities.
That rabbit is mischievous.
He's like a bug, a country bugs bunny I guess.
A abrasive voice.
He's a trickster.
Uh, it's the whole thing that he's like, please don't throw me into the briar patch, but he
lives in the briar patch.
He wants to be in the briar patch.
Okay.
So he's a trickster.
The, uh, the laughing place, the topic of the laughing place comes up.
This was interesting to learn in my research that the laughing place goes back to like
African folklore in Africa and to like, to, uh, uh, it relates in some parts to a Nancy,
the trickster, the spider trickster folklore character.
Oh, let's see.
Following bare rabbits capture the hero leads his couchers Wiley, Brea, Fox, and dim way
to prayer, Brea to his laughing place.
This can be enough for me.
For my money, my laughing place is the UCB theater in Los Angeles, California.
The beautiful UCB theater.
Uh, yeah.
So similar trickster tales, I feel like exist in a lot of cultures throughout the world.
Right.
So, so I have never seen the movie.
It's not been distributed in any time lately by Disney because it's widely regarded as
being racist.
It's a racist movie, but they have used it in the recent past.
They would show the animated segments on the Disney channel in the nine.
They would take out.
So there's a character, uncle Remus.
He is basically excised from the sequences you're talking about.
They just use the cartoon characters that end up appearing on the ride.
Wait, but how do you, because like when we were kids, Disney singalong songs are still
using zippity doo-dah, which is him.
The live action kids and uncle Remus.
Uncle Remus is in the Disney singalong songs.
Cause I remember seeing those like, um, and like preschool and whatnot.
Cause that, that particular like zippity doo-dah, uh, like the bluebird is cartoon, but he,
yes.
Okay.
So that's from the movie.
And then in the parade we watched when we did the braids episode, they refer to the
song as a South float, uh, that bear Raman, bear rocks are on.
So like there's certainly, we're not doing like an incredible lead, good detail.
Look at like what was wrong with this.
No, you don't know.
We're not qualified.
But like, we're just talking about how God damn weird it is because there are so many
properties they did this cause so, so like this is a Tony Baxter, right?
It's again, a great ride.
He's the guy.
He's the man and he's talked about this before.
Like they were not sure if culturally people would like it.
So they re-released the movie in the eighties to see if there would be a big uproar about
it.
Test the waters.
And it was no one complained or there was no, I'm sure did fairly well in 1986.
Something that today is referred to, like I feel like now it's spoken of as like a sort
of urban legend.
Like, do you know Disney made this movie that people feels racially weird or whatever, but
it was in theaters in 1986.
Not too long ago.
And is award winning in, in it won the Oscar for best song for Zippity Doodah and the actor
who played uncle Remus, James Baskett won an honorary Academy award for playing uncle
Remus.
But, and that's reading about this movie.
There's so many instances of this where it seems like one step forward, two steps back
because like the U S government after World War II was doing like an anti racism initiative
and part of it was like trying to tie in this movie and like, yeah, and this guy eventually
he did get this honorary Academy where the first African American man to win an Oscar.
However, the movie premiered in Atlanta and he was not allowed to attend the premier due
to segregation.
Oh Jesus.
So there's all of this crazy stuff.
I mean, people thought, you know, some writers at the time were like, this is good.
These folklore, these oral tradition, these American folklore stories of bear rabbit,
bear Fox and Agorimas, uh, could bring people together.
But then other people were very, uh, certain that it's like, no, this is offensive.
The stereo is playing this old uncle stereotype.
It's just, it's just so interesting because like, what was it about the character cartoon
characters that they were like, we gotta get this, like, why wasn't it just a rescuers
down like not done out there that was nineties but like rescuers move.
Like I had this rescuers mountain or a one of the great mouse detective come out.
Well no, but even the, um, I mean the, the newer minecart dwarves ride, it feels like
they could have themed that as a splash mountain.
Right?
Yeah.
You could have done another get people into critter country, right?
Like people were going to be related to bear country.
It was bear country before.
And then when splash mountain opened, it became critter country.
So they were trying to populate that section and it must've been, I think, uh, Tony Baxter's
about worlds is a world, but I think he wanted that like that, uh, that, that old south vibe
or the holler.
But ironically that is the vibe.
I think from what I could tell, didn't look into it too hard, but it seems like a big
thing that people are upset about or ever were upset about with song in the south is
that it like portrayed this rosy, uh, post reconstruction south that is not an accurate
depiction of there were not singing bluebirds on people's shoulders.
You'd believe it.
But, uh, but I also understand like, uh, I don't know, I guess it's that like, uh, um,
that that sort of folksy, uh, um, you know, homespun kind of vibe that does feel with
the riverboat and everything.
And it's related to the rivers of America.
You could see how it ties into a vibe that was already in Disneyland.
I mean it's because of course I love the ride itself.
So of course I get that that's all a very good idea.
It's just interesting surrounding all with all the controversy.
It's interesting that they, even though they released it, they were just like, they did
even try to do it, which is, it's just kind of wild.
I would be interested to know even more right out of one of those cartoons where Donald
fights Hitler.
Well that I can get behind.
That would be a fun ride.
Yeah.
Watch him like a launch missiles into Hitler's head.
So it still seems split of whether people think they should release it on home video
or not.
I mean last year whoopee Goldberg at D 23 said like, yeah, release it, put it out there
and start a conversation about it.
But I mean American pop culture, American media like nuance is not our strong suit in
America.
Uh, so I don't know.
It seems like there is people who think like, yeah, release it, but just to academic institutions.
But then anyone could buy it then.
Like students for students to study it.
I think that was Roger Ebert's thing.
Like yet let film students study it.
Also in terms of its weight as a film, I didn't know it was the first movie shot on color
by the cinematographer Greg Toland who shot Citizen Kane.
So like a major work.
That's why in a piece of, in the giant body of work, a very talented guy.
Um, yeah.
So, so I mean most people that go in ride the ride.
I have no idea really what it is, what it's connected to and like, yeah, it's just like
some cartoons and it's fine.
Right, right.
Well, and that's the question.
Is there anything could you could screw anything in the ride itself as being a weird or problematic?
And I don't, I don't think so.
Not that I could tell.
We just watched a ride through on YouTube.
I wasn't, I watched, they feature the bears big ass a few too many times.
I mean they've definitely softened some of the voice.
Like I went and found the, that's the other thing about this.
There's a large black market for bootleg, a song of the south DVDs and you can find
multiple clips of it.
You can probably piece the whole movie together through YouTube.
But like some of the voices, they're rough.
The voices in the original movie have not aged well and they've definitely softened
them in the ride.
Listen, okay.
I don't want to start talking, uh, what we would do with the ride.
We still got to go through it.
Through the ride still, but yeah, it's definitely on the docket.
Mr. Bear.
Yeah, sorry.
So we'll, we'll start going through the ride.
We'll go through it as if we didn't know anything about this other movie that existed.
And that's the thing that show up in the closet.
Tony Baxter on a recent season past podcast, they've done a long running interview series
with him brought up that this ride is unique in that it technically it is an IP ride.
It's based on something that already exists, but a lot of people don't know about it.
There's no way I would have known.
Some people think it's just an original thing.
Right.
They don't have the context.
And of course, many of the animatronic characters in this are not from Song of the South because
this isn't too deep cut of theme park nerd knowledge.
But very doesn't know they were, this was another big thing.
Tony Baxter was trying to solve two problems.
One that Bear Country wasn't getting a lot of population.
People weren't heading back to that corner of the park.
So America Sings was closing, which was in the Circle Vision, not Circle Vision, the
Carousel Theater in Tomorrowland.
They were going to evict that show and put in something else that actually George Lucas,
they were talking about some ideas with.
But that was going to do away with hundreds of audio animatronic characters.
Yes.
So all of the characters are moved over from America Sings.
That's a ton of money.
They sit like all the things on the riverboat at the end.
Like those are all just everything on the at a certain point.
Like some of those characters were like voiced by Burl Ives and like sung like rockabilly
songs and yeah, it's all what America Sings is kind of.
Yeah, it's like I love it.
Have you watched him?
No, I actually, I never have.
I've actually, you know, they sing like that sounds very much like showbiz pizza to the
max.
Yeah, it is.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
And they would, they would do more like, I guess more modern songs as well, but it'll
be like turn of the century songs, but then they would do a little rock and roll like from.
So if you wanted to see like a stork would say, let's crank it up a notch.
Play Johnny B. Goode.
Yeah.
They Marty McFly solo played by a stork and with reality subject matter, like grabbing
your girl and sharing a milkshake.
That was all going off the bicentennial fever, right?
Like America Sings was around the time.
I think it did open in 76.
Yeah.
And the bicentennial fever.
America had bicentennial fever.
It's accurate.
Jason still contracts once a year.
Yeah.
I take a Z-Pack and then I knock it right out.
First time I met you asked me if I got my bicentennial vaccine and I didn't know.
It's it's from this little side note from seeing what has happened to the old America
Sings and the old carousel progress.
They may as well have just kept America Sings in there.
They've done nothing with that space.
The worst use of a major space.
So what's there right now, I can't really right now is Star Wars launch launch launch
and then upstairs it's like some couches where you can pay $50 to sit with dad and mom so
they can chill out for a while.
Special cookies.
It was, it was interventions.
It was the house of the future and it would like circle around and it was, it's so depressing
that area.
I don't even read good rumors about stuff that might happen to that.
There's nothing coming.
Also when I went there as a kid, I think the first time I went, America Sings had just
closed.
Um, yeah, that's right.
Cause they were building splash man.
And uh, so, and then it was not as I went for the first time in 88, uh, 98 finally,
interventions open for a decade.
That space is nothing.
And it's a sign.
Uh, Mickey's holding a sign that says we're like imagining up a grand new experience.
It's been dog shit ever since they closed America Sings.
My whole dog shit my whole life.
Oh gee, well that's, that was briefly where it was interventions and you go to the HP
house of the future.
You could meet your old friend.
Awesome.
Oh, awesome.
Oh, I love awesome.
Awesome.
Oh, is now on Autopia though.
Yeah, he's awesome.
Oh yeah.
He's standing dead still on Autopia.
He doesn't move at all.
One thing he was built in the one thing he was supposed to do walk awesome.
Oh, I remember when awesome.
Oh, it's like first, I don't know how to phrase this on the scene.
Um, but he was like, Honda, Honda was, uh, this is when I was in college.
Honda was bringing him to different universities to kind of put on some sort of show for like
the engine mostly for, I guess for engineering touring awesome around.
And so I was like, you know, I was coming out of a class and I saw the sign for it.
I was like, yeah, I want to see what this little guy can do.
So I went in and I sat down and it was just like in a, like a big auditorium and they,
uh, they showed this video, like a representative from Honda came out and said, yeah, thanks
so much.
We're very proud.
We've been, you know, so many hours, really years of work.
And they show like kind of that classic video that I'm sure you guys have seen where it's
kind of creepy, where it's so hard to teach a robot to walk.
Like it's like this kind of like weird Terminator skeletal thing.
And they're fucking, it just looks like sad and they're tipping you over a lot.
So they showed this evolution of awesome.
And then it leads up to like the awesome.
You know, so if you don't know, awesome is this kind of like robot that Honda built and
it kind of looks like a little space man.
Uh, so anyway, so it culminates with like what he can do and he's helping old people.
Like he's like, I'm part of the family.
He has so much utility in the video they have, they show.
And then the video stops and the rep goes, who wants to meet awesome.
And so they put your hands together for awesome.
Awesome overseas to come out, wave to the crowd and without missing a beat, the rep
thing goes, who wants to see awesome?
Oh Dan.
And they ended up playing something like UB 40 or something like that, like red wine.
And this like this feat of engineering dancer, red, red wine.
Uh, it was what it was all building to.
It was all building to, and then like they, they pick it, like they kind of like, uh,
had him like kick a little ball at one point.
But it was so, so fucking funny to like them for them not to see the contrast and like,
this will change the world.
You want to see it Dan.
So people with their medicine and work.
So they were essentially doing 10 minute versions of that in interventions for, for years.
And I think there was also a test to segue.
There was a Disney infinity test out stations when that was a thing.
It is a building of junk.
Yeah.
It was junk warehouse.
I mean tomorrow land needs a multimillion dollar.
This is sounds like a great platform idea.
Yes.
Well that's the, the tomorrow land is the thing that needs the most care.
And would you say tomorrow land is a disaster, utter and total disaster.
I don't want to go that far because I like to lean more towards imagining a better world,
a better tomorrow and a better tomorrow land.
You're not about Disneyland and carnage.
Uh, you're about hope for the future.
That could have been a line from the Clooney movies.
We're out land like where it's just so clunky.
That's by the way, we've talked about this before.
That failure of that movie is I'm mad at it because we would have gotten a new tomorrow
land if that was a big hit.
The sequel would have come out already.
They would have been like, we got to put $500 million into tomorrow land and now it's not
going to happen for others.
Speaking of tomorrow land and like ASIMO type robots, uh, when I was there, so I went to
Disney world in May, 2017.
Um, there's an unrobot like an eye can.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Robot who is like half human, half robot.
Who speaks with the lid.
He like drives himself around.
Yes.
Yeah.
And I sent you guys the video I think when I was there, but when we were there, I met,
I can, you were saying it's supposed to be like a
predecessor to star Wars droids.
Is that right?
Well, they're, yeah, they're testing out certain things for star Wars and I maybe I forget
if it's, I can specifically, but I think they're there for sure.
Testing out different like autonomous robots.
And then I think people in robots, you had told me at Mike had told me about I can and
uh, when I saw him, uh, I got, well, you talking about this is, I can write as a picture.
I thought there was somebody called push.
Yeah.
There's a robot garbage.
I think there's a man who was retired.
Wait, no more push, but I can, I can is this, I can is more of a man.
He's not the garbage.
Oh, I got you saying can really confused me.
I don't know why.
Cause there used to be a trash can that wandered around and I believe may have run for mayor
of tomorrow land.
Oh shit.
A predecessor of an enemy to destroy.
Well, like the democratic party, I'll have a lot of highly paid consultants that you're
not quite sure what they do.
So I would hire a push on to pop in one day a week and a spout off some aphorisms about
pushes.
I'm gonna sink your campaign pushes pushes my Robbie mook, which is why John Podesta.
There's so many of these people to list.
Yeah.
There's so many.
I, I, 33,000 push emails.
We've never seen.
Philippe brains, he's my Philly brains, the guy who infamously got so into playing the
Donald Trump stand in the Clinton.
Oh boy.
The hall of failed DNC consultants.
One of these is literally a trash can.
Yeah.
Push push.
You're going to be advised on the Clinton campaign.
Uh, so this is kind of like my, I'm not sure, but in Disney world, it's frontier land that
space or splash man.
There is, they did not make a separate critter.
I really love frontier land.
I think it's like, it's an exciting, uh, area of rides, uh, in Disney world.
And it's well, and yeah, with it having splash mountain as part of it kind of flushes out
the area cause really the only ride here is a big thunder.
Uh, but yes, it's a more fleshed out land there.
Um, and they, and I believe I read that they had to, they, the score is different in Disney
world and they made it sort of more frontiersy.
It's kind of a more country fried music score.
I think it's tweaked a little.
I, we were talking about this a little before.
There's little differences between, uh, Orlando and Anaheim in terms of this ride.
Show scenes slightly slight differences.
Yeah.
The score is slightly different.
Orlando and Tokyo, I believe are like almost identical replicas of each other.
Scott, you pointed out the, the vultures you mentioned.
Oh yeah, apparent from watching the Disneyland and Disney world ride through is the Disney
worlds vultures have top hats, big difference.
Jason Mayer esque top hats.
And I think the Disneyland ones are lacking.
There's something I would ask of you is to let's get some, let's dress up those Disneyland
vultures, get them some hats forthwith.
There's a Disney world.
It's two seater cars and Disneyland at single seats.
So there's more capacity in Disney world as well.
That's another change.
Yeah.
That's a very interesting change.
A lot of people are riveted right now.
Has anyone died at either of them?
I don't think so.
The most deaths, but they, they did install lap bar.
They didn't used to have lap bars.
I don't think there's no lap bars and bars in Disneyland.
Oh, Disney world.
I think they may have put them in in Florida.
Interesting.
Cause it's Tokyo.
There's no seats at all.
I, uh, standing.
I, so there are doubles there.
There was a, so what we got, we'll, we'll go through.
The ride in one second.
I just, I remembered a very amusing anecdote.
Uh, they have a single rider line.
So when you're a childless man in his thirties, uh, with his childless girlfriend also in
her thirties, you guys, we don't need to sit together in the same.
Yeah.
Right.
So we go to the single rider line and the single rider line in Disneyland is just the
exit.
You just walk through the exits.
So what happens is they'll put you in a log flume with a family because the family, maybe
it's just dad and the two sons and then they're like their fourth in the party is you a 30
something man, probably the same age as this dad, but like he looks 15 years older and
he's not wearing a Mickey shirt.
He's like, he's like a little angry to be there.
So I'm in the back of the flume and there's two kids and the two kids are, I've described
this before.
They are looking at me, they're trying to figure out how old I am.
Uh, they're looking like this guy, this guy dresses like me, but he looks older than me.
So that, but you can tell they're like, they want to talk.
So like one of the kids is just like, Hey, uh, he like points to his younger brother.
He's like, he won't go on tower of terror telling you.
He tells me this and I go, Oh, I go, you gotta go on tower of terror.
And he's like, I'm too scared.
I'm like, no, come on.
It's good.
And then like we're harassing this kid the whole time.
Me and this other older brother.
And then like we get off the flume ride and the kids are like waiting for me.
Like they're running to get their dad, but they stop and they're like, they like kid
puts up his hands like, Hey, w w are you coming over here?
And I was like, Oh, I got away from my girlfriend.
He's like, Oh, okay.
And like you, you could tell the kid was like, Oh yeah, that old man is not part of our party.
They're disappointed.
They weren't getting a second dad that day.
Maybe you were going to be top dad.
I look, I could have been top dad.
You could, I certainly could have come in there and I would have wild these kids with
what I mean.
They would have loved it.
And how many videos?
Meanwhile, dad is being a real pain in the ass cause he's got a real job.
And yeah, yeah, yeah.
I would have been a much better father to those two kids and he, what he is.
Mike's livid.
I'm livid.
I could tell on a ride.
I thought that where that was going is I did the same thing.
Well, can I, I got a little tip.
I don't know if we ever did tips.
Yeah, but it's kind of a, it might be like frowned upon, but I'll say I took advantage
of this.
So my, when you go and you do the, like you have a fast pass, like you can also, if you
have a small child, do something called a ride share.
Have you guys heard of this child?
Child swap.
Are you talking about child swap?
Yeah, that, yeah, yeah.
That's what it is.
I don't know why I called it Russia, but that's what I was calling it.
That is what Uber, Uber star.
Yeah.
A child swap.
So we were, I was child swapping and like I didn't mind his uncle Anthony to like, and
you had a child with you.
Yes.
Yeah.
I would just literally like hold the child in like a baby bonnet pretending to be a child.
Right.
Like a third font LeRoy looking a giant lollipop.
It helps with the illusion.
Okay.
So it's not much of a tip, but I thought it really, it made me like very excited.
I'm like, Oh, I'm really conning this thing.
And then I would take the extra one and I would hop into like the fast pass lane.
But when I ride, when you ride that way, you also are the one stranger with the family
and their photos.
Yes.
That's my point.
Yeah.
So yeah, I should have said that too.
Like that's, it's odd because it's odd.
It's like all photos of just most of the ride photos I have from like, cause my sister gets
like the magic band photo pass and I'm downloading them and there's hardly any pictures of me
with my own family.
I'm just with random families.
Some alternate family.
Right.
Cause that has to happen for people like us who go a lot and we do single rider.
There's probably families that that's their once every couple of year trip to Disneyland.
They buy the photo.
Yeah.
And then they're mantle forever is like mom, dad, Jimmy, Sally and Michael Carlson, 33
year old man sitting in the back, men like bored because he's been on this 150 times.
I wonder, this is probably statistically unlikely, but listeners, you know what, you can Google
me, Mike and Scott.
And even Anthony, there's pictures of us out there.
Where are you going with this?
Listen, listeners might have family photos with us in the audience isn't that big yet.
Look, it's like collapse.
You know, there's a lot of collateral beauty in the world.
Like there's a lot, but you never know.
I like the idea that we'll get like 50 people with a picture of you in the back of the ride
vehicle.
Jack Nicholson, shining style, that was a day I fell asleep and they left me in the
log for a while.
So I just saw him in a ton of family photos.
Speaking of which, I was watching the ride through, we were kind of checking it out and
there's a little frog at the beginning of it who has a fishing line.
He's sleeping, he's sleepy and he's got a hat over his head and the fishing line's tied
to his toe.
And I think if mayor doesn't pan out, Jason, you can have right now.
I'd be hanging out with that.
Hop right into that.
Is that the same frog?
Because there is Brer Frog, he talks at some point.
It might be him.
He plays the bass at the end I think.
Yeah I think so.
And there is also a porcupine playing a turtle like it's drums.
I really love that part.
Which is really cute.
But Brer Frog is voiced by James Avery, the late actor who was also Uncle Phil on The
Fresh Prince of Bel-Air.
The voice actors on this are very interesting.
Nick Stewart, Brer Bear, he's the voice in the original movie and the ride.
He was the only actor still alive at the time and he was the only one who did both.
And then Brer Rabbit in the movie, I forget who did it in the movie, apparently the actor
who played Uncle Remus in the movie does the voice of Brer Rabbit in one sequence.
In the ride it is a guy named Jess Harnell who is also a wacko, warner, and anomaniacs
and Crash Bandicoot.
Two extreme characters.
Well I guess Crash is more extreme than wacko.
And then Brer Fox is a guy named J.D. Hall who is the voice of Blade on Spider-Man the
animated series.
Wow.
And Gargenis in the ancient mythology, I don't know what that is.
Who's the other anomaniac?
Would you have said Yakko or was it wacko?
Yakko is Jess Parnell.
Wacko, the voice of Yakko, Rob Paulson plays a big part in David Copperfield's current
show at the MGM Brands.
Oh wow, awesome.
And I don't want to say what, I don't want to give anything away.
He is awesome.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Rob Paulson is really fantastic.
But please, I really, ooh I cannot even spoil it, everyone listening needs to get their
asses to Vegas and see what Rob Paulson is up to.
It is an out of this world experience.
Okay, anyway, so let's, do you have more facts Jason or do you want to?
No, no.
Oh, just that former Animatronic of the Month contestant, Man-Tized Dog in a Spinning Rowboat
is in this ride.
I forget where to describe, he's after one of the little drops.
Hard to spot, hard to spot.
Hard to spot, but he's really spinning in that rowboat and because it's mostly a darkness,
it is unsettling.
In a domesticated animal amongst wild animals.
Domesticated but also man-sized, like very large.
You need to domesticate those.
I'd like to say that many of the animatronics, the animatronics carted over from America
Sings were designed by Mark Davis, one of the great, the original nine old men, one
of Walt's trusted early crew people who also designed the first Animatronic of the Month
striped shirt pirate among many of the Pirates of the Caribbean characters.
And I'm not totally sure, but possibly the second one, Uncle Orville, because I think
he did a lot of carousel of progress as well.
I see Mark Davis was one of the guys that Walt was like, you're a great animator and
guess what?
Now you're building robots.
Yeah, he really carted people over who had no experience in this area, which who did?
No one had experience in this area.
I had the thought as you were saying that, like one of the first, like where do you fucking
begin?
Where do you even, I was just drawing a mouse.
My job Monday was drawing a mouse and my job Tuesday is building a robot pirate.
It's like, right, right.
Well, I guess robotics people are different.
I mean, he did, when I say he designed, he did like the concept art for like, he didn't
like go and learn robotics.
Yeah.
So it's way more science.
A lot of cross-disciplinary stuff in the first few generations.
It's a simple time.
It's a simple time Jason's going to bring us back to it.
A bunch of, as we say, usually like a bunch of short sleeve dress shirt, older men who
like smoked ton and drank and didn't have any sort of nostalgic love for Disney because
it didn't exist.
Just did all of this amazing stuff.
Yes.
They look like all of the regular people in hidden figures.
They're the people who the hidden figures women had to break into be included with.
Yeah.
They didn't treat women very well.
Mary Blair and Alice Davis there too.
Alice Davis, wife of Mark Davis, a long time Imagineer as well.
All right.
Yeah.
Well, so I, which I think is part of what, that's a great thing about all these characters
in Splash Man is they like, they have like a classic Disney feel because they were made
in the seventies by this like classic Imagineer.
Yeah, I love, I do.
So earlier I was like, Oh, the characters, like when we were talking about why this IP
and whatnot, I do love like the look of it.
But like the, there is something like a little abrasive up rare rabbit.
And if they, I don't want to get into the changes.
I don't want to get the changes I make, but there is like a little bit of like the voice
work feels like it could use a, a little, a little update.
And they've softened, like I said, they've softened it since the movie.
Less abrasive than the actual film.
Yeah.
So there's an idea.
Right.
Get, get your Rob Pulsons in the mix.
Yeah.
Maurice LaMarche is the cable guy.
You Larry, the current Disney voice actor, Larry, the kid with maybe meter is just one
of the characters.
Maybe they just swap.
Yeah.
I'm in here too.
All right.
Is asked down the Hill.
Like put me in Mater.
Oh, you want the car to be made?
Man, we're plussing it up already.
Ooh, I like that one.
That is a great idea.
At least a seasonal Mater change over or like, Hey, I'm an Easter egg.
My thing with was both.
SpongeBob is one of my favorite rides.
It's as all the things you were saying, like it's a nice long ride.
You get a lot of show, you get a lot of robots, which is all we'll ever talk about.
It's like you get so many of that.
It's got a nice fun thrill in it.
It's got a couple minor thrills to it.
I don't go on it as much cause sometimes we're there.
We decided to go down at night and I don't like being soaking wet at 9 PM.
Yes, it is a certain rides like log flume rides.
You have to time and like there's a, there, there is a chance like maybe you'll be at
the park and like you wanted to ride it, but just the weather's not cooperating cause you'll
be, you'll be really a chilly.
There is a tip.
Here's a tip.
If you don't want to get that wet, do single rider and ride as the creep with another family
because that last seat is the least wet seat.
I rode with my buddy Jeff like in September and we got a fast pass and we were, we were
in the first two and we were drenched.
It was crazy.
I mean it wasn't as bad as like a universal Dudley do ride ride, which just literally
like you should, they should have another change of clothes for you after that ride.
But this one, this splash mountain definitely soaked my socks and shoe and like ruins you
for like an hour and a half.
And they, if it's not that crowded, they don't load the boats to capacity and then like they
load it so that the wheat is kind of distributed.
So then the backseat is not necessarily very dry because then there's no one to catch the
water.
The water light hit.
I think we, I rode the, I think I rode the ride with you once and it drenched you and
didn't touch me.
Yeah, I love being, and I, and you are, I will say the thing about Jason, he loves being
soaking wet at a theme park.
The only person I know that is a embraces trench foot.
Yeah.
I mean, I will say this ride is very well suited to Orlando because you can ride it
at midnight when it's like 75 degrees and sure I'm already soaking wet from sweat.
Fine.
But like Southern California either got a, I mean you can, if you try, if you hold your
feet up and you, you got a hoodie on or something like you can get not that wet, but there's
like a very small portion of the year where you're like, I want to ride this and I want
to get very wet cause it doesn't get that hot here.
Right.
Yeah.
Another thing about it is that it's like, it's got a lot of moves.
It's got a lot of different emotional moves, which I like, like it's fun and then it's
like psychedelic.
There's like a weird drug trip part of it and then it turns scary when the full opossum
is telling you don't fall into the briar patch.
Right.
So it's got these nice moves.
I will say also this, the ride often is broken a little bit and a lot of show scenes are
in pure darkness.
So sometimes you ride it and it's truly a sinister feeling because it feels like you're
riding it with the lights off and it feels like, I don't know what's lurking there.
There's a bear, but he's not, I can't see what he's doing.
And like a lot of randomly placed laughs like, yes, there's a lot of laughs.
You don't know why people are laughing or animals are laughing.
It's hard.
It's, it's, it's, uh, historically hard to fix this ride because it's like water ride
and you have to shut things down.
So when stuff starts breaking, they just kind of have to go with it a lot of time.
So like you ride it and like half the show scenes aren't lit up.
It's truly creepy.
It's a very creepy thing.
For like a chunk every year essentially.
And you can tell when it's opened back up again cause that last show scene with all
the animatronics on the boat and it looks so great when everything's moving.
But there were times every now and then where only half the people are moving.
Do you think there's a like a threshold where it's like, you know, if there's 18 little
animals on there, they're like, all right, we crossed the thread.
Like it's 10 aren't working.
We got to go up there.
But like nine is like, I'm not going up.
I think so.
There is a clip, but we should find it and post it.
There's a clip not long ago where someone went and saw the boat foot goes into that
last scene on the showboat and all of the robots aren't working and it's truly creepy
and they're just like staring at you.
They're not moving.
The song is still playing.
So like someone's singing, but it's not these characters and it's, it's alarm.
It's very alarming.
They're ghosts.
By the way, I think it's fun sometimes when we just call them robots.
You can't say animatronics every time.
It's such a low word.
Pretty mealy mouth.
We like to have a little sense of humor about it.
So it's funny to say like that robot over there.
I think I just to say robot or get it even more wrong.
I think I called them people a moment.
I guess all them people know what are those metal people doing?
What are other details of this?
Mike brought something up that I really like it in that, um, if there's for me, cause I
haven't been on it a lot.
You fall for those, those fake drops.
Like those fake drops are like nice moments of like a surprise.
They kind of get the anticipation level up.
It seemed like in that one moment that you get distracted by that big old bear butt.
That's a kind of, and then you aren't looking down and then that they, that one's in pure
darkness so it sneaks up on you.
Right.
So if I'm a kid writing that for the first time, I think that's a, that's a good fake
drop.
And then you got a good, I think at the top too, if you've been on it for the first time,
you go up, it takes you up and you go around and you're outside at the first point and
then you see there's a drop coming.
And I think if you didn't know, you might think this is the first, this is the drop.
So you don't even know it's, it's, it does such a good job of making you not even aware.
So I bet if you're going on the first time you go, Oh, this must be that drop I saw.
Cause you don't, yeah.
As you said earlier, you're disoriented.
You don't know where you all are already.
So it's such a maze.
I want to see the plans of it.
I probably, I'm an idiot, so I don't really probably even know.
I understand like if I saw blueprints, but like I would love to like know or even, I
mean like I know from listening to the podcast, the dream is a mid ride shut down and a walk
on and people have had it at the top of the lift Hill on splash mountain.
Whoa.
Right before.
Yes.
So it'd be the big, that's the dream.
That's, that's one of the big ones.
I mean obviously Indiana Jones, a pirate.
So, but yes, at the top of the lift Hill on splash mountain, certainly one of the walk
off dreams.
Oh man.
That'd be my dream if I went on it.
Yeah, that would be the best.
Steven Spielberg riding the Jurassic park ride who got off right before the drop.
Yeah.
If I could, well, I don't want to, it's like, excuse me, I'm the director of song of the
south.
Can you let me off please?
Maybe that'll be how the special ends is that you start having a fit on the way up and then
you try to get out of the flume and they have to shut the whole ride down and then like
you end up in Disney jail or something.
I mustered into a straight jacket or shoved in my mouth.
You put a, are you sedated or maybe we do it where like we bring two top hats and we
try to put the top hats on the crows.
So you can reach out little hooks.
Yeah.
Well, you know, a lot of people do bring props on this ride.
It's become a real thing that the photo that they take as you drop a P that, you know,
there's been like a group of people are playing like donkey Kong on xbox.
They like set up an entire, one of them's holding the console.
The other two people have the, uh, the controllers and somebody's holding a TV.
This is like, like I feel like someone playing chess.
Yeah.
How did they get that stuff on?
I have no idea.
In your bag.
Yeah.
It's a whole, also Dwayne Johnson, the rocks photo is very fun.
There's a photo of him going down splash mountain.
He's just like cheering.
He's just super psyched.
But there's a lot of, yeah, I think, um, as I said earlier, people who've read this, written
this 150 times, they start getting fucking cute with this shit.
And I'll tell you what, I don't care for it.
I don't like it.
Well, you know what I don't like, and I feel the same way of like, I'm seeing a live show
or going to a premiere of a movie.
Uh, the audience will never be the entertainment to like, like don't do that.
Like don't talk during a comedy show.
Yell during the trailer of a premiere of a movie, like especially don't be the second
guy that does it who thinks he's going to get as much of a response as the first guy.
Because I've seen that happen at every Marvel movie where someone says something and then
a second guy tries to say something else and like he's crucified.
Uh, some, yeah, we've seen some, uh, opening night showings at the city walk at universal
and lot of bits during those.
Yeah, don't know during the movie cause they're so excited.
Yeah, but the trailers, there's some performative stuff going contain it.
Yeah.
You're a tating area.
I feel like I have some blood on my hands as one of the original people involved in
the beginnings of the room.
Tommy Wiseau's the real right.
Uh, like for like it became this dream for me and my friends cause I was part of the
group that like found it first in 2003 and like, Oh my God, that there is this movie
and we know no one else will be in it.
It is daring to know one and we can go in there and yell and make up our stuff.
And I remember I started throwing spoons at the screen and now it is such an, it's such
a nightmare.
It is like it's, it is pure bedlam.
It's those room foreclothes, the room screenings I say, they're out of control.
We'll never, uh, like just fire bomb the whole thing.
You just see pictures and you're like, what hell half I wrong.
Absolutely.
Um, yeah, I couldn't do it.
I have no desire to go to one of those.
I had a, not to get too far off topic, but I had, I saw Joe's apartment when I was a
kid.
Roaches MTV's first like a foray into film on which a, uh, Owen Burke, who you see be
mainstay was like, he was like a pa on that weird facts.
First movie he worked on, I think.
Yeah, that was very much our experience where no one else was in the theater and I don't
know how old I was.
I was probably 10 or so and I'm looking around and I'm like, wait, we can kind of do anything
we want.
And I was too much again of a weiner, but like I definitely had some friends that were
looking gummy bears and the winging them at the screen and stuff.
It's pretty fun.
Yeah.
Well it feels, it feels fun with it's you and your friends because you know them, but
if it's some jerks you don't know, there's 200 shut up.
Um, anyway, well the other bit of fun obviously that people have on, have had on the, on splash
mountain is you go down that drop, you lift up your shirt and you show them boobies.
A phenomenon known as flash mountain.
Flash mountain.
And this is like, this is very much the like care for it.
I don't, none of us care for it.
Well there's, yes, we're good little boys and we don't approve of a R rated materials
occurring on our beloved attraction or rated material in general.
No, no, no.
I see now here's the thing I heard about flash mountain whenever it was having its heyday
and I of course stay away from that.
Not for me.
Good.
Uh, but I just for pure research purposes, I thought I should see what's going on on
flash mountain these days.
And it's still a thing.
It is not still a thing.
The address, so the address was flash mountain.net.
They didn't get the.com.
And it seems to have disappeared around 2006 or so, but via the wayback machine at web.archive.org,
you can check out the remnants of, of flash mountain.
Let me tell you what you've all been missing out on.
A warning splash page and then 16 low res JPEGs, which all do contain nipple content,
but some of them you have to search for.
In some cases it's like, is there one?
Oh yeah, I guess so.
And then there's one of the 16 that is not splash mountain.
It's a different roller coaster entirely.
This is, and I, and I checked from like, I checked in 2003 and I checked in 2005 and
it stayed the same 16.
It is a wall of 16 JPEGs of blurry boobs in motion.
I just want to point out to the listeners, Jason's glasses have fogged up.
My trademark bow tie will not stop spinning and my shirt, Dickie has rolled up like an
old timey blind.
Jason is usually just dressed like Big Bird at the symphony.
Pupils have turned into giant breasts.
I believe TMZ also did a segment on it, but back, back around that time.
And it seemed like I read a writeup ballot and it seemed they, they went like, Oh, there's
this website.
Yeah, we'll just do the same thing.
We'll just take these pictures down and show them ourselves.
But blur them.
Oh sure.
Yeah.
Like this thing's crazy, right?
Harvey like, you know, I just couldn't believe that it was so thin.
I think I'd always imagined it was this vast archive.
When you brought it up, I thought, Oh, this must've been like a real issue that they had
to make changes for about 16 and one of them is not, but so actually only 15.
Now they could just catch it and hide it immediately.
I digitally, although I heard there's also some stories in 2009 that they do do budget
cutbacks.
They had to get rid of the person who was doing those checks.
So I don't know if that remains true, but there was thought of will flash mountain return
and it did not.
The rumor that is, I mean, I don't, I don't know if I've ever had this confirmed, but
the rumor also was that in Disneyland they had to get rid of captain Jack Sparrow walk
around character because women were flashing him.
Hmm.
I don't know if that's ever been cause they still have him in Florida and I saw him when
we were there, but they, I have not seen captain Jack.
I gotta say my ex like when I'm going to Disney, my experience there is not what those people
anticipate their vacation to be.
Like I, I really wanted to be escapists where like there's no murder.
Like I'm in a new world where it's safe and it's fun.
Sure.
Yeah, it's safe and it's fun and it's like, there's no, uh, I'm very anti only.
You know, like you don't even like the idea that like there's this dark, uh, secret underbelly
of Disneyland.
I think that all the bad characters should go.
You don't know why they keep this haunted house.
Haunted mansion is a problem.
They just bullet these spirits in this thing and they keep it open.
Let them rest in peace.
A lot of them seem to have died in a silly ways.
Look, I totally agree with you for my money.
The only body ness I want is a couple, uh, burlesque bird dancers on a steam ship lifting
up their dresses a little bit while they're dancing.
That's as much body ness as I like.
You leave it to the imagination.
Disneyland's a land of imagination.
Isn't it sexier if you don't see all the way up the skirt?
Of course it is.
Direct quote from parents.
Save that funny business for your official Disney hotel rooms or the Disney dream suite
or Walt's apartment.
You have a key.
If you happen to know a mayor who happens to be lonely that evening.
I'll still party.
Just in the privacy of my own home, which is Walt's apartment.
You're like that Canadian mayor.
Rob Ford, the late Rob Ford.
I'm sorry.
Rest in peace Rob.
But instead of crack rocks, it's rock candy.
Yeah, made on site.
The Disney convexary.
Do snort it.
He's snorting rock.
He's got a pile of rock candy like Scarface.
Have you all done like a food based episode yet where you check it?
Not entirely though.
Our Harry Potter episode is very food centric.
We covered the food more than any other element.
The doughboys are very litigious.
We don't want to do that.
So does anybody have any other thoughts before we get to the scale we've been talking about?
I have one final thought which is I'd like to send some appreciation to the main.
There's all this music in the ride that's very of the period, very 40s.
The 40s Academy Award winning song, Zippity Doodah.
But you know, I'm a kid of the rad 80s.
I don't know if I can relate to this stuff.
And I appreciate that in a lot of these specials, they updated Zippity Doodah for the hip hop
generation.
And there are several pieces of material.
There was some special in the sing along songs.
Not only is it kind of a hip hop out Zippity Doodah that they present where there's like
a sample of a guy.
Zippity Doodah.
There is a little added rap verse.
You know what, here I'll just pre-say this is my plus it up is to get this great rap
that only exists in promotional materials into the ride itself.
And I could play a clip, but I think I owe it to everyone to perform it myself.
It's very brief, but I think it's very beautiful.
Well you know it is a thrill when you go downhill cause you're riding on a mountain of your
own free will.
And you're zipping in a flash on a daring dash down a waterfall so rapid that you go
splish splash.
Zip, zip, zip, zip, zip.
Let's get that beautiful refrain into the, that's echoed in, that's my favorite rap song.
I don't know about Kendrick Lamar, but I do know this.
It's a good little tune.
So kudos to the writers of Rappity Doodah.
Is that what it goes by?
No I'm going to call it that.
That's a long way from Percocet, Molly Percocet.
We'll put that up too.
That's one of the old sing along songs.
So I combined some segments.
That's my plus.
That's all right.
That's great.
So let's plus it up for Scott.
Jason what do you think?
Yeah I think, well my plus it up is like let's get those show scenes always lit.
Let's get those animatronics always moving cause that show boat scene is so fun.
I'm wondering if you know, sometime soon, maybe a few years down the line, we reexamine
some of those voices.
Maybe soften those voices a little more even cause I feel like when we were watching the
ride through I was like oh there's one or two moments where I don't know.
I mean I still think it's more fun.
Well again get them doing the rap.
Put the rap.
Make the dialogue with the rap.
Yeah but I do think it's fun and I do think I would be interested to see as we get older
what the conversation is around the source material if something eventually does come
out or if consensus, I don't know if consensus will ever be reached on that movie but like
I think it's an interesting thing.
If a consensus is reached let's put that next to the safety instructions on the ride.
Here is where history has landed on Song of the South, the film on which this ride is
based.
Yeah but I do think it is an example of a thing that was inspired by another thing that
has transcended its original source material.
I would say that yes the fun ride is better than the racially disputed film.
It's official.
That's a mayoral decree.
People enjoy this ride.
Alright, G you want to go next?
Sure.
Well I've kind of already said a bit of what I changed.
I'll reiterate a little quickly.
I'll say that I think it's an almost perfect ride as is.
I really love it.
Obviously I have a very bizarre emotional attachment to it.
Maybe Brain was mentioned a couple times on the podcast today.
But if I were to make some fun tweaks I always feel like there are moments and don't get
me wrong, the animatronics are great.
When I'm on a slower dark ride I almost want to interact a little bit more.
I would love if you could bring a mug, maybe a souvenir mug with you and maybe one of the
animatronics pours you a little something into it.
You're going slow enough.
You can tie in some sponsorships if you'd like Coca Cola products.
Maybe you bring some of the sodas from Cool Club, from Epcot, the Coca Cola, some international
sodas.
I don't know how that feels.
I'm really a bitter one.
Yeah.
Holds into the South, American South.
That's the beauty of the river wine.
That's the beauty of the rivers of America, right?
America is a melting pot of sodas.
So I would say maybe it's a little interactive tinge there.
I agree with Jason.
Voice changes.
Bring the Rob Pulsons of the world in.
I don't need Selena Gomez voicing rare rabbit.
I don't want any celebrities that usually takes me out of it.
But those are my very minor changes where I find a very fun ride experience.
Okay.
That sounds good.
I have a, okay, I'm going to say, I'm going to say plus it up, but what I'm going to say
when I say plus, I guess it's kind of a lateral move.
Here's what I want.
Pull all the America Sings animatronics back out, put them back into Tomorrowland, bring
back America Sings.
That place has been empty for too long.
There needs to be something in Tomorrowland that people want to go see.
Take those characters out.
Now the Winnie the Pooh attraction, kind of less popular.
Take Pooh Bear, all the animatronics from that, replace all of the America Sings animatronics
on Splash Mountain with the Pooh Bear and the Pooh characters.
This is the honey pot slow ride?
Yes, the slow butt.
Tigger, Piglet, Kanga, Little Roo, all of the characters.
Put them on the riverboat, put them in like fun dresses, dancing.
I don't care.
I'm just saying that Splash Mountain is such a good ride, it can withstand to lose some
of these robots.
We cannot take Tomorrowland being like this for much longer.
I mean, the thing should be condemned.
It's unbelievable.
Hold on, wait a second.
Excuse me?
That's madness.
What do you mean?
Pooh and Tigger company live in, what is the name of the wood?
The Hundred Acre Woods.
Isn't that in England?
That's in Christopher Robin's imagination, Jason.
It can be anywhere.
Okay.
He can imagine it to be in the antebellum south.
Post antebellum.
Wait, does antebellum mean current?
Antebellum means pre-war.
Oh shit, well I learn something every day.
Post-Reconstruction era.
Okay, you're right.
So the war's been fought, things are fine.
See, and that was the problem with the movie.
People weren't sure when it took place.
Yeah, that was it.
But you, yeah, that was it.
So these swamp creatures, their friends from Britain are just visiting?
It does not ever occur to me that Winnie the Pooh is British.
Yeah, no.
He's not, he's no Paddington.
He doesn't wear his country on his sleeve.
Christopher Robin is British, but we don't need him in the ride.
He doesn't, he's, yeah, if anything.
He's the boring character.
Yeah, he's the boring, I don't really.
Tigger's hijinks are gonna be perfect for the Laughing Place, Jason.
He's laughing constantly.
I agree.
I think Pooh could fit in.
I also think like, Pooh is like, he is pretty malleable.
He's just kind of like a slow, hungry character that like you can just put in.
But Jason, do you have a rebuttal potentially?
I don't mean to hijack the fact.
No, no, please.
But like would you put a different set of characters in?
Wait a minute, I don't want to replace your answer, but the, what are the country bears
doing?
Hey, they're sitting around somewhere?
Now there's a plus it up to my plus it up.
Yeah, former residents of the country.
Let's get all these fucking characters off the ride and let's put Liverlips McGraw in
there.
Let's put Gomer and his, let's put Trixie in.
These are beloved characters as far as I'm concerned.
I've never been more passionate about any of my life.
It's a shame that timing didn't work out that no one went like, wait, why don't we do the
same thing with the country bear?
Let's put, yeah, let's put the country bears in.
The country bears is subject to some of the craziest timing in Disneyland history where
they took the ride out as they were prepping the release of the film.
What are you thinking?
You're going to make a movie that looks that you know is bad.
You guys know this.
You have a bunch of bears singing with Bonnie rate and shit.
You know, this isn't going to be good anyway.
At least use your one tie in opportunity.
Yet another episode we have to do is watch that goddamn country bears movie that doesn't
even use any of the character country bears from the show.
Yeah, just a bunch of different weird bears and they all sing with like Ernie.
Yeah.
They sing with the voices of Bonnie raid and Don Henley and it's not even like, where's
your classic big owl voice separate though from the actual country bears.
Yes.
There'll be many country bears episodes.
There'll be many.
Okay.
Very bear holiday in Japan anyway.
But I think we stumbled upon something interesting.
Get some more animatronics in there.
I find that.
Yeah.
Take all the characters out of splash mountain and put the country bears on.
We have to put America sings back together.
Yes.
Boy, we have the hundred year, the 300 year centennial is right around the road.
We need to get ready for the next, ready for tricentennial fever.
Yeah.
It'll catch you.
I mean, if there is one thing that could heal our nation right now, it might be America
sings here in here in an Eagle with the voice of burl lives singing.
You're a grand old flag.
You're a high fly and flag.
Maybe even bring back old Bonnie right to sing.
Like, I don't know.
To do Ron Ron.
Sure.
Yep.
Nation.
He'll do it.
No doubt.
That'll do it.
All right.
Very nice.
Well, we figured it out.
We figured out what to do.
Okay.
So the last thing, geo, we've kind of constructed a little bit of a game here and I'm going
to be the game master.
I put this together and it's based on, Oh, and Lindsay and I went to Disney world a couple
of years ago.
There was some construction walls up and when they have these construction walls up, they
put things on them to entertain you.
So it's not just a standard wall.
And for, I forget what was, I think it was seven dwarfs and they put up quotes from Walt
Disney and you know, there's a couple of quotes everyone's familiar with, which is like, you
know, just remember it all started with the mouse and uh, let's see what another famous
quote.
Uh, show doesn't go on because it's ready.
It goes on cause it's 1130.
Walt's not ready for prime time.
Walt Disney started Saturday night live.
Didn't he?
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
I thought that was a quote about weekend.
Or a studious, no, it was a studio 60.
I think that's a Matt out.
Who would Walt's, uh, who would have, he would have had Wally Bogue in his cast.
Who would Walter all Ravens, girl Ravens, crawl, freeze, Sterling Holloway.
Oh my God.
Can you imagine a net Louie Armstrong, a regular cast member, uh, Kurt Russell and then, uh,
Joseph McCarthy, Senator Joseph McGarthy, Nixon.
And Suzanne Plachette.
That was a hell of a cast.
I like the Nixon Plachette era the most.
You like the era you grew up with.
Yeah.
People, yeah.
I know people say this, but great music during those seasons too.
Great music.
The guests.
Yeah.
Zippity doo da performed every single week.
And the Sherman brothers.
The Mormon Tabernacle choir.
So you were saying.
Yeah.
So I was saying, so, so once those quotes were out of the way, there were a lot of mundane
quotes to put it mildly stuff that seemed very like there was no specific character
to it.
Okay.
And then I started looking up like other walled quotes.
So I'll give you a one of the other quotes when you're curious, you find lots of interesting
things to do.
And that is a Walt Disney quote.
That is a quote.
It's been attributed to him.
I don't know why, but I looked it up and there are many of these quotes that are just very
mundane seeming.
There's no magic in them.
You don't, you couldn't tell who said them by, if you gave them a list of famous people.
So I found all these, I wrote, I found six of them and then I wrote six fake ones.
Oh, okay.
So what we're going to do is I'm going to read both of the quotes and you guys are going
to guess what's the fake walled quote and what's the real walled quote.
Okay.
So if some, well, I'll, I'll keep a score here.
All right.
So let's start.
I'll give you one line and obviously I'll switch them around so you don't know what's
first.
So, so one of the lines is the two things that have best aided me in my professional
life are ideas and persistence.
Okay.
Now the other line is laughter is America's most important export, which is the real vault
quote.
I can repeat them if you want.
I think the first one is real.
Okay.
You want me to repeat them or no, I'm going to agree.
I think the first one's real cause it's like has that kind of sad depression era vibe to
it?
The more his era.
Yeah.
Uh, what do you think?
The first one, the second one is the real one.
Wow.
The fake wall quote.
The fake is the two things that have best aided me in my professional life are ideas
and persistence.
That is fake.
I wrote that.
Excellent.
Sounds real.
Laughter is America's most important export is a real Walt Disney quote.
All right.
That sounds like something you'd hear it like at the NBC up fronts or something.
Oh yeah.
No, it's these full of these.
Okay.
So, all right, here we go.
The first line, uh, Disneyland represents the America that exists in our hearts.
And the second one is, uh, you may not realize it when it happens, but a kick in the teeth
may be the best thing in the world for you.
It seems I'm going to say second cause the first one seems so clean.
It seems like a fake out.
Yeah.
It almost is too, too, uh, Disney.
I think, I think the first one is real this time.
I'm going to, I'll say, I think it's the second one and he said it on his deathbed.
Final words.
Uh, I don't know where any of these quotes came in his life, so I don't know if he was
dying when he said these, uh, the correct is the second one.
Jason loses that.
I've stopped keeping score cause who cares?
Uh, all right.
Drag of your own.
All right, here we go.
Next one.
Uh, I would rather entertain and hope that people learn something than educate people
and hope they were entertained.
And then the other one is when you find a great collaborator, someone who you get along
with and who can understand and execute your vision, hang on to them.
Okay.
You can play at home too.
First one feels, uh, like it could be like an Epcot.
I will have no, he like when you were his idea of Epcot, he wanted it to be like educational
and utopian.
Uh, I'll say the first one.
Yeah, I'll go with that too.
I'll go first too.
This time.
The answer is the first one.
All right.
Good.
Now you guys are on track here.
So I have at least two, but I don't know.
Yeah, let's just do, we'll do one more cause I think I only have one more good one.
Uh, all right, here we go.
Uh, the first one is when you're in the thick of something, remember to take a moment for
yourself.
Now the second one is of all the things I've done, the most vital is coordinating those
who work with me and aiming their efforts at a certain goal.
That one's Hitler.
No, I jig is up.
First.
Uh, yeah, I think it's the first one or the second one could be his deathbed quote.
Now that I think about it, I think it might be the first one cause I can just picture
that picture of him wandering through the castle before the park opened one day.
Just smiling that that seems like, okay, sure.
Yeah.
All right.
So first and second to you, you're all wrong.
What?
It's the second one that was Walt.
No quote of all the things I've done.
The most vital is coordinating those who work with me and aiming their efforts at a certain
goal.
Walt Disney inspirational Walt Disney.
So if you want to go look up Walt Disney quotes and there's so many of them and most of them
are just the most boring Disney dry.
Yeah.
There's like career counselor.
I swear this is probably a bit weak, but like it just felt like he was on the, on the wall
when we were walking by.
It was just like, make sure to always have a good executive assistant, like just like
very dry, like advice he'd give to a colleague who was starting an office.
Right.
If you're building a river with a massive boat, make sure that it's simple enough to
pilot that a teenager can do it.
Yeah.
That's good advice for a theme park.
I take a car to work.
It's quicker.
I think Burbank is a perfectly pleasant place to work.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Say that again.
I'll get it down on the statue at the California adventure.
Did you all, when you're at Disney world, did you go through the, like that kind of,
um, they have like the museum and that one man's dream and then it ends on the theater,
but the theater doesn't show anything about him.
It's just like whatever new Disney movies coming out.
So I went through Walt one man's dream.
I was like, Oh, this is kind of nice.
Uh, they harped a little too much in his hometown.
Didn't care too much about it, but, uh, uh, yeah, but I, uh, I got to the end of it and
I was like, Oh cool, there's a movie and this guy's like, the movie starting and he didn't
tell me what it was.
And I walked in and it was just like 10 minutes of the new pirates of the Caribbean.
That I think they changed cause it used to be a movie where the only dialogue was clips
of him.
That makes way more sense.
And then at some point they're like, we gotta get people aren't using chest clips in here.
Right.
Maybe without Walt's imagination and pension for dreaming, you don't end up with Paul McCartney
as captain Jack's weird uncle in jail.
And what a scene.
One never could have dream Paul McCartney pirate in jail.
Uh, well on that note, yeah.
Hey Gio, you've survived podcast.
The ride man.
Well, it was the splash mountain of podcasts.
Hey, now, uh, here, let's get a photo before you go.
Hey, uh, lift up that sweater.
Hey, flash those titties.
Well, is it, you don't want to do that.
Was there anything you do want to promote or alert people to?
Um, no, just, uh, maybe check out people of earth.
Season three will come back in the fall.
Um, Twitter, you want Twitter?
I'm on Twitter every couple of months.
By that you mean years.
Um, yeah.
At, uh, a G I O E uh, oh, and I perform on Friday nights at UCB on Franklin, uh, with
the group called JV.
So you ever want to do a Friday night thing there?
There's something for you.
Yeah.
Great.
Uh, yeah.
And you can follow us.
Podcast the ride at Twitter, Instagram, uh, podcasts, right?
Gmail hashtag Jason for DLR.
You know, it's catchy when the host forgets.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
And well, let's do this.
We'll make Jason Mayer by 2031.
Great.
That starts now.
Thanks for listening everyone.
Bye bye.