Warning, today's podcast may include Hollywood vampires, guns that shoot CDs, a Californication
revelation and an in-depth look at the ride featuring the bad boys from Boston, rock and
roller coaster starring Aerosmith.
Yes, we're the ones that jaded you.
It's Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show hosted by three men who at best could be described
as late bloomers, but even that's a reach.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Scott Gertner.
Hi Jason.
Hi.
And Mike Carlson.
Yeah, hi Jason, thank you for that.
I was a late bloomer.
I guess I'm still blooming if you really think about it.
Hey, we all are.
Yeah, I guess we are.
Who's to say?
What a not magical world it would be if the blooming process was ever totally complete.
That's a good point.
We should all aspire to keep blooming even into our golden years.
Well, we're all always students of life, aren't we?
Yeah, I guess we are.
You have a real professorial vibe to you today.
We never stop learning.
Yeah.
This is kind of like this wistfulness, this wistful intimacy I feel like we have right
now without a guest.
It's just the three of us, no one to introduce and I don't know, I think it allows us to
be in this sensitive headspace, whatever it is, which pairs great with the rock music
themed ride we'll be talking about.
I mean, look, once we get into this talk, we're going to transform from three thoughtful
professorial types to three dirty dogs.
And I'm not talking about Edwin, the official show dog who's lying on the couch already
starting to fall asleep at the sound of these three men talking.
I will take a photo of the official show dog right now during the show and I will post
it.
Oh yes.
Well, now that we've exposed our show dog to the...
To the Twitter.
Edwin, the podcast ride show dog.
Yeah.
Part of the mythology, you know, before we get going too far, there's a little bit of
theme park information that just came across my desk as it were.
And just to get you guys into it, I want to do a little bit of a word association because
this is a word that I was not previously aware of and I want to see if you guys are.
So I'm going to say a word.
Okay.
And tell me if the word has any significance to you.
The word is HALYX.
HALYX.
Can you spell that?
I sure can.
It is spelled H-A-L-Y-X.
Y-X.
HALYX.
No, I don't.
Am I supposed to word associate?
Like is it a psychologist's office or no?
Is it just me and do I know anything about it?
Well, does it make you...
I'm not necessarily...
HALYX sounds like helix.
I think of helix, which is I think of a roller coaster.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, look, I mean, it's a funky spelling.
It's a pretty wild spelling, which I think indicates...
Three consonants.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, all in a row.
All in a row.
It makes me think of like a Kinect set.
Like one of those cool, like not...
You know what I'm talking about?
Like it was like a...
Oh yeah, I had a Y in Kinects of a roller coaster.
Oh yeah.
Well, there you go.
Was it a HALYX set?
Is that what you're getting at?
I am not.
Well, here's what HALYX is.
I'm so excited you guys don't previously know about HALYX.
Yeah, I don't know this.
Is that proprietary thing?
Like a very specific thing?
This is a Disney property, perhaps the least utilized great Disney property.
And here's what HALYX is.
HALYX was a band that was invented specifically for Disneyland that played at the Tomorrowland
stage in the early 80s.
Wow.
It was used to combine the appeal of the band KISS with the Star Wars franchise.
No way.
What?
And I'm now going to show you a photograph of HALYX.
Whoa, what?
Look at this.
This is wild.
Check the Twitter.
Holy shit.
Look up Google HALYX if you're listening to this.
If you're driving, get off the road.
Or keep driving and immediately check out HALYX.
Worth the potential collision.
Oh wow.
So if I could...
I mean, if you want to help me describe what I'm looking at, this is a...
I'm looking at a two now.
Sea of musical rapscallions.
You've got sort of a Rick Springfield dude in a puffy 80s jacket.
You've got...
It's very Battlestar Galactica in look.
Yeah.
And even costuming.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
It's cool.
Very 80s, 70s, 80s space for sure.
You've got kind of a solid gold dancer dude, sort of a Jufro vibe.
Whoa.
Couple more solid gold dancers in the back.
And then kind of a big, an abominable snowman.
Yeah.
He looks like the guy that Luke cuts open.
Or Luke kills.
Luke kills in the cave an empire.
Ah, right, right.
Uh-huh.
I don't know what that is called.
I know the Tauntaun is the beast that Luke rides on.
I don't know what this guy is called.
Nothing that big in the band.
But a lot...
Look, it's an armada of humans and creatures who unite with their common interest in the
power of rock.
So I found out about this because as I told you guys off the air, I met a gentleman who
worked for Disney in the early 80s.
And we were sort of doing our little like Disney nerd off.
As you do, you just start dropping references and see how far you can go.
And I said, oh, you know, we just did an episode about Videopolis.
And he was like, oh, I was at the opening of Videopolis.
Damn, losing.
And then he threw out, well, you know about Halyx, right?
I do not know about Halyx.
Whoa.
I mean, yeah.
You know, it was Disney's Kiss.
I'm talking about it.
So I immediately looked up everything about Halyx.
I had to like try to I had to really suppress not telling you guys.
I wanted to tell you here in the moment.
So yeah, they played at the Tomorrowland stage, which is where the Captain EO theater is now.
Although what is currently Star Wars previews in New Oblivion.
I don't think we're getting rid of that path of the Jedi thing.
No, that'll be there for until 2030 at least.
Way past when all of the film, many trilogies come out.
We'll still be looking at it.
I like the younglings and who become Padawans.
The path of the Jedi never ends.
For even when you become master, there's still a lot more to learn.
And even when one trilogy is over, seven more start.
Seven more.
Hey, everyone gets a trilogy now.
Y'all get it.
Hey, depending on how meetings go this week, we might end up with a trilogy.
Yeah, hopefully.
Oh, there's Star Wars meetings we have this week that we're already plugging on a podcast.
We're as primed as anybody.
Anyway, so this is a band that performed basically under Space Mountain, the greatest venue in
the world.
I would have to think for a band.
And OK, so yeah, they wanted to Disney wanted to have some summer entertainment.
They wanted to bring rock into the Disney fold.
And there I don't think had been you know, we're talking about Aerosmith Rock and Roller
Coaster today.
And I think this might be the first attempt to get rock music into Disneyland.
So this was put together, a guy named Jim Magon helped supervise it, a guy who later
wrote for Darkwing Duck, Tailspin, Goof Troop, a goofy movie, a guy who in the 90s was one
of their primary writers.
And he has a personal website where he sadly, as far as I could tell, there's like a part
one and part two of the Halyx story and part three was never done.
It was like six years ago.
So hey, Jim spelled J-Y-M-N, a similarly odd spelling as Halyx.
And to your part three, I want to know the full Halyx tale.
So yeah, Disney wanted to put together a rock band that they enlisted the help of a guy
named Mike Post.
Does Mike Post mean anything to you?
This is the guy who did like all of the 80s, 90s, 70s theme songs, primarily known probably
for Greatest American Hero.
Right.
Believe it or not, I'm walking, which was my the first dance at my wedding.
Sure.
He also did.
And then utterly unsurprising news.
He also this guy did with the full list, Magnum P.I.
Blossom, My Opinionation.
Wow, this guy's a titan.
Yeah.
Doogie Howser, Hill Street Blues, Quantum Leap, NYPD Blue, and then like Don Don't, Law
and Order is him.
Wow, really?
He did Don Don't.
But before he was quite the industry titan that he is today, he put together the songs
for a Star Wars themed rock band.
An open cast and call was done.
And they put together this odd little posse.
Probably probably the most notable thing, if you're looking at art of this, is that
there is a robot who has like kind of a full cart apparatus around him.
And so this guy had to play keyboards in a full like droid costume and inside a vehicle.
I'll show you guys this.
They like took an industrial golf cart and put space dude ads all over it and then built
a Prophet five synthesizer into the vehicle.
So Andy is wearing like robot gloves.
So this dude is driving a cart around the stage because they didn't want the keyboard
player to be stationary.
This is a space band.
We need to revolutionize.
Oh yeah, you got to move around.
Space is about movement.
Certainly.
I was sleepy before this and it feels like you shot the Pulp Fiction needle into my heart
with adrenaline hearing that there was a space band with aliens at Disneyland in the 80s.
This is insane.
Robots, aliens, and then just regular cool people.
Just guys who look like they'd be on like they look straight out of the movie Semi Pro.
Yeah, it's their phenom.
It's hard to just describe this.
We'll post pictures, see what we're looking at.
But also it's one of those things, you know how like we love to romanticize and talk about
the Chuck E. Cheese band, the Rock of Fire explosion and how all these things have this
deep mythology and names that people keep track of and only people like us care about.
This band, not the case.
They didn't bother to name anybody.
There is nothing you can look up.
Oh, we know what it is.
Oh, names.
Yeah, kind of disappointing.
And everyone involved in this project universally just calls the big guy a Wookie.
Even though he's clearly not a Wookie, he is white, he is an abominable snowman.
But they're like, ah, you know, and then the Wookie basically are.
They were using it like clean and you say Kleenex when you mean like tissue.
They were just like a big hairy guy at that point was just a Wookie, even though it was
not a brand.
It was not a on brand Wookie.
It's a type.
Yeah, yeah.
Whether it's the bottom shelf of the serial aisle or the top.
Also, all those costumes very clearly like half trying to look like Star Wars and the
other half working very hard to skirt the line so they don't get sued for copyright
infringement or like.
The keyboard player is basically a stormtrooper.
But then there's just kind of like Sun Ra space Egyptians and tight gold pants.
I don't know the whole thing.
There's a real aesthetic happening here.
Just to say the whole history of it.
Also, they went through different names and styles.
I'm looking at concept art of the original name of the band Starfire.
One word they also thought about calling it strike and they thought about calling it squad
SKWAD before finally landing on Halyx.
They all agree they didn't know what the word Halyx meant, but let's call it that.
So not only a keyboard player driving a golf cart around, but also a Wookie bass player
and who has to play bass in a mask and gloves.
And he's really doing it.
There is no pre-recorded anything going on.
He's covered in yak fur.
That's what the suit was made from.
And then the percussionist of the band, not particularly themed, but he is doing somersaults
and backflips with a rope when he is not being called on to hit mallets and wind chimes.
This seems to me like the finest band.
This is the best band I think I like.
This is my favorite band, I think.
Without having heard anything, you just know from pictures.
I know that this is my favorite band.
I Googled this as soon as you were telling me about it.
I find out there is a YouTube video that says Halyx performs Jailbait.
Yes, I've heard the song Jailbait if I could approximate.
These are original songs.
They are original songs written by the guy who wrote Dun Dun and Blossom's My Opinionation.
The pedigree is very high.
So there is Jailbait, which if I could approximate the chorus, it's a female singer.
Well, I want you, but you're Jailbait.
Who approved that at Disneyland?
This is a song being played only at Disneyland.
There is no other venue for this and they are doing a song about Jailbait.
The common scenario of a woman who is lusting after an underage boy.
Was she also a space high school teacher?
Is that a part of the canon?
Oh, they didn't have a canon.
I'm going to add that to the legend of this.
That might help justify their lyrics.
Every lyric is justified at the end by going, and we're in space.
Laws are different here.
Don't forget, we're in space.
We're talking space years.
But although no matter what the years are, if you are Jailbait.
That concept is universal regardless.
If they're using that term, unless it totally means something different in space.
Unless jail isn't as much of a problem.
Jail is good in space.
I guess in the space of Halyx, yes.
It's not so bad.
Jail is good.
Why, it turned out that Han Solo and Luke Skywalker.
No, I fucked that up.
Oh, Jason.
Han Solo and Princess Leia turned out to almost be Jailbait for Luke Skywalker and F. Broward
Strink's back.
Oh, yes, sure.
We really walked around to that one.
In the most literal, I know.
I walked and tripped down the stairs along the way.
A different reason you would go to jail for a space relationship.
I don't have the song.
I don't have that song pulled, but I do have a song called Lightning.
So here now, ladies and gentlemen, a little brief taste of Halyx.
This is my favorite band.
That's kind of the vibe you need.
But if that's where you're starting, it's only getting better from there.
Not a lot of views on these videos.
I feel like a lot of people do not know about Halyx.
I want to get the word out.
The sound there is sort of a it's kind of a kind of a foreigner meets meets Toto meets
Bon Jovi's runaway and like a vocoder at the start that sounds sort of like Main Street
Electrical Parade a little bit.
They got that vibe with the Main Street Electrical Parade still in action at the time.
I mean, I feel like if I'd been if I was going to Disneyland in this era, it would have been
one of the three things I talked about.
I'm not sure I'd be excited about Pirates of the Caribbean as much as this band with
the Wookie and the guy driving his keyboard around.
Well, let's let's let's real quick.
What would you give up to have Halyx be in the park today in the same version doing the
same songs?
What ride would you give up?
Monkey Monkeys?
Oh, no, you you have a simpler idea.
I thought I thought you were trying to get us to know we have to have souls or like that
helps.
Yeah, I want Halyx in the park now.
And I'm wondering what I would give up for it.
You mean like an attraction?
Yeah, it's a big attraction.
Something's got to go.
But Halyx can come back.
It's a trade with the devil.
The devil is at your door.
Autopia says, yeah, that's easy, though.
But it's well, hang on.
What if they're in the Autopia trail?
What if you're driving around them?
They have to play all day in the sun around the Autopia track.
They sure do to make up for their many years of absence.
Halyx has got to sweat it out in the sun and we'll be better off for it.
And they take all the Autopia cars and they put keyboards in them.
So you can play along just like the unnamed robot man.
ToonTown.
We're getting rid of ToonTown.
I'll get rid of the Matterhorn.
How about that?
Hey.
For Halyx?
Are you kidding me?
Yeah.
Well, again, what if they transform that the much hallowed basketball court?
They turn that into like a private Halyx club.
Oh, man.
See a secret show at Disneyland?
You get me.
You got to line up outside the Matterhorn.
Yeah.
And you have to do a lot of concerts.
Wow.
I'm sure this would take.
It is your reward for actually climbing the mountain.
You have to.
Oh, you have to climb to get in to see Halyx.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a danger element.
You got to show how much you want it.
But then that mountain sort of becomes a space mountain also.
So it's sort of a second space mountain because they have to be playing in space.
Yeah.
Well, look, it's overlooking Tomorrowland.
I think you can.
Yeah, OK.
Fine with that.
It's kind of on the border.
That's sort of pulling it over.
Halyx.
Yeah, this reminds me, the concept of Disney making a band reminds me of a thing that I
have to occasionally look up and remind myself to make sure I didn't hallucinate it is Devo
2.0.
Have we talked about Devo 2.0?
Not in this setting we haven't.
I know about Devo 2.0.
Yeah, Devo 2.0.
According to Wikipedia, a quintet created for Walt Disney Records of child actors who
sing and dance and in the music videos and photo shoots, mime playing instruments along
the songs re-recorded by some of the original members of Devo.
And this album, I guess there was an album and a DVD came out in 2006.
And in the spring of 2006, I would have been at Disney World in the summer of 2006.
I just remember signs everywhere for Devo 2.0.
And I kind of knew about Devo.
I wasn't the biggest Devo.
I'm still, I like Devo, but there's some people who are like, Devo man, like Devo fans.
That's one of their guys.
I think of that era.
Yeah, they have attracted a particular, which I've gone in and out of.
I know them a little deeper than other people.
But it didn't make me any happier to hear about Devo 2.0, I'll tell you.
And I guess my equivalent band would have been the Pixies.
Like in college, I got really into the Pixies and read a lot about them and went to one
of the reunion shows and that sort of thing.
And then for some people, that was the Devo reunion.
But yeah, Devo 2.0 is just all these signs with kids.
And I feel like on the bus, they were playing the songs.
They're like, check out Devo 2.0.
And I'm like, I don't get that.
And then some people have tried to explain it.
It's like, well, in the mythology of Devo, it makes sense because it's all about consumerism.
And then there's all this backstory about Devo that I get little bits and pieces of
sometimes.
And I don't quite understand it.
But look, I'm into backstory stuff.
So I'm sure I would enjoy it if I went a little deeper.
I like the idea that a band is commenting on the de-evolution of society and culture.
There's some truth to that.
However, that justifies you putting out a cash grab kids record and having the song
whip it be turned into Swift it in Swiffer commercials.
I feel like they have taken a little too much license in saying, oh, no, no, no.
But we are being subversive.
I've heard about Mother's Baw doing backwards messages in Devo songs.
He's doing a song for a commercial, but then it's actually a backwards voice saying, corporations
control your mind.
And nobody even knew what was in there.
But you're still getting a check from the vacuum company.
I don't know.
I think I've always had an issue.
Not saying I wouldn't do it.
Not saying.
Oh, yeah.
Well, that's the thing.
Yeah.
Just sell out all the way.
Yeah, sure.
Everyone has.
Yeah.
Maybe his mind is more focused on his two decades of movie soundtrack.
It's wonderful movie soundtracks.
There's a lot of good ones.
Oh, I'm a Mark Mother's Baw fan.
Yeah.
This particular line of logic that I have an issue with.
I can't believe Devo 2.0 was given concert space at Disney World.
I wonder if they drew a crowd.
If you watch the videos.
Oh, I didn't see that.
I just saw posters for the album.
Oh, gotcha.
OK.
I think they were playing it in part or like certainly probably blasting it in downtown
Disney or whatever.
And then kids without knowing it are suddenly on the drive home asking their parents, like
are corporations actually controlling us?
Dad?
Fun fact, one of the members of Devo 2.0 was the actress Jacqueline Emerson, who went on
to be in The Hunger Games.
How about that?
Good for Miss Emerson.
Spreading the subversive vibes still to this day.
Well, if you're going to compare the well, hey, actually, that that ties it in because
whereas now Disney has the full record label and they have a mechanism on which to put
out great rock music like Devo 2.0, they were not comfortable with putting out.
So also they cut a Halyx record.
There was an album produced by this legit producer of it was Disney was not comfortable
putting it out on their label because Walt Disney Records was like Cinderella storybooks
and that kind of thing.
Oh, boy.
And we're looking at a hell of a poster here.
Is that real or fan?
I don't know.
What do you think?
I think I think that might be official.
I think it looks real to me.
It looks so cool.
It looks so of its time.
It's perfect.
Yeah.
It's very much.
It's not just the Star Wars vibe, but a little Flash Gordon, too.
It's kind of all the craziest 70s, 80s laser excess.
And so, yeah, they similar to that, Disney didn't want to put out adult films on their
own label.
So they did Touchstone and other things.
They put they were going to put the Halyx record out on Electra Records, still major
record label, and then it got bought by something else.
And the new head, as often happens, the new head of the label was not was some inhuman
monster who didn't want a space band getting released.
But like, oh, there's got to be bootleg.
There's got.
Is there a leak?
Is there a bootleg?
You would have to find it right now.
I couldn't.
I couldn't find it.
I dug a little bit.
Interrupt all proceedings if you find it.
But I'll just put out generally into the world that if there is a Halyx record out there,
if anybody has it, please see it to us.
Our DMS are open.
Yeah, the EMS are open and and maybe maybe do some advance.
If anyone out there is on the dark web, turn your turn your Bitcoin mining setups into
mine.
Hey, hey, hey, look, hey, looks fine, you look straight most powerful dark web search
engines that you're like hackers flying through the world wide web.
Find us.
Something that matters.
Help three nerds hear an album where a robot sings
about a woman wanting to have sex with a minor.
Oh, that's all I want.
We finally have a goal.
We have something to look forward to in our lives.
I have the song Jail Bay, right?
You heard that?
And there's also a song, His Heart.
That's what I, these are all live recordings.
They're all excellent.
I enjoy all of it.
We'll see these out there.
But here's a bigger proposition I have,
which is we're about to get,
you talk about bringing Halex back.
We're about to get a great new venue put into the park,
the Cantina, the Star Wars Galaxy's Edge.
Pulling the thoughts right out of my brain.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
And we have DJ Rex coming, which is very exciting for you,
Star Wars Tour fans.
We're of Rex, the original captain of the Star Speeder.
Scott, you love your big Rex fan.
I'm pretty excited.
I don't know, there's something that seems a little cheesy
about this use of him.
And also, how is this bumbling pilot
suddenly a confident, cool DJ?
Well, I don't think he is a confident, cool DJ.
I think he's a bumbling DJ.
Maybe he's knocking records over.
I'm pretty sure that's gonna be the angle.
Spilling glasses.
How do we know that piloting Star Tours vessels
was not his nine to five day job?
And DJing was his true passion.
Mm-hmm, you know what?
If he introduced himself to a person on the street,
you would say, I'm a DJ, but on the side, I'm...
Perhaps.
Well, like current Uber and Lyft drivers.
Yeah, right.
He considers his primary function a DJ.
Huh, pretty ahead of its time, actually.
But I'm excited to see him come back,
and I'm glad he's gonna be manning the stage,
but I'm saying, I don't know what's going on there
in terms of it being an actual venue,
but this seems to me like a place for HALIX
to retake their mantle.
And not only that, but there is kind of,
there's a little history of robotic or futuristic bands
in the Disney and or Star Wars universe.
You have the Max Rebo band from Return of the Jedi.
You have, I can only imagine, Max Rebo is an elephant,
and he must be friends with or a relative of Hooter,
who ends up playing music with Captain Eo
in the climactic final musical battle.
I think you could get Hooter and the gang
banging on their metallic trash cans
or whatever's going on there.
Yeah, let's get all these bands,
well, and also, with the news about Chuck E. Cheese,
and the Chuck E. Cheese's band disappearing,
Munch's Make Believe band,
there's gonna be a lot of out of work
Chuck E. Cheese animatronics.
Why don't we get them into the canteen as well?
That's great, too.
It's an animatronic surplus, right?
It's like America Sings all over again.
I'll take your idea, I'll see it one better.
The three of us will be in HALIX.
Yes.
We'll play in the band.
We will take off from whatever we have to do next summer
whenever this opens.
We'll put Jason in that thing, that writing thing.
He plays keyboard.
He doesn't even have to play, it's just a track or whatever.
But you know, I play a little, Scott plays a little.
I think we should be HALIX.
I will take some classes, I'll learn gymnastics.
I'll take up the role of the summer salting percussionist.
This might also be the only way we get into Star Wars land.
If Armageddon, they seem to be preparing
for an end of the world sort of scenario.
For the crowds there.
Yeah, the crowds.
I don't know that the performers will even get to go
on the rides for months.
They might just put a black bag over your head
and rush you into the cantina and that'll be it.
Yeah, I think from what we're talking about,
that there's gonna be, we've learned that there's
potentially a lot of restrictions on annual pass holders
and can they get into Star Wars for the first summer
or not, like different levels will be.
It sounds like you might get punished
for being an annual pass holder.
Yes, I think you're gonna be outside of Galaxy's Edge
and there's gonna be big people cages.
It's gonna be like a children of men scenario
where people are caught in the hinterlands
between borders and dogs are barking at them
and pushing them into the corner.
And I don't know, I'm a little worried about
just border chaos at Galaxy's Edge.
It's gonna be a nightmare.
Unless we're Halyx.
Unless we can soothe the beasts with our musical tunes
and our hyper futuristic golf cart.
Hey guys, put your differences aside and check this out.
Din din din din din din din din din din din din din din.
Space boy, you're my space boy.
Wow, he's right.
Let's hug it out.
Hug it out.
We've launched a lot of different campaigns lately,
but I do think, let me see,
hashtag podcast the ride boys for Halyx.
Is that a hashtag?
Or how about just, let's tie it all together, Halyx 2.0.
Hashtag Halyx 2.0.
Oh great, Halyx 2.0.
Halyx 2.0, yeah.
If they start feeling the street team power
that is building about Halyx 2.0,
they'll be sure to, if they know it's gonna get,
I think we virally could get equal attention
to Star Wars Galaxies.
Just so we're on the same page,
that's Halyx 2, the number two, the word point,
and the number zero.
Because if you put a period in 2.0,
it will break the hashtag.
Oh, that's a good point.
No punctuation.
Okay, okay.
So Halyx, the number two, the word point,
and zero.
We'll show you online.
Should we also, in keeping with the bizarre spelling,
should there be an extra Y in there?
Or maybe the I in point is a one, or an exclamation point.
I'm just saying, while we're having fun with this
and complicating it.
Yeah, we might need to get a whiteboard out
and workshop this a little.
So check out the Twitter after this episode goes live.
We will keep noodling with this,
and we will determine what the hashtag is,
and hopefully it'll be ready
by the time you're checking out the Twitter.
Thanks again for, I know we give you a lot of assignments.
There's a lot of supplemental reading
and homework on this podcast.
That's what I love about theme parks, homework.
After you've listened to three guys talk
for an hour and a half, perhaps more, perhaps many more,
then go read further essays,
and do voting and street team work.
For free.
If we had our druthers, people would have to read
all about these parks to even be allowed in.
To understand the choices about crowd flow.
You would have to pass a written exam
to get into Star Wars land.
Why should you come to Galaxy's Edge?
You don't know what was here before.
You don't know it was the Hunchback of Notre Dame
Festival of Fools, and also backstage storage area stables.
Yes.
Prove your worth before you enter Galaxy's Edge.
All right, well, we're tossing a lot out there,
but mainly above all else, check out HALIX
so you can truly appreciate HALIX 2.0.
So from the beginnings of Rock in the Disney parks
to some grand total, the highest HALIX they ever reached.
Worldwide status.
Yeah.
Let's start talking about the Rock
and Rock in roller coaster starring Aerosmith.
Or as it is known in Paris, rock and roller coaster,
Avec Aerosmith.
Right.
Whichever you wish.
I think we should start by,
what is each of our personal relationship with Aerosmith?
That's exactly what I wanted to talk about.
I think it's important to calibrate this.
I'll go first.
I got into listening to popular music a little late.
My mom force fed me Herman's Hermits and The Beatles,
but mostly just the pop stuff, not the psychedelic stuff.
And like 60s pop music.
So when I was like 13 or 14,
then I started getting into the cool stuff.
We're talking The Cardigans, Love Fool.
We're talking anything that was on the radio.
That, by the way, is a great song.
Paula Cole.
Paula Cole, sure.
All that cool stuff.
And then at that point, my parents were like,
oh, he's getting into rock and roll music.
So then they started buying me, you know,
Best of Led Zeppelin and Best of This
and then Best of Aerosmith.
And man, I loved Aerosmith.
I'll tell you what.
All right.
I loved Aerosmith.
I thought they were great.
I liked the Don't Wanna Miss a Thing.
I liked Armageddon.
I liked that song.
I was very basic at the time,
as I guess you would say, with music.
And boy, did I love,
there was no song I loved more by Aerosmith
than 1999's Jaded.
I was gonna say, I think that is still my current favorite.
A pretty good song that I still kinda like to this day.
It would've been the right age.
Got a lot of play on the radio.
Probably got some play at school dances, right?
Does that sound right?
Yeah, a little bit.
I remember I was at a school dance
and I was dancing, it was like a slow dance
and it was I Don't Wanna Miss a Thing.
And I remember the girl who went with me at the time,
it started playing and she went, oh.
And I was like, what?
I went, what?
You pushed her to the ground.
But she had a cool, she liked Weezer
and like cool stuff that I didn't even like in high school.
That other platinum selling, the cooler platinum selling.
I wasn't cool enough to be in Weezer.
You weren't there yet.
I was like 17.
I got into Weezer like I was 18,
maybe around that same time.
But I wasn't way in yet.
As Jason said, I'll late Bloomer.
So yeah, I really liked Aerosmith.
There was a song called Girls of Summer on a Greatest Hit.
Oh, that's good.
That's a pretty good song as well.
Some girls.
Yes, still pretty good.
You know what?
I think we tend to like these sort of generic,
pretty good pop songs.
I think any band that had bought those songs
would have gotten something out of them.
Because they were like, I don't know actually
who wrote those songs, but they were,
in the 80s, they've kind of famously started writing
with five different songwriters at once
and all their hit they had.
I don't want to miss a thing.
Diane Warren, the most balladeer.
That was the very end of the insane selling albums era,
I feel like, insane CD selling.
I don't want to miss a thing.
That's about right.
A couple years left after 99.
A few years, but yeah.
Sure, and they were compilations and stuff.
What a weird take that we have on it.
Because you jaded and you like this Girls of Summer song.
And I specifically bought a single of the song Pink.
Oh yeah, Pink is.
I continue to like Pink, okay.
Pink is not a bad song.
We'll get into that.
It's a dirty song.
But it's a very catchy.
Joe Perry, I think famously, was a little upset
of all these pop songs.
He wanted to rock a little harder.
But Mr. Steven Tyler likes having hits.
Yeah, didn't Joe Perry end up in some Satriani
sort of like noodley indulgent,
jammy band.
With the Chickenfoot?
No, he's not in Chickenfoot.
This sort of tips my bit at the end,
but he's in the Hollywood Vampires.
Oh, that's what, oh wow.
The Jelly Dab Al's Super Band.
And he's in, I'm sure he's in his own,
he's had some solo albums as well.
But he's very much like a rock and roll guy.
And I think he was fighting with Steven
about having all these pop songs.
But Steven wanted hits, Steven didn't care.
I think Steven probably likes pop music more than Joe does.
This is similar to the tension between Brian Wilson
and Mike Love of the Beach Boys.
And probably at various times,
Mick and Keith and John and Paul,
except there is no genius anywhere in this scenario.
There's less of, like there's a few,
I'm about 25%, I feel like, through my Aerosmith feelings.
I'm gonna come back in an hour.
Because this seems right in your guys' wheelhouse.
Yes, it is.
Yeah, now I'm having 500 thoughts at once.
I will say the riff in Sweet Emotion is still awesome.
That is a very good riff.
And it's cool and I will listen to that any time.
Richard Linklater would agree with you.
Yes, Richard Linklater and I.
Do I like 70s Aerosmith?
I don't know.
Walk This Way doesn't hold up so much for me.
No, I find that sort of corny.
And I have a real, I get embarrassment goosebumps
very easily if I think something is corny and hokey.
I sort of, the hairs stand on my arm.
And I find.
Like a spider sense you would say?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
My cheesy sense is tingling.
Which happens during theme park shows a lot.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, you're gonna get a lot of corniness there.
But I think the Super Bowl halftime show
that they did with NSYNC,
where then they are joined by Nelly and Britney Spears
and they all do da-da-da-da, da-da-da-da.
And they're all like walking back and forth
and NSYNC's doing like pop locks.
It's happening.
My hairs are standing. Wow, getting.
I get such sheer embarrassment
for a big cornball musical number
that I have a literal bodily reaction to it.
I believe if we go back and watch that,
Joe Perry's having the same reaction.
I'm sure he was rolling his eyes
when they pitched him all that stuff.
The hair on the top of his head is.
But Stephen was like, yeah, wow, that's great.
Or whatever.
All of those people in one halftime show,
how much money, how much would that have cost?
I mean, I guess that's an amazing marketing at the time.
All deals.
There's deals happening.
Also, there was like a filmed segment
before everybody came out with Ben Stiller and Chris Rock
because it was an MTV produced halftime show.
So not only that, they had to pay Stiller and Rock
to do improvised cameos for this thing.
Stiller used to be great at those little pre-show sketch.
That was his wheel.
And the awards with him and Tom Cruise.
Zoolander born from the VH1 fashion awards.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, a rare film made out of award show sketches,
which they tried to do with,
oh no, Les Grossman, the Tom Cruise character
is from Tropic Thunder,
but then he did like a big dance at the MTV Movie Awards,
which they were, it seemed to be them,
that was like their fundraising effort
to make the Les Grossman movie,
which sadly did not occur.
Anyway, we're off the track.
Wait, Jason, what's your feeling?
Yeah, sure.
I think I said this before when Led Zeppelin came up,
but I knew them as like,
I knew them as like a huge band
and I would hear the singles on the radio
or like at the, they played it in the mall
or at theme parks and stuff.
I don't think I've ever owned an Aerosmith record.
Mm-hmm.
I don't think I've ever heard
an Aerosmith record start to finish,
but I knew the hits.
Like I think I probably knew all the hits.
I bet there are people who have Aerosmith tattoos
who have not heard an album all the way through.
Yes, that's true.
I guess I probably knew a lot of like the great,
what would be on the greatest hits.
I mean, when I would have been in like the,
in the middle school,
we started going to dances and all high school,
I mean, Don't Wanna Miss a Thing and Jade It
were like huge hits.
So they were certainly being played there.
So I probably knew them best.
The fact that there's potentially people more
in Aerosmith's era and who like them more
who are possibly screaming about the fact that all we,
oh yeah, I like them.
I like Jade It.
I like I Don't Wanna Miss a Thing.
We are not referring remotely to 70s, 80s
to the Alicia Silverstone era.
I praised the Sweet Emotion riff.
You did.
Yeah.
That's a cool riff.
What else do I like?
Dream On, I think I like Dream On.
It's okay, right?
Yeah.
Dream On is okay.
We're kind of, we're classic rock fans.
I don't know that we really need to think about Dream On
for too long.
I like, I'm looking at just the greatest hits right now.
Mama Kin, do we know that song?
I don't.
That's kind of a fun song.
I'm not gonna sing it, but it's fun.
Oh, I guess that's probably a big place I knew.
There is, I grew up with 1029, MGK, Philadelphia,
classic rock.
And they, I think would play,
they're at Bass and Marismith and they're for sure.
Back in the Saddle.
Don't know it.
I'm back in the Saddle again.
It's a very obnoxious sort of song.
They're pretty bluesy, which I think eliminates me
from a lot of musical runnings.
The more bluesy it is, and they did an entire album.
I wrote it down.
Yes, I have that album.
Yeah, what's it called?
It's called Honkin' on Bobo.
Why?
Oh, this is another thing with Aerosmith.
It's all just like, just the lamest bawdy dirty crap.
It's just, it's like, there's like one of their albums
is like one car humping another car.
It's just some lame.
How did I forget about Honkin' on Bobo?
That's what I wanted to call my Seth MacFarlane
crooner-esque album, where I sang American Songbook
standards and then Aerosmith sued me.
You know, it's weird that I forgot about that.
The chapter, I try to not bring it up around you,
but since it's out there.
Even I've buried it.
You'd think I would have brought it up very first thing
when asked what is my relationship with Aerosmith.
The lawsuit.
Yes, yeah.
Big Ones, which of course is dicks.
They've famously covered Big 10 Inch,
which is an old blues song.
It's an innuendo for a giant dick.
Is the fact that they covered The Beatles Come Together,
where they think they're a different type of.
Oh boy.
Maybe even their covers are sexualized.
I'm gonna say that is right.
Here's a big thing I remember knowing about Aerosmith
was like, when did this come out in the 90s
that Steven Tyler was Liv Tyler's father?
And I remember that being news and just a fact I learned.
I think I just knew it as like,
oh oddly enough, Steven Tyler is Liv Tyler's father.
Steven Tyler was Liv Tyler's father
and he didn't claim paternity for years.
I didn't know the second part.
Yeah, and that she grew up thinking
one of my favorite musicians, Todd Rungren,
was her father.
Oh, I don't think I realized that.
From one to another, very strangely,
because who's the mom?
Is it B.B.?
Yeah, Buell.
Yeah.
And then, well, which then once they got back together,
once father and daughter are friendly again,
what do you do but put her in a highly sexualized
lesbian themed music video?
If Trump were a rock star, that's what Trump would have done.
Trump would have put Ivanka in all of these sexy videos.
Really get the hair blowing.
Yeah, get her on set just directing her, yeah.
Get that long sweater she's wearing
flapping in the breeze.
Were you guys into the Alicia Silverstone?
I liked them at the time.
I like them less now.
I liked Cryin' Okay.
Amazing, I feel like, is the worst of the three.
Oh, it is, but then my favorite,
because it's got digital tunnels and virtual shit.
I probably should, I haven't listened to it a long time.
Cryin', what's crazy?
Crazy is okay.
Cryin', I feel like was my favorite at the time.
The best song probably of the trilogy.
Probably the best song is Cryin'.
The videos, I guess, the videos are good of their time.
They're very of their time.
I haven't watched them in a while.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, the point is,
I don't think this is an uncommon level of fandom
for Aerosmith.
Like am I, I don't know.
Are there people who are,
if you're like really into music,
or if you're a music critic, do you like Aerosmith?
I don't think so.
But at the same time,
I don't think it produces animosity.
Like Big Lebowski,
I hate the fucking Eagles level animosity.
Yeah, I think you're right.
And even I don't, yeah, I don't dislike Aerosmith.
I've had some good times with Aerosmith songs playing.
And so, but you know what?
What I'm saying is they would not be my first choice
of what to put on.
Right.
And in fact, when Disney in the 90s decided
to do a rock themed roller coaster,
Aerosmith was not their first choice.
Was not the first choice,
which I just learned about.
And it's crazy.
Yeah.
Can you guess?
Can anybody know?
As you might guess,
the Rolling Stones were the first band approached.
And I believe they actually were approached.
This is some Jim Hill info.
I believe they wanted seven to $10 million a year
in licensing.
That's a year in licensing.
Disney every year.
That corporation would have to pay the Rolling Stones
$10 million out of pocket.
That's wild.
Is that worth, and I think,
I don't think it is worth,
I don't think people are going,
I don't think anybody's going to the park
because there's a Rolling Stones ride.
Well also then that means that Aerosmith came in
at a much lower rate, a much more reasonable.
Yeah, 10% is what Hill claims.
10% of that amount?
Of one million split.
How many of them?
Five, six, four?
Depends on who's a,
well wait, of Aerosmith?
Of Aerosmith.
There are five.
There's five Aerosmith members.
Can anybody name them?
I can name all of them I believe.
Do we want me to do it?
Sure.
Steven Tyler, Joe Perry, Brad Whitford,
not Bradley Whitford, Brad Whitford,
Joey Kramer and Tom Hamilton.
How about it?
Wow, see five guys the whole time.
I didn't look that up before.
I just knew that.
That is weird that it has not been,
nobody's changed out.
Yeah, that is pretty odd.
There's a lot of personnel changes in bands of this level,
but they're all, they want those checks.
They don't want the checks going to some guy
who looks like them.
That is impressive though.
And I also think it's funny that these names
that are sort of obscure to some people,
Tom Hamilton or whatever,
the amount of acting and performing
these people have had to do and have to do in the ride.
This is a ride that thousands and thousands
of people experience every day
in which you watch Tom Hamilton recite dialogue.
It's kind of funny.
For 20 years.
So Rolling Stones say no,
or Disney's not willing to pay that amount of money.
Aerosmith says yes.
This is a question I had for you guys.
If Aerosmith says no,
what do you think Disney's list was?
They're obviously going for baby boomers.
They're obviously going for dad.
And Timelessness, a band that might keep going
for another decade or so.
They've lasted a while.
Yeah, you gotta have something.
Yeah, Jason.
Well, I wish, you know,
one fact about this ride
that I feel like is often thrown about,
and God knows how far this even was along the pipeline
in terms of actually happening,
was that there was gonna be a West Coast version for DCA.
Really? No doubt as the band.
I've never heard that. The Rock and Roller Coaster
started no doubt. Yes, I already read that.
But that was a few years later too.
A few years later.
But I think- I don't think
they would have gone no doubt
in 1997 or eight. No, I don't think
they would have, yeah.
But I think that would have been something else.
That's kind of crazy.
A nice way to tribute, yeah, the band.
Clearly Disneyland fans.
Yeah, in Orange County.
Being Threaded Kingdom.
Gwen Stefani went to Studio K as we learned,
at Knott's Berry Farm.
But I'm just like, who?
I think Aerosmith says no.
I don't know who says yes.
It's hard to think about a band
that has been around that long
and has some staying power.
And yeah, in the 90s had a bunch more hits.
It's pretty rare.
You gotta give it to them.
We're being snarky about it.
But the longevity is pretty impressive.
Yeah, there's no one else.
I mean, who else was in the,
who had a hit, who hits in the 70s
and then had hits in the 90s?
Well, Tom Petty.
Yes, that's true.
And Tom Petty will not,
He would not have done this.
Yeah, maybe not.
I bet he'll do, you see him on The Simpsons or something.
Yeah, but he thinks that's cool.
He likes, he's a comedy guy.
He likes Gary Shamlin.
Gary Shamlin.
He was on those shows.
It could have been like,
what is the Diddy song, Come With Me?
Jimmy Page.
Yeah, Jimmy, oh man.
If it had been a Jimmy Page
and Puff Daddy, Come With Me ride.
Okay, that's something.
Oh man, that would have been wild.
That timing just about works out, I feel like.
90s, late 90s?
Avoiding 98 specific Godzilla.
Right.
Yeah, no Godzilla.
Just like, hey, we're here.
We're just recording another new version of Come With Me.
Oh, or yeah, or just another,
yeah, it's Come With Me 2
and it's a different Led Zeppelin song
with Puffy rapping over it.
I do like to circle back to Petty.
I do like the idea of call it like,
running down a dream.
Sure.
Where you're in the car and you're.
You do a quick launch to that.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
Yeah, that's probably the only appropriate.
So American Girl probably it ends with, but yeah.
We're getting sued now.
That's fun.
That me just doing that approximation.
Now I'm on the Sam Smith list.
I did Sweet Emotion earlier.
I.
And whatever record company that doesn't know
that they own Halix, if they find out.
Oh yeah, yeah, we're fucked.
Yep.
I guess who, yeah, who would have been a band,
because you can't go like to.
Another question you would have to consider
is who would play ball with Disney?
Like who would.
Aerosmith was all about playing ball in the 90s.
All about playing.
They would loved playing ball.
It worked out very well for them.
But like the bare naked ladies
would have been a little too silly.
They were too fresh though.
They were too fresh.
They hadn't been around a long time.
But the chickadee China, the Chinese chicken walk around
in the character in the parks.
That would have been great.
Oh, that would have aged wonderfully.
Pearl Jam, Smashing Pumpkins,
early 90s bands that sort of seemed like
they might have been around a while.
Another issue you have with picking a band is edginess.
Although you're right, Aerosmith has.
Very edgy.
Yeah. It's all edgy.
And in fact really bit them in the butt many years later.
Yes.
The choice of Aerosmith.
I don't know, I think it obviously had to be.
It had to be Aerosmith.
Aerosmith.
So what else do we, what do we know about this?
Should we talk about the plot of the ride?
Yeah.
The star, I mean the other two famous actors in it.
Sure, okay.
Yeah, you go into a recording studio essentially.
Like a record headquarters,
but it's got a recording studio in it.
It's called, do you have it written down
with the recording studio?
G-Force. G-Force.
And then it's called Tour de Force in France, I believe.
But then there's also, that said,
once you get inside the building,
there are posters for Hollywood records bands.
Yes.
I remember that.
I remember going like, oh, Hollywood records.
That's a good fake name for a record label
to have in this movie themed park.
No, that's this is actual record label, Hollywood records.
Sure it was.
One of them.
Yeah, they have in France,
they have like John and Yoko up
in different like pieces of memorabilia.
So it's not all.
In France, they have Vanessa Paradis,
French singer with basically no awareness in America.
So it's a totally bureaucrified experience
at Tour de Force Records.
They still, look, they have some American,
but it's not total.
Yeah.
It's not totally just specific to the land.
So you go to recording studio.
Because Aerosmith is, are you there
to see them finish a record?
It's unclear.
So this is always the thing that even confused me in 1998.
You go in and they're recording Walk This Way.
It doesn't make any sense.
They've already recorded two versions, famously,
of Walk This Way in their hist and their life,
the Run DMC version and the original.
But they had probably had to do it again within sync.
They might.
I guess that's a good point.
Maybe they are constantly re-recording.
Probably for Swiffer commercials and stuff,
just like Devo.
Swift This Way, Swift This.
Yeah, so you go in there,
they're in the middle of recording.
Ken Marino from The State and many other things
is the engineer.
He has no lines.
Yes, this is a, I imagine something
that nobody took note of when it was, yeah,
they're recording a song.
He's manning a mixing board.
And probably nobody noticed it or thought about it
at the time.
That's just an engineer.
But years down the line, he's much more famous
and popular from a lot of shows and stuff.
And it's a strange, distracting fact that he is,
that it's Ken Marino.
And you think, was he there to add a comedic value
or punchline?
No, he says nothing.
He sits there silently.
This is being, there's a technology being deployed
similar to hologram technology,
similar to what you see today at,
oh, I don't know, the Hologram USA Theater
on Hollywood Boulevard.
Oh, there it is.
You're in a recording studio and there's the glass
that separates the booth from where the recording
takes place.
And Aerosmith and Ken Marino and their manager,
Ileana Douglas, are on the other side of the glass.
But it's done in this projected way
where it sort of looks like they're there.
It's a little bit of a photo real kind of shooting.
And to do this, they had to shoot
with unbelievably bright lights.
The exposure had to be crazy high.
And I found Ken Marino talking about it
on the Nerdist podcast.
And he apparently had to wear special contact lenses
so that he would not go blind during the all day shooting,
staring it.
I can only assume the other people,
it was the same deal unless Steven Tyler's brain's
already too fried.
Just toss that in there, man.
Oh, we'll do that to you, my man.
That effect is used, I believe it's similar
in the queue line at Gringotts where you go into,
you go into one of the bankers' offices.
You go into one of the many Weasley brothers' offices.
It's kind of hologram-y.
It's kind of on the other ride too, on Forbidden Journey too
when you see the kids and the poke of invisibility.
It's sort of a similar thing of like, yeah.
It kind of looks like they're there.
Now the film looks a little old.
It looks a little old.
Yeah, it still looks pretty good.
I was there six months ago.
Holds up, cool.
So you're there to see a recording session
but then Ileana Douglas, their manager, comes in and says,
you gotta leave right now.
You got a concert to get to.
And they initially accede to this demand.
They leave and go back into a very CG limo
in the back of the room, out the door of the recording studio
which leads straight out to the street, obviously.
They start getting in the limo and then pretty late
after a lot of like, after 10 seconds of just milling around
and Joe Perry asking for his blacklist Paul,
yo Chris, can I get my blacklist Paul?
Then it occurs to Steve and Tyler, wait a minute.
What about these people?
We're just gonna leave them here?
They're not gonna come to the concert with us?
Yeah, and because he says they love their fans.
You know how we feel about our fans?
You know how we feel about our fans.
Famously love their fans.
And yeah, so they also kind of like lightly harass
Ileana Douglas.
It's like kind of a, like they're all sort of,
you get the set, like if cameras weren't rolling,
like they'd hit her on the butt or something.
Or they probably did during the taping of this
and they just couldn't put it in.
That's digitally edited out.
Yeah, they say like, they're really,
all she does is come in and very gently ask like,
hey, you guys gotta go maintain the schedule
that I set up for you.
And they're like, ugh.
Yeah, fuck you.
Yeah, she's always like this.
Yeah, they do say that, she's always like this.
You all know how Ileana Douglas can be.
She's incredibly apologetic.
She's very polite.
And then is very nice, helps all the fans.
Immediately, yeah, come on, what are we gonna do?
We gotta give them a, like,
we should give these people backstage passes.
She does.
Yeah.
Immediately, she's a very kind character.
Gets a super stretch limo, gets a super fast car.
Yeah.
Super stretch limo.
For everybody in that waiting room.
For everyone in the waiting room.
Here's a issue I have with this.
Concerts typically don't start until the band is there.
And bands of this caliber kind of don't give a shit
if they're running late, right?
Well, you know, it depends.
It depends, Jason, what venue we're talking.
Because there are curfews at certain places
and you do get a large fine.
Oh, I guess you're right.
If you're playing past, say, 11 o'clock
at the Hollywood Bowl. I guess you're right.
Or 10.30 maybe on a weeknight.
So if you're close enough to residential areas.
Right, so you know, Mr. Steven Tyler,
even though he doesn't wanna play by the rules,
still doesn't wanna pay a large fine
at some sort of an outdoor venue,
depending on where we are actually
in the narrative of this ride,
which I hope they explain. Well, look, there's rules
and then there's city ordinances
that are in place for the good of our communities
and fellow citizens and we need to be good neighbors.
Right, and no one appreciates city ordinances
more than Jason Sheridan. Oh, I love it.
I love those ordinances.
You go to the Burbank Town Center
to just discuss the ordinances
with the different council members every weekend.
Yeah, which is a mall.
So I bother them at the mall.
The town square. When they're trying
to spend time with their families.
Well, as an aspiring mayor yourself.
That's true. Hashtag.
It is true. What was it?
Jason for DLR. Of course.
Yes. I believe.
Keep using it in addition to the many others
that we've thrown your way.
The thing with our hashtags is they're great
because they're cumbersome.
Yes, that is what this great path looks like.
Well, we know no one has used them before.
So that's a good thing. That's true.
Yeah. Yeah, we're still flying blind
on if these have been used at all.
We do know where the concert takes place.
It is at the Forum.
They name check the Forum.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
Which is a great venue in Los Angeles
that has now been converted to only be for concerts.
It used to be sort of a shared space with sports,
but there's no teams there now.
So we know where they're playing.
We know where they're going.
And you know what?
It takes a lot of freeway driving to get there.
Those wild LA freeways.
And that's what you have to navigate on this ride.
Well, wait, where was the...
Man, now do I want to know.
I don't think I realized they were going to the Forum.
But now I want to know where the recording studio was.
Across town, Santa Monica.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Sound City in the valley.
It's Sound City.
It's the girls' sound city.
That makes the most sense to take freeway.
I guess if you hop on the 10.
Well, they go on the five.
I think there's a five sign on the ride.
All right.
Oh, maybe they were recording right here in Burbank.
That's possible.
One of those quiet,
one of those little unmarked recordings.
Sure.
Tons of little studios and sound stages,
purposefully non-descript in the valley
so that people don't come hunting around
for stars and celebs.
Trying to get limo passes and what have you.
Yeah, trying to get limo passes,
or in some case,
like accidentally stumbling onto porno sets.
That's probably another.
That's a different kind of unmarked for a reason.
More accurate.
So there's an alternate story in France.
Yeah.
Scott, you told me not to read about the France squad.
Because you wanted to share some of the France stuff.
Look, I didn't want to be strict about this,
but just because it was a surprise to me
when I found out about it,
when I went to Walt Disney Studios Paris,
the worst Disney theme park by Leaves and Bands,
I did not go on this ride in continuing with my,
if you're surprised.
But you've never been on the Rock and Roll Culture.
I have not been on it.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But hey, look, we aren't talking about
Gs and inversions and whatever.
We're talking about the plot.
And I can consume the plot via YouTube videos
just as well as anybody.
Anyway, I waited while my wife did it.
And I probably went to some other nonsense to the show
where Martin Short takes you through the history
of silent film and deals with a wizard
played by Alan Cumming.
I was doing some other nonsense.
If I may ask though,
because the difference between this and Space Mountain
is probably just it goes faster.
Is that why you don't wanna go on it?
It's the quick launch.
I have a problem with these quick launches.
I should get over this.
What this would open up to me
if I were willing to do these things.
Well, I mean, the logistics of this,
well, sorry, sorry.
What is the plot in France?
I wanna know from either of you.
Okay, so because Erin went on it,
I asked her out was she was like, fine.
And I said, yeah, was it that weird thing
where you're like, we're late for the concert.
We gotta get you there and Ken Marino's there.
And can we get backstage passes for everybody?
And she was like, no.
I said, no, what do you mean?
Were you just not, was the show down?
No, no, no, it's still them.
They're there, there's a recording guy there.
But instead they tell you that, okay,
you're still, it's a different record company.
It's not G-Force Records, it's Tour de Force Records.
And you're there in a recording studio, mind you,
to experience a new music and ride experience
that Aerosmith has crafted for you.
And it's still Ken Marino, still a recording booth,
but they have like a model of a roller coaster.
And they're putting, well, at first it's all of the members
besides Steven Tyler.
And they're kind of murmuring about where's Steven?
Oh, he's on a ride.
And then Steven comes in, all hot and bothered,
excited because he was, how many Gs he was experiencing.
There's a part, then he said.
He can't do heroin anymore,
and this is the only way he can get Gs.
This is the only high he has available.
He's describing very eloquently the specific feelings.
I was feeling two Gs, three Gs, four Gs.
And then suddenly it felt like I was,
and he cues the sound, going down.
From loving an elevator.
Sacrebleu.
Works great with the French.
He says going down, and then Ken Marino is like, ah, I see,
and writes that down as a note.
I don't know what he was meant to take from that.
So Ken Marino gets to do more,
he gets more business to do in the French version?
He writes a note on a clipboard,
if that counts as more business.
But otherwise, still no dialogue, still doesn't talk.
On the Nerdist, he said he had lines
that they recorded for the European one,
and he didn't know if they were there.
But he did not, they didn't make it.
These were shot on the same day?
Presumably, because it's the same super bright lighting,
everybody's in the same clothes.
So for some reason, they felt,
and the other one, the Paris one,
didn't open until like five years later,
but they thought ahead, the plot needs to be different,
and the plot needs to be, instead of,
you're late for a concert, the plot is,
Aerosmith built a new ride for you,
are you ready to go on it?
And which is, so that's, as far as you know,
when you're watching the video, that's what the plot is.
But then, I've seen other things saying
that the plot of the ride is
that you're in an Aerosmith music video.
And that's, so in your experience,
you're going through loops and concert lighting,
and that's you being in a music video.
And still, another source I saw said
that the point of the France one is that you,
your car, is a note.
You're a musical note.
And you're going through all of the vibrations
and twists and turns that a Joe Perry guitar note
goes through when traveling through the acoustics
of an amphitheater.
So the point is, nobody knows what the plot of this ride is.
That is the sort of whimsy I would expect
from a country where Jerry Lewis is a national hero.
Mm-hmm, yes.
The kind of creativity.
In fact, there's like,
I'll just read from the Disney Paris website.
Get ready to rock out in an Aerosmith music video.
The bad boys from Boston are working with engineers
on a revolutionary new sound.
And they want you to be center,
spelled the European way, stage.
So jump into a soundtracker with onboard speakers
and turn the amp to the max.
Every electrifying riff is met with more G-force
than an astronaut experience, not pluralized.
Maybe proofread your site, Disney Paris.
Blasting you through lightning rigs.
What?
What's a lightning rig? Lightning rigs.
It's everything you'd expect from the amped up,
neon lit, smoke-filled excess of a rock and roll lifestyle.
Wow.
Famously.
Should that be lighting rigs?
I think so.
Well, it's a play on that.
It's like they have a new version of a lighting rig
called lightning rig.
Okay.
I've given them a lot, unless it is.
It's possible it's just an error.
Possibly just a misspelling.
So, and that's another thing that in the Paris,
I'm sorry, in the Orlando one, you get on a limousine.
In the Paris one, you get on a soundtracker,
which looks like a limousine.
Except the front of the car has a CD embedded in it.
Oh boy.
And there's also a giant CD outside, right?
There's a giant CD outside.
That's another thing I'd like to say
comparing the two versions.
That courtyard in Orlando is kind of nice.
Big classic guitar with a roller coaster track
coming out of the neck.
It looks like it was always supposed to be.
It fits right in with the better end of the architecture
of Disney MGM Studios.
Such a nice area that a Britney Spears concert
for the Disney Channel was held there.
I have very fond feelings about this giant guitar courtyard.
However, the Paris one is like the worst graphic design
you've ever seen.
I consider this an international crime.
If we, just to bring it up for you guys,
really doubling down on the CDs, there's CDs everywhere.
These are never going away.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, this'll be the tech.
Well, how would you, what would you do now?
Would it be, songs are invisible now.
They're on a cloud.
Just ones and zeros.
No way to represent.
So, and then like, it's a font.
Like, this logo.
It's very busy.
It's the busiest thing you're,
it's a leopard print guitar.
There's roller coaster tracks exploding out of it.
The font is on fire.
It's a truly hideous.
It's very, it's green, but there's so many colors
and they kind of go together, but they kind of don't.
It's very strange.
There are like 25 colors all fighting each other.
Not covering the sound stage that it's in.
Like you can see the corner of the sound stage
in this picture.
Yes, and this is the thing with Disney Studios Paris
is it's all just cheap metal buildings.
And there's this corner of the park that is,
it really is just Aerosmith Alley
and they should call it that.
I wish they called it that.
You know, you're getting yourself into, but there's-
Steven Tyler's parents were gunned down
in front of him after-
That's the origin of Aerosmith.
I must fight back with rock.
I must fight my feelings by rocking it.
We were leaving a Robert Johnson concert and-
With the strains still echoing.
Yeah.
Bullets were added to the soundtrack.
So the Rock and Roller Coaster is next
in a very cheap building,
is next to another very cheap building
with this unpleasant Armageddon experience.
It's like, and not-
Which really is perfect.
Yeah.
Because Armageddon,
don't want to miss a thing.
But I don't want to miss a thing.
The song is playing outside of that building.
Wow, that's crazy.
So Aerosmith just owns a couple acres in France.
That's crazy.
Outside of Paris.
But this, you just, you get a headache
from every component of this area of Disney Studios Paris.
Like the songs, I will say, I think are unpleasant.
The graphics are unpleasant.
It's all like the buildings are nothing to look at.
You're lucky if they slapped a poster up there.
This is a, I want them to firebomb this zone.
This is an atrocious area of a Disney theme park.
That's too bad.
I will, I'll say this about the France version.
They played Jaded on the ride.
Ah, and not here?
And not in Florida.
Wow.
Jaded is nowhere to be found in Florida.
Maybe outside, it might be played outside in that area,
but on the actual ride or inside the ride,
Jaded is not played, which of course we've both determined
is the best Aerosmith song.
Is the best Aerosmith song, let there be no debate.
Although maybe, I think you gotta give some points
to the customized version of Love in an Elevator.
Love in a Rollercoaster.
Right.
Great.
Live in an up while I'm going down.
Pretty cool.
Maybe that's later is like,
if my parents are listening, which they are,
just stop listening, it's just something like having
bone in an elevator.
And so I guess, but that's crazy that they just changed it
to Rollercoaster, because that's sort of what.
Still the same thing.
Yes.
It's like getting it on in a Rollercoaster.
And the fun.
Just more dangerous.
The fun of sex that has to be over in 15 seconds.
Yeah, the ride is like a minute 15.
The ride is so short.
Yeah.
Like sex.
Always is for three podcast hosts.
I have to say, this ride,
I do have like, I have more associations with this ride
and Aerosmith than I do with Aerosmith alone.
Cause I remember going on this ride,
probably it probably would have been that opening summer.
I was probably there.
I remember seeing it on the information channel
and seeing it on the map and like going into the courtyard
and liking the courtyard.
And I, my very specific memory of it is asking
multiple cast members, does this ride go upside down?
Because I didn't like, I hadn't really done looping coasters
besides maybe one at like a little seaside park
in New Jersey.
And for whatever reason, I could not get a cast member
to give me a straight answer.
And so we're like, I guess we'll just try it.
And there's a very unpleasant outside cue.
That's just like a few TV screens.
Yes, it is not dressed up at all.
It's not really dressed up.
Playing music videos, what's on the screen?
Yeah, they're playing music videos.
And you hear the Aerosmith songs and stuff.
There's some songs.
And then when you get inside
and then you go through the little pre-show area
and then you come out of that.
And I kind of like the cue out of that
that looks like the alleyway behind the recording studio
with the chain leg fences and stuff.
But then as soon as you come out of it,
you see people sitting in the cars
and the cars fucking launch.
And I was like, not only will no one tell me
if this goes upside down,
I've never seen a roller coaster do that before.
Because this would have been the same summer
Islands of Adventure opened.
So before this and the Hulk,
I didn't even know about the concept of launch masters.
And then my dad and I got in and yeah,
that launch is still to this day.
And I've ridden a number of them,
still a very unnerving feeling.
Sure, I'm not willing to have.
I love it.
I love it too.
I love a launch.
I don't know, I've said this before.
It gets the whole thing over with.
My whole thing with roller coasters
is I don't like that slow up.
I don't like the dangling.
I don't like feeling like you're gonna fall.
I like momentum on it.
So this is similar to what you're saying.
I was very scared when I went for the first time.
And I remember my mom asked the question you're asking
to a lot of employees of like, does it go upside down?
She was like, I mean, I think she was like late 30s,
40 at that point.
And she was like worried and they're like,
you'll be fine, don't worry.
Yeah, and now I feel like if you ask a cast member that,
immediately they'll tell you, yes, yes it does.
Yeah, yeah.
Once or twice.
Yeah, and it's.
Once or twice?
I don't know.
I hadn't been upside down
because the only thing I'd ever been on
that was anything close to being a roller coaster
was Space Mountain.
And Space Mountain is still pretty tame.
I mean, it was the one in Florida
I had not been to the one out here.
There's no strong element to it that is like,
there's not one thing in it that's more scary than.
Yeah, I find.
Just generally it being a roller coaster.
Yeah, I find Space Mountain in Florida now a little scary
because of how rickety it is.
Fall apart.
Yeah, they gotta fix that track.
Yeah, yeah, but I, yeah.
So I went, I think it's probably opening summer
and I hadn't been yet.
So Tower of Terror is there.
And so I went on Tower of Terror and Rock and Roller Coaster
for the first time on this one trip on this one day.
And if you were to have stopped me at the end of the park,
at the end of the day and say,
how do you feel about Rock and Roller Coaster?
And Tower of Terror, I would have said,
they are both the same level of great.
I was so happy with both these.
I may have even said Rock and Roller Coaster
was better at the time.
Which in hindsight is crazy.
It was and it is cool that like launch
because the launch kind of varies.
I mean, reading about the ride each, I don't know,
we don't have to say all of the,
there are five cars and the six in rotation
that can play any of them.
And each car plays a different song or set of songs.
And the launch is different for each one too.
Sometimes it counts down to five, four, three, two
and then launches you.
It tricks you.
And Steven Tyler is counting sometimes
and then he leaves one out.
Yeah, and sometimes he says one though.
His Rock and Roll mischievous tomfoolery.
I see.
Yeah, but it is fun.
Like I do like, I know what you mean.
The first time I wrote it, I thought it was great.
And I still like it.
I mean, it's gone in the last few years.
And it's like, yeah, this is great.
I am not saying I still feel that it's the same goodness
as Tower of Terror, but at the time.
No.
And also like I did, it is something
where I felt like alive.
Like I could.
Oh, absolutely.
I was like, oh, I'll survive on a roller coaster.
I'll be okay.
This is very fun.
It's a landmark day for you.
A day I haven't had.
Yes, I know.
We would be honored to be with you on your first launch.
Well, look.
There's negotiations.
Scott, you have one of those famous grapefruit flavored
drinks at the Brown Derby and a slice of their famous grapefruit
cake.
And then we'll take you down to the hospital.
The Incredicoaster might be the place to start.
I would do the Incredicoaster.
Yeah, you guys see that.
Dynamo animatronic.
Yes.
To see with the temptation of a big doll or whatever is in there,
I'll brave it.
To see that big doll.
I got to say, yeah.
So as a kid, I was this end of the park.
I was like, wow, two big attractions down there.
And now, now looking at the current state of Hollywood Studios,
this end of the park is doing some heavy lifting.
This end of the park is carrying this park.
So much is closed.
So much is under construction.
Only end of the park.
See, I mean, I keep forgetting the great movie ride is closed.
I'm like, well, there's nothing there.
If the great movie ride was still open,
I would say that this would probably still
be one of my family's favorite parks to hit on.
Even though there's three rides.
I guess there's the Indiana Jones stunt show and Fantasmic.
Indiana Stunt Show, Star Tours, Fantasmic is I like because it's
insane, and the great movie ride, and then this in Tower of Terror.
And then my family also really likes Mama Melrose.
There's a Woodfired Italian, Woodfire Pizza Italian restaurant.
I feel like most people are like, oh, we like the sci-fi dining,
or we like the moms, the 50s.
The gimmick places.
Right, the gimmick places.
But then there's an actual decent restaurant in there, too.
I remember that being OK.
Oddly enough, I've never eaten at the Brown Derby.
Oh, we ate once.
That was pretty good.
I did as a kid.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not bad.
So there's still a lot I like in this park.
But you know what?
We will get tweets or requests for general Disney World travel advice.
And I'd have to say for the next six months or so,
the advice would be skip Hollywood Studios.
Do a four hour.
Do get Rock and Roller Coaster hit tower.
At the very least, hit tower.
But people who are, if you're trying to save a couple bucks,
let's be conscious of people's pockets.
Well, but you've got to get the Mark Hopper option.
You know?
I mean, you do it in park hopping anyway.
I say you do those.
You do a lunch at Mama Melrose, hit up Star Tours and then another lunch
at Mama Melrose.
Yeah, then another lunch at Mama Melrose.
And I mean, I love that Indiana Jones stunt show, too.
I'm wrong.
Well, I don't know.
My advice is pretty similar.
I think we just like this park a lot.
All I'm saying is Tower of Terror is worth it, especially now
that we don't have any version of it.
I mean, we have a version of it, but not a version, the Twilight Zone version.
This is certainly true.
But I'm presenting the world in which people do not go to Disney World for nine days.
That's true.
You aren't doing the indulgence.
I don't understand that.
There are those people.
I don't know why they're listening to this, but there are those people.
You can take a boat from Hollywood Studios to Epcot.
It's a quick thing.
So say you're doing a full Epcot day.
You go at 8 o'clock in the morning or 9 o'clock in the morning.
You do an hour.
You do Rock and Rollercoaster Tower.
You take the boat to Epcot.
That's not much of out of the day.
I don't want to nitpick, but I don't know that you're right.
Is that a boat?
I don't. Well, there's a boat, but I think you have to go to one of the hotels and then go to Epcot.
You can walk from here to Epcot.
This is the bigger thing.
Will we ever trust Mike again?
I don't know that there's a direct friendship boat from Hollywood Studios to Epcot, Michael.
I'm looking this up now.
Now I'm really upset.
Will our relationship ever match?
You know what I say?
Skip this park.
Just put on your headphones, download the song Jaded, get in a revolving chair and spin around.
And then that's like you were on the ride.
The end.
And I don't know, ask the hotel you're in to cut the elevator cord or an emergency level.
I think this park is going to look pretty neat when you take the Skyliner into it.
Oh, there's going to be a big...
Now, if you're listening to this in 2019, post Galaxy's Edge, now it's a crown jewel of a park, I would have to hope.
I could care less about Galaxy's Edge.
I'm just excited for a new mode of transit to get around Disney World.
This is a sort of a gondola thing.
You have to like stop at one of the hotels and then you go to Hollywood Studios.
Like that's that crazy from the thing that I said.
No, but great hotel.
That boat, you can go to the boardwalk, beach or yacht club, swan or dolphin.
A lot of fun stuff.
Again, also you can walk between this park and Epcot, which is a little bit of a hike, but it's a beautiful walk.
That is the thing.
My genuine advice is at some point in your Disney World travels, take a day to just wander around hotel lobbies and stuff.
Oh, I mean, yeah, if you're into it for the theming, the hotels are a treat.
Yeah, if you go for that fast roller coaster bullshit, then fine.
But if you want themes, if you want accurate Cape Cod architecture, then do it Scott's way.
If you want to see what carpeting would have been put into a hotel in 1997, go and see all of the Disney World hotels.
A strike against this, according to some people, I don't know that I completely agree, but it's the Rock and Roller Coaster is what they call an off the shelf coaster.
It is not a Disney specific design by Imagineering.
They just basically look at a roller coaster catalog and they pointed and said, I want this.
They designed everything that's around it.
In the case of Orlando, they put up the five freeway sign and you probably go through like a Hollywood sign or something.
I imagine you sure do.
You absolutely do.
Great.
Good guess.
But that's, of course, to simulate some sort of out of control drunk drive that Steven Tyler had while he drove a car through the Hollywood sign downhill.
It's a real story for him.
We shouldn't be.
I get to the big boy and Burbank.
I'm going over the hill.
He went the other way.
You're saying he's going up.
He's driving up the hill and then he went the other.
He went reverse and he's like, well, I'm going to go home.
Time to go back the way I came.
And at the end of the ride, you crash into Bibi Buell's house.
Yeah, I'm here to see my daughter.
And Elvis Costello is there with another gentleman caller.
Can I can I point out also the you said that it's different experiences based on which limo you get in?
Or sound caster in Paris.
But you know, you can you know which song it's going to be off of the license plate numbers, which we're in rock and roll style have attitude.
The license plate numbers include you go, babe.
Bye bye.
H8 hate traffic and too fast for you, which is correct.
In my case, it is too fast for me.
Thanks for letting me know. Right. Yeah.
But so that's a fun that's a fun little Easter egg.
I also hear there's a lot of hidden Mickey's on this ride, but I don't think I care.
I think we haven't talked about this yet.
Do you guys care about hidden Mickey's?
We've got a lot of episodes and not talked about them.
I think like if I can if I spot one, I'm like, oh, that's fun.
That's about my extent.
Yeah, I feel like a lot of them are lame.
I feel like sometimes they're like cool.
Like sometimes there's one.
I think there's supposedly one in the queue for the Little Mermaid ride in Florida,
where it's only when the sun it's in the rock work in the queue and the sun.
When the sun hits a certain point in the sky in the day, it casts a shadow of a hidden Mickey.
Yeah, that's cool. I like that.
And the MGM studios is it has a giant.
You're in a giant hidden Mickey with the mouth being the courtyard of the MGM of the great movie
ride and then like the eyes are the lake and something else or the ears of the lake.
And you ever seen this?
If you go to Google Maps and look down on Hollywood Studios, it's the biggest hidden Mickey.
My favorite part of the hidden Mickey the map.
All right.
Okay.
No, it's a joke because it's just traditionally three circles.
Uh huh.
You don't really see about that.
Okay.
No, you have a you have some kind of giant fetish and you want to get swallowed by Mickey.
Oh, I do want to get swallowed by Mickey.
Just say you wanted to get eaten on alien encounter.
You want to roll around in Mickey Mouse's mouth.
Yeah, he can spit you out.
It's up to him what happens.
But I also I'd like to say I think a pretty good poll quote if we needed like a
catchphrase that explains this podcast to people who haven't heard it.
I think sometimes hidden Mickey's are cool.
Because that conveys both that we think that but some time we're a little picky about our Mickey's.
Sometimes it's lame.
So yeah, let that be a defining quote forever.
Two videos I watched this ride.
One, like Space Mountain, there is footage of this ride with the lights on.
And it is like Space Mountain terrifying, maybe even more so because of the like
metal work on this is so like intense.
The track is just very gruesome looking, just very like industrial
steel.
And then it's also just built in an unthemed soundstage.
So there's just girders everywhere.
It feels like you're like you've been Space Mountain with lights on or Rock and Roller
Coaster with lights on feels like you're in like an industrial like a kill floor or something.
Like it's a place you've been brought in to be slaughtered and cut into bits.
You are like Charlie Chaplin falling into the machines in modern times.
Scariest movie I've ever seen.
Scariest movie.
There was a one night Star Wars overlay of this attraction.
Yes.
Where you were I mean, they didn't take any of the black light signs down, but you were
racing to get to the premiere of Star Wars The Force Awakens.
That's how they justified it.
That's the way I figured the way like it said premiere at the end.
You're like, well, we got here to the premiere.
And I'm like, oh, OK, I guess you're racing to.
Yeah, that would that would start without you.
You know, talking about overlays and musical overlays that were briefly around
the success of having roller coasters sets to rock music kicked open the door to the
Rockin Space Mountain and Rockin California Screamin that were open for a summer at
Disneyland in which the two primary roller coasters at the Disneyland Resort were taken
over by those rapscallions, the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
And I got to experience both of these.
This is my first summer at Disney.
Really?
Disneyland, the first time I had ever been to these parks.
And I got to experience California Screamin and Space Mountain in the best possible way.
Soundtracked by the Red Hot Chili Peppers, a band.
I mean, how do we all feel about the Red Hot Chili Peppers?
I think it's similar.
It's one of those.
Similar to Aerosmith.
It's fine.
They're spotty.
They can be around.
They don't bother me.
Flea is a fantastic actor.
No hits, never had an album.
Back to the Future 2.
I have had, I have a few of their albums.
I do think that Aerosmith and Red Hot Chili Peppers are very similar in a lot of ways.
In the way you're saying that, but they have a very like rap, rocky, they're very bawdy.
There's like a lot of dirty stuff in it.
I was very into Californication when it came out.
The song.
I like music video.
Not having sex in California?
What?
The song you said.
No, it's in the album.
I'm very into California, Californication.
The song.
Well, isn't the album, isn't the album awesome?
Also, I meant the song.
I didn't have the album.
But I like the song.
I like the music video.
I miss the joke.
Whatever joke you were going for.
And he was saying you're open to the act of Californication.
Yeah.
Having, doing sexual things in California.
I'm just, I'm not going to lie.
I didn't know about the, I didn't pick up on that word play until just now.
Oh, really?
You just thought it was like a process.
Like being in a California machine.
I honestly did think it's just like, yeah, these fuckers love California.
I also too mostly think of that music video where it becomes a video game for a little bit.
That he's like hopping through.
Is that right?
Is that Californication?
Is that the video?
I can't remember.
There's a lot of, there's a lot of hits on that album.
There's Other Side, there's Scar Tissue, there's Around the World.
Danny California on that?
No, Jason, please.
I don't know.
Danny California is on Stadium Arcadium.
Oh, I mean.
We do our research.
No more three stars.
But I just, but you had not done your research about.
I had not done.
Fornication was.
Oh man.
Dirty stuff.
It's all dirty stuff.
I'm glad I punched up and reused that late bloomer joke for this episode because we really.
We really illustrated it.
I was so shocked that you were like, what are you talking about?
And then it all comes out.
We taught you a classic pun today.
We learned something.
Oh, that classic pun, Californication.
It's a pun is what it is.
It is.
Yeah.
California.
It's like up there with the Mark Twain zingers from the American Adventure.
Anthony Kiedis and Mark Twain.
America's greatest words.
Could you imagine that's what they're going to update it to.
Oh, shaking hands.
Shaking hands.
Like at the end of American Adventure.
Oh, I'm fine with that.
Throw Benjamin Franklin off the torch.
It's Kiedis, baby.
Well, it looks like one of the.
You know, talking about the body nature of rock bands, which is what we're doing.
We should say the you know, this ride was just having a pleasant.
It was just chugging along.
The train kept a rolling, as Steven Tyler would say.
But and with no without incident.
But I guess after many years of murmuring, people noticed that Steven Tyler in this
pre-show with Ileana Douglas and Ken Marino at one point peers out into the audience as
if to see us, the guests and refer to us and say, but I love my fans.
They have to come with me.
And he makes a hand gesture in doing so known as the shocker.
He holds that, which is he's holding up.
I'm not even.
Hey, somebody's going to have to explain to me how to make it.
It's it's two fingers and then one is down and then one is up.
There's I will not.
Sexual innuendo.
I will not say the thing that the kids in high school when they taught me this
would say about it.
You can look it up.
It's a dirty equation.
Yes, it's an equation.
You know, the recipe for a shocker.
It's cool and funny to do.
It's cool and funny.
But I hold on.
It ages well, even though we have an explicit podcast.
I won't be that explicit.
We're not.
Yeah, we haven't blooms that far yet.
What's odd is that they left in Joe Perry doing that thing where you put your hand
under your chin and you drag it.
A let sort of like the Godfather.
The Godfather.
Fuck you like the Italian.
Fuck you.
Joe Perry does that like the entire time he's on screen.
Yeah, they're fine with that.
But yeah, they so yeah, they digitally took it out.
They had in 2016 very recently.
It's some Disney graphic designer.
So like somebody was sent this footage and they had to digitally add a finger
to Steven Tyler's hand to make it a regular palm up and not a gesture.
Hello.
Yeah, so it's just him trying to see it.
Yes.
In practicality, when filming it, it was probably blocking the very bright lights
from his eyes while doing a lewd gesture.
But yeah, Steven.
So do you do you see what Steven Tyler wrote on Facebook after this went down?
No, Steven Tyler on his Facebook in all caps wrote way to give me the finger.
Now, Walt Disney World dot dot dot 17 years later.
And then he just wrote the greatest ride at Disney.
So is that footage of him getting off like walking, exiting the ride like years later
and and him go and I feel like at one point he says like, just checking in on my ride.
Like and then everyone with pictures, taking pictures, high fiving people.
He I think he was real psyched about it.
I think he's psyched about it because he went on.
I think it was like a 68th birthday.
He was down there.
He went on it.
I think he's happy to be on a ride.
I don't think he thinks it's lame.
I swear to God, if I am 68 and I don't have a ride to check in on, just pulled me off
whatever support.
Yeah.
I will.
I'll do something.
I'll purposefully fall down the stairs and then plea.
I'll tell you guys, my co-hosts, I'm giving you permission to pull me off the dialysis
machine if I don't have a ride yet.
What another name I have to write down giving me end of life.
Well, you know, that person, I had to pull the plug.
Will you be OK if we're just still performing in HALIX at Star Wars Galaxy's Edge?
Oh, that counts.
That's fine.
Great.
The opening ceremony, Aerosmith showed up.
I believe they played.
Yeah.
And contest winners got to go and enjoy a buffet meal and drinks with them.
And they were.
That's true.
I was going to mention the buffet if you were not going to mention it yourself.
I'm glad you took note of it.
But then you got to ride with one of you, you got a chance to ride with one of the members
of the band in your car, which is a foolhardy thing to do after enjoying a buffet.
I ate a bunch of macaroni pasta that looked like guitars.
And then me and Brad Whitford, not the actor, the Aerosmith Brad Whitford,
got to ride in HH traffic to the tune of Jaded.
It was the greatest day of my life.
It was if it was France.
Oh, if it was Orlando.
OK, OK.
Yes.
They also at the opening ceremony, they were joined by Denny Dent, the speed painter.
Oh, yeah.
Who speed painted.
No need to say his credit.
We all know Denny Dent.
Speed painted the big pick, all five Aerosmith members.
What?
Really?
Yeah.
He's one of those guys who just throws paint at a camp or was.
He has passed away, apparently.
And then those canvases hang throughout like employee offices in Walt Disney World, apparently.
Yeah, that is weird.
Why didn't they just put them on the ride?
Why did.
Oh, good question.
Is that you?
Is that your father?
No, it's Tom Hamilton.
I'll share.
Who did it?
Denny Dent.
They were all fighting for Steven Tyler or Joe Perry.
Well, you know, that's in Iger's office.
You know, the big dog got that one.
Oh, yeah.
He took that from Iger.
They do famously call Bob Iger the big dog.
Yeah, yeah.
That's Disney lore you should know.
He's like WWE star Roman Reigns.
Bob Iger.
Yeah, their explosions go off when he enters that building with the dwarfs on it.
It's similar to how Pitbull is named Mr. Worldwide.
That's his nickname.
And I am also nicknamed Mr. Worldwide.
That's true.
Not Mr. Californication, though.
We know that.
No, clearly not.
Interesting actual fact about this ride is apparently the second fastest ride in Walt Disney World.
Test tracks supposedly goes faster.
Really?
And I can do that, but their launch doesn't go uphill.
I guess that's where I don't want to leave my heart and lungs at the bottom of the ride.
And then, you know, you don't want to go zero to 57 in two point eight seconds.
I guess I don't.
I guess I don't want to live the rock and roll lifestyle.
That's what it's like at all times when you're.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Well, I should do it.
Hey, next time I'm there.
I don't know.
I mean, who knows how long it'll be there.
Let's be honest.
Yeah, the Paris one is being turned into a Marvel attraction.
Iron Man.
Oh, right.
That's why we're talking about it to their farewell.
And how do you say goodbye in French?
There's been a.
I didn't know that.
You didn't know California Cation.
I didn't know or even though I was in France.
Two years of French.
That's all you remember.
I bet Iron Man will tell you to get in the.
What are they called in France?
Not sound snappers.
What are they sound casters?
Yes, soundcast.
Quick, get into soundcaster.
The Avengers need your help.
I'm building a ride.
The Avengers are building a ride and you have to go on it and test it out.
OK, the G's are almost complete.
OK, we're here at Stark Industry Studios.
We're in Studio B.
I'm cutting my new record and we're finishing a roller coaster demo.
If the narrative is that Tony Stark is cutting a demo, that's great.
It's not tied all together with producer Steven Tyler.
He's sitting back there.
He now has taken the Ken Marino seat.
Sounds good, Tony.
I would love it if there was a gag in one of the Marvel movies where one of them
released like a novelty single like Disco Duck or the Super Bowl Shuffle.
Sure.
I guess I guess you would need to introduce Wonder Man for that.
Like his characters.
He was an actor.
He was like that.
That's good.
I mean, the superhero and a musician.
In Thor Ragnarok, there's a pretty good runner that Jeff Goldblum's character plays weird synth
and like makes up songs.
So maybe he's that.
Maybe he's the what is his character's name?
It's not the collector.
The collector is Benicio.
He's a.
Oh, God, what is his name?
Which, by the way, OK, in Los Angeles, you likely know that Jeff Goldblum does jazz piano shows.
Yes.
And so he's more than willing to.
He'll always take a concert venue.
Let's get him down in the Cantina as well.
Oh, great.
I'll give him in character in Thor character.
It can't just be the jazz piano.
It's got to be a synth component.
You got to bring it into the future.
But I think he'd love to do.
I don't think that would be hard to book.
I really don't.
I think Jeff Goldblum would be thrilled to perform at Disneyland every once in a while with it.
Does he have like, I don't know, space hair?
Does he have like a blue goatee or some shit?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And a big robe, a fun robe.
Great.
I guessed the wardrobe.
So let's get him in character performing in that Cantina.
But mainly Halix, only between Halix sets.
Oh, the Grand Master.
The Grand Master, of course.
The Grand Master.
He's great.
I mean, he's great in that movie.
That is a side note.
That's like totally him.
Like, I almost think that's the best use of just like him, his essence,
like letting him just improvise and it's odd and off timed and they keep takes in it that are like
no other movie would keep that take in of him just making a weird noise.
Anyway, that's a side note.
What do you think is the best use of Steven Tyler in a movie?
In a movie.
Is it, let's take the ride out of the running, although he's great in it.
Because I don't know if you're aware of the full filmography,
but he is in the film Be Cool, the sequel to Get Shorty.
He is in Polar Express.
He does a big musical number.
He's like an elf, is an elf that is mocap amended to the features of Steven Tyler.
And he's also, I swear to God, I can't remember the name of this movie,
but it was on in a hotel room once and it's an animated movie where he's a big fat worm or
something.
And the only way you don't know who it is because his speaking voice is very generic.
He's just kind of a, uh, just kind of a raspy voice dude and he acts very stiffly,
but he's a mystical worm.
And his name is Nimglu.
And this is video I love where he like, he says, he like,
I was, I always dreamed of being in an animated film and now my wish came true.
I'm Nimglu.
So I'm very fond of Nimglu, but I, of the film, I can't remember the name.
It's Epic.
The movie is called Epic.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
I never would have got there.
Why is him big worm movie called Epic?
He's a caterpillar.
Oh, okay.
And it is, yeah.
Oh God, that movie, I think I saw a little of that movie.
Who made it?
Was it Ice Age?
Is it Dreamworks?
No one knows who made, I already forgot the name.
It's Nimglu the movie.
It's called, I am Nimglu.
I have not seen any of those things you've mentioned.
I've never seen Be Cool.
I've never seen Epic.
Your head is better for it.
If I'm giving the non-funny answer, I guess it's Wayne's World 2.
Oh, right.
Of course.
He is good in a film.
He is good in Wayne's World 2.
They're great in Wayne's World 2.
And that's a good song too.
The song they play, Shut Up and Dance.
Yeah, yeah.
That's fun.
Yeah.
So, so an American Idol, he was good.
He sure was.
Now, he didn't factor into the American Idol experience.
The very unpleasant Disney World attraction, did he?
No, I don't think so.
So there wasn't an Aerosmith Alley in Florida.
Joe Perry also very upset at Steven Tyler that he did American Idol to sell out like that.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Pitbull is also in Epic.
Oh, wow.
How about that?
Mr. Worldwide.
There we go.
There's also a great video of Pitbull playing beer pong with Jimmy Fallon outside of the
Simpsons ride while all the characters cheer him on.
Simpsons and Sideshow Bob included.
They put their famous rivalry aside to cheer Pitbull and Fallon.
Look, that's great intra-company marketing.
That's great synergy for NBC Universal.
That's great inter-intra network marketing between Fox and NBC.
And it's just good fun for all of us fans.
For everybody who loves beer pong.
And Florida.
There's rumors of what might replace this ride.
Is it maybe going to be replaced in Orlando?
Yes, there's been many different rumors over the years of different bands.
There's also, I think most recently, a rumor that they're going to just put doors on it
and it'll become a Monster Zink coaster.
Monster Zink, I think, has been like the most rumored to have new rides that never pan out.
There's going to be a whole Monster Zink door coaster that was going to replace
the Monster Zink ride out here in California Adventure.
But it's got to be much tamed.
This is way too crazy.
I don't think it does.
This is way too intense to make it a Monster Zink because then little kids are going to go on it.
You do have to be of a certain height to ride this intense of a coaster.
It's got to be a Twizzler.
You got to be a Twizzler.
You got to learn.
These kids got to learn sometime.
It's 48 inches to ride.
So they're going to be, look, you're going to have to wait.
48 inches to ride another Aerosmith album.
Jesus.
They're always sneaking stuff in.
They could do, yeah, the big 10 inch and they could say like the big 48 inch.
They could change that song around.
And then there was also, and this is published on Screamscape,
and a lot of people were goofing on it because it's probably not real, but supposedly one night
they tested out the Powerline song eye to eye on the ride.
Supposedly.
For the public.
The public was, oh yeah, I remember they.
This was a rumor.
People have said this is not true.
This was just somebody lying to Screamscape, but as we know Screamscape, kind of a rag.
And they'll publish anything.
We love Screamscape.
They don't give a shit.
No, we love it.
No, I'm going to stick hard to the mic stand.
So that would be my, I guess we're getting ahead of ourselves of what we would do to it, but I like that idea.
That doesn't make any sense.
The song from, yeah, why exactly?
I mean, it's sort of a concert vibe and you're talking about the song from a goofy movie,
which culminates in this new Jack Swing concert with this particularly good song.
Which we've, yeah, we've said is like the best Disney song of all time, maybe.
Well, so we thought until Halix's Lightning, which I just played you,
and you can see how Jailbait and the other one factor in.
So Powerline's moving down the charts, but yeah, it's up there.
Still up there.
Top five.
And obviously Hakuna Matata.
Yeah.
Number three.
Can't mess with the classic.
Number three with a bullet.
Does I Don't Want to Miss a Thing count as a Disney song?
No.
Okay.
But wait, didn't I determine it was it's Mickey's favorite song?
But Mickey can like songs that aren't in the Disney family, right?
He can, but he chooses not to.
Fair enough.
So why would you?
So you want to put, you want to get that Powerline.
I like that.
I have other ideas too, but I mean, do we have anything else before we sort of?
Yeah, I think they will redo it to a Mary Poppins coaster and Lin-Manuel Miranda will
wrap along to new songs about Mary Poppins.
That sounds hellish.
I think I just, I want to keep what's there, but you know, let's capitalize on the talent
involved now that we've, now that people are familiar with Ken Marino, let's give him some
lines.
Let's make it a route.
What if there's a little more of a story and you're chasing this bumbling audio engineer
around the freeways of Los Angeles.
Are you trying to hit him?
Yeah.
Uh, you're trying, he, well, maybe he, uh, messed up the, like, uh, he, he mixed Joe
Perry's guitar over Steven Tyler's vocals, right?
Which is verboten in an Aerosmith record.
And now you're trying to track him down and punish him and ram him with your soundcaster.
He makes it out alive.
I like Ken Marino.
I don't want to hurt the guy, but he's got like a cartoon, like bandage and like a sling
after the ride.
Yeah.
Yeah, he gets only as abused as, as goofy would, but yeah, but through the streets of
Los, he like, uh, uh, yeah, he like tumbles out the hole of the Randy's donuts or, uh,
uh, yeah, lots of LA themed, uh, uh, injuries.
Yeah.
I, I, I will say this.
I think the France version might be better.
I think the narrative is a little more interesting.
Steven Tyler creating a ride is crazy and more fun than them just going to a concert.
And I'll also say, and this is a full free of irony or free of, of, of joking is that
I think the ride itself looks better.
I think that the sort of just the sort of generic lighting rigs on the France one with
the lighting kind of looks cool.
It looks like a concert.
It looks how like concert lighting is, and it doesn't look to be quite honest as cheap
as the one in Orlando.
Cause the one in Orlando sort of looks cheap.
It's, it's a, once you're inside, once you're inside, the signs all look kind of cheap and
like, it looks like kind of like that kiss, uh, the kiss golf mini golf course in Las Vegas.
Have you ever been there?
I love that.
I wish it were that quality.
Yeah.
Very similar to some of the mummy, uh, blacklight paint in Florida.
It's like, there's some cool effects in the mummy ride.
This is what opened right around that time too.
Um, but yeah, some of the actual signs on that ride, a little just kind of blacklight paint.
Erin went on it though.
And she said exactly this.
She said it was like blacklight.
She said it was like a youth group haunted house.
Well, she, she found the video, the video, which in Orlando, she went on the France one.
No, she thought France was a little credit.
Well, from, I'm all I can go off of is just the video.
So I think that the video I watched made it look a little less cheap.
I'm sure it's cheap because the same coaster, they didn't do a ton of work on it.
But I like the narrative better.
I think though you like the narrative that you're either a note or you're in a video
or Steven Tyler designed a ride for you.
I like that Steven Tyler designed a ride for you.
I think like you were saying, we should update the video.
Aerosmith should still be involved, but I think it should show like, you know,
what's been happening more.
It shouldn't be 20 years old.
It should reference Steven Tyler's new solo album, red, white, and you,
the country album he put out about a year ago.
It should also like somebody should say, Hey Joe, how are the Hollywood vampires going?
And he should talk about them for a minute or two.
He should say what's happening.
Maybe a cameo from Captain Jack Sparrow himself, Johnny Depp.
He's the guy.
Hey Joe, we need you in the limo.
Yeah, that's see, that's great.
That's what I'm talking about.
The vampires of we got a gig.
We have to go play our cover of paint it black for an audience of record executives who paid
$600 a pop.
Are they, are you yet now in this new version trying to make it to
a co-headliner Hollywood vampires Aerosmith concert?
That's great.
But Steven probably would put in that he gets them to do also a solo set of just the country
songs as well.
Well, then you're getting your money's worth.
It's a star started event.
But you don't see this concert that you're on the way to this concert that doesn't exist.
Hold on.
I have a plus up as well.
Tell me more.
In regards to that.
Yes.
I also think that it's they build the whole thing up that you're going to see a concert
and then that doesn't pay off.
So that's a bummer too, because like you really there's video screens when you get off the
ride in the gift shop that's showing the concert and that sucks.
I think you got the gift shop.
You build the stage, take some of the pirates off of pirates of the Caribbean.
They already look like the members of Aerosmith in a lot of ways.
Their age, their skin is rough and oily and their hair long and stringy and scary.
One of the mules is Steven Tyler.
That's fine.
I don't think anyone would notice.
Just put a microphone with a scarf tied to it in front.
I think you put those guys there at the stage, much like that Minions room where you get
to dance with the Minions after the Minions ride.
Oh, yeah.
This is a better version of it.
You get a robot concert going for you.
It cycles through.
If you want to stay there forever and see their whole greatest hits, all the dirtiest
songs, you sit there.
You watch this robot concert.
It's like the Chuck E. Cheese Band.
I think that's a great idea.
That's truly a fun ending to the Aerosmith ride.
And Wayne and Garth appear at some point, say they aren't worthy, ask them to play at
Wayne Stock.
They resist, but ultimately have a change of heart.
Of course.
Then the robots all have to leave at the end because the limo pulls up to take them to
Wayne Stock.
So you're tying together all of the things Aerosmith ever had to go to.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Or you could really tie it all together and at the end they are kidnapped by an evil group
called the New Order Nation and their horrible leader Helga who are trying to enslave all
of the world's youth population by suppressing all forms of entertainment, which is the plot
of the video game Revolution X.
Of course.
Oh, man.
So if they get to perform for three hours, then Eliana Dufferin and the others are going
to say, Eliana Douglas pulls up, you bring her back, we got to get to Wayne Stock.
Of course, you know how I feel about my fans, Wayne and Garth.
Of course.
And then they're walking, the animatronics have to do all this and play accurate chords.
Then they're on their way to the limo and then the evil Helga from the video game Revolution
X swoops in with, I don't know, ninjas, spies, whatever.
She has her disposal.
She is General Goons.
Hey, I have some great memories of playing Revolution X.
Switching between Area 51 and Revolution X at the game room at Disney's Key West Resort,
which is crazy to think about how graphic both those games kind of are.
Oh, yeah.
Very violent.
You're just firing shots into a concert.
Just firing shots, yeah.
I believe, tying other stuff together, you are like, I think the secret weapon that you
unlock at the end of the game is a big CD rifle.
So Aerosmith, again, going all in on CDs.
You're definitely shooting CDs at some point.
I think the CDs function like grenades in other games where you can clear the screen
with CDs.
Well, I think we've come to the end here now that we're discussing all of the multimedia
that Aerosmith has been a part of.
The primary one and the greatest one being Rock and Roller Coaster.
It seems like this thing is good.
I think we dig the Rock and Roller Coaster.
It may be less so Paris, although, hey, it takes all kinds.
Sure.
And I haven't been on it.
So when I make it out, well, I will never probably see it unless I go quickly.
It may be replaced by the...
Well, then, you know, we wish you a fond a du, a fond au revoir.
I'd also just here as we to play us out.
Here's a little thing for I didn't realize that Aerosmith, in addition to the film
appearances, in addition to the video game Revolution X, they did two other video games.
Did you guys know that?
That the guitar hero, there was an Aerosmith guitar hero.
And then...
Yes, yes, I played that.
OK, how was it?
Well, actually, I mean, another version is of what I was saying earlier, not another
version, sort of to continue what I was saying earlier is I played that with an ex-girlfriend
in like 2008 and she was like, Aerosmith sucks.
And we played it and I was like, well,
maybe they aren't so good.
So, yes, I would know you were just under her spell, like the villainous Helga of the
revolution was a lot like Helga.
That's true.
Now I think about it.
But you unkidnapped yourself.
But they were part of another third video game that I only heard about today.
A CD-ROM actually called Quest for Fame.
Oh, there it is.
OK.
And it was kind of you heard of it before?
No, I just remembered like a string of like CD-ROM games with a celebrity.
Mm hmm.
There were a friend and listener of the show, Tyler Burton.
There's a lot of crazy like rock oriented CD-ROMs, which I don't know,
we'll justify talking about them on the show.
So I will bend the topic.
They were sold in theme parks or something.
Who fucking cares?
But so I just so this was kind of a proto guitar hero where the vibrations of your
V pick let you play along with your favorite band, Aerosmith.
You didn't need a full guitar like Guitar Hero requires.
All you need is your pick that's attached via USB cord, I assume.
And you can play it along a tennis racket or a or just your leg.
It's just strumming against anything you want.
And so just to play us out, I'm going to play a little bit of the gameplay of Quest for Fame.
This is what it sounds like when you add your tennis racket guitar to Dude Looks Like a Lady.
But with that with that being said, before I play us out here,
you've survived podcast the ride.
Check us out at podcast the ride on Twitter, on Instagram.
We'll try to post some some Halyx there and hashtag Halyx to point.
Oh, point spelled out.
We'll figure it out.
We'll make it available for you by the time you head there.
Hey, thanks so much for listening, everybody.
And here now is you playing with Aerosmith.