Warning, the following podcast contains a not entirely confident explanation of haptic feedback.
Special shoutouts to K2SO and Reverend Jeremiah Wright.
And a fond farewell for the Glendale Galleria restaurant 9021FO.
Today we tackle the Star Wars hyperreality experience, Secrets of the Empire.
Enter the void on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the podcast hosted by three men who would gladly take jobs as longshoremen at Pixar Pier.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined today, as always, by Mike Carlson.
Hey, yeah, that sounds like a pretty good job. You know, you're unloading candy for Bing Bong.
Not bad, his new Bing Bongs candy emporium.
Bing Bongs and that chicken restaurant are opening there.
We've all seen the art for what's coming in Pixar Pier and Disney's California Adventure.
But we haven't seen the crates. What do the crates look like at the pier that we are to unload?
Yeah, it's it's to me, the third host, Jason, you have to introduce the firewalls.
Scott Gardner, you started talking. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I figured I was trying to save you the work. I wasn't trying to.
Scott Gardner and I love saying my own name, too. So two birds with one stone.
Yeah. Well, let's let's look out for those jobs and yeah, we all need to work.
I mean, we don't really have regular jobs. We're in the entertainment business.
You never know when you're going to get your next job often.
And if we could get, you know, some actual work doing like honest to goodness, real labor, I think we would all be good for us.
Get a little sun. Like most entertainers, we romanticize a blue collar backbreaking labor.
Yes, that's true.
And we'd like arrogantly assume it wouldn't actually be that hard. Right.
Yeah. Yeah. If I wanted to, I could make the shift. Yeah.
I could carry stuff all day. It's just I got too many ideas I want to figure out.
I'm a creator. We're storytellers.
We're some young creatives and we just have too much. We have too much to give in that department, I think.
Yeah. Loading with ideas.
This room is filled with whiteboards and they're covered in different shapes.
You use different shapes to tell different kinds of stories.
Different shapes of different cards. A pink octagon is different than a blue.
Blue circle. Yeah.
Yeah.
That's how you crack stories. Yeah.
We're all about breaking stories, but if we have to break down crates, we can do that too.
That's as specific as I could get about long shorings.
Yeah. I know that you wear like a hat, like a winter hat that's kind of falling off your head maybe when you're a longshoreman.
Even on sunny Pixar pier. Yes.
And also people know what you are. You talk like this.
This is the voice I think of a longshoreman. That's what I know.
Yeah. A platonic ideal longshoreman would have that voice.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Like an idealized.
An idealized. You're saying that there might not be accurate that some longshoremen don't talk like that.
Yeah. Okay. It's possible.
It's possible. We know so much about real things in the world.
We don't just have our heads in the fantasy clouds. We know about real stuff.
I worked at the container store for years. Okay. I planned closets for people.
I told them where boxes were and I told them where other types of boxes, different types of boxes that might not be.
This was labor. You were basically a dry longshoreman. Yes.
An indoor longshoreman. I had a neat and tidy blue apron on and I had a, there was a certain.
Which you still wear. It's torn and worn and sun bleached.
I certainly do. I like people asking me questions when I go into a retail store.
I want them to think that I'm some sort of authority. Yeah. No, no.
I think as many container store memories as you can fit into the podcast. Is this the first time it's come up?
I think I mentioned it to me perhaps one other time. I think once before. Yeah.
Yeah. I, there's a lot of content. Look, I have a lot of containers to remember.
It's my first job. One of my last jobs really, because I hadn't had a job in a long time.
But yeah, it's a, it's a great place. I was in a container store a couple of months ago and no one asked me if I needed anything, which first of all is against sort of the code of the container store.
You should be very accommodating to people.
And no one did, which I thought was maybe a problem with corporate and I was going to write a letter, but I forgot.
But yes, I feel you have lost the luster that you once had.
Also with the container store, and this does drive me nuts.
They taught me that when you would do an announcement over the speaker, you should not hang up the phone because you hear that like that noise of like the head, like the receiver hitting that clunk noise.
So when, when in Ralph's or whatever, and they're, they, you know, say something about aisle four, you hear that horrible noise.
The phone makes when it hangs up. We don't do that at container store. You put your finger, you hit it before, and then you put the phone down.
And then you put the, yeah. So it's a much cleaner sound. And then you say, have a container-y day. Yes.
And you walk out and there's a man in a corrugated box waving to you. It's corgi, the container store mascot.
That part is not true. That is corgi and that he's like named after corrugation. Yeah.
I don't know if things are corrugated at the container store. Oh, we have corrugated. Yeah. Oh, good. Oh, do you? Yeah. Okay.
Well, look how much more helpful you are still just on a podcast than the people who are in the store right now. Yes, that's true.
And that's a store that you can upsell people at. Like when people are trying to get their shit together, if you start like, oh, well, what about a couple of these little boxes to go in the bigger box?
Like I think most decluttering books say figure out what you need and then go to the container store.
But a lot of people start by going to the container store. Oh, yeah. Yeah. There was. Look, we sold a bill of goods to many people and they probably didn't help them at all.
Yeah, in a way. Sure. I mean, if you utilize the products correctly, it certainly helps.
But for many people, they went in thinking that they were going to change their lives. And no, they just spent money.
They filled the pockets of the fat cats in Texas that had corporate container store corporate at big container, big container and container fat cats.
Yeah. Do you just moved recently and did you feel that your container store knowledge helped you move more efficiently?
No, no, I'm disorganized. I am a disorganized person in some aspects, not everything, but in a lot of aspects.
No, it didn't help me. It helps me. I will know how to plan a closet a little bit, even though my closet looks like shit right now.
But if I ever have a giant closet, I will know how to make shelves and put them in the right spot.
You will not be addled by the big problem that the people have. I don't even know where to begin to find my own stuff. Yeah.
I need an atlas to get into my own closet. You'll be the most organized rich man.
There are a lot of rich people in the Chicago suburbs that have closets that I designed.
Wow.
Which is just, it's a night. You know, people will once they hear podcast the ride, they'll be like, whoa, did you know Mike from podcast the ride is who planned this closet?
And then the house value will go way up.
And they'll be like, he got away from containing? That seems like a misstep for him.
They will say that they won't be wrong. Should have stuck with what he was good at.
He was very good at this and he decided to go out to California and blow it.
A lot of money in those Chicago suburb closets. I mean, there's got to be, you know, Obama's birth certificate is there.
He's real Kenyan birth certificate is there. Sure.
He went into a container store in disguise. Yeah.
Now, if I wanted to hide something, I want to hide something in a non-descript container.
I planned everyone. I planned Rahm Emanuel's closet. I planned Reverend Wright's closet.
Obama's reverend. I planned the weather underground guy. What's that guy's name?
Ayers? Yeah. Bill Ayers. I planned Bill Ayers' closet.
And I planned Man Cow Muller, famous radio personality Man Cow Muller's closet.
Now on like Fox at two in the morning.
And a lot of your containers are full of the bodies that we don't even know about that Obama had to dispose of in order to get the job to begin with.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There were trunks. I would suggest trunks to people.
I knew what they were for, but it was against company policy for me to like come on.
That's the Chicago way, right? You know? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Well, the Daley family.
The Daley's, the Capone's, you know. Yeah, yeah. When they go like, I need a trunk.
And I was like, got it, my man. And then we went back there and I showed them.
And then I would. Yeah, it would be a very download thing.
Like, why doesn't Muller or Leaker Comey talk to Mike Carlson? These containers contain all the answers.
It's a cover up. This has been a lovely tangent into the world of right wing conspiracy theories and organized crime at the start of a Star Wars episode.
That's true. We're going to have to change the title of the episode to Star Wars, secrets of the Empire slash the container store.
Part one slash hashtag the truth.
Well, there's one there's one other topic that I'd like to squeeze in before we enter the void, which is that I just returned from a trip to Vancouver, Canada.
I left this dear country of ours for a few days and missed it.
So it's pining for all the everything it's been making America so fun lately.
And I had I had a wonderful time. I had done Toronto and I'd done Montreal, but I had not done Vancouver.
And I was very excited to be there because there's a lot in Vancouver that was set up in the wake of Expo 86.
If you were if you're not familiar with with World's Fairs in general or Expos, if you're a fan of Epcot Center, I like the I like Expos and stuff because they give you that Epcot vibe.
You know, there's that there's that futurism and idealism towards the future and a lot of bland music playing everywhere and weird robots.
There's a guy named Ernie. There's a robot named Ernie running around the you ever seen a picture of Ernie?
I don't think I have. Should I look it up right now? Oh, look up Ernie.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Should I just Google Ernie from Vancouver? Yeah. Ernie Expo 86.
That's good. There's a lot of cute bots out there in bot lore, but I think Ernie is one of the most adorable bots.
And in fact, he was a topper on our wedding cake on Aaron and I's wedding.
Yeah, it was it was Vancouver Ernie.
I have you look familiar. Yeah. Yeah.
If you're listening at home, do yourself a favor. Look up adorable Ernie.
He was a he was rolling around. Yeah.
Oh, that's very cute and very in your wheelhouse. I feel like.
Oh, yes. Absolutely. Yeah.
Blocky 80s logos and faceless minimal adorable robots.
It was the top of our wedding cake was Ernie from Expo 86 and our two D2.
Our two D2. We gave a little bow tie to and Ernie, despite being a boy, got a veil.
Ernie was the bride and is a wonderful.
It was a wonderful cake. I loved her cake.
So we got to see Ernie's birthplace, his home.
And among the things that Expo 86 left around Vancouver is a place called Science World,
which has this this big, awesome Epcotty dome to it.
And that place is home to the OmniMax theater where back to the future, the ride was tested.
As we talked about in that episode many months ago, there was this alternate version of the ride
that they ended up testing up in Vancouver and canceling and starting over because it was making people sick.
And I will tell you, I sat in that very dome where it was tested.
Pretty major motion sickness. Wow. Really?
Yeah, I thought so.
While watching the film that we chose to watch, which was a 1988 French movie about beavers called Beavers.
And as you were following beavers around their meadows and watching them build dams and such.
Yeah, we got a little. We definitely got a little motion sick, which doesn't happen to me often.
It doesn't happen to me on boats or planes, but watching the plight of the Beavers.
Yeah, apparently it did it did it for me. What year was it? Sorry.
1988. Pretty old movie. And it was filmed with it like in it was an original IMAX or I'm not sure.
Maybe OmniMax movie as well, which I liked getting to see like a janky old film like there were jib shots of this thing
revealing the grand vista of the dams that were built, which were incredibly impressive.
I'm very impressed by Beavers or as the French call them, le castor, as they said constantly, le castor.
They teach their children work ethics and minimal architecture.
Has that been playing exclusively since 88?
No, it was a special thing. Every day at 11 at Science World, they have a slot called Teacher's Choice.
So if you are a Canadian teacher and you want to do a field trip, you can call ahead and they'll pick whatever.
And for some reason, this group of English speaking kids wanted to see the French film Beavers.
And they told us it was just us in a big field trip group.
And which was kind of funny. A lot of kids laughing at the Beaver antics or the when the baby Beaver encounters a skunk for the first time and then runs away like a lot of weird Foley Beaver.
I recommend Beavers in general, by the way. Excellent film.
But I like that it was like a janky, all the jib movements were real clunky. It was very not digital. It was very analog but in a charming way.
Anyway, Beavers made me sick because if you look to the side of the screens, like seeing a forest and with a lot of trees, those trees with the fish eye bend like crazy.
Oh, they were. Yes. Yeah, yeah. Not straight at all. So now I understand why they had to start over with the Back to the Future Ride.
More, I know the audience was clamoring to hear more about Omni-Max curvature issues.
Sure, of course. Did you wander into the projection room to see if maybe they had an old reel of the Back to the Future Ride just hanging around there?
Yeah, just that. You know, there wasn't there was not that but they on in the exit you do get to pass by the projector, which is an incredible sight.
It is the actual thing. Yeah, yeah. It's like such massive military looking technology and you see the film reels and it feels like it's like a foot wide.
What they're running through that thing. It takes up so much space in the room. I'm so impressed by old crazy IMAX technology. I don't know how any of it was ever done.
Do you know what's playing in there? Not during the teachers thing. There's some space movie narrated by Jennifer Lawrence.
It's you know, like any IMAX theater in a in a science setting. They're cycling through a lot of things.
I think there's probably some something to be had. If IMAX counts as themed entertainment, which I'll declare it does.
Yes, I would like to delve deeper into some of those odd like, you know, like Michael Jordan at the Max.
Oh, yeah. Is that the correct name doing something like that? Predating Space Jam. Michael Jordan's first. Oh, sure.
OK. And the what there was a Rolling Stones IMAX movie, I believe, maybe multiple Rolling Stones.
That sounds right. It was right in the center downtown Philadelphia.
There's the Franklin Institute named after Ben Franklin, which the the original Institute of Future Technology game of the Franklin Institute.
It's like it's a museum, but it's fun or it's like a museum, but it's like whimsical.
Like you walk through a giant version of the human heart.
Like you walk through all the valves and stuff. That's like there's play areas and they have one of the first IMAX, if not the first IMAX in Philadelphia.
And and we'd go on field trips or like, you know, go into the city on a Saturday with family.
And yeah, we'd usually go to the Franklin Institute, usually pay an extra eight or ten bucks at the time to see an IMAX thing.
It was always nature or science based as opposed to now, where it's like you can just see pretty much anything in IMAX.
But it did feel like, you know, a treat in the way that I think of like theme parks as a treat.
It was special. It was rare. There wasn't that many. It can only be done there. It's place specific.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It is really impressive. Like watching this this this dome just in Gulf.
You really mean it's bigger than the Universal CityWalk IMAX. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Much bigger. And then curved and like wraps around it.
Which we were just at the other night. We were just there. We saw the premiere.
Or what did you think? I left with a headache. Jason was depressed by it.
Jason felt sad for all the little children that would see this movie because they would be so sad going into the summer.
Also myself. I don't know. Sad for you.
It was funny because a lot of people were people. Some people who don't like it are like, oh, it's boring or it's stupid or whatever.
But Jason was like was affected, just too sad for him. Freaked out by it?
Yeah. Well, by one of the effects like in the ending. Yes.
Yeah. I mean, this will be out for a few weeks, but I guess we should just avoid talking about it for another month or two.
Yeah. Everyone say what the effect is.
An effect is depressing enough.
I found it unnerving. Huh.
And then in the other part, I realized, yeah, usually what happens is we come out of these movies and I like a very, Mike pointed this out, that I'm very cheery.
And I'm like, oh, that was fun because it's like, oh, it's a thing. We go to the big IMAX opening night. Maybe we have a drink of Margaritaville beforehand.
And this one I left so bummed and Mike came out going like, yeah, it was great.
Yeah, I, yes, I was very enthusiastic about it.
Usually I'm like, oh, pretty good. Or I liked it. And usually you're like, yeah, hey.
But because Mike, you're a real death merchant.
You are a friend, a friend of the show who has yet to do the show, Nick Mundy. He also liked it. He went with us and he immediately was like, you're going to hate it by tomorrow.
Right. So he said to me, I was like, I like most of these people complain about the Marvel movies. I like most of them.
Like, you just, you know, it's tomorrow today and it hasn't happened yet.
So wrong again, Monday. I like come on the show and to argue on the show.
Yes, let's be a let's movie fight it out. Yes.
But that said, my headache was not the content of the movie.
The fact it was the fact that it was an IMAX 3D and I already have pretty big glasses and to put those on top of it, it gets a little jarring.
Like we had good seats, but I feel like the 3D, I don't move my head a lot. I feel like regular movies.
I move my head more and this I feel like it was just kind of planted.
So that was my not quite motion sickness, but that was my IMAX. I see. I see. Old man illness.
Well, look, you go see Beavers, you might get you might get motion sickness, but on the other hand, no depressing effects in this.
The only the scariest thing that's going to happen is when a bear tries to break into the dam.
Spoiler, he doesn't because the Beavers built it to last. Wow. Yeah.
That sounds like a movie Jason would come out of like glowing. I think you would love Beavers.
I can't imagine. I don't want to meet a person who wouldn't love Beavers. Yeah. Who wouldn't love Lucas Thor.
It was so charming. But you know what? That's not the main thing.
This is going to take forever. That was about that was three lines of my notes and it's already taken up 80 minutes of the podcast.
What I mainly wanted to talk about is I got to experience an attraction called Fly Over Canada. Oh, yeah.
Which is another IMAX related experience. It also stemming from Expo 86.
This is this big pier area that has a hotel and it's where ships leave from in the barred inlet.
I think I'm getting that right. Anyone in Canada? Let me know if I was wrong about that.
But yeah, they had an IMAX theater there that was about to close and they wanted to see if they could figure out something different to do with it.
And I think a local company pitched. They want to do something like really specifically Canadian.
So they figured out this attraction where you fly over Canada and this ride is Soarin.
It's not even similar to Soarin. It just is Soarin.
And I found this really strange that there is just a free standing Soarin not in the Disney Park because Disney is so notoriously litigious.
It seems odd to me that they would just like, yeah, do it. That's fine.
And what year did this open?
Hmm. A couple years ago, 2013, I want to say. Yeah, yeah.
I think. Yeah, yeah. Soarin well established. It's the same color scheme.
Wow. It's the same blue lighting like the little like the rails that you hold on to. You keep your belongings in the same place.
I think it does. They don't. The hang gliders, quote unquote, don't swing out in that erector set kind of way.
They don't do that upward and forward the way it does in Soarin. It just like it just moves straight ahead of you.
But that's the one thing I will say about this. I think the the range of motion may be better possibly. Really?
Then Soarin. Yeah, there's a little bit more going on. It's a newer, newer ride.
Yeah. And I think and what I believe that people who worked on Soarin for Imagineering went on to do this.
Turn coach. I say. Yeah. Yeah. But you're a betrayers. Yeah. I don't know that they own the ride system for Soarin.
Maybe not. Like I think Disney is trademarked older ride systems or like we talked about the Kuka arm like exclusive rights being sold to it.
But I think this was a third party came up with. That might be why then. Yeah.
Maybe the end and it's end by not doing the erector set thing by having it just swing forward.
Maybe the system is different enough that Disney could not claim that they they own it.
I don't mean to to say something opposite to what you were saying.
But I do believe I've heard Tony Baxter talk about a gentleman in Imagineering who did come up with this system.
Uh huh. So you're saying no, no, no. I think you're I think because I've heard that too.
That's something they couldn't figure out how to swing the he came up with like out of his like a record set and yes.
Yeah, yeah, I think that story is true. But maybe I don't know.
But it doesn't use that system is what I'm saying. I see. Otherwise, it's exactly the same as Soarin.
But it's just it's different the way it gets you to the screen. Yeah, I see.
But I just it's the same color scheme. It's the same lighting. Right. So it is so utterly similar.
Is there a guy who was like a side character on Seinfeld that does the introduction of it?
He may maybe he's a side character on a on a Canada specific show.
He's on Bruce McCulloch's Young Drunk Punk.
He's the only one I could name.
The Warburton of Canada. I'll assume this guy was the putty of Canada.
Yeah, but there is it's the same. He's also in like a flight suit.
There's a joke about sorry. Hey, sorry. You can't bring your bring your hat on.
Then it comes to a Mountie instead of a mouse ears thing.
Yeah. Wow. All the same just steps.
So, yeah. Yeah. You can't have loose belongings. Sorry.
We've got to put that hockey stick away and it's like the same.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Wow. And then the guy the guy smiles like that's OK.
And he's missing teeth. I love it. I don't mean to sound like a yeah.
I saying that I think that it's odd that there's another Soarin.
Please don't take it down or anything.
As if this podcast would cause that I love I love that there is that there is a
free standing ride just like next to a convention center and a hotel in like the
deep city of Vancouver. Wonderful. I think that's so great.
And yeah, the whole thing was was pretty neat and well done.
And oh, I should well I should also say oh yeah, it's eight minutes long.
Twice as long as Soarin says you're paying a little more.
So you got to get bang for your buck. And they don't have the turnover rates that
theme park attraction would have. So they're able to make it longer. Right.
And I should tell you some of the places that you get to go.
You get to go to Muskoka, see some classic boats.
You go to Wheatland Hutterite Colony in Rockyford.
It's real pretty up there. You go to Lake Magog.
Go to Bella Coola. See the see the heli skiers.
That's pretty neat. The heli skiers. The heli skiers.
I wrote that down off the website, but I couldn't tell you what a heli skier.
You just jump out of a helicopter and start skiing. OK, that's awesome.
Whoa, that's really insane. That's hardcore. Huh.
All right. Well, I should find out more about heli skiers.
But yeah, it's it's really neat.
The one one issue I would say is that as opposed to jumping from the Eiffel Tower
to the Serengeti to the Taj Mahal, I don't know that I know the difference
between Craig E. Mountain and Lake Magog.
It just becomes you're in a bunch of fields for a while.
That being said, still pretty.
And yeah, you get to see some fireworks just like in Soarin.
You get to go over Niagara Falls. That's nice.
Yeah. One complaint that I do have, though, is that there is a part in Soarin where there's
there's like a little bit of water in Soarin, correct?
Yeah. Do you get sprayed? Brits, maybe?
Yeah, I don't know that there is. Maybe it doesn't happen.
I think it's so immersive. Oh, maybe it's just pine.
Yeah, I think it just smells. I don't think you get sprayed at all.
OK, OK. In this ride, you get sprayed hard in the face.
Oh, yeah. It's universal. Shotgun blast.
The old universal. Yeah, it's way more universal.
For some reason, they just they want to obscure your vision.
And on these rides. And it happened four times.
So many. And it is just a thick cloud burst.
And we got we got off there and my wife like couldn't see for a little bit.
And I think it just like messed up her contact line. She replaced it.
But like we were wondering for a sec, did you get an eye infection from fly over Canada?
So if I had any notes, I would say, yeah, maybe not such a gigantic stream straight in the fat.
But otherwise, hey, fly over Canada. Great work.
If you're heading up to the Vancouver area, check it out.
And yeah, they also do it. They do a Christmas version, I'd like to say, which is the same ride.
You still go to Lake Magog. Don't worry, Lake Magog. OK, good.
But then you fly over Santa's workshop and stuff and they pump in gingerbread sense.
Oh, that's fun. And then there's a Halloween one that is even more exactly the same,
except I think a witch flies through every once in a while.
But it did make me think changing up Soarin, but doing like holiday overlays of Soarin,
I think is a great idea for the Disney parks.
Do you mean just have like a witch randomly go inside or like actual difference?
I mean, sure, that. Is there a popular Disney witch?
I guess I'm thinking of the Warner Brothers witch, that one witch, the June Furet witch.
Right. Now, I don't have great ideas for that.
But like, how about, you know, Jafar hijacks your, you know, your little magic carpet rider?
Hades. Yes. James Woods shows up in the middle.
Uh-huh. And plunges you down into. Is he also from Hades? Is Hades the place?
He has. Yeah, because his name is Hades for sure. His name is Hades.
But he seems like. But that's the name of the god. I think they call it the underworld.
That's the name of the god. Yeah, yeah, they don't call it Hades.
I think they just call it the underworld. They don't call it hell.
I would say like Hercules, you're going to hell.
This is the debate though, because Soarin' is so even though.
Yeah, well, now that it, now I'm taking this back.
I was going to say Soarin' is just real world locations with no characters.
That being said, Tinkerbell shows up at the end of it.
Yes. And totally ruins the reality of the fact of, of the. Yeah.
Well, also you're constantly flying over Main Street at Christmas time.
No matter the year. There's a lot of lights in Soarin' as well.
So if you want to, if you want to really believe you are hang gliding in March
and that last scene really fucks it all up.
Yeah. You're expecting to see like a grad night.
Like you're expecting to see kids like in the alleyway where the ice cream window used to be sneaking cigarettes.
Oh yeah. Sneaking cig puffs.
Maybe, maybe it's just like when you go into Egypt and you see the pyramids,
it's just like the pyramids have a big bow on top.
Like there's just little, little fun things to do that way.
Why is there a bow?
Because it's Christmas time. Oh, I see. Oh, okay. I missed that.
Okay. Pyramid packet.
Like a Lexus December to remember sales event with the big bow that goes on the cars.
Yeah. It's like a Lexus December to remember sales event.
Yeah. Or. I like the Christmas decorations on the Taj Mahal.
Uh huh. Yeah. Or when the, that glacier like starts to melt in the Antarctica or the Antarctica scene,
it's like there's a snowman that's like waving goodbye to the glacier and it's frosty
and he's got his, his old silk hat.
Like I'm, I'm due to die soon. Yeah. That'll be me in the, in the briny soon.
Uh. There's a way to do it. I guess what I'm saying.
Those polar bears could crack a Coke. So we know they're the Christmas Coke bears.
We could do some more product promotion on that ride too. I think that would be good for them.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That'd be nice.
So anyway, it did, it opened up my eyes to the possibilities of, of a change in up soaring.
I think it'd be, it'd be fun. I think they got something called flight of the dragon too for Chinese new year.
Oh, interesting. And I think they do fly over America as well.
And it's all in the same thing. It's not like, cause, cause uh, the avatar ride is very much soaring in Florida,
but it's like a different riot, a little different system.
But we talked about the holiday overlay of that. Correct? Yes. Back in the Christmas episode.
That would make that one happen too. That was the one where you throw presents out across the, across Pandora.
You get to be the Santa Claus. Yeah. You're Santa basically riding cause Santa's got real sick.
Navi Santa got so sick. And then you're riding in the back of the mighty Akron with a bag full of toys.
Well, I'd love to deliver presents to the Hella skiers, Bella Coola. That'd be great.
Yeah. I believe that was also where people tweeted us and rightfully so.
They're like, you guys fucked up. You missed police Navi.
Yes. I mean, yep. Great call. We absolutely, we absolutely missed that.
It is really shameful. I mean, there's a couple of things we could probably make corrections on,
but none more glaring than that. And I'm glad we've, we've addressed it. It's my fault.
I'll take credit cause it was one I pitched the ride and I didn't think of it. And uh, you know, I suck.
We made it right. Um, but here, well, you know, to, to tie it into our primary topic of the day,
as I said, I love the idea that you can, you can round a corner, uh, in a, in a, in a busy Metroplex in a shopping center
and that there is a big themed ride experience there. Yes. I think that's so wonderful.
And that's what is attempting to be built by, uh, by this company, The Void. The Void.
Yes. This attraction, Star Wars Secrets of the Empire, among others, there are voids going in. Yes.
To, uh, to a bunch of places all over the, the world, I guess. Voids are popping up everywhere.
There could be one just, uh, on your block in your mall and your doctor's office. It could be anywhere.
Taking over the Schomburg container store. No, please don't say that. Never.
That's why that was where I was born and raised essentially. They could find a way to fit both of them into the space.
Maybe. If The Void was like, you got to go back in time to what the container store was like in 2002.
You know, if you had to experience what it was, the history of the store. We're already doing our, our version, what our ideal VR.
I would like to do the VR experience of being Mike Carlson at the container store in 2002. Yeah, that would be great.
Having, only you can put this on the correct shelf. Having friends walk in and just laugh at me because I'm wearing the apron and I'm trying to look busy.
That's basically what it would be. Like high school friends would come over and make fun of that. You had a job. I did a lot of that.
I made fun of my friend who worked at start. Like what if I came in and ordered like I did stuff like that where like we pretend we didn't know each other and I'm kind of laughing at him.
But I, I, that was just a regular coffee transaction. There's no joke there. Yeah. It's just funny to see your friend in a context of like an adult man.
Really is. That's all it really is. Yeah. This doesn't make any sense. This isn't a shirt you'd wear in real life. This doofy idiot is actually like trying to be professional.
I was a utility clerk at a supermarket for a summer and, you know, putting the carts away and cleaning up spills and like taking restocking items and that sort of thing.
And like I specifically remember friends coming by once and they're like, all right, we're going to go put some carts askew in the parking lot. And I'm like, oh, please don't think it's a joke.
And I go out. They had just to give you work. Yeah. I think I did stuff like that though. Probably. I'm going to. It was a harmless thing. Yeah. I hearts.
They're going to have to go. Yeah. Yeah. I bet that did happen to me. They went and like moved the cart way far away and I had to like walk down to where the Schlotzky's deli was and go get the cart, which was the other side of that.
That that start shopping. But you handled it with aplomb and it's nothing that somebody who's a longshoreman at heart couldn't take care of.
Yes. That's why I think that I'm ready for that job is because I went through all that hard shit. Rough day. I on a skewed for carts. Oh boy. I need to crack a cold one after that. Did your friends actually say like I'm going to skew some carts? No.
That seems pretty professional for a young rap scallion to say. So the void, I think we have to. So. So the void. Yeah. So basically the void is like it's a pretty small area, but it's virtual reality.
And it has this and it first went in like I was made aware of it when it went into downtown Disney in California and then Disney Springs in Florida. Yeah. With this like big Star Wars thing.
And it was a lot of fanfare, a lot of promotion made with Lucasfilm involved. Of course. Yes. An original story. We should say before and I think we should do because we want to full transparency on this podcast.
This is the first time we've been invited basically after doing some inquiring. We were invited to this. We got a perk baby. We got a perk and got to experience this. So we want to be like. We got the press invite.
We've put out feelers to places and some of them have been pretty receptive, but they often, you know, they've been receptive. But this is the first time where they were like, hey, come check this out.
You guys VIPs and it's wonderful. And I just like to make a pledge like a pledge and a plea. If you invite us or comp us, we're going to go to be there.
Yeah. And we'll spread it to all the theme park. Head arenas who listen to this podcast on the weekly. Sure. They'll get butts in your seats. Right.
In your virtual seats. We're going to goof around about controversial people in President Obama's past. Sure. But that's fine. You're going to still get people that are going to listen to three idiots and they're going to come to the place we're talking about no matter what we say because we're excited about all this.
Oh, yeah. And that's even if we and even if we were to give a place a bad review, which I can't imagine we are about Star Wars secrets and empires is very cool. But even if we did, according to Twitter, we've gotten some knuckleheads to go to some places that were dumb and bad because we told them to because that's part of it too.
So no one should be offended if we give something a bad review, which we're not going to, which we're not. We had a great. We all liked it.
This is a you know, you did remind me of something, though, when you successfully sent out this email and got us into the void, I thought, why don't I do the same thing and copy paste some of your text and try to get comped for fly over Canada?
And it didn't work. Nobody responded, which is maybe I would have looked the other way on that thick mist in the face and my wife's near eye infection if I had been comped. But so we're still we're figuring out fly over Canada, however you want to make a means to the Garener family.
I think they should make it right. And I think basically, look, if you're with an earshot and you have anything to do with PR, any of the big places we're talking to, obviously Disney is going to be hard. But like Knott's Berry Farm, we're listening to these other podcasts that do the theme park stuff. We know season pass. We know mice chat.
We hear these hosts. They were invited to the Boysenberry Festival at Knott's Berry Farm. OK, where was our invite to the Boysenberry Festival?
Yeah, because I was at home crying that I did not get a Boysenberry Shakespeare. Three weeks of nonstop Boysenberry at Knott's Berry Farm and we weren't there to cover it. Yeah. I mean, come on.
And if you if you let us come to BBF 19, I promise to be as as the fusive and glowing as everyone has been to Beyonce at Coachella. That's how I will treat. I will treat whatever free Boysenberry flavored pizza I get.
I will be I will consider it the Beyonce of food. Yeah. So I think, look, the famously the podcast Doughboys, Nick Weigert always says Doughboys can't be bought. And I'm not saying we can be bought, but we can certainly be kind of bought.
We remember who our friends are and our enemies and our best friend at the moment. The people behind the void.
Thank you for inviting us, Void. Everyone was very nice. Everyone was very nice. Someone said, I was Scott for taking a photo, but that's all. Someone said he did break the rules. And when he did it, I was uncomfortable. No one told me you couldn't take photos.
It was unclear. This was my issue is that I took a photo of a TV screen with nothing on it and I was immediately scolded for it. And I was like, well, I just thought that I could because there was no signage anywhere remotely implying that I could not take photographs. That's why I thought I could take photographs.
Very minor complaints. So that's actually that's where the complaints stop, because once the television was turned on, we got to meet one of our favorite characters. So we're going to say, if you don't, I mean, I guess stop listening.
If you don't want to hear spoilers, which would mostly be what characters show up and what the there's a story plot point in it. But I feel like we can't talk about it without mentioning these things.
So if you want, then here's the non-spoiler review. Fun. Very fun. Check it out. Liked it. Yeah. Check it out. And yeah, that's all I have. That's the non-spoiler review. A better use of the space in Los Angeles's Glendale Galleria than the restaurant 9021FO.
Yes, we went to the Glendale Galleria. Resident Peace 9021FO. No offense, I have no idea the quality of that restaurant. I don't know if it was good or bad, but going to Mustafar instead. Yeah, well, Scott spoiled it.
The poster has lava in it. Isn't that so sorry everyone. The presence of stormtroopers. No, Scott, you can't say that either. It's implied by the poster. No, maybe you haven't seen the poster. I guess so. Oh my God. Folks, we're so sorry what Scott just did to you. Bad boy Scott taking photos of TVs and spoiling names of planets.
A couple things to note. One. It's going to be a spoiler. No, I'm getting into spoilers. It's a thing to note, not a spoiler. Let's give them the official break now. This is the official break. If you don't want to hear spoilers about the Star Wars void experience. Hyperreality. Hyperreality. That is a term I've seen used by them. Hyperreality because it's full vision and audio. There are also effects. There are very cool effects. Hapsics.
There's heat effects. There's haptic effects. Haptics. You wear a haptic vest. So if you don't want to hear what the haptics specifically are. Stop listening. You have survived the spoiler free part of podcast. Travel to Anaheim, Orlando, Vegas, London or Glendale and bang out the void and now start listening again.
Or yeah. Alright. Alright. Now. Okay. Whole music. Darth Vader, Cassian, Andor, NK2SO show up. Jason all at once. Too many spoilers at once. I almost didn't want that. One of them. Whoa. What a reveal. What a stinker. You are a stinker.
We can build to the McGuffin though. We can build to the thing. Let's go way back. How do we suit up? How does the whole thing happen? Well first of all we should say that the void is the work of a company that is headquartered in Linden, Utah for some reason. Did you know that? I did not.
It's like a weird, it's a big fancy ornate shed in Linden which is south of, it's in the vicinity of Salt Lake City and that's where all this VR magic happens. Isn't that weird? I believe, so I read a little about the company too and I believe they were going to build an attraction or a park or there and then kind of pivoted more towards this VR hyper reality stuff.
There's something called Evermore Park in Pleasant Grove, Utah which now is being built because I watched drone footage and the village of Evermore is starting to be put together. It is described as perhaps a British or an English pastoral Victorian, perhaps even steampunk kind of place.
And I think, and I went to the website and all of the artwork and everything looks very cool. I think this will be an extremely cool place. But building a theme park in what Pleasant Grove, Utah, south of Salt Lake City, doesn't that feel like a hard rock park waiting to happen?
Yes.
That seems like a very bizarre place to build a theme park with no IP that is not, where people are not coming because they're going to meet the Star Wars characters.
Right.
I'm sure, I don't mean to be, I'm just questioning the business of it. Right. It seems very cool what they're planning.
Evermore Park, please listen to our episodes on Hard Rock Park and learn, learn, learn going in, learn the lessons. Learn the lessons of John Binkowski.
I think the lessons though of, I think it would have succeeded if there was more advertising. So I do think even though Hard Rock Park was a disaster, it's all the advertising, lack of advertising's fault.
Yeah.
You know what else didn't sound like a good idea is a place called Disneyland Park. That's right.
Oh, that's true. And we were just talking about like liking attractions in cities or odd places.
Yeah, that's true. So Linden, let's get you on the map. And I guess if you are in Linden, Utah, you can go to their facilities and do some of these experiences.
So they've been starting to put these up throughout the globe and some locations of the void do not have the Star Wars experience. They do have a Ghostbusters.
That Madame Tussauds in Times Square. Yes. And I think in Toronto also. Oh, okay.
I think in Toronto and I think perhaps in Dubai at a place called City Walk. No relation. In Dubai. Wow.
Yeah. There's a very confusing looking like interactive mall there where they have the void. Did you guys look much into the Ghostbusters?
I watched the trailer for it. Okay. Yeah. I watched like the promo ad. I mean, yeah, that's cool.
Fire a proton. A smart property, I think, to use it for. I think the potential for, you know, other properties that could use this is really great.
I mean, Disney bought some part of the company. So I can only imagine they're looking into other like Disney properties to put in there.
But I hope so, because, yeah, this was this was very well done. And you like it's pumped up for the ads and everything.
But I watched a lot of videos on YouTube promoting this stuff and people are very earnestly saying like I've this is the world I've been watching since eighty four in the case of Ghostbusters or, you know, watching Star Wars since I was a kid.
And now this is the first time I really felt like I was in it. Like people seem to rank these experiences.
This I mean, it definitely is. You're more in Star Wars world than than Star Tours is. This is the best V.R. I have ever done. Yeah.
And I think primarily because of combining the V.R. with practical sets like you are walking through like when you walk through a doorway, you can reach out and grab the doorway.
When you grab a blaster, you are holding a blaster. When you pull like a lever, you're pulling the lever.
But an interesting thing I found out like this space, I mean, I'd love to go back and see it with the lights on.
This space is just like a room with like some barriers and stuff and like chairs and a rack and like it's not massive.
It's not massive. It takes up a very small footprint. I was reading about the company.
I believe they could use that same space and put a new thing in there tomorrow without changing the physical space.
Wow. And you could even maybe run multiple shows like at the same time. At the same time.
Yeah, it's not huge. Oh, another thing I found out, which I didn't realize doing it.
It worked on me so well is the term here is misdirected walk or redirected walking where you think you are.
Oh, I'm walking in a straight line. And that's what you're seeing in the helmet.
It seems to be a straight line. You might be walking in a curve, but it tricks your brain.
Really? I didn't even know that. That's interesting. Utterly mind blowing.
You can look at diagrams showing how this works. Like I saw one that is there's kind of a diagram overhead and a side by side with what the guy's seeing in his helmet and what he's doing in reality.
And he's like literally touching a wall, hugging the wall. And it looks like it's a it's a hallway that extends for 50 feet straight ahead of him.
And instead he is walking around at completely curved. Why? He has no idea.
And there's another I watched another demonstration of it where they like they they send a guy down a big hallway and then they ask like what do you think you just did?
I went like 20 feet ahead of me and he walked like it's like diagonal into the side. It's so great.
There's something where like the vision, like what you're seeing is curving a little bit ahead of you, just anticipating your movements.
And because and I saw an overhead of the downtown Disney one and it's just they took out two stores to do this.
The fossil and RIP fossil and something else.
So the but you yeah you feel like you're exploring like giant spaceships and planets and stuff.
It seems like such an effective use of like especially dying storefronts like when malls and do I have spaces and malls are going out of business.
You plug this void thing in and you get so much out of so little. Right before we came here, I sent you guys a link.
There's already competition. They already have got there's an alien.
The Ridley Scott aliens. There's one in Orange, California, Orange County, California, the outlets at Orange.
The outlets are named them all called Aliens Descent.
And it's a similar thing to this where it's a storefront.
You have VR. Now that one supposedly they don't there's not a backpack.
I think they use like they might use like wrist and ankle stuff to monitor where you are.
But they're using a different system. So this is already like a competitor.
Tickets to the alien VR. So if you were listening and you work there, holler at us, which might cause us all to have some sort of episodes.
I was going to say the alien thing could scare the shit out of us.
There might not be a thing in pop culture scarier to me than the xenomorph.
Yeah, that might be number one. I'm not dying to come face to face with the xenomorph.
I'm not either. But as theme park journalists, I feel that it's our duty to have these experiences to give the public our opinion on them.
And I'd still rather do that than, you know, a 40 foot drop where ragtime birds sing at me. For some reason, that's more terrifying to me.
You would rather go on the xenomorph alien VR than Splash Mountain.
That feels pretty silly as I say it. I should do all of these things. Yes, at least those.
Now, you're not getting me. I was with Matt Mazani, our past guest earlier.
He's trying to convince me to go on. Was it X2? What's the oh, the spinning?
Why in the world would I brave X2? Yeah. Sorry, Matt. No dice.
We'll see. Maybe if you successfully complete the mission, the alien mission, maybe that will give you sort of the strength.
It'll bolster my confidence. So maybe. Yeah, that one I think would be interesting to do because not about not a bachelor movies that typically end happily.
Alien? No. Yeah. Yeah. As opposed to I mean, it's probably no specific spoiler to say that, you know, if you do pull off the mission in Star Wars, it's like congratulations.
You've done it and the galaxy is safe. There's never that moment in any alien.
Yeah, it's just like we can sleep for a second. That's the victory.
Or another whilin to you, Tony, a nerving thing happens. I was wondering if on this thing that like we will go back to like the start of everything.
But like I was wondering on this thing, if somebody got shot too much, would one of us like die?
But obviously they can't do it because it's like hard. And then like, how do you disappear?
The person does like an employee just like grab you and like pull you out of the thing.
But like if you were to jump into lava, which technically appears to be a possibility, right? What would happen to you then? Right.
What happened? Right. Who knows?
We have I mean, it tricked me enough that the one there was a narrow walkway sequence and I'm like, all right, be very careful walk.
Like I was like, you know, it's probably you end up tightrope and we don't know.
Maybe that might we might have all been imagining that because why would they make it so that you would trip?
I truly don't need for so much of this. I don't know what I did.
And I think if you showed me an actual lights on overhead of the room, I'm not sure I that would make it make any more sense.
No, there's a real magic trick thing going on here. I loved it. They suit up.
They saw the so the start of it basically is you sign your waivers because they don't want somebody falls over.
They don't want to be sued. A lot of way complicated to sign. They are yelling at you about they're like, sign away.
You're signing it. And it's an iPad. And yeah, so that is I mean, that is a thing with VR.
That is a thing that I'm sure as the technology changes because you could see somebody freaking out in here.
Yeah, I was worried it would be me to say, Scott, I feel like as we were suiting up, I was worried Scott was going to freak out.
Well, they I thought they did a great job of telling us if you start to freak out, like raise your hand, say I need say help
because we can't touch you until like until we hear please help me.
Like we're not going to start that phrase ology scared me. That's some weird matrix we cannot.
It's dangerous to unplug you. You get trapped in the void forever.
I mean, but they were pretty clear of like they were one help.
But they did say like, oh, don't just pull the thing off. Yeah.
Like, well, you got to get there's got to be a whole system, a whole way we do it. OK.
That's probably very unnerving. Yeah, I could really like that could cause you to get motion sickness or fall or something.
I think I'll rip it off.
There was also a liability because if somebody sort of was like goofing around maybe and something like pulled the thing off,
like then they would want their money back or something to maybe there's also an element of that.
Like we think I think specifically they said like we cannot pull you out of the void unless we have your expressed consent.
Yes, scary phrase ology. Very. Yes.
You sign a lot of forms and then you're led into this whole suit up room.
But you are essentially doing that when you go to Disney and Universal. Oh, you're essentially doing it.
You just don't see it. Yeah. Yeah. You've heard all sorts of fine print that comes with tickets or admission tickets.
Is it on the ticket? Is it like somewhere? Yeah.
I mean, there's fine print on tickets and then like I'm sure there's a massive thing on legalese on the website.
So, yeah. So so so the three of us were sitting up and we did we went with a friend of ours also.
So there were four total people. Should we say who the friend was?
Oh, I guess we could mention it, I guess, if we wanted.
He didn't he wasn't really. He was just flying around with his name.
He was outside. We didn't catch his name. Yeah.
He was just buzzing around the American.
But yeah, we asked him because we just we know he's a big fan of Mustafa.
So we knew that. Yeah. We asked him. Never saw his face, though.
Never saw his face. He he made the point that it felt like it was the Tom Cruise movie Edge of Tomorrow.
Because like people like they put this stuff in and you're kind of like hanging almost off of it
because it's the easiest way to put on like the jacket or the best kind of a thing.
The helmet, the visor comes down from from a wire.
You feel like you're putting on a harness that's going to lift you into the air like in a show.
So the four of us are like hanging from the harness, like basically at what we're suiting up.
And it really feels like that part where they're about to just drop you into a war zone.
Yeah. Yeah. The suit up was the scariest part.
Right. Which is when I looked over you and I was like, oh, yeah, well, I also freak out.
And I haven't done a ton of VR things. I was analyzing why I think just because I didn't know what it was going to be in general.
Of course. But I think also maybe I'm freaked out by hearing my own breath.
Like in a scuba situation or when else would you? I haven't put on a hazmat suit for any reason.
I hope I don't have to. But anything I think it freaks me out in movies when you're like in the POV of somebody in a confined space and you can hear.
So it's something about that being able to hear my breath that here in Burbank, there is an indoor go kart course and you have to put on a real racing helmet and a guard because the cars can go up to like 35 or 40 miles per hour.
Now, driving it once I was actually doing it, I thought it was fine.
It was it was fine. And like I even hit the wall once or twice and like, you know, I thought that was fine.
But suiting up for it was that was very unnerving. So I get where you're coming from. I have a similar.
I did a very well paying funny or die commercial many, many years ago. That's just a joke. It was not.
I was at the end of motion. You're doing what is that? Your fist is kind of clenched and it's going up and down as you say that.
I was not making the jerk off motion, but my voice would suggest the jerk off motion. Is this what got them the Peabody?
Yeah. But it was a video. You can probably find it.
Jeremy Piven was involved, but I had to wear like a racing helmet and I had no idea.
This video, it's a I think it's a Hot Wheels video, branded Hot Wheels video.
A different time, a different time. Yeah, I think it's like an eight or nine years ago.
And I were all in a lot of if you're interested in the deep body of work of Jason, Mike and Scott, we're all in a lot of branded garbage.
That captain we talked about the captain Morgan. We have not.
Cannon blast. Oh, yeah. What a nightmare.
I mean, I don't think you'd enjoy even if you enjoyed the joy of this podcast.
But that at least like we were just telling you can see you get to see Mike in a in a nice sweater wailing away on guitar.
Yes. And I have like lines. This one I was no lines. I just had to wear a racing suit.
And as you were saying, I put the helmet on and went, oh, my God, I hate this. Oh, OK. I freaked out a little bit.
And then you get used to it. And I also had a similar thing when they put a fat suit on me at Conan when I did a bit that was cut last year.
I had a brief panic attack as this very, very like tight fitting suit went over my head and got stuck.
And I was like, yeah, yeah. Oh, my God, I'm having a panic attack.
And they pulled it down as like the hard as they could. They slipped it over.
And then I was like it was on me and like everything kind of was like, like and I went a little like like they didn't notice.
I don't think what was going on. And then I recovered. And then I was like, this is still got to come off of me.
And I do not like it because you had you speaking of alien and you had like a chest.
That's true. So like a man was going up between your legs and shoving a puppet out of your chest.
Yes, it was a whole thing. Yeah. And and they were like pulling stuff and ripping stuff and like creating like hole.
And I'm like, oh, this is like a PVC pipe is going very close to my penis.
Like, and I don't want this to be. But they figured it out. That wasn't that was fine. They were very safe with that. It was just initially.
So, yeah, that was where that was where the week was such chaos.
And then you had a full fat neck put on you. And then as soon as it was finished being applied and painted, the bit was cut.
And then they spent two really went to comic book. We went to the convention.
Yes, I spent three hours in makeup and they did the people, the makeup people kind of my goodness.
It was good. It was amazing looking like stubble.
And like they went hardcore to make this thing look like it's not like one color.
There's like a there's like a flow of the flesh tone. It was it was a work shaded, contoured.
They should have won an Emmy if this thing had had. I know that wasn't me worthy.
And then I got downstairs and it was right around lunchtime.
And one of the nice producers came up to me and was like, OK, this has been cut like immediately.
And I was like, OK. And it's like, but here's the thing.
You cannot take the makeup off yet because we need to get like official, official approval that it's been kind of go. OK.
So I sat there and I had my lunch in front of me. And it's very hard to eat with all that makeup on. Oh, yeah.
You're just a fake beard is pretty annoying. Right. Yeah.
So I said and this is what you learn when you've been a little bit in the business.
I'm not acting like I'm a grizzled veteran, but you always.
Here's my advice. Always ask twice. Ask a couple times. Hey, yeah.
Measure twice, cut once. Yes.
Yes, exactly. Jason, thank you for that. Better learn that if we're going to be working on those docs.
So I said I went up to the nice gentleman and I said, look, I would like to eat my sandwich.
Can you maybe just like ask someone and like officially you told me it's cut.
So Conan himself has to approve you biting into this sandwich and just say like you cut that sketch.
Make sure is it for sure. Cut. And he says, yes, it's for sure. Cut.
And then I can go take the makeup off. And he was like, OK.
And then he like checked and he's like, when the makeup comes back from lunch, you can take it off. OK.
Fifteen minutes. And I was like, thank you so much. I really just sit there.
Your mouth just just be waiting for that sandwich.
Yeah. But many times in that scenario, they would have let me sit all day.
That's just what happened. I mean, there's people are thinking about it.
So many pieces to make one episode of television.
So I'm not even blaming him. It's just the nature of the beast.
What's crazy is that you're you're down at Comic Con and people just at the convention are willingly wearing perhaps more difficult wardrobe.
People are in full Ed two oh nines stomping around the fat bastard cosplayers coming or they've spent they're in that thing all day and they're loving it.
People. There's people who don't don't exercise all year who then lose 12 pounds in sweat by wearing this costume.
I meant the Austin Powers character. I wasn't being insulting.
Yes. Yeah, you're not referring to anyone at Comic Con.
I realize that movie is almost 20 years old at this point.
Austin Powers too. But no less beloved and relevant.
I don't know about that. OK. The world just mourned the death of Verne Troyer.
People were saddened. That's true. But he was from the surreal life.
They probably knew him from. Mainly from which season was he on?
The one with China. Oh God, that made me sad.
Anyway, so we got suited up. Well, before we got suited up, we saw there was a little pre-show where, as I said, yes, Cassian Andor.
Cassian Andor. Diego Luna. Yes. From Rogue One.
I was impressed. I was like, whoa, it's him. Yeah, they got they had that.
Also, I love a little video that's only shown in the Galleria.
We got a movie star, Diego Luna. We were this is what we're in a shopping mall.
We walked into a pretty open room and there was just like a high def normal TV and it's a pre-show and we all went, oh, we all knew that coming.
But we're like, we all like micro targeted entertainment. This this Diego Luna piece of media only plays 100 feet from the JCPenney.
Yes. The screen came on and it said a long time ago in a galaxy far, far away.
So like you're getting the full Star Wars. Yes. A thing. And he tells you no no scroll, though. No scroll.
No scroll. That's I wanted to walk around inside a scroll. Oh, touch the letters as they move upward and away from you.
So you're you're you are rebels by your rebels. You're going to sneak in to a base on Mustafar, which is the lava planet, which is where, of course, Obi Wan Kenobi has his iconic fight with Anakin Skywalker.
Yes. In part in three. The Revenge of the Sith. OK, of course. And then it's also where Darth Vader builds his castle.
Vader's castle is on Mustafar. You see it a little bit in Rogue One when he makes that pun. Right.
To Ben Mendelsohn. You are sneaking in. Orson Krennic. Is that the character's name, Jason? Director Krennic, I believe in Rogue One.
Yeah, that guy was great. Ben Mendelsohn. Yeah, I like that guy. So you are sneaking. They stole the transport vehicle and you're sneaking in in disguise as stormtroopers. Yes.
And that's your mission. And then you go get suited up for the mission. And you're going to get you're going to get like a little little pill shaped item that I couldn't tell if it was like a if that was like a thing I could hold in my hand or a thing that I could fit into entirely.
Yeah. It was a big crate. It was a big crate. We couldn't quite tell the scale of it. I was really nervous about that. Actually, if you if you listen to the audio, you recorded audio, you'd probably hear me going, what is that? What is that? What's the size of it?
Like I was worried we couldn't get out of here. Right. Unless I recognized what the what the cargo thing was. Right. Right. Is it something you sell at the container store?
It's very similar to the poster tube, I feel like, where you would, you know, of course, sure, send a poster in the mail. So that is the the MacGuffin of the story. Yeah. You know, there's some sort of super well, I think they allude to like it's something powerful. Yeah.
Yeah, it's a little vague. But then he all spark. He has it is like a lot like the all spark. He also then has like a gunfight in the video. Oh, yeah. The angel just starts having a gunfight with someone or a blaster fight. Yeah.
Because it's one of those where like we don't have much time and yes. And there's there's rounds being fired and explosions going off and rumblings. But he took the time and it's so dark.
Theme park trope. I'm always on board. It always gets me. It always works. And it's great, too, because literally within 100 feet, there's a cheesecake factory. Yeah. It's so great. Like we're watching this video on a TV and I'm not being facetious.
It's just it's just there's an extra fun element to the fact that we're watching a pre show ride, as you said, near the JCPenney. And we didn't know what was like you don't know where you're being led once you're in the home.
It's like it walked us across the street over to the sprinkles cupcake ATM. That's true. Quick. Get quick. Get one quick. Get your money out. What do they credit? Sorry. Wow. It's so real.
Eat your your most of our rations. Yeah, it would have been that you it's an ATM dispensing that rising bread, that magic, which is the best part of Force Awakens. And I like Force Awakens.
I agree. That rising bread. So you're you're suited up and they get the helmet on you, but they don't put the visor down until they put you in what is literally a very tiny room. Yes. And I believe they said, may the force be with you and close the doors. And then it tells you put the got put the visor down now. Yes. And the room.
One of you said what? Well, I think our guests pointed out. Yeah, it was like we walked into the Christopher Nolan's production company logo. Yes. And he added buzz buzz. Yeah, very similar. Very similar style to it. And then at this point, when you put the visor down, we all become storm troopers. You're looking at each other and you look like storm troopers. And the room kind of has like, yeah, that weird inception II kind of. Yes. Yeah. To it.
But it's still not clear because like that's sort of almost like a loading screen, basically what's going on because it's going to change track screensaver. Yeah, exactly. And we should. And I do have to point out that you were looking you were looking around at your three companions. Yes. And they are all they are all storm troopers all doing live motions as they are actually doing. And you're trying to wait. Who's who? And then you turn. I turn all the way to left and oh, that one is Jason.
And the heights are equivalent. I apologize.
The heights are very accurate. Yeah. Yeah. So like you and our our guest mystery surprise guest, whoever it was about similar heights. Yeah. And then me and I'm towering over. And then yes, Jason. I mean, it is. It was fun to see a short storm trooper. That was my only shortcoming with it was that it's like I was worried the tall I was worried about running into the tall people.
Like the space between us made sense. But I was kind of like, oh, right. Some tall friends got some tall friends. This is actually if we if I'm if I'm remembering correctly, correct me if I'm wrong. Doesn't Princess Leia famously say to Luke Skywalker, aren't you a little short to be a storm trooper when he's rescuing her? Yeah. So in a lot of ways, I had a real experience. Yeah, I had a real Luke Skywalker experience. You knew what it was like. Yeah, because Princess Leia if I rescued her, she'd be like, you're the exact right height to be a storm trooper. I was also the first one of us to be a storm trooper.
I was also the first one of us to pick up a blaster and go, I think this were and then just shot a wall. You did comically like shoot your gun accidentally like your gun misfired like the way the misfit storm trooper would do. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You do kind of get to be like the you know, like like the jokesters, the guys who don't belong like the only thing that's weird about this world is you and we weren't we were pretty committed. We weren't like, yeah, you know, riffing or tearing the thing apart.
On board and that yeah, that room with all the lines. Eventually, it like starts to transform and you were on the ship. So it's so yeah, it's basically changes into like sort of just what looked like kind of metal walls and a door opens and then like very like too close to your personal space is K2SO and he's very tall.
And I think we all went, oh, like, yeah, we were like, yeah, I got to get this place credit because like they set up everything pretty clearly, but they didn't hold your hands about it. Like there was stuff where we had to discover by doing it.
And I thought that was really that was very nice for us as theme park fans that where you're constantly bit like there's a video that's kind of selling the illusion.
But then just like a disaffected teenager is like, okay, everybody step all the way into the theater. Like you're like the the illusions are broken constantly on Disney rides and the fact that you're watching like safety videos before you go fight the battle.
But here, yeah, no one is telling you anything. You were absolutely in the world and figure and there's massive decisions you have to make and sort of systems you got unravel that you've never been warned about.
And you got to react to live in the moment. Yeah, it's weird too because they don't even like tell you be careful. Don't knock into each other. Like there's none like just general stuff like that because I was thinking like, oh, we must be in close quarters.
So we're going to hit into each other and we did. You did a little bit. We kept planning who was going to leave the room in what order. I think that did feel necessary. I kept going.
Jason first. Sure. This one first. You are often times though by the door. I think I think I would just say that was right. You were trying to get out. You were trying to escape every room.
I mean, I just wanted to keep going. I mean, like, yeah, I think I was the first one when the doors opened up when the ship landed and then you got to go across a catwalk. Like I was walking through and I grabbed.
That was the first time where I was like, oh, this door frame. I can touch this door frame. Yeah, I didn't touch it. I should have tried was touching the robot that we said it was there. Yeah. Yeah. So a lot of stuff. So what happens? Yeah. So K2SO welcomes us basically into the main like cockpit of the ship.
And he tells us sit down and that's kind of the first crazy part too. Right. Yeah. Because we all four of us just sit down in different chairs. You look and there's a bench and they like the trust that the whole thing. Yeah. Like like what it buys to hear sit and then you do sit and it works.
You're like now you're now you're less afraid of every all my fear of the suiting up was kind of gone once the sit works because your brain is now just going well this is reality and I trust it. Yeah. Trust this reality. It's a trust fall. Right. So yeah.
Immediately sitting down does does really do something to you and you're looking up and it's a cool looking ship and the guy whoever the guy is a pilot up in the boiler alert. He gets killed later. That's him. Right. Or am I wrong? Was it a different? I forget. I think he gets killed because he gets impaled.
We'll get to that. But then there's a guy piloting the ship like up high and K2SO is tower. He's a very tall robot. Yeah. And he's like seven eight foot and he's in the corner and four of us are just sitting there listening to him and your brain is like oh I'm in the spaceship. Yeah.
And you're like like this is cool. Like this is a thing when I think about the memories of this when I think of my memories I want I mean we want more time and all of it but I was like man it would be cool if we could spend like 30 minutes in that ship. Yeah. Going around and seeing what what's in there.
Oh yeah. Details and talking to K2SO and seeing if he like would be our friend for a long time. Yeah. It's all the it's it's all the dream of my friend Tommy Boccia who like his complaint about the the Star Wars prequels is like I just want to like I don't want to know about this plot.
I just want to like stare out this window for an hour. I want to treat this like I have a layover in a Star Wars airport and I just want to like I just want to look for a while. I want to people watch this story who gives a shit. Get these carry get these characters out of the foreground.
And he just right. What's the shit flying by. He's gonna get that wish in 2019 when Star Wars Galaxy is edge open. Oh yeah. He'll just he'll just get to go. He'll be able to look at a skyscraper sit and be surrounded by people.
He's not gonna do it. He's not gonna get too much and sound like him. But so K2SO is giving us directions and I admit I don't remember exactly what he was saying because I think you're still trying to like your brain is still acclimating to it. That was just kind of the Star Wars like all right.
Everyone be cool. Right. Like sort of that like in something about weapons in there. He does mention I think what tells you to keep an eye out and find a weapon. Yes. Yeah. He says yeah we're going in on arms specifically because we can't go in arm because I have blah blah blah.
I don't know what he says. It's it'll look unusual. It'll look unusual. I think they don't they tell you on the way in like act imperial. Yeah. I think that's the line in there. That's fun. Yeah. Because it takes place like in the rogue one timeline. So it's not yet the first order and the resistance.
It's firmly in the rebellion the rebellion in the empire. No. Kylo is here. No not yet. Soon I'm assuming we will face to face with Kylo then which then comes the scene which may be my favorite scene in the whole thing.
We get on a little platform. We land close to Mustafa. We all four of us get on a tiny platform over lava and we float down to the surface of Mustafa to like this base. Yeah. And it's hot in there. Yeah. They're blowing heat like and we're all I believe we all want.
Whoa. Another like just four idiot like go blah. Wow. He like so impressed. I mean and then I'm being clear but it's truly it's awesome. It's like we're full like you really feel you're going down and it feels like you could fall. It feels like they're like nobody better make a false move.
We don't want to get shot at it. We don't want to fall in lava. Yeah. And what is happening to you there. I guess you're just standing still. You're on some little vibrating platform. Yeah. Nothing. But it's so like this this sweeping.
Vista you get. Yeah. It is a great trick and reading about the one co-founder of this company has like a background in magic and illusion and tricks and stuff. And I think it shows like the thing I think that takes this above like VR that I've seen other places is like a not just a commitment to immersion and story but also like the ideas behind it of like yeah incorporating multiple
discipline nary stuff into it. Sure. And stuff that like that it's that it still is a physical experience makes it so much more essential than I don't. None of us have VR and how we don't have an Oculus in our home. We're not just at like someone's house party or something like doing like you want to do a Jumanji one or do you want to do like. Which those are cool. I've done. Yeah. They're very cool. But yes this is an extra level. Yeah.
I also when I've done it I've done several little VR demonstrations where somebody is watching me and like moving wires out of my way and stuff. And what a it's it's it's almost like a one like a like an old one player video game where the person you're with just has to watch you play or maybe you trade on and off or whatever. But the fact that this is a social experience you drive to a place be in a place you're not only with friends or you're with your family or you're with your friends and you're playing with your friends. You're with your family.
You're with your friends but you're you have to work with that you have to all like figure out stuff together. It's I think I think it's what makes the whole thing so so much more essential than other VR stuff. Yes. It's yes.
I think it's it's specifically a social activity. Yes. I think it's what will elevate this void thing above other VR. Yeah. I mean they don't even predict it. I mean in the hit film ready player one there are basically everyone plays VR but they don't really address like exactly how you get to a level of immersion like this.
They have obviously like we all know of course we've seen it read the book but you know they have like vests and like treadmills to make it feel like you're walking. But like I'm not quite sure still how any of that at home stuff would work in real life.
Which of us have read the ready player one book. No I haven't. Oh OK. That seemed to be an ingest. I was doing that. I know a lot of people have read it. So what I was joking about. I'm just an asshole. We don't read. Yeah we are not.
Jason's the best reader I think of the three of us. He reads like old crime novels. I have read the canon. I have read some of the works discussed in that famous pillage for ready player one where he's like I've read Vonnegut and Heinlein and Crichton and whatever other bullshit.
Whereas I'm just I've seen back to the future. I know what a DeLorean is. Yeah. As far as I go. Oh is there back to the future stuff in ready player one.
There might be a little Easter eggs. That's how you do it. All right. Vancouver Omnimax though I'll tell you that. I don't care. But this is this is like the Oasis. Oh well this is we were saying before the Oasis. Yes before we went in this is a lot like the Oasis and I was concerned that one of us would have fallen love in there.
I was worried you know what could happen because we had vests on that did react. So like in the famous scene when you know they're having like a romantic time in that like club when they're flying and dancing like what if you know like a lady storm trooper like grab Jason and like put her hands around his side or something like you know you could feel that.
It did not happen. It did not. Maybe in future incarnations of this like you'll be. No a lot of unrequited love in this experience. Yes. What if what if Mike had to avoid the wiles of a very realistic Minnie Mouse. That's true. Yeah.
No it's not the same universe but a future VR experience. Watch out for those those gloved hands grabbing at you. I mean I think in The Force Awakens I think we're going to have to deal with if like if for instance it was the four of us and it's the Force Awakens timeline.
I think we're going to probably go into Maz Kanata's bar and I'll be honest with you. She's going to be horny because that's her whole character. She's like where's that Chewbacca at and she's obviously horny for very thirsty. She's very thirsty.
So I think that yeah that's probably going to be a future thing and we'll all feel like like when Maz comes up and she just kind of like feels our abs or something.
You're sitting over there pretending like this would be an issue. Oh like I'd hate that. I'd hate that. Oh boy getting flustered just talking about it.
It's only the second ever void experience. I think virtual love is probably in a few versions later. We're going to get those crotch haptics going in the next incarnation. That's the word right. Haptics. Haptics.
This word. I just learned this word inside my phone. I was probably turning on airplane mode and then like wait haptics. What the hell. And then haptics are things that that's the vibrations you feel. Is haptics a common word that I missed until this week.
I think I became alerted to it once forced touch and stuff was added to the iPhone. I mean certainly in the iPhone 7 where the button is not a real button that's haptic feedback like 7 and later. That's like what it's called.
Always good with the new slang. Give it up for haptic feedback. Or if you force touch to like get different options and it like pings you a little. I see.
Well I mean I don't want to jump around too much but since we're talking about haptics you do end up. Well we have to go backwards. We have to go to one thing which is that when you pick up your weapon.
This is a truly wonderful experience. The platform lowers you down. You get in the base and then you go like down a hallway. You're trying to blend in and then you do go into a room with like a blaster rack.
Yeah. And there's four blasters and four players. You pick them up. They are real. A truly insane experience. Yes. I remember hearing that that was something that happened and thinking oh cool and then but to be doing it to like that they've earned the trust or you pick up and then you can cock it and everything.
Did you. Did the cocking do anything. I didn't realize cocking was a thing until later. I started to. I couldn't really tell. I think it helped with the speed of rate of fire maybe. Did you cock it immediately because when you've misfired. No. And honestly I kind of pulled the trigger just to see what happened.
I kind of like wanted to see. I thought you did like a Gomer Pyle style like you shot the rifle into the floor accidentally. Well I think if even if we had just walked back into the back hallway with the weapons I think that same thing would happen. The alarm. Because the alarm starts going off.
Well I would be interested to go in. Now we're all as you as everyone knows out there good boys and we followed all the rules. We tried to do everything perfectly. But I would be interested like if we started shooting each other would we have felt it.
I think I did accidentally shoot one of you. Yeah because it's close quarters a couple of times we were trying to escape stuff. Did I feel it though. But did you shoot one of us accidentally while we were also being shot at by other stormtroopers. No it was like in a quiet room in a moment of peace. I might have. Yeah. I forget. There was a lot happening. Yeah. Yeah. We're not the biggest gamers and we're not the most graceful. So. Sure. No. So a lot of. So you pick up guns and then you end up in a in a big battle. In a firefight. Across. Yeah. Across a big lava.
River. I don't want to get words wrong. Something like that. You're shooting at stormtroopers and you see them fall when they get hit. Yeah. You are also getting you make them fall. It's so neat. And you hit them. I believe if you hit them in the head it's like they're immediately dead. So it's like golden eye 64. Sweet. Yeah. I think that's what happened. But yeah it's shooting and it's also like they told us not to crawl. I think that was an instruction. OK. But I did realize I could crouch. Yeah. We kind of like crouched and moved around and dodged shots.
Then I realized I realized this later I go this is what I thought Nick Arcade was that Nickelodeon. Yes. This is what I thought it was. It was a miserable experience for the kids doing Nick Arcade because they were just in front of a green screen watching another screen. Probably a very tiny little monitor. Yes. Yeah. Because it was impossible. No one ever won. And you'd be a kid at home going what. It's there. Just put your hand up. But the kids like so were so lost. It must show so confusing. And probably the cockier you were you were going to get in there.
Do it right. Yes. I'm like I never got to go to the Nickelodeon studios very famously but that was very cocky like I can do it. It's just that the coin was above their head and they didn't put their hand up. It's obviously because they were squinting at a tiny like low definition television. Yeah. They couldn't tell if that was like a bad guy or everyone is screaming screaming children screaming host probably producers pointing that way. So yeah. Well you get to be Mikey the iconic. Oh yeah.
Avatar of Nick Arcade Mike. Right. So now that's what this is what I want the void to do is start doing you know jungle round up for. Yeah. Yeah. Those generic games that were on Nick Arcade. Yeah. Counter. I'd like to those. I would absolutely love to be in any of the arc. Oh yeah. No. Believe me. That was a dream. Believe me. Believe me. I would. I would ace Nick Arcade. Perfect score. Believe me.
Very cocky of a Nick Arcade. But so what I was what I want to say about the haptics is that you can you shoot stormtroopers but they can also shoot you and the feeling that you feel when you get shot. It's certainly not painful. It's not like an awful vibration but it's not a nice feeling either. And it's unpleasant enough that you really want to make sure it doesn't happen to you. Right. And I like as opposed to if I'm playing a video game at home there's no real motivation for me to
shoot well and do this right. Those feelings were so bad that I was like I need to figure this out. I need to cover sides that you guys aren't covering. I need to feel like can crouch good that'll make sure I don't get hit as much. It is like it motivated me to do better because that right feeling
sucked. It sucked just enough to not hurt you. Which became more unpredictable when the lava monster showed up. Oh yes. Because they're throwing stormtroopers at you and once you're like all right we got them a monster comes out of the lava and you got to start opening fire on that. And it's big and it's getting close and then it is getting to the point where it's getting so close to you. Your brain is going a little uncomfortable with the size of this thing. Like it is starting to screw with your brain. You want to hold it back. You want to kill it before it's screaming in your face.
But you hit like its chest was like glowing a different color. Like it clearly had like an unarmored part. Like a ghost video game trope of like oh aim for that. Yeah we had hit it with so many shots. I do wonder if it's like it's just designed to get this close and then it dies. So if you were just like hitting it with three and then you let it get close and you shot it again. I wanted to know like how close could it get. Like that would be. And if we when I do you know round two three four five and six of the void.
I'll one time I won't shoot it at all and see if it eats me I guess. That is our like attraction instincts of like OK the fifth time I'm going to go on this I'm just going to look to the left. Yes. Like oh I'm just going to see if I can see Easter eggs. Yeah. In hindsight I should have when we were talking to the nice people the void I should have said look this is great but can we go on it all day. Can we just do it from 1030 to 1030 at night. Yeah we want to try everything in it. We want to see what we weird thing we can do. He's very
avoiding too hard. We got unplug him. We may have void seizureing. We may have hate everything. That was our reality now and coming into the real world just didn't make any sense for us anymore. Yeah. Yeah. Too much. Don't bring me back. You bastard. Plug me in. K2SO. Help me. Yeah. So we so yeah we were shooting at this this lava monster. There were the first like puzzle isn't really a puzzle.
It's just like pull the lever on the wall. And I think you did it Jason I believe I did it. Yeah. So yeah you just pull it. I think by that point I was like that's a physical you did it perfectly. And then it's not. And this isn't in perfect order. But then the next puzzle was basically Simon says. Yeah. So you got that was a cool part because that was where us and our guests we kind of like split up. You guys are trying to figure out the puzzle and then we realized there was like another corner of the room and more stupid. Yeah. Our troopers started coming. So then we just started
blasting while you guys were doing that. So you can like it's done in parties of four or like you know I think they try to send in groups of four. Yes. Is the ideal number for it. So that was cool to like oh we'll split up. We'll take it naturally. Yeah we had to make a little plan. Yes. And that's yeah again another figure as you were saying figure it out thing. It's like an all we were shouting instructions like we'll do this. Well you go do this. It made me pretty sure that as just as we would be excellent longshoremen we would all be great in the military. Yeah.
Yes. Yes. I mean because we certainly had a natural instinct for it. Absolutely. Yeah. I'll do. I'll solve the Simon puzzle. So to get into this Iranian fortress. That's what you go. That's a basic training is solving Simon puzzles over and over again because so many different you know jails unlock by solving six Simon puzzles. Right. But will they ever guess. Green red green purple. I did. So I did the Simon puzzle.
And were you doing with me Scott or was. Yeah I stayed in puzzle land. Yeah. You guys are brave. And I believe so what would happen is I would get kind of caught up because I was still getting shot at. And I'll be very honest with you. You and our guest was that we're not doing a great job holding up because I was getting hit while I was doing the Simon puzzle. Well so are we. No I know that but your job was to make sure I did not get hit because I'm the one. I didn't know that. So I was trying to provide cover fire but I guess I wasn't. I'm about to making an excuse.
So basically what's happening is the Simon puzzle. So I would do the puzzle but then I would forget because I get hit and I turn because I got hit and start shooting and I would miss a piece of the puzzle. So I failed a couple of the Simon puzzles and then I have to go back and watch them do it again.
I think Scott and I like to turns and I recall you Jason goofing on me during this and saying oh what's taking you guys so long which I guess that is part of the which I guess you know I can't be fault you too much because like that's something rock and raccoon.
Yeah. What's taking you so long Star Lord or whatever. Come on Star Lord. So I guess I was upset when I started this part of it but now I realize that that's part of the fun of it. You were just goofing on your comrades.
You understand why Han Solo is so cranky and quips so much. She's beleaguered. So doing this shit all day every day. So all I'm saying is maybe maybe you could have done a better job making sure I didn't get shot while I was trying to help us.
But that's why I think that's when I figured out that cocking the gun did something because I was like why is there. Why are they coming out so slow because you were like maybe I can shoot Mike in the head. Shut the fuck up.
You were taking out all the aggression from from us goofing on you on the podcast and you were like I'll just shoot this years and years of it. I'll show you who's the shortest stormtrooper.
I will be mayor someday and you won't be in the in the cabinet. I'm gonna be like boss. I will be boss. What a tremendous ending to that experience of like only you emerged from the void.
You had taken the three of us out and you were like I did it alone. Well what happened to your friends. Where are their bodies. The lava pit of Mustafar.
Yeah the forms you sign dictate that we keep the bodies and we don't tell you where they are which containers they're hidden in. Is the void a black mirror.
Man we got a good spec black mirror now. Yeah. So so we so eventually Scott and I solved the Simon puzzle opens up another door opens up a red yellow red yellow yellow and you get into the bay and you see the crates you see the crate that you're looking for.
Yes we so we see the crate. It's like was it floating. I thought it was on the other side of like a chasm or like a gap a gap. Yeah yeah. Chasm is like a natural.
Oh yes I guess we were inside still inside it was manmade or alien made. And then I think the pilot he goes to get goes to get it. Then he takes it out. He opens it up and he pulls out a sword.
Yes what looks like a very rudimentary lightsaber but it looks it looks like a long sword. It looks like a knight sword but it has a lightsaber blade in it. Right. And it's a real Knights of the Old Republic.
Right. It's an idea. Yeah that's sort of what I think. But it's not yeah it's not clear what exactly. I mean somebody's probably really mad at us because they know exactly what that sword is. Yeah.
But and then the sword gets yanked away and then I believe he starts getting tossed around and then he gets this maybe if you really don't want the final spoiler.
Maybe we should one more spoiler space. So if you're done with it so you don't want this last one. You wanted to know some of the spoilers but not the ultimate spoiler. Yes. Who would you think would be most likely to show up on Mustafar.
He has real estate there. It's not Orson Krennic. It's the guy who owns property there. At least a vacation home. I realize now Ben Mendelsohn Orson Krennic is also the bad guy in Ready Player One.
Oh how about that. That's fun. It's Darth Vader. He shows up. We see the lightsaber first. He turns on his lightsaber and then he comes down. And you hear his breath and as you know I don't like heavy breath. No. So we all open fire on him.
Yes we all shoot at Darth Vader. And it's doing nothing. We all suck so bad. And he's getting closer and closer and I think we're also going screaming because Darth Vader is about to come and get us. And then I felt that was a little quick that our interaction with him because then all of a sudden K2SO now piloting the ship.
Yes it was for sure the pilot because K2 is now driving. He flies the ship and crashes the thing in. He collides man's ass in. And kind of just knocks Vader away and a platform emerges and he says here walk up the platform and get back in the ship.
I was so relieved. Thank God this is over. And we got into the ship and it was exactly the same as the ship before. And K2 was driving and he said we did it. And I don't know if we said a prayer for our fallen comrade. I don't know what happened.
I think they said they're analyzing the data on the weapon. Right. So it's like a cliffhanger. It was a relic. They said a Jedi. Why are they collecting Jedi relics. Right. So like we don't there wasn't even a conclusion. I mean maybe maybe the next void is the second part of the story.
My guess is there is that it's serial. That it's serialized. That there's going to be a chapter two. What a great idea. I'll be back. That's really cool actually. Like a separate narrative going on that you only can do through the void.
That would absolutely that would sell me. And if it's not so serialized you wouldn't understand it. Like you could start with that one and it wouldn't. Right. Screw you up. It's still the basic thing. We've got to get in and out and we've got to find a thing.
But if yeah if you if they announced you can continue the story. Oh I think you know that out and appreciate like you know on your last mission you've got this. I would that was our friend Andrew Grissom's proposal of like a way to make this thing more you know enticing and essential to do is not only that but he was saying and I think he's right.
Like if you could keep a consistent character profile like if you could like because we had wristbands that they scan. And so if that contained if you brought that back in four months and they could refer to stuff that you did wrong or right.
It's talking like the Star Wars Star Wars land stuff where they're saying if you don't have a reputation. Yes. If you do bad on the Millennium Falcon ride they'll be like I heard what happened on the Falcon or whatever. Like same thing with this.
It would be great. Also our guest our friend said he thought there should be a scorekeeping element would be fun as well.
Oh really the most accuracy. Yeah yeah just to sort of see what that was like. I mean it doesn't I guess if we're being realistic it shouldn't have that because that's not how the real world works. But it's a fun element of like oh we got to play again.
We got to play again because we got to see you if we can get your like a higher. It'd be funny if they gave you a score at the very end if it wasn't in your in your field of view but then at the end like or I got 40 and Mike got the hundred thousand or it just got sent to you later.
Yeah I would be interested. I mean I like playing rounds of PUBG of Player Unknown's Battlegrounds like at the end of each bout of that like there is like accuracy kills survival time that sort of thing. And I know that's very popular in those big battle really out kind of games.
Yeah so all that stuff is fun but I get why it's not in there and it's not necessarily necessary. Well let's why don't we talk about about pluses up about ways to how does this become. I think we were all really impressed by this but how do they take this to the next level to where this is really a thing that you do.
Because I think it could be and Matt Mazzanio I mentioned earlier is really a fan of all this stuff and he said it's like you know if escape rooms can become as much of I think it could be analog to escape rooms and that you don't do it all the time but it's an event and you go spend money and get a bunch of friends together.
You know that's a great comparison I never really thought about it because it is priced like according to escape room like yeah. So it is tickets are 30 dollars like 29.95. I'm sure there's going to be specials at some point or like group rates I have to think I'm sure they're looking into that sort of thing.
I was very interested when we were coming out there was a mom and like a 10 year old boy there like at the front desk like talking so what is it and they're like explaining it and they're like oh OK that sounds and she's like you want to do it and he's like yeah and she's like OK we'll take two and he's like oh cool you're going to do it too.
So they were walk ins they walked in and they sold them on it and you know I think it was smart to put it in the Glendale Galleria because that shopping complex in the Americana next to it I think people are spending a little more money at those higher higher in mall.
It's a rare mall that's not dying and dying yeah so you get a 10 dollar piece of cheesecake and then you walk over and a 30 dollar yeah right. I had the trolley because they could. I mean one thing I would say is like all right in in you know once this is cooking like drop the price to like 20 dollars even.
Sure now I don't know that'll happen I don't that clearly it's not a case for escape rooms are doing play well they're all at the 25 30 dollar price rate right.
Yeah so I think that alien one is a little less I think that's closer to 20 but honestly they're getting walk ins and there were people right before us and there was people right after us so it seems like it's doing well.
I think they have the right idea attaching themselves to IP Star Wars being the the ultimate one but a Ghostbusters one a cool idea although it didn't seem to penetrate as much I hadn't heard about it before.
But it seems it does seem like the test for this stuff and for the void will be like could you do original stories this way would you get people in if it wasn't you're in the Star Wars universe and I think you could eventually.
Yeah, because you have to be a real staple of like entertainment. Yeah, like we're poor people whereas I think people still kind of go I want to go to a movie and they when they say movie they don't necessarily know what they mean like they don't necessarily know what movie it's just like well that's an activity we do.
So there'll be like five years from now. Do you want to go to the void. Do you want to enter the void tonight, the big what's playing at the void, and then it could be yes if it's something that or V whatever VR whatever people use VR slay well there that's one thing is that maybe
you need a better shorthand like movie or escape room, because how do you what's the quickest you could describe this hyper reality experience. Oh, you want to go hyper reality tonight.
Not really. I think the void I mean I think void is a good name. That is a catchy good logo. I like the void logo.
Yeah, I mean, a past guest Eva Anderson saw the guys behind it. Oh yeah, like an immersive theater conference and was very impressed.
So go see him talk if they're in your town. Yeah, so go see a lot they've got a lot of good coverage. Wired had an article about them.
Yeah, I just I want this to work. I want this to be a thing that's but it's all over the country because one thing I'll say I am not on board for and I know we've all watched some of these is this because a big trend in VR in parks is like, yeah, we've got this 15 year old
roller coaster and now we're going to strap an Oculus and a Samsung phone to your head and it's going to seem like Superman is rescuing you and some of these are kind of rough stuff. I mean, there will post it. There's a New York, the big Apple coaster.
I could not believe that. Yeah, I watched that on the way out the door. Thank you for sending me that. I mean, I said that like three times because I come across it every month and I'm like, just remember this. It's so rough. We Aaron and I like make fun of that coaster a lot in general because it's just kind of just sort of yeah, it's rust in a way.
It doesn't seem safe. Oh, I wrote it once. It's bad. Yeah, that was 11 years ago. But now you get in and it's stuck with you. You remember the headache you got or what it did to your back was walking around the strip with like, oh, my neck.
Right. Right. So that now you get on board a big, long New York taxi cab and you put on a phone on over your face and you see a story about a area of 50 one bizarre. So we have basically like to set up. There's that big. There's a big roller coaster outside the New York, New York.
Yeah. Hotel and Casino in Vegas. And yeah, as we were saying, it's like inside and outside. It's huge. It's huge. But it's like shitty and decaying. And this VR that will post a link to is really weird. Area 51. And you're a scientist in a Jeep.
And then a helicopter picks you up and you fly around the strip trying to get this alien back when you go up that weird like when they're sending you up, you know, one of those like 45 degree angle cliff walls that looks exactly like a roller coaster lift hill like a paved cliff in the Nevada desert.
And then, yeah, you get picked up by this bizarre cyborg helicopter machine and the alien jumps into like a little console that looks like a fucking vagina. That shape is so vaginal that he's in. Yeah. Yeah. There's no and nothing explains the plot phones because like you don't have much sound.
And they also don't. There's no name for this. It's like, do you want to pay five extra dollars to do the virtual reality thing? They didn't call it like escape from Area 51 at New York, New York. Wait, is that true? It costs extra to do it.
It's you get on the same coaster as everybody else. And there's other people not wearing the helmets. But if you want to pay an extra five to so there's there's sending out coaster cars were like two of them have a Samsung phone in their face.
That's a bad show to pull the industry turn. That's bad show. It's really strange and inconsistent. Marcus Lamont is would hate it. It's also weird because the whole thing when I was watching it, it's like the first part I go, OK, it's Area 51.
You're like aliens and stuff. But then most of it is just like you're flying around Vegas, which is what the coaster already is kind of doing. You fly past the coaster that you're on.
And I don't think you can see the coaster. You just fly past the New York, New York, but flying past, I think specifically MGM Resort owned casino. Like it's really.
Correct. Don't the family. You don't go to the down to the Venetian end. You certainly don't see these Trump Tower. Yeah, it's it's all. Yeah. Like, wait, where's he going? Oh, he's looping back around to the Excalibur again.
What a coincidence. The other one that I thought was pretty rough and was much more shocking was they have one of those at the drop of doom at Six Flags Magic Mountain.
Yes. Superman, Wonder Woman and Lex Luthor fighting and also no dialogue literal word balloons appear. You have to read. Yeah, very odd.
Traveling hundreds of feet in the air and reading. It's a very odd experience. Then you get dropped and Superman catches you. Of course, there's a different one for there's a Superman coaster at one of the other Six Flags parks with a different like Lex Luthor has a levitation gun.
Same gag from Star from Spider-Man the ride. The Amazing Adventures of Spider-Man, excuse me. And but it's just very odd. No one's talking. There's a little bit of sound effects. You can kind of hear the Superman.
It's probably all combining with the wind of Santa Clarita. They don't want to put headphones on you and the roller coaster sounds so overwhelming anyway. This is why the tech in the void looks great. I'm sure you could probably has room for improvement, but I think in five years it'll look super realistic.
Yeah, it's the graphics are really, really good. It's just but it is like a little dull and a little less bright than reality. But that's what a great good and good sound for sure instantly responds to everything. Yeah, all of the I mean, I'm sure there's sensors and stuff in the rooms.
But most of the computing work is in the backpack. Backpack has processors and graphics card. All of that in the backpack and connects to the visor. And there's I mean, there's a word some word came out that like the Millennium Falcon ride, which is going to be it's not like VR, but it is going to be like a giant video game that's supposed to look real to you.
And it is an eight processors going at once for each car, industrial grade, like pro process. Yeah, so for each not like consumer grade, each ride vehicle has eight different processors working hard to render every single part like so that basically kind of means or it seems to mean that like, like everything is like changeable.
It's not just there's a background and a couple things you could get shot at. Like it seems like you could really like crash through anything you're seeing. Yeah, because everything to look around because all the processes working are like making everything like every piece of the background like changeable or destroyable or or who knows what exactly does this.
This, Aaron is hates all of this. The idea that it's like interactive and you have tasks and stuff. And I'd like to give a voice to the person who is worried about having jobs. It would in the ride. I can't I understand that it stresses me out a little on mission space having like even though it's just essentially a button to hit.
Is that valid? Is it invalid? Is it like is it is she just wrong? Is it super cool to for it to be? It depends because I don't think there's G forces pressing on you in the Millennium Falcon.
Thank God your head won't burst open. I think the Millennium Falcon. I think that really there's got to be a pilot and there's got to be a couple people shooting. There's got to be a cannon. But there's six people. It looks like there's a six people in the cockpit.
So it seems I think this makes a lot of sense. There'll be a couple seats for people that just want to enjoy the show. OK. Oh, maybe you can also not really have a job. So I'm thinking the Falcon maybe has low impact jobs or no jobs at all in the back seats. Her other fear though is that you OK if a kid gets to pilot the Millennium Falcon. That's amazing. That's so cool for the kid. What if the kid messes up sucks. Yeah. Yes. Most kids are miles better than any of us going into blind.
All right. Yes. Let's change that. OK. So what if a man in his 40s or 50s is the pilot of the Millennium Falcon and he can't do it. I don't know any of our dads. That is the thing. I look believe it or not. I was having a conversation with someone two weeks ago about this very topic saying hey say say like Star Wars.
It's gonna be so hard to get into. You're gonna wait two hours to get on the Millennium Falcon ride. Say you get in that cockpit and the person flying it sucks. Yeah. And just like just nose dives the thing keeps crashing. How do you still serve. Yes. How do you still like kind of make that experience good for the person on it that waited two and a half hours. I think the play aspect of it will probably be closer to like less like a PS4 and more like iPhone game.
In terms of the mechanics of how you do this. You think you're on more of a track. I mean I think it. I think there are there will be decisions and stuff will be destroyable and you can fuck it up. But I think they're still going to hold your hand a little. It's probably this. You're probably right. It's probably like you're in the hangar. You're trying to get out of the hangar. If you cannot get out of the hangar it just like kind of takes you out of the hangar and takes you to light speed. Yeah. R2 does it. R2 does. Right. Which I suspect is what happened to us with Darth Vader.
I think we didn't do something. I think maybe it was like all right close enough. You guys are you get maybe that's it felt so abrupt to me. So maybe we got a little what that experience was like you get you have some wiggle room but if you're screwing up we'll keep it moving on our guns stopped working at a certain point.
Oh he like he like yeah yeah he broke our guns. I think that's probably what happens but we don't know. Yeah. So well so obvious all this is building to some like parks. There's got to be a big parks implementation of this.
I think that there's some I think there's something interesting about the idea of what like Six Flags is doing with a cheap Samsung like thing. Yeah. Like there's some cool idea of it.
It's it's probably honestly I've not tried one of these yet so I don't know if maybe it's kind of cool but the graphics are janky. I haven't either an interesting one I heard about was Busch Gardens Williamsburg has a new attraction called Battle for Eerie.
Eerie. And everyone puts on like a helmet but you until you're seated you don't put on the VR part. So it's like it's it's kind of like it looks closer to when there was Quidditch goggle 3D goggle. So it's like a helmet with no lenses in it.
And then I think either the employees come around and snap it in or they hand it to you when you snap it in. So seems to be getting closer to something. I mean I think that's why the parks haven't gone like full hog in terms of Disney and Universal is just trying to figure out like oh how do we get the headsets on.
How do we because there's been that slows down. That's a hard it's a lot of load in. So it does make sense for it to be wavers and lot you don't you buy. Yeah. It's going to make the screens bigger and they don't have to put anything on like well there was a rumor for a long time that Tony Baxter was working on like a sugar rush ride.
Yeah for Florida record record Ralph you're saying the racing game where they were to strip out all the stuff from Alien encounter and put in like carts and everyone would race. Everyone in the room would be racing each other.
But I know more hot dog fart cannon that would get stripped out. Hopefully. Well it's a it's like a candy right. So you could like crash land into a hot dog thing and someone would fart at you. I hope so.
There would have to be some farting element. Yeah. So that that application of VR in the park makes a lot of sense because you're in a station probably a mostly stationary vehicle. There's a whole load in load out process. You have the headset on but it's not like you're on a roller coaster with it.
Yeah. It's like that. Yeah. That makes a lot of sense to me to do it that way to use VR. But yeah I don't know if there's it's like as far as like real estate it does make a lot more sense to me to have it in downtown Disney or in Disney Springs as a separate out as sort of a separate thing.
I think so too. But I can one thing is that this stuff upgrades a lot quicker than theme park rides theme park rides could be there for 10 20 years and they have to be constantly upgrading to match people's expectations.
Right. There's some screen rides that already look old and they're like two years old and they already look. Yeah. Oh yeah. There's probably a good application for something like even like that Tomb Raider ride. We were talking about a Kings Island or something something that's you're still you're getting moved.
It's like it would be almost like that astronaut training or something. Yeah. You're in that big sphere like you could move people around but it's not like you have to move them from point A to point B. They kind of get to stay in a place in that way. I feel like you that's I don't know maybe it's a simpler process.
I don't know. I guess question is what do you want to see done with this technology. Well this is my honestly this is I was thinking like what rides now would be better if they were sort of this type of ride and not what they did. And my first thought I swear to God just now was Jimmy Fallon's escape from New York escape through New York whatever the hell it's called.
Let's not do the same sort of like like 3D movie ride. Let's get you on the show in a weird way like 3D you're walking you walk through the curtain you're on Fallon some fun stuff happens in the audience celebrity cameo you have to actually play a game with you have to play.
That's great. I didn't even think you got a drink perfect Jimmy under the table and like it'll be like a celebrity. Celebrity you have to talk about your new project. It's you and Josh Brolin versus not set up properly. Confusing setup and like you're looking you're staring right at him and it's him.
It's photo realistic Jimmy Fallon and there's Higgins over there and you can go up and you can touch Higgins and you can touch like you can do. Higgins is really there. He's in the attraction. The real man. The roots there they're there and you can like play a pick a song like that's.
That's a whistle of sprains his wrist and you have to take over at the drum is fantastic. Now we're thinking here like this is what I'm doing. I think a much and I'm being funny and sincere at the same time. I do think this is a better attraction. It's kind of a fun idea to actually be on the show as opposed to like most people aren't like well I'd love the Jimmy Jimmy Fallon experience which is like racing on his supercharged desk to the moon. Like that's not as much.
But I think it's just what Jimmy Fallon's life is like right. I think the tourists come in they would they would love stuff like that and the celebrity cameos and getting to sit there and really feeling like you were on the show and getting applause. People love getting applause.
Go into the makeup department and make a young actor wear a very constricting neck suit. I'm applying copious prosthetics and then you can go hungry guy.
And then you can go up and you can tour the SNL offices 30 rock. You know you could. It's a whole 30 rock virtual 30 rock virtual 30 rock. Hey it's Tuesday at two o'clock in the morning. You got to help these guys crack David S pumpkins three. Yeah.
Oh my God. Were we. Oh no we're in Matt Lauer's office. He's locked the door. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out of Matt Lauer's office. He has a button under his desk. We've got to get out of here. Fire at the handles. Override the code. Red yellow green.
There's Charlie Rose taking a general to make that horrible TV show he was trying to make. Push him out the open window. He's a CBS man. What does he do? He shouldn't even have a general here. He's not an NBC guy.
What's that sound. Oh no. Broca. Broca's here. He won't leave. They want him not to anchor the news anymore. Brian Williams is lying. He's telling another lie. He's making me listen to a playlist of his favorite tunes.
Rachel Mann. Chris Hayes and Lauren. So Donald is spreading more fake news lies. Throw them out the window. Make them shatter on the ice. Read. Oh she's got a bunch of paper. Everyone don't don't talk about it.
Kathy Lee needs her box lot wine refilled. Oh my god. I would kill to be on hour three. I tell you every goddamn mom and dad who loved that fourth hour of the Today Show, if they had virtual Kathy Lee and Hoda and they got to grab a wine and drink it, they would tell that story for the rest of their lives.
And I'm not joking. They get that. I want to do that. I want to do it too. But that's a slow loader because you're spending a whole hour there. Ain't nobody leaving before the hour is up. There can be like literally make it 64 different tiny rooms and you put everyone in and you can load a ton of people that way.
And they'll live respond to photos of your children that you show them. This is a legit good idea we should maybe cut from the show because it's so good. We got to put it behind a paywall at least. And the grand finale you get to sing a song. You get to sing an old standard with Kathy Lee. Are you kidding me?
You get an avatar too. So you get to pick your movie star avatar as well. So before on the screens like a test track, you get to pick the big wheels and stuff. But you would get to pick who do you look like or whatever. So then you get to buy the video or get sent the video of you in VR with Kathy Lee and Hoda as your avatar.
Okay. So I could pick like I'm Joe Biden and I'm promoting my new book about what I learned from my children. Yes. Yes. How my children inspired me. And trains. And taking the train. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I get to monologue about trains to Hoda.
And there's one where you and Roker like do the weather. Oh, here's what it's like in your neck of the woods. Here's what it's like in your neck of the woods. You get to pick what neck is being looked at. Oh my god. I know. And it's like where you're from. You pull again on the console before. This is such a good idea. All I had down was void experiences for like Frozen and Avengers could be fun. But we're thinking big now.
Yeah, no, we're entering the NBC Universal and much like I made a plea earlier to anyone in PR at these theme parks. Let me make a plea to anyone who works in Imagineering or any whatever the equivalent of it or to who runs NBC Universal now NBC something. You know what, Disney. I want to hang with Stephanopoulos. Good morning America. You kidding me.
Fine. Yeah, that's great too. I'm just saying any is the plea from us is that we need to work for you. So hire us. You great ideas. We're just tossing out for free every week. I had not had this plan. This is just a great idea. We came up with.
Hire us and also give us free things and we will create the experience where you go into Seth Meyers is green room and drink the sparkling waters that the Meyers guests get. Of course. And they get the gift bag. Yeah, you can take the gift bag home. It's a real item. Yep. Wow.
Wow. These Vermont cookies are real. I don't know what they give you. They got his Vermont cookies probably something like that artisanal cookies. Okay, well full 30 rock. Do you get to do the other floors of 30 at the not entertainment industry one at the gym.
Yes, the commissary is even though this isn't time accurate is Max Weinberg still in the gym. I know where I'm spending my hour and 30. You get to go ice skating on the 30 rock pond. Oh fun. I think it's a full. Yeah, I think they would have a
lot of fun. I think you could get the whole experience of winning in line for Saturday Night Live being denied standby tickets standby tickets being passed by as the cast walks in and out yelling for Darrell Hammond to say hello and being being shut down or
being put in a cab. How about a meeting that Lauren has with you that's bizarre where there's the popcorn on the table and he's just like kind of telling you about you know when Chevy and Danny were doing the show and you're just like what's the point of this.
And then he's like well you know we're thinking about would you live in New York, and you're like am I being offered the job of my nuts and he's like well you know we'll be in touch and then like that's it you have to leave and you're confused go
downstairs and like stress eat a red Reddington candy bar like a blacklist snack. And again because it's not time specific Marin is down there and he's like oh he's had a meeting with Lauren I don't know I don't think I'm getting an update. I ain't getting an update job or whatever.
We can do this for another hour. Yeah, yeah, boy, if we don't stop ourselves now. We'll do a whole extra hour just like Kathy Lee and Hoda, but I guess for now, we have to say you survived podcast the ride. Yeah, Star Wars secrets of the Empire edition, follow us on Twitter, rate and review us.
We need the review so really just like come on do it because that'll get us in the charts and then people see us. Yes, the iTunes charts are very confusing and secretive. You know what are we way over can I do something really fast I were over but this is the this is a rare we just got a review and I want to encourage you to read to give iTunes reviews.
Because this one made me so happy I actually want to read it on the show really fast. This is from minus s 11 the grand adventure of a podcast five stars. Thank you for a group of guys who do not like turkey legs pizza port dole whip parades shows fireworks fast rides drops launches or roller coasters.
They sure have put together one hell of a funny amusement park podcast. I love that review and it boy it made me aware we are cranks we don't like the record I like all of those things but parade. Yeah, so, and I like parades.
I think I between all of us one of us likes most of those things. Yeah. So, but you're right that the group think minus seven 11 s 11.
Yeah, we got a lot of good but I don't know hey there's a lot we love we talked about everything charming I love the review as we had a recent review where someone said I really had a lovely time walking through the woods listening to these guys talk about a parking garage or two
transported you out of nature into a parking garage so it means a lot.
So we really appreciate it and obviously and get us free stuff, free stuff jobs in the imaginary, and also, even though I said I was canceling my Facebook I didn't, and I started the Facebook page for the podcast so go to podcast right at Facebook,
it's a Facebook group you can post you weren't you weren't thing terribly middle, you didn't look us in the eye when you said you were going to shut it down. Yeah, no. Yeah, whatever. I was in the heat of the moment and sometimes you say stupid stuff.
We're going to be ready to forgive Zuck soon so you're fine and they will be trying to reopen our account we're all too busy being mad at line James Comey right.
The truth, the liar, a leaker loser. All right, thanks for listening everybody. Thank you. Bye.