Tonight, a once-in-a-lifetime podcast party that spills out into the streets.
Every minute of this episode is a New Year's Eve celebration featuring heel kickin' country,
cool jazz, madcap explorers, and the funmeister of podcasting himself, Mr. Paul Scheer.
It's Pleasure Island on Podcast the Ride in three, two, fun!
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men who despite not
having children still possess strong opinions on the best diaper changing station in Disneyland.
Joining me is all, I'm Mike Carlson first of all, joining me as always Scott Gardner.
Hello, too crowded in Adventureland, you gotta go deeper into the park.
It's Tomorrowland I think, because it's that bathroom in the very back by the Autopia.
Well Adventureland bothers me, you're saying Tomorrowland is the good one or the bad one?
I'm saying that's the good one, yeah yeah.
Oh okay sure.
So, also Jason Sheridan is here.
Yeah I'd have to agree with the Tomorrowland one, that bathroom's nice, kinda out of the
way, it's the opposite of the New Orleans square one, which is like a dead end and there's
a lot of traffic back up and constantly construction there for some reason.
I'm glad we're in concert with this.
Let's bring our guest in for his opinion on the best diaper changing station at Disneyland
from the upcoming podcast Unspooled.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's Paul Scheer!
As someone who has children, I will say that I have an issue with the changing tables in
all of Disneyland and I think they are too small.
I have two children and they do not fit on those changing tables.
I have to cram them in there, it's like a very small trunk that I'm trying to pack for
a very long vacation, putting my child in there, legs are going up, I have no room for
my gear, my wipes, everything.
It's a real mess.
It looks great, not functional.
Wow, and it's a length issue.
My kids are not abnormally long, I don't have very tall children.
I have average sized children.
And also, it's made of concrete.
It's made of a very hard substance.
It's not like when you go to like, or at least the ones I've been to, because I feel like
I'm looking at your face and you don't look, when I go to normal bathrooms, it's like a
pull down thing, it's a little bit of plastic, it's not hard concrete.
I feel like I'm changing.
Is it like marble surfaces?
Yes, it looks very nice.
I don't want to change my child on marble.
It's not good for someone who is not cool with me changing their diaper and their heads are
whipping around on marble.
It is, anytime I have to change my kids, not only one of them, it gives me way too much
anxiety in there.
Yeah, if there's like a jerk of the head and they slam backwards.
Yeah, it's too much.
That's the way I broke my arm.
The only serious injury I've had was slipping on a marble floor and falling backwards and
broke my, in New York City, and then I had to like do all the New York tours with a broken
arm.
The first I was ever in Studio 8H or the former Conan Studio, I was like, yeah, I was a little
dork and a sling.
So you had your arm treated in New York?
Yeah, or actually, wait, no, nothing had happened in New York and then we went to Boston, the
best children's hospital in the country, apparently, so I lucked out.
But yeah, but marble and child dialing, it does everything, moves every which way.
I'm demonstrating now.
But yeah, keep kids away from marble and when wetness.
Like Walt Disney probably, like he changed his children on marble.
Like there's a generation that changed children on a marble surface and they lament the loss
of this as a character building moment in most kids' life, I think.
But now, like playgrounds and parks, everything's like shredded rubber, right?
Everything's like really cushioned.
Yeah, I mean, you think I am a ball of anxiety with my kids at these parks.
Everything is there to hurt them in some way or at a certain point.
Then they get to an age where then they're not hurt.
But at this age, I'm at I'm a four and one and a half year old.
Like there's too many.
Yeah, even though it's hard rubber, they can still fall.
They can still get it.
I'm here to say as a man with a child who's been to Disney World now, there's issues.
There are issues.
But you bring them over to that Pluto's house and it's great.
Great time.
Well, that's good.
What ages are the two?
What age?
Four and one and a half.
So I spent, I spent spending a lot more time recently.
I don't bring the one and a half year old.
Yeah, yeah.
What's a waste?
That stuff.
Yeah.
I but I spent a lot of time in Toontown.
Toontown, USA.
Yeah.
As a theme park fan, do you ever feel obviously you're happy to be spending time with your
kids, but do you feel like frustrated that you're stuck in the kiddie area?
Well, not exploring the I have a very cool kid who happens to be 40 inches tall, which
means as a four year old, he's much taller than normal four year olds.
Maybe he's larger than normal.
But he can ride roller coasters.
So he loves big Thunder Mountain railroad.
He goes on the go go.
He calls it go go gadget coaster.
I think this is called the gadget coaster.
But and he goes on a bunch of things.
He's allowed to go on Space Mountain, but I feel like that will freak him out.
And I tell him he is not allowed to go on that.
That the Matterhorn are off limits.
And every day he wakes up and asks me, am I tall enough now for the Matterhorn?
So we have like a thing in our house where he stands up against it and we see the 42
inches and we are tracking until he can ride the matter.
Almost there.
It's current.
It's 42 inch watch right now.
We are.
I mean, we've been on 42 inch watch now for a while.
So I feel like when it happens, it will happen.
But it's it's been a slow go.
Soon your child will have the coming age of coming of age experience of getting injured
on the matter of just getting thrown around.
Spine is young, really getting upset by that.
Yeah, he's he's already having issues with the big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
There's you know, which is a great ride.
But you know, scary.
Yeah, scary.
Scary.
I was as a little I was very short now is very short as a child.
And I would get like tossed around on those rides like my dad was like, thankfully, just
there.
And for whatever reason, it was both my parents were always like, all right, make sure he
sits on the inside of the thing.
Right.
So that way you can just slam into your parents.
Yeah.
We kind of sandwich him in the middle of big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
It's good.
Yeah.
It's a bit you're in that.
But that's uncomfortable as an adult.
Oh, yeah.
Like three across in there.
It's not a not a fun ride.
Yeah.
But I will say going with my kid has been an amazing experience because I've got a I'm
a Disney World Disneyland all theme parks person.
But it's kind of great to watch a kid experience all of this and and see them just do it and
get excited by it.
And you know, I don't bring them to the parade.
I don't even know that exists.
I'm like, I don't need to get into that.
I like smart.
Yeah.
I'm like, no parades.
And almost to the day that way.
And it's a small world has become a great like refuge because it's kind of tiring to
bring a kid and it's all air conditioned.
It's a nice ride.
It's about it feels like 20 minutes.
Yeah.
And you get like a friend as a parent, you get a nice recharge on there.
So I'm I'm appreciating different parts of the park.
I've probably done Roger Rabbit more than I ever have done or probably want to do.
But yeah, but yeah, I've definitely I've explored a different side.
But that being said, in the last three weeks, I think I've been there three times.
No.
Wow.
Yeah, I went there once to go to Club 33.
Right.
So you posted about this.
Yes.
This is no private.
I got a for a birthday gift.
Someone got me an invitation to go to Club 33, which was amazingly fun.
Yeah.
You all been there?
I've never we've Jason.
I have never been.
Scott, I mean, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was it was a great experience.
I thought it was a pretty lovely thing.
Did you stand out on the deck?
I did.
I got to see the end of Fantasmic.
And I forget if I've told this story on the podcast before, but I at the time was like
I went to propose to my now wife and I had I had the wedding ring in my pocket and I
was like, huh, like in case a moment struck us and we were out there.
Well, that would have been great.
Finishing would have been great.
And our my rationale in my head was like then our friends who were nice enough to let us
in there like that then takes over the dinner conversation.
It's entirely about we just got engaged and not about how cool you let us into Club 33.
I understand that.
Yeah.
I was just connecting.
But yeah, I could have.
I will say as someone who is also married that it is nice to do that moment privately.
Like you don't want to like immediately.
And we just did it.
Like you want to kind of just be able to connect, which by the way, you know, yeah, I think
that that's yeah, I think that's a good good move.
I think so.
Yeah.
Even when I ended up doing it, we were on like the bluffs in San Diego, like along the
beach and the I was still I was extremely stressed out by how many people were there.
Yes.
I mean, the sunset, a reasonable thing for people in the world to do.
And I was so stressed out.
And she's like, why do you care that there's people around like you kind of clicked with
her right before?
Like, are you suddenly having this people phobia?
So yeah, I felt the privacy pressure big time.
No chance, though, you were going to run into a Captain Jack Sparrow face character.
And then he'd steal the ring.
Yeah.
He loves those jewels.
You know, and sometimes it's Johnny Depp just stealing people's jewelry.
Yeah.
The I proposed to my wife on a beach as well.
And we did it at night.
And there's like all these cool fire pits.
And we did it.
And there's a whole story to this.
But the only thing the end part was like we finally kissed and and this kid yells, get
a room.
The literal nightmare, the movie scene.
1980s.
Wow.
Get a room.
We are.
We will.
This is very special for us.
What do you guys think about a Disney wedding?
I mean, there's been a lot of talk about a lot of things in this podcast.
But where do we fall on that?
It's well, there's first of all, I'm a big pro wrestling fan.
OK.
And some pro wrestlers got married at Disney a couple like a year ago.
And they did.
I think they didn't do the big crazy version of it, because I think there's tears to it.
They don't have it on the website.
But like they did like there's like a little chapel out to the Disneyland Hotel, hurling
that chapel, but like a little spot where they do.
And Floridian has like a whole big thing on.
Oh, there's a wedding villa there, which is really funny to walk around.
I think there are tasteful ways to do it.
And then like there's obnoxious, like Saudi prince style version where like you're like
you're walked down the aisle by Gaston or something or a less evil character, I guess.
There's a beautiful courtyard like in the Grand Californian out here.
And it's sort of like self contained.
Like you can't see downtown Disney from it.
You can't see a Starbucks or like sprinkles, cupcakes and all.
But like there are rooms above it.
Like I was my family was visiting a couple of years ago and they were staying in a room
and I walked out on the balcony and I looked down like three stories down.
There was a full wedding reception going on.
But it is like very private and intimate and like beautiful foliage.
Well, if I'm getting married there, I want to get married.
I want to have my whole reception to be my guest.
It would be a very expensive.
Who went to that?
Be my guest.
Be your guest.
I've been twice.
Yeah, because you mentioned you're the one who.
Yeah, OK.
I'm only knowing your voices and now I'm always trying to.
So you did.
You went there to get the 830 reservation, right?
Yes, it was a whole.
Yeah.
Was it worth it?
You didn't really talk about the experience.
I had so much to do.
Well, yeah, I convinced my friends to bail on the rent a car that we had paid for already.
I was like, they'll reimburse you.
I figured out.
Yeah, it's it's great.
It's it's got the three different like you have the ballroom where they dance and you
have the beast swing, which has the flower, the rose that like is wilting.
It's just sitting there, though.
It's just sitting there.
But it does fall like they have an effect that makes it look like it's falling or whatever
throughout your day.
It was a worth it to ditch the rental.
Yeah, of course.
Well, I mean, but was it worth it in general?
I feel like it's a coveted place to have dinner.
It's hard to get a reservation.
Yeah, very like stock it, which I did for like weeks.
Yeah.
If you unless you book like a year out.
And but I mean, so but you felt like it was a it was it was worth the hype.
It just feels like it's like you're eating in a place that looks like the Beast's Castle.
If you're a weirdo like we are.
Yeah, it's worth the hype.
But if you're a normal human being, you're like, OK, yeah, it looks like the movie.
Got it like, well, I mean, it is good.
Yes.
And the atmosphere is good.
But I guess my question and I'm not trying to be difficult about it, but does it fall
like above Bayou?
Does it go below it?
Where does it where does it fall in the in the atmospheric Disney experience?
I think the food is a little better than Bayou.
We're talking blue Bayou.
Yeah, we just call Bayou.
Yeah, yeah.
The blue, yeah, the atmosphere, I think, is on par with it.
The blue like it's it's it's cool.
It's really cool.
If you like doing the beast a lot like they do, like the snow is falling behind you.
I'm down with that.
And like again, the beast swing is like the coolest play.
They walking around.
Yes.
They well, he's you can take pictures with him, which doesn't quite make sense because
like he should be upset.
You're in his house.
Yeah.
Maybe he wants company.
But yeah, he's he's lonely.
He's a lonely man.
Yeah.
So you see that they walk around when he walks through, there's a big like, I'm now introducing
the beast and he goes through.
So that's fun.
Like introducing the couple that just got married.
Yeah.
First time.
So it's great.
I mean, it's great.
It's if you like this type of nonsense, it's on the high end of this type of nonsense.
If you're listening to this podcast, you're probably yeah, you're on.
You're on.
You're in.
What's the best?
What's the best restaurant in a park?
If we leave out hotels or a sort of subsequent.
Yes.
No Napa Roses here.
I guess you'd have to count that out.
Oh, I have one.
I think it's Lacelle A in Canada and Epcot.
Oh, I think it's a steakhouse.
Oh, yes.
It's a steakhouse.
It's like looks like it's supposed to be in a cellar.
I guess back in the day, it used to be a buffeteer.
Like a full cafeteria, like buffet sort of thing.
And then at some point, they made it into a steakhouse.
And it's great.
That is a very hard reservation to get because it is so small.
And I think Epcot across the board has like really solid food choices like the Italian
Pavillion has a good food.
That's a great like go to dinner place.
Did not love the French restaurant there though that my mom.
I had an okay right time there.
It was fine.
There's a couple there and I feel like they've turned over a lot.
Like they've redone them a few times now, but it's but they're never like at the top
of anyone's list.
Yeah, Italian.
There hasn't been one consistent Italian restaurant as there is.
Alfredo's was there for years.
Alfredo of Fettuccine, Alfredo had been there for years.
The man who invented it, which was amazing.
But then I think I always heard that they didn't want to accept the Disney dining plan
or they didn't want to lower their prices or stuff.
So eventually, like when the licensing agreement ended, they were not except what do you mean
they're bartering within the overall Disney?
They was very fancy.
I mean, it was a really intense place.
Like they're very serious about their pasta.
Yeah.
Snudy restaurant.
I haven't.
Tiffin's is supposed to be really good.
I've never had that at the Animal Kingdom.
That's their high end.
I've eaten there.
Is that good?
It is very good.
Yeah.
Do you have an answer to this?
I'm thinking of my answer.
Like I'm my go to it, but continue.
I'm sorry.
I think the best I'll say this, I'll be very bold to the best fast service restaurant is
the Sala Cantina in my.
Oh, oh, I was I know the Cantina in in Frontierland that's all Cantina.
I thought that's the same of it.
Maybe it's let me look the name up.
No, is that Bill Pekos Bills?
No, it's a Mexican place.
Disney World or Disneyland.
Okay.
Disneyland.
Yeah, the Zocalo Zocalo.
Sorry.
That's not a Navi word, all is a Navi word.
Which language you were speaking.
I'm sorry.
I mispronounced it.
Such huli canteen.
Okay.
Sorry.
Fans were screaming.
They're very upset.
All of us right now.
In their cars.
My Pandora experience was really a bust.
Oh, no.
So I went to go.
My mom has a timeshare at Disneyland.
My mom got into the timeshare game at Disneyland.
It doesn't world.
Oh, sorry.
That's a guy in the Disney world early on.
Early on, but just late enough that originally when you bought a timeshare there, they would
give you a lifetime free pass.
That was the first wave of it.
Oh, wow.
So my mom got into the second wave.
How long you've been doing that?
Over 25 years, I think she's had it.
So she's on the second wave of it.
So she has, whenever I tell people, I don't know her points.
She talks about her points all the time.
But whenever I mention the amount of points, she has to be like, whoa.
That's a comically large amount of points.
And she has them for life.
But now the new points, you only have them for 99 years.
So you can't pass them on to your family.
That's basically like you can, but it will eventually.
But they got to use it.
Yeah.
My family was in it for a little while.
Like five or six years were in it.
So as a kid, I was like, so how are the points looking this year?
Are we doing what?
Because one year we went for two weeks.
We spent two weeks in Disney World, which was wild.
That's amazing.
I think that Trump should repeal that.
I think that it's like a death tax.
I think that he should allow the kids to get the full amount of points.
That would only be good for.
Kids need to get those points.
Yeah.
I was going to say that my favorite dining experience is, and I apologize to your listeners.
I am a ardent Disney fan.
I forget names a lot of the times is the either.
I think it's a carnation cafe in Disneyland.
It's like the old timey cafe Main Street, Main Street, where it's like where they do
the character breakfast in the morning.
I feel like that is a quintessential Disneyland experience in both parks.
I think they like because it looks like old timey diner, like red and white kind of thing.
And like poos there and they have good French toast.
There's something about that one that's a higher quality.
Good cheeseburger there.
Like a good like whatever a good version of a Johnny Rockets cheeseburger you can get
at the Carnation Cafe.
If you're facing the castle, is that the one on the left or the right?
Disneyland if you're faced on the left.
OK.
Yeah, that's the one.
I've never been there.
But it's in the middle of the street.
Carnation's in the middle of the street.
Oh, is that the one that does the breakfast buffet is one.
I see.
Yeah, I see.
I'm always wrong.
What is that?
It's called the Plaza in Disneyland and in Disney World, it's called the Crystal Palace.
The one I'm thinking of that was great.
OK.
And Carnation Cafe had a good breakfast here last week.
I had a good pancake.
I had a pancake with although they served it was the pancake and granola.
And I was like, oh, that'd be good.
Like a granola pancake.
It was just granola sprinkled on a pancake, which was an odd.
That's your choice.
That's odd.
Yeah.
And I felt uncomfortable eating it.
Mike and I went down recent because they have all the Pixar Fest stuff.
And we went to the Pizza Planet restaurant and we're like, there's there.
Oh, look, it's let's try the cheeseburger pizza, which I've like had before.
I've had this con.
I've had the idea of cheeseburger pizza before.
And this usually is just ground a layer of ground beef under the cheese or on top of
the cheese.
This was like they like quartered hamburger patties and had chunks of it like it was fine.
It was nothing.
It was fine.
But we posted it on the Twitter account.
It's Scott replied immediately spit back.
That's fucking disgusting.
Yeah.
It was a joke way to say it.
It just looked horrible.
And I showed my wife and she said the same thing.
We're just jabbing you on your trip from afar.
It was covered in rain like a Thousand Island dressing.
So like miserable.
No, but I mean, if you have you ever dipped like a real cheap pizza in dressing before?
That's the Papa John's like key to success.
I mean, essentially, it was not that good, but if you just dip it, you'll you'll forget
about that.
So yeah, put enough sauce on anything.
It's delicious.
You know, Jake's pizza and some creamy ranch.
Sure.
Well, we should talk about, you know, there's there's plenty of fine dining options and
of course, entertainment options at today's topic.
Oh, yes.
Island.
Yeah.
Hey, if you're if you're looking to, you know, we can talk about rides all day.
But if you want to talk about the finest entertainment, the best top 40 Jams and and there's some
restaurants and shop.
It's all there.
So we're talking about pleasure.
It's amazing.
I want to tell you like a little bit of my background of Disney and why I feel so connected
to pleasure.
I grew up in New York and from the time I was three years old to 21, we went to Florida
every single year, not just the Florida.
We went to Walt Disney World.
So we were there all the time in a minimum of five to six days, a minimum of that.
And then maximum dream.
Yeah.
And I didn't understand that you could take vacations anywhere else.
And I didn't understand why you would want to go anywhere without a theme park.
Like I wasn't like a purist in the sense that I was like, I'd like to go to Universal.
We went to Universal.
It was great.
Sure.
I wasn't, you know, but yeah, I that was my my entire life from three to 21 was that.
And when I had my girlfriend in college, she's like, well, we should go to Hawaii.
I was like, why?
And then we and then we went to France and I made her go to Disneyland Paris.
And we were only there for a very short period of time in France, like a day and a half.
I was like, we're got to go there.
You made the majority of it be Disneyland Paris.
The good thing was it was completely empty so we could like really knock that park out
real quick.
As it mostly has been in its history.
Yeah, it's a little bit of an out of the way place.
But it was it was fantastic.
I actually found it.
I found the Haunted Mansion there to be quite spookier than the any other one that I've
experienced.
It's scarier.
I love that.
Right.
That was the best part of the day.
Yeah, they did a great job of land.
It's like still the it's the scenes and characters you recognize, but with this layer of the
old west and it is.
Yeah.
That that phantom is scarier.
It's a it's a real it's a real good one.
So I so I spent a lot of time, a lot of time at Walt Disney World.
And then and so as I got older and even when I was younger, like pleasure island was like,
um, this is cool.
Like I am going to like my idea of what like a like where, you know, people go to like
whatever, like senior frogs or whatever.
I was like, this is my where my people are, you know, and like and as I got when I when
I got a little bit older, like high school age, my parents would like let me go to pleasure
island by myself.
OK.
Oh, yeah.
But and then but yes, but I originally went there with my dad and we would spend, you
know, I needed to get there to watch at least the midnight celebration, which I think happened
at 10 o'clock.
This OK.
So I was telling my dad we were doing this and he went and tried to hunt this because
he was convinced of the same thing.
And yes, it seemed like on weekdays they would do it at like 10 or 1030.
Yes, because every night was New Year's.
Yeah, every night was New Year's.
If you were to ask me like what like I did my research, everything that my research is
not my memory of pleasure island.
Like it was like, yeah, it was like the theming behind it was like that was not out in front
of this place at all.
Like, OK, OK, because it was like it was like this guy, James Pleasure invented of like
it was like to me it was like this moon that had sunglasses on that looked like a rejected
like McDonald's character that was the fun.
Meister.
Yeah, the fun.
After my tonight, Mac tonight already exists and they still go in on like the moon.
The cool moon character.
The fun Meister is different from Mac tonight.
Everyone be very clear about that.
But it felt so cool to be like it's midnight.
It's New Year's Eve every night like they would have fireworks and music and they count
down like that's a crazy great thing.
And I want to acknowledge because I like I there's people I know who are like pretty
advanced in their theme park knowledge who still when I talk about this.
Oh, yes, this nightclub district where every night there was a New Year's celebration and
so many people have been like the Simpsons joke.
That's real.
That's an actual thing because in the itchy and scratchy episode when Homer and Mark from
the kids, yeah, when they go to Parents Island, it's there, it's New Year's Eve constantly.
Just like every five minutes.
But like it just seemed like kind of like an odd joke of like how a place like that
could be irritating.
And I've like recently told people there was a real place.
And like you're fucking kidding.
That's so crazy.
It was like this cool.
It was an interesting thing.
It was kind of like I think in my opinion, like at the height of like good, bad Disney
decisions.
It was like it was like we're gonna we're gonna appeal to Orlando.
Like this is going to be a place where Orlando people can come.
You get a wristband and you would be able to come in and just go to any of the like
but it was almost like a separate park like pleasure island park.
Yeah.
And that was another thing my dad came across.
There was a season pass just for Pleasure Island.
You could buy a pass for an annual pass just to go to the clubs and then you could.
Yeah.
And I remember like my dad and I would like figure out like, well, we're going to go here
every night.
It was worth buying like the more expensive.
Yeah.
Band.
Have you all gone to Pleasure Island?
I have not spent a lot of time.
I really only went in the middle of the day on a band trip and I cannot figure out which
place I went to.
And my mom was chaperoning this trip kind of and like I was dancing with girls and I
had never been more insecure in my life.
Oh, wow.
Because also like it's like a year or two prior the girls introduced like what would
be called grinding, I guess you would call it.
And then like they're like kind of and it's also in the middle of the day.
So everyone's like not really, you know, feeling it.
I didn't even know the pleasure island was open during the day because I always thought
it like started opening up at like six.
But this is pleasure island was like gasping for air at multiple points.
I feel like yes.
The last few years of Pleasure Island, because that's what I came across looking up the researching
for this episode.
A lot of videos on YouTube and the type of video you're going to run into is I transferred
a VHS tape from a camcorder in 1991 of walking around Pleasure Island or I'm here in 2008
and it's shutting down.
Yeah.
There's a lot of planters and a lot of stuff is already closed.
By the way, I need to get my videotapes out.
I have like literally like boxes of videotapes of like all we did was this tape everything.
It's almost the most uninteresting home video because it's like who's who is this for?
Like yes, here's four rides on Mr. Toad's Wild Ride.
Like none of them are better than the other.
But yet we taped it.
It was almost like we can tape this so we should.
And now we have this property.
It was like I felt like the same way that you feel like if you've got like a ghostbusters
on tape now, like I got Mr. Toad's ride.
I can live it anytime I want.
In a pre YouTube era, that was important.
Yeah, I remember having like I took my own video of Alice in Wonderland and I don't even
need to go to the park anymore.
I to me, Pledge Island was two things that were like my favorite things besides the New
Year's every night.
And it was not the dance clubs.
It was this place called Adventurers Club.
Sure.
All right.
That was the best thing ever.
It was like kind of a spin off or at least my memory of it was like of like the Jungle
Cruise and you go in.
It was like a basically like a fully themed like kid friendly cocktail bar where they
would have like people singing songs or the gorilla that ran around certain points.
And and then, you know, you would play games.
It would bring some of the people into like one room and then the other people go into
another room.
And it was kind of like everything that people are doing now.
It was like the it was as a kid, I would make my dad say there for hours.
I did the same thing.
I talked about this on the show before, but the Adventurers Club was like loom so large
in my childhood.
The Adventurers Club and the Comedy Warehouse that's the first two places that I ever saw
live comedy.
Oh, the comedy warehouse.
Equally amazing.
It was like we're just running back and forth there.
They're right across the way from each other.
But the Adventurers Club, the most notable thing there there was, do you remember the
giant idol in the main?
Oh, yes.
There's a giant animatronic stone head and it talks to you and it always asks for volunteers
to do like an embarrassing dance and stuff.
And I've gone there so much.
I knew those volunteers got like pins you couldn't buy this door.
Yes.
I pimped my dad into I was like, get up there.
You do get up there and do it.
And then I don't remember if this was the same night.
In my mind, I've mushing together, but we stayed so late.
It was like last it was closing down and we walk outside into pouring rain and like an
electrical storm with like chain lighting in the distance and the bus stop is on the
other side of like the movie theater and the Cirque du Soleil had been built by that point.
So we had to run through torrential rain because I was like, well, we got to see all the shows
tonight.
Some of the best memories of my dad and because my parents are divorced, but was like being
like me and my dad just in in those yellow Disneyland ponchos, just like braving like
awful, awful storm.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Terrifying.
It was fun though.
It was like, cause then my dad was always cool.
He'd be like, let's go on the line now.
That would be very long and it would be empty.
And then, you know, you know, he'd tough it out.
Yeah.
Once you get that poncho on, you're fine.
Use it.
But yeah.
Adventurers club.
I'm upset that I didn't go to this.
I'm so, I didn't know it existed.
I didn't know it existed.
It wouldn't have been cool when you went with the band.
I don't think, I don't think people would have been like, I want to go in for an interactive
theater experience.
Well, it was open though, when I went with my family, I just think that I wasn't in the
know.
I was, I wasn't really designed.
The, what do you zines you call them?
The old Sting Scott was reading these.
Yeah.
Cause I did read all these, all these dorky magazines and stuff.
And for some reason, the adventure club was not on my radar.
It's everything I want.
Or maybe I thought I couldn't go because I was a kid, but this wasn't all ages.
Well, to me, that was the coolest part about it.
Cause like, I had no desire to go dancing at mannequins, you know, or Videodrome or
whatever it was.
I, I wanted to, I wanted to like watch, you know, these people like say they had, they
had like a special thing to say when you walked in, it was a, here, I wrote it down.
It was a Jason might have a kongaloosh wiggle your head.
You take a drink, you wave.
It felt so adult.
I think that was the thing that was so cool about it as a kid.
I think I would go back there now.
And it's probably, I'm sorry.
It's probably what you assumed adult entertainment would be.
Like you put it, like it's, it seems like in a similar, it's, it's like Disney tried
to start a magic castle.
Yes.
Like all of a sudden from the, from scratch.
And I like, now you realize magic castle is this odd particular anomaly, weird LA thing,
but you probably like probably as a kid, you think like, oh yes, these bizarre secret room
cheeky theater shows are, it's just the kind of clever, cool adult entertainment that people
are always getting up to.
I almost think if the pleasure Island had like, like, I feel like they kind of like,
again, they appeal to like Orlando and they don't appeal to like the people are going
to the parks.
I feel like adventure, like the adventure club would be better served as they did more
of those type of feet, like more Disney type themed things instead of being like, and you
can totally do like, I remember they were like shots girls in like, in pleasure Island.
And that was like, it's so incongruous to what you know of Disney.
Like they had like syringe shots.
I remember at one point I was there and it was like, they had like syringe shots or something.
Did you ever get, did you drink there?
Were you old enough to, okay.
Huh.
I feel like I was a two, I was a good boy.
I wasn't ever going to push it, but that was the thing too, the wristbands.
I think the wristbands would dictate if you could drink.
So yeah, you, there was no way to even fake it.
Sneak it.
Yeah.
Okay.
It's a, it's, you said, I believe Jason, before we started, you said that they were
like, pleasure Island was like trying to be everything to everyone.
They were trying to give it every single demographic would enjoy.
And that's like the bat, the good, bad Disney.
It was like, this is a good idea, but it's too, it's too scattershot.
There was so much going on.
I mean, Mike, even your description of like going there and like dancing with girl, like
that, uh, I think I would have been a little younger the main times I would have gone there.
My most memories of being a pleasure Island was like between like 11 and 14 and I was so
focused on the comedy warehouse and the adventures club.
I was like, the concept of meeting people is alien to me.
I would go there by myself and just sit quietly in the comedy warehouse.
I mean, a lot of my time at Disney is spent by me by myself, like, cause my parents would
be like, we're just staying at the hotel.
I'm like, well, I'm going to go to there.
You know, I bring a book, you know, like, and like read books online.
And uh, like, but yeah, like I was just me by myself at those places, not talking to
anyone.
Just like watching.
I would do that.
Like I remember taking like the bus once, like I want to go walk around the Virgin mega
store.
It was like a giant three story.
I spent a lot of time there too.
I could be by myself.
Right.
I got, I bought blood sugar sex magic at that mega store.
Perfect.
Years, years after it came out, this is like 97 or something.
This is a lot.
I bought a Beck biography that I read front to back and learn and learned a lot from as
a very formative item.
Thanks Virgin mega store.
Ask the listeners which item they purchased at the Orlando Virgin mega store.
How do you, how do you Virgin?
I think I bought an optic nerve collection.
Really?
The Virgin mega store used to have a really intensive graphic novel selection.
Yeah right.
They had a cool, they had cool stuff.
I had like cool comics.
I remember like finding cool stuff there like once in Orlando and then like on a high school
trip to time square.
Yeah that like that time square one was amazing.
That's when I had the, my most familiar, familiar with the other thing I loved about, I have
a whole story about the comedy club.
Oh yeah.
I have a, oh man I'm like, it's even hard to like break down what it is because it is
an assemblage of insanity.
It's like there's a Jessica Rabbit like only clothing store and then there's like four
dance clubs and then there's the ventures club and there's a comedy thing and then there's
the nightly New Year's Eve celebration and then there's Disney Quest, which I like Disney
Quest.
Yeah.
I love Disney Quest.
Right, right.
Which is like a pay one price paid video arcade.
Like you like, or at least when I was there it was like you paid like 25 bucks and could
play any game you want.
And that to me blew my mind.
With Cyberspace Mountain and Aladdin Magic Carpet.
I got Ilan.
What's that?
I felt, I almost threw up on that.
Oh really?
Yeah.
I was so excited about it and then I almost threw up.
It was probably weird old like VR.
Oh yeah it was bad.
It wasn't.
It was awful.
Yeah, yeah.
But it was so exciting.
I mean to me the best part of that place was like when you get in there by yourself and
you could ride the elevator up and it was like a special like Robin Williams did like
a special like Aladdin or a genie from Aladdin like thing.
So he was in the elevator with you and he would you know make the Disney Quest appear.
There's a thing that's only in this elevator in this particular themed experience that's
so bizarre.
I was, you know, there's a, that thing is similar to our friend Andrew Grissom just
turned us on to a, did you ever go to Mars 2112 in Times Square?
Yeah.
I'd never heard of it until recently.
Which had like a, there was like a simulator you had to go on to get into the restaurant.
It was a very, it was the poor man's version of like a planet in Hollywood because the
simulators where they spent all their money.
It was like they, it was, and simulator is a generous way to describe it.
It was like you were in a little box, you sat down and it was so janky and it just like,
it just shook.
It didn't really move.
It just was like, almost like you could picture like five kids just like pushing it really
hard and then the door would open on the other side.
It wasn't, you know, so you get out and you'd walk into Mars.
Oh, it didn't take you anyway.
It didn't elevate.
Oh no, no, no.
Yeah.
It was like, well, yeah, it was the same thing as Star Tours, but take away all the cool things
of Star Tours.
And then you would walk into this place, but then they had no money.
So it was like just the surface of the, of Mars as a restaurant.
So there was no real theming besides like, now you're here now.
That's it.
Like they, they, they, it was like a big open space and it just became notorious for everybody
who worked at MTV and VH1, which is right upstairs to get super drunk at their bar.
Cause like when I started working at VH1, people just go, yeah, we're going around Mars
2112 and everyone was psyched to get into that simulator.
And then they would get really drunk and then get on the simulator.
So like, like it was, cause that play at that time was becoming like, this is not going
well for the Mars 2112.
Like sometimes the simulator wasn't even working and you just had to walk through the simulator
like just to get through into the restaurant.
It was, it was bad news.
We'll show you a video if you're curious.
Just keep walking.
They had one in Schomburg, Illinois where I grew up.
Oh, really?
Oh wow.
There was another multiple.
This mall had, we got to do all episode about the Schomburg mall.
Oh, Woodfield mall.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's, yeah, there was a lot of weird.
The fans demanded.
The only rainforest cafe still there.
Geez, really?
One of the only rainforests that still exists.
Wow.
And the, and of course the Disney, the Mickey's kitchen.
Oh yes, that was one of the Mickey's.
Whoa, I didn't know that.
The Disney store.
There were only two locations of a Disney store restaurant.
So it's kind of like the one here in Los Angeles that's attached to the movie theater, the
ice cream shop kind of.
Yeah.
It's an ice cream shop Disney store.
That's an audio elevator.
Yeah.
With El Capitan.
But you were, well so that's like going to that bar for stupid reasons in Times Square.
You must have had all this like, this, this, this Pleasure Island and Disney affection
growing up and like, you must have like badly wanted to take this into your adulthood and
get people to dumb restaurants.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, it's a constant battle of people not wanting to go and do my stuff.
My wife, like, like, uh, for my birthday this year, like it was just, it was weird timing
we were away, we were back and she's like, what do you want to do?
And I was, she, oh, my wife was working.
That was what was happening.
And, and she's like, uh, and I was like, I'm just going to go to Disneyland.
I was like, it'll be fun.
Like I don't, like I didn't have anything planned for the day.
I was like, I'll come back.
And then she's like, why, why would you go there?
Like during the day by yourself?
I was like, no, no, it'd be fun.
Like I had a great time.
I went on that new Star Wars, like VR thing, which is amazing.
We just, we just did it.
Yeah.
But we're, yeah, we loved it.
I mean, it's great.
They're now they have one in Glendale now too.
Uh huh.
We did the Glendale one.
Yeah.
Right next to the JC pennies.
You got a VR spectacular.
You're making us fit that you were, your willingness to be open about going to Disneyland by yourself
makes us feel less alone.
Oh, I feel, I, I don't often admit it.
Like if people, I, I, I try to hide where I was, like I just got busted by my wife.
I didn't want to even tell her, but there's been days when I'm just like, I, I've had
that season pass or to do, I'd be like, I'll go down there and ride when they switch over
the haunted mansion into the nightmare before Christmas thing.
Like, and come back.
I don't care.
Sure.
Yeah.
Just that.
It's a luxury.
Yeah.
I, you know, I, that's making me realize I have been to Disneyland by myself and been
too ashamed to tell my wife.
That was what I did.
She'll find this out from listening that you ever done that.
She had maybe Lindsay knows where you're coming from.
You feel alone when I go by, I feel like I'm not.
So you guys have all gone by yourself.
I've gone by myself.
It's usually like I have something to do at wonder con or there's something around.
I don't think I've gone down alone and not told anybody, but I've certainly been in the
park.
I've drank alone at trader Sam's.
I've drank alone at the bar at the car.
They circle.
I've maybe drank alone at that circle one in the middle of downtown.
By the way, I'm going to say car thief circle might be my favorite.
Yes.
Very good.
We love the lounge too.
Have you ever done in the middle of the day?
I'm sure there's a 10th time I've said this, you go and you have a, a, a Walt scotch mister
Manhattan and it totally reinvigorates you for the, like it's a good mid day.
I had a martini there.
I should have done that.
I did a mid day drink there cause I was like, why not?
I'm here.
This is great.
Not a bad line too.
I went down in December, like just on a weekday just to see, cause I was like going home like
two days later for like a week or two to see my family for the holidays.
And I was like, oh, I'm not, I didn't, I can't schedule.
No one else could go down and it's like, well, I want to see Christmas.
I want to see Disneyland at Christmas.
So I just went and then I was like middle of the day, I was very tired.
I was like, I'm going to go eat at the hotel and I went to whitewater snacks.
The quick service restaurant.
It's all the way in the back.
It's very quiet.
They pump in nature sounds and soothing music.
I had the whole restaurant to myself.
I remember now I went down, I have said this before.
I went down to see Dick Fendi in the parade.
Oh yes.
I remember.
For like an hour.
It was an hour.
I don't think I went on a ride.
I think I literally got out.
I bought a cupcake.
I watched an old man in a car go down main street and I was out of there.
Cause I had like, I think I had to do an, I think we had an improv practice that I had
to get back to.
I think that's right.
You know, it's like my, like when I, I think I got used to it because when I would go with
my family, I'm an only child.
So they would like my parents, they, even though they have a Disney timeshare, they
don't seemingly, uh, like the parks.
They really like the hotels and the restaurants.
I think they almost just like that.
They don't have to think about anything.
It's like, why would I go to France when I could just have a nice French meal at this
place?
And you have to do research and look up where are the nice hotels and where are the nice
roads?
You know, you go to Disney world, they'll all find them somewhere.
She's so excited.
She's like, I checked my bags at the airport and then they're in my hotel room.
Cause she does like the Disney, the bus and everything.
So I mean, by the way, I'm speaking about, oh, this is the thing.
That's what happened.
I went to club 33, but I went there with friends.
Then I spent a week in Alani, the Disney resort in Hawaii.
And then my son's birthday was on Monday and I brought him there and that, that was the
most Disney I've done in a very long time.
You know, I know somebody who was in at Alani when the, uh, the death notice went out when
like, oh, like the alert.
Yeah.
What did they say it was like?
Uh, like it just, it was almost too surreal to believe and just everybody's looking at
like, he's got to maintain calm for the kids have to just, but like you go outside and
everybody was, it was kind of like people lying each other.
Like, is this real or we all is a, is a, is a bomb coming our way right now.
And he said like the bonding after it had happened was phenomenal.
They're like every single person you ran into is like, Hey, we made it.
Wow.
Like just every, there was this like the great bonding of humanity happened from that.
We all had the experience of getting a fucking alert on our phones saying we're going to
die.
Well, it may be most of us had to deal with children and like, how do we, yeah, I could
like, I could not imagine.
I talked to, like, I did this little boat trip at off the Alani and I asked the guys
like, what was it like?
And he was like, yeah, they were really nice to Disney people invited us into the hotel
and they were like, Hey, you want to hang out here?
Like, you know, like, you know, like, you know, like, because I spend your last hour
home or whatever.
So we just like hung out in the hotel with them and they were like, nice to us.
And it was like, which is seemingly was surprising to me from about Disney, like being like,
I can see Disney at that point being like, you know, you guys kind of work on the water.
So I maybe stay down there and you could be great.
Cost us money.
Also, yeah, this place gets destroyed.
Well, the hurricane last year that hit Florida, like Disney got a lot of good press because
like they went out of their way to feed people and like they gave like next to nothing rooms
to Florida residents and there were characters around.
There was activities for kids and buffets and like Kristen Bell was singing like show
to the show tunes.
She got Josh Gads family rooms, which and I believe that was a one 80 because I think
they've kind of miffed it on hurricane prep in the past, but they seemed like they did
a good job in 2017.
Well, you know who really miffed it on hurricane prep was the pleasure family who let the island
fall into disarray.
I don't know if you read the backstory of Pleasure Island.
This backstory is so confusing.
Can you like try to break it down because they turn to you, Jason.
I have a couple of I have a couple of questions about it because I did enough research that
made me confused about it.
I don't think any amount of research there is so much.
There's so much.
Merryweather Adam pleasure.
Before we start this.
So what and maybe you guys found this.
This is called Pleasure Island, which is from Pinocchio.
The name Pleasure Island is from Pinocchio.
It's the evil place.
It's the debaucherous place that the kids go that they should not.
They learn a lesson not to drink and smoke and turn into donkeys.
And now here's my question.
So that's the theme.
Right.
You should just stick to that.
Call it pleasure island because it's based on Pinocchio and yeah, and make it.
But I guess it has a very evil negative connotation.
That must be.
They had to invent another definition.
Yes.
But they're not named pleasure yet.
Right.
That don't call it Pleasure Island.
That's that's what I find so bizarre about it is because when people hear it, 99% of
all the dads who went here were like, let me look into the backstory of this place.
And then he's like, oh, it's not the Pinocchio thing.
It's a man named Merryweather.
OK.
And then the big mascot is not Merryweather pleasure.
It's Jessica Rabbit.
Right.
But also the fun.
Funmeister.
But then there's no visual depiction of Merryweather pleasure anywhere.
Right.
Only in the Adventurers Club.
He's in a picture in the Adventurers Club.
But but then every place had a plaque.
Yeah.
There were 26 plaques scattered about the island.
The plaques were black with like gold ish.
So hard to see at night.
And they made an incredibly convoluted.
I mean, here at the entrance plaque, this is like a video drum one.
The video drum one is one of my favorite ones.
Well, this is just a snippet of the unverifiable anecdotal purely subjective theoretical alleged
purported history.
Also your stats.
So like there it's a gag.
It's like this is fake.
They're telling you it's fake.
Founded in 1911.
Merryweather Pleasure's profitable canvas manufacturing and sale fabricating empire founded on this
island provided him with capital to indulge his lifelong interest in the exotic, the experimental
and the unexplainable.
And very quick side track to that, because I found a longer history that explained that
he was he made sales.
That's what Merryweather Pleasure did.
That's what all these warehouses were were sale manufacturing rooms, warehouses.
And there was like a failing business until World War One.
So he was he's a war profiteer is who Merryweather Pleasure is.
He is a war profiteer.
He is also known as the Grand Funmeister.
So the funmeister is a nod to its own made up history.
How much fun would it have been to have a man dressed like, you know, like almost like
a life sized version of the Monopoly man.
And I remember the brother, well, yeah, and walking around and just being a gregarious
sort, you know, you put a big mustache on him, give him a monocle and let him just run
around there.
Like he's the ghost of Merryweather.
Merryweather Pleasure.
They didn't they don't want to go all in on him, though, because like that's probably
like teens are like, who the fuck's this old man?
Like they wouldn't like that.
They want a sexy cartoon woman or they want a moon man.
By the way, speaking of ghosts, I just remember that one of the things the Avengers Club,
they wanted to do is drink with a ghost.
Yes.
They wanted to do the Haunted Mansion technology to project a ghost next to you.
So you'd be in this ghost bar.
I thought that was so someone would be playing a ghost and talking, but it would look like
they were.
Yeah, it's amazing in another room.
Yes, they are.
It is live.
Yes.
Whoa, that's cool.
I know there was a bunch of like expansion plans for it if it was like the most popular
thing ever, which it wasn't.
But I will say I bet it would be now.
Yeah, it would be now.
And there were plans to put an adventurous club in downtown Disney in Anaheim, according
to Jim Hill, I believe he mentioned that on a recent podcast.
They were going to put it out here.
And then as they started to dial back with California Adventure in downtown Disney, we're
going to be that was gone.
That stinks because, you know, they put in like that that store that take pictures of
babies and like Bean Pods or whatever it is.
You know, that may be gone now because of that.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That was there for a long time.
But maybe now in this like elevated with the level of escape room and all that stuff.
I think the teaming and everything.
Yeah, I feel like that's what Star Wars is going to be.
Yes.
It's kind of like interactive, fully like, you know what I think?
And this is it goes back to like this dumb thing of like, I feel like 40s is lost on
people on how this get maybe just watch Sky Captain and the World of Tomorrow.
And at a certain point, someone's like, yes, this is what people want.
They want to watch.
They want to watch a movie that was like the old serials because that's what Indiana Jones
is like.
Indiana Jones is like, no, no, Indiana Jones is still like a contemporary movie.
Yes, it takes place in the 40s, but it's not like literally like it's not like it's not
nodding its head to the 40s so much.
You're like, hey there, what's going on over there?
You know, it's like, it's not like that.
People don't want.
I want it.
But you know who does?
Yeah, me too.
Yeah, I'm all in.
The Avengers Club imprinted on my subconscious so much.
Anytime I see something of like, you know, mid century explore, I'm like, all right,
got to make sure to see that at least on DVD.
Oh, 100 percent.
Like, yeah, I would.
I would be going if it was like if it was that.
I mean, that's why I like Trader Sam's to a certain degree.
Yes, because Trader Sam's has that same kind of energy.
It's like it's an explorer.
It's a pirate theme.
It's a this, you know, with all the artifacts he brought back from.
Yeah, that's that's why.
No one has like art of artifacts.
Yeah.
Well, if you go on to the oh, I haven't gone to the Trader Sam's.
It's like a year old to a year and a half.
Something like that.
It's in the Polynesian.
Oh, I just went to the Indiana Jones bar.
Yes, John does.
He's bringing you guys.
Yeah, that was fun.
Yeah, that's a great bar because that's like, you know, that's a perfect theme.
It's Indiana Jones and like they got the plane is like a big decked out restaurant out there.
It's perfect in the former Pleasure Island.
Exactly.
And that's in the landing is what it all became.
Yes.
Specific area.
Right.
So you had the Jason.
You were getting there.
Twenty six.
Well, one of my favorite ones.
Huh?
I can't read one of my favorite.
OK, this is I think the one on the video drum one, which is basically a club that had just
a lot of music videos playing in it.
Video video.
Sorry.
I was East.
Yeah.
Oh, it was all ages.
This was the only all ages built for Island founder.
Meriwether Pleasure's son, Henry, the mad genius of Lake Buena Vista and Henry's life
work, the pleasure cellular automation.
OK, so that's so that's that Henry died thinking his experiments in artificial intelligence
had failed, but when the building was reopened in 1987, the Ottoman the automaton was alive
and thriving.
In fact, it is directed the refurbishing of its home and design the sophisticated computer
hardware that shows itself to its best advantage.
That does not make sense.
It's a poorly worded thing.
I'm not I was reading it.
I'm hitting the periods.
It is.
It doesn't really.
Yeah, no, it's yeah, it's all wordy.
It's tough.
They needed an editor.
He had to in the history.
He had two sons, Henry and Stewart, and they're like Trump fail.
They're like Donald Jr. and Eric.
They just like if you follow the line through these plaques, they're constantly fucking
up.
Literate.
Their mismanagement led to the bankruptcy of the island.
Yeah, and they had gotten vacated and then Hurricane Connie hit and that wiped it out
all together.
So yeah, it was a wealthy industrialist who had two idiot sons who fucked up his empire.
This is my favorite plaque.
It was at the lookout point at Pleasure Island.
And this this is my favorite because it's so off game of everything else.
Son of Island founder, Meriwether Pleasure, paranoid Henry Pleasure camped up here every
single night from 1981 from December 8th, 1941 to VJ Day.
He was convinced that the Axis powers were plotting an assault on America by coming ashore
at Pleasure Island, which was then and remains 80 miles from the Atlantic Ocean.
In his nearly four years of vigilance, Henry fired his musket only once.
Musket is a weird detail.
He mistook a family of herons for the leading edge of an invasion force.
The herons escaped unharmed.
This is like a this is backstory that seems like the stuff that you write and you're like,
oh, I'll never use that.
And I guess it's like it's almost like they go, well, I don't mean like it's like that's
for me to know to write the story, but no one should ever know because it's inconsequential.
Like you're like actor backstory and something just in case anybody needs to know.
Yeah, it's it's so sad.
We could make a better pleasure island right now in the give us just give us the same exact
material we could make.
It would be more functional and complete than this.
This seems like this seems like Michael Eisner is like dumb ideas.
Yeah, it's pleasure.
Go, go, go.
I feel like maybe it was the imagineers were like, here's the deal.
We're going to make 26 plaques.
You guys write whatever you want on them.
We're going to sneak them in in the middle of the night.
I'll never see it.
No one will care.
Like we won't get this approved.
There's no like this is our we're a bunch of fucking nerds for the 40s and for like
people like firing muskets.
We're going to put these plaques up like because again, no dad ever read these.
No no one cared.
Ninety nine percent of the people didn't know you were walking around by yourself.
Yeah, right.
You didn't really read them.
I didn't know that these even existed until I did this research.
I mean, let's in front of the comedy club.
This is this one.
This building became a storage facility when Pleasure Island was electrified in 1928.
So does that mean hit by lightning or got electricity?
Either way, it's not clear.
And then it goes six years later, the power station became home to the Pleasure Island
thespian players founded and featuring Isabella Pleasure, wife of island founder and drama
enthusiast Meriwether Pleasure.
The players specialized in elaborate central Florida historical pageants, including the
Seminole song of the Seminole.
Now, but why do we need to know that it's a storage facility that was electrified and
then it became this other thing?
It's like it's it's not it's not it's nonsense.
It's nonsense.
Also, I read all of these plaques.
And if you ask me right now how many of them were power plant themed, I'd go like, uh,
half half of them were power plant themed.
They're all where that's the that's the flaw in the design of all warehouses.
I mean, it's like it's like it's like too much like there's too many points on the scale
because they're supposedly like this thing was discovered by the Imagineers who got it
back on its feet.
Yeah.
It's a much simpler line to draw, like, well, this man owns the things and it's a fun place
for children to like or for teens to go.
That's so much cleaner.
It's like it's not an unheard of thing in this world that you take like a dilapidated
warehouse area and turn it into a bar area like that.
You don't have to buy the way many, many pages of novel.
They were already stealing Church Street Station, which is like the downtown Orlando.
Thank God you said church station because I spent two hours last night going down this
rabbit hole.
I'm ready.
Church Street Station, I think just like Adventurers Club opened me up to this thing.
They had the they had like a haunted mansion there.
Yes.
I'll walk through haunted mansion like a reach out and like the whole you had to walk through
by putting your hand on someone's shoulder in front of you and you walk through as a
line and it was the first time I ever gone in anything where people like jumped out at
you or chased you with chainsaws like one.
It was a very like a lot of money.
You went.
I went.
Which is crazy because I never went.
I didn't even know really this existed.
Scott said this like Church Street Station me a while ago.
Is there anything weird to do in Orlando?
And I was like, Church Street Station, but it's it's totally desolate, much like a merry
weather Pleasures Island.
It was like 70s and 80s was the heyday of it.
And it's the reason why Disney made Pleasure Island to put it out of business to try to
get some of this money.
Yeah, yeah, this is what they do.
This is what MGM Studios was.
They tried to put Universal out of business or to or like Barbush Gardens.
We don't want people going to a zoo.
Let's have a zoo.
Exactly.
So a man named Bob Snow came up with Church Street Station and he was the one and it was
a crazy like you would pay like ten bucks or five bucks and all these different places
were available to you very quickly.
I'll name some of the places.
Apple Annie's, Rosie O'Grady's.
I wrote your grades.
I brought a date there.
Yeah.
Wow.
Great.
It was actually the first time that my parents met my girlfriend's parents at Rosie O'Grady's.
Wow.
I have a souvenir mug.
But the say the full title Rosie O'Grady's Good Time Emporium.
Yeah, sorry, sorry.
Again, a very Simpson's.
It's so much like Uncle Mo's.
I know.
Family feedback.
Yeah.
The Chenyan Opera House, which they like recorded a TV show from there.
And if you look at look on YouTube, they have all the episodes of this Chenyan Opera House
show and they have Merle Haggard on it.
Lee Greenwood, Tammy Wynette, Boxcar Willie.
Every country star you can imagine did this show that was at Church Street Station.
It's insane.
What was the word you were saying before Opera House?
I couldn't hear it.
Was I mispronouncing it?
Chenyan?
Cheyenne?
Cheyenne.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, okay.
I only know that because I have a relative name Cheyenne.
I otherwise might not know.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I probably wrote that.
It was also the Orchid Garden Ballroom.
And then my favorite title is Phineas Fogg's Balloon Works.
That's so Disney.
Which is the most.
That's so Dream Finder-y.
Yeah.
It's before Dream Finder and before like fantastical like Man in a Balloon.
Is Phineas Fogg the character from Around the World?
I believe so, yeah.
I think that's right.
That makes sense.
It sounds like that Troy McClure.
Another one.
Horatio Ocknagels.
Those are the era of Simpsons writers must have been down with Disney stuff.
And obviously as South Park is and I think the Adventurers Club is referenced in a little
bit in the last episode with Chef, the Super Adventure Club.
Yes.
That's got to be a little Disney reference.
I was going through like people's like memories of this place and I was getting so nostalgic
for a place I had never been.
Like Hard Rock Park.
I was like Hard Rock Park, but like Hard Rock Park was a little funnier.
I was getting legit like, wow, what a place.
If I was only like I was imagining working at Phineas Fogg.
It was like 2 a.m. and I'm so tired.
And I'm like really getting nostalgic for all of this bullshit.
And then there's also people like talking about, you know, just how much fun it was.
Then there's people that are talking about how they would pregame for a Jimmy Buffett
concert at Church Street Station.
Well, to me Church Street Station felt like very like adult.
And I think Pleasure Island tried to split the difference.
It was like, can we do adults and kids?
It felt like this is where people in Orlando went to get hammered.
It was like, you know, and it was like fun and safe.
And I think Orlando didn't have much outside of the parks.
And this felt like the community of Orlando to a certain extent.
It's like we're going to go to like we're going to go down to our like New Orleans,
like whatever that Main Street in New Orleans is where everyone.
Oh, sure.
And the bars are all it's separate establishments, but it's all one big neighborhood.
You're walking down one block and it's like and everything's there and everyone's seeing
each other and it's like no cars are there.
And it's like, well, at least my memory of it was like that.
It was like you could walk from place to place.
Watching people's home movies on YouTube of Pleasure Island, it was very clearly like
a mix of locals in club where see like couples, couples in like vacation leisure where like
a lot of flowery polos tucked into jeans and then four person family, like families with
kids and they all look tired.
So that is a very odd melting pot to encounter.
Yeah, it's it's it was again, it's a bad it's a bad thing.
I think the reason why like even Disney Springs is having issues now, it's like they want
to like attract people from Orlando to come there and do their like mall shopping.
Right.
It just seems like it's out of the way.
Yeah.
And I feel like if you live in Orlando, you're probably like, I don't want to go there to
do my my mall.
Right.
Just basic shopping.
Yeah.
Do you have more?
Is there more church?
Well, they have to think about that.
I don't want to go to anyone.
I didn't see I didn't have a memory about that.
I did find the Church Street Station promo video, which is a big.
Did you see have you seen this?
Didn't we text about this?
Did the disease with with I think we did in the streets?
Yes.
OK, yes.
I found it.
There we go.
So we'll post this, obviously.
This time.
Yeah, I love the vibe of this.
It's like a more slower themed like Cheers.
I mean, it's like if Cheers didn't have all those lovable characters.
This look some of this looks like Farrell's the ice cream.
Oh, yeah.
Old timey.
Yeah.
And then there's this other ad that's that's like eight minutes long.
That's like this.
A man just carving a Marlin out of some ice.
A good place for good people.
That's a little sexy.
Lady putting a garter on.
But this is like this whole idea, like these places came alive at night.
Yes, that was like that.
Wait, wait.
I'm ready for a brand new season
So I'm here every time I try
To advance into the future
I'm looking for a car
And even now I'm alone
It's really sincere fun and Eisner is like, I must crush this. Yes. It...
False Louis.
This was the fourth most visited tourist destination after Busch Garden Seaworld Disney.
Wow. Wow.
Well because I think it felt like adult... I mean that's what my parents like going to Church Street Station.
Because it's a real place for grown-ups. Yeah. It was established by not a Bizarre Kids Corporation.
Yeah, so this goes on like this.
But you end up with the dinner where things get a little more stately.
See we didn't leave the Disney bubble that much. We mostly left to go to Universal.
My dad and I would leave the bubble. My mom would stay in the bubble.
Oh and then if we had a kitchen we would go to the grocery store.
So you get the classic song Dancing in the Street in all these different styles.
Yeah, there's a dinner is my favorite. Where was this ever airing?
That's a very good question. It's just called a marketing video.
Oh, okay. Yeah. It's pretty warm.
If you don't feel like hearing this part up, it's all the different clubs sing Dancing in the Street.
And then it changes to a more stately dinner where you hear, it's a place for folks to eat.
That's a change I really like. But so Mike, I don't want to jump ahead of the order of things.
No, no, it's okay.
But do you know why what happened to Church Street besides Disney crippling the business?
I probably came across it, but I don't remember.
So it's in the window where Pleasure Island was doing well.
Church Street station decays. Businesses start moving out.
And Orlando has to do something big to try to get this area back on its feet.
And they turn to the greatest industrialist in Orlando at that time, Lou Pearlman.
Oh, wow.
Will you, sir, turn this area around?
Okay, I guess. I'll get some of the guys in here.
And so in 2003, they give this guy $1.5 million in loans to the city of Orlando.
And in 2003, the bands have already sued this guy.
Backstreet and NSYNC have already sued.
And there's certainly by 2003 the implication that this man is like a pedophile.
And still Orlando is like, he's the solution.
He's a guy saying that he's going to turn Church Street station into the hub of boy band culture.
And he makes a promise that this is a place for him to like score dates.
So well, this is all the boys here.
All the kids will be dancing in the streets here.
There'll be many alleys that are difficult to escape from.
All dead ends.
Every alley is a trap doors spikes that close in on you.
That's like four years after City Walk opens in the other side of Orlando.
You've already got that going too.
How is Pearlman going to and he makes a promise to he's like, we'll start small.
2004 we will have we'll do some concerts.
We'll have 150 outdoor street events, 150 days out of the year.
And then the next year we'll get it up to 200.
And I found an article from the Orlando Weekly from 2005 like for liberal writers like anybody been to any of those concerts?
Any of those happen?
No, not a single like he just didn't do it.
And he pocketed the money and then he was arrested by the FBI in Malaysia or whatever.
And he died in jail.
Oh, my God.
What a sad thing for the people of Orlando.
All they had was a place where they could hang out where they weren't going to be totally inundated by like tourists all the time.
Maybe there's a little bit more of a local culture there.
And even though it was the biggest tourist attraction, I feel like they probably had their own thing and then not every like, you know, like Bannister everywhere you look at it.
Not everything is shaped like Mickey or Jafar or whatever.
Like there's some unbranded things in this area.
Yeah.
Characters like Phineas Fogg, you know, and the fake Gary Armstrong.
The you know, and Laurel and Hardy.
Oh, they were like Laurel and Hardy running around in all the places.
That sort of like old timey stuff like that still hasn't gone away.
I mean, Mike and I have both been to Disney Springs once it's like been fully operational and like the Edison is power plant theme.
Right.
Turn of the century power plant theme.
Maria Enzo is an Italian restaurant in it.
Looks like a 1940s like Golden Age of airline travel, 1940s, 50s airplane hangar.
And then Jock Lindsay's that there's still all this old timey theming.
It's a weird thing.
I think it's like I don't know why we are doubling down on that because in my opinion, you know, look, it may be controversial.
I think that City Walk is the only one who's nailed it.
Like City Walk is like this is what you want.
It's kind of like you got a big movie theater.
There's some restaurants that you know, it's we're not theming these out to be like 1940s.
There's no Keystone cops here.
It's like it's Olive Garden.
It's Bubba Gump.
And like and we got a fountain that does that thing so your kids can run there and get soaked.
And you know, and then there's like a couple of fun stores, a magnet store, the sock store.
Sure.
John Lovett's Comedy Club that's out here was out here.
But like, you know, they're just kind of like walking around the Saddle Ranch if you want to get a little bit more risque, you know, you know, the clothes.
Now I know it's a sad sad day.
There's like, you know, like there's a big cup or something or the King Kong.
There's big giant things you can take a picture of if you want, right? You don't have to learn a whole fucking story.
It just seems like that's what you like when you want to go out.
It's like, yes, we'll get a pizza and then go see a movie like I don't need to like.
Yeah, come my friend to a universe that your eyes may not understand.
That said, I mean, obviously we like the theming restaurants itself.
Also, when I was there packed everywhere, I walked by lines out the door.
Yeah, August, if I was eating a bubblegum and Laurel and Hardy wandered by, I'd love it.
Oh, I'm again, I'm seeing dismissive of all this.
I'm 100 percent there. I ate at Jock Lindsay's by myself and waited until I could sit in the little like portal.
Of course, like the submersible submarine thing.
Populist idea.
City Walk is the one that appeals really to the most.
That's what I think everyone's trying to do.
When they try to get too cheeky with it and I feel like Pleasure Island walk this weird middle ground of like a good bad idea.
It's like it's almost Disney and it's almost City Walk.
And what it turns out to be is a mess because the theming is half ass.
It's like, well, Disney Quest doesn't fit with the theming of this.
The comedy club is very different than an adventurous club and the clubs are just clubs.
Well, that's I mean, we've barely talked about, though.
I mean, even after reading for hours about these clubs, I had to go like, wait, so neon armadillo was the country.
What was your age?
Cage was different from Mannequin.
And then one was the the roller skating one.
I do. While we're on Disney stealing, I may have I have a story.
Yeah. So I used to do comedy at this place called Chicago City Limits.
It was in New York City and they did short form improv very much like what you'd see on who's on this.
And anyway, like every time a bell rings, we're going to change our thing.
So when they're opening a pleasure island, some people from Disney came and saw Chicago City Limits.
And they're like, this is what we're opening up a brand new place.
This is what we want to be in in in our in our new park.
And we'll call it Chicago City Limits and we'll buy it.
We'll do the whole thing. We'll move you guys there.
So the head of Chicago City Limits at that time goes.
We want 10 million dollars, you know, for the name, the name that didn't even really mean that much.
Now, I was a member of Chicago City Limits. I've heard this now from multiple people.
This is a true story. And then in Disney, OK, OK, OK, let's think about it.
And Disney walked away, then went to behind Chicago City Limits, the owners back, hired everyone in the main stage show,
took them and stole the entire show. So what you see, they open up with this review.
And that was essentially what Chicago City Limits was. It was like improv, very mediocre sketch, improv, mediocre sketch.
And that's kind of what this thing was.
And then and then everyone, those people who perform there, who sold out Chicago City Limits, would just occasionally steal another performer.
They would come down and then they would teach improv and then go.
So I have all these friends who, like, migrated down there to do a essentially Chicago City Limits show that they just completely stole.
And and it was lamented when I was at Chicago City Limits.
I was like, oh, we could have been this we could have ultimately branded ourselves by being like Chicago City Limits at Disneyland.
And the step to making it like a second city multiple others, like a silly or second city like that.
They have a Vegas thing and exactly whatever something that feels like it makes it.
But I just said that was like the best example of hubris and also the smartestness of like of Disney just going like, right, right, right.
And then I was like, OK, cool. Think about it. And now we'll just take everyone from your show and make them.
When it first opened, they were doing like a review called Forbidden Disney.
Right. It was like a body sketch show about it was like body to the body.
It was like I think it was like someone would play like Small World and let's kill this guy or like shoot him or something.
But even if they shot him, it was like a gun that's a bang.
Like, yeah, slumping down the adventure club, much more body in terms of people, the characters being drunk and horny.
Like, yeah, like to me, like the Disney body was like, oh, the lines at Disney are pretty long.
Oh, I can't believe they said it like, hey, we just spent a lot of money eating these hot dogs.
It was like the most like we're poking fun, but not that much.
Yeah. Thanks for coming down and, you know, it's a way we're we're always here.
I appreciate it. It is a good value for your money.
Really, if you think about all the things we have to offer.
But it doesn't seem like that lasted.
It seems like they pivoted to that short form.
That short form thing.
And then, yeah, and that's when I would go when I got a I think I'm back there in college.
I went and visited a few friends that just were doing that show nightly.
And I once got to play on that stage because I said, oh, yeah, so that was a very, you know, a fun thing.
But then also a nerve wracking thing, because it is a level of improv and a level of language and a level of content.
Yes, they are very comfortable with.
And so I could only do the latest show that they had.
And because it was like it's severely monitored by everybody like and it was like I was kind of snuck in to do the show and kept it very clean.
It was a sort of like but yeah, it was not it used to be you can sort of do whatever you want.
This is like this rules and parameters. Yeah.
It's really polished. Yeah. And it was very simple improv games like literally.
I think like every time this bell rings, you'll say something different.
I was like, I just went to the store. Ding. I just went to the mall. Ding. I just went to the car dealership thing.
You know, it wasn't like you weren't like improvising. You were just basically like coming up with specifics and puns.
There's lots of rapid speed. Yeah.
Did you that's that's cool. You got to play there.
The other there's there's folks who are there people who like did improv there who've made it out to New York or L.A.
Jamie Denbo. Jamie Denbo. Yeah, I thought so.
Yeah. James Dembeau. I performed at that comedy club as well.
And then she had the real, in my opinion, crappy gigs that she worked at like innovations like she was doing like this this atmosphere of innovation.
The innovation in the event in the Epcot. Yeah. And then inventions.
Yeah. And I know I'm the only show you'll ever be on that will correct you on that.
I knew I was like, I just want to make sure I wasn't trying to be a no, I didn't take it.
The video drone. No, I'm like this is where I knew I was going to.
I have so much Disney knowledge, but it's all falsely categorized.
That's OK. But yeah, like she had like those jobs where like you'd have to like showing the houses of the future and doing the funny.
But also we're also showing off that like, you know, Black and Decker does have a pretty cool back.
You know, wow, that's a thin line.
And she was saying that there were like these dots on the floor that you'd have to step on and that would activate a light like it was like an automated show.
It was a one person show that you were controlling all by what you were doing on the stage.
Wow. Did you ever think about like, did you try to do like theme park entertainment as a regular anywhere?
Yeah. All right. I'll tell you the two darkest moments of my life.
That's funny. That's the response. They all involve.
Yeah, I know. It's like so I was dating this girl.
This is a girl who we met their parents at Rosie O'Grady's, you know, fun place.
We got flaming drinks, watch show girls. A lot of fun time.
But we were on the down. We were in the downward spiral of Rosie O'Grady.
I think it was your great. He's like stuck it out because it's a great establishment.
You know, it was on its way to being a bad time.
Emporium. Yeah, it was an OK. Right.
It was like a mediocre time to show girls not not on the bar.
They would just be in the back. They don't kick all the way up.
Yeah, like 30 degrees.
So we were dating in college and I went to go visit her at home and she was like, we got to break up.
And, you know, you're I was doing improv in New York City at this point.
I was doing Chicago City Limits and and I was not going to spend New Year's Eve with her
because I was going to do this New Year's Eve show in New York.
It was like a really cool opportunity. It was cool.
It was exciting. Like this is like the beginning of my career.
I still kind of in college at this point.
And she's like, oh, you got to break up.
And, you know, you're too involved in this stuff and I can see it's not going to go away.
And this is not going to work out.
And and I was like, all right, you know what? I need to keep this relationship going.
I'm going to join the comedy company at Pleasure Island and literally like because I know I've been in there.
I can do this. And if I would have made that choice, my career would have gone in a drastically horrible, different.
I would argue of not be here.
I would probably be in Orlando, you know, working at some something sad.
The king of Orlando. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know.
I would go to Orlando a million times.
I just feel like if I would have just went there and been like, hey, I'm like trying to do comedy and be an actor.
And then like I just maxed out at the comedy connection or whatever it is.
Or you would have gotten it in sync.
I think right. You've gotten the dance in that alley.
You probably want to grab me.
And then the second is this is not a dark moment.
It was more like again, it was an opportunity.
I always made this choice of not taking like the easy path.
Like so Disney Cruises came and Disney Cruises like, hey, you want to come do Disney Cruise.
And that was a really like you make one hundred and ten thousand dollars like for like a six month cruise.
You couldn't get off. You were on the boat for six months.
Like you could get off the boat. You could get off at ports, you know, but like you were you couldn't go home.
Right. Right. So you're there. All your food was provided for.
So you're you're keeping your hundred and ten like your room and board and your food is paid for.
And you're just doing an improv show on that boat.
And it was right at the start of the UCB.
And I was like, should I do this? Like one hundred and ten thousand?
Like that seemed like a gigantic sum of money.
It is a gigantic sum of money. And and I and I opted not to do that and just do like free shows at UCB that were like, you know,
robot TV at midnight on a Friday night, which I'm so happy that I did do.
But it was like a moment where I was really like, what do I do? Do I do Disney?
Because I love Disney. I was like, oh, that would be kind of great. I would. And that's the other part of it.
I would love to work at Disney. Like my my dream thing would be like, wouldn't it be great if you could like run the Jungle Cruise like one time?
Like that would be awesome. Yeah. Yeah. Like something like that would be fun.
You know, I did. I was a tour guide. Oh, I know. Yeah.
And I like I always say I would do if I could do it once a month, if they give me one shift a month, I would so happily.
That's the best. Then that was a fun one, too.
But now it's like, isn't all it just like Jimmy Fallon doing it all. Right.
They kick a lot. There's a lot of like clips and things you're required to do, but not necessarily any way.
Anybody at the tour guide gig listening, you know, unless you're being secret shopped, you can kind of do what you want.
Unless and then you imagine you had to fill a lot of time and that guy died on the earthquake ride. Right.
Oh, I did talk about that. Yeah, that was an hour straight.
The tour guide, the tour guide prays for something like that so we can really let it rip.
That's what they told us in the training is like you will beg for these moments because it'll throw you off.
It's like something different happening is such a big deal. So when so when that man died of a heart attack, I was time to shine in there.
My friend, my friend who into like worked at Disney, like a couple of people I knew who worked there like out of college.
And again, last night and I don't know, maybe I'm just depressed or something in general in life.
But I was again getting very nostalgic. I go, why didn't I just go for six months and intern at Disney?
That would have been so much fun because I'm reading all these pleasure island and we'll get to it.
But I found the Pleasure Island memories Facebook page and I was reading through all of this stuff and I was legit going, man, this would have been fun if I was a certain age.
And it was like there's no I think there's a right time to go.
It's almost like you can go to Europe or you can go to Disneyland or Disney World.
Like my sister in law did it, but she got like she worked there. She had a great time. She all lived in these big dorms. Everyone was in college.
It was like a college thing. But she like was the pooper scooper behind the animals in the parade.
Like that's what I was like her like her face job was that like, you know, some people like to be like Pluto.
She got to be, you know, the person who picks up the poop in the parade.
I went to an information session at my college for the college program and answered a trivia question correctly and got like a antenna topper.
You know, the other pleasure may as well.
But it was some sort of thing where it's like there was no competent like my hand went up immediately.
But they they have their own semester schedule.
So it's like I would have had to missed a semester and missed half of a break. Like it was very it's almost it's almost built to mess up your college life.
Yeah, it's like it because it doesn't work with any other kind like everybody is there.
It's like, oh, yeah, you you mess up a year. Yeah.
And you can do it after you finish your undergraduate.
You can start right after like you can get your degree and then that summer like do the college program, even if you're out of college.
But then at that point, I was kind of like, no, I did internships in L.A.
And I have a lot of friends out there and I think I'll just go right out there.
But yeah, I mean, I would love to like work in the like the if you could imagine years like that kind of level, that would be like the dream.
That's what this is. This is just an ad for us to like, hey, guys, let us in.
Like we got ideas to like it would be me.
I would just love to see that like that to me is like because again, we can make a better pleasure island.
We would never make a Jessica Rabbit themed store like you would.
You know what? That's not going to be that's not going to run the life of this park.
Sure. You know, I a store for Jessica Rabbit.
That was like the third piece of the puzzle.
There was like the pleasure island as Pinocchio, the fun of the pleasure island backstory plaques and then also the massive Jessica Rabbit Idol.
Yes.
And that very briefly was above the Jessica Rabbit store that didn't seem like it lasted long, but sold like sexy T-shirts and like lingerie with Jessica Rabbit on it, which is insane to say.
Yeah, yeah. It's it's all like a comp.
I assume I didn't read this, but this from other other stories about all this stuff.
It's a compromise between the imagineers, probably like the sales department for merchandise and then just like corporate.
So like I feel like it's all everyone's compromising.
So like the imagineers, I'm assuming because we know Joe Rody is an imagineer behind the Avengers Club and he's a guy who did Avatar land.
He's a guy who did the Guardians.
Right. Alani. He's very he loves these backstories and stuff.
So that's Alani has like Kiki like I met Kiki at Alani.
Alani is a Kiki is just like a Hawaiian woman who is yes.
Yeah. And you go to Kiki's house.
That's where the kids like have a thing and Kiki does breakfast and it's like and there's a story about Kiki.
Kiki is a Disney character. She is in the mythology.
I met Kiki. I have a picture with Kiki.
Sure. You know, but how do they teach you about when do you get accustomed to Kiki?
Do they send you a video or something? Kiki is it's sort of like where were you?
Of course, this is Kiki's house. Like it was like you like you like catching up.
Is it like Duffy the Disney? It's like hey Duffy, you love him.
Yeah, because they have like a they have a great thing there where you can like they will babysit your children from like eight in the morning to nine at night or later.
Yeah. And you could do that.
And I saw many people drop off the kids. We didn't do that.
We just would go there for family play every morning from eight in the morning to nine thirty.
And then Kiki would be running family play.
And, you know, and you think, all right, because Kiki's house and oh, well, so Kiki's house and you go in Kiki's house and you can go up the stairs.
And you can go up the stairwell to her room and you put your ear to her door.
You could hear her and her husband and they're talking like, oh, we're so excited.
The kids are coming today. It's like a pre-recorded thing.
And they're like they have like a whole conversation, Kiki and her husband about what they're going to do.
So like that's yes, we got to watch the electrical bill this month.
It's just way too high running the air this much.
There should be like one day when they play of like again, kids are coming over again.
We shouldn't disturb Kiki today.
This is all news to me, this mythology.
Do you do you think because I am like I am a legitimate Disney World fan and theme park fan, but I think I am because I don't work there.
Like I never worked there. Well, we talked to a past guest, Jenny Nicholson, about it.
I worked there and she said she was exactly the same coming in and coming out. OK.
So I mean, I think it's probably different for any of everyone.
But the first script I ever wrote in L.A. was called Enchanted Kingdom, and it was a Disney World based script.
And I'm like it's the one thing I wish I always got to do.
Like I read all those books and stuff like I like it because there's like a book called like Mouse Secrets or something like that.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. What's the what's the other tragic kingdom?
Mouse tales. I think it's two books of mouse tales. Yeah.
By the way, I feel like you guys often on the show reference some sites that I'm not familiar with.
You don't say them by name. What are the sites that what are the sites?
Oh, yeah. I see that on these Disney sites. I don't know what those Disney sites are that you guys go to shout them out.
Is mice chat or mouse plan? I was I was mouse planet was a godsend for this.
They had a lot of Pleasure Island, Screamscape, theme park.
University played a lot into Hard Rock Park.
Yes, there's WDW magic dot com, which I go to for the boards.
That's the real gossip. There's a couple.
There's a couple of real gossip pounds on that message board and you get some good tidbits from these people.
Those are the basic ones. I think then the podcast we always talk about.
Yes. Yeah. Jim Hill. I mean, I'm all on that.
Listen to Lentus. Oh, yeah. I'm all I'm all on board.
I have like sometimes two to three Disney podcasts.
Season pass. Oh, I haven't heard season passes. Very good.
I see. Like sometimes I always like the things they always shut me off about Disney podcast.
Ultimately, there's a lot of them that are really hard to listen to from a just audio standpoint.
Yeah, like Golden Shoe Horseshoe Review. I was like, I'm kind of interested in this, but I'm just having a.
So everyone's someone's always calling in on Skype.
You know, they're never in that same room together.
Yeah, I was going to tell you that there's a great one.
I was on a podcast and they challenged me to they challenged me to like they they find out what you like and then they go.
OK, well, I gave them like 10 10 things and then they surprised me with what they were going to test me on.
They test me on my Walt Disney Land knowledge and I did very well.
But I met this guy who was like the expert on Disneyland and his his Instagram tag is exploring Disney World.
And he has all this really cool stuff. He runs the Walt Museum.
So he will occasionally post pictures that you've never seen of like Walt's apartment on Main Street in Walt Disneyland.
Like he you know, a lot of times there's normal stuff, too, but he will do some cool stuff from an Instagram thing.
I mean, I'm on Jolly Poppins and stuff like that, too.
Wait, I think I. Yep, that's it. Yeah, I follow this guy. Yeah, this guy's real good.
I can't believe you have you have different ones. Jolly Poppins. I don't know. Yeah, I don't know that one.
Wow. I used to follow a guy and then it depressed me.
He goes to Disney. He goes to Disneyland every single day and would take a picture and he was going for the biggest consecutive record of Disney.
Like the like unbreakable record. And then it was a sort of like, I got to stop following this guy.
Just say I don't know why. I just don't know. Like because it didn't seem fun anymore.
It seemed like it seemed like day 4000, you know, or like whatever it was.
I was like, I can't since he was like the smile wasn't real anymore.
It didn't feel like it was like, well, then when it becomes a job, like it's like you're just like, I like got to go to Disneyland today.
Just like that seems like the other part of it. That's good to hear that she likes Jenny.
You like to go in it. Yeah, yeah, I think so. I think it's possible to come.
I think it's all the line to ride is like not losing the joy and the silliness of it and not because you do get a sense from people on the message boards a lot that they are that they're they've they've gotten cynical.
Some of them and they're so like they're mad that things are changing and they're eyeing every like, you know, a piece of paint that's scratched off and they like, I don't know, you got to like have a little bit of blinders on.
Remember, this is all stupid and fun. It's just fun to incorporate this into your adult life and we'll take it.
So yeah, like I mean, to me, the place I'd like to hang out though is that Disney bar where they have all the name tags up on the wall.
Have you heard about that? That's in Orlando. I've heard of this. Yeah, I've been. It's like I've never been either.
I don't even know where it is. It's basically all the former employees whenever they that's like their watering hole, which is prominently in the script that I wrote.
But but but but when you retire, your name tag goes up like on the wall.
So apparently the way it sounds is like it's just covered in name tags.
When I was in City Walk in Orlando last year, they told me that all the people all the Disney people party at City Walk.
That's where you go to party, just to party on site.
They go. Yeah, they leave the mouse to go to City Walk.
I found a TripAdvisor post where someone was like, hey, I bought I was going to book a trip to Disney and stay by Pleasure Island and mostly like eat at the restaurants and down to Disney and go to the clubs.
I found out they're all closed. Like what else is there doing or land?
And like immediately two people wrote back. Yeah, you're looking for City Walk now.
Like what you want now is just go to City Walk like that is probably what you're the best approximation of what you want.
They really they struck back like Disney got Disney was winning in this nightlife game.
And I think now they're losing it. Maybe maybe Disney Springs will eventually take the metal bag.
I think what's interesting with Disney Springs and what is slowly happening to downtown Disney in Anaheim is that it's like becoming like a fashionable L.A.
sort of like an L.A. or Brooklyn neighborhood was like two, three years ago because it's like, all right, there's going to be an intense milkshake place.
There's going to be a cocktail bar. There's going to be a brew pot like it's all sort of stuff.
I think they realize if they put places like those VR places in like because the void is awesome and they should almost have, you know, they once they are able to have multiple experiences in, then it even be better.
Like, you know, it's when they have the Ghostbusters one, the Hulk one and the Terminator and Star Wars ones like that would be like, but like I think what they want to do is get people there.
But you don't have to go to the park, but you have to do that by.
I don't like that restaurant. Is it KTAL like that one?
It's all.
Yeah, I don't like that one.
I like it. They just need to get kind of like revamp.
I think they have to continue to revamp that place a little bit like it's all it's this odd.
None of them are actually that great. The best that some of those dented Disney restaurants are like, well, it's better than the park.
It's close to like a good restaurant. You'd go to 20 minutes north of here in LA.
But like when they put in the bowling alley, the bowling and Disney Springs has this to those are like I think Disney Springs is the right direction for Disney.
It's like, yeah, good, legitimately good restaurants, bars where you can kind of bar hop, which is like, but it's respectively.
Nice looking architecture, nice looking architecture, free parking parking garage.
Huge, huge benefit. Big deal, I think, for the locals.
Yeah. And then you have like the nice bowling alley. It's, you know, based on the the Incredibles or whatever it is.
You know, it's like splits or whatever V8.
So it's kind of got that 60s. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it's it's all getting there. The bowling alley is a good step.
Every time they do stuff like that's more like like kids, like, for instance, the Videopolis out here, they closed once violence started erupting in the parking lot.
And a very similar incident. I found an article from 1989.
Videopolis East also a stabbing happened very early.
I remember this. Yeah, because I remember there was a nervousness that there were like that.
That means I used to bring it back in a very big way that there was a little bit of an unsavory nature to it.
Now, when I look back on it going like to ever feel unsafe.
And I did. And I do remember like the line to get in was intense because it's like imagine every line to get into a bar.
But that was to get into the pier or whatever it was, the war.
So you're on the line to get into like as a child, you're still on the line to get into the bar or it's like the line getting into Disneyland or Disney World.
But like when it opens, but is all people ready to party? Yes. And that energy, I always felt a little it was intense.
Yeah. I was 20 was the 21 under club in Pleasure Island. Yes. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And that was the stabbing. I have the article here. I mean, I don't need to read from it.
I mean, we get the gist. A guy got stabbed a couple of people.
But then I also I didn't find this maybe someone else did it because they quickly changed the name of Videopolis, Videopolis East to Cage.
OK. And that's the one I know nothing. And then they changed it like pretty quickly in a couple of years to Atrax.
Oh, I remember Atrax. Yeah.
No, that you know, that to me was I would like like my big move was when I got older, walk in, do like a circle through it and then like walk out and then like head to the adventures.
I don't know what I was looking for there. I didn't know.
Like maybe my like high school mind is like, well, I'll pick up.
I'll either pick up some girls. I literally just do a full circle through here without stopping or drinking, you know, and I don't know what I did.
I didn't talk to anybody like but I wanted to look and see what it was like. They had a roller skating place there.
Oh, yeah. That was the one like the roller skating was on the second floor, second floor.
And the backstory on that one is also it's saying that's where Mr. Pleasure wanted to like built his experimental aircraft spruce goose kind of aircraft like.
And that that leads me to the fact that a lot of these clubs would change names or change themes. And so the plaques would get taken down or the backstories would just never get updated.
And so that all reality started to fall apart, the funniest of which to me is the neon armadillo.
The country western bar eventually became the B.E.T. soundstage club, which that seems like a conservative meme like made into life of like our honky tonk became a hip hop club.
What is happening to this island of bars? What happened?
Also, the neon armadillo is just like, again, reading spending hours reading all this, I had to still remind myself like, OK, yeah, that was the country one.
And the backstory was that a family of armadillos they found in that abandoned building like it's so so many steps.
It was abandoned. And then when they came back, it was full of armadillos, armadillos creepily similar to that part of Discovery Island that was full of vultures.
Yeah, they stuck them in a shed and they all died. It's crazy. It's one of the strangest pockets in the world.
Absolutely. So real quick back to this pleasure island. So I found this Facebook group called Pleasure Island Memories.
And I don't is it legal for me just to say things that people say in a public place? I won't use their names, but they'll know.
Where are the audio when you say that? So you were talking about the roller skating rink. So what's that? It's XCFR Rockin Roller Drome.
And when Pleasure Island was announced, there's a different club called Zephyr Rockin Roller Drome.
All one word and kind of like the Guy Ritchie. So many index cards on white and white boards.
I mean, there are terrible names. I mean, yeah, you want to go to the XCFR ZF Rock and Roll good time. It's Drome.
No, I'm going to the Portobello Yacht Club. Mannequin's Dance Palace is just an eye.
And they all seem like they were also like hitting very weird music.
It was like, oh, yeah, we need we need a new wave club. We need a techno trance club country. Country makes sense.
Country makes 100 percent sense. But like New Wave and techno trance are like very niche.
It's like why don't you do like a country and like a rock club and like just like again, it's like too many things.
Yes, they're trying to hit every demographic. They're trying to hit everything.
Mannequin's also filled with the scariest phrase I've ever heard. Human mannequins.
Yeah. Which are like mirror suits. They all look like something out of American Horror Story.
And the music at mannequins from all the videos I saw seems like horseshit.
It's like Sub Hataway. What kind of music is this? I'll debate that.
I kind of like the music in mannequins. The few videos I've listened to.
It's insane. And there's a whole don't don't don't don't don't.
It's very like not as good Mortal Kombat or something.
Had a very cool light show. Had a very cool light show. It starts off with a very like floor lit up.
Right. That was the whole thing. Like there was just so many lights everywhere.
It seemed overwhelming. Again, the theme of this episode is Pleasure Island was overwhelming in numerous ways.
Except with restaurants. There was not a lot of restaurants.
At the start of mannequins, at least for the thing, either would be like a calming, calming female voice.
It was like, good evening. In the next hour, we will take you into the world, a world of music, spirit, meditation.
Take a deep breath and relax. And then like, boy, I mean, it's it's bad, but it's also very good.
So what what were you pulling from the memories? So pleasure island memory.
So what's very great about this and I everyone should go on this message board if you if you have any fondness for this place.
If you're still on Facebook as you. Yeah.
Even though I claim to get off of it like two episodes ago, I totally forgot because we recorded it weeks prior.
And then I said, who cares? And then I don't know. You need it for this show.
You need to find the dirt. Yeah. You know, stay. I'm staying on it.
I'm so sorry. I will never lie to you guys again. Anyway, so pleasure island memories.
And what's great about this is that it's it seems like it's mostly former employees.
So there'll be a thread, for instance, that just said like, hey, biggest celebrity you ever waited on a pleasure island.
And this is like 50 long, 500 comments long.
So, I mean, I just picked out some of the greatest in the roller skating reminds me.
So somebody just wrote Michael Jackson was the biggest roller skating with Eisner and George Lucas.
And so this is full. So I'm going to quickly run down some of the other ones here.
I was talking to you. So somebody says, yeah, I was at the comedy warehouse one night.
And Robin Williams and Bobcat Goldthwait showed up with their wives and they got Williams got up and did about 20 minutes of stand up and improv based on the drink.
The wobbly Wally that was sold on the island. Whoa, that's amazing.
Then Bobcat got up and joined him. He dropped the bomb and all the Disney suits almost passed out.
Somebody just lists all the celebrities that came through here. Michael Jackson, George Lucas, John Lasseter.
Bobcat Goldthwait, Dorothy Hamill, Taylor Negron, Larry Miller, Demi Moore, Howie Mandel, Al Jarrou, Mary Tyler Moore, Charles Barkley.
So somebody's got a fun anecdote about Leslie Nielsen. He says, surely whatever that one is fine.
Multiple people, multiple like more than three say Jimmy Carter.
And then someone has an anecdote. President Jimmy Carter was using the upstairs at eight tracks and he sat right next to the DJ booth just smiling and singing along the whole time.
Whoa, songs of his presidency. Yeah, 70s and 80s. That's it.
He's up there. That means there's secret service. Yeah, of course. Eight tracks in Pleasure Island.
Don't you feel like it's like Jimmy Carter went there and then like whatever his itinerary is like now you go to the nightlife. You go to Fulton's Crab House, which is like an old riverboat or whatever.
And then you go to eight tracks. Steam ships. I can imagine them probably saying, I have dinner. What kind of music do you like? We have every we have everything you want.
Yeah. Oh, I don't know. I like stuff in the 70s. Great. We have the club for you. Jimmy Carter. I like techno trance. I want to see the mannequins with reflective mannequins. That sounds trippy.
I need to go get some souvenirs for my daughters. Meet me at Doodles. So somebody just wrote OJ.
Oh, man. I enjoyed speaking with OJ two weeks before he committed the murders. I was going to say right after he got out of jail. No, it's not recent.
So I mean, first after the trial. This, this, this, I love this. I was again getting nostalgic for a time because all these people worked there and they loved it. Like that's the commonality.
Can I ask one quick question? Of course. Do you think that the layout of Pleasure Island was so insane that it drove OJ Simpson to murder? Like he was carrying the weight of it.
Like it doesn't make any sense. The signs don't make any sense. He's trying to make someone. I want to know. I want to be Merriweather Pleasure. I can do it right.
I think he went and he got some bad advice at the Adventurers Club. That's my guess. Oh, no.
There was a comedy warehouse joke about like, you know, like, like Wanda kill your damn wife. And then he took it seriously.
It's like, oh, yeah. All right. When I first was there and I was probably there when it first opened, it was a good vibe.
I mean, we're talking, we're breaking it down because it doesn't really make sense. And ultimately, the end of the day, I guess their thought was who cares if it makes sense.
It's it's places where you can dance places, you can drink places where you can like and they have like a little bit of the theming towards the end of the island, which is the New Year's every night.
And but it was for me as a kid, it was super exotic and it felt cool and and not dangerous, but different than Disney.
It didn't feel like clean, you know, I'm sure it was, you know, if I was there now, I think it was a good hang.
And then it fell off hard. And I only saw that part in the daytime.
If you went every year, do you have any idea when the turn started to happen?
I think I remember when like when more shops are coming, like you like when you feel it, see that first like Sunglass Hut or something like that.
Like, you know, it's going to get shut down for like a fully like some like like, yeah, like a thing like that.
The Sunglass Hut was the harbinger of death.
Well, I think like I mean, they expanded to that, like what they would call downtown Disney Westside with the Virgin Megastore and the Cirque du Soleil and all that.
And like that was a very different concept.
And then also there was the, you know, the shopping village downtown Disney area and then Pleasure Island kind of just in between.
And then like I think it was 2004 I came across was when they're like, OK, no admission to get on the island.
It's just admission per club now. And then they dial back.
They stopped doing the midnight every night celebration, which they did right when it closed as like a, you know, send off.
But even like an adventurous club, they always referenced one character.
And then on the last night he appeared, but he never appeared.
It was like, you know, yeah, I met your mother. Yeah, like kind of.
Yeah, like they were like, and he came on the last night. He was finally there.
Although that has a weird story like the adventurous club closed and then like one year later open for one night for like a special ticketed event that I think like WDW radio organized.
God knows how much those individual tickets cost. But yeah, it was the full thing.
And the Avengers Club, it seemed like towards the end, the reputation became like shows are still great characters still great.
The way they've cut back is they've dialed back on the waitstaff. It's impossible to get a drink.
I see. I think I remember trying to go there and it was like less shows.
I think when I went there, it was like you could go in there like eight and stay for a long time.
And I think now is eight o'clock is when we do our adventures club.
And then it was like over by like that. It's just a nine thirty or something.
I think no, I think again, my memory of this might be bad, but I remember being so excited to go there.
Like, no, no, no, it's done for the night. Like it's done for the night at a certain time. It wasn't like, oh, OK.
It wasn't just like and it's improv until midnight, you know, which probably makes sense.
It probably was for sure. You know, like, yeah, let's not keep this.
So I mean, even if they're not paying equity rates, they still have to pay those people decent money.
Yeah. If this were in the park, I think it would be maybe still there.
Like it like this is this to me is the outlier of all the obviously of all the stuff because the most thing that's the most.
But like if it was in the park right now, either park, either coast, I feel like it would be like reservation only.
And especially now that the parks are so insanely crowded versus 2008, 2008, everything was going downhill.
We talked about you get a pass for 200 bucks. Right now it's like like 500 times the price.
I feel like if it had just stuck it out or if it was in a location like inside the park, the adventure club could have hung.
I mean, the venture, the debt, the venture club is the thing that just was in the wrong spot at the wrong time.
And but I feel like I do. I do believe that people don't want this experience from Disney Ventures Club.
Yes. You know, but I even think like Disney Quest was that went down like that should never gone down.
You are a place that is full of children.
You're saying pay 25 bucks and play every video game you can play.
You're in a giant pinball machine. You're in.
I played the first the most fun I've ever had.
There was like they had the Star Wars game where like the first cool Star Wars game where you had the lightsaber and you could play that for free all night.
And it was like that. You know, I don't know.
I feel like they just couldn't people that weren't there for nightlife or kids weren't allowed to go there.
I think there was some not enough of the audience was like making it out because this if you don't know the Disney layout, this is this whole mall zone is this separate area as opposed to downtown Disney or the area outside of Paris.
It's not like or CityWalk. It's not connected to the part you got to specifically get on a bus and go to this different area.
And maybe if you only had three nights or whatever, you're not going to take a bunch of your time to go find this.
But if it was right outside the Magic Kingdom, right, that would be easier.
I mean, the Disney Quest, I also think is 10 to whatever 20 years ahead of its time.
Because I think Disney Quest now Disney Quest was not when I went to Disney Quest, I was so hyped about it.
And it was a letdown with all the stuff like the VR for the medical for the for the magic carpet thing was not that cool and all the other things like water rafting.
Yeah, you're just on a thing because as a kid, I was like the VR is amazing.
I'm so excited about it. And it just it fell short. Whereas the void is lives up to for the most.
The void is the future that the void that we saw, you couldn't still be running that in five years like they're going to have to keep updating it.
And I think that the void, though, is it is a simple maze that they all do is give you a new VR thing to watch because then they can reconfigure the walls.
But the quality of the footage and stuff, they'll have to keep. Oh, I think they're rated.
I think I know that the void has like literally like five or six things in the.
Oh, yeah, they've got the expansion plans.
Yeah, I think. But like Disney Quest never changed.
Yeah. Wow. They've made the Terminator Hulk like it's all like it's they're not like going they're not going like do a virtual reality experience.
Like, no, no, no. You know, this world, you're going to now be in this world.
That's really smart. I do think they could do it.
I do think of Disney Quest were like starting now and they had like five experiences on the void level.
I think it would last. It would have like I guess the Disney Quest honestly lasted a long time, but that would have wowed everybody.
I didn't come out of Disney Quest even as a kid going, wow, I like playing arcade games, but that was the best almost part of it.
All the stuff that was supposed to be amazing fell very short.
It was like it was like sort of like the scope was big.
It was like, you know, like like whatever that stupid pinball machine was where like the Mighty Ducks pinball machine where you're in the pinball machine.
It's like it's like all right. It was fine.
It was like, yeah, but like I feel like, oh man, I just lost my.
Oh, I mean, I bet you Star Wars land will have a lot of the themed hangout areas.
But I think this is going to make a comeback like things like the void, which are simple and you're it doesn't take up much space.
But I know you guys are talking about like shield and a couple of episodes ago.
But the idea, like if you created like the collectors, if they made that, like if the new Adventures Club was attached to like the Guardians of the Galaxy, right.
And it just like it was like you're on nowhere.
You're in this weird club of all these cool things.
And, you know, and then you're like these aliens that you don't have.
They can all do funny things and sing and you would be it would I mean, I would, you know, but it would be fun.
It would be the most popular thing. I think I said it on the show that idea also at Dr. Stranges Sanctum Sanctorum.
A magic. It's like a magic club. It's also like there's weird spirits.
There's people coming out of doors and dimensions like that's that would be the hottest place to go.
Well, and at Disney's Hollywood Studios, it seemed like they were so close the way the rumor blogs were.
It seemed like they were so close to pulling the trigger on putting a bar at the exit of Tower of Terror in Florida.
They have a huge like unused like storage area by the store there where it would have been like a smaller bar like Trader Sam style.
But like a bar that would have made sense for this, like the hotel bar for the Hollywood Tower Hotel.
And that would have been a huge hit. Now, like that also would have driven a lot of traffic to a dead end in the park.
But honestly, it could have helped. It could have helped with people complaining about how like there's so much construction in this park.
There's not enough to do. It's like, well, if you had a fun bar there, that would have been something to do.
Well, that's I think that's the thing they should be playing to.
And ultimately, it's I think it's liquor. Bars are better than dance clubs or anything like that, because it's sort of like for the people like us.
It's like, oh, I would like to go to and sit like that same. I won't go to Trader Sam's.
Like I want to I will go for the like give me the really good Disney experience in a theme bar.
And I'm way like it's like it's it's so much more fun.
Having a drink at Trader Sam's is more fun than yes than going to, you know, Rosie O'Grady's, you know, you know,
or like, you know, like how much people like Clifton's here in L.A.
Like how fun it is to be like to be having a drink, settle in and there's you're in some weird forest.
Yeah, people I think appreciate those themed experiences more.
And maybe it's just I'm sure there's a cynical angle of it of like millennials never put away childish things.
We still just want to go to Disney World.
But I wonder if now the future will be it all needs to be property based.
Like you can't just be like a Ventures Club is like if you put a Ventures Club next to the Jungle Cruise,
then it's like, you know, the way they have Aladdin's Oasis in Disneyland.
It's like, you know, oh, this is something that feels like you have to really connect it like the hotel bar to the hotel.
It's like, I think or it's just got to be Marvel Star Wars.
Yeah. If there's an adventurous club in the Rock's Jungle Cruise movie.
Yes. Then the adventures club could be built anywhere. And if that's a hit.
That's an interesting idea. But Paul, do you know about CSEA, the Society of Explorers and Adventurers?
No. OK, this is the Mike. Correct me if I get anything wrong.
This is the the continuity that ties together all of Disney's like explore.
Like so the Adventurers Club, the Jungle Cruise, Harrison Hightower, who is the basis for Tower of Terror in Japan.
And he looks he's he's modeled after Imagineer, Joe Rody.
Yeah. Oh, wow. Portrait of him.
They and it shows up in little play like there's C stuff in Trader Sam's like. Oh, cool.
Is that Alani part of it? Is it?
There's got to be some C something in a lot.
I will tell you that Alani bummed me out because I I am again, as a dad, I was like, this is great.
It's like a Disney hotel. It didn't have anything that was like it didn't have enough theming for me.
They went to like they went to a hotel, right?
Like they're too like they didn't want to like it's goofy Hawaii or something.
It's like it's kind of like the big. So it's basically like I think the conceit is Mickey's on vacation.
So like I mean, like that, like so like he's walking around in cargo shorts, you know, and and then goofy is like hanging out by the pool.
So like that's like so you see the characters are interacting with the characters there.
Kiki's house is the kids thing.
So if I didn't have kids, I wouldn't be able to go in Kiki's house.
And rightfully so, I'm not advocating for that.
I'm kind of sad I can't see Kiki's house.
But and by the way, I was really excited because I've heard about Never Neverland Club and that's supposed to be like amazing for kids to like that's a Walt Disney World.
Oh, yeah. Where it's like, oh, I did that. Yeah.
So but they didn't have anything like they had no cool restaurants.
By the way, Trader Sam's is the perfect place to put in a lot. Oh, right. Yeah. Yeah.
No, it's it's hotel restaurants on the most mediocre level.
It's like fine hotel restaurant. You could put that restaurant in any hotel and you'd be like, you know, huh.
And and I was like, give me something. Give me like they have a lot of boats, you know, hanging from the thing.
It's it's you know, it's nicely done. But there's no there's no and I actually the thing that was really bummed out about was their luau.
I've been to many a luau and oh, yeah. You know, and that's that again just speaks to my like theme park love.
Like I'm always like, well, we should go to that luau. I mean, I think there'll be something there.
And like, no, why? And we went to the luau there.
And it was like, like pretty unspectacular, like Disney, you should be doing the best luau in Hawaii, like because you could afford it.
Like you could just like there should be like fireworks and fire dancers and this and like and it was big should talk before he gets cooked.
Yeah. Wait, don't. Yeah. I thought it was the most I was surprised that the lack of like nothing for the Disney people there at all.
And when you're I assume you're paying like exorbitantly more than the tip.
Well, we use all of our points. So we had a we had a sweet three bedroom place.
Oh, good deal. Did your family ever go to the other the Disney timeshare hotel like Vero Beach or the one in the Carolinas?
No, yes. My dad just went there. Yeah. My dad went to the Carolinas because it's awesome. He's like, it's great. It's really good. He's talking very highly.
There's no rides and shit. Yeah. My parents were like kind of into like they were like, that idea sounds good to me.
My brother and we were kids were like, there's no rides. And now to me, I'm like, oh, that sounds great.
Just a Disney hotel in the middle of nowhere. Sure. Yeah. Well, then, you know, but it's like to me, you want some of those.
I don't know. You want some of those things like I remember being so excited when I was a big Universal Studios fans because I loved Islands of Adventure and it was so fun.
I just went back there recently. I was so excited. Like I had a day in I basically like detoured my day.
I had to make sure I got to do Universal again because I hadn't done it in years.
And it was right before the Jimmy Fallon ride opened. So I didn't get to go on that. But like they had some cool stuff there.
I did like the Max Pass and Harry Potter land is amazing. But I remember like Universal's like we're going to do our hotels.
Every one of them is going to be themed. So one floor will be the psycho theme and one floor will be like it was every floor is going to be a different movie.
I was like, that's awesome. Like I would love that. And then they just never did. Yeah.
I think now they're going back to like trying to do more stuff with like Volcano Bay. And I think I think I heard her talk of a Harry Potter theme.
They've rumored that it seems like it because they're doing it with Star Wars.
That's going to be amazing where you don't even see daylight. You just have the windows.
Like you'll easily go insane. Oh, I mean, I'm like I can't wait to justify to my wife why I need to go to Orlando by myself unless I can get my kid into Star Wars real quick.
Yeah, more of them than there used to be. Yeah, you got to get in.
But the only people who do seem to tell is great. In my opinion was Legoland. They have like they have like a every floor is a different thing.
So one floor is like the Indiana Jones like adventure floor in your room has like monkeys on the wall and like it's every room is fully themed out.
Like and there's a special safe there and there's clues around the hotel.
And if you get the clues right, you open up the safe and there's a gift in the safe. It's like really, really well done.
I'm like more of that. I want to think Great Wolf Lodge has like little adventures and games.
Oh, really play like yeah, there's the other some like in or like through the hallways of the that's kind of fun. Yeah, I like that.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, so I mean what we're finding, I feel like is there's like this fun ideas in a lot of in some of this Pleasure Island stuff that maybe has not been capitalized on to its full extent.
I think like yes, some some new if it has to be an IP, whatever, but the general notion of the of the Adventures Club in a place where there's like a lot of odd little different shows and experiences and skill and like puppets clattering around that puppets are cool.
Oh, the animatronics puppets in the Adventures Club were great.
Well, but what if you like if you really just committed to the idea of an adult playground, but you don't try to be like it's almost like could you make Chuck E Cheese for adults and like that's like like that would be the perfect kind of thing.
It's like where you're where adults can kind of be kids without kids. I don't know like what that middle ground is. It's like that's what you want.
Ultimately, I think that it's kind of the odd ones. We may be the odd one. We're odd, but we're getting less odd.
Yeah, that's the greatest generation dies off. I think we're more common is that we're all stuck in our child like our childhood.
Well, that's what I because I pleasure Island totally made sense at the time and it made sense for Disney World because like I seen a lot of the like 70s and 80s like Disney World Resort and the promotional material emphasized the resort stuff and they were angling for like couples and stuff to like come without kids.
Even we've got nice restaurants. We've got dancing and and shows and all this sort of thing. So it made sense.
But now people want seem to want something more and whether that is I think part of some of that was people want more bang for their buck like after a couple recessions.
Yeah, and that that sort of thing. I mean pleasure Island closed right around or right before the recession. But like I was just saw like a blog post about like new Disney afternoon mugs in the park.
I was like, what? What is this? And I'm like, oh, they're to cater to adults. Now they're not building nightclubs. They're making mugs that you look like you would find at Goodwill from your childhood.
Well, that's the newest thing. I feel like everything is retro. I bought an Epcot sweatshirt that I love that it was like looks like it was like it's designed like the top from the drawer full of like retro Epcot.
Like stairs. I'll show you.
Off guys. So impressed.
I do think you're right. I think that is becoming more and more common. But now he just said they're getting into escape rooms now. So that's a big oh yeah. And so to me it's like if you had like like I like I like the scary ones like a scary walk through like you like a maze or some sort of like jumpy out thing.
Like a scary one like that. You had an escape room. You had the void. You had like like that sometimes like that kind of like more mature experiences. But they're all fun. Yeah, I would. I think that would be great.
And like you could still do a comedy club. Some version of that. I actually do think like the improv stuff is probably very fun for a lot of people that are there for like a vacation.
Oh, this is they made it a rare. They probably are not pursuing improv typically. Yeah, it's like maybe the one of the only times they see something like that.
Well, you and I said like we got like that was my end. That was amazing. Yeah, that was the first live cut that and like a cruise ship like a topical review on a cruise ship where like the first things I saw in terms of live comedy.
Maybe Disney Springs needs to just exist. That was Disney Springs and maybe a new Pleasure Island must rise somewhere on the grounds of the Disney World Resort or maybe we're like we're River Country used to be.
I think this is Anaheim. That's what I think you do. I think you start it in Anaheim. Okay, because I think because I think I know you're saying there's more land there, but I guess I think you rip up that that strip and you build out from the void like you sprinkles is good.
That's good. Like the void is good. Like start doing more of that. They got a whole restaurant. That's Adventurers Club. Yeah, two point. And you have a bowling alley there. It's like I feel like you have to make it a place where people will be like, do you want to go down to like, we can go down to Disneyland.
We got VR thing. We can go play go go bowling go. If you can like name like three things you could do right now to go down there to do the void.
Well, I'm going to the park because I'm not going to go down. I'm not going to go down there for one thing. Right. They're putting like two micro breweries that like to like a ballast point is doing a restaurant brew pub.
And then there's that black tap. Something like that. The desserts. Isn't that crazy milkshakes with like a slice of cake in it. Oh, yeah. And then they're building a massive new hotel like on top of where the ESPN zone and stuff.
And that seems like this like it's a four diamonds, triple A, four diamond. It seems like they're trying to actually build a luxury luxury hotel. So yeah. Yeah. But more tent pole jams.
Well, I obviously I want themed experiences everywhere you can possibly fit them. Hey, shout out to Glendale for that. You can go to the void and you can get on that trolley.
It's like my pitch is that everywhere in the world be like this rides everywhere. I want I want them. I mean, more church street stations. I think that's what we're saying.
It's like how can we find like that? That is I think what people want. It's like it's like almost like fake community. It's like you like this is a place where you can go.
We can knock off like five things and not have to park one spot and you can have when you make a night of it. Right. It's a little we all need to like we just we need some capital.
We all need to start a sale company. Use the earnings from that to become the new pleasure. The new grand fun Meisters.
Don't you think I mean I just that to me the simplest thing would have been just to have a guy like always there every night like I'm very well the pleasure and this and tonight we're going to like his and his whole thing is you have to live every night.
Like it's the last night of the year because tomorrow is a new day and that's the thing. And so we're all going to make a resolution like you just it's like a simple themeing like he just he's like almost like a spiritual guru like and we're going to have this experience.
You're going to laugh. You're going to dance. You're going to this you know you have like a near death experience on New Year's. He was like sailing lightning struck his ship and he almost died but he made it back and he knew when he got back to port.
I will live every day like it's New Year's Eve because that's the most exciting part of the year because on New Year's Eve anything can happen in the new year.
I would like it if they would do put these plaques outside the businesses in Disney Springs quite frankly if there was a plaque outside the unique low and it was like well as you know his son was you know messing around with some textiles and we found them in this place and we decided to sew them into t-shirts here in the Coca Cola store.
Like we I we could still do that. Hire us to write these. Yeah we'll write for everything there. What is there what's those pretzels there. Backstories everywhere. I have one quick question for you rabbit.
You know the comedy the comedy warehouse has done reunions you said the adventures club came back for one night only. If you guys if everybody here if suddenly Pleasure Island was back you could go for just one night and you can only there's only time for one club.
Which one how old how old am I. It's you right now. Okay. Yes. Pleasure Island exists and you because it was twenty two I would say mannequins.
Yeah.
I think I'm mannequins today. That's my kind of music that I really like the light show. I guess it was the one on watching of the Disney in room entertainment just like mannequins. What the fuck. Oh yeah.
When when the episode we were talking about that that watching that Disney in room TV was my favorite. I literally made a big an adult swim commercial based on an in room like hotel commercial because I just I got like obsessed with it was like I got obsessed with Steve Wins version.
Yes. And I made a whole like it was it. So the idea was that your TV at midnight or whenever it aired just came I was like welcome to the so and so spot. It's like it's on YouTube. I don't remember it's called but it's it but it looks just like a hotel screen and then it just like it's like this is what we have this we have this we have this and it's a crazy. I mean I don't want to build up too much but it was it was like something that I'm obsessed with. I was like oh I love like yeah I love that like soft music playing.
It's like impossible to convey the appeal of this to somebody who doesn't just naturally get it. Yeah I feel blessed to know so many people now like those in room. Oh yeah. It's hypnotic. I mean I don't know what the guess it's the music and there's something comforting.
And I was like clearly the theme is like specific like location specific experiences and I like that this is a video I can only watch in this hotel. Yeah the only place that it exists and occasionally you'll hear like Mario Lopez chime in and be like hey we sat down with everybody from Slender Man and to answer your question.
I mean it has to be. Yeah I got it right. Yeah so I'm taking a venture because mine was going to be a venture scope I'm taking it off the table because I feel like that's my go to. I'm trying to like challenge myself. What's your number to AMC 24 movie theater.
Yeah. Big awning. I saw the Santa Claus there as a wonderful place. I think I would go to I think I would be really interested in going to the roller skating place. I feel like that like that to me feels really unique in the sense of like yeah I would be curious to see what that is about.
On the night that Michael Jackson was skating with Michael Eisner and George Lucas I mean that's the answer. I want to be Michael is also brought up in that through I'll send this thread to you obviously but Michael has brought up so much in this thread like Michael was a pleasure island nonstop.
That's perfect guys of course he was one of the mannequins. Oh yeah.
Very possible. Another thing I said the rock and roll the rock and roller drum at some point turned into the rock and roll beach club. Yes. And look up as many in sync references on this episode you can look up an in sync like looking for a record deal concert from 1995 in that venue in the beach club and they and they're so young.
Oh my God they are they're so tiny is forever good but the like they do a weird like boy bandified version of we can work it out. We can get out we can get out. Life is very short.
Big recommend for somebody on the message board says Joey Fatone hit on me. He asked me out. They turned him down. Do you ever see Joey Fatone's like his home movie theater. No designed it to look like the Death Star. So it's like you enter and it's pretty cool. It's pretty pretty well done.
Have you screened a film personally or no I just thought of some sort of I think I think I think I saw it on like a hotel TV. I was like we went to Joey Paton's. I don't know why I was watching whatever it was. I was just going to mention one thing here which I thought was interesting.
It was another thing another fact about Mary Weather pleasure that they he there's a restaurant called the fireworks factory. Also fireworks. This is a band of fireworks but then they did a good deal with the group cheese who were like we're now I mean at least when I was growing up the group cheese like these big like fireworks people in New York like they just would set off like a ton of and like they did a thing where they would like give them their old fireworks setup. So it's like like the after the cannons were used to do the Macy's day whatever.
Like so the place is like full of like discarded fireworks like paraphernalia to make it look like. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah which all smells great. What a great I also I in my notes I have the drinks menu from the fireworks. Oh yeah. Oh and just just to name a couple. These are explosion themed drinks. You got the detonator daiquiri the you got the 21 rum salute. You got the the bang master and then finally very bizarre name even at the time and the most bizarre today.
The border bomber. Oh my God. Why. And I know we're wrapping up. I will just say one thing I just realized this when you said that thing about the daiquiri I just recently went to the saved by the Bell restaurant that opened up here in L.A. I brought a Weiger and Mike Mitchell the doughboys there because I figured that would be right up there.
That place is incredibly packed there sold out or there have limited availability for the next nine months. That's the right like tone to like again themed great. It's fun. I'm like a medium saved by the Bell family. I know all I think I know all the references I can understand all the menu jokes but I'm like I'm not obsessive but it's like that was great.
Like that's the kind of like that weird. It's like I don't know what that is. I guess it's brand. It's like you know it's a brand and you go there but like I think that would pack them in like if they say by the Bell restaurant in or like in Orlando in Pleasure Island that would work.
I think maybe downtown Disney and all these places need to have spaces that they trade out and like put in. It's like every couple months. Yeah. Disney should embrace the pop up. That's a great idea. They never ended up using the plan for a bar where all the Disney villains drank at.
Oh. Great. Because also like Universal does the horror nights mazes and they put up very crazy elaborate mazes that are themed to like movies and stuff and they do it for what three months. And the in the park works functionally during the day with those mazes. Yeah. It's sort of like that's you can do it. Yeah. I also feel like the fact that Disney has had Star Wars for such a long time. They never built a cantina bar like I know they're building Star Wars and yeah. I think they've done that. I think that's great.
And they never built a cantina bar like I know they're building Star Wars and sure that will be coming. Yeah. But it's like but they've had Star Tours since the 80s. Yeah. Like and this even the and even jocks like that was just built.
You've had these properties. You could have done any of these things and you've never. Well when they opened the Star Wars launch bay and there's just like a little corner with a table and then it's like hey Star Wars themed food and every I know you and me were like blue milk and they're like no hamburgers. Huh huh. Yeah. And yet in all with everything that you're complaining about this is all felt as though it is the last factoid they did not even opening Pleasure Island for some reason not a priority to do an Indiana Jones thing or Star Wars thing or something from any of the.
The big animated films. Did anybody come across in their research Madison's dive. No no Madison's dive is was the first bar to be cut when Pleasure Island started going over budget and this was a bar themed after splash. It was Madison. Whoa. A mermaid from splash and it was going to be a place where you could sit and watch an old sailor wax nostalgic about the one that got away and then behind it was going to be partially sunken.
Oh my god. So in the actual water behind the sailor the mermaid swims by. Holy crap. For some reason we've talked about this with splash. That's where I want to go. I would love to go there. Wow. I actually legitimately yeah. Now let's do the splash pop up now. Why not. I know no one remembers. Why. Why are the good ideas are the ones they never come in on like the villains on these are all simple like down the middle ideas but then they go no no no mannequins wearing mirrors.
That's our thing. Like you know it's a coked out guy had too much power at Disney at that he was like they were scared of him like we're going to do it's going to be living mannequins and they look like disco ball. Sure whatever you hear just go away. It's got to be like the Imagineers like when you hear any story about any movie being made it's always like well I had this idea it was pretty good and then there's a producer that had just an insane idea that he got stuck on. So there must be like some executive that was just like a club with mannequins is good. We should get that club with the mannequin in there and they're like yeah yeah that's fine but how about we like do a cool.
Theme thing. Yeah okay you can have your theme thing but can I have my mannequins please because you will be fired if you don't finish the mannequins are like oh sorry ran out of money. Here's my one pitch on pleasure and what would have been better instead of having a badge on your thing.
What you do is every time you went to a club you put on a you're getting full donkey like like you're like Pinocchio. So like so the first couple go to you have nothing on but you have a head. You have a headband when you go in and the headband if you're the red if you're this or that you know and so you get an ear and the next time you get another ear and then next thing it knows. So like when you're full donkey you've done all the things right and then that's when you have to leave and when they pin a tail on you that means like don't serve him. Yeah.
How amazing would it be if everyone left looking like donkeys like it was like you've partied too much now you must go home. That is such a good idea. They would be hundreds of donkey's leave.
And there would be all these people with like CEOs of Polaroids of them in college looking like donkeys.
And everyone would cherish those. Yeah. Yeah. Man what an idea that is. I'm in if you're OK Disney new pleasure island 2.0. Let's install the donkey system donkey system. Sleep No More escape rooms adventures club and the boys splash club.
We want all of it. Damn it. We demand it. Paul Scheer demands it. Thank you. You will show you survive. Thank you so much. So much. Anything you would like to promote or especially key us into while you're here.
Yeah I'm trying to know. I mean you guys gave me a lot of good stuff. I would say listen to unspooled which is now wherever podcasts are listened to. We watch 100 of the AFI is movies the best movies of all time apparently. Wonderful.
And then we have actually some we have a quick we have an exciting and exciting announcement. We actually were talking a little bit about this place earlier and I got so excited. But here we go.
We'd like to officially announce that we are doing podcast the ride presents the city walk series a 19 part exploration of universal Hollywood city walk. All right. This is obviously something that you guys have been demanding that we really get.
This is the exploration of the parking garages of the hotels of maybe some of the sock related businesses that are at city walk. We're going to do it all. It's not going to be in a row. It's going to take like six years for us to get it. But I've divided city walk into 19 sectors and we will review each sector.
There's a moment where I was like this is April Fool's joke. We're doing it. I talked about the defunct mall for two and a half hours. You better believe it. Yeah. So I have we'll post some of this stuff. There'll be more details to come.
And start to let us know what you want to hear about. Yes. One of the city like stores with the artificial waves outside. Can I make a request that of course when you get halfway through you should do one of these live from city walk like the Gordon Bursch brewery because I'm waiting for you guys to go.
Like I was like I'm waiting for you guys to go and start touring around like Jim Hill and Len Testa like yes. Yeah. Get the podcast the right fans. I'll come down to Orlando and you guys could guide it around to a live. We got a Pandora.
We know you're willing to abandon your family and go to Orlando. So you won't be so. Yeah. Well let's find a spot. If anybody at city walk has a hook up to a live entertainment venue. What's going on that comedy club. I think John Lowe's comedy club has been empty for a long time.
Make it the podcast the right. We've been to the Kevin Smith podcast lounge. The second theater inside there. Podcast the ride podcast lounge. Yeah. I think that I think we could do a live Hall at the Moon episode where we just go on. We do you know five hours at Hall at the Moon.
We're doing piano guys learn our theme song. Oh yeah. Screaming at them by the end. Please stop. We paid you to stop. Why won't you stop. So we don't have the rights to don't stop believing. Stop playing. I can't wait for the one where you guys do the parachuting one.
Where is it. Yeah. I guess. Is that crazy with that freak pansy like me out. Probably. Yeah. Yeah. I think it's safe. I think I think I think it will be scary because you'll be in the air and get a voodoo donut afterwards. You'll be fine. Not in the same sector though.
There aren't they right across. Well but in the way I've sector. That one's closer to the comic store. Yeah. I like that comic store. Yeah that's an actual business at City. Well something do you what sector we starting with. Do you know that information to becoming forthcoming.
Yeah forthcoming. I already said too much
Not figured that bad plug. This sounds very exciting. I don't hear anything else, but this I think you should just go
19 episodes in a row
Entire season and more for a summer and half a fall
If you did I think if you did this
19 days in a row you released an episode a day. It would be amazing
You know, it wouldn't even be like you then you go right back to the normal schedule
But you have a break where it's 19 episodes that are out. It's a good idea
Yeah, it is a good idea. I just spent 30 minutes on each section. It would be we don't have to do a full two
Yeah, two and a half hours
That's a relief. I was assuming we were we owe two hours on all of these sock market will get two hours
We'll scale them based on I assume by the way the sock market is doing very well right now, too
Yeah
Thanks Trump appreciate it
Well for all the updates on the exciting City of Waukesha series
Follow us at podcast the red on Twitter add us on Facebook
As we what are you calling this series by the way? I did I had written just the city walk series
So you need a class? I think you like a bright lights big city kind of like you need like a
Like a kind of a moniker like someone's like bright lights big city
Not that that's a good title by like colon the city walk series like you need like that, you know
It's like yeah
Well in the trailer it starts with the Avengers music and then it ends up it turns into walk this way. So
It could just be called walk this way. I love that. That's yeah
Well, and if you have any name ideas, let us know
Hit us up on our social medias on our Instagrams in our Facebook's email us a podcast the ride at gmail rate and review us on
iTunes and yeah, stay tuned Paul once again. Thank you, sir. Thank you
Oh my gosh, this is my favorite. Yeah. Yeah stay tuned big things coming