Warning, if you're a preteen fan of the Disney Channel's Andy Mack listening for
the first time, this podcast may include mild swears and even worse, grown men
rambling about fake rocks. Recent Disneyland cavalcade participant
Lelon Bowden takes us under the sea with the Little Mermaid. Life is the Bubbles,
it's Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men who
judge a restaurant not by the quality of its food but by how many robots are
nearby. My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always Jason Sheridan.
Hello. And Scott Gairdner. Yeah, but it's a tough standard to meet these
days. Robot driven restaurants are increasingly few and far between unless
it's Japan. Yes, which is like every restaurant has a robot in it in Japan, as
I understand, I've never been of course. Yeah. We've argued about going to Japan,
but yes, I have very basic understanding of the country. That's why you can't
spend the whole trip in the Disney parks because you got to go see what robots
are running around town. Believe me, when I go to Japan, it will all be nonsense.
It's just a matter of how you do you want to spread it out since. Yeah. Let's
bring a very special guest in though. You know her as Bex on the Disney Channel
show, Andy Mack. Ladies and gentlemen, it's Lelon Bowden. Yay. Can you believe it? You're here.
I can believe it. But that's not to say that I'm not very excited to be here.
Well, thank you. You are our first Disney family member. You're in the family. Yeah.
And after this, you will be out of the family. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's gonna be rough. But yeah, you are.
Just like the Matterhorn. Yes, the Matterhorn is very rough. Is this humor on brand? Yeah.
It's such a rickety ride. Did you prepare a bunch of jokes about each ride? No. OK.
But maybe I can think of them like, give me a ride and I'll see what I can do. Space Mountain.
To tell you what, it's with the new buying of Lucas Films, it's Hyperspace Mountain. That is a statement.
That's a true fact. Oh, wait. It is Hyperspace Mountain. Yeah, unfortunately. Well, all right.
All right. We will do the rest. But if one comes to you, please interrupt whatever we're talking
about to just make a quick joke. Hey, look, that's a sort of off the cuff skill that thousands of
dollars of the improv classes we took, we all took together back in the day. Oh, no.
Were you all in the same groups? So to really get into a topic that's very interesting to the
audience, Jason Leilani and I have been taking improv class together probably, what, nine years
ago, ten years ago? Yeah, probably. It's been forever. This could be the first time that the
UCB theater has been discussed on a podcast. Yeah, no, it's very rarely brought up in the comedy
circle. What are the behind the scenes like in the comedy world? We'll never know. I believe
someone will answer this question one day. Some series of some kind. So yeah, we took improv classes
together. We loved every minute of all of it. And now we're here. Now Leilani is a big star and
the three of us are podcasting, talking about rides. So we're all doing good. A hit star podcast.
Yes, yes, yes. We're not stars. We're hyper space stars. Oh, gosh, how embarrassing to admit to how
many years of improv I've done. So sorry. Do you want me to cut that out? It's just like, what's
the joke on? It has to be Space Mountain like two, like in comparison to something. Like, am I making
fun of Space Mountain? Well, on this podcast, we never make fun of Space Mountain. We're very, we
love Space Mountain. That's scripture. We're afraid to even, that's on the list of episodes we're
afraid to even do. Yeah. Because some of the rides loom so large, we're putting, we're like punting
on them as long as we can. We haven't done Haunted Mansion. We haven't done Captain EO. Where's like
afraid they're too big of topics to like the existence of God or not. They're too, uh, too
giant of topics to even tackle. Hold on, hold on. Now we have roasted the Florida Space Mountain a
lot because the Florida Space Mountain uses the same, uh, sort of toboggan kind of track that,
uh, the Matterhorn does. So imagine the Matterhorn, but in pitch black and wrecking your body. Not
fun. Yeah. Yeah. It is scary. Turn down a free trip if Disney gives it to you, it'll mess up your
back. I can't show weakness in front of my younger co-stars. Oh, right. Oh yeah. I can't be like,
guys, it'll hurt mama's back. I can't go. I'll wait for you at the bottom. Do you find yourself
trying to, I mean, impress your co-stars or do they ever do stuff that's like cool? Do they ever
like want to like hang out behind a 7-Eleven and you're like, this isn't where people should be
hanging out? No, I think when you're like, you know, the kind of kid that's living the life where
you're on a TV show, hanging out behind a 7-Eleven is not really like on your cool roster of things
to do. Like it's not like, oh, that's the, that's the hotspot, uh, where, where, uh, you know,
life happens, um, because, you know, you're getting invited to like the solo premiere and stuff like
that. That's a good question. What are they like, uh, you know, you've, you've done the,
done the press rounds and you get to do fun stuff on your show. What, what, what is the most exciting
to, uh, uh, to your co-stars? Um, to my co-stars, uh, yeah, well, I think it's all really exciting.
Um, you know, I, I think that it's, it's gotta be crazy to be so, like for me, I feel like I revert
back to a child when it's like, oh my gosh, we're going to the Wrinkle in Time premiere. You know,
we did the, uh, we might talk about this more in the podcast, but we just did a Disney channel fan
fest where, oh, that we're going to talk about it. Oh boy. But that was just like, where just so,
oh, it was in Disneyland. Um, it was so much fun. And so for me, I just like become a full kid again,
but I think that for, like for my co-stars, that's a time where they're also growing up,
you know, at the same time. So it's like, it's like, they still have that joy of a kid. And at
the same time, I can see them like managing all this exciting stuff that's like coming their way.
Like they are, um, like, like giving all the good things, like at a birthday party that you could
have it and being asked to be adults by the amount of responsibility that they have for life. Yeah.
And you are, you are more just like, yes, I've hit the minimum for sag health insurance.
Oh, it's a good feeling. Oh yeah. Like, like I hit that party threshold like a long time ago where
it's like, this is awesome. Like, you know, even if like just guest starring on a Disney show would
have been great. So everything past that point has been just like icing on the cake, which has been
a cake that is nothing but icing. That's great. Let me ask you this. Has Andy Mack made you
eat a Tide Pod? That's the only thing I know. That's all I know about millennials.
You know what? I actually don't think that's like eating the Tide Pod is a, is a millennial thing.
I think that just like, you know, people of all ages, A, do stupid stuff, right? Um, and when
you're experimenting with like, you know, when you're becoming, when you're just like, your brain's
not mature yet. You're going to do weirder, stupider things. But you know, a couple of kids ate some
Tide Pods because I went down a rabbit hole of like reading articles about kids who ate Tide Pods.
And it's just like, there were enough copycats, um, that, uh, that, that like, it's like, oh,
millennials eat Tide Pods. But you know, remember 10, uh, 15 years ago when American Pie came out
and then there was that case, there was a couple cases of kids putting, putting their junk in pies
and getting burns because they were putting their junk in pies. They're all doing it. That, yeah,
that didn't define the generation, you know, of like, this is the American Pie generation
of where kids can not stop putting their junk in pies. But now we're in such a think piece culture
that, uh, it appears that all millennials have eaten Tide Pods and that all millennials are
actively trying to kill the Olive Garden and Applebee's. And, uh, I've seen this so many times.
Millennials are killing chain restaurants and they're killing big box stores and they're
killing, uh, go-kart tracks. Like millennials are being blamed for the downfall of lots of things
that would have naturally have downfalls. So this is a format for articles about like
millennials are killing blank of like, it is essentially just changing taste. Like people
aren't as into fa- like, you know, casual dining anymore. People want more like a Chipotle fast
casual mix sort of thing. So then the other kinds of businesses aren't going to as much, but then
there's so many websites that just need to churn out content. There's just like a lot of millennial.
Although this week I saw- Yeah, millennials take a lot of, and at this point, like a millennial is
not somebody who's 13. You're a millennial. No, we are technically older. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm at the cutoff of it and I love it. Yeah. Wait a minute. You, you're in or you're out?
I'm in. Okay. I just made it. You're, you're creeping on Gen X though.
Well, yeah, I am. Well, you are too. Yeah. Is it X though? Isn't there something in between?
Well, there was Gen Y. Oh wait, what's Gen Y? But then I think Gen Y like turned into millennials.
Well, that's, it's weird because I think the, the definition of a generation is like you were born
within a 20 year age range, but then there's also for the sake of popular culture, it's like, yeah,
if you were born around here, you're this. The point is I'm personally killing Olive Garden.
Yeah. You didn't even realize it, but you are. There's not an art. There should be an article,
though. Jason Sheridan is personally saving Olive Garden. Oh yeah. Well, no, that's not true because
I, I define endless pasta. Like I see endless pasta and it's like, keep, keep it coming boys.
Jason's destroying Olive Garden in a different way, but bleeding them dry.
I did see this week, my, the first millennials are saving blank, which is millennials are saving
the frozen food aisle. Apparently like frozen. Oh, that's straight up true. Food like is very,
it's doing very, especially like higher end, like organic or like natural, you know, frozen foods.
Oh, they have my number. That's what I do. I go straight to the organic frozen food section
of the grocery store and then I'm done shopping. Are we talking like Amy's? Oh, we're talking Amy's
because I like a lot of the Amy's stuff. And that rice mac and cheese. Yum. I have that. That's good.
Is that the gluten? That's the gluten free or no? I don't know. I have this gluten free macaroni
cheese for Amy's. It's very good. All right. Anyway, do you guys mention a lot of brands on this
show? We love brands. Like, do you get sponsorship by these brands? No, no, no. Oh no. Well, we were
open. If Amy's wants to get involved in podcast, the ride, we're here. We're ready to have that
meeting Amy's. I think that like you're already doing it for them. So I feel like if I was part
of the Amy's like marketing team would be like, we'll just let this be. Sure. Yeah, we already
did it. Why do they have to pay us? Wait, no. Okay. Here's what we'll delete out. This whole podcast
is just an ad for these theme parks. Really? I guess you're right. They'll say the F word once
in a while and we'll be like a little bit salty about certain rides. But like really people are
just listening and going, yeah, I want to go to these parks and then every now and then I'll drop
in like a very forced like, oh man, you know what I was doing the other day? Enjoying a great blue
e-cigarette, like really ham fisted, like just trying to get that endorsement, get that sponsorship
going. That's your number one. I got to keep my podcast and pipes running fine. Yeah. I can't
have a scratchy voice. That's what blue helps me out. I quit dip and I've gone to blue e-cigarette.
It would be great if we all buy like in a year or so each had like a sponsor, separate sponsor. So
like at the UFC when, you know, Brock Lesnar has Jimmy John's on his shorts, each one of us will
have a different sponsor that will constantly be plugging personally in addition to many other ads.
So we want this thing to become, you know, very corporate, very. Anyone, do you guys have ideal
sponsors? Well, Tristan's is a e-cigarette or a Olive Garden. Yeah. Or Raytheon,
the defense company. I want to be sponsored by GRP records, a jazz, a smooth jazz vinyl label
from the eighties that I'm not sure is still around, but quality albums. Kevin Eubanks put out
a lot of great jazz. Wow. Yeah. So yeah. Kick. Give me some kickbacks. GRP records. Thanks for
the jazz. I've been buying a lot of pants lately. So Levi's I would go for Levi's if they would,
they would be a sponsor of Michael. Also heels in your quest to always look younger. Oh,
prove you're on the millennial side of the fence. That's true. That would prove it.
A personal brand. Yeah. I mean, uh, no. Okay. I don't know. It's just like, uh, I mean, I have
things that I like, but I feel like part of my deal is that not one brand can't own me
unless I guess it's a Disney, which I'm very happy about. So cool. Any brand is going to,
and they own most of the best things. So you're on a good list. So yeah, before, so, so we didn't
even say like, we're going to be eventually talking about the little mermaid, Ariel's undersea
adventure ride. That was your choice. And we're going to get way into it. But first we do have
to talk about this fan fest that you just participated in, um, for promotion for the show.
Oh, let us know. Let us know. Just tell us where we were. I was, I was watching. There was a live
feed of it. You were in a little car. You were in a parade. You were honored. Those older Disney man.
He has a little cap on you. Pluto was in the car with you. It was in the car. It was a whole thing.
It was down main streets. You drag race the DuckTales cast. Yeah. It was, uh, it was super fun. I
believe it's the first one, um, that, uh, Disney channel has done, um, where they take all the
stars from their shows and on the lineup to come and, um, pop them in cars and we get to do a little,
it's called a cavalcade. Yeah. I love that. Um, I'm going to show Scott a photo of the car.
Oh yeah. I'm going to miss this. Whoa. I learned some really cool trivia about that car that we
were in. Um, the driver was, uh, I think that's like part of his deal too. He's like, do you want
to know about this car? Um, that car is, is, uh, almost as old as the, the Disney parks. Yeah. Um,
it's like only a couple years, like, uh, a couple years younger. It's like super old and there's only
a couple of those cars. So there, I wish I could remember how many, but there's like five or
something and a couple are in here and a couple are in Disneyland, Florida, um, Disney world. Um,
and, uh, the fire engine, um, that was one was the very first. And there was like a whole story
that he told me about how the designer of that car literally drove that car, um, from Burbank to
Anaheim. Um, but it's like, it's not a real car. Everything's five, eight scale. So those, um,
I mean, it's a, I mean, yeah, it's five, eight scale of like a, uh, a normal car,
like main street itself. So it fits in. Yes, exactly. Main street is five, eight scale. Wow.
And so it fits right in. It looks normal. He looked funny driving this thing down
from Burbank to Anaheim. Um, the, the, the cute joke is, is that like, uh, a, um, car was passing
and a kid out the end was like, Hey, Mr. By the time you get to the fire, it'll already be out.
That's one of the original imagineers getting roasted going down the five.
And this was, but this was a Burbank long before Jay Leno, uh, was constantly driving old timey
cars around. No one was used to it yet. Man, Jay, I bet Jay would love to drive some of those main
streets. He ever driven one of the main street cars? I bet Jay Leno would love to, if he ever
went down there, an idea for a Leno's garage. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I would also like to,
drives a double decker bus and stuff. I would also like to be sponsored by Jay Leno's garage.
Sure. That would be cool. He has a show on CNBC. Is that right? Yeah. Jay Leno,
he just goes around and fixes cars and drives cars around. Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah. That's for some
people. Sure. Yeah. It's all, it's a foreign language to me, but so is this podcast to a lot
of not remotely. Uh, I can't even, if I have to like improvise fake car facts, I'm dead in the water.
20 horsepower silence. 20 horsepower silence. E-pants run away from wherever I am.
Yeah. Believe it or not, Leland, we're, the three of us aren't big gear heads.
We don't love getting our hands dirty in a garage. Or the sun. Not big fans of the sun. Or the sun,
unless we're outside at a park. Getting our skin toasted. But we do love the Autopia at Disneyland.
Actually, we don't love that. I tried to look, I think it was Ward Kimball was the Imagineer
who designed the fire truck. Oh, right. Well, he was the, he had his jazz band, the Firehouse 5
or something of that. It was like, or Firehouse 5 plus two, something like that. It was a Firehouse
themed, uh, jazz band. Yeah, this all tracks. I didn't need to keep explaining, but yeah, it must be,
uh, I'm done. You're the fire guy. Oh, you know what y'all are? Trivia heads.
Yeah. Oh, we love it. That's pretty true. I'm really good at, like, I, I, uh, I don't absorb small facts,
uh, well, I can, but it's not my strength. Man, I'm so sorry that you're here then.
We hide our notes. I'm just here for the party. Our voluntary notes documents. Small facts. So,
we made you do this, uh, eight, nine years ago when we would just pull out random
bullshit on stage, uh, doing improv. Oh, I know you guys were constantly like, so, well, uh, not as
bad as, as like, uh, when I was on, um, tab, uh, with our friends, uh, Casey and Jacob, they would
constantly, um, set me up to no sports specifics. And that was just a nightmare where they'd be like,
oh, look, everybody, it's LeBron. Tell us what team you're on. And, uh, you know, I should know.
And I did it and it sucks. That I feel like is easier to fake than just random, like.
Trivia. Brainy bunches made for TV movie bullshit. Like. I don't think that's true. If, if, if you
get the name of LeBron's team wrong, people are going to know. You can't. Oh, you guys go like,
oh, LeBron, you're on the, what team? You're on the best one. My man, LeBron. You did not take that
at all. That would not fly in front of an audience because they could tell you. The good team,
that's not easy to fake at all. Anyway. Um, we distracted from the general. Yeah. So we're back
to being in this parade. You're in a tiny car. Some of these cars, by the way, I look at that,
that car is a bright yellow car that you were in. And I look at that and I remember seeing
footage of parades where like Ronald Reagan's being driven around and I know it was like that
car could have been used by very famous people. Apparently the fire truck is the one that was
reserved for diplomats and like a big, big town, big time people. There was a, I think the one when
I went, I went to alone to Disneyland a couple of years to go see Dick Van Dyke in a parade
and he was driven around in the car, but I believe it was the green car. So you guys were in a yellow
car. Oh, oh my gosh. Oh, this is why I wish I knew trivia better because the driver of the yellow car
told me which car Dick Van Dyke was in for his like 90th birthday or something like that. Right?
Yes. That's what I was there. I went alone. He told me which car he was in and I don't remember.
You got pretty good recall though. You got pretty good recall of this. Uh, it's a,
all the anecdotes this guy gave. Um, I have a picture of Dick Van Dyke somewhere so I can find
it. We can figure out what car he was in. Cool. Um, but you, so, so you guys started the parade
back, what, by a small world? That's generally where, where the parade comes out. Here's a thing.
Uh oh. I have no idea. I have no idea. It's just like, did you just black out and wake up in a
parade? Yes. That's what it felt like. Well, because, uh, we, the, the ready station was in the, um,
uh, the hotel, the California hotel. Right. Um, and so that's where we were prepping and stuff
like that. And we were ushered, you know? Um, and so we were ushered, um, on a, on a, like a moving
bus, not like a parade bus to the start of the parade. And, uh, I don't, I didn't know where we
were and I didn't recognize where we were during the parade. Cause I was so overwhelmed with like
people waving. Right. And so like it, it was a blur. I was just like, wow. So more photos were
taken of you in that, uh, I don't know how long to 15 minutes to half an hour, probably than ever
in the rest of your life. Like you gotta be on, you're posing. Oh yeah. Yeah. Like there's no time
until I kind of scratched my head and be like, wow, well, this is the fancy land, you know, like, uh,
did you just call it fancy land? The fantasy land. I said it was this fancy land. This is, this is
fancy. All of Disneyland is fancy land. Yeah. That's accurate. Yeah. Um, that's maybe frontier land.
That's rough and tumble. Yeah. Um, but so, so it, but it was a lot, I guess we're by really,
I'm asking like it would felt like it was 15 minutes ish that you were actually in the parade.
That sounds about right. Yeah. It, it, but it went by so quickly, you know, it was, it was just like,
oh, and people are excited and the, oh, the, the cutest thing is that there were a group of young
girls who were all together who maybe around like a young teenager age, um, who saw the Andy Matt
car and they were like weeping. Oh yeah. And like, and they were smiling and taking pictures and just
like, just like overwhelmed and, uh, Peyton like straight up like leaned, like leaned over, like
the car was like, Hey, are you okay? And they're like, yes, we're great. Okay. Wow. It's like,
you'll meet, you were like, be experiencing Beatlemania or something. Yeah. It was,
it was pretty wild. And it was like, uh, it, like I talked to, uh, Kate McCoochie after who was in
the DuckTales, uh, vehicle. And she was just saying that she just cried the whole parade
because it was just so moving and cool. And it's like, and Disneyland is such a big part of,
you know, all of our childhoods and to be like an attraction. It is just, you know,
mind boggling to the other end of this where you're literally in, you're in areas people
don't get to see and yeah. And you know, I didn't get to take advantage of that anyway,
cause I was just so like, Whoa, it was crazy. Yeah. A lot of those sorts of things you get ushered
from thing to fit, like, you know, people are just like, okay, we got to go over here. Now we
got to go do this. Now we got to take pictures, that sort of thing. Yeah. Oh yeah. The whole day
was just getting ushered around, um, uh, by the, uh, the, the guides in plaid. Of course. Um,
super cool. Let me ask, did you guys, did you guys get, you didn't get to choose Pluto as the
character in the car with you? Uh, Pluto was assigned. He was assigned. Okay. I would know
we didn't, we didn't show us like a look book and they were like, you know, find what, what
character speaks to you. Um, no, but you know, no complaints. Sure. No, no. I mean, I just was
wondering like, if they were like, all right, Pluto's with you, we're sending Mickey over here.
Yeah. Was, were the DuckTales people with the DuckTales characters? You know what? I feel like
I have this vague memory. I mean, it could be, it could be corroborated just by looking online.
I think I know the answer to this. Um, but I think Scrooge McDuck was in that, the, uh, Raven's Home
vehicle. Okay. I believe that. Yeah. I was confused too, cause Scrooge was not with. DuckTales. Yeah.
Let me see if we can find the feed of this. We'll, we'll post it of course, for the audience. If he gets
too close to David Tennant, like a wormhole open, like reality starts to bend. Um, what, what, like
that's DuckTales, uh, cast is the ultimate hipster lineup. Right. Who else is in there? Who's in the
new crew? Bobby Moynihan, Ben Schwartz, uh, Danny Pudi. Yes. Yes. Uh, Beck Bennett, but he wasn't there.
Correct. He wasn't there. Um, yeah, it's yeah. Kate Mccoochie, like it's, it's like a perfect,
like all star cool town lineup. Right. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Scrooge and Launchpad are in the Raven's
Home car. Yes. Yes. For whatever reason. They didn't want to be too obvious, I guess. Yeah. Two on the
nose, I guess. Yeah. So, but for whatever reason, but you're the fact that you're, you're, uh,
streaming through a video of this parade. Oh yeah. I, well, the, when this fan fest was- Cavalcade, you guys.
Cavalcade. Cavalcade. When this was happening, like I was looking at, like I have a Twitter list of
like theme park news sites and blogs and stuff. And I was like, there's Leelod, scrolling through it.
It's like, there's Leelod. There's Leelod again. There's Leelod. Like as people were there posting,
but we're sharing like, you know, whatever pictures they were sending out on the wire.
You were the star of theme park social media. Uh, so it's something, an honor usually reserved for
ice cream cones. I finally made it to ice cream cones. I'm in. So, so you get through with the parade.
And then you have what, a signing, was that right? You like, was it a meet and greet? Yes, it was a
meet and greet. And so it was like, uh, it was a thing where fans could, um, walk a step and repeat
and take pictures with the Disney channel shows and stuff. Uh, and that was, uh, that was fun. But
also, yeah, like a big whirlwind of like, Hey, what's your name? How's it going? Blah, blah, blah.
Let's take a picture. Hold the sign. Yeah, it's fine. Okay. Bye. You know, like, um, and, uh, and
then after that we had a, uh, a talk back panel with, um, the cast of stuck in the middle and,
uh, with radio Disney with, uh, so radio Disney was the host, the panel, and it was so much fun
because like the fans are like, so like pumped, you know, that they were not afraid to shout out
exactly what they felt about characters, you know, like it was like medieval times, you know,
where it was just like, you know, and, uh, well, nobody says I hate you today. The nights and
medieval times. Yeah, I did. Well, Mike, if they were in the other side, I would yell something
like just screaming. I hate the monarchy. You're all part of the problem and oligarchy for this
kingdom. Um, but, uh, but yeah, like they were very vocal about like who they shipped, you know,
and, and like what, what care? Yeah. What ships they like better than other ships, you know?
Yeah. Ships are you sure? Well, everybody's shipping me and Bowie, who's the father of
Andy Mac. Uh, cause you got to, you know, you got to root for the family. I have, I searched your
name and hashtags on Instagram. Did you search Tumblr too? I didn't search Tumblr. Oh boy. Jason,
search Tumblr for Leland. I don't know if I want to go down that rabbit hole. Do you know what my
persona is on Tumblr? No. What do you mean? Um, uh, well this was, I, you know what? I haven't
checked Tumblr in a hot second now, but, um, when Andy Mac first came out, uh, it was like,
I got a text from one of the, the, the, uh, I got a text from the main writer being like,
wow, you're really popular with the lesbian community. Like the, the Bex's style and persona
is like a hit, you know? And I was like, cool. Um, I was just, I, uh, mine was not about the
lesbian community. It was just that I had seen a lot of different pictures of the two of you and
the people are like, they are so cute together. People like just posting like photos and photos
from the Disneyland like press conference. So, um, yeah. People ship Bexie, hashtag Bexie.
Is there any weird, is there any weird one? Like you like ship with a real, like a random guest
star or like a different show? Have you seen any weird one? Like you and Pluto? Hashtag Plex.
That's pretty good. Yeah. Very, very snazzy ship name. Um, well, I mean, the internet is a weird,
weird place, you know? And so I think that like the goal, you know, of the collective
internet body is to try to make every ship possibility, you know, every combination.
So I've seen it and it's weird because it's like they just ship everybody in the show,
but I'm much older than most of the people in the show. So there's less boundary should be kept.
Boundaries should be kept. Right. That's why I said like random guest stars. Cause I didn't want to,
because there's not many options for you. No, I mean like Bex has pretty much just had, you know, Bowie is like,
the, there's not really a contender. Right. Shipping though, in general is not necessarily, it's not,
uh, there's like, there's a pretty like sweet component to it. I don't necessarily have a full
understanding of it, but like it's not, it's not like erotic fan fiction necessarily. It's like,
I want them to be together. Yeah. No, it's yeah. Yeah. Exactly. That same feeling and tone and
cadence. Like, I wish they were together. Yeah. They'd be so happy and so would I. Yes. It's gentle.
Drawing of a Bex exchanging Valentine's gifts with Bob Iger. Interesting. I guess they, uh, yeah,
they did run out of age appropriate characters to pair off with. Should we declare if we're,
if we are to be shipped, I was just trying to combine them in our, it's, it would be
hashtag Garrett Garrett son, Gerson den. Oh, you mean if we were all shipped together? Yeah.
If people were to say like with other first names guys, it would have to be like,
huh? Like we don't have a lot of room to work with. Yeah.
Yeah. It would be like, go to the next go to the next hashtag. Go tonight. I don't know
the spelling. You figure it out. That is your ship name. I think people should ship Jason
with different treats. Oh, I think they should too. I just want to see him eat a funnel cake.
If he would only eat a funnel cake, hashtag J C's cake. Like what treats would you like to ship Jason
with? Let's ask the audience though. They can come up with some good stuff to be with fried Reese's
pieces at my local fair. I just want to see him with sorbet. Please someone please draw like a,
a sailor moon escrow drawing of like sorbet. Are we calling for fan art? I don't even get fan art.
Like you guys get fan art. Like we've, we've had two and we demand it also. I've seen them.
I still post a picture. I have the original art. Oh yeah. You got sent the original. Oh yeah.
Yeah. So I have the original art and the artists, uh, very nice. Uh, I will give him a shout out on
Twitter. The specific artist, the twain and the mayor he sent to, and he also said a lovely opening
MGM studios, a program guide guide. That's cool. So, uh, a picture of that. When this goes up,
have you gotten any fail? You have to get fan mail somewhere. Like you have to get some. Yeah. Um,
yeah. I mean, do you have to go pick it up or you don't get it directly to your, no, uh, the,
the Disney channel will keep fan mail for us, uh, at the office and then we get to read them and
they're the sweetest things. Like there's, uh, I just, like my heart explodes, you know, like
there's glitter on the outside of the envelopes and there's stickers and, and, you know, you can
tell that like, you know, kids have spent a lot of time in the block lettering and stuff like that.
It is just like, it just makes your heart melt, you know, and they just have really nice things
to say. It's like, you're my favorite. Oh, you know, what's really cool is, uh, when we were
doing our New York press junket, um, Josh, one of the kids in the show handed me, um, a paper. Um,
and, and it was just like a random paper and he was like, Hey, uh, a gal asked me to give you this.
And it was like a note of being like, I love your character on it, Andy Mack. And at the end,
she wrote stay woke. Wow. And it meant a lot. Yeah. Very cool. That is cool. That's like, yeah,
that would be overwhelming by like, like people, like seeing so many people's feelings at once.
It is like a good version of Twitter or something. Yes, it is. It is constantly overwhelming.
Yeah. It's like, yeah, like I, you can't see cause it's a podcast, but I just squinted my
eyes and blinked really hard because it's like, you can't look at it directly. It's like the sun.
Is this really happening? Sure. Yeah. So cool. It's nice to know that it like comes,
that it can come back around to you. I feel like I've always been, uh, uh, confused about
does fan mail actually, uh, actually get to the person or is some, uh, guy in an office, uh,
writing form letters back and says to here, can, uh, can make it to you. Yeah. It's the,
there's a high volume, you know, um, but we, when we're there, we get to read them.
And that's why you just have a rubber stamp made up that just says best of luck in your future
endeavors. And you just stay up ahead shot and I should bulk media mail and I should, well, like
when Andy Mac first came on, I did try to, you know, reach out to fans and send pictures and
stuff like that, you know, because it's like, oh, I could. And then just, it was like, oh, okay.
I won't be able to keep up, uh, with this. Cause it was just, it's one, one bit operation here,
guys. You also have to, uh, work. You have to do the show. I don't have like, you know,
and, uh, yeah, assistants or whatever, you know, they're not going to let you write letters back
in the shots. You have to do the things the scene requires. Yeah, exactly. That's why,
that's why sometimes people get paper cranes or like a stew or whatever Becks is making that day.
I got to get my responses out where I can. You don't have an assistant, but you have a very, uh,
imposing bodyguard standing behind you who keeps really giving me a look.
He looks really mad at me.
I'm nervous you acknowledged him. Yeah, they come with me everywhere.
Um, so not true. So Mike, for my, I had a question this whole time. Uh, which was this out all at
grand California in the fan fest was that the hotel, where was all that? Where were the questions
being asked or was it in the park? Um, the, the panel was, uh, in California adventure. Oh,
it was. Okay. So it was probably in that big area by the monsters, ink ride. I'm assuming stage,
stage 12. Yeah, that's where, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right. The former, uh, who wants
to be a millionaire. Yes, of course. I know that there needs to be a huge, who wants to be a
millionaire in that stage. We're pretty sure. Oh, or was it also where the Tron arcade was? Cause
that was in a big like open space. That was really well done. Did you ever see the Tron?
Oh yeah, of course. Yeah, that was great. Very cool. Well, I'll load history flex. Wait,
Tron, Tron is the game where you sit in, it's a two person. Um, and you, and you sit in it and
I'm sorry, I'm thinking of T-mech guys. Um, all right. Is there a specific, well, there is a
specific Tron game that was based on the movie. I've seen the movie, but, but I just confused, uh,
you T word of your arcade. Yeah. They made a replica of the arcade that they like. Understood.
In both movies. Oh, that's really cool. Yeah. It was fun. And then they had like an electronic
dance show as well. They had like a, the whole area looked like the, the Tron for a little while.
So yeah, when there's the Andy Mack, uh, rave, then you'll know when it's a permanent fixture
in the parks. That's when you'll know it. It's a themed rave. You gotta be in bed by nine.
So once all that stuff was then out of the way, did you guys get to just do whatever you wanted
at the parks? Like how did it work? Were you escorted around at that point? Or did they say,
have attitude, whatever you want? Um, uh, we, uh, we stuck with the guides, um, but it was,
you know, a lot we did, we got a lot done that day. You know, we did promos for different things.
You know, we, uh, uh, we took pictures with like Jesse and Woody and the, and Mike and Sully and
stuff like that. And so we had a lot of things to go to. So I was excited to hit the rides after,
but it, like I said before, I'm, I don't have the same kind of boundless energy as my younger
co co stars. Um, so I went on like five rides and I was like, I gotta go home. Each one. I,
like, I felt like a little bit more like sick than the last one. Oh my gosh. I was like,
but I kept wanting to go because like, a it's Disneyland. You have to, and, um,
B like I've got like my mother's mentality, you know, where it's like, oh, you can't just waste.
You have to actually have that in different ways. Like my mom just kind of has that, like,
you know, you just can't waste money, you know? And then my dad is just like a Disneyland fanatic.
He is, he, oh yeah. It was so cool last year going on Thanksgiving, the Thanksgiving holiday.
This was my first time going with a guide and I took my dad and my little brother and his girlfriend
and, uh, I like, we were exchanging emails and my, and it's like, yeah, we can decide when we want
to be there. And my dad's email back was so intense. It was like, we will get there, um,
right before the park opens, we will go on all the rides. I would like the park hopper tickets
and we will leave at midnight.
Road drop to midnight, baby. That's how you do it. Uh, even we weren't able to, to stay until
midnight at a certain point, we're like, okay, I think it's time to go.
Wow. So you can't keep up with either generation on either side of your,
younger or older. Well, I mean, the thing is, is that like, if you're the way we did it when we
were kids, it was like, we didn't have the luxury of a guide, you know? Um, and so the times in
between are actually important when you're waiting to get on a ride because your body is at a state
of rest, you know, but a guide gives you those like special powers where you can fast pass it and,
and, uh, you know, uh, you can, you know, do so many more rides and, uh, like it's, you don't
realize that like, you know, you just put your body on like, like a machine going like, you know,
a hundred miles an hour or whatever. And then you, and then it's like, okay, now this one,
you spin around and then this one, you just go like loop de loop. And then there's colors and
lights coming at you from all directions, every single ride, you know, we did the entire California
adventure park before 11 AM. Oh yeah. You know, and so it was just like, we just, we were going at a
much higher, um, uh, pace. Sure. That's also on top of like, I mean, if you go to a park all day,
especially in Southern California, it's probably going to be sunny all day. Like, so you spend a
lot of time in the sun, which can be tiring. Yes. And then the sun goes down and, uh, it gets cold
at night a lot of the year in California. So then you have that beating against your, uh, potentially
sunburned skin. Uh, so I find, I find Florida, like I can go for a lot longer in Florida. I mean,
I guess it's also like vacation. But it's the hottest, most humid. I love it. I love it. That's
insane. I love to sweat it out, but like, I hate, I don't like the cold nights here. You prefer
humidity and hurricanes? Oh, I love the humidity. Yeah, I love it. I'll, I will take a humid night
over like a cold night in Anaheim, but it's so, it can get, I was, we were there in like September
last year and it was a press, it was 90 degrees. The heat was unbearable and it was also humid.
Like that's, it was, that's a crazy climate. I like humid too. I'm just saying to still prefer one
drastically over the other, I think is just as pure insanity. Jason, I think you used to say
just as pure insanity. Jason, I think you just gave me more empathy of, uh, what it's like to
not have my, um, pigment of skin, you know, cause I would never, I would never think of like the,
the factor in, oh, well we're going to be in the sun and then the night will beat down on your,
your skin, you know, like, that's like, that's my fine Irish heritage. That's why, uh, the people
made to, uh, uh, drink whiskey and then die from lack of potatoes. Uh, so not exactly the most
evolutionary advanced, uh, people and run from the British, like hide from the British or fight the
British. Y'all have survived famines galore, you know? Like that's, I would say that you're
evolutionarily strong. So the young Jason can eat all the treats. Mike is like, Mike is stuck cause
he's got like five jokes at once. Yeah, it's too much, too much clogging the pipe. I'm just saying
I've been with you to Disneyland many, many, many times and there's never been a scenario where by
six o'clock you're beat red and like you have a crazy cartoonish sunburn. I think I just find it
more draining. I'm also pretty diligent about sunscreen. I have the place, I, you are drained.
What's the problem? I will say this. I've seen you drained every place in Los Angeles, except
Disneyland. That's the only time I don't think you're exhausted. You've fallen asleep on my
couch in various apartments over the years, but Disneyland, you are wide awake. I've told other
people, this is your place. This is the place where you will see this man at his most alive.
We added that is accurate too. We edit out the moment in every podcast where you're like,
sorry guys, I need a break sunburn nap time for me. You are, you are, you can stay awake. I'm,
all I'm saying, I'm giving you credit. You could do a 16 hour Disney day. I can do a 16 hour. I'm
not sure about Scott. Scott, I think is the one who likes to, cause Scott will generally be like,
I'm coming down. Uh, we're going to go on one ride and then we're going to leave. We're going
to eat dinner. Then we're going to leave. Yeah. When we've hung, it's usually, yeah, we join you
for one or two things. Yeah. The car they circle lounge for a while. We have like, it's me and the
wife speed. We have two cocktails. Scott goes on a ride before that. He goes on a ride after,
and then they go home. And then we were Lindsay and I stay. That's the way to do it. You know,
I don't want to like jump ahead in the order, but this is a perfect segue into, uh, today's ride
topic because the little mermaid ride is a perfect ride for that. If I just want to go have a couple
drinks and take, take some nice photos by the, by the old sun wheel and walk around and like, all
right, solid three hours. Uh, uh, the little mermaid is a perfect one to, uh, that's, you know,
that reliably doesn't have a line or it's a very fast line. If, if, if the park is clearly, uh,
jammed to the brim, I know I can at least get on the little, we are, we are talking about California
adventure. Yes. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Cause that's the one you can, you can drink at. Yes. Oh,
yeah. I see. Yeah. Uh, sometimes I'll go down just for like, you know, two glasses of white wine
purposes. It's great. No one should be upset about it. It's a gas. This is the way to do it.
I've had some of the best days and nights of my life, having two glasses of white wine and then
leaving. Oh my goodness. I can't deal. That's the nice thing. 16 hours where you fit in everything.
Sounds good too. Like, oh my, when I was a kid, I would, I would force my, I was definitely,
would you call it a ropes to a road drop to like, park clothes? Yeah. Oh, I wore out my parents. I
was definitely that way as a kid, like an exhaustive and then like midnight is technically the closing
but I, you can still kind of dilly dally and main street for a while. I would do all the way from
8 AM to one. So I, I've done my, my time in the exhaustive manner, but man, these days, oh boy.
If you linger long enough, you can see the kiss good night. Leland, you know about the kiss good
night. I don't know about the kiss. This sounds like a phrase I would make up. When we saw the
mainstream electrical for it, didn't we see all the characters? Yes. That's a different thing than
what you're talking about. Oh, it is. Okay. Nevermind. What's the kiss good night? It's, it's shortly
after official park clothes, the castle like twinkles and an announcement comes on and it
says like Disneyland has concluded its operational day. Like, you know, we hope you had a magical
time and get home safely. It's a magical use of the word operational. But it's just like a little light
twinkling. They make a lot more of it in Florida. They do a lot more of the kiss good night and they
play it like over every 15 minutes after the park closes. Basically, I think I don't know the actual
number. People are yelling now at their phones. Wait, what is the kiss good night? I don't,
it's a phrase that why Walt use that would say like, it's a little, like a nice little thing to
say goodbye to everybody at the end of the night. Okay. That refers to the recording of like,
Oh yeah. And a little light, light. Yeah. There's no kiss. No one gets kissed. That would be illegal.
Every guest. When Jason is mayor, he will, he will make that a law at Disneyland. But until then,
Pucker up everyone. Come give Jason a kiss. Jason is like Richard Dawson just standing outside the
exit gate and you have to kiss him on the way out. That's for the younger folks. That's a,
that's a very old reference to a host of the family feud who liked to kiss all the contestants.
And it was more okay then than it is today. Oh yeah. No, he would not, I don't think anyone
liked doing it back then, but especially today that would not, that would not fly. Steve Harvey's not
kissing all the guests. Don't get a little mustache brush if you're a guest on the show.
So little mermaid ride. Yeah. Yeah. Ariel's undersea adventure. But in Florida it is called
under the sea journey of the little mermaid. And there's also a live show, which is called
voyage of the little mermaid. Yes. There's a lot of little mermaid title confusion going on across
these parks, but it was, you just end up calling it the little mermaid ride. Right. I just, what is
the, why call it two different things in Disneyland? It's confusing because I, the ride is I'd almost,
they're almost identical. I was, I've been on both of them in the last few months. So,
and you will again. Yeah. It's just the exterior is really the cue and the exterior is the
difference. Out here it's in a repurposed golden dream, which was the old whoopee Goldberg film.
They repurposed the building, which is an old piece of California, like architecture. It's the
palace of the fine arts in San Francisco, right? When there were a lot of like many recreations
of California things in California adventure. They really trivia. Yeah. If you want to like,
just shout nerd or like, like push us or something you can lead. I'm gentle in heart. That's, I know
that. Uh, body guards who I've learned are named brick and mortar are making her a sandwich now.
Mortar 1920s, going from seven friends of Bugsy. Uh, so, and then the, the line outside in Florida,
the outside is, is more like rock because it's more of a theme. What you're saying that it's like
the cave of one, the not the cave wonders, not Latin, but the cave with all her, it's sort of
like the, where does Ariel live? Castle from the movie. Oh, right. Yeah. There's sort of like a
castle. This is, this picture is pretty small, but it looks like you're the two back to back.
Oh, oh yeah. They're very different, huh? Yeah. Okay. So you're saying one you,
Ariel is inside of Ariel's castle. And then another one, Ariel is inside of a concert
venue in San Francisco. I am saying that. And yeah, so, but though I like the, um, the California
but that's no slam on that. I think it's, I think it's kind of fun that they weaved that into that
space and left that kind of that dome and that glass walls. It's a nice piece of architecture.
It's kind of cool looking. I mean, I think I probably prefer the one that seems like you're
more like by the sea. That would make more sense to be like, Oh, I'm going under the sea now.
I mean, the Florida one is. I never judge the outside of a ride. Oh my God, you're on the wrong podcast.
That sounds insane to me. The ride is about the ride. The ride starts, the ride starts from looking
at the outside of the ride and then going through the queue because your experience should start
there. It's like the Indiana Jones ride. That's a whole part of it. I guess you're right. And it is
really important to have a good line experience because you will be in it and stuff like that.
I think my favorite is probably Space Mountain because it's cool. Yes. In there it's like cool.
And there's like machines just going, you know, like, yeah, I think it's a little bit of a bummer
that they like, I don't know why this changed, but I think you used to like kind of do the ride,
do the line all the way inside Space Mountain and maybe it's a capacity issue, but now they kind of
rush you through all those tunnels, which should be fun to hang out in there as opposed to on that
like that deck for a long time. It's like Indiana Jones too. Do you mean in general or like when you
have a guide or whatever? No, no. If you go, anytime you go on Space Mountain in Disneyland,
like you get, once you get in the actual building, you like rush through all that interior stuff.
They have a lot of outside line space now. And that led in like groups of a couple dozen at a time.
Oh, I know what you're talking about. Okay. Yeah, yeah, I hear you. But it'd be nice to be in there.
Yeah. Yeah. There used to be like, like more lax codes, I think, like for having like fire codes,
I think where you could like, cause the Indiana Jones ride and the Space Mountain, they're like
pretty narrow and they probably don't want to pack people in a place where if there was a fire,
it would be hard to get them all out. That totally makes sense. So in the old days,
no one cared about that. And it was fun because you just get kind of trapped in these fun little
lines. But now it's like, you got to sit mostly outside and then they kind of rush you through
the cool line. Do you have a lot of capacity complaints like we do? No, I just think it's like,
even then like being in the line, that's still the experience of the ride. You guys are talking
about straight up the like the outside. Oh yeah. Oh sure. Well, but I'm a fan of architecture in
general. And I like when it's a cool looking building. Space Mountain is a cool looking building
and it makes sense that it looks like a cool spaceship thing. You know, it's a good example
of this issue is that it's a small world in Disneyland is that grand 60s pop art exterior.
And in Disney world, it's just kind of jammed into like a storefront and you don't really get
all that. And it sort of makes, even though it's almost the same ride, it makes it like a little
less of a full, yes. Yeah. Magical experience. So yeah, so it's, it's a little, it's underwhelming
of a line. I guess we're starting in the line here, but for a little mermaid in California,
I'm not even saying that necessarily. I'm saying, Oh, you are. Oh, we've done the Florida one,
which I have a floor. One is just a little better as well. All that rock work and everything.
Rock workers. We love fake rocks on this program. We love, that's one of the things we all agree on.
We love fake rocks. That's a Disney. That's a really good, I want so badly for you to find
a fake rock company to sponsor you. Oh yeah. Oh, we love that. What a match. Like what other
thing is going to seek out a company of fake rocks to be like, we want to promote your fake rocks.
However, the, the like who out there listening to this podcast has a need for, and the money
for a lot of fake rock work. Yeah. I mean, if you build it, I think you will be pleasantly surprised.
We have a couple like very rich listeners that like have a lot of room to make like fake rocks
and stuff like a fake Mesa rich. Maybe it's just like, you know what? Everybody's got something
that they want to invest in. And it's like, I think it would be cool to have fake rocks in my
living room or whatever. Like, I don't know. I would do if I had like a crazy backyard is like
fake rock work, water slide. Oh yeah. I want like, I want a level slide. There we go. I can't,
it's beyond that. I would need like some more money to have that. I would need tens of millions
more dollars to have that. I will not real rocks. They're fake rocks guys.
But somebody has to design them and mold it. These are, these are artists and technicians.
I think you could figure it out. I really want to, a few weeks ago when we were like
looking at the star Wars land progress and we're like, wow, fake rocks looking real good.
Yeah. We're getting really good at these rocks. We love looking at the rocks and progress.
The rock is because right now you can see sort of like that inside the steel before they put
the fake rocks out of the new star Wars land. Cause they're building it. Um, we love literally
yawning fake rock caused the other, but it's not, it might not be unrelated.
I would want like, we're going to get in the car after this and drive down to Glendale,
down to the flower street campus. And you're going to meet some of the extended Disney family,
some of your extended family members in the engineering department. And they'll tell you
all about the fake rocks all day long. You know what, we're throwing the topic out. It's fake
rocks for the rest of this podcast. Change of plans. Sorry, Leland. Fake rocks from here on out.
I've been duped. It's an ambush. Jump in if you want, but we'll be talking anyway. Yeah. Um,
um, so good fake rocks. So good fake rocks in Florida. That's basically what I'm saying.
Here in, in, uh, Anaheim, there is a lovely giant painting inside.
Giant painting. I watched a panel from D 23, a few, a number of years ago about making this ride
and like someone they like paint it that it's like, it was a giant canvass like that. It was
painted and like had an insane, they were talking about how like the guy who was painting it had
like a brush with a single hair on it to like do the eyebrows of this painting. Like that's how
labor intensive it was. That sounds like the lore of a Disney movie. Like, it's like, get the brush
with a single hair and then you can find true love. It's an artifact that Ariel would find
in treasure and keep true that we've been, you know, we're talking about, uh, murals and rockwork
and so we haven't asked you why you chose this. What is your relationship with the rider with
the little mermaid in general? Um, it's the reason why I chose this one is because it snuck up on me
as far as how, how I would feel about it. Uh, I went last year, uh, with my dad and my little
brother and his girlfriend and, uh, it was one of the first rides we did of the day. So it's like,
we're all coffeeed up. It's like eight 30 or something like that. I'm just like, I'm still
trying to, you know, manage it. Like I, I have a thing when I'm with my family, I want to herd them
and I want to feel like I'm the person, like I want to be the guy, you know? And so like, I'm just
like, is everybody good? Is everybody, you know, like have, has gone to the bathroom, hungry,
whatever. And so like, I'm distracted. This is one of the first rides we go on in the day. There's
like no line. Yeah. And, uh, like you said, cause it's no line. Um, and we get it. I'm like, oh great.
Yeah. We can just like knock this one off. Like it's also, you know, my family has like a checklist
mentality when we go to the park. It's like, we got to do them all like Pokemon. Um, anyway, um,
I got to do them all the Pokemon. Great. Uh, you get it. Um, and like a third of the way into this ride,
I just start sobbing. Like it was, and I think what really made it so effective is that
I feel like a lot of the rides are usually like a take on the movie, you know? So it's like, uh,
uh, you know, it's like, oh, remember this from cars, you know, it's the, it's the cool, uh, like
low rider station, you know, but they give you something new. And I think that's, that's important,
you know, but what's special about the little mermaid ride is they don't give you anything new.
It's just straight up the scenes from the movie. It's the actual lyrics. Um, it's a, it's, it's
real voices. Yeah. It's the real voices. I think at least in the cases of any, if it's them singing,
if it's a, uh, or so are Ariel, it's the real recordings. And, and so it was like living
a movie, you know, it was, it was like being a child again, watching little mermaid and three
dimension. You can look wherever you want. And yeah. And so it was just like, it was layered
because it was like that movie I watched all the time as a kid. And you know, I was at Disneyland
with my family and which, you know, brings back those childhood memories too. And it was like,
just us on this ride. And it was like our own personal ride because there was no line and stuff
like that. And I'm like, it's beautiful. Like I was just like, and then I like pulled myself
together and it did not have the same effect on my family. Like, cool. Let's do California screaming.
Let's do a real ride. Um, but they probably like, I probably the ages line up where you were like,
you were super young and indelible and that must've been your movie. I think it was my movie.
Probably all of us to some extent was one of the first ones we were aware of,
or had been. So if they don't have the same, if that movie doesn't have the same pull,
yeah, it wasn't like my dad's childhood movie or my brother's, you know? Yeah, you're right. It was my
special movie that I watched again and again as a, as a tiny tot. Yeah. That's it. It's funny. And
you described that it has that effect on you even as an adult, because I imagine like that, like I
think it's neat and I like going on it. It's, but it's not, I, I, I, I'm always thinking like,
when you, when it spins you around and you see Ariel for the first time, probably young girls
must be so like heart drained. Yeah. It's nice to hear that is the case. Oh, it's, it was so true.
And I didn't even see it come in. I was like, oh, we're just having fun as a family. Does everybody,
has everybody gone to the bathroom? And it caught me. Was there a specific show scene or was it just
sort of all of it at once? Well, you know how bad I am with specifics. Sure. I mean, but it was like
not Ursula at the, like stealing the voice that would be, and you're like, oh, Ursula. I just want
that power. Was it Flotsam and Jetsam or what was, was it under the sea? It was under the sea. I think.
I think it was, it had to be under the sea because that's, that's where the whole party is.
Everybody's there. It's like a family under the sea is the family reunion of the little mermaid.
Yeah. Interesting. You know, everybody shows up. Right. The flute plays the lute and the car plays the harp.
Wow. And the boy fish blow. One thing again, listening to Imagine, the panel with the
Imagineers talking about building this ride. I mean, they, they encountered a thing that like a
lot of ride designers encounter when they're basing a ride on a movie. It's like, how do you
condense an hour and a half, two hours into a three minute experience. And with this one,
they said, well, we figured out, we just built it around the songs. Like we built,
essentially build it around the set piece because Little Mermaid was the first in like,
I mean, it was the first of like the big Disney animation revival in the late eighties and early
nineties with like Little Mermaid, Beauty and the Beast, Aladdin, Lion King, kind of all in a row.
And a lot of those kind of have like a Broadway musical sort of structure. So that's why, like,
you see under the sea and part of their world and kiss the girl. One thing that I always laugh at
in this ride, cause some, sometimes you to like condense a whole movie under ride, there's some
stuff that's gotta go, which in this one, there's no song for the let's kill Ursula at the end
sequence. So that's why she just kind of like at towards the end of the ride, she's just like
sinking in the background. Like there's no fight scene in the room. She's in the shadows.
Yeah. I think that- Her death has occurred off screen or she were watching her demise in progress,
I guess. Yeah. It's weird. I mean, that's the one that I think the first time anybody goes on it,
generally, I go, wait, what? There's a, there's a, like it skipped a scene. It skips a scene
because because the, because the ride is so literally the story, it, I feel like everyone
expects like we're going to watch a giant Ursula get stabbed by the mast of a ship and it doesn't
happen. It's a little dark. But you could still have like a giant Ursula somewhere in a ship sort
of like coming at her. So you don't have to actually show an impaling on a ride. Or do the
classic, there's some sort of, um, strobe-y the way the witch dies in snow white. Right. The witch
dies at the end of a snow white ride. Oh yeah. That's strobe. But we don't see the, the old
woman's corpse hit the ground or anything. Like, Oh my gosh. I mean, I don't know. Do you think if,
like, if they just didn't have any Ursula in it, like at the end, like would it kind of make the
ride feel not as whole? Like, I feel like the struggle is like, you gotta, like, like the whole
tension and stakes is like, you gotta get kissed before you become a little sea urchin guy, you
know? Um, and so it's like, that's the whole thing. And so once you do it, it's, it's like,
well, I guess we see them kiss at the very end. That's when they kiss in the movie.
They're, they presumably are in the, in the, in the kiss the girl sequence. Are they like leaning
in for a kiss? They don't kiss because Watson and Jepson, uh, top, top of the little boat.
Oh, that's right. Oh, I forgot. And that's the name of the Eels. Watson and Jepson.
Yeah. Alternate names for your body guards.
Don't like that. They are just like the actual Eels. Don't make eye contact. Make some angry guys.
Well, also though, characters, animatronics kissing is a hard thing. Does that occur in
any ride? Oh, that's a good question. Are there any rides where animatronics kiss?
It would be as awkward as the Mark Twain handshake. There's gotta be.
There's people again, yelling at the podcast right now, cause they know the answer to this.
All the dwarfs kiss. Remember all seven at one time.
Snow White makes them kiss for a reason. I like to think of as the,
the pirates of the Caribbean chasing, which is like, no, that's not kissing.
They're trying to get a kiss. Yeah. Yeah. Um, and pursuit.
We'll figure it out. We'll see if there's kissing with little mermaid. Yeah. I think
everyone has this, um, I, not every, but most people have an affection for a little mermaid
because as Jason was saying, it's like Disney got good again. And I mean, we were all little
at the time too. Um, so those, those few movies, we were talking about like the songs too, like
is part of your world probably like the best song of those move of Lion King, Aladdin, Beauty and the
beast. Oh, I don't know. It might resonate the most. I feel like people always say that's their
favorite. I feel like, well, I don't know if I'd say the best, but I think it's a very crucial
song in the really the revival of animation at Disney in general, because that is the heart of
Ariel and the character in the story. And it's a, and kind of a, you know, the, uh, the, the,
the character singing about what they want, which is some variances in that in most of those movies
you just described. And it's just such a soaring, uh, and supposedly isn't there some lore that
Eisner wanted to cut it? Oh, I've never heard that. I think this is addressed in some documentary,
which, and they, they had to plead, they had to say, how could you rip the heart out of this film?
We can, he's like, it's boring. It's not testing. Well, he like, really, hopefully I'm not throwing
him under the bus, but I feel like that is a true story. I don't know how seriously it was considered.
Katzenberg tried to cut it. Katzenberg, Katzenberg. Try apologize to Michael Eisner, Scott.
Officially apologize to Michael Eisner. Apologize to Michael and apologies to Breck, his son, who
we would love to have. We want all the Eisner's podcast to talk about all the rides that he
inspired. It's such a, like, it's such a huge, uh, want song, right? That's the Broadway term.
A one song is like a big part of a lot of musicals. Yes. And every Disney movie has that one. Like
Mulan has the reflection song. Yeah. Aladdin has the street rat song. And the Beast, the, uh,
I want adventure in the great white. So that, which is the very like, um, sound of music kind of.
Oh, so sound of music. Yeah. Uh, does, does blanking have one? He's going to be a king.
I'm going to be a mighty king. Yeah. I guess that's a one way. It doesn't always have to be a.
That's his literal want. Like out of all the songs, that's the most, that's one. It's like,
this is what I want. The title explains the desire. I was just thinking, because often these songs are
like these kind of stirring melancholy, but I guess in that case it's a fun one. Yeah. The Mrs. Pot song from Beauty and the
What is that called? Mrs. Pot sings the, I was trying to think, I was thinking more about
part of your route being like a very emotional, uh, song in terms of like, can you feel the love
tonight or tail as old as time? That's the love song. She doesn't have a want song about wanting to
pour tea out of her nose. No, no, no, no. That's like the, can you feel the love tonight? Yeah.
That's the kiss the girl, you know, the, that's what that, um, that song plays in the Mrs. Pot says no wants of her own.
Whatever you want, dearie. She's just happy to be there. I just want Chip to move out. I don't want him to
steal. When he's an adult, I mean, when he's of age appropriate, I just don't want him crashing in the
basement of the castle for too long. Find a girlfriend. Just meet a nice girl, a nice cup girl. But didn't,
part of your world is, part of your world is like, is the, if it's the first one of those, what became
a trope by the time, because much more like, uh, uh, calculatingly that song exists and like hunchback,
um, uh, or, and just around the river bend is good, but we're starting to get people are a little
less moved by these, these want songs. And then which takes you into the South park, um, uh, uh,
what's it called? Bigger, Longer, Uncut, which has the devil's want song. By the time they were doing
that movie, it was like a, such a trope that there is the want song. I don't know if that takes us
into South park. That's a hard turn, Scott. Why me? Like, you know, you know how like little mermaid takes us to
lion king that takes us to Pocahontas, you know, and then we go to South park naturally. Well, that is
interesting because there was a Terrence and Philip cameo in this ride originally. No,
no, my mind wouldn't make it past that piece of trivia. That's too much. Well, there is, we're
going to get to, we're going to, I mean, I guess we're going to get to it now. There is, stop that.
You creeped out by that. What's that crab doing buddy? Stop that.
Now we know you're scared of Terrence and Philip. Yeah. It's just the combination is just creepy,
creepy. It's weird. Yeah. The, uh, that I was going to say though, the quick, we'll quickly go,
we'll go back to this topic, but the, the cameo on this ride, which might be my favorite part of this
ride. What? I don't know. Do we not know this? So it's only, I believe in California, but if,
when you're on the ride in the end of the sea room, if you look kind of behind your clam shell,
cause it's pointing to more toward the action. If you look toward the end, as you're exiting the,
the incredible Mr. Limp it, the fish, the Don knots fish character from the old movie is in shadow.
He's not a Disney character. He's a Warner Brothers character and he is hidden on the ride.
And I look for him every time I'm delighted by this bizarre choice to put him on there.
How's this never come up? You've never, I didn't, you never seen, we've talked about this. Yeah.
We've been on this ride, I think at the same time, and I'm surprised I wasn't just talking
about Mr. Limp it the whole time. Yelling back out of your, there he is. Look kids cheering for an
old Don knots movie. Here, I'll find a picture of it. Yeah. Yeah. So that is such a cool Easter egg.
I have not heard why they did it. He's a fish. I guess is all you need to know. And there's probably
a fan and he's the only like, here he is. Whoa. Mr. Limp it. It's a picture. That's so fun.
It's my favorite thing. Accurate enough, but also copyright free enough. Yeah. Yes. And he's just
kind of peeking out. He doesn't move or anything. Isn't now there's some weird thing that our buddy
Andrew Grissom talks about where they, there was like an, there's artwork you can find of a Mr.
Limp it remake with Jim Carrey. Is that correct? Someone else where like you can see a fishified
modern actor and it's very terrifying, like, like nightmare concept art that makes you glad
there was no film. Does that ring a bell though? Is that? Yeah. This is what Don knots. This is the
movie. The fish looks like I'm a little weird. So yeah, that's another very timely reference.
That's a cool little trivia. Yeah. So that's, that's very fun. And that's the only like
fish out of water on the ride. Ooh. As far as I know, I mean, I haven't seen, there's no like
secret, uh, apple dumpling gang animatronic, the other Don knots Disney movie. Yeah. What are their
famous cartoon fish? I mean, yeah, there should just be more Don knots animatronics on this ride.
I think fish police arresting her. So, Oh, wait. Oh, now I'm forgetting. I, you know what,
as part of this, I was recalling that there was a little mermaid animated series. Yes. There was
an animated series where she had like a buddy. I didn't watch it. I don't know. I've maybe was it
on Disney channel. It was, um, not sure it may have been syndicated and it was like, it was kind of
like the movie never happened. Like Ariel was a mermaid. She has a buddy, like I forget the guy's
name, but she had a friend who was like, uh, another kid flounder and, and, uh, they're all in it.
I think she's got a little orca friend too. I'm looking it up as fast as I can, but I think there
were like fish police esque elements in the show. Like they're, oh, there, yeah, there's a,
a race of shark, like merfolk, uh, who are like, uh, mean and like, and shady like sharks. And
they're called the shark canians. Wow. Really? That's the, it's something you didn't know about
little mermaid world, the shark canians. And there's another, there's another like mobster group.
I'll, I'll interject if I find it. And then one, the other bizarre, oh, there's a lot, the lobster
mobster. So there's a lot of crossover between the odd failed show fish police and the little
mermaid animated show. There was, there's an underworld that Triton has to deal with.
You think Triton's just like a king in theory, but he's got to like cut deals with the
sea underworld. Tony's a piano or something. He's keeping the, keeping the sea together.
I mean, that was in the era of like, you know, these big tent pole Disney movies would come out
and the sequels would either be TV shows or like direct to videotape, like the return of Jafar.
Yes. Yeah. Aladdin movie. They weren't valuing these things as many multi-sequel. I think
Toy Story 2 was probably what, what broke it, which itself was going to be straight to video.
Right. Yeah. Until they bought Pixar and retooled. The other thing I want to say about the show is
that there is an episode where Ariel meets a young author who she comes to know is Hans Christian
Anderson. She saves him and he's looking for inspiration for a book and boy does he find it
with the little mermaid and he writes the book and becomes the author we know and love today.
And Hans Christian Anderson is voiced by Mark Hamill. Wow. That is incredibly meta.
Yeah. Very weird. And then there was a Tarzan. And that's cool because it's like, that's the
beginning of the marriage of Star Wars and Disney. Yes. This is the, yeah, actually canonically,
that's where it, that's the juncture point. That's where it started. Really the tale begins with,
but then there was also a Tarzan animated series where they did the same plot with Edgar
Respiros. Oh really? Where he meets Tarzan and inspires. So, and this, this all, this is all
like what we talked about just recently with, you know, chubby checker learning the twist from,
from the quantum leap guy. Right. White guys teaching black guys that about their famous thing,
basically. But in this case. Like getting back to the future. It's that authors have no ideas
and they steal them from accidental run-ins when they get lost in the jungle or the sea.
Just real quick here is the concept art of what the Jim Carrey fish was going to look like.
That is terrifying. No, no, no. That's a no go. Oh God. Oh wow. It's a. Are you going to say you
like this? Like the baby Grinch? Hold on. Let me see it again. Maybe I like it. It does look like
the baby Grinch. Do you put these pictures like up when this? Yes. We'll show it. Yeah. I still,
I still like baby Grinch. I like baby Grinch more than this. Okay. Cause baby Grinch from the movie,
the Grinch, the Jim Carrey Grinch movie. He is a little scary, but he's, I like him. He's cute.
And I think I'm not alone is what I'm saying. Also, you know, if they had made that movie,
Jim Carrey would have gone really method. Like he would have insisted in floating in a pool all day.
If he got out of the pool, he'd be like, I can't breathe the air. Is that something that Jim Carrey
does? Is he a method actor? Well, kind of on the man on the moon. I think on the man on the moon.
That's different because like Andy Coffman was such a. He was, it was a level of commitment.
But you're saying he wouldn't have gone full fish. He wouldn't have gone full limpet.
He wouldn't have gone full. Jason's remarks about him are untrue. I don't think that like
Jim Carrey tried to break into an insane asylum, liked for research for pet detective, you know,
like either one he could use one for the other. We're the number 23. Well, he has, he's since gone
method. He's stayed as his number 23 characters since the release of the film. That's a good point.
Um, so, okay, we're talking. He's not in it. What have we missed? Oh, you know, the songs and the
songs and the ride. That's a weakness. So another interesting thing about the ride, uh, uh, that
the imaginators talked about was if you think about the ending of the movie, the little mermaid,
they get married during the day on a boat, which is difficult. It's difficult to do daytime in,
in dark rides in Disneyland style dark rides. It's difficult to simulate daytime inside. That's why
a lot of them, I mean, that's why they're called dark rides. Cause it's usually darker because you
have to hide stuff in the dark. So they had to get approval and pitch like the end of this.
What if they get married and it's night and what if it's just like them waving from a castle instead
of a boat? Yeah. That's why the end, the end is a little different. And some of the fish come back
and King Triton is waving at you. Yeah, I do remember that. I was like, okay. Yeah. Yeah.
This isn't right, but fine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. King Triton, a very handsome animatronic at the end.
Yeah. He's, I always notice him. He like, he's in a good shape, but like he looks younger than King
Triton does in the movie. I feel. Yeah. Uh, he has, he looks, I mean, if it weren't for his like
white flowing hair and beard, he would just be like a hunk Fabio same body of like Hercules,
you know, like it's just like the same template, you know? Uh, but was he really that like,
he was jacked in the film. Okay. Without that white hair on the animatronic, he has a very small head.
Really now? Yeah. I guess that might be a giant body at a tiny head because it's like, well,
you don't need to finish the head if it's going to be covered in hair. Yeah. He's jacked, but he
does look like more of an old man in the cartoon. Like he looks, he's Jack. He's like a jacked old
man. He's like her all over the hair. Mostly hair, you know, you've seen that picture of her all dough
with his shirt off. He's 70, like he's incredible shape. I have not exaggerated. The beard is,
I mean, it's a huge, all those selfie. I'm good. It looks like he has a small head in the cartoon
as well. It's consistent. Is it, I think it's, I'm freaked out by him because he has the real hair
and Ariel has the odd plastic hair that was issue kind of in making the ride. Hey, we got her all
together. Jacked as a King Triton, but he's in good shape. He's 70 year old man. I mean,
he's a good shape. I'm glad that Triton is like sunken lower in the sea. So as to not see his
pelvic region, unlike the her all the selfie, you just, I don't want to know what's on the way
to the balls. Her all the must've seen the DeAngelo video recently. And he was trying to
recreate that with that picture. He's not, but DeAngelo doesn't have that much more going on
than her all though. Her all those not looking bad there. Yeah. Um, so it's got no mustache. So,
Oh, that's another DeAngelo is hidden in this ride. There's a brief DeAngelo.
Who is DeAngelo? Uh, he was a singer, the singer, he had the, the, the music video. That's just one
long revolve around his perfect body. Uh, is a very sensual R and B.
How does it fit? Okay. Scott'll do a couple of minutes of the song for you right now.
Can you just please. You can't understand a Leela. That's basically what it is. Uh,
All right. He's good. Does this look familiar? This man, this is the video. Uh, I mean, no.
Okay. And whose butt, if you look at him versus her all the versus Triton, who's, who's back in the
very cut. We'll do a poll. Who do you like best? Try to draw the DeAngelo shirtless guy of all
types. We already narrowed it down to three. We all agree that the top three, but who's the top one?
Right. Please decide for us audience. We have a huge bracket on a white board here in the
recording space. Uh, sure do. And this is what we all want to, sorry, my guards had to take that down.
So yeah, it was casting a weird shadow on my face. They're always looking out for me, you know?
Yeah. So we've, we've put it, I've put it off long enough to the, this is the thing we have to talk
about to many people. And I will consider myself included. This ride is a little disappointing.
I find, I find that Jason, do you not disagree? I'm so sorry. I was curious. Uh, I know why though
it's, it's so Lizzie and I went, we went up, it was an eight back when they used to do an AP preview,
which was an annual pass holder preview for a ride. Now these days they're doing like a $300 party
that you have to pay in addition to your pass to go on in these rides early. We waited, I think
four hours for this. We were very excited. Uh, three or four hours. Um, and we went on and we
were like, it's fine. And I feel like that was a review that this ride got a lot, like, oh, no,
no, it was nice, but it feels a little still. It feels a little static. It doesn't, uh, it doesn't
do to me what pirate pirate, excuse me. Uh, Peter Pan does it. It doesn't transport you as much.
Uh, I, I agree with that. I think that if you had to wait four hours with anticipation, I think that
it was just kind of this happy, you know, planets aligning of, of it's just like, it was bright in
the day and we were just, we were there. I think what made that experience for me so magical is
that it was just like, it was kind of thrust upon us before we even know, knew what was happening.
Sure. Um, but yeah, it doesn't move very quickly. And like I said, it doesn't give you a lot of
things that are new and things that are new are like, just like confusing. Well, I think even
that three or four hour, like I waited for it. There's a, the Harry in, in, at the Harry Potter in
Florida, there's this ride escape from Gringotts, which is like a roller coaster with like show
scenes. Like you're trying to get out of the bank and escape from Voldemort. And I waited three or
four hours the summer that opened and I was afterwards, it's like, yeah, it was good. I was
glad I did it, but I feel like shit. But I'm going to say, like when I say we waited three or four
hours, I'm not trying to say, oh my God, we were depressed and like, that's going to affect the
ride. I've been on, we went, we waited three or four hours for guardians of the galaxy last year
and we loved it. When I was younger, three, three or four hours for Spiderman in Orlando, we loved
it. Well, I mean, yeah, like if you wait three or four hours and then you just get like suspended
air and dropped over and over again to eighties music, like, like you're going to completely
forget like that you waited all that time. Yeah. I guess the endorphins like take over. Yeah. And
the same thing happens with Peter Pan. Peter Pan is, I think it's the most popular ride at Disneyland.
Is that right? You guys would know. Well, it's not, I mean, it's all the first certainly,
sir. Certain it's the dark ride. That's the most popular. It's always the long, like, yeah, it always
has the one. I believe it's the one that fast passes don't work on, right? Something like that.
They don't have fast passes for any of those. They have it in Florida, but they
don't have it out here for the family. My dad's favorite ride. Yeah. Cause my dad really likes it
too. Yeah. Yeah. That's his little mermaid, I guess. Yeah. But I can completely understand,
uh, just because there's a whole like, yeah, like that is a transport.
It's a ride. It's when we're talking about when imagine, like I've, we've talked about Mr. Tony
Baxter, who was one of the top imagineers of all time. He didn't make this ride, but he, he calls
this type of ride and many people do, and many message board people do call this more of a book
report ride versus, you know, Peter Pan. It's, it's a ride that just kind of tells you what happens
as opposed to what does Peter Pan do that? Uh, it's not quite as like Peter Pan has moments
where you're just flying over the city. It's, you're the sort of star of the story as opposed
to little mermaid where you're watching things happen. Peter Pan has show scenes and stuff,
but it's not so dependent on a narrative. It's not like you go through the things that happen in the
movie where you're the car that's out of control. Yeah. You're you're it's your adventure. That's
sort of what Tony Baxter talks about. You crash your in hell. Yeah. That ride ends in hell. So
I guess they could have had Ursula getting killed. Uh, I don't know. There's something just so like,
I mean, I didn't even remember that in the movie until you mentioned it. She gets impaled by it.
Oh yeah. It's crazy. Because she is like a Kaiju level monster. Like even like Gaston, he just like
drops off a building and we assume that he's dead, but he disappears in like literal fog.
Right. We don't see him splat. Yeah. Yeah. Where it's like, you just see it, you know, like,
like, and it's so, it's a close up, you know, it's so intense. All the deaths are like, Scar
gets eaten by the, uh, people he was praying to a little while ago. That's true. This is the one
where you see it the worst. You're right. Yeah. Oh geez. And like, she's like, oh, like it's just
like terribly upsetting. What is Jafar ultimately? He goes back in the lamp. He goes in a lamp.
Snake is before Jeannie. He's a big snake. He turns into the snake and then he tricks. Yeah. Then
he tricked or they trick him into saying he wants to be a Jeannie and he gets put in the lamp.
So he's trapped. So there's no like, yeah, it's not a bloody, he doesn't get murdered. Yeah.
He doesn't get stabbed to death. Got it. So, so, so yeah, so that's a, that's what, uh,
you reminded me of a point I wanted to make. I feel like it, a ride, the way it affects you
depends on, I think, where you are in your life as well, because I feel like I'm now in like a new
stage of Disneyland appreciation where it's, but I felt like the longest stage of it's like bigger,
faster, better, you know? Uh, and so I didn't want to waste my time on like the Snow White ride when
I could do, um, like, uh, Space Mountain and Star Tours and, uh, Indiana Jones and, uh, and Peter Pan
I could, I can handle because it's like, that's the one that felt like it was moving the most.
You know, Mr. Toad was like, Whoa, that's the one that's like a smaller ride. That's not as intense
where it's just like, wow, that you still get like a lot of like action and endorphins and stuff like
that. And, oh gosh, like you had to do it's a small world, but yeah, like I would just kind of like
grit my teeth and smile through it. Cause it's like the family wants to do it, you know? But like,
but that ride, The Little Mermaid hit me at a point where I was so open to nostalgia.
And so as far as a ride itself, I agree with you, it ranks lower than Peter Pan and blah, blah, blah.
Um, but as far as a nostalgic experience, it's, uh, top notch because like you said, Scott,
it goes slow. So it's like a two white wine ride. And like, there was so much time to absorb those
memories and recall those memories and stuff like that. So yeah.
Huh. I'm trying to think of what the, like, how do you resolve this exactly?
Exactly. Here's the thing. I think I did it really well.
No, no, no. I just mean, what is the fix? I mean, like if you were going to be more actively,
are you, are you going to talk about this? What's going on there?
Pre-alternate ride. So on one of the DVDs, they were trying to make this ride. They were,
they've been trying to make this ride for years. Yeah. They were going to make it in the 90s and
put it in most of the magic kingdom style parks around the world. And it's like, in, uh, I took
Disneyland Paris that has never been filled by anything. And it's mentioned on a special,
it's described by Melanie Griffith as like a something it's cause she, she in this very
sedate manner, like in 1994, Ariel will join the family. It's a very odd clip.
And this is the sort of thing they don't really do anymore. When we had Eva Anderson on, like,
you know, we showed, uh, uh, the clips of, or we talked about her, there was a Disneyland history
special that her father had hosted. And like, and it's like, here's all the rides coming in the next
five years. And most of them didn't happen. And Ariel was mentioned in that. And so when they put
out the little mermaid on like special edition DVD in like 2006, this was in the special features.
It's a CG animated, like here's what the ride was exactly what the ride would have been.
And we're watching it here. So yeah. So like it starts out in like a cool, like it's like wreckage
of ships and the dark ride thing. Yeah. So like, it's almost the start of pirates where you're like,
you're in a place, but then very quickly you're about to go under the sea. Yeah. So I would say
that the ride itself does not really honor like the dark ride can do, you know, um, this is spooky
and cool. This is spooky. It's more like place making going on in this you'd say, right? We got
Prince Eric's ship. Uh, so instead of just, you round a corner and Ariel's in Ariel, Ariel, like
emerges from the shadows and this grim seascape and she brings light to it. And then you go
under the sea. And what is the deal with this? How was this going to work? You mean the, how the water
I've heard Tony back to talk about this. So they were going to work. They were going to do like,
it was going to be like laser, like a laser to like make the like surface different from
the water. So it would be like missed and laser. So it would look like there was like a layer of
water and then you would go under it and then it would be lit differently. Once you got down there
to make it completely look like the bubble transition parts in the existing ride is very
pleasant. I enjoy it. I like going under and coming out of them. I think it's clever that they use
the blank space of the shells to project the bubbles. They like, yes, and they changed that.
They had to add more bubbles as the, as I think after thing happened. So yeah, this is just more,
it's just more like kind of in the Peter Pan tradition. You see stuff that happens from the
movie, but it's sort of like, you're kind of going on your adventure, exploring this world.
Yeah. As opposed to just sort of, yeah, like you're just watching examples of book report rides.
Yeah, I'm trying to think. I mean, like kind of the monsters ink ride in California adventure is
a little, is like that. Yeah. You're not really, there's no real premise. Like you're the most,
there's a monster on the loose or there's a kid shot and Lisa Monstropolis, but how are you?
Yeah, it's a little duty within that story. Yeah. Which is opposed to like radiator Springs racers
and cars land. It's kind of like, yeah, you see the characters, but it's sort of new. It's telling
like a new, you're in cars, you're coming to radiator Springs, you're going to race that
the adventure you have to get right. Most of them aren't, if they have a property, most of them are
sort of their own little original thing, not a rich, completely original, but like have that element
of like kind of exploration. However, what you just showed, does that really solve that? Well,
first of all, what vehicle, what's the ride? You know, what's interesting is that, that, uh,
that simulation has a couple of like pirates of the Caribbean ish elements to it. Especially like
the shipwrecks and the mist and stuff. Like I watched, it reminded me cause there's a different
sort of pirates ride in Disneyland Shanghai. And it seems like that is kind of big moments in that
ride. Remind me of this animatic. Yeah. Yeah. So the, the vehicle was not just sort of a, uh,
a thing that would be on the ground. And it was not, it was like something that would be kind of
suspended in the middle. Basically. I mean, there was, I think you can see to the start here. Um,
it's like, I think it's like technically hanging from the ceiling. It's what kind of shell,
it would make you feel like you were floating. You're in a big shell and it's that like corkscrew.
Right. It's a mollusk kind of shell. Uh, um, but yeah, wait, I don't even know what I'm looking.
It's not from above, but yeah, there's two, there's two like wires that are hanging. So like you would
be a little suspended and it will allow you to kind of like Bob, which would make you feel a little
bit more like you're under water. Why didn't they do it? It's, I'm sure it's just politics. It's just
like, what, whatever expense is a big thing. Watching, watching that, cause I watched that
through a couple of times and it's also like, uh, uh, it looks like the blue sky version of that
ride. Cause like, yeah, they would have to invent a new ride system for that. Also like trying to
wrap my head around the space of that building that it could go in. It would have had to have been
huge. Right. It would have been probably a different building. The show scenes in that are very large.
It's a double decker. If we haven't described this properly, you're, you're like, it's all surrounding
the boat and this stuff above the water and below the water. So it's this double decker ride,
which I agree makes it a more interesting setting to explore. Uh, it's like how Alice in Wonderland
is made more interesting by the fact that you're going upstairs and you go outside for a bit and
then go back into this different room. Yes. That just that subtle that it's this double decker
thing makes it more interesting. So, so yeah, this is just look, the ride I, I, I'm being on the ride
is some cool robots. The Ursula robot is awesome. That scene when that's my favorite, I think,
scene in the whole thing is when she's in front of she's singing poor unfortunate souls. Incredible
the animatronic. It's huge. Like, you know, we've gotten stuck there and that's great. Like, oh,
please last longer. I wanted to stare at the robot more. Um, but I do think a lot of people
have a feeling after they get off of it, like, good, good. Like, and it doesn't, that's, that's
my feel. I wouldn't argue with you there, but I don't mind that feeling. I think some riots can
have that. Sure. I also think like Leland, I thought you brought up a great point about like
how you are feel the context you are in going into a ride can affect it. Cause I remember going on
this. Uh, I, when I first went on it, like it would have been a little while after a couple
months after it opened. So it maybe had a little weight, but not a huge weight. And it was like,
the context for me was like, Oh, this is a new ride. This is one part of the big like redo of
California adventure. And I was like, yeah, this was nice. This is a very pleasant ride. And also
like was greatly missing from this park. Like for years, this park had very few rides period, let
alone these kinds of like classic Disney dark ride. So I was like, Oh yeah, this makes it. And
now it's technically was in the San Francisco section of the park. So that doesn't entirely
make sense, but yeah, that's a weird thing. Like where it's like this, it's, she's like the outcast
prince. Yeah. Everybody else is chilling in fantasy land. Like, and it's just like, you have
to get to Ariel, like all the way into another park. You were in the Bay area. She's, she's,
she's very privileged. She's, she can afford to live in the Bay area. So why wouldn't you?
That real estate. But yeah, so I guess in my sense, so I did not have like a huge weight for it. And,
and I was kind of like, Oh yeah, there's construction walls up everywhere. So I'm just
kind of happy to be on something, be on something in 2000, fall of 2011. I guess like the statement,
I was just happy to be on something. It doesn't sound like a ring endorsement, but it was also
like, Oh yeah, more of this to come. And then it was good. Good world of color. Uh, came right
around that time. Yeah. Um, but you know, I really like seeing that, um, animation of the, what the
ride was gonna be originally, because I've never really thought about the architecture of rides.
I've never really thought about it, you know, and, and, and I, I like thinking about now,
cause that does make me appreciate it's like, Oh yes, there's a lot of thought. And it's like,
this ride is to make you feel like you're on a bubble. And this ride is to make you feel like
you're flying in the air. And this one is to make you feel like you're trapped in a jungle, you know,
like, um, or like on a, on a rickety car, like, uh, that's, uh, like through a temple and, and,
and it's like, Oh yeah, there's a, there are people who, um, have spent a lot of time and teams,
like in perfecting, you know, how to make it feel like you are running through a temple. And,
and that's so cool. Yeah. Never thought about them. Things are like impossible to achieve. So,
you know, in the, like I've said before, like sometimes you're dealing with like military grade
technology things that like, so like star tours or whatever, like the simulators had not really
been in the public before. Like, so to be able to create some of these feelings, you have to
deploy very crazy new technology and which is probably also very expensive. And I bet when
they were analyzing, how do we get this little mermaid ride into that space? I bet it was like,
we got to take out that movie theater quick. And so we can't do this double decker thing.
And it was also probably, let's do a vehicle very similar to the haunted mansion so that it's not
an new untested technology. Like what you're showing costs. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, cost has a
lot to do with it, but then like, I do think politics, like politics and up like this guy,
Tony Baxter is clearly like salty about the version of the little mermaid that's in the park
now. And he's, he's of course, we've talked about him many times, big thunder star tours,
figment in Florida, uh, splash mountain. He did all these, like the main guy in church of all those,
but he's like cranky. You can hear he's cranky about this version of the ride being in here
because he knows there was a better version. And it probably like, when he walks by it, he goes,
oh, like he's upset about it. It took them like over a decade just to get this made. So I'm sure
it was also like handed off from designers and teams and stuff just in terms of politics, but
like, yeah, I mean, cost is a factor too, cause however many, was it a couple billion to revitalize?
Yeah. So like if one thing turns out more expensive, they have to take the money from
something at that balance, the book somewhere else. I always wonder also if this, if the, uh,
if, if, if it kind of backwards, if it was backwards dictated, like the Disneyland one, um,
caused the Florida one to have to be a little less interesting. Like if, if they weren't jamming,
cause it's, it's kind of copy pasted for the most part in terms of layout and everything. So,
so in other words, is the Florida one, the exact same layout as the, as the whoopee Goldberg
theater, like did they have to make it exactly the same? I watched, there's a video where you
can watch both rides side by side, which is a disorienting experience, but they are pretty
much identical. The lines felt identical. Yeah. The lines are clearly different and the loading
areas a little different, but like, yeah, I mean, Florida benefits Florida is sitting though. The
one in Florida is sitting on top of what used to be 20,000 leagues under the sea. That's where
it's located in the Florida park, but I, by putting it in fantasy land, like, I mean, it's
literally called fantasy land. So there's like a carousel next to the dwarves house next to a,
the Winnie the Pooh ride next to, uh, the, the beauty and the beast be our guest castle restaurant
is what you're saying to the little mermaid. So yeah, it's just kind of like everything can be
next to each other. All your toys are on the floor. Yeah. Kids love it. Yeah. That's the funnest time.
You know, you had a good time with it. Yeah. You're aware you have to show us the, cause the one big
difference. Oh yes. There's a big Ursula here. You do look at that. Yeah. Yeah. There's a massive
Ursula and there's a slide next to the ride. You do get the Ursula death. Probably the biggest
difference in this version. Is that, is that better? Do we like that? Yeah. Oh yeah. And then,
I think six year old Scott doesn't like it. Six year old Scott is screaming and crying.
I think 32 year old Scott also probably doesn't like the giant Ursula. Well, I talked about how
I don't like big things in small rooms. Like I am afraid of the giant boo in a super Mario world.
Right. Like, Oh, on the video, just on the straight video game. Giant, the, yes, I'm not even there.
When I see my avatar of Mario paired with a gigantic boo, I freak the fuck, it gives me this weird
spatial relation. It scares the shit out of me. So this Ursula gives me some of that big boo feeling.
What an interesting phobia. What do you think about in small rooms? I feel like weird body tension,
even talking about big boo. It's the thing I'm the most afraid of. If big boo, like imagine
we're in a pretty like, you know, like I guess it's kind of a small like living room here. And if
boo was filling all of it, Jesus Christ. What if like Mike had like a giant like great America
stuffed teddy bear or something? That's fine. I feel we're the size of the room. If it were all
the way up to the ceiling. I guess I just think that was odd. I saw your eyes. You looked at the ceiling.
Yeah. And you're like your pupils got smaller. You went big things. Maybe freak me out. Let me ask
you this. How do you feel about the big Muppets? You mean like sweetums? Like sweetums or like,
I'm thinking of, do you know the Muppet Christmas Carol? Yeah. The ghost of Christmas present.
He's like a large man. He's like, he's a large, jolly man, but he is like one of the big walk
around Muppets. Or I feel like there's some of the lab or just sort of like the big kind of Muppets.
Not if, if your size is big already, then it's fine. But if you are supposed to be small and
then you become big. I know you're a small version. Now you're big. Is your worst movie like Alice in
Wonderland? There is weird stuff with Alice in Wonderland. Yeah. Yeah. This for this drinking
in the ground. Because that's exactly what that whole movie is. Yeah. I think it freaked me out
when she like grows and is the size of the house. It's an upsetting thing to think about happening
to you. I don't think that this bothers you, but I'm just curious. I just want to really explore
this. I like the tests. Thanks for this therapy session. So like part of the Disney channel fan
fest is we took pictures with Mike and Sully and we were in an enclosed space, maybe like this
living room-ish. And Mike is like four feet tall, which is really interesting. But Sully was like
eight feet tall. Does that make you feel weird? Weirdly, no. But I bet my wife would feel weird
about it because we all met Chewbacca together. And when Chewbacca rounded the corner in that
tight little corridor, she like, ah, like, I think because he so filled the small. And he's so real.
And he's a hugger. And he's a hugger. He is a hugger. He'll grab you. I think again, I don't know
the size of Sully. He could be that, but here's what I was going to say back to the Muppets,
is that when there's walk around Muppets, which there have been in the parks a little bit,
when there's a man sized Kermit freaks me out a little. Yeah, because Kermit is supposed to be
small. Yes. And Sully is supposed to be big. So it's like, okay. Or I just don't know. You can
define for me for the first time how big Sully is supposed to be. I'm kind of weirded out by,
maybe not scared of, but I think it's funny to go back to Mrs. Potts that in the Beauty and the Beast
live shows that there is a Mrs. Potts that is much bigger than Belle. I'm not scared of that,
but I think it's strange. Two questions. Scared of the baby in Honey, I Trunked the Kid,
I Blew Up the Kids? No, no. I don't think I have any like weird childhood trauma from that. Amazingly.
Yeah. Scared of animal at the end of Muppet movie, when animal grows giant. Oh. Because I actually
think if I think about it, I was a little uncomfortable by how big he was. Maybe I've
blocked that out. Maybe I avoided. You don't even remember it because there's a big showdown. Mommy,
I don't want to watch that one. I just politely requested. You know what, actually, but maybe
that's an outdoor, this is the strangest specific issue we're dealing with. I think I'm, if I'm
freaked out by any of Honey, I Blew Up the Kid, it's when the kid is in the living room as opposed
to walking around the street. If I've got, if there's open air, I'm fine. Big Boo with open sky
is okay, but if I'm in a room and it's just me as Mario and Big Boo, that's the scariest thing.
If you're in Bowser's Castle, it's bad, but if you're in Mumu Farms, it's fine. Yes, because I know,
you know, I could, I could fly away. He could fly away. I can get away from him easy. I'm not
tripped. I'm going to go the other direction. Do you know Mulholland Drive, the David Lynch movie?
I haven't seen it in decades. Okay. Do you remember there's an old couple in it that they're like
riding a bus at one point? I don't remember this. Okay. So there's a sequence where there's like an
old touristy couple and they get on a bus and they're really like creepily smiling and they
don't say anything. And you're like, and it's kind of comes out in nowhere. And then you don't see
them again for a while. And then at some point, like one of the versions of Naomi Watts, cause
there's like two realities in that movie. She like lies down on the couch in her living room. And
then it, it cuts, there's a shot of the door, the front door of the house. And it's like about
an inch gap between like the door and the floor. And there's just teeny tiny versions of that old
couple like running and are screaming. And then they get into the room and I think they like pop
up to big size and like terrorize her. But I just remember watching that and these teeny tiny couple
of like, Oh no, how did they get small? Yeah, that might do it for you know, uh, Edwin,
just as I said that Edwin just very quietly walked into my field of vision. Edwin is very small and
he has just returned from a walk, but if he came back from the walk and was the size of the room,
this podcast would be over forever. If he was like coming back here, we got to do it outside.
From now on, if he was Clifford size. Oh yeah. Oh, maybe I'm scared of Clifford. Yeah. He hates
Clifford. I might hate Clifford. I think I actually prefer, wasn't there another Clifford where
Clifford was small? I think I chose the normal size around on his knees. I mean, that's a terrifying,
that's a Freudian terrifying movie. What if you're big like, like when you go into Toontown and
there's like small, small things. No, I don't think I have issues there because I'm, I have the power.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. But you're the oppressor. I'm having one more and then we'll move off of
this. We better move off of it. Uh, I think the, I think maybe I was somewhere as a kid and there
was a, a walk around Kool-Aid man. It freaked me the fuck out. I don't want to keep adding to this.
I was scared of giant balloons in front of car dealerships as a child. So if it was a giant
ape, there was like a giant eight balloon. I didn't like it. And once my dad one time made me go up
and like touch one of them to like, to break my fear of it. I kind of, I think I was still kind
of uncomfortable because there would be like, if we were driving down the expressway, um, there would
be like, like maybe there's something promote, I don't know what it would be being promoted,
but seven of them would be in a line. And I remember kind of just like looking to the left.
So I guess I had that too. Now that I think about it. Well, I think I would have had the same issues
with you, but only if it was indoors. Uh, that's where these, these particular deviations of these
fears. Very bizarre. Anyway, to bring it back to the, I, so what I'm saying is, uh, uh, fuck this
ride, uh, fuck Tony Baxter. I don't want this giant earth. So they'll get it out of here. The
ride is perfect. I'm going to enjoy my wine and not see any giant things. It'll be the only ride
you're out that day. So to sum up, you are saying keep as is Scott, cause Leland, so what we do at
the end is we say like, what would you do to the right? Would you keep it perfectly as is,
would you plus it up? Do you have any ideas or would you burn it down, uh, in a mysterious fire
for insurance money? I'm mysterious. Uh, no, I keep as is. That's why I brought it up. Okay.
Jason. Well, you know, uh, a couple of years after the ride open, they did like, uh, uh,
some minor plus it ups. Like they, they changed the, the hair, like this is such a weird thing
to talk about that the hair in the under the seat sequence, Ariel's hair, like they tried to mold
the hair. So it looks like the one shot in that sequence when she's like swimming directly down.
And so her hair is above her in the water. So they tried to recreate that in three in physical space.
And a lot of people's complaints were that it like, this looks like she has a beehive, like a fifties
I do. Yeah. It looks like an ice cream cone. It looks like, yeah. So I'll serve ice cream. So they
changed that. And they also changed, like, there's some sequences with screens where like when she's
transforming that were much more CGI 3d back in the day. And then they kind of changed it to be more
2d animated in the style of the movie, which I think works. So I think like, and then they added
some more fish, I think throughout it. So like, I think just keep adding to, I like seeing little
touches to rides, like little plus ups, more animatronics, more fish. I say fill that under
the sea room with fish. Like I want there to be so many fish. Uh, not that they would form a giant
Voltron Scott that you would be uncomfortable. Thanks for anticipating my worry. Uh, but like,
yeah, more, more, uh, dance. Oh, you brought me to the worst one of all the fish that swallows you.
Oh God. The one that jumps out of the water, the big red fish. Uh, that was in Mario.
Dear that is me. You were terrified of Mario. Just playing the game. Mario. It was terror.
I've never been a big gamer since level number one, there's size levels too. There's giant
Goombas and all that. Uh, so I, when I was thinking about fish to add to that scene,
just not that one that swallows you whole reasonable size.
Reasonable size. So, so a few more reasonable size fit just every now and then. I think that also
shows a attention to detail care when parks are like, Hey, we shut this down to clean it up,
make sure everyone's working. We put a little couple of extra things in there. I like when
parks do that. And also on April fool's day, I think they should put in Terrence and Philip
animatronics, uh, to just wave at you when you go by. Uh, okay. That's all. Big thumbs up to that idea.
Brick and mortar and not please. Yeah. Brick and mortar and not please.
I gotta say, yeah, I plus it up. I mean, I think it would be real cool if they were do,
would do something with the ride vehicles that did kind of give you like a little bit of an up
and down motion. That's probably very expensive, but I would like them to do it. I would prefer
it if they did it. Uh, cause I think that would go a long way sort of in making you feel like you
were really, uh, under the seat. Uh, I also think they should take out the kiss the girl and put in
a death scene for Ursula. I think that's more important. I think that there should be a full
sized, I think that should be the bigger than the one we saw in that video of Ursula. I think she
should be in the room. Her head should be maybe like 20 feet long. Do you want me to stay here or not?
Well, you're just driving me out of the room. You want that. You just want a scene of like,
cause in the movie Prince Eric Prince, Prince Eric is like his shirts all ripped and he's like a
heroic hunk and he steers the ship with the last bit of strength. So you want like something for
the guys. You want some guy, you know what? Here's, I got an idea. You just gave me a very,
very good idea. Okay. You add a, like a, an old broken mass to the front of each car. So, oh,
Mike, no. Well, wait, let's see where he's going with this. Cause I can't see it.
So you see like you, like there's a room and obviously they have limited space. So it's just
like Ursula's giant head, but then her body. So the way to defeat Ursula is to have each car
drive their dirty wooden mast into her stomach. And then you go kind of through it and there's
like kind of a lighting effect and like it goes black. So obviously you're not making contact.
Oh, it's over the track. Yes. It's over the track. You go through it. It's kind of like a door.
So we're all now, now it solves the problem of, of it's our adventure. We are helping. We're
the hero. We're the hero. We're the heroic sea witch murderers. We're the shit. And we all can
feel like Eric with our shirt ripped and we're like handsome now and we're finally doing it.
So I think that would be a good, I mean, let me throw one more thing in for context,
which is that what if there was a way to see what you would look like as a little shrunken,
uh, zero voice creature so that you could see what hypothetically Ursula might do to you.
And then that gives you blood lust. Like I want to tear her rib cage. That's good too. Yeah.
Yeah. You guys are ruining this. We're blue sky. This is just, these are ideas.
Yeah. You think adding horrendous violence would not be a help? More creepy creatures, more death.
Of your possible future. And the only other thing I'll say,
the only other thing I'll say is at the end of the wedding ceremony, just give me Mr.
Limpett and a little white like tuxedo and a little top hat wishing him luck and he's
having a good time. Cause he appeared earlier and I want to see where he's at by the end of the ride.
I'm for that. Yeah. It's that one's at least I think we can all agree that's a nice cheap way
to plus the ride up and we'd love it. Have a nice laugh you two. Oh, Andy.
One of us has to have a Don Nuts, right? Uh, yeah. I kinda, I don't, I don't know.
We'll work on it for future. My Don Nuts are just like, whoa, Andy.
Yeah. It's reaking, it can be real close to Jimmy Stewart. Yeah. Whoa.
Or Andy. Yeah. Oh well.
Do you have one? Oh, Andy.
Wow. I think it was better than ours. Well, Leland Bowden, you've survived podcast the ride.
Yeah. It was awesome.
What do you want to plug? Plug away. Andy Mack is returning to the airwaves,
June 4th, 8 PM Monday nights on Disney channel. Yeah.
And you're going, what's going to be more? You're doing more.
Also, when does this come out? Cause if it comes out, like anytime before the next two weeks,
I want to plug me being in LA to all my friends and I want to hang out.
What's the cutoff? June 2nd guys.
Oh, we probably won't be out by then. No.
I'm sorry. I missed you guys. So apologize to your friends now.
Oh yeah. Guys. I really want to make it to your thing. I'm so sorry. I can't come visit me in Utah.
Okay. That's nice. Twitter. Do you want a Twitter plug?
Your, your want song is wanting to see all your best buds while you're in LA.
You want to be part of their world. When's it my turn? Um, at your friend Leland,
Leland is spelled L I L A N. Don't make it Lillian. That's not my name. Whatever I can do.
That is what people think. I think I thought that's what was your name for a month.
Somebody's squad on that name. And then, uh, uh, you're, uh, then you're an alternate.
I actually own Lillian Bowden.com. I use it to sell all sorts of, uh, multi-level marketing schemes,
diet pills, that tea that people promote on Instagram. You sell fake rocks. I sell fake rocks.
Hey, anyway, I can help my friends. Thank you. And you are Instagram's my main squeeze though.
Oh yeah. Same, same handle at your friend Leland. Nice. Uh, and then obviously like
send all your shipping requests, uh, to that Lillian and her Twitter and your hashtag ship
request. Who do you, so, so yeah, so for this episode, we're shipping Lillian and various Disney
characters and executives and we're of course, most importantly, shipping Jason and many
and different treats and treats. And also if anyone wants to draw a picture of us recording,
but I'm just real big and take up the room and Scott is like sweating and really nervous.
Oh, if you want to draw that for like 10 days, it would be funny. Like just a picture of Scott
and then like Clifford and the baby from honey. I blew up the kid surrounded by all of these things.
Scott, this is how we calm you down. Like the mushroom omelet in a Phantom thread for all the
thread heads out there. This is how we calm you down when you're a little too wound up and you,
we, we sort of set you back to one and I've been too demanding in setting this podcast schedule.
Scott is the Reynolds Woodcock of podcast, the ride. That's for sure. It's not to my liking.
Throw this episode out. All right. Well, we are you dare, but do dare go to our Twitter
podcast, the ride and Instagram and podcast, the ride at gmail.com. If you want to email us.
Mm hmm. Yeah. And rate and review us on iTunes and do all that. Is it called iTunes? I keep Apple
podcast. Okay. I podcast, whatever. Yeah. We need, we need those sweet reviews. Five stars only. Of
course. I just saw somebody give us a four star and said that we need to tighten the podcast up.
Not going to happen. So go back and amend it. I think that's a great note. I think every podcast
could be tight. I believe it specifically, um, uh, they, they go on tangents a lot, which that is,
uh, all podcasts. And I hope you like that. 10 minutes we did on giant things.
All right. Uh, that's it for us today. Uh, thank you. We're in the process of not keeping it tight
right now. We could just keep going just to punish that Mr. Four star four stars here. This is for
you. Here we go. Probably not listening. I think it was a woman or she are she. All right. Bye.
Bye.