Warning, the following podcast may include heated advocacy for Disney workers and country bears,
a cacophony of loud scissors, plus my fascination with a dirty animatronic foot.
Please go buy the most expensive headphones possible to fully appreciate this binarisode.
It's Great Moments with Mr. Lincoln on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast where we're confident we could do a tidy five-hour episode
about the outlet mall on the way to Disneyland, the Citadel. I'm Scott Gardner joined by fellow
Citadel heads, I assume, Jason Sheridan.
Hi, yeah, I haven't really explored many of California's great outlet malls. I guess I hate
one coming back from Palm Springs. Oh, that one. Yeah, yeah. Well, I find outlet malls to be sort
of generally unpleasant, though I'm like a mall connoisseur in general. I feel like the outlet
malls are, you know, but as the name implies, less decorated, less of a fun, casual experience and
more just a, you know, a cattle call for bargains. Sure. They're fortresses. Yes. I find often.
I, by the way, am like Carlson. And I'm like Carlson. Fortresses, the one that you're talking
about, the one on the way to Palm Springs and the one at the Citadel, it's like they're impenetrable.
It's hard. You got to drive like for 15 minutes into the parking lot. It takes forever to park.
It's like a madhouse in there. And then once you actually get to the like mall part, you have to
like wind this labyrinth. Like it's crazy. Like it's more unpleasant than a normal mall. I feel
though. Palm Springs one when I was there was also being redone. So it looked like kind of an open
air prison. There was like a chain link fence everywhere, but like in confusing spots. Yes,
they are prisons. I think I went to the, I went to the Citadel once. So this is really going to be
fascinating to people that don't live in Los Angeles. Oh wait. So the Citadel, if you're
driving down the five from the Los Angeles area where we all live, you will on the right before
you get in Orange County, you'll pass by this big castle type thing called the Citadel. And it's,
to me, it looks like a, it looks like a Mario castle from the outside. That's what I always
cool. Yeah. Yes. But only the outside because then you go in there and that is a facade. There is no
continued cool castle theming. There's no medieval times type arena show. The food court doesn't have
medieval pun names. It's just, it's very dull. And especially at Christmas time, the exterior,
there's a giant present. And let me ask you this question. Does that present make you uncomfortable
because it's such a large present? Oh, and I've since, I've recently revealed my, my issue with
giant things, especially giant versions of miniature things. No, I think, I think seeing a big bow on
the, the big Citadel box is a lot of fun. It gets me in the holiday spirit and it's outside.
Yeah. Right. Right. No one's forcing me to be in a enclosed space with it. So, but thanks for your concern.
Okay. Just wondering. Yeah. Cause there's, it is, it is like that, especially on Christmas time,
it's so bright, it's distracting. There's a giant present. There's these screens that are like,
it should be illegal to have a screen that bright next to a freeway. Cause like people would be
distracted the whole time. Yeah. I'll advertising like local DJs and like, uh, you know, like, uh,
Pasadena presentations of Aladdin or whatever. I feel like I saw ads for that on the Citadel.
Off-brand e-cigarettes. I went to that Pasadena Aladdin show. Yeah. Yeah. You're talking about,
uh, uh, um, starring a Bruce Velaunch, uh, Richard Karn and Ben Verene.
Uh, all three legit, uh, royalty. That's not, that ain't bad. And they put all these,
like, it was not a Disney show, but they put in all these like Disney references just cause they
knew people like the only idiots now know the Aladdin version of Disney from Disney. So they
added like a bunch of Disney jokes into it. And they had Ben Verene say like some lion king joke
and he called Mufasa Mufafa. That's one of my favorite memories from the show. Cause all this,
like there was, they were talking about that's not like missing the, the, the name,
saying it incorrectly. Maybe. I don't know. Okay. I'm not exactly sure. Uh, it's because look,
these, uh, shows they do in Pasadena at this playhouse, uh, lightly rehearsed, I would say,
these aren't like, these aren't Broadway style. Sure. Seeing Ben Verene on Broadway 20 years ago,
he was like on top of it. This is like, he kind of glanced at the script before he went out there
and he just kind of dances around and he's so talented. He can make it work. He knows it'll
get a cheer just by, by going out there. Yes. Um, you wait your Citadel story though. Let's, let's
keep track of our, sorry, sorry, sorry. People very upset when we tangent, um, our tangents about
local Los Angeles things, which by the way, that bothers, I feel like a large contingent of our
audiences in Los Angeles, or at least fascinated by it. But if you're, if you're bothered, but we
don't ever give enough context, please let us know. Hashtag no more LA. I mean, if you're
listening to any comedy podcasts and you're like too much, too much tangent, too much LA talk,
I would encourage you to look at, uh, any comedy podcast and you will see the same.
Yeah. Well, and we're going to balance it out with an equal amount of Orlando
local mundanity. We'll always make sure. And, uh, uh, and France Martin, Levaly and, uh,
Schomburg, Illinois and the wonderful Woodfield mall and all the different things I grew up with.
I'm really looking forward to the eventual Schomburg mall episode. I have it. I it's,
it's amazing how many odd things we found that were there and I'm excited,
but, but here let's close out the Citadel first. Yeah. The Citadel, I mean, the Citadel, look,
uh, an unspectacular story. I went to the Citadel. I think it was, uh, like Christmas Eve
for after like the day after Christmas. I can't remember. Uh, I was driving back up and I went,
you know what? I'm going to stop at the Citadel. It's Christmas time outside. It's so lovely.
There's a big present. Uh, and I know there's a Disney store there and a Disney outlet store.
So I stopped. It took me what I said, 15 minutes to park 20, like just crazy, like people stalking
spots. There's not enough spots. Well, after Christmas sales, you know, but I think, yeah,
I guess you're right. I guess it's my fault for going there. Um, and then you go in the Disney
outlet store, which is not dissimilar to just a Disney store and everything is like $2 off.
And it's, there's nothing, cause I was like, wow, there's going to be deals. There's going to be
everything I want. There's going to be theme park merchandise. Cause we're so close to Anaheim.
Right. It is not the case. It is just a, a mater shirt for a little child. It is a, you know, how
dare they Rapunzel doll. It's all the stuff, the normal stuff you would get in a Disney store.
Well, cause in Anna, uh, cause in Orlando there are Disney outlets specifically for park merchandise,
which I think there used to be out here and then it moved and then it closed. And,
and so I never made it. So I stupidly thought that there must be some merchandise here cause
we're so close to Anaheim and no, of course not. There's no America sings shirt. There's no
old America sings animatronic in here. This is just a Disney store. That's slightly discounted.
Yeah. I'm an idiot. The sizes are slightly misprinted. Right. When we went up to
WrestleMania, WrestleMania 31 in San Jose, we were, we pulled into a shopping mall
or a strip mall and there was a Disney outlet there too. And we got very excited and it was
the same deal. It was not, it was nothing, nothing special as well. I'm saying.
spectacular. Hey, stick, stick to J crew factory. That's what I like at outlet malls.
I've had a lot of good luck at J crew factory. I think the shorts I'm wearing right now are from
there. Let me take a photo though so we can post on Twitter of your J crew shorts.
This is one of the first warm days we've had. It's going to hit 85 here in Southern California
today. This shot of Jason's bare legs is going to tear up the Twitter. Like the pirate, uh,
on pirates of the Caribbean dangling his leg over the bridge. This is going to be just as iconic.
That is weird that you're just under, under bare feet.
That's one of the most memorable things I feel like about that ride is that foot.
We'll, we'll get into this. I don't think I've really thought about the foot. What's a lot of
people have shared that with me privately that they remember the foot on pirates of the Caribbean.
Does that foot have a wiki feet page? Is that, I don't know. What is that website? I don't know.
I know what you're talking about, but I haven't explored it. And I assume you have explored a
little more of the foot fetishes on the internet. It's not really, uh, just intellectually, but it's
not really my, uh, bag. But you're interested in all the fetishes. You're a little more curious
than Scott and I. I'm curious about how people engage with that sort of thing. You know what I
know about wiki feet is that the, uh, whereas like, you know, there's not a lot of like nude
scenes out there to choose from for your Mr. Skin kind of websites, but wiki feet, if there's an
actress who has a TV credit, anyone we know, probably anyone who's been on the show, they are
on wiki feet. If you've ever been on television or in a movie wiki feed is, they're just more,
what's the word? They're more, they're in depth. They like, they, they catalog everything, right?
But you, we all might be, you will be as soon as that picture goes live. Is it equal male and female
feet? Do we know? What do you think? Yeah. Well, no, of course it wouldn't be, but as Scott said,
we could be on there. So I thought maybe it is an equal opportunity because Mr. Skin has a different,
I've heard, I've heard is that there's a male version of it now too. Oh, really? That, that
does like, you know, the, for hunks, the fame, yeah. Harvey Keitel scene, the Kevin Bacon scene,
you know, all the famous dick scenes. Uh-huh. Burt Reynolds, but he's naked in like a centerfold
type setting, not a, not in a film, though he might be in a film as well. But the foot, yeah,
the foot thing, the foot fetish, I feel like this is another tangent real quick, is so prevalent
that we must have friends that have it, but I don't have it. I don't get it at all. Yeah,
that's probably true. And I'm not covering it all for my deep, dark secret. I swear.
Somebody's got, because you may have it. I don't want to out you guys unless you want to say it,
but anyway. Um, I do not, and about it though, I am on WikiFeet currently and I've just looked
up the word pirate and uh, there are no results. Oh boy. Jason, do you, do you also, isn't that foot
memorable? Am I really? I think so. Well, like, cause they made it, they painted it to look very
dirty, right? It's a dirty foot. It's a dirty foot. And that dirty foot is one of the most memorable
things to me about Pirates of the Rhine and Disney. My mom brings it up too. You're speaking in code
though. Now you, this, you're, this sounds like a foot fetish. It's not. It's just memorable. It's
distinct. This is actually Illuminati. He speaks, the code is Illuminati. Oh, okay. It's not a sex
thing. It's not a sex thing. It's a deep, cause if you're, if you get into the Illuminati, it's a
secret foot shake. Yes. Yeah. A dirty foot shake. You have to have the right amount of foot stain.
My mom would always talk about the foot. She would be like, Oh, isn't it cool? The foot is over. Like
what's there to say about the foot when people have discussed the foot with you privately?
What's the, what's the discussion? People always say, we'll just, I mean, it's a quick discussion.
We don't get into it too much of like, what would it be like to touch the foot or what it'd be like
there, but everyone's talking about, you know, like it's, it's cool having that foot hanging there
and their memory of it is very specific. Cause sometimes you miss stuff on the ride, but it seems
like almost everybody knows that and fixates on it a little bit. And it's a very like, I don't know.
I guess it looks real. I guess it looks real. And some of the other stuff, like, you know,
the chasing around doesn't look so real cause it's on a track. And maybe, yeah, yeah, sure. And like,
you know, the Lincoln who we're talking about today, we don't know what his feet look like.
I was an early animatronic and it didn't get too much into the details. So it got a couple of years
down the line and they are confident enough in their animatronic making abilities to have a
realistic dirty foot. Right. Right. Yeah. I do think we do know, I mean, historically in that
Doris Kearns Goodwin book, she does refer to Lincoln as one sick fuck. So like he may have been
in two feet. Yeah. I don't know if that affected the Imagineers when they were building the robot
statistically speaking, several of the presidents have to have been in defeat. Oh yeah. And we don't
know who necessarily, but we can all guess. I think. Did anyone show their cards in any way?
There, you know, I, this is pretty tangential, but the, who was it? There was a guy who worked
for Reagan, who banned the beach boys, America's band from performing their fourth of July
concerts in the Washington mall appropriate for a fourth of July episode. And he said something
about how they, they, they bring the wrong elements. The eighties beach boys bring that,
that seedy rock and roll elements to the Washington mall that we don't want. And they replaced him
with Wayne Newton instead. And this was so unpopular. I forget the guy's name that the beach
boys came to Washington on Reagan's invite and the guy had to, was given a, the secretary of the
interior, whatever was given a giant foot because he put his foot in his mouth. He was given like a
foot in your mouth award, perhaps by Reagan himself. So if that foot in the mouth given to James,
whatever Reagan's underling, maybe he just had a lot of cast iron feet hanging around the white
house. So that's, that was a long winded way of saying, I think Reagan was a foot in me. Yeah.
I think we're, I think we can declare officially here. Reagan was a foot guy. We have all the
proof we need. Anybody else we think was a secret foot fetishist? I'm still processing someone going
like beach boys, no, Wayne Newton. Yes. Cause this many years later, it's just like, I'm sure if you
told people that they would just go like that's both old music. Yeah. That's both stuff. My parents
like it's a lateral move. But, you know, the beach boys have guitars and there's girls in bikini tops
who come to dance to the surf music. Whereas Wayne Newton is just kind of swinging and quiet. And it's,
it's a more composed horniness. I guess you get with Wayne Newton. It's a subtext. Also had no
involvement with the Manson family, Wayne Newton. Not as far as I know, but you have to imagine some,
some mob ties to be that much of a fixture. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. For sure. I found a completely
unsourced Yahoo answers, answer to how many people have a foot fetish. They claim it's from a,
the Kinsey study done in the seventies. 15% of Americans have a foot or related fetish. Pretty
high. So if you then forgive me while I pull up my calculator, 45 presidents times 0.15 and that
gives us 6.75. So somewhere between six and seven. Reagan we know with certainty, but there have to
have been six other presidents who were foot fetishists. Grant. I say Grant. Sure. I don't
know why. I just have a feeling. That's a good one. He probably saw some feet get lost during
the civil war. Yes. He probably saw a lot of stray feet lying around. I bet he did.
Was he disturbed by it and the, but the fetish was a way to process it.
Anyway, we just want to wish everyone a happy 4th of July.
To sit with your loved ones and tell tales of severed feet. And let us know who you think
of the presidents was a foot man. Was a foot man. I feel like we would. Against my better judgment,
I'm going to say tweet at us. What's president you think had a fondness for the feats. We got so many
more tweets today than any other day. We have blocked everyone who tweeted at us.
Somebody will have like read a biography and it had to be in there. Like this probably for a few
of them is documented. So yeah, we'll hear. We'll find out. I feel like an obvious answer might be
Clinton because he was an old perv, but I think we'd know the foot thing because we're pretty
aware of his fetishes or specific interests. I think the foot fetish is too innocent for
Bill Clinton. Well, what do we think about Abraham Lincoln? Let's cover that first of all. I don't
know. He seems like a very staid. I don't see a lot of sexuality in Abraham Lincoln. There's been so
many like books or like was Lincoln gay was there like, but I don't know that anyone. Oh, right.
Yeah, anyone has some definitive like a thing and to just just say it for the record, we're talking
about great moments with Mr. Lincoln today. Yes. There's nothing about his sex sexuality on that
ride. No, but like the pirates ride, probably the only one of the few rides with a dirty foot in it.
This as I was watching a couple of different versions, I was like, is this the only Disney
ride that openly mentions suicide because they quote that Lyceum speech of Lincoln's where he
says like die by suicide. Like that's the only way America would go down by suicide. Yeah, by suicide
voice rattling in my head last few days. Sounds like a boss. Nass
he's shaking his head around while he talks this prequel. There should be great character
boss Nass. Great moments with boss Nass in Star Wars land where he talks about like the now, but
the are yeah. Yeah. The I was going to say now V or Naboo, the Gungan war.
Oh, it's such a tizzy. If Disney can get an animatronic to shake their gels
accurately, let's get that boss Nass attraction. I think you just like use the kind of the Ursula
like body and then you just change your head and make some water effects where
he shoots water at the people. Well, they can mimic someone tweeted at us that we did not talk
about on the Little Mermaid episode. We didn't mention earlier this year when Ursula's head fell
off. Yes. The one park. Yeah. But that looks that kind of swung around a lot. If they could
program an animatronic to have the motions of that dangling head, I think you'd get something
closer to like a boss Nass. Well, we'll start working on it, guys, guys and girls.
People demand the gel shake the immortalized. You know, you mentioned suicide being mentioned
in this attraction. And I found on a similar note, I read an interview with the Imagineer Mark Davis,
who was one of the primary imagineers who worked on all these early attractions and the World's
Fair stuff. And he, you know, the great moments with Mr. Lincoln was made for the 1964 World's
Fair, as was the carousel of progress as was It's a Small World and as was the primeval world and
Magic Skyway, which is now the dinosaur tunnel at Disneyland. So they're doing four attractions for
the World's Fair. This is a magazine, the E ticket asked Mark Davis was of the four attractions for
the World's Fair was great moments of Mr. Lincoln, the most complex. Mark Davis said, well, it was
the one where we quote, sweated blood. You know, Walt, Walt was about ready to cut his own throat
and we were ready to jump off the bridge with him. Wow. So suicide was heavy in everyone's minds,
creating this attraction. I read was that they had Walt Disney famously loved Abraham Lincoln
and they had Robert Moses, like a longtime New York political fixture. I was reading about the
parks commissioner, the parks commissioner, but he also like held like simultaneously helped like a
dozen different titles, but was always appointed, never elected, but was insanely powerful. Anyway,
he was given like Disney gave him a tour of the stuff they were working on because Moses wanted
him to, you know, was interested in getting Disney involved in the World's Fair. And the very last
thing they showed him was like a prototype of early prototype of the Abraham Lincoln animatronic.
He's like, yes, that's great. There's an Ellen. It'll be in the Illinois Pavilion and, uh, uh,
that was nowhere near ready. And the, but he promised like, well have it done. So like,
I'm sure the pressure of that and also the pressure of trying to recreate, uh, what of
America's most beloved political figures was probably like, yeah, I could see you sweating
some blood. He was like, I mean, that's, I feel like that is a thing that most maniac innovators
are like where it's like, do this now. I don't care if it's not ready. You figure it out and
we'll all be the most stressed up until somebody figures out. Oh yeah. Jobs was famous for that
sort of shit. I read the nicer Steve jobs biography and he still comes out looking like a lunatic.
Yeah. But we are same with Walt where he would just demand something and then like
keep checking in on it and they'd be like, it's impossible. And you'd be like, it's not impossible.
And then they wouldn't be like, that's the thing also with maniacs is they are often proven right
because then it's not impossible. They got it. They fixed it. They did it. It had to be pushed
harder and it's where you do it. You have a lot of respect for like what you're seeing in the
presidency right now is this syndrome, but all of the people carrying it out are not good.
What they're doing incompetent, but it's the syndrome that typically works with, well,
thank God the guy's surrounded by geniuses. In the case of Walt Disney, yeah, he, these people,
it's, it does defy logic the way people who were like, uh, pay animators on paper or like, uh,
we're suddenly able to switch mediums and pull off something that had never been done before
within a year on a crazy timeline or like a Bob Gurr frequently, uh, uh, touted imagineer who's
you mainly associate with really technical attractions like the Autopia. He mainly worked
in vehicles and big blunt, uh, instruments and stuff. He ended up coming aboard the Lincoln
thing, even though he had not done character animation before, but he did, he did understand
complex machinery, which is what, uh, Lincoln ended up being.
Yeah. I read there's a story about Orson Welles when they made Citizen Kane, like he was a theater
guy, uh, uh, for, for his early life, he did so much in the theater and on the radio.
He really didn't know that much about making films. So like when it came time to like, all right,
this is where the scene's going to fade out and we'll fade up on another scene. He just had them
slowly dim the lights, their practical fades. And that's why they don't look some of them like,
Oh, that looks so different than any other film. And it's because, well, he didn't know you did
that in post. He just did it on set. Wow. Wow. Um, yeah. So, I mean, this is a, this is a big
victory for, uh, you know, taking, taking big swings. And the other cool thing is that Walt
got to do it on other people's dime, like all of these attractions ended up coming to Disneyland
en masse, but he did not have to pay for them the usual way. Everything was financed by the,
in this case, the state of Illinois or GE sponsoring the carousel of progress. Um,
and also just to put things on the contextual animatronic timeline, the biggest animatronic
thing, was it the first, I guess, the Enchant Tiki Room? Um, it must've been to some extent.
I guess that depends on if you classify the, uh, fake animals in the jungle cruise.
Those were pretty rudimentary, but yeah, I guess they move a little,
they move a little. Um, but yeah, Tiki Room was, I think the first big. First ones where they
speak and it's like, yeah, so the Enchant Tiki Room is it happened, but those are all fairly more
simple creatures. It's eyes blinking and mouths moving and wings flapping. And this is such a
giant leap up that it's a per, not only a person, but a person that everybody knows and has very
fun feelings about. This one, I, I didn't realize until reading about this, that, uh, you know, so
there were two seasons that the World's Fair ran. There was like six months in 1964, six months in
1965. And while the 65 one was going, they put in, uh, great moments with Mr. Lincoln simultaneously
into Disneyland. So they were running at the same time and they did it to celebrate the anniversary
of the park. And, uh, uh, and then there was also, you know, pictures of Walt everywhere because the,
the mythology of Walt Disney is kind of like, uh, attached to this attraction throughout its history,
I feel like. Um, but yeah, I always thought they just moved the animatronic like they moved all
the other crap out here, but the original Lincoln animatronic was like, they thought lost to the
ages until they found it in a crate not too long ago here, like buried in a warehouse in California.
Yeah. I think it's been a D 23. Have you, I've seen a new Lincoln animatronic, but I've not seen
the original. They had a couple, like three or four years ago, they had this crazy, like expressive
Lincoln that is quite frankly, frighteningly real. And I don't think they've put that into
any of the parks, but they were showing just like the new technology of how much they can make a
face, a robot face move. And it is frightening. I'll try to find a video of it. It's gotta be
online somewhere. I think I've seen a real close up that seemed recent of showing what, uh, like
it's trained really close. And he's like, he's a little more cartoonish than normal too, which
makes it even more like frighteningly real or like, just like perverse maybe. Oh, I've got it. The
original one is now at the one man stream attraction in, uh, Hollywood studios in Florida. Oh,
interesting. So, um, you can see that there. Well, I didn't know that. I didn't know that they were
running at the same time. This is before there was a Disneyland and a Disney world. So that makes it
the first multiple locations. First clone attraction. Wow. Sure. There were people
sending handwritten newsletters back then of like another clone, another clone attraction, nothing
new. The fan boys are furious. Message boards. I was, I was impressed to learn that it's a re it's
a real face that it's all they had a life mask. Yeah. Yeah. If it's in the video, there's a video
where he's introducing the ride. Not a death mask. Not a death mask. A life mask. So in what regard
this was done? Like his, his face was immortalized like for statues and they said this was before the
presidency that they took this life mask. That's what he says in the video at least that they did
it before the presidency. So yeah, I don't know if it was, I should look more into it. If it was
during the, when he was running for president or I'm not sure. Or was that just a thing that everyone
got when they were in the olden days? Where like, honey, you get your life mask and I think it was
an option, especially when photography was so new. Right. Um, but, or maybe they knew that one day
they'll, there will be robots and that we should have this great man and, uh, have his face be very
accurate. I want to be flopping around on a stage. I think an interesting, uh, about this, this ride
and a lot of portrayals of Lincoln and popular culture is everyone hones in on writings about his
weird voice because like, I mean, this attraction, uh, uh, what is the, the main guys, what is the
name of the guy who does in the attraction, in the attraction, Royal Dano, Royal Dano, um, who, who
later there's, uh, he was an old character actor, uh, and is survived by a, his grandson named
Hutch Dano. Great. Wow. Perfect. Best names. Wait, is he related to Paul Dano? I don't know that one.
Let me look that up. Yeah. Look that up. Uh, but yeah, so a very distinct voice on this traction,
uh, uh, and a very distinct voice in, uh, Daniel Day-Lewis doing in the movie Lincoln from a few
years ago. No, no, no. We're on the world stage now. No, no. I was with a group of friends who
were really fixated on the Lincoln now. No, no, no. We are, uh, what's the other thing? Oh, I'm the
president of the United States, clothed in immense power. He gets a little less, that's not nasally.
It's the now, now, now is really odd. I don't even know how to describe that. It's a little,
it's like kind of whiny. It's a little emo. No, no, no. It reminds me of, of around the same time
as Lincoln came out. Uh, I never saw the movie, but war horse. You remember the movie war horse?
I never saw it. In the trailer, uh, there is an audio clip and I saw this trailer so much. I feel
like they played it before everything for a while of, um, uh, Benedict Cumberbatch yelling, be brave,
like screaming at a battlefield of soldiers. And it's just, it's never like, again, I've never seen
the movie. I know it's about a man and his horse, uh, but that be brave just comes into my head every
now and then old time, like historical bizarre lines in historical films. You just unlocked
another one. There's some movie, maybe you guys can tell me the title. I want to say Natalie
Portman is in it. It is a historical film, not America, but like Renaissance. And I just remember
a trailer with a lot of like, but you are my sister. She is my sister. Um, and I don't, who is it?
Who's the other one? I don't know. There's, I have the title in my head, the other Berlin girl.
Oh, what is that song? What is that movie called? Uh, the other, but you are my sister.
And as such, we must maintain Boylan. Okay. The other Boylan girl, Boylan B O L E. Yeah. And Bolin
or I've just always heard wrong. Uh, yeah. Anyway, why do, why do things, why do odd
phrase ologies jump out so much? I mean, in the intro to this, when, when, uh, uh,
Dano is reading like the, the biography, the Lincoln was asked to describe himself. Uh,
it always stuck out to me when he goes like, I was large for my age. It's like, oh man,
Lincoln was a big boy. He was a large son. Uh, real big, big one. As a large son, do they have
to be, can they just be tall? Cause he's very lanky guy. Yeah. He's very lanky. He's not a husky boy.
He wasn't husky, but he was, he was certainly large. I mean, he called himself large. He's six,
four. Yeah. You ever play Lincoln in anything, Mike? You're probably, you're of the question.
I don't think I have. No, no video or sketch or a play. Maybe an improv show. An insultingly low
amount of money to play Lincoln for 12 hours. No, I don't think so. Maybe president's day related
sketch. I think it's in an improv show. I'm sure I've done so many improv scenes. Sure. But no,
you weren't specifically hired because like a lot of, I feel like every heavy set actor we know has
had to be Santa. Yes. Perhaps five times minimum. You just, it's just what ends up happening, but I'm,
I'm kind of amazed you haven't been employed as a Lincoln. I don't think there's as much demand for
Lincoln and Santa. I think maybe there's just so I think yes. Lincoln only comes around once in a
while, but no, nobody sales when like, you know, presidents day car sales. I like, I'll put it out
there. I'm happy to play Lincoln. I will play him like boss NAS, but I'm tall and you can put the
beard on me and it'll look right. And I'm fairly lanky. So yeah, yeah, I'm, I'm open for it.
Lincoln too reloaded. Sure. I'll do the direct to DVD sequel, but we've already show the Lincoln.
He's already been used for, you know, schlocky entertainment with the vampire hunter. Oh yeah.
Out of the realm of possibility. We, Lincoln has been put in the category of like ninjas and
pirates and like, yeah, like random stuff. If you want to convey that your thing is random,
get a Lincoln in there. There's no better way to let people know you have a twisted
sense of humor. Whoa, what are they doing with Lincoln? I thought that was sacred.
Wow. They don't care about anything. Their sensibility is so twisted. Yeah. Wow. They're
implying he's a foot finishes. They go there. The, well, to keep talking about the minutia
of Lincoln's voice and other articles, I think at various times, Lincoln historians have been unhappy
with this attraction because while that, the Royal Dano performance does seem like that,
that seems like what Lincoln might've talked like to me, but apparently it was a little higher.
It was a little more nasally. And I guess the criticism is that he should speak like an Indiana
guy or a Kentucky guy. And what does that mean exactly? I found one article that explained it,
that if you said, you should not say, thank you, Mr. Chairman, you should say, thank you, Mr.
Chairman. So you fucked up Disney and have him say cheer instead of chair. Wow. Who cares? Who's
analyzing this? And I guess if you're a, well, first of all, if you're a Lincoln expert and a historian,
you are smarter than me and contribute more than I do. So I have no right to be taking you down,
but I don't understand caring about not getting the dialect right in this robot ride.
I, it has to be much like us who have done a lot of, a lot of things, comedy wise, improv, sketch,
TV shows, and now we can't watch any comedy because it bothers us. It's the same for historians. They
can't watch any movie. They can't enjoy anything. I was talking to somebody the other day who knew
somebody who was an expert on pirates. And they said that this person, this pirate expert hates
the pirates of the Caribbean movies, hates the ride, hates all of it. So this is not what pirates
were like, and it bothers them. So like, I get it that if you're like so immersed in the topic,
you can't enjoy just a frivolous, fun adventure that, that fictionalizes pirates or something.
Like there's too many inaccuracies is what I'm saying. I mean, I, I find it personally very
tiresome in pop culture when it's like, Oh, we got to go to bingo world when like theme parks are
like, there's some very like a lame theme park stuff. There's a, there's lazy portrayals of
theme parks in films. Yes. I mean, then, then there's like most Simpsons stuff is on point.
Most Simpsons stuff is pretty good. So great about their theme park episodes. They're very
specific, very specific. All the California adventure jokes from like 2001. Did they make
California adventure joke multiple times? Just roasting that real. Oh yeah. What, but this is
like season 19, right? I haven't seen that would have been like 10 or 11. Really? I think real
later. I was watching 10 or 11. Did I just, did these go over my head? You were so offended. You
blocked them out. I guess the one that sticks out in my mind is like, we need to go where
no one would ever find you. Uh, or we need to go somewhere totally empty. Disney's California
adventure. Wow. They really even just spell it out. Let me look for this. Oh, also Royal Dano,
not related to Paul Dano as far as I can tell. Perfect. There are a lot of, uh, legacies. There
are a lot of legacy families in Hollywood. So, so Royal and Hutch different Dano than Paul.
Hutch, that's the greatest name. I also just real quick on the, on the Paul Dano, not the Paul Dano
point, the, uh, which, which one? Royal Dano. So he, he had played Lincoln in other stuff and he
looked sort of Lincoln-y, uh, in general and he, and I was looking up, well, can I see him play
Lincoln? And he did it in a film or two, but he also did it in a very strange episode of a show
called the Rifleman. Oh yeah. West, uh, black and white show. And, uh, I don't know the rest of what
happens on the Rifleman, but there's a really strange scene where the Rifleman's son is like
wrestling with a, with a guy and rough neck and, uh, you know, like, uh, tumbling all around the,
uh, the stable. And then when he flips over like, Hey, all right, you guys come in for dinner.
All right, I'll be there in a minute. And it's Lincoln and you're left for like seven minutes
going like, why am I watching Lincoln in this old West, uh, like having dinner with these farm
people? And then you re then it's spelled out to you that he is a crazy man who thinks he's Lincoln.
And in order to keep him at bay, everybody has to like act like he really is Lincoln. And at some
point, a little girl innocently says, I know everything about you. I know that you were born
on such a state and you were assassin. Uh, I mean, you wrote the emancipation very good. That's
right. I don't know what that other word was. You were starting. Well, this is the Simpson plot,
the Michael Jackson Simpson's plot. Oh, you're right. There's an imp, a guy who thinks he's
Oh yeah. Yeah. For once. Wow. The Simpsons did something after. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Speaking of little children, this is a good segue back into the world's fair, uh, uh,
version of this ride. Um, so I, I had some of the, I was listening to some of the audio files,
from this, the box set about the world's fair that Disney put out a number of years ago. Um,
you sent us this file and there's a, this is a box set. You can hear audio of, yeah. So, uh,
there's this box set. Uh, I think it's called like Walt Disney and the world's fair. It's great. And
there's a disc dedicated to every attraction. I mean, what you really want, the main thing on
each disc is the source audio from each ride. So it's source audio from Carousel, the full Lincoln
show, um, uh, uh, all of these different ones. And I got this from my dad a few years ago,
cause he had been at the world. He went to the world's fair multiple times when he was kid.
Um, and, uh, but the, the intro to this attraction when it was in the Illinois pavilion
was a thing called the Illinois story and it involved children reciting facts about Illinois.
Oh boy. And it's very odd. And it's just like, you know, uh, uh, agriculture,
commerce, like all of this stuff. And it's, it's already creepy cause it's little kids
just reading like it's like founded in, in 1645, like just saying this. And then halfway through
this, they start talking in unison. So it's just a group going like home to science and innovation,
the land of Lincoln, but it's very odd.
Oh, why are children made to recite historical facts? That was my, when I graduated from
elementary school are the, what we, for some reason we all had to like get on like risers and
tell the story of America. And there were a lot of in unison parts like that, where we all said
the declaration of independence together. That was our tree for graduating six year, your longest
school, six years. And we all had to read the tale of Paul Revere. Why are these things
tied together? Why are kids made to, yeah, it's very strange. Uh, the audio, actually I did
Paul Revere and I nailed it. That was like a solo I had and whatever this American history
piece was. And I was, I was real proud. Attend the tale of the, um, Scott, the audio file that you
refer to that I sent you guys, uh, is, uh, outtakes of the recording of the Lincoln, uh, attraction.
And it's, it's Dano reading the lines, like, you know, and it's just like, or die by suicide.
And then you hear the classic, okay, hey, that was great. Um, let's take it back in this time,
really believe in the words you're saying. Like it's so odd to hear the words of Abraham Lincoln
get noted from a sound booth. Like it's very funny. You know, you know what it made me aware of is
that the, the directions are given so precisely, make sure that it's clear that you have no lack
of confidence in the Republic heading towards the future. All right, great. Every note is given by
some old, you know, some like war horse guy behind a desk. And I do, I direct things and I do VO
directions specifically. And I'm sure if you heard audio of me doing that, it'd be like, oh, that
was pretty cool. Uh, just maybe, I don't know if, would it be interesting possibly if you could
maybe, uh, also like I was shamed by how succinct this Lincoln director was and I'll strive to be
like him in the future from now on. You'll be like, uh, say that like you love our flag, please.
Those are the only, I'm only given patriotic notes from now on. Imagine a soaring eagle while you do
this one, please. It's a good note actually. Yeah. I will give that. Uh, I, the side note that
there's others, there's other versions of, um, or other versions, there's other, uh, audio,
like outtakes, like the Haunted Mansion, you can find the outtakes of the narration, the Paul
Frese narration, who also was the narrator on this, right? Yeah. Um, and there, it's wonderful to
hear like, like stuff that, you know, it just doesn't feel like it exists. There's a, there's,
there shouldn't be other takes of it. It felt like it feels so like, I don't know, like it was born.
It was just there. It was always there. It's so adhering, like somebody fuck up or trying a
different take or a different voice is very fun and weird. But also everyone's a lot more composed,
like you were saying, Scott. So these outtakes usually aren't like, you know, anyone doing the
voice of Lincoln and then going, fuck, I thought I had it. God damn it. Yeah. The freeze one on the
Haunted Mansion is a little more loose like that. Oh, is it? It's a little more, I don't know if he
says that, but I hope he does. God damn it. Yeah. Me. You can hear that with Paul Thomas Anderson's
dad, who was the voice of ABC, the wonder years. And you can hear him. Fuck me. He started it one
more. Yes. All right. God damn it. Give me another. He was the great Goulardi. Uh huh. Yes. He was one
of the early horror. He was a local horror show host. Where? Uh, was it Pennsylvania? Somewhere in
Pennsylvania or something? I was somewhere on the East coast for sure. Okay. Um, but he was, he knew
Tim Conway. The look up is he was Ernie Anderson. I believe if you look up Ernie Anderson outtakes
and you want to hear a great dulcet voice, say, fuck me. Um, the, in general, it being Paul freeze
is fun because like, I think I'd forgotten that and I don't go to this attraction very often. And
this preceded the Haunted Mansion, but, uh, so this was done before his eventual role as the ghost
host. But you so associate him with like ghoulishness and malice that went to hear him. It makes the
entire attraction today seem sarcastic. Like it won't, it won't. He says like, it was in new Salem,
that yet the young Lincoln worked as a clerk and postmaster. What are you, what are you getting at?
Do you, is that a lie? Did he not do it? Was he a bad clerk? What are you implying? Yeah, like just
here. And I don't even know if he says this, but in my mind, it's like great moments with Mr. Lincoln
and you're like, ah, it's scary. It's a scary ride. It's just scary now, like Leslie Nielsen.
It's hard to back up and see Leslie Nielsen being a serious part. Unless he's doing a crazy, like he
does the Ludwig von Drake voice, which is the scientist, the duck, and he does one of the, uh,
which, uh, Tiki bird. So like if he's doing a voice like that, I think you can get away with not
sounding sinister. But yeah, when he's doing his normal voice, it really just like, you really, Mr.
Lincoln. He was assassinated in 1865. Are you glad? Is that good to you? It would have been better
if Thurl Ravenscroft did the narration. Oh boy. That's what I was, yeah, the, the Holy Trinity and
maybe I might be forgetting a big one, but I was thinking about this. Paul Frese, who's the ghost
host, Thurl Ravenscroft, who's the, the deep, uh, with area is grim, gritty and good. And Hans Conn
Reed, who I forget what he is in the parks, but he's captain hook and he's on a lot of things with
all those guys. And these, uh, these old character actor weirdos, I love them. I love when they come
up on these episodes because they're in everything. These guys are such workhorses. Uh, another, uh,
Royal Dano thing from that Lincoln, uh, uh, him reading Lincoln's like self autobiography portion.
He talks about in it, uh, a thing that at the time was probably very common people being self-taught,
but now takes on a different meaning when he goes like, I decided to borrow some law books and, uh,
taught myself the law. And it's like nowadays if someone describes themselves as a self-taught
lawyer, you're like, Oh no, this is a sovereign citizen or some other form of a John Berger
society maniac. Better call Abe. Yeah.
Would have been a real ambulance chaser if there were ambulances. Uh, yeah, that is very interesting.
This guy, I don't think self-taught. I mean, that said, we talked about the imagineers,
like teaching themselves how to build theme park, pretty much inventing theme parks as they
learned how to do it. Uh, so, you know, not that long ago in people still are self-taught or jump
between, uh, media, but like Disney himself had no right to be being able to draw doodles and steal
other doodles from your friends doesn't imply that you'd be able to be a, uh, you know, a, the opener,
a guy who builds massive real estate and theme parks and perfects robot technology and tells
stories. And, uh, yeah, Hey, it's the American spirit that is shared by Abe and Walt and that's
why their stories are intertwined. A earnest thing to say, but I felt like I had to say it weird or
sarcastic because it's, uh, uh, you know, I'm insecure with how earnest this podcast is.
How would Paul Friese say it though? Add a little bit of a spin to it.
I remember one of the great American innovators. Was he not, uh, Disney or Lincoln? He was saying
all they were both disruptors. It's the, yeah, we have to reverse apply that term. One of the great
terms. Yeah. Disruptor. What else? Oh, uh, okay. So one thing that was different at the world's fair
attraction was, um, uh, uh, the Illinois pavilion had, uh, you know, cause the world's fair,
these giant worldwide events so they can get stuff like the Illinois pavilion had the handwritten
manuscript of the Gettysburg address. That did not make the jump to Disneyland. No, no, I don't
think that's there. I haven't seen it. Uh, wow. When this is a crazy attraction. Yeah. Uh, when
it opened at Disneyland, of course, um, uh, uh, lots of Abraham Lincoln and also Walt Disney exhibits,
uh, in the, in the lobby that has pretty much never changed. Which is also true of the hall
of presidents and of the American adventure is all these, this is a trilogy really of attractions.
Walt is essentially a president in terms of the Disney mythology, the story, the company tells
like maybe you think he would have run if he hadn't died in the 60s. Maybe it would have been
Nixon versus Disney and 68. No, he would have run with them. Nixon would have been his running mate.
Oh, there's something Disney would have been. That's an Avengers lineup. I think Nixon would
have rat fucked him. Well, yeah, yeah. Uh, but I mean like this, I think Disney was a savvy enough
businessman to know, to not explicitly, even though he was hanging with Nixon, not to say exactly
where he fell on the political spectrum for his business. He didn't really put it out there so
thoroughly. We know he's probably more conservative. Yeah. But unlike a Bob Iger who wants to be a
centrist Democrat, he wants to run as a centrist Democrat. Um, and he's been very explicit about
that, except he keeps re-upping his contract every, he's going to say, like he'll say he's done. And
then he goes, Oh, two more years for me. Oh, I see. And he's not running in 2020. He's right.
He can't do that, but he was, he was going, Oprah wants him to do it. So, but he, so he's taking,
it's a different approach is what I'm saying then. Why would he want to stay on for $400 million
when he could get $400,000 as president? It's strange. And criticized by everyone roundly at
all times and potentially shot at or assassinated. But he's being, we're currently, we're recording
this in a weekend where he's been, uh, Robert Iger specifically has been, been criticized by
Bernie Sanders. Yes. Yeah. Getting his ass roasted. Getting his ass for Disney's poor, uh, labor
treatment. Yeah. I don't know. We're not like obligated to talk about, but I've thought about
how we haven't. No, I think we have. We've touched upon it. Yeah. We haven't. Here's what I'll say.
Devoted a whole episode to, uh, labor theories, but, uh, I just, you know, I feel like we should
make clear though we like these parks, we don't like that. I think we have said that before. Yeah,
we said pay them more money. Here's what I want. It's entirely unethical to like keep charging more
for tickets and hotels and everything else and not share that with the workers who do the brunt of
the labor. I would like, like these, and I, this truly, I'm saying this with the most love I can
possibly muster. These, uh, these wonderful nerds that run this park and are responsible for the
day-to-day operations truly are the backbone of this, this whole thing that we love. And these
people deserve more money for it. It is a hard job in a lot of cases. They have to deal with a lot
of people that are angry and yelling at them. There's so many people that come through. The
crowds are insane and maintain a level of friendliness. Yes. He'd be a ambassador of
Disney magic, a very hard thing to do. Uh, we had Jenny Nicholson on, she was like so clearly a, like
it's in her, it was an inner DNA to do that. She doesn't do it anymore, but like, did you ever get
mad or flip out at anybody? And the answer is no. Right. But she, and she, and Jenny was not like a,
you know, robotic weird made in a lab Disney person. She just like genuinely believes in it
and was probably very good at, uh, at all. These people are very, are very valuable and it's, uh,
it's amazing that they're, they can keep that up. And on top of just being, you know, nice and
helpful and stuff, they love it. They give a shit about all of it. The history. So much. Yeah. Most
of them at least, a majority. Um, and it would be nice if they would show them, you know, basic
decency by giving them an amount of money that would let them live comfortably in Anaheim. Yeah.
That's the other thing. It's like, it's not cheap to live in California. I mean, you can live here.
Uh, uh, you just have to make sacrifices to live here pretty much unless you have a lot of money.
I mean, Orange County wouldn't be, well, obviously Orange County has is very rich areas, but like,
there's, you know, like you go around Anaheim and there's some, like there's apartment complexes that
are so lame looking, you like make fun of them. And then like, who would live here ever? Oh, people
who have no choice and work really hard to 50 year Disney veteran lives in this apartment.
Three others. Yeah. And someone, someone pointed out like online, well, you know,
anytime this comes up in any industry, it's like, well, if they're not making enough money,
they should find a new job, which first off, fuck you grow a heart. Like second. Yeah. There's a lot
of people on Twitter that are like, well, they should just leave then it's like, shut the fuck up.
One of those other jobs that are so easy to come by. Yeah. Oh, love to get, uh, uh,
love to get scolded by, uh, uh, cranky, uh, baby boomers who had a million more like, uh, uh,
safety net that we had pensions and like, uh, lots of vacation and all of this stuff
as we live in the gig economy. Hell. Um, but when they say like,
I really enjoyed doing the pod and yeah.
Well, you also like, uh, what you're describing the, uh, the, the people who believe
in the mythology of the park and these attractions so hard, never will you find that type more than
in the trilogy of, uh, patriotic attractions. Oh, sure. You have to put on who do these little,
because if you go see the great moments show or American adventure, I think you talked about this,
on that episode, they do these verbal presentations that are like, yes. So carefully
manicured and full of love and enthusiasm. Uh, uh, you know, they, it's not just like
press and play on the robot show. Please enjoy. Grandma's and Mr. Lincoln. Like they,
specifically these positions, people are like these docents and, uh, and they do a good job.
And they're great. And they deserve, uh, more money, uh, money and benefits that an in and out
burger employee gets. Like, how about that? That's a good, that's a, like a pretty decent company as
far as they're like, nor they're starting wage and their benefits. And yeah. Uh, but one thing
specific to the parks, I saw someone point out when that like, get it. Well, maybe they should
find a new job. Someone pointed out like, yeah, often they do. And, uh, uh, cast member turnover,
like can hurt the experience because you have less and less experienced people sticking around
who, uh, uh, and more like newer and newer people who great. I mean, you always need to refresh,
uh, your employee base, but like, you know, someone's got to, you know, show the new kids
how it's done. Yeah. And if you don't know how to pilot those canoes, they could sink.
If you don't know how to pilot the main street ambulance, it could go off the,
off of main street and into the Emporium and run over 20 people. And even just those like little
extra touches that, that Disney is famous when like someone goes out of the way, your way, like,
Oh, we don't have this item here. Let me call another store. And that, that sort of thing.
Yeah. We did that the other day. Yeah. Oh yeah. That seemed very specific. 30 minute,
a 30 minute journey from somebody trying to call different stores and like they're at a different
kiosk. And I was like, you don't have to do this. And I'm like, yeah, yeah, it's okay. And they're
like waiting on hold. What were you after? Uh, it was, uh, I had to make a bulk purchase that
we'll talk about on a different show. Oh yes. Those have been alluded to on social media. Although
this may come out after that. So I may have to edit this. Don't know. Well, if you're not hearing
it, then it's, uh, it didn't happen. You're one of us. Uh, okay. So, uh, well we've been on a
labor. Yeah. We could go to one. Hey, I think it was you started it. Scott. We're ready to go.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, you can't always be in inflation. I mean, like Disney, the Disney
pricing and stuff has outpaced inflation so much and the wages across the border stagnant
or like very slowly rising. But like Disney certainly isn't leading the way. Yeah. If I'm
paying this much for the annual pass, I would like to think that the workers are getting paid a
little more. That would be nice. Yeah. Cause it's gone up about 500% in the last five years. Yeah.
And I, uh, as I am not a Disney shareholder, I don't give a shit about Disney shareholders. Sure.
Oh, I am one though. I'm sorry, Jason. Oh no. Do you have a single one? Do you have a single
souvenir one? No, I might, might just my, my dad, I'm like a grandfathered into it. Oh, okay. Um,
that was apparently very shit about you. I guess. Now I know I've been hiding in plain sight this
whole time. All right. Uh, this was, it used to be a very common thing. People would give like
a share to newborns and then also you would get the, the shareholder reports used to be nice
souvenirs. I'll tell you this, you know, I liked that my family is also shareholders. Okay. But my
mom refuses to vote in the elections. My mom won't vote. I told her, uh, and like for years,
States elections. No, no, no. She, yeah. Yeah. She votes in those Disney shareholders. She doesn't
want to offend anyone though. Cause she thinks that then like a CEO will see that she voted
against them and that they'll be mad at her. And that, so she would not, she would never,
cause I would try to tell her what to do and she, she just wouldn't, she would not vote.
Well, that's why I don't vote in national elections. Cause you don't want to make the
candidates mad. Yeah. I just want everyone to have a nice time. Trump might have a list of everyone
who didn't vote for him. That is true. Probably did have, got me the ledger of all the people.
Yeah. Yeah. He probably, if he's criticized on Twitter, if you've been blocked, he might've like
looked you up. Yeah, I think that's probably what I thought. Hey, this is a good Nixon, uh, is a good
jumping off point. So, uh, as we said, this ride opened at the world's fair, then opened, uh,
simultaneously in 65 opened at Disneyland where it ran, uh, until 1972. Uh, also funny note, uh,
sponsored by Lincoln savings and loan association. Fun. Very cute. Um, never required an A through E
ticket. Walt wanted this, wanted everyone to see this because it was important historically.
So it was free. You could just walk over to Disney and go on this, this show or enjoy it and then
leave. So like Scott, for instance, in the old days could go down. He'd probably have to smuggle
white wine in and they drink air and you and Aaron would drink it in the car. Would have had to know
a, uh, we would have, we would have paid for club 33 just for, right. It's for wine cheaper. Yeah.
And then you'd go on Lincoln and then you go home. Yeah. You know, it's a thing with no line.
They see, although we do it, we certainly do not do it. Uh, these days, do you guys go on this?
It's a once a year for me. Once I believe there are a couple of attractions around the park.
That's once a year. Jason is smiling from ear to ear. I think he's about to tell us that he goes
on it very frequently. I do pretty regularly. Do you really? Well, sometimes you hit that point
in the day where the wait time for everything else is just, it's just, it's just like a stalemate.
Like, Oh, even pirates is too low. You point where I leave the park. That's what I, I haven't gone on
this with you. Have I, or have I, do you have, I don't really recall us going on this. Jason needs
to be alone a lot. Well, cause I had never center Jason. It's an emotional experience. Apparently
Walt would like tear up when he watched this and, and, uh, Lily and his wife would have to cover for
him and like, Oh, he had something in his eye. And that's, is that your situation as well? Well,
I mean, especially when it's hot, it's air conditioned. You're crying because it's so hot.
Uh, I just, I, you know, I like the animatronic. I like, do you bring a treat in with you?
I don't think you can. I don't, I think they say you have to finish that before you go. Sorry.
You're tearing up right now. Jersey Mike's and also where did you get it from? Like
you hit it in a locker several days in advance. There's, there's some very odd portions of it in
the car. Well, the thing I was getting to earlier about Nixon, uh, uh, I'll talk more when we get
to the current version of why I like it. Um, but, uh, Nixon probably among the people, uh, uh,
came from orange County Republicans. Um, and they were, I believe where some of the people not very
happy in 1973, uh, when Disney opened the Walt Disney story in place of great adventures with
Mr. Lincoln. Oh, uh, great adventures. What did you say? Great moments. Great moments with Mr. Lincoln.
It's not a great adventure. That's for sure. Abraham Lincoln vampire, Hunter, if you want
to do a great adventure, greatest American adventure there is. So this lasted, uh, two years.
Nixon was mad. No, no, I'm just saying I think orange County Republicans were mad because they
just got rid of this Lincoln attraction for a Walt Disney attraction. And the, and the rap was,
it is a dishonor to Walt Disney's legacy to take out Lincoln and put in a thing about
Walt Disney's legacy. Very confusingly, people felt that it was more of a tribute to Walt to keep
Lincoln in there. So they eventually sort of combined them in this odd way, right? I think
like they played the Walt Disney story in the lobby and then it had like a tortured title that
was the Walt Disney story featuring great moments of Mr. Lincoln. Um, I think they would play it
partly during the show too though. And then Lincoln would appear. Oh, like, so the main theater is
still playing a Walt Disney movie. It was like half and half. I believe, huh? Um, I, none of us
are interested enough to know officially. That's where our research sometimes lags is when you're
bored by the information. So you don't keep looking at it. This two year old attraction that people
really didn't like, like is not exactly archived that well. Nobody took an old bolex camera and
filmed a film off of a screen. Film was 23 minutes long says here, stitched together archival film
and audio footage, blah, blah, blah. Similar version was in the magic kingdom. Where was that?
The magic kingdom from 1973 to 1992. There was a Walt Disney story in Disney world kingdom. Yeah.
I'm trying to write. Sure. I saw this episode cover us on that. Or we're going to have to talk about
that and some other horrible episode down the line. Uh, uh, we're going to do magic kingdom
specific Walt Disney story. Walt Disney auto bio stuff and whatever. So one man's dream and the,
we can talk about how, um, my, um, I owned a couple of Walt Disney biographies as a kid,
if you can imagine that. Yeah. And my dad gave me one one time and the, uh, he just,
I had some book about wall. There you go. Happy birthday. And then, uh, he didn't look at it too
carefully because the book was called Hollywood's dark Prince and it was a picture of Walt, but then
his shadow was like, like weird and scary and grotesque. He was like, like his shadow showed
the true devil that was walled. And I read this whole tie it all together. It was like largely
about his union and labor issues and the strikes that he crushed and, uh, communism. And I was D,
I was like 200 pages into this book before my mom figured it out and was like, maybe you shouldn't
be reading that, but I was like, no mommy, please, I must finish Hollywood's dark Prince.
And it was a good book credit where it's due. I think, hold on one second, Edwin laid on my
mic cord. There we go. Um, credit where it's due the Disney family museum, uh, uh, that his daughter
was, you know, that is up in San Francisco that the family was involved in making does not gloss
over the strike stuff. Okay. It's like a pretty big chunk about like the strike. Unlike the moments
of mr. Lincoln that glossed over the foot fetish. Yeah. During, uh, I think during Halloween,
they should rename the Walt Disney story, uh, the dark Prince story featuring great moments with mr.
Lincoln. Ooh, yeah. What a, when in a time when you celebrate villains, let's talk about the
villainy of, uh, Walter. Yeah. I, this, well, this is, I, you know, when I wanted to talk about the
labor stuff for a second, I think I'm like, I want to convey that we aren't so rosy cheeks and
bushy or whatever adjective that we will not, though we are very sincere in our love of the parks.
Sure. And I don't, I never wanted this to be a podcast that's about a Walt was secretly,
you know, he hated the Jews and like all that, which I always find like, uh, is that based in
factor? We just, is it all urban legend and what are we, I never wanted it to be like an ant, this
to be a, uh, so dark of a podcast, but I don't want to ignore that stuff either. I agree. We've
got a realists take on all of these things. Well, I think we also would agree that like the
imagineers should probably be paid board. Sure. Like, uh, these are the real heroes. They're real.
Yeah. So the Disney corporation, but then again, the wonderful nerds in all levels of the, of,
of, uh, or the, whatever the hierarchy of all this stuff. I don't know what they're paid,
but it should be more. Let's bring them on. We love them. We love what they do. And ask how much
they're paid. Let's just ask him to show pasted. It'll be like a Howard Stern interview. How much
you, how much you make do something like that, which imagineers you want to bang?
Anyway, Hey, back to Lincoln facts. Um, there was also, uh, there was like a couple other little
exhibits in this, in this zone. There was like a, I think you could, you could look at Walt's office
for a long time. Is that still the case? That is in, uh, well they've restored his office on the lot
and then, uh, uh, the last time I was in Florida, there was a recreation of it. Yeah. But the one
man stream in that same, yes, but there's not one up in Anaheim. I think there was at one point.
And there was also this little thing. Do we guys ever there when there was a, uh, there's this
little show that was kind of well done that you would watch with four other people. Nobody ever
sat and watched this. That was, it was like, it was an owl with a, with the graduation. I saw,
I saw a picture of this and I got very excited, but I was not, it was before my time going to
Disneyland. This might've been like pre 2000. Yeah. There's this little show in the corner
of the lobby where you wait for the Mr. Lincoln attraction and there's a, yeah, it's like a
owl with a chalkboard. It's the owl tells you about the true life adventures, the nature movies
that Walt made in the fifties and sixties and how he, and his interest in and love for animals.
It's the owl from the old like music shorts. Oh yeah. And the sing Disney sing alongs.
They would repurpose that footage to do those Disney sing alongs. Yes. Um, yeah,
that's why I got so excited. I was like, holy crap. It's the owl. I don't know what his character's
name is, but you would have loved it because as a, as a checky cheese fan, this was seeing an
animatronic, uh, that played to audiences of no one quietly in a corner, wasted animatronics.
Sir. Wonderful. I didn't, that was news to me when I was looking this up that that existed,
that they ever had one of those. Yeah. Well, it was fascinating to see. And then he presses play
on a video and then I stopped watching the video. Uh, but the first two minutes of the video of the
video that I watched were a fascinating, uh, I, maybe I have not been less engaged in the
source material of a topic before I never, I don't know what you guys did. I don't think I
watched a full Lincoln speech. I don't think I don't really know a lot about how the versions
were different. Um, I, uh, I know that it got shorter every time. Like the state fair one was
the world's fair one was very long, got a little shorter when it came to Disney and got a little
shorter again in the seventies, shorter and shorter and shorter. All these, all these shows
over the years, I think I've gotten a little shorter, which is fine by me, but a problem
for you, Jason. Well, no, you can't, Jason cannot get to REM if the show is in a certain way.
Minutes isn't enough time to fall all the way asleep. They, they've made, they've certainly
made some edits. I mean, the speeches are, uh, uh, now Edwin is getting, uh, fidgety. Um, they,
they've certainly made some edits over the years. I mean, the dialogue of the, the Royal Dano, uh,
section, the actual animatronic is kind of a hodgepodge of speeches. Like it's not one
speech all the way through. Yeah. Uh, I think that happened at one point. Um, well, I, I want to get
to that cause I know Scott, you're excited about that version. Oh yeah. Real quick in, um, the
eighties, uh, so in 1975, Lincoln comes back, uh, at Disneyland. Um, and in 1984, they added in
the, uh, golden dream and two brothers from the American adventure in have caught these songs
rear in their heads on this podcast again. Yeah. Uh, uh, again, I would like to, yeah, I would like
to talk about how occasionally I like to just yell like one war blow and one war gray, like just out
of nowhere. I think it's a very funny bit to do on a date. Where do you do it? Yeah, sure. Let's go
with that. Um, just anywhere, just anywhere. Um, and golden dream, I think used to be in the show
somewhere. Now it just kind of plays as you walk out. Oh, it plays in the lobby. Really? I think
it's after the show. Like when the lights come up and you're leaving, when was the last time you saw
the show? Um, I think I went in 2014. I'm on a once every four years with Lincoln. See, it's been
a while. Although you know, the most recent time you have been in the theater. Oh yeah. This was
a blast. When Scott and I watch when our respective, our significant others, uh, watch the Oscars.
Yeah. There was a special annual pass holder event. Yeah. Um, where, yeah, we watched the live
telecast of the Oscars. Um, this ended, what ended up being the, uh, the, the Kimmel, uh, wrong
envelope, uh, snafu year. Although we had long vacated for our blue Bayou reservation by the
time all that happened. But yeah, we got to watch the Oscar opening with Justin Timberlake and
Kimmel's monologue with an audience. Second row. With a screen blocking where what you know
has a Lincoln animatronic behind it. So Hollywood's biggest night you got to see projected on a
screen in front of like a sleeping robot and animatronic. Yes. Yeah. It would have been nice
if they opened the curtain once in a while and see him. Yeah. But they didn't. The brightest stars
in Hollywood sky are out tonight, but the real brightest star is right here. And he was our 16th
president. And he rips through the screen. Who cares about this? All this fluff. Um, let's talk
about fortitude and having a pride in your bosom. That was a blast. And there was a trivia contest.
Yes. And I won one or no, it wasn't a trivia contest. It was a raffle. Yeah. And they had to
keep skipping past all the empty seats. So eventually once the seat was reached with a
person in it, I was that person. And I got a copy of the guardians to cartoon. The guardian
guardians cartoon soundtrack, which is by believe still in its original packaging in a closet
somewhere and a palette of bulk, uh, Perry, the platypuses, uh, that have not been sold.
You get to take these off our hands. Um, that was a lot of fun. And that, you know, I, I,
pre-thinking about what else do you do with the space? Uh, you know, I leave Lincoln in there
certainly, but more, more events, more award shows and stuff. Yeah. Let's do football games.
Let's do the Miss America pageant. I want to watch everything in modern, new modern family
episodes screened in live as they air to watch it with a laugh track. I, I was there. I happened
to be there once, I think it was when family was visiting, we were staying down there and it was
an AP event in there and they were showing, um, old documentary. They showed like, um, either the
Disney world story or they showed like one of the wonderful world of Disney, like documentaries in
there just for APs and you got a button. So, so, so, uh, while we, the certain things about
Disneyland, we're not thrilled about the AP program is one of them. That's not on our
show list. You get a, honestly, it is kind of like, oh, no, I feel like they've dialed back on,
they've dialed way back on events. We used to get crazy perks. You would go down and if you signed
up or I have on my Twitter, an alert that sends me a message that says if there's an AP thing,
you can sign up for, there used to be wonderful events that would be like closed off. I think
they did one like a year ago and I was too, too slow getting it. It was for Cars Land. And then
it was, it would just be APs after dark. You get two hours with just a small group of people. They
used to do that stuff all the time. They would do previews for new rides, not anymore. Everything
sucks now because of how many people are there. And so as protest, you're only going to go, uh,
one and a half times a week on average. I only pay $300 to get into Star Wars land. I will not pay
five. I swear I have a limit. I am a disciplined man. I will only slip some bribes to the people
controlling the line for Star Wars, Galaxy's edge. Scott, I started to tee this up. Uh, now
eventually the Walt Disney story with great moments featuring Mr. Lincoln, that's Mr. Lincoln,
not Abraham or president. It was never Abraham in the title. Yeah. Uh, but eventually you got a
refurb. Yeah. In the, what was it? 2000 2001 is what I'm saying. At which point? Well,
you're talking about the Walt Disney story featuring great moments with Mr. Lincoln,
the journey to Gettysburg colon colon journey to Gettysburg. Yes. I saw a sign that said that had
even more. The sign was the Disneyland opera house presents the Walt Disney story featuring great
moments of Mr. Lincoln, the journey to Gettysburg. Incredible. Boy, there's a lot of convoluted names
out there. Uh, people that were guardians of the galaxy mission breakout to shame. Yeah. I was
going to say people that were complaining about that, Jesus, that this was double the size. The
Disney, it's important to know that the Disneyland opera house presents it. I mean, what, cause how
do I, they might be presenting something else. Yeah. Could be the Oscars or, uh, um, do you know,
did anybody know what the opera house was before Lincoln in general? I don't, I didn't know this
cause I was like, was that building there or did they build it? Cause it was always there, but it
was kind of nothing. There was, it was, I think just a facade and then they put in babes and toy
land sets for real years. Yeah. So that's what was there from 61 to 65. And then for Disneyland's
10th birthday, Mr. Lincoln evicted the toys. Wow. I didn't know that. Yeah. Um, and that was just
there forever. It's time to learn. Babes and Toyland is a horrifying movie. Yeah. Yeah.
Horrifying, but it's, it's very weird and not great. Yeah. But it gave us those, uh, soldiers
who factor into so many parades. Yeah. The soldiers are cool. And, uh, there's, there's a great Ed
Wynn performance in it. Not Ed Wynn, your dog. Not Ed Wynn the dog, but Ed Wynn. Is that is why your dog is
Ed Wynn though, you said? Yeah, basically he's sort of named after Ed Wynn. Oh man. Have we talked
about how I'm a Keenan Wynn guy? No, I don't think so. Ed Wynn's son Keenan, who was an old
grouch. Who's an old like old curly mustache weirdo who's a villain in a lot of old Disney's
and like the shaggy DA and the love bug. Oh, get that love bug. He's just this old, sour, cranky.
I like him as much as Thorol or any of them. Wow. Love Keenan Wynn. Uh, he, he's responsible for one
of my favorite scenes ever, which is in the movie Super Train, where he's the billionaire who presents
the idea of a super train. Gentlemen, we must build Super Train. And then kick into hard disco
and shots of a high tech train. Uh, a great scene. Love Keenan Wynn. We've got to do a bunch of Wynn
episodes, I think. Yeah. Let's just go through the filmography. Not Steve Wynn though. No, that's a
bad Wynn. That ship has sailed. But like the Danos, that's multiple families. Right, different.
But anyway, great moments with Mr. Lincoln, the journey to Gettysburg. Uh, this was a very bizarre
attempt to revitalize this attraction because a complaint you might have to this day is that it's
a little dull. It's a little dry. And they decided to bring in some technology that was a smash hit
at the show Sounds Dangerous with Drew Carey in Florida, which is a show that is a, uh, where
Drew Carey is a private eye and then the, the lights go out and you experience his adventure
with headphones and, and the head, the audio is so precise. It's actually the same as Alien Encounter,
where the audio is so precise that you feel like these sensations are actually happening, uh, to you,
such as, you know, liquid being poured right next to your ears as often happens. Well, and getting a
haircut, right? Getting a haircut happens in this. And this is binaural audio. Binaural sound you
were the, you were given these fancy headphones. Yeah. So disgusting reuse throughout the day,
headphones. Yeah. 3D glasses are one thing. They clean them now too. Most of these places,
as you and I know, cause we went backstage to see it. Oh, that's right. We were given an odd
tour of the Despicable Me. Years ago, we were at Universal Studios and employees came and said,
Hey, do you want to get a tour of the backstage and then go right in front of the line? And we
were like, what are you talking about? Who are you? And we're like, you don't want the tour. And
we're like, why are you giving us this tour? And this sounds like I'm doing a bit. This is literally
what happened. And then we were like, I guess so, but like, do we have to, is there like a price?
Do we have to pay for it? No, it's just free. Come with us. They were like such kind of sedate girls.
And we're like, okay, I guess, but why is this happening? They're like, come on, we're going on
the tour. This is the, this is the happy fun land. This is where Grue goes to his daughters.
They're like, you don't want the tour? And we're like, what are we touring? And then they're like,
just, we're like, all right. And we were like laughing, like, why is this happening? And then
they were laughing too, and they don't have an answer for it. And we just like saw where they
washed the glasses. So this is where I watched the glasses. Okay. Why are you showing us this? Ha,
okay. I never understood any of that. And you know, what's funny is that we were with,
we happen to be with the hallowed bug main. I'm not familiar with this entity. Oh, really?
Yeah. Well, bug may, well, he's a villain who haunts podcasts. And the internet is a twisted
man. And he, with this is, we were at universal studios within a month of a man blowing his brains
out at the Despicable Me area. I forget the whole, it was some like ongoing dispute with,
he had been dating an employee and he committed suicide next to the Despicable Me fun land.
And which caused when we were so confused, why are we getting this Despicable Me tour? And bug
asked, is this because of the thing? A reasonable question. Is it some strange, like, do they have
to like go overboard to show that this area is thriving and that it was not effective? Yes.
They were showing us there were no ghosts in the glasses cleaning stations. I guess. We never,
we never got a good answer. They didn't answer that. They didn't answer anything. I also remember
that we were led into a room where we all just started dancing to happy. That's the end of the
ride. That's the end of the ride. You come out there anyway. Oh, okay. Well, they did it in the
opposite way and we were there and we were dancing for a while sort of without questioning it. Okay,
we're dancing. And then bug was like, can we stop? And they said, yeah. Well, they were,
they were surprised. Like we felt like we had an obligation to dance in the happy room. Yeah. And
we didn't apparently. And they were like, no, you don't have to keep dancing. So for whatever
reason, we felt like we had to perform for these people. Well, if somebody comes up to us and is
bossing us around and leading us with a clipboard or something, we better do everything they say.
Let me ask, were these people flirting with you? I don't think so. I mean, Scott's with his wife.
I don't know. Okay. Hey, it doesn't mean anything. That's all that's are off with these despicable
me maidens. They didn't, they did not seem interested in us. They didn't seem like they
really wanted to be doing what they had to randomly give people every 20 people. They had to give a
tour to like once an hour. The minions have their own morality. Sure. They have their own laws and
rules. So, so they claim mates are their husbands and wives within minion worlds or is it just,
is it like a question? Is it like wild, wild country? Are they all, do the minions all have
sex parties? Probably the second one. Probably that. Yeah. Hey, look, they didn't have to ask
me to captain the Mark Twain many years ago, but I still, you know, I think it's just so,
it's those little perks we were talking about. I thought you begged to do that. I thought you went
up to the captain and were like, please, it's my birthday. I'm 30 years old. Let me drive the boat.
Let me drive the boat. I thought that's what it was. Anyway, I guess not. So the journey to get
his birthday. It's been as long as the journey to talk about. How, I, I, I, one of the Drew Carey
experience when I was young, I did not go on this binaural sound version of Great Moments.
What were the, were they, I'm trying to remember, were they full headphones?
Um, they weren't, I don't think as they weren't thick. They were, they were like a little thicker
than, it wasn't earbuds, but it was not as, as you're monitoring the audio and your headphones are
covering your whole ear. Maybe they were though. I don't quite recall. I kind of have a feeling,
I kind of have a memory that they were, at least it's a Drew Carey thing.
Okay. That it was like cushioning. I don't remember if you came in with them.
I came in with them. During the Lincoln episode. I, yeah. Just talking about Lincoln is making
him remember the naps he's taken in the ride. Yeah. Scoring seven naps ago. So this version
of the ride, I mean, look, every ride from nine, every new ride from 1990 or to 2008 involved you
getting your hair cut some way. They had to use this haircut thing, which, because it does really
work, you feel like there are scissors snipping right at your ears. You know, a fun feeling that
there are scissors so close inside your ears. Like, why would you want this? And they make jokes about
having cut people before. Oh, that's right. Don't worry. I won't cut you. I've cut a lot of people.
Their hair, of course. Yeah. We now this one I did listen to and maybe I, in a way I do like this
more than just the dry Lincoln speech because it's so bizarre. So the premise that they lay out,
like the lights go out and now you are taking on the role of private Cunningham. You fought in the
war and now you're going to get, you're going to meet Lincoln. I don't know if you're, you know,
you're going to meet Lincoln or if it's, it just happens to happen by accident. By accident, you do
meet Frederick Douglass. So, uh, audio, but also then just, he's talking. They can't simulate,
Hey, this is Frederick Douglass. He's going to put his finger in your ear.
There's no way to the audio doesn't enhance that. And it was like, must your hair up or anything.
Hey, old boy, old guy. Yeah. He had like big weird hair. Yeah. Matthew Brady also in this.
Yes. But yeah, you get the civil war photographer,
but you get your hair cut so that you can get a photo taken by civil war photographer,
Matthew Brady. I'm going to keep talking. I'm going to go get you guys keep talking. I'm going
to go get a couple of pairs of scissors and I'm going to try to recreate this.
ASMR experiment live on the podcast. I like this. Okay. So what can we explain?
You, yeah. So then, uh, also, uh, the, they say after you get your picture taken, they say,
Oh, are you mating Mr. You're meeting president Lincoln. I'm heading to the white house too.
Let's go together. Yeah. So you hitch a ride with some guy, uh, and then,
there's a fly at one point, a fly buzzes around your ear, which, all right, I'll give you that.
It was a weird, uh, dirty smelly time. The 1800s, there were flies everywhere. I assume.
Um, they, their line is literally said, so private Cunningham, are you ready to meet
Abraham Lincoln? Like, Oh, the writing of this. Yeah. Uh, are you, are you ready for this
experiment? You have scissors now. You guys can finish a recapping and then I will,
and then we'll run an experiment. Do you have a fly you can make go into the listeners ears?
I can do a Michael Winslow style, uh, impersonation of a fly. Can we make just this episode by NARL?
This episode is officially by NARL. Hey, the first by NARL podcast. The ride. Uh, all right.
So here I'll, I'll just say my name and it by the, in editing, this should be shifting back and
forth rapidly in a Doppler way between your ears. And if it isn't, then Mike fucked up the editing.
Was that pretty crazy? Do you feel like you were inside a washing machine or something?
You know what we should do? Uh, let's do, we'll do a quick, like a quick improv as they call it.
Sure. You're going to meet Jason Sheridan. All right. So you're okay. Let's figure out a
scenario here that you would be going to meet Jason at, uh, what, uh, what if you're trying
to petition me to make it so that white union soldiers and black union soldiers get the same
pay. So it's still the same scenario, but you're the president or you're just around. Uh, yeah.
I think it's better if you're like in an ice cream parlor. All right. So we're at the drive
through. You pick the parlor. Yeah, sure. Uh, we're at one of my favorite LA spots, uh, uh,
that I try not to go to a lot less. It becomes less special. The drive through Baskin Robbins.
That is also a regional training center. Uh, oh yeah. Right here in Burbank. What is the
training center do to make it different? Uh, I don't know. Well, it's just like an office building
that looks like it has like a Baskin Robbins glued to it. Uh, that also has a drive through.
Okay. The drive through is the real star of the show. In this case, are you eating inside?
You're inside. All right. That's good. Okay. Which Mike and I discovered recently pretty nice inside.
Yes. It has to be pretty nice. Now is it me? Me? Because really in the show, the audience would be.
Well, I think it's the audience. So we have to come up with a name now that the audience is going
to assume. So they're, you know, like private Cunningham, for instance, a different name. And
we're all sort of assuming this character. Yeah. So maybe, but it has to be a non-gender specific.
So let's say that the listener is a doctor. Uh, so you're, you're Dr. Reynolds, Dr. Reynolds. All
right. And you're going to meet Jason Sheridan. But of course you're in the parking lot now
and a barber comes up to you. Excuse me. Um, um, Dr. Reynolds and Scott, you'll be Dr. Reynolds.
Oh wait, but I thought the listener is Dr. Reynolds. All right. I'm getting confused.
You just have to direct it to the audience. We could both be, we're two, uh, both barbers.
We're both barbers. Okay. Great. Uh, excuse me, Dr. Reynolds, uh, before you go inside this
Baskin-Robbins training center, I think it's very important that I cut your hair in the parking lot.
Yes. And me as well. You need to look your best after all you're meeting Jason Sheridan himself.
Yes. So president of ice cream eating. Yes. Uh, and so I think we're going to both be working
on you at the same time. Uh, so just a little bit of a trim. You'll, you won't regret it. You'll
look smashing in that photograph and you'll show your grandchildren. Yes. And I want you, we're
very good at cutting hair. You know, we've, we've never injured a man. Seriously. Ha ha. Just a bit
of a joke there. Seriously. We're very safe. Yes. So, uh, of course you have such, such large hair
here. Uh, we're just going to take a little while. Uh, here we go.
Almost there. Just a little bit more off the side. I know we're focusing almost only on the sideburns,
but that's what they were incredibly long, almost down to your waist. As you know,
this is the style that Jason prefers when he meets a stranger. He is very specific. All right. Hold
on. Let me just pour a cup of, let me just pour a quick cup of coffee. Ah, yes. You'll need your
energy. Okay. Here you go. Would someone get that horse fly out of here? All right. Are you all set?
Are you, are you ready to meet Mr. Sheridan? It seems as though you are right this way.
Ah, Dr. Reynolds, welcome to ice cream.
And that's it. I guess that's the experience. Wait a minute, Dr. Don't you want to eat ice cream next
to Jason and hear what it's like when he eats ice cream? Look, I've been coming here a long time
and I'm telling these people, they have to use more fudge. There's just not enough fudge for my
taste. Hold on. Uh, some of the fudge has hardened and I need to cut it.
It's my fudge scissors. I keep on me at all times. America, spend your golden wings.
And this is an accurate, new fangled simulation of binaural great moments with Mr. Lincoln.
I hope you enjoyed this. The podcast The Ride presents great moments with Jason Sheridan and
a Baskin-Robbins training parlor presented by the podcast The Ride Historical Society. Yes.
Sponsored by culture since 1872 sponsored by scissors.
We should have also said before all that to either close your eyes or shut off all the lights,
whether you are in a car or on a jog, you should have for full effect, you should have listened to
that in pure darkness. Yes. So go back and do it again and do all the things Scott just said.
Experience it the way it was meant to be. Well, that was good. I think we've really illustrated
what was so successful about it. We really illustrated. Great moments with Mr. Lincoln.
This is another issue. We're missing a big part of this and that is that you're not going to be
missing a big part of this and that is that you get in a battle and you lose a leg. Oh, that's
right. We should have had a moment where an ice cream machine, a freezing machine, a freezer
goes haywire and a bunch of springs. And you get amputated by the ice cream machine. So after you
get the joy of meeting Frederick Douglass and then meeting Mr. Lincoln, there's a great little stiff
exchange that's like, oh, he's getting a haircut as well. And it's like, you'll look like you're
going to look very natural, Mr. Lincoln. Why, that's exactly what I'd like to avoid. Oh boy,
just clever politeness. But Douglass and Lincoln are arguing about pay disputes about Union soldiers.
We were talking about pay earlier. I see. Well, you, in this scenario, you were probably talking
about union disputes with the Baskin-Robbins employees. Yes. In between. I was trying to
unionize the Baskin-Robbins employees. Yeah. A valuable effort. And the training center is
really the place to do it. That's ground zero. Yeah. But anyway, you meet the president and then
you get, and then you're immediately back in the war and you get amputated. You get a leg,
you get a leg blown off. You like, it seems like somebody's just saying your name, Private
Cunningham, Private Cunningham. And then you wake up and you're in the hospital and the doctors did
everything they could, but they cut your leg off. And then Lincoln comes in. But there's no, there's
no like sound of like while they're cutting your leg off. No, no. All right. Just a quick snip.
Here, hold your leg up towards your ear, please. Make it easier for me to trim it off. And then
Lincoln arrives to see the wounded. So not only do you meet Lincoln once, you meet him twice.
And he tells you, you have to live son. He gets right up in your ear. This is ASMR. Yeah. You must
live boy. You must live. Which is then followed by the narration of Private Cunningham followed
the president's order and lived. He would not have. This was a different time. This was before the
president would go visit victims and call the people who shot them wacky and goofs and nut nuts
and whatever with paper towel rolls and throwing paper towel rolls. So after many years of dry
speeches and choruses of children talking about Illinois, suddenly we end up with a little
headphone role play the same that previously had been used to make an alien growl on your neck.
And now it's the president, you're getting a haircut to meet the president. This was so strange.
This is one of the strangest things ever in the Disney. This is the forcing technology they had
onto this. It makes more sense for the other applications. A little more sense. I didn't you
get to try on Lincoln's hat. That would have been perfect. A little bit of hair Russell,
the famous stove pipe is low. And he'd like you look why I think you look better than me. Not
that that's difficult to do. Sure. Also this ends with the entirety of the Gettysburg dress.
Oh yeah. The animatronic does a full speech. And what I don't remember is,
obviously the Gettysburg dress is iconic. But I feel like I maybe caught the criticism that it was
less interesting in a way of a full speech than this great moments for where that's stitching
together the great moments. It's all the hits. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. It's like a medley. Your favorite
thing in a concert when a band plays a medley. Right. Just the choruses or something. That's
weird that that happens. I don't like a medley. Except for when Prince did that sampler set.
That was kind of cool but also a real cock tease. He's just plowing through. We know we're not
going to hear the whole song. He's just playing the beginning of When Does Cry and he shuts it
off. And then he would play like the first like five seconds of Darling Nikki and then he would
be like uh-uh. I saw the roots play once and it was an hour long medley. Really? At least. It was
the whole thing was it. Was it their songs or something else? It was their songs. I feel like
you're pro medley to get done with this quicker. I don't know. I was just more like oh this is
one long jam. Like I didn't really know them that well at the time. That doesn't sound too bad.
Yeah that doesn't sound as corny as the Beach Boys doing a medley of all the car songs
or uh. Oh no. Yeah. No. Who else does medleys? I'm trying to remember. I mean Lincoln does medleys.
Lincoln met Lincoln, Beach Boys, Prince, Jason. Like that's it basically. All the greats. The
greats. The great performers of our time. But so this was very strange. It was very odd. And
people seemingly not satisfied with Gettysburg. Yeah and then what replaced it was a 50th
anniversary movie starring Steve Martin and Donald Duck. Yeah. Now did you ever watch that? Yes I did.
Was that is that was that any good? I don't think I ever did the whole thing. I still play it in the
lobby. I've watched it in the lobby. I don't think I saw it when it was actually in the main theater.
I saw it in what? 2005? I didn't see it on the big screen. 50th anniversary. I saw it that would have been
when I first started going to Disneyland in 2006. I would have I remember seeing this. I must have
missed it when I went to because the first time I went in 2007 I think. So I must have missed it.
Yeah. For some reason I didn't feel like I needed to go watch a movie. I thought it was nice.
Sure. I thought it was very pleasant. Again it was your air conditioned theater. Yeah I like a nice
little movie break or a little show break. You know what I like about this and Lincoln is that they
would run continuously. I don't like a show with like a set start time. Wait what do you mean? As
much. Like can't box you in. Like if you go to Universal Studios and the animal show is going to be at 11 and 1230.
Okay I take it back because I do like the animal actor show but like I like a show that you can
just squeeze in wherever because you know oh every 15-20 minutes. It's easier to do if it's robots.
You're just saying it's like it's that runs more basically. Yeah it runs continuously. Still I don't
know what it says on there but it'll run like 50-20 minutes. It runs continuously for no one and I think maybe
we should talk about the greater issue with this which is I would say at this point it's not a real
priority to like replace this or do something better but there was a moment where they were
going to evict Lincoln for Muppet Vision 3D. Yes. And there was a lot of people were I remember
newspaper articles growing up here. I remember people being upset about that and I even saw a
quote that is so weenery that it sounds like something child Scott would have said which a
12 year old was quoted as saying Lincoln was president Kermit is a frog and that's why you
can't put the fun Muppet show into the theater. Wait frog or fraud? Not a fraud. No this child
didn't think that Kermit didn't earn his entertainment success. Did you just call him Kermit?
Did I say Kermit? I'm pretty sure you just called him Kermit. Probably force of habit I do
something called Tiny Fuppets which is a Portuguese ripoff of Muppet Babies. Did I say Kermit every
time? No no. Last time I think you said call him Kermit. I do a thing with all these ripoffs of
Muppet characters so it's very so I've said the word Kermit a lot more than Kermit so it's very
force of habit thanks for pointing it out. I figured you could get a plug-in real quick too.
Um that's true yeah well and yeah we'll go to tinyfuppets.com and there may be some
new Tiny Fuppets activity in the near future. But anyway Kermit people were upset I was going to
evict Lincoln. There were like like fans really this was an early this is a pretty internet
instance of the fanboys being furious that they were going to take away something beloved and
yet even in that article it's clear like the Imagineers are a little baffled they're like
it's funny that everybody's so upset about this because you know what they weren't doing was
going to the show attraction. Now I don't think they boned that decision necessarily because
Muppet Vision 3D did make it to Disneyland in California Adventure and they don't even run it
all the time anymore. They use that it's done. Is it done forever? I think so. They use it mainly for
to that theater to preview upcoming films and your wrinkles and times and what have you.
But the so I don't know that they made the bad decision but Muppet Vision was real hot at the
time. A lot of popularity a lot of hype about it coming out of Florida and I maybe I don't know
at the time maybe it would have been a good move too and I think we just we should be open to the
idea that if there's a better idea one day why do we have to keep this attraction? Well it's
it's interesting you're bringing this up. I have I'm conflicted on that because as you know we're
all very progressive when it comes to rides and people changing things at the parks but I do think
there's something nice about Main Street sort of being untouched like the idea that it's still
Lincoln that is a very dry pretty boring historical lesson through the lens of Walt Disney.
It's nice that it's on Main Street because Main Street still kind of feels untouched even though
there's a little Starbucks in there but it's nicely hidden and it's still themed. You know what I will
you know what maybe I'll take that back. I love the Muppet show they do in Orlando there's a real
puppet practical puppet show they do in Liberty Square. Oh yeah they like they poke their heads
out of the windows. It's wonderful and everyone gathers around and it's so nice to see the actual
Muppets like you see them in person and there are five different shows so if you do something I feel
like that might be in the spirit of Main Street it might be okay but I do like I do like having
something dry and boring in that place. Well it also makes the most sense there yeah and it fits
the theme yeah of everything so I would be I would be almost more precious about it than I would be
other places in the park for some reason. I don't know why. I think it's weird that they got away with
taking it out for like four or five years to have Steve Martin and Donald Duck talk about Disneyland but
it wasn't supposed to last that long but yeah or four years sorry four years and then Lincoln came
back with the new and improved in 2009 the current version that we have now. They made a big deal.
And it is improved yeah what you were saying you were withholding your thoughts. No I just like it I
don't know that I have I like it. It's no revolutionary they actually they went back to a lot of original
stuff. Yeah yeah they did. To Paul Freese. Because they had taken Paul Freese off and Royal Dano there
have been another who are much better than the journeys to Gettysburg. Yeah yeah they had different
actors there and they put the original stuff back on. Yeah that might have been also like the like I
wonder if you actually were to gather up the amount of people that were protesting though the Lincoln
going away and added up to people that were protesting like Tower of Terror going away.
Is it possible that just because it was early on and people protesting things it felt like a bigger
deal. And because there was less precedent. I think that's what that's what that may be the first
instance of like a beloved classic thing being taken out. And they were like oh shit like
where people are so mad and it was really like 150 people. We may have just not heard about when
inner space was taken out. Well that is a question I have for imagineers and historians is what were
that what was it like back then when a when a move excuse me a ride like that where was taken out
were people really upset or did people just go to the park and go huh it's gone it's something else
and they didn't give a shit. The way it probably should be although there's things we're upset
about I guess. Yeah it depends I mean obviously it depends what it is. But yeah like I wonder if it
was like just a very vocal 50 people and imagineers and management was like oh no like I don't want to
I don't want them to be mad at us but like Tower of Terror had maybe some stupid petition online
that was 15,000 strong and they're like who gives a shit they're gonna go on the new one they'll
like it. I'm sure there's a damned if you do damned if you don't element of like well in the if we
change it people complain if we don't change it yeah either people complain it's boring or
no one goes. Like there should have been I'll say this there should have been a massive protest when
the country bears were taken out of Disneyland. I wasn't here at the time and it wasn't even my
favorite ride at that time but I am so upset that it's not there that that might be the one of the
only ones I would actually like go down there with a sign. I let you down I could have I could have
represented California. Yeah I didn't I apologize. The country bears. I wasn't mobilized now I'm more
engaged and I'll I will fight the fight on anything else that. I would like I will go down there and
protest the wages for the workers and the removal of country bears over a decade ago. Those are two
causes I really believe in. You flip a sign and it says and while I'm here yeah right as well get
this out. Yeah. Is there any way to reverse that? The heads are still up in the back. Yeah can we
please poo no one goes on that poo bear ride. I think I think my Lincoln thing is like absolutely
leave it and they it's good that they did a refresh and they're you know keeping it you know
pristine but I think we should be open to the idea that if something was better to go in there but
the Disney show situation like I'm not I'm not so into anything they've recently done. I'm not like
dying to get PhilharMagic in their Florida show. I don't think there is a good candidate I'm just
saying if it ever. No. There are probably there's probably a way to make the show a little bit more
interesting. It's not putting headphones on the audience. Well because a lot of it is the paintings
like from the Epcot. Yeah yeah yeah. From the American Adventure a lot of it before Lincoln
starts talking. Is Two Brothers still in it? Yes oh yeah. Two Brothers is very much alive.
Honestly I would like more of the animatronic. That's what I'm saying. I'm saying there's a version
I don't know if we have other animatronics added to it or he becomes like that cartoonish
robot more and he like gets up real close to the stage can we get him to walk a little more
because right now he still kind of just gets like pulled it seems like there's like an invisible
string that pulls him out of the chair. Like if we could get him to walk a little bit if we could
get that robot a little more sophisticated I think a lot more people will go in if he's like maybe
like doing the Jay Leno start of the show he goes down and he slaps hands with the front row or
something like let's get something flashier in there for Lincoln to do. Have you heard about this? Have you seen this?
I don't want him to do Lewinsky jokes but I'm just saying if he can do something more impressive maybe.
Well you know what we missed is the fact that the the urban legend of the story and I think I saw
an engineer talking about it so I think it's true that when they were first testing this robot during
the uh the 64 World's Fair that they they they brought a bunch of Illinois specific dignitaries
and they ran a test for them and the uh there was a problem and hydraulic fluid leaked out of the neck
of the robot the shot out of the neck and straight this is where it seems made up but the
engineer says that it is true that the hydraulic fluid they were using was red.
My god. So it seemed as though he was gushing blood from the neck as though he had been shot.
There's a clip online of the Lincoln animatronic in the hall of presidents slowly falling over.
Oh yes. It's very funny. I think it was in America's funniest videos episode too.
They had creaky sound effects. Yeah. Oh we'll post that though. That is in the speech. It's great.
Never stops. It never stops. He keeps but he just bends perfectly. The show must go on. But anyway
the I I think maybe you nod to that history and you just I think maybe we do shoot Lincoln
on stage. Oh wow. We load him up with blood. Look I don't normally I wouldn't go for that normally
but for a Halloween overlay yes. Oh that's that's fine. Uh I found a weird fact about this uh show
um in okay in the modern family episode from season three where they go to Disneyland. Uh huh.
Uh okay this is uh quote the episode closed with the family sitting together watching great
moments with Mr. Lincoln. Jay Pritchard which is Ed O'Neill's character reflects that watching the
show with his kids while they were young inspired him to stay with his wife for the sake of the
children. Isn't that weird? Yeah it is weird. Huh well and much much earlier I guess uh on a
different sitcom Lincoln offered advice uh to a different character who was having love issues
uh Blossom's brother. Uh we I did a lot of tweets about a very bizarre Blossom episode that was
shot at Disneyland and there's a very strange moment where you watch the end of the Lincoln
show where he just sits down and then no curtain comes it's just the lights stay on the end.
Everyone gets up and leaves they don't lower the curtain on Lincoln so he's just sitting there
but then you find out why because everybody leaves but then Blossom's brother stays behind
and Lincoln starts talking to him in kind of like a borshbelty voice uh and uh
and he I had one all the audio is great but I just was one of my favorite joke that he says
here you go. I just don't know what to do. Do? Enjoy. You're lucky. Ever see what married Todd
looked like? Whoa! This is this lounge lizard voice delivering a joke about his Lincoln roasting
his wife. Lincoln's unwell wife. Mentally unwell. The old ball and show boy I love the if I had a
melania on my hands it'd be no problem. Um I yeah quite a moment and it's unclear whether it's like
magic there's never a moment where he like somebody comes back and taps Blossom's brother on the
shoulder and says like hey are you okay you fell asleep there I think just in the reality of Blossom.
Lincoln comes to life. Lincoln came to life. Or he was possessed. Or was possessed sure uh but not by
Lincoln's ghost but by the ghost of like uh. Cat skills comedian. Yeah yeah. Lenny something. Yeah
yeah Lenny or Lenny Allen. Forgotten. Favorite comedian Lenny Allen. But so uh and also but also
they did custom uh animation I think for the like like Blossom got them to do specific programming
uh um uh in an episode apparently directed by Bill Bixby the Incredible Hulk uh odd fact about that
so Bill Bixby was overseeing custom animation turning Lincoln into an old comedian um so I think
all this does is show that Lincoln is you can reprogram him you can do other things. Yeah. He
can break character a bit. Lincoln sings the atardee let it go. I mean that would kill at the park.
Sure. People would love that. Pack the house in. I think yeah I think you can do with with the big
thing in in rides now is that you know it just changes up every time you go on there's a slightly
different experience or you'd get a different like Indiana Jones you were at a certain point you got
different like temples with different colors and stuff um but with Guardians you get different
songs so I think yeah maybe changing up the Lincoln show sometimes you get the Gettysburg
address sometimes he sings uh you know famous Disney songs. One is all roast jokes about his wife.
Yeah. She's so crazy. I'm gonna uh say you know because because trends are so cyclical um if they
go back to a thing that seemed like they were trying to really get to catch on a few years ago
of personalization so it's just the full Lincoln speeches but just every now and then he has they
have to slip in like Jason Jason no no pal all the armies of Europe and Asia and Africa combined
could not take a drink from the Mississippi Eric. Well you know what you could actually do so you
don't have to use that terrible ET technology where he garbles voices just do the turtle talk
with uh with crush technology have some teenager backstage he's making Lincoln talk so Lincoln can
do crowd work so like he can do the speech too but also he can address the people and they can ask
him questions oh yeah I think that would be great hey that was my time folks but we got a little
bit left if anybody was wondering if you want to line up by the microphone over here he could do
that like a real inoffensive kind of topical comedy where you don't really take a shot at anyone it's
like I don't know about this guy and the current guy in the White House but the opposite isn't much
better either right like it's the most whitewashed. That was a little controversial for a theme park
that that material I feel like it would have to be the non-political he would have to be like uh
like he would have to be the Simpson's congress joke like those those kooky guys those clowns in
congress on then everyone would clap and that would be it yeah uh what's the uh the congress oh it like
well I thought the civil war was bad but uh I'd trade it in in a second to not have to sit through
a capital steps performance and then there would be like and it's a small it would be some of the
same jokes from that improv disney show and pleasure island and you'd be like uh you know
it's not as annoying as it's a small world after all that'll make anyone gush red hydraulic fluid
up their neck when I see those little dolls in the animatronic lounge I get I get mad creeped out
what else what else is going on hold on let me check my composition book I mean this would be
the hit of the park quilled any other ideas lately oh here's one
oh well there we go that's that's a fix yeah you know live puppeting um hey and we I think we all
just clearly proved we could be the puppeteers if they suddenly need three guys to do perfect
Lincoln impressions yeah yeah and then if if that or if you if maybe they want to bring back
binaural sound obviously we're also very good at that yeah so we can and we'll we'll do it live
and we'll do the one here with one hand and scissor with another and like here
maybe that's like an enhanced experience at gibson girl
we have ice cream with jason jordan i'm in yeah uh you get to hear the sound of the scoop
and then like you're whispering into their ear like isn't that rocky road good
isn't this a sweet treat check out the seasonal flavor ooze pamoni a favorite of mine
uh folks you survived podcast the ride thanks for listening i don't think we could sustain doing
the entire wrap up in asmr i'm already drifting louder check us out on twitter and instagram at
podcast the ride join our facebook group email us a podcast the ride at gmail.com and rate and
review us on itunes and get your haircut hey and make sure you get your haircut happy fourth of
july i'll be fourth America spread your golden wind you