Warning, today's episode does not feature me, Scott Gardner.
Much like an experimental eight passenger DeLorean, the podcast has been hijacked by
a devil may care stowaway named Jeff Garland.
As I am trapped like a rat in my own office, I cannot guarantee the podcast will stay strictly
on the very important topic, defunct Eastern Airlines branded ride, If You Had Wings.
Mike, Jason, Jeff Garland, the fate of the podcast is in your hands.
This is If You Had Wings on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three childless men in their
30s, one of which was recently reprimanded by a Disneyland cast member for running in
the park.
I'm of course talking about myself, my name is Mike Carlson, I'm 34 years old.
Joining me is always Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
When did that happen?
That happened two weeks ago and it was at the end of the park and I was trying to make
it to Big Thunder Mountain, it was 1157 right before the park closes and if you get in line
before 12, they let you ride.
So my girlfriend and I sprinted from Indiana Jones and they were like, sir, don't run in
the park.
You can't do that.
You're an adult man.
Did you stop or did you keep running?
I slowed down a bit, but I didn't.
Did you make it?
Oh yeah, we made it.
All right, then you're good.
Yeah, 59.
This voice joining us, a very special guest today.
This man has many credits, but for the purposes of this podcast, the only one we care about
is Buttercup, the voice on the Toy Story Midway Mania Ride.
Oh yes, because you're in the park.
It's not about Disney.
Yeah, we don't even talk about the park.
It's about the movies, yeah.
Right, so because otherwise you would add other Pixar shit.
And I was also in the Computer War tennis shoes, the remake.
Oh wow.
Kirk Cameron.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow, I didn't know that.
How was that?
Fun.
Okay.
Yeah, that's good.
I've done lots of weird stuff.
Yeah, you're in Wall-E, of course.
You're the captain in Wall-E, which is a crazy good movie.
Yeah, that's, well, that's, I would actually, I don't often say stuff like this.
That's a great movie.
Yes.
Oh yeah, agreed.
So is Toy Story 3.
Toy Story 3 is, yeah.
He is great too.
I'm happy to call things good and I'm happy to say when things stink.
Sure.
You know, I'm lucky enough to be in a few great things.
Yeah.
Lucky is the word.
Sure.
I looked right before we did this, I looked at YouTube and I found your dialogue from
the ride.
Do you remember?
Oh, from the Toy Story 3?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you remember this?
Was it part of another recording session?
No, it was all, it was strictly for the ride that I went to.
I went to a place where they had, when I recorded this, I saw the Cars Land, like they had it
on a table.
Wow.
In a big room, a giant room.
They had the whole, the mountain and you know, all that stuff.
Sure.
That wasn't built yet and they were showing me all that.
So I was at like some place where they do ride recording and show you.
Was it possibly in Glendale, California?
It was in Glendale, yeah.
That's what Imagineering is.
Imagineering, it was at Disney Imagineering.
That's where I went.
I went there with our co-host Scott who couldn't make it today.
But we went there because an Imagineer invited us and she was horrified by how nerdy we were.
She works there and she'd be like, well, you guys don't want to see this room full of pictures
of Imagineers.
And we're like, oh, well that's Imagineer Bob Gurr on the wall there and over there's Tony
Baxter and she just had this like look on her face.
While we were at the campus though, it was clear that she had to go back to work and
Jason wanted to go get a sandwich from the commissary.
I really wanted to get a commissary sandwich.
He can't do what's going to take forever and he's like, she's got time.
And we were waiting.
She did have time.
She was in line for Starbucks and I was in line for a sandwich.
We had like an hour and we spent most of the time in the gift shop because that's the only
thing they let you see because you can buy the special merchandise that's only available
to Imagineering.
So we were let loose in that gift shop and we spent like 45 minutes in there.
Was there a lot of good stuff?
There was a lot of good stuff.
Was there anything that I would want in that gift shop?
I'm trying to think.
You're Mr. Haunted Mansion.
Well yeah, I'm Haunted Mansion but what I generally do is I buy things then give them
away.
I'm sure there was like-
You've learned that from me because you've-
I've gotten, yes.
Yeah, you've got on the table there is a Beatles Hot Wheel that I'm giving you.
Yes.
Brand new in the package.
Yes, and when we went to the park, which we'll talk about in a second, you got a lot of Haunted
Mansion stuff and you just gave me the shirt.
You bought a Haunted Mansion shirt.
Shirt.
I gave it to you.
I gave you something else too, didn't I?
I think, well, I think you were giving away a lot of stuff.
I'm not sure.
But I bought you stuff then too, right?
Did I buy you something from there?
I don't think I, nothing specific that I requested.
Okay.
I thought I did.
But you did offer that which was insanely nice which-
Okay.
I'm a generous young lady.
A very generous young lady.
Yeah.
Of America's top ten generous young ladies.
That was just voted recently by Granddaughter Magazine.
It's a great publication.
Yeah.
I suggest everyone read it.
Subscribe.
They need your subscription.
Yeah, yeah.
That's where the real money is for magazines.
For who?
For which magazines?
For any magazine.
For any magazine specific.
Granddaughter Magazine.
That's what I'm saying.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
Come on, Jason.
Yeah.
Yeah, so-
Jason, you write for Granddaughter Magazine.
I'm surprised that you-
I'm a stringer.
I haven't earned my, I haven't made my dues yet.
I haven't earned my chops yet to get them all in staff.
A staff of where?
Granddaughter Magazine.
It's never not funny and it's never not gonna be funny.
If you're listening now and you don't think Granddaughter Magazine's funny, I'm gonna
stop listening.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah.
Get out of here if you don't.
Get out.
Because that's gonna come up a lot today.
It might.
It's a funny phrase.
Do you imagine it being a publication for granddaughters or made by granddaughters?
That's what I would like to know.
Both.
Okay, vote.
Yeah.
There's a lot of granddaughter pride and the last page is always a different message
to, it's called Message to a Granddaughter and it's written by a grandmother.
Oh, okay.
That's the back page.
Again, you should know that, Jason.
You worked there.
You were in the commissary in the gift shop every time I come by.
I was thinking about the older publication where the last page is always Stephen King
writing about something he likes.
Yeah, Stephen King loved the, he wrote great granddaughter stories better than anybody.
And by the way, I am saying specifically great granddaughter stories.
Not great as in how good they are.
He wrote great granddaughter stories, but better than anybody.
By the way, his great granddaughter stories were possibly great.
Yeah, I think they were.
He wrote great, great granddaughter stories, but he never wrote any stories about a great,
great granddaughter.
Yeah.
I mean that, but he still has time.
Yeah, he's got lots of time.
I think that that's, look, if the fans demand it, I think he'll do it.
Write great, great granddaughter stories for granddaughter magazine.
I mean it's, yeah, come on.
Come on, Jason.
I know you have listeners right now that I'm already irritating and they hate me and they're
thinking why did they have them on the show?
I love that.
No, they're not thinking that.
Okay.
But actually if they're listening to your show, I think they probably find that stuff
funny.
Yeah, I think so.
You know, it's podcasts are not, you know, you make a choice to listen to a podcast.
Oh yeah.
And it's just, I mean most podcasts are exclusively tangents.
Yeah.
So around your, so this is what you say.
Do you remember saying this?
You say, I think, knock down the animals.
And then you say, nicely done.
Then you say, hurry, you're running out of time.
Then you count down in this, in like simultaneously with Ham and Rex, which is Wallace Shawn and
John Ratzenberger.
And then you say, I think great way to play.
And then that's it.
Okay.
I probably recorded 75 more lines.
Those are the ones that you...
Because I remember I was there at least for probably an hour, you know, recording.
And it wasn't like, do it with more, like I got it like first or second time.
It's my voice.
The intent is pretty obvious.
So I recorded a lot of stuff, I'm sure.
Did they let you ad lib?
Do you remember?
No, there was, it's a ride.
I don't know how much they're not going to, it's not like a movie where they'll change
the ride based on what Jeff said is so funny.
All right, everyone get in the airplane.
Like, hey, good shooting.
You ought to write for granddaughter magazine.
Well, you can't give them that gold, you know, they're not going to pay you for reuse rights
on granddaughter magazine.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
So it was just pretty standard.
But when you first, were you moved when you saw the ride?
How like when you were, when you wrote, you've written it, right?
You've played the game.
I've written it many times.
I did.
It was closed when we were there.
It was closed when we were there?
Yeah.
Mike and I went to Disneyland, what about two months ago?
About two months ago, yeah.
Yeah, it was awesome.
It was amazing.
And what was great for me was watching you with our guide, who knew more.
I feel you knew more, but he knew a ton.
He knew a ton.
He was so impressed with you.
That's the truth.
He's like, I can't believe this.
He kept saying to me.
He couldn't.
Nobody ever, people claim to know.
He knows, you know.
I said, I think it was early we were waiting for Soren and I said something about Tony
Baxter, who's like one of the big Imagineer guys.
And he was like, oh, I know.
Now I could, he could see it in my eyes.
But also how about going up to Walt Disney's, uh, well above the fire stage.
You want to save that for later?
Well, no, we've, we've, we may as well talk about it now.
So you guys went down.
So we, we went down and, and, um, because of, because I'm on an ABC show, because I
work for Pixar, I get a guide to really nice.
It's a better than a nice perk.
It's an amazing perk.
So I walk around the park and I've never had a guide that was less than wonderful.
Yeah.
I mean, they're always so smart, so kind, so thoughtful.
They're nice to whoever I bring.
But Mike, I had promised I was going to take him.
We had talked about it for a while and it was just he and I, no one else.
But for me, it was him and the guide and I was tagging along because I didn't care about
most of the information, but I got such great joy from their excitement at the information
because you gave that guy information too.
Both of you were like, it was like they're a building on one another.
It was amazing.
It was like my first day of granddaughter.
Of magical time.
That was great.
This was a plaid too.
This is a full, they call it plaids.
So a guide basically like you can get, anybody can get a guide.
It's just, it's an indulgence and I've never done it before.
And a nice young man or lady walks around the park and get you basically on the rides.
You get on the ride quick, you get a reservation.
I treated him to lunch because I wanted to watch the two of you talk more.
Sure.
You know, it was nothing short of a delightful day.
It was wonderful.
And he like, he gets on a phone too.
This is fascinating to me is that he'll say like, if there's something you want to do,
he'll call ahead and he has to negotiate with people.
Yeah, with his bosses and stuff.
So he's like your consigliere or he's like Robert Duvall and the godfather.
Can Jeff do this?
And we ended up making our way above the fire station.
So early on.
And seeing Walt's apartment.
Yeah.
Early on I said like, okay, here's the deal.
I've been here a lot, but if there's anything I've never done, I'm talking about the Matterhorn
basketball court.
I'm talking about Walt's apartment.
If any of that stuff is possible, let us know.
You got as close as anyone could get to the Matterhorn because you got lots of information.
You got people who had been on it.
Everybody was open, which they normally wouldn't be in talking about it.
Yes.
We went up to the Matterhorn.
It was for some reason down when we walked.
And I walked, you told me you were like, go up and ask to see the basketball court to
the employees.
And I go, hey, can I come up and see the basketball court?
And they're like, no, really only people who work on it can see it.
Because Jack, our guide, hadn't seen it either.
Yeah.
But apparently only something that people work.
It's not super easy to get to.
Yes.
And it's like a rare, it's a rare treat.
And I think it's also like not a real basketball court.
It's just like a little half court.
But the thing is Walt's apartment is so much better than that.
Oh yeah.
So he told us like in the middle of the day, he's like, can we, was it okay if we go at
the end of the day?
And we're like, of course.
Yeah, we had no, that's also by the exit.
So it's a perfect thing to do at the end of the day.
It was a perfect close.
And he, I remember he, he was like, all right.
And he's like, I feel like he whispered it too, like it was something we were, cause
he was like, it's not usually for guides.
It's usually for like a historical tour.
He goes, but go wait over by the fire station.
Yeah.
And I'm going to go get the keys.
And we were like, Ooh, like I felt like glee, like pure glee.
So we went over there and you go just exit out by the fire station.
You walk up the stairs into this tiny apartment.
In the back of the fire station.
Yes, in the back of the fire station.
And then you go into this old, well-preserved apartment.
It looks like an apartment from like the thirties.
Yes.
It's not the thirties.
It looks like the thirties.
Yes.
It's very old and it feels, it feels ghostly in there, but I think it's because all the
decorum is still.
No, it feels ghostly.
It does.
It feels, that's a great way to describe it because it's got that old time phonograph.
Yes.
And then where the dishes are in the sink and then the shower.
Like we saw the whole place.
It's very tiny.
It's so small.
It was much smaller than I thought it would be.
It's really extraordinarily small.
Like it's tiny.
It's like, I think it's small.
Like my first like shitty studio apartment in LA, I think it's smaller than that.
Right.
It's a small studio apartment.
Which yours also was covered in like phonographs and like lace doilies.
No, that's your apartment.
By the way, there are lace doilies.
It's like that.
Yes, of course.
It's really that, it's what you imagine it to be.
But then there were pictures and then they, like Walt and his family hang out here.
All the children, grandchildren too, if I'm not mistaken.
Perhaps grandchildren.
They were there.
Like there's a lot of people in a very small room.
Yeah.
And they had, he told us that Walt and his wife, Lillian, had separate beds.
They just had two couches.
Like there's no room in beds.
They would just pull out couches.
But not only would they pull out couches, but they were on opposite sides of the room.
Like I Love Lucy or something.
No, it was different.
Lucy and Desi were next to each other.
Their beds were pretty close.
These were far.
But that's the way it had to be set up.
It's like you couldn't have done one.
And I know they crawled into each other's beds and made love all night long.
Walt loved that.
Yeah, of course.
Walt reminded him of when he, he started Granddaughter Magazine and it reminded him of the early
days where he slept in the office.
But then he lost the rights to Granddaughter Magazine.
Yep.
When he used, no, he sold Granddaughter Magazine to help play Pay for Disneyland.
Oh, right.
That's right.
You always forget that.
And Roy told him not to, but...
Roy stayed on.
Roy was always the sensible one.
Roy stayed on at Granddaughter for a lot longer than people know.
Yeah.
Crazy, he was able to hold down two jobs.
I know, it was amazing.
Walt Disney and Granddaughter Magazine.
Roy was always the unsung hero of the Disney story.
I met Roy.
Did you?
Yeah.
The young Roy, obviously, not the older.
There's two, because Roy E. Disney was the younger one, right?
Wait, I met a very old man named Roy.
I think that's probably Roy's son.
Because Roy was Walt's brother who was older.
Older than Walt.
Roy's son, yes.
Yeah, Roy's son, Roy E.
He was involved with the company.
Yeah, I met him at something, a couple things.
Sure.
I've been involved with Disney for a long time.
I was on the very first, when ABC became part of Disney, I did a pilot for Disney that was
the very first show that they ever did, that Disney, ABC ever did.
Wow.
It didn't get picked up.
It was a mid-30s version of, it was like an old, actually late 30s version of Friends.
I'm not making this up.
Really?
It was like an older group of Friends, the same sort of thing.
And you were regular on it?
Yeah.
Wow.
What was it called?
It was just a pilot.
It didn't get picked up.
Grandma, granddaughter magazine.
No, I really don't remember what it was called.
I don't remember much of it.
Any other, do you remember any other cast members?
Chip and Dale?
No, I really don't remember.
I don't.
Wow.
We're going to look into this.
We're going to see if this is available maybe.
Yeah.
See if it's somewhere.
It's got to be somewhere.
James Burroughs directed it.
I remember.
That's usually a good luck charm.
I know you'd think.
Yeah.
So for this Disneyland trip, we were talking, like Jack and I were being very, I didn't
feel like we were trying to outdo each other in knowledge.
His name's Jack, right?
Yeah, Jack.
Yeah, he's such a good guy.
And he-
No, you weren't trying to out, you were just- excuse me.
Use the term.
You were getting off on how each of you-
You know what I mean though?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You both loved how each of you knew and you would get more and more excited.
And it wasn't even like you were testing each other.
You were like, do you know about this?
And like, of course you know about it.
And then when you guys didn't know something that the other one said, you got so blown
away.
But not in a, ha ha, I got you.
But in a, wow, how about that information?
Yeah.
It was delightful.
Thank you.
I do- you said at one point that this was your second favorite Disneyland day ever.
Yes.
Do you remember?
Yes, it was my second favorite of all time.
And do you remember what your first was?
You told me a little bit about it.
Yes, correct.
It was, it was not grad night.
I had a great grad night.
It was Disney World.
By the way, that was my second favorite Disney.
That was probably my favorite Disneyland trip, to be honest.
Disney World, I had a better trip when I was like, I'll say 15.
I went with a group of kids, like on a youth trip from my temple or something.
And I remember having the best time because I was not following directions.
Right.
You felt like you could like go wild a little bit at the park.
I went wild.
I went wild and I had a great time.
It was the most fun I'd ever had at the park.
You were number two.
Well, that's pretty good.
Pretty good.
So think about it.
I was 55.
I'm 56 now.
I've had a birthday since then.
Happy birthday.
55 and 15.
So my favorite trip was 15, second favorite 55.
And in between, I'd say I've been to the park at least a dozen times, if not more, which
I know for a lot of people who have the passes, that's not a big deal.
But for normal people, I mean, I'd probably, I bet you even more than that.
I mean, since I lived in LA, I go at least once a year.
I'm planning on going again in July, actually.
I love it there.
See, that's the thing too.
I love it.
The only thing that gets a little bit weird for me is I don't go on the scary rides.
So I'll sit there and when I sit there, if I say anything or I get recognized by one
person, it sort of opens up a thing of like a lot of people.
But look, I'm honored to be recognized and honored to talk to the people.
But it can be unsettling at times.
It's like a line forms.
Sometimes, yes.
Yeah.
It's weird.
Yes.
Well, no, it's like I said, Chip and Dale.
It's like I'm one of the characters.
Here, come take a photo.
And I just take photos with people over and over and over again.
Yeah.
You would wait for me a lot of times.
It was tough.
Thank God when my kids were little, really little, and I took them to Disneyland.
I didn't have to deal with that.
But as they got older, I remember the last time was kind of a drag.
Did the kids, did you guys go often?
Also, would you bring the kids?
The kids love it as much as every kid?
Oh my God, my kids love Disneyland.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Yeah, of course.
We went, I went and I've stayed overnight before.
No, I love Disneyland.
And there, by the way, as you guys know, there are people out there who don't like it.
And I'm like, what's wrong with you?
And they think I'm nuts.
Like I think my record for going in a year is twice, which is plenty for someone who
doesn't have an annual pass.
You know what I mean?
Right.
But I love it.
Oh my God.
And that doesn't even include the number of times I've been to downtown Disney.
Oh yeah.
In addition to being at Disneyland.
Do you have a favorite downtown Disney spot?
I've never been to Epcot, by the way.
Really?
And it was even built when I lived in Florida as a kid.
Never went to Epcot once.
Oh, that's a, that's a tragedy.
Yeah.
I guess.
Epcot's like my favorite place.
Yeah.
It's fallen apart a little bit in the recent years.
But yeah, my granddaughter works there.
She works at the pumpkin house.
Yeah.
The pumpkin house, one of the best places in the world showcase.
Oh my God.
And by the way, it's pumpkin H A U S.
Yeah.
Cause it's in the German.
It's in the German.
Is that your drink or my drink?
This is my drink.
Oh, I don't know what I did.
Did you not have a drink?
No, I did.
I don't know what I did with it.
Sorry.
We can pause and you can go get it.
No, I want to stay here.
All right.
We'll stay here.
I don't want to break the flow.
There was a, we were, we were talking when we were at that Disneyland, I remember oftentimes
I would give Jack my opinions about things and I would kind of like foster him.
I feel like he would get like, he couldn't, couldn't, like I would say, Hey, I heard a
rumor or I would say, Hey, I don't care.
Right.
Cause you can't say you heard from him.
Of course not.
He, no, he didn't give me any rumors.
But he also would be like, well, I can't deny that.
Right.
I don't have to deny that, you know, he was delightful.
He was wonderful.
And he was very respectful.
Here's what I love about it.
And I love about you with it.
You both are very respectful of the park and the history and where it's going, where it's
been and he cares.
He cares passionately about his job.
I love that.
We yeah, he, well, we, we all the, all of us on the podcast, we don't like it when a
guest comes on and tells us they ever like got really like fucked up and went there.
Oh, I hate that.
We feel that's disrespectful to the park.
It's so disrespectful.
That's a six flags type of thing.
I don't drink, you know, and I love the park.
So I mean, I could see pot enhancing my trip, but it's not something that I mean, to me
going to Disneyland in itself is like getting high.
Yes.
I get very happy.
Yeah.
And what is it?
The happiest place on earth.
Of course.
Yes.
And also a second most fun place to granddaughter magazine.
Oh, that.
I'm sorry.
That wasn't funny, but we'll bring it back.
No, we won't.
Uh, the granddaughter magazine adheres to the classic comedy rule of a rule of a three
hundreds, right?
We went on, uh, we went on Haunted Mansion and that was the one I think that you were
particularly like, we went by ourselves.
You went by yourself.
I was in a car with Jack.
You would let me travel with just Jack and I, by the way, that is the truth.
And I'll post a picture.
And the things you wrote with Jack, our guide, and I wrote by myself.
Yes.
But when we went in the Haunted Mansion, we did the whole elevator thing alone.
We did all that alone.
So three, so yeah, imagine just three of us in the, he said, wow.
Yeah, it was really good.
It was three of us just empty in that elevator, which is really cool.
Which is really cool.
Yeah.
And, uh, I think that the guy who operated that room was quite uncomfortable.
Really?
Not, not without a crowd and me looking directly at him.
I think you were yelling a lot too.
I was.
You were like, why is this happening?
I think you were like, why is this happening?
Like the bodies would stretch.
See, that's I'm fine with if you guys are in there alone.
Oh, it's hilarious.
Yes, of course.
I would never ruin it for other people.
Oh my God, no.
But it just is so joyous.
See that's the thing.
They say the happiest place on earth.
And by the way, sometimes when small kids have their, they get burnt out and their breakdowns
or you have problems with your girlfriend, it's not always the happiest place on earth.
But I got to tell you, it does its part for joy.
But sometimes it's hot.
And if you have to wait in the lines, which I don't have to do anymore, but it, I could
see it not being the happiest place.
And I can see a lot of people going, you know, thinking of their breakup at Disney.
I bet you Disneyland at this point has hosted so many breakups.
Oh yeah, for sure.
My God.
Yeah.
And there's not that many people go through these places.
There's going to be all sorts of stuff that happens.
I'm sure plenty of people got engaged there.
Of course.
Plenty of people.
I don't think about people having sex at Disneyland.
Oh yeah.
I find it inappropriate, but I just, I just, it's natural, but I don't know how natural
it is for a theme park.
They had a-
Are you talking about at the hotels or in the park?
One of the hotels is fine.
Yeah, well the hotels are-
Yeah.
You know.
But they had, before the Matterhorn, I think I said this to Jack and he knew what I was
talking about.
Before the Matterhorn, there was a, it was just a hill of dirt and they called it holiday
hill.
Oh right.
You told me that.
And that's where teens used to make out.
It's a neck.
They used to neck.
Go a neck.
Yeah.
So like that was already, that-
I just love the idea of teens.
Yeah, teens congregating.
Teens.
Just that word so inapplicable to the miscreants that are, are, are 14 to 19 year olds that
exist.
I don't think of them as sweet teens.
I think of them as major annoyances.
Teens does represent, I feel like teens does like is an annoying word that really represents-
Well teens reminds me of old days.
Oh it does.
Okay.
I don't look at like those, like who would ever say it was a group of teens.
It was a group of kids.
It was a group of-
Yeah.
They were, they were spitting on me.
I don't know.
I bet you that's happened at Disneyland.
I mean I think we've talked before how we are scared of teens.
By the way, that's also the thing too.
It's so unnatural that I find them scary.
Yeah.
But that's just like a built in thing from your childhood.
If there's like a group of five or more teens, I'm petrified.
They might rag on me.
I'm petrified of one teen.
But by the way, it's nice if they, you know, if they, if they know who I am because they're
kinder.
Sure.
Yeah.
If they don't know who I am, I'm just an old annoying guy.
The last thing I think I can remember from the trip off the top of my head is we were
on Soarin', which is one of your favorites.
Oh, I love Soarin'.
And I got the candle.
Yes.
And you, we got, yeah, we, we tried or you ordered, there's this like company that makes
third, they're not licensed candles.
Yeah.
But they're unlicensed candle.
By the way, it was burning all day.
Do you smell it?
Is it smelling here like the Haunted Mansion at all?
A little bit.
Yeah.
There's a Haunted Mansion candle and it's like, they don't have the exact scent, but it's
very reminiscent of it.
And it's very-
Very much so.
It gets you in the nostalgic Haunted Mansion mood.
But we were on Soarin' and you, I think you were talking to Jack or something.
I heard you like kind of whispering to Jack, like, this is great or something.
And then Tinkerbell came on the screen and you went, what?
It broke the world for you.
Because Soarin', you don't associate with Tinkerbell.
Right.
Soarin' is like, I used to love when it was Soarin' just over California.
Now it's the world.
Yeah.
And I don't like it as much.
Right.
I used to, I really, it was, I loved the California thing.
Although it's really good still.
It's great.
I'll still go on it.
Right.
But that being said, Tinkerbell, not necessary.
I mean, I really am pro Tinkerbell in any Peter Pan situation or in an animated situation.
But she sort of jumped out and it's good.
Well, she is on the California version too.
She was on the other version as well, but you must have forgot.
I must have forgot.
I wiped it away.
Yeah.
But I'm pro Tinkerbell.
Sure.
Although she, I do find her one of the more annoying characters.
Uh-huh.
I'm pro Sparkles.
Um, I was, before we talk, so we're going to talk about, sorry, what you got?
Well, I was going to say, uh, uh, Jeff came into play with a trip you and I took down
to the parks too.
Which, what are you talking about?
We went down a few weeks ago.
So we were at the parks one day and, uh-
Were you with him when he bought the butter cup?
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, uh, Mike, we were in a gift shop and we were looking around and he's like, oh,
look, there's butter cup.
There's a, one of Jeff's character, it took a picture and sent it to you and, uh, you
texted back, buy all of them.
Yes.
Yeah.
Um-
I'm already, I've given away half of them.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Why not?
Oh, I'm not getting them for profit.
No, I give them-
You're not sleeping in a pile of butter cups.
No, but I bought it and I, yeah.
Yeah.
So we still had a lot of hours left in the day.
So Mike went over to the one stand to-
Yeah, in Tomorrowland.
Yeah, to, well, you, in California Adventure, you went over and asked-
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Where you could find it.
And I was just sitting on a bench eating a corn dog and I was just watching you talking
to this person for-
Well, you love, but while this was going on, you were eating what you talk about as one
of your favorite seasonal treats at Disneyland, which is a corn dog-
Oh, this was great.
Yeah.
That you're hoping they make permanent.
It's like a triple, it's like a mini, like, Cajun dog and then, like, Pepper Jack cheese
above that and then a Hot Link corn dog above that.
So it's really good for you.
Yeah, it's really good for you.
I was checking to see to make sure they had them over in Tomorrowland and this one, a
very nice woman was checked for me and she said, yes, they did.
So we went to, so I was like, well, right before the park closes, I'm going to get all
these-
Right, you don't want to be walking around with them.
Right.
So I-
I told you not to.
Yeah, you said not to.
Yeah, I said, if you got to carry them around, do not buy them.
That image of you did not bring me joy.
Yeah.
And I was saying-
If I hated you, yes.
It brought me joy.
Sure.
So we got in, so I was like, you know what, I better buy them before 12 and it was like
11.55 and so I went in, I got all the Buttercups and then, as I said on the start of the podcast,
if you get in line before midnight when it closes, you can get on one more ride.
So we went on Space Mountain.
So I had the big-
With all the Buttercups.
With the big bag of Buttercups.
And I asked an employee, I go, could you like hold it to the side for a second?
They were like, yeah, you can keep it on the ride.
So I brought, I rode Space Mountain with a bag of 12 or more Buttercup dolls.
Oh, wow.
Just sort of on my lap.
I need more next time you go.
Sure.
Well, I'm going to go soon too.
Yeah.
I can tell you where.
That'll be like for them.
They won't even know who I am.
But imagine, I wonder how many times people who are the animated character buy the-
Buy it.
You know what I can't find where they really didn't market is the Captain from WALL-E,
like those dolls or things.
I got a few things and I can always find them on like Amazon or eBay, but it was not something
that, you know-
I guess-
Kids love unicorns.
Yeah.
So that's an obvious choice.
More than how popular the character is.
Yeah.
Before we start, so we're going to talk your favorite ride of all time if you had wings.
Yes.
But real quick, would you mind, you told the story on Conan about Disneyland and it involves
your son.
Oh, that one.
Oh, geez.
I mean, we can cut-
You know one needs to hear that.
All right, fine.
We'll cut this part out then.
No, no.
You can leave that in.
It's just, it's not for this.
Okay.
All right.
Check out the Team Coco website to hear this story.
I don't even know if it was on when it was still Team Coco.
I think it was like as old, I told it on NBC maybe or-
It's two years ago.
Two years ago?
Oh, then it was Team Coco.
Okay.
Well, look, we're going to talk-
It's more appropriate for Conan.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
Our listeners are a little more sensitive.
Well, no, I imagine they want to hear about the rides and stuff.
I don't want to ruin things for them.
That would ruin things.
Seriously though.
Maybe, maybe.
Yeah.
You know, you talk about the Haunted Mansion and it's very common people try to sneak scattering
ashes.
Oh, well, that's disgusting.
Yeah.
I've heard a lot of those stories where people do like gross stuff.
Well, my thing was to do it on Pirates of the Caribbean, but the line was too long.
Right.
Yeah.
And I think it's a different thing entirely, but we won't talk about that.
Let's get to the topic though.
If you had wings-
If you had wings.
Which is a ride that hasn't been around for, God, 30 years, 20 years probably.
Was it ever in Disneyland?
It was only Disney World.
Only Disney World.
Right.
Yeah.
And it was sponsored by Eastern Airlines.
Eastern Airlines, yes indeed.
It was the first ever sponsor of Disney in general.
And the big deal about it was, besides being fun, free.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Before, when the ticket, when their ticket books were going on.
Carousel of Progress-
Was either A or an E ticket.
It was like one of the tickets free.
Right.
Yeah.
Carousel of Progress and if you had wings because they were such heavily corporate, corporate
sponsorship-
Yeah.
Was General Electric Carousel of Progress?
They still would have been doing it at the time.
Yeah.
Carousel of Progress was pretty great too.
And that-
You sit there and see the family and-
Yeah.
It was really cool.
Right.
That was a cool thing but it wasn't as good as if you had wings.
Which, so what was your first trip?
What was the first time you remember going?
What you remember probably going on it?
I remember going to Disneyland for the first time, geez, it must have been 10 years old.
Yeah.
I mean the park open when?
70?
71.
Yeah.
I went to the park in 72?
Mm-hmm.
73?
Yeah.
I lived in Chicago and my grandparents lived in South Florida and I remember we visited
them in South Florida and then we took a bus from South Florida to Orlando, stayed at
like a Holiday Inn type place in Orlando.
Right.
And then went a couple days to Disney World.
Yeah.
That was the first of many Disney World experiences.
Right.
Yeah, when I talk to my mom about her memories going when she was a child, she has a very
similar like if you had wings of like memory of like, because it was like free, you just
rode it over and over and over again and it was her favorite.
Yeah, you'd go back in line.
Yeah.
So for people who didn't go on it or don't know what we're talking about, this was an
OmniMover which is like Haunted Mansion.
The Haunted Mansion ride system.
Yeah.
Which is the vehicles on the Haunted Mansion.
Right.
How do you say ride system?
So very similar.
Very similar to Adventures in Inner Space which was just out here.
Yeah.
In a Hine.
And it's not this similar to Soarin'.
Uh-huh.
Where you would kind of go in and it's like you're waiting.
Yeah, you travel around the world.
You travel where United Airlines goes.
Right.
Yeah.
Where Eastern Airlines goes.
I mean Eastern Airlines, yeah.
It was a travel where Eastern Airlines goes and they kept that song the whole time.
If you had wings, if you had wings, which is really not a great premise.
No, it's a very simple song.
I mean, which allows them to like tweak it a little as you go through the different locations.
And I remember it got very exciting, they had bongos at one time and like they would
add different sounds, musical sounds from around the world.
Yes, depending on where you went.
And then if you, there was two moments that stood out for me.
I realized why I love the ride.
Yes, go ahead.
Okay.
So, it was generally hot out, especially in Florida.
Of course.
And I realized why I love the ride.
I didn't care if it was free, we had tickets to all the rides.
Sure.
Because my dad would let us go on and over and over because it didn't cost anything to
have the ticket.
Right.
But there was a little section where it was watery.
I don't remember what it was, but they would like a light spray in there.
A mist.
Oh yeah.
Not only that, but there was a breeze.
Like there's this one part where you went through where the wind blew and it was air
conditioned wind.
Sure.
And I realized that's why I really love the ride.
That's why a lot of people seem to like it.
Yeah, it was so good.
It was so refreshing.
Right.
But you didn't even know it at the time.
You just felt like this was doing something to me magically.
Yes.
And it also gave you the sense that you were going faster than you were.
They figured that out back then.
Right.
And then yeah, there weren't any robots on the ride.
It was all projection.
And then they had the pirates, like right before you got off at the end of the ride,
they had the pirates come out and pretend to attack you.
That was like the thing that I think everybody loved.
That didn't happen.
What?
Sure.
Were there pirates?
There are pirates.
They come out with like their plastic swords and they just miss your hat with their sword.
Then they fight each other and they did that for a while until one of them was actually
killed.
That would have cost a fortune.
It actually happened.
Well, there was an expose.
Where was it?
Where was it published?
I don't know.
I don't know where it was.
I'm trying to remember.
Do you guys remember?
I think it was run in Granddaughter Magazine.
Right, Granddaughter Magazine.
But it was a Stephen Glass article.
So then they had to retract it when they revealed it was a fabulous.
Stephen Glass wrote for Granddaughter Magazine before, was it The New Yorker?
The New Republic?
New Republic, yeah.
Anyhow, no, that didn't happen at the end of the ride.
But what did happen is there were Eastern Airlines representatives there waiting to
sell you a ticket if you were interested.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Oh, because I was little.
I didn't notice that.
Right.
But they were, yeah.
My dad probably said to me, keep walking.
I guarantee it's what my dad said.
Keep walking.
We don't need any of that.
Do you remember who the ending narration of the ride?
I believe it was Jeffrey, you know, the guy from Live and Let Die.
What's his name?
The Uncola.
Am I wrong?
Even a bigger name.
Oh, I don't know.
For a little while.
It was Orson Welles.
Was he the end of If You Had Wings?
He was the one who said, like, you do have wings.
You can do all these things.
You can wide in your world.
Eastern, the wings of man.
Boy, that guy made a living from voiceover at a certain point.
One of the greatest actors who ever lived, one of the greatest filmmakers who ever lived.
And for a while he was telling you that I did have wings and that I could get a what
was the wine that he did?
Oh, yes.
No wine before its time.
The one that's the one with the.
Paul Mason.
Yeah, that's the one with the outtakes.
And there's a famous outtakes.
Yeah.
Well, there's the If You Had Wings outtakes.
You've heard those though.
Of course.
Yeah.
He curses up a storm.
Well, no, it's not him.
It's not him.
Oh, it's.
No, it's Dean Jones.
Oh.
Yelling at Walt in that little room saying.
In the apartment.
Why were they recording there?
Why did you give the job to Orson Welles?
It was a big fight.
Yeah.
No, I'll never forget listening to those.
Jack let us listen to those.
But the weird thing is we had to take off our clothes and sit Indian style on the ground.
Yeah.
And then he put them on and then we got he's got a cupcake.
But we had to eat these.
He said, you got to eat the cupcakes slowly.
I remember.
Yeah, but it was worth it.
And then we looked out the window and there was a photographer from granddaughter.
But like a telephoto lens, like really trying to scoop them.
I covered myself, but good.
They didn't get anything.
Yeah, they got me pretty good, though.
They did.
Yeah, they got all of me.
They got your wiener.
Yeah, they got my wiener.
And by the way, for a while, it was going to be the first wiener in granddaughter magazine,
but they decided against it.
I use my influence.
Yeah, I really appreciate that.
Yeah.
Because we bought the pictures back.
And then we sold them to Piper to the Caribbean monthly.
Yeah, which I'm proud to be in for my first nude nude spread.
So if you had wings, I do you remember this?
You again, probably didn't notice as a kid.
I feel like a lot of people did it that you could hear the project.
There was like 85 projectors scattered throughout the rise after having been on the ride so
many times over the years, you started noticing the nuances of the delivery of the material.
And I looked around, I could see the projectors because it was all projectors.
There were so many.
It was all images projected onto.
But a lot of times it was projected onto like moving screens.
And then you your your thing would go through the screens, like underneath the screens,
you know, because this is well, we were talking about this change into another I call dream
flight eventually.
Oh, really?
We went on when we were kids.
Oh, OK.
I may have written if you had really I went when I was two, but I don't have any memories
of it.
In my mind, I just kind of messed up.
But in your mind, you should really just go to that you were on if you had wings.
Yeah.
I would do that.
Why not?
I mean, I wish there was better getting ready for this.
Like there is some footage of it, but like VHS or people have like super cameras, like
did not do well in low lighting.
So you can't make out a lot.
I mean, but I have such great memories for of it.
Yeah.
And like you sent me the song I did.
I put it on and danced because it's like a child.
It's like one of your favorite types of music.
No, I just danced.
I just danced.
But you like cha cha.
I just like I get gassy.
Sure.
And then I have to dance.
And that's a great song.
Remember in the middle of you if you guys weren't on if you had wings, but Chippendale
came out and they made they did like they made pottery.
Wow.
The ride stopped dead.
And if you were lucky enough to be by Chippendale, they showed you the pottery.
The rest of the ride, you're just sitting there.
Right.
And the music was, you know, what's going on.
But it's like 15, 20 minutes of nothing.
But some people got a good how to make pottery thing.
It's an Easter egg, I guess.
What did they do with the finished pots?
Well that's been a mystery that Disney's had to deal with for years.
No one knows.
No, not even Jack.
I asked Jack about it, but he didn't know him away.
He didn't know.
Yeah, they're somewhere though.
Yeah.
Former Eastern Airlines executives also didn't know.
No, they know it went deep.
Well you know who did the investigative article that went deep?
Stephen Glass in the New Republic.
Nope.
Try again, Jason.
Was it me and granddaughter magazine?
No, no.
Oh, you did it.
Jason.
No.
Hmm.
Try again, Jason.
Grandson Tri Weekly.
So does that come out every three weeks or three times one week?
Every three weeks.
I like to think it comes out three times a week.
I would like to think that's more what it is.
If you pay the premium, it comes out three times a week.
Yeah, well you have your choice.
Yeah.
It depends on how often you want grandson news.
Right.
There's many grandsons doing big things.
Me, I want as much as I can get.
Yeah.
I think the full count of projectors, there were 41 16 millimeters, 40 special effects
projectors, 370 millimeter projectors and 135 millimeter projector.
But 370 millimeter, I wonder what part of the ride that was.
I think that was for the- The big thing at the end?
What they call the speed room.
Oh, the speed room.
That was the thing that was amazing.
That's what I told you.
You felt like you were on like a scooter, like a car.
It was a car race that you suddenly were in.
Right.
And then they had 15 years, June 1972 to June 1987.
Oh, was it that long?
Yeah.
Wow.
They had a 15 year contract for the Eastern sponsorship and then Eastern opted not to
continue the sponsorship.
So it closed for about like five or six days so they could take out any references to Eastern
and they renamed it If You Could Fly, which pretty similar ride, different song.
Okay song, not as good.
Oh really?
They recorded a new song.
Yeah.
If You Could Fly.
If You, was it like that?
Was it like instead of If You Could Fly?
If You Could Fly.
I actually, let me look it up.
You're not that far off.
That only lasted about two years.
I don't remember that one at all.
You don't have any memories.
Yeah.
So what was the last date of the actual If You Had Wings part?
June 87, like June 2nd I think.
You said that, how long was the sponsorship?
15 years.
Oh, so it was 87.
Yeah.
Okay.
And then If You Could Fly went 87 to 89, the Delta Dream Flight moved in from 89 to 1996
and had like the same thing happen, like they lost the sponsorship in 96.
Was this in Tomorrowland?
Yeah.
This was in Tomorrowland.
It was kind of not churned out quickly, but like they only had like three things.
Was it next to Neihae Stocking Mountain?
No, no, that's on the other side of the park.
Okay, my mistake.
That's the totally wrong land.
Yeah.
That's in Stockingland.
Stockingland by Frontierland.
I never understood Stockingland.
It's next to Frontierland, right?
Yeah, next to Frontierland, Liberty Square.
The transition from Frontierland to Stockingland is the Horseshoe Cafe.
Uh-huh, yes.
The Horseshoe Cafe, because that's a person putting a stocking on over the horseshoe,
when you know you're in Stockingland.
I'm going to stop now.
Let's get back to If You Had Wings.
What did you find over it?
Did you pull- I have all the If You Had Wings lyrics.
Were you paying attention?
These lyrics are a little, I'm amused by them.
I think these are fun.
These lyrics by the great ex-Atencio.
Yes, ex-Atencio who did the Pirates.
He wrote the Pirates song.
Yeah.
Well, Pirates Caribbean song.
Which is a great song.
Great song.
Uncle or great uncle of comedy director Peter Atencio.
Yes, of Key and Peele and many other things.
Keanu.
Keanu, the movie, yep.
So we have all these lyrics here and there's so many different ones.
My favorite one, where is it?
It says, want to buy a sombrero made of real fine straw or how about a nice handbag for
your pretty mama?
That's my favorite line out of all of them.
It's all about like-
Well, that's the one that I experienced.
I was in Mexico and I got a hat and it was made of straw and then I bought my mom a handbag.
That was quite the day.
Your pretty mama.
Yeah, she's very pretty, my mama.
And you said that, I would hope you would ask the man at the store for a gift for your
mama.
Well, I just bought her a gift.
Oh, okay.
So it was no transaction.
I had to buy her a gift.
She was touched though.
She loved her son.
Sure, of course.
I mean, I'm looking through here.
This was the old, we'll put this on the Twitter.
This was the old pamphlet you would get.
With the tickets or with telling you about the park?
That, well, telling you about Eastern Airlines.
Oh, great granddaughter.
How about that?
There was a lot of cross promotion like in airports of like, cause Eastern was the official
airline of Disney World for a long time.
Eastern was a very popular airline.
I remember flying it a lot.
Do you think was that the one you flew the most as a child?
Do you remember?
I would say Eastern Airlines.
Eastern and Delta were the two that I remember flying a lot as a kid.
Did you have an association that it was Disney's airline?
Did that make it fun?
I don't remember.
Sure.
That's okay.
I was excited.
My favorite part was the airport.
Yeah.
Well, flying was better in those days, I've been told.
You don't remember that either?
Cause that's what my parents say.
They say flying was better.
I think my mom.
When you flew first class, it was really first class.
Now first class is just a bigger chair than the other section.
It's not that exciting.
Unless you fly first class to Europe, then it's really delightful.
I think my mom just wanted the women to wear dresses.
I was saying if you could fly the brief two year replacement, yeah, whole new song for
that.
When Delta Dream Flight moved in, that ran from June of 89 to June of 1996.
Similar thing happened, I think I'd say, where they lost the sponsorship and then it became
Disney's take flight.
For that, they just took all the words Delta out of the song.
They just found words they could squeeze in instead of Delta.
What was it called again?
Disney's what?
It was called Dream Flight.
Then when they lost the sponsorship, it became Take Flight.
They would lose the sponsorship and they'd have to change the whole thing of the ride,
which just happens.
Cause there's so many different sponsors here.
Siemens sponsored Space Your Birth for a long time, which is an Epcot Center, which is the
big ball, the golf ball.
Then they pulled it so they have to pull all references to the thing.
That's what happens.
It happens in baseball parks all the time now.
You start calling it one name and it's a new name five years later.
Like Comiskey Park was what I grew up with, but now it's a US cellular field.
Now it's now called Japanese Woman Park.
All the women of Japan sponsor it.
Wow, they all got together and pooled their money?
They did.
Wow.
Is that a profit making venture or a charitable thing?
By the way, you know the Staples Center is now called Granddaughter Magazine Arena.
They have well outpaced Staples.
Their acquisition did not go through.
That makes sense though.
I mean, I think it's, they're going to do a lot of good with it.
I think that they're the type of company that needs to go to the arena.
This will either be your most popular podcast or by far the one that people go, please don't
ever have them on again.
We had an episode that's a little divisive where a fifties gangster hijacked the show.
That might be our most divisive.
Was it one of you playing a character?
It was not, well, not us.
It was a different person.
But there's a ride called the Great Movie Ride and on that ride you get hijacked by
a fifties gangster.
So we had a-
Was there a ride called the Great Movie Ride?
Yes, it was at the MGM Studio in Florida.
Oh, so this is like one of the separate park.
Yeah, it was a separate park in Florida.
Yeah.
They never allowed that in like Disney World or Disneyland.
Well, it was, no, it was Disney World.
It was Disney World's Hollywood Studios and you get hijacked a guy like a college student
would come out and be like, hey, stick them up, give me a Jules or whatever.
You're a liar.
I swear to God.
Somebody thought this was a good idea.
It was a great idea.
It ran for decades.
It was one of our favorite rides.
It just closed.
It was open for 20 years.
Sometimes it would be a cowboy would ride.
Yes, sometimes a cowboy, a person-
You know who got their break on that ride?
The Olsen twins.
Really?
Were they the cowboy and the gangster?
They were the babies.
The babies when they were hands.
Because for one year, Disney did some research and they found out people love babies.
So before they did Full House when they were actual babies, they were the babies on that
ride.
That makes a lot of sense.
I didn't even know that.
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
Yes, I did.
Oh, okay.
Well, he knows he does more research than I do.
And you know, people are mad at Disneyland in Paris.
Yes.
You know what's going on there.
Apparently, every single ride is sponsored by a diabetes drug now.
I didn't know that.
You think that would happen at the American parks.
Nope.
It's in Paris.
Yeah.
And they have, well, you know what?
Now that you say that, I...
They have the Glucophage.
Yeah.
The Glucophage Mountain.
The Glucophage also sponsors, it's a small world.
And they say it's a Glucophage world after all.
After all, I know.
Yeah.
And that's all.
I thought there was something different last time we were there.
Yeah.
They're taking over other rides too and using their other names.
There's Metformin teacups that you spend.
Sure.
Yeah.
And there's also reps for the diabetes medicine that hassle you after the rides.
They're waiting there with Eastern Airlines pamphlets.
They haven't gotten their act together yet.
Wow.
Yeah.
They're giving away money.
Those might fetch some money for collectors.
They're really not...
They don't have it together yet.
That makes a lot of sense.
Yeah.
Do you have anything else or do we want to get to this last segment?
I think that's everything.
I mean, I thought it was interesting when we mentioned this ride to people.
It seems like a real fan favorite.
I told my dad we were doing this episode.
It was truly delightful.
I remember having dreams of the other one.
I mean, this was about where everything, everywhere Eastern would go, but the replacement Dream
Flight was more focused on the history of airline.
Was it the same images?
Oh, okay.
There was some projection.
So they would change the visuals.
They built a bunch of new sets.
Oh, that's my...
Siri just went off.
That's that thing I have in my kitchen again.
A HomePod?
I have a HomePod.
Oh, okay.
By the way, it's not gotten the best reviews.
I'm loving it.
What have you just been playing music with it?
I play music.
I ask questions.
Like I ask...
I say, Siri, Siri, Siri.
Hold on.
Siri, Siri, play the new issue of Granddaughter Magazine.
I think I see why people don't like this product as much.
By the way, I'm talking to it too far.
We're too far away.
It's two rooms over.
Two rooms over.
We just spoke out of nowhere.
I don't even know what it said.
We love Apple.
We don't want to put Apple down.
No, no, but the point being is that I really am enjoying it.
Sure.
And the sound, you heard it the other day.
The sound is great.
Yeah.
So there you go.
Jeff Garland induced.
Induced?
Jeff Garland endorsed HomePod.
I induced Siri to go on a few anyway.
Siri, take me...
Wait.
Siri.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Siri, hallucinate me and make me think I'm in a few at wings.
No.
Too far away.
Hold on.
Let's do it here.
Okay.
Let's see if Siri would know.
Hey, Siri, tell me about Disneyland's...
Oh, I screwed up.
Hey, Siri, tell me about Disney World's ride if you had wings.
I found something on the web about Disney World's ride if you had wings.
Check it out.
Oh, she's not going to read it though.
Oh, yeah.
I was just giving you a...
She's just going to show us the entry.
And then the HomePod had no information.
So they're two different minds.
They're two different brains.
Hey, hey, Siri, play the theme to the ride if you had wings.
I don't think that...
This is not it.
What is this?
I think it's something very smooth.
Hold on.
Disney, stop.
I mean, Disney.
Siri, stop playing.
I think that's just going to be on for the rest of the show.
Stop playing, Siri.
Oh, dear God.
Oh, well.
That's okay.
Now I have to go.
Excuse me.
All right.
I think that's Andrew Gold.
I was listening to an album from my childhood called All This in Heaven 2, Andrew Gold,
which had a huge hit single on it.
What is it?
Thank you for being a friend.
Hold on one second.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm sorry if your listeners might get upset with me.
I'm just picturing them being like, why does he make up things about the ride?
You can include this.
All right.
Keep going.
Hey, I'll put that in there.
Okay.
So we do...
So basically when we're done talking about the ride, we have a scale.
So we say like, if you were like an Imagineer, would you say, I want to plus the ride up?
Would I want to keep it absolutely the same or would I want to burn it down in a mysterious
fire for insurance money?
You mean, so if you had wings, that right?
If it would still exist, if it still existed.
Oh, I would want to plus it up.
You would want to plus it up.
So then we talk about what would be...
Yeah, I would make the same sensations, but make them more modern and better, like more
three...
More three dimensional, not 3D.
Right.
Although that's the same thing.
But you know what I mean?
I wouldn't want to wear 3D glasses.
But I'd want to make it more, you know, I'm sure that if you went on it now, it'd be nostalgic,
but it wouldn't necessarily be like, oh, that was amazing.
Right.
It'd be like, wow, if they could do that now, how good would that be?
The sensation of being on the water, the sensation of being in the car race.
But it is similar to...
To Soarin'.
Yeah.
A lot of people...
To Soarin' is like an advanced version of if you had wings.
A lot of people like point at that this is like a precursor to that.
Very much so.
It is.
Without a doubt.
I think the speed room looked really cool.
I wish they did more stuff like that.
Like that would be so cool.
That would be so cool.
The sensation.
Like 4K.
Well, by the way, what a great ride it would be if you say the speed room, let's just say
it's called the speed room.
In a room where you get the sensation of being in an auto race, being in a boat race.
Like all these speed...
Even a desert speed test.
Like simulating that.
And not in terms of your face or feeling it, but seeing visually what that would be like
the experience.
Yeah.
I would probably enjoy that.
I don't like up and down.
Yeah.
You'd say...
Fast on a straightaway?
Delightful.
Did you ever like roller coasters or anything like that?
No.
Never.
At no point in my life.
I always...
I avoided them like the play.
Did you go on one and it ruined it for you or you just never even tried it?
The only roller coaster I've ever been on, like of any, is Space Mountain.
And when I was done, I must've been like 12 years old or whatever, 14.
When I was done...
No, I was older because that came about later.
What year was Space Mountain?
It's...
76?
Yeah, somewhere around there.
76.
So I was probably 14 or 15 and I went on Space Mountain.
It had been open less than a year, I remember very clearly.
And when I was done, I was like, why did I do that?
It scared the hell out of me.
It was too scary.
Yeah.
And then like now, I can't even do like the Cars ride.
Yeah, because it's too over the top.
Yeah, I can't even do that.
You said you tried it though, right?
Yeah, I went and I watched the dips.
You didn't like the thing where it goes dips.
I don't like dips.
Oh yeah, there's a lot of dips.
I don't even like going on a swing.
That's why Soarin' scares me to a degree.
Oh, a regular swing.
Yeah.
75, 75 in Florida.
The good thing about Soarin' is you can close your eyes and you're fine.
Yeah, it's not.
It doesn't jostle you.
My mom says she hates being jostled on the rides.
By the way, is your mom's name Jocelyn?
Jocelyn, Jocelyn.
Jocelyn Carlson?
The other ride that it really kind of influenced was the boat ride in the Mexico Pavilion at
Epcot.
At Epcot Center that you've never been.
I've never seen it, but it has a lot of sets with that kind of projection.
Oh wow, is it still up or no?
Still up.
It's made, it's had some changes over the years.
Oh, I should go to, I should go to Epcot.
I need to do a road trip to Epcot just based on that ride.
Your ABC privileges, they extend to Florida.
They most certainly do.
They have to.
It's all the magic of Disney.
Oh, you would love the World Showcase.
You know, I don't want Disney to buy Fox only for one reason.
Go ahead.
I'm not a big Fox fan.
I'm a big Disney fan.
Sure.
You're on your career on the line saying that.
I think the big acquisition would be Fox if they got Disney.
I go look at them, but I don't see the excitement, but they still might not get it anyhow.
Because now Comcast is fighting for it.
But doesn't Comcast own Universal?
That'd be weird.
So and then there's some Marvel properties that they would get.
So they would control some of Marvel and Disney would control other parts of Marvel.
Fantastic Four, the X-Men.
And the X-Men.
Oh, and then Barnaby Jones.
And of course, Barnaby Jones, who people have been fighting over the license for for years.
You were talking about remaking that, I think, for a long time.
By the way, I see myself, no, excuse the term, on a crash course with playing Barnaby Jones.
I mean, see that'll my the more I last, the more beloved I'm going to be.
And then at a certain point, it'll be logical for me to play Barnaby Jones.
Yeah, yeah.
Barnaby Jones over Colombo.
Or kind of played Colombo Handsome, which yes.
But I here's the thing.
Truth be told, if they were to do Colombo, they'd want somebody more talented than me.
Probably.
No, no, they would.
Peter Falk was pretty amazing.
And he was great.
They want something interesting.
Whereas I think that Barnaby Jones, you just have to be old.
But he absent, if I remember, didn't dance and he didn't really talk about the Beverly
Hillbillies much.
But Barnaby Jones, he had memories as the character of the.
What about Father Dowling Mysteries?
That was was was Tom Bosley.
Yeah.
How long did that last?
I think it was seasons.
Was he a friend of what's her names?
Friend of who?
Father Dowling, I think, was a spin off of.
Yes, yes.
Yes.
And I used to live in a building and the landlord was a regular on Father Dowling when he was
a younger man.
But Father Dowling ride at Disney World was that's a memory.
That's a whole other show.
Very relaxing, very slow moving.
They pair you with a senior citizen and you have to solve a crime.
That's the Barnaby Jones ride, which they had out here at Universal.
You're getting it mixed up.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Universal.
And they used to feed you mushed rice and applesauce and mushed bananas.
That was a sensation on the Barnaby Jones.
There was no murder.
OK.
Rockford Files became the first themed bar.
That was the first.
Wow.
Was it really?
No.
Because that sounds believable.
Yeah.
Like if there was a Rockford bar like in Malibu, I would so totally go.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Like it looks like his camper, you know, and the bartenders all look like Jim Rockford.
Man.
Yeah.
Now this is alienating the audience too.
And I also think your ideas are pretty horrible.
Oh, OK.
Good.
That it would look like where he lived and all the bartenders look like a middle aged
man.
No, I don't think that would do well.
What would your plus it up be for the Rockford Files bar?
The Rockford Files bar would just be like a lot of memorabilia from the Rockford Files.
OK.
So it would be immersive.
But really pretty bartenders and an area where you could go smoke pot because I don't drink.
Oh, OK.
So that's just like a dry.
That sounds like a dry cleaner that's like had a lot of people from the Rockford Files
use it over the years.
I'm going to say this is probably a worse roasting that I went to one of your shows
at UCB like 11 years ago.
You gave out pop tarts to the audience and you gave me a real hard time about how I was
eating that pop tart.
Oh, you were.
How were you eating?
I think I was breaking it into pieces.
Oh, well.
Because I was like on stage in the light, so I didn't want to look like, you know, a
man just like shoving it down.
So you were taking your time.
I was.
Yeah.
Taking my time.
I give up pop tarts.
Maybe I'll do.
I know you do.
I can't drive my car right now.
So not physically.
My license expired.
Oh, that happened to me.
Yeah.
So I'm waiting now.
I paid online for the fast appointment, which is coming really slowly.
So hopefully by next week, I'll have my license and one of the shows coming up.
I'm going to buy pop tarts for the audience.
Yeah.
You know, I told you this already, but you gave me a 10 years ago.
I wouldn't go to your show, too, when I first came to LA and you gave me a shirt of yours.
What shirt did I give you?
Like a white dress shirt.
Wow.
It's just like sitting in my closet somewhere.
Yeah.
So like, yeah, for people that came to LA, that show at UCD with the pop tarts.
I gave away stereo systems, TVs.
I remember.
I got a white dress shirt.
Wait, what?
I gave away TVs.
I gave away computers.
I remember.
Well, most of my audience was made up of young people who I think I charged a dollar.
Yes, it was a dollar.
So that's where we would go because we were fresh off the boat.
Yeah, and I loved it.
Yeah.
So yeah, I don't know.
What do we got?
Anything else?
Now with times changing, the price to see me at the improv every Friday is $18.
Oh my.
Which is still a bargain.
Very good deal, but yes, much.
Because that's a good luck 18.
You said that you picked the 18?
Yeah.
They don't have like a set?
No.
It could have been 20.
Okay.
Two item minimum, too.
What's that?
Two item minimum.
I don't know what they do with that.
I don't get involved, but I'm guessing it's two drink minimum.
Well, we always say to our guests at the end that, Jeff Garland, you survived podcast
The Ride.
I actually think it's quite different.
I think you two survived your podcast The Ride.
You're like the 50s gangster that hijacked the podcast.
Yeah, I did it.
Well, who was this episode sponsored by?
I forgot.
Well, I think we have a couple sponsors, but the main one?
You're talking about the main one?
The main one.
Yeah, Granddaughter Magazine.
Granddaughter Magazine.
Yeah.
And we want to say that the digital copy is very good, too.
Well, reading it on your iPad is the way to go now.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
They have a lot of links, like video hyperlinks.
Hyperlinks to things.
And it's really intuitive.
It's an enhanced issue.
And a wonderful app.
Yeah, it's an enhanced issue.
Do you have anything to plug?
Do you want to talk?
Well, come to my show if you ever want on Friday nights at the Improv.
I'm recording this week Toy Story 4.
Really?
Yes.
And on the script or they only show it to you there?
They only show it to me there.
So you can't prepare at all?
I also saw Tim Allen on the street in Beverly Hills.
We talked for a while and he's recording soon.
Wow.
That's exciting.
Yeah.
And you're doing it here, but you're not going up to Emeryville or whatever.
No.
Generally, the more times you record, you rotate.
Like you do one up there, one down here.
And this is the first year I'm not recording at Disney.
I'm recording at a studio in Hollywood.
I forgot the name of it.
Sure.
We don't have to give.
We don't have to know.
No, no.
I really can't remember the name.
Sure.
Or Formosa.
Well, it's not Formosa.
It's probably Formosa.
It's right there.
Yeah.
It used to be Warner Brothers.
Sure.
I don't know what it's called.
Well, that's fun.
That's exciting.
Yeah.
I'm recording this coming week.
Anything else?
Shows?
When does Goldberg start?
Goldberg's is on now.
I don't know if, you know, and Curb's on.
Everything's always on.
It's always on.
I start filming Goldberg's in August and then Curb in October.
New season of Curb.
And then, yeah, but, you know, come to see me at the Improv Friday nights.
And then starting in August, I'll be at Friday nights at the Improv and Saturday nights, Sunday
nights at Flappers.
Yeah.
In Burbank.
That's a fun place.
In Carlson country.
Terrible name.
Wonderful place.
The staff there is lovely.
They're lovely.
So, yeah, there's plenty of places to see me.
And tonight I'll be doing, you won't be hearing it, but tonight I'm going to do an hour monologue
about the history of granddaughter magazine.
Well, people, well, all the kids will be posting about it on social media.
It's about time this story is told.
You know what I look forward to, Mike?
Can I mean this?
Go ahead.
Is anyone ever coming up to me on the street and pointing at me and saying, granddaughter
magazine?
Because I'll know that they listen to this and they'll make me very happy.
I think it'll happen because we've had a couple of nice people come up to us in Disneyland
already.
So I think people in the park are listening.
More often than not.
Yeah, because it's, but gosh, I just got to say, I love the idea of the show because I
love as much as I made up things that happen on the ride.
I love Disneyland.
It is just, it just thrills me.
I don't eat sugar anymore.
Yeah.
So, so a lot of certain things.
A lot of treats are off the table.
Specific treat that I always loved was the two cookies with the ice cream in the middle
and they move to the other side.
They don't even have the, they used to just be that one little place down the alley where
you could get it and they actually made it fresh.
Yes.
I don't know what goes on with that, but it doesn't concern me because it's sugar.
So I can't concern myself, but there's so many treats.
We saw some new treats.
You're like, oh, this is new.
And it was a sweet treat and I couldn't have it.
I asked, well, I asked Jack, I said, I know that they have a Dole Whip donut now.
Yeah.
And he made a call on his phone to see where they were.
But then they, then the person that like, they didn't have any fresh.
Yeah.
She was like, don't worry, but it's not actually that good.
She didn't say that.
She did.
She quietly.
She said a few.
Yeah.
Cause to me they made out like it was great and they said they would have them in like
an hour, but they'd be in line.
You'd have to wait in line.
Yeah.
There'd be a line and you know,
And ABC couldn't
I get a sugar.
So, you know,
And Jack couldn't let us cut that line for some reason.
Yeah.
That line was not cuttable.
Right.
But I have to say, I feel rude cutting.
Like when you have a guide and they take you to lunch, you don't cut.
Right.
There's a different area you walk in.
Or you go to the exit.
Cause I would not do it if you had to walk by all the people.
Oh yeah.
I would not do it.
That would be rude.
It would just be so horrible.
I would never do it.
Yeah.
We'd go on the exit.
So Disneyland is wonderful.
A bunch of wonderful people.
That's why I'm on a plug.
For anyone listening, if you have the time, go to Disneyland or Disney World or Epcot
or yeah.
Or the Disney Hollywood studios where they used to have a great.
Go to the gift shop at the Imagineering place.
Or the Rockford Files bar.
The Rockford Files bar.
Either Jason's version or Jeff's version.
I think my version is better because there'd be women.
Well, I think my version would have some very nice stories from middle-aged men.
And I think having women bartenders is much better than stories from middle-aged men.
Just a middle-aged guy kind of coughing a lot.
And you want to hear those stories.
Talking about his alimony.
You want to just say, how'd you get your cough?
And then you'll hear it.
Yeah.
By the way, my voice became very distinct after working on WALL-E.
Yes.
Because I worked on it three years and I blew up my voice and it became much more distinct
than it is now.
Right.
Or the performance in WALL-E.
I sound like that now.
And prior to doing WALL-E, I of course sounded like that, but it's not as extreme.
Did you have to get like therapy after that?
Yeah.
I did vocal voice stuff I had to do.
I had to do singing lessons to learn how to talk again.
Sorry.
How was your singing?
Everything's good.
It's delightful.
Although I lose my voice on occasion.
I got you.
Well, look folks, we've done it here today.
Yes, it's been great.
We've talked to a few at Wings.
It's been great.
And I also, how do they follow you?
They follow us at PodcastTheRide, at Twitter.
Twitter and Instagram.
They email us.
PodcastTheRide at Gmail.
Do you have an Instagram account?
We have an Instagram account.
Okay, I'm going to go on there right now.
PodcastTheRide at Instagram.
Follow me on Instagram at Jeff Garland.
Oh yeah, yeah.
You post a lot of fun stuff there.
Hold on.
I'm going to go there right now.
And our Facebook group too, PodcastTheRide.
It's a whole, there's a collection of folks now talking about all this.
Yeah, it's great.
We love saying that.
I don't go on Facebook.
Yeah.
So follow us at those places.
So let me just go, let me find you.
Sure, sure.
Okay.
So it's called what?
Podcast, what is it?
PodcastTheRide?
Yeah, PodcastTheRide one word.
We post some fun stuff.
Do we post pictures when we go?
Here it is.
Wow.
It's got a little purple logo.
Yeah, I see it.
It's like an Epcot-ish.
Is that your girlfriend in that picture there?
Where?
I don't think she's on.
No, that's, that's, that's a picture that looks sort of like my girlfriend, but that
is not my girlfriend.
Who was that?
Julie Prescott?
Julie Prescott.
She was a guest on a couple of episodes ago.
Yeah.
All right.
So are you just going to follow it?
I like it.
Yeah, I'm following it.
I just followed it.
Well yeah, follow us there.
And you are not following me.
You're right.
Well, we'll be following you.
We can do that.
I'm sure that each one of you does the-
Jason does.
It's his fault that we're not following you.
All right.
How else am I going to get more followers if you're of all the places?
Thank you everybody.
Thank you for listening.
Thanks.
All right.