The future. The domestic film industry is in freefall. With no viable properties on which to base a new aquatic stunt show, Universal Studios must subsist on a Kevin Costner movie from 1995 that ate shit.
A group of raiders known as podcasters set out to snark about this show, even though it's honestly pretty cool. Fellow Sea Warrior Jordan Morris embarks to a stunt show known as Waterworld, a live Sea War spectacular. Meet us at the atoll on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast about theme parks where we used to do fully written comedy segments. You guys remember that?
Yeah, I guess we haven't done one of those in a long time. It's been like months and months. They weren't always fully written. But I mean really, what I should have said is we used to do segments at all, because that's been out the window for a very long time.
Right, we haven't had actually a conversation. First of all, my name is Mike Carlson. Yeah, I'm Scott Gerner. We haven't had a full conversation about that, but I guess we may as well just do it on the show.
That's what I think. Bring the listeners in? Yeah, because I like doing all the written pieces, but then we would find that like, oh, there's too much in this episode. We think the audience doesn't want to, you know, sit through this whole thing. So that's what I'm going to blame it on. In reality, is it that we're all lazy and that we didn't want to write a minute of comedy?
And I'm Jason Sheridan, and I just want to say I fell in love with the sound of my own voice. Okay, so that's my justification. You were saying the comedy bits too? That's true, but sometimes reading them at the same time, and that took away a little bit of brain power from just listening to the dulcet tones of this bad boy.
Acting like you fell in love with the sound of your own voice just a year ago, please. I've known you for a decade. What's that? Self-satisfied for the whole time. When you make a joke or you eat a treat, you've been always very happy with yourself. And that's not a bad thing. I'm just saying it's not a new thing to happen.
It has nothing to do with the elimination of segments from the show. What with our new format, talking without confines for over two hours. Yeah, well, let's make a pledge to do some written comedy. Oh boy, that's not why I brought it up. I was just pointing out something.
Well, I'm curious if anyone misses any of that. And you know why I thought of it is because when we had Nick Weiger on the parking garage episode, I just recalled that episode the other day and thought, and then we still did like a segment. Remember at the end? Yes, we used to do extra segments at the end. Yeah, yeah.
I think there are bits we wrote that we haven't gotten to. Yeah, I think there's a couple of written things that we were like, oh, we'll do it next time. We should just do an all segment episode. Yes, all written. It'll take us a month to prep it. I mean, that would cut down on the research aspect, on the research hours. But I like to rewrite and rewrite, so I'm going to need time. So we better plan this now. In 2019.
The full first fully scripted into the fall of 2019 podcast arrived fully scripted comedy episode. Oh boy. Well, we're here. We'll go. Let's get this less inside right now and bring in our our guest who knows not of our internal politics, but who certainly knows the world of podcasts. You know him from Jordan, Jesse go and from the new comedy sci fi podcast bubble. It's Jordan Morris. Hi, guys.
Hello. As you mentioned, I'm very familiar with this world. I just want to say it was such a delight to be here for one of those classic podcast moments where the host talk about the logistics of the podcast.
Top of the podcast. Can we talk about whose mic is sounding weird? Why one guy was late? Sure. We we thankfully have not done too much of that. Yeah, I don't think we've ever had to talk about losing files. Right. Knock on wood or the political bit about the helicopter that passed over the house. Sure. It was all. Wow. That's coming for you, Jason. Yeah.
Yeah. For what you said about the about the Matterhorn lines. Can we have a discussion about what we're all doing after this? I think I think we're just we're we're getting it. And again, it's classic podcasting. We're in a living room.
Yeah, that's true. We're playing into a stereotype. We I think sometimes we've referred to the dog that will sometimes run around where we're recording. And also, I think the dog has been very popular on Twitter when posted about. So I have no regrets about including Edwin. I think in general, maybe this is good.
This is a policing role you can fill tonight that if you sense a trope being played into. No, I'm not. I'm not bagging on the trope. I enjoy it. I you know, I enjoy this this vibe right now. It's very it's very old school. It's very like I feel like I'm in CBGB.
You know, three quarters of the bathrooms are filthy. You know, I love that. This is why we do it, guys. Yeah, we're getting back to the roots of it. Yeah, Scott steered the ship in this direction and then immediately started roasting it.
Yes. Yeah, I think I tend to do that. I like things on them from now on. Scott, just these jokes should just be about us liking robots. Let's go back to the bread and butter of jokes that we start with where we like a robot or there's a restaurant and we only eat there.
There's a robot. That's what all of our jokes should really be about. Who likes the robots? We all we all like robots equally. But there's many I think maybe some of the jokes that I like to write or start the show with are about how much we like robots.
I said that our best friend from childhood was the chunky up cut robots smart one.
I'm familiar with this robot. He is a delightful robot. I'll show you a photo of him. We got to go robot by robot. Yeah. Well, someone tweeted at us.
Has there been an animatronic of the month in a while, which is a segment one of the segment.
It's worth bringing up the thing that makes me laugh that I think is funny is that it is very rarely monthly holding up a big picture of smart one. Yeah, really. First time I'm seeing this bot and he's a peach.
Yeah. Do you have Jordan? Do you have I don't know about your full history with theme parks, but do you have a love of robots and animatronics like we do or a favorite? I'm sure this has come up on the show before. Sure. I really, really miss the Paul Rubin's robot in Star Tours.
Well, this is Scott's favorite greatest favorite character in fiction. I believe greater than edepus. I don't even know any of who you're talking about. I number one is RX 24. I hope I didn't get the number wrong. I don't think I did. Yeah. Yeah. Really miss him.
Got to see him in Paris, where he was still installed later than all of the other rounds. He talked in French. He's spoken French and it was delightful. Maybe so happy. Yeah. You saw his girlfriend. Yeah. Yeah. He also in Paris. So you also saw his mistress.
Yeah. You meet the whole of different mores over there. But yeah, I'm glad you agree. He's number one. He's number one animatronic for me. Would you guys have different answers about that? Well, yeah, it's like I mean, I would probably pick a country bear. I think I would have to like Gomer or big Al. But if I would maybe you have to.
Well, this is an unfair limit. If you had to pick within people who are knowingly robots like smart one. I guess that's a lot. That's a devia because it would be like smart one. It would be Rex. It would be one of those robot butler from horizons. Yeah. Robot Butler. Who else? Who else knows there are robot? Man. This is a great. This is the beginnings of a great like blacklist script here where the robots from Disneyland who know their robots. Yeah. Each the other robots who think they're other things that they are robots like they go to Lincoln and
convince him. Oh, yeah. Lincoln rather a slave of this theme park Lincoln as a slave. What? Yeah, I know. And then, you know, you have a Westworld situation. It's a very it's not as confusing. It's a very Buzz Lightyear style Toy Story one. Yeah. Yeah. I was going to say my fear about this plot is that they would get smart and leave Disneyland, which I it breaks my heart to even consider that notion. So I think the robots would have to teach the less knowing robots that it's there.
That's the goal in the world. It's servitude. I want that lesson to get out there. I show business if they pull the timekeeper or the time is right out of deep storage. Oh, yeah. Do the timekeeper. The timekeeper was a robot voice by Robin Williams that hosted like a show in Florida where he would you would travel through time and meet like great historical figures. Yeah.
Nine I also a great robot. The was the oh, yeah. That was the it was a circle vision movie. If you recall that format ever from a Disney experience with a movie goes all the way around to Mars. That's not a circle vision. No, no, no. Basically, it's like a circle vision is like you stand in a big circle and the movie goes all the way 360 around you. OK. So there's a couple different places in Epcot Center where you can see a circle vision movie one in Canada, one in China. Yes. Right.
China, France. No, France is not a circle vision. Oh, is it not? No, it's just a movie and confusingly Mission to Mars is a circular theater where you watch a movie that is not a circle. OK. Very disimportant distinction. No, this is great. Fascinating.
You will hear knowing. OK. But wait, we asked you. Yeah, you miss Rex. You miss Starter. Well, I'm curious about your your theme park journey or leanings. Yeah. So I grew up in Orange County.
The shadow of the great one. Of course, very far. Someone made that joke before on the show. No, no, no. The misdirects. No, no. Thank you. It's almost not even a joke in a way. We're very fond of not. Oh, yeah.
And a lot of people probably would be like, like listening or misdirect and be like, oh, he said exactly what I thought he'd say, because that's very far.
We all know that that's the greatest theme park. It's more of Montezuma's revenge. Of course, people would argue probably. Oh, it's more pure. Sure. It's more less corrupted by fried chicken, too. Yes. Oh, sure. Yeah.
So no. So, yeah. So so I had a couple of years in high school where I had a Disneyland pass. Oh, yeah. And I think I was in a really kind of special Venn diagram of high school student, which was, you know, drama kid, but also cool youth group kid.
So like when we wanted to really like cut loose, we would go to Disneyland and goof off. So we had that, you know, we would like find out like where the Jungle Cruise was going to go by. And then we would like jump on the fence and like make monkey noises and see if we could get the guard to like the guard, the guy who drives the boat.
The skipper to like acknowledge us. So we were like just fucking like annoying assholes. You know, boy, we were. Yeah, we were all we would. This would stress the three of us out if we were in the boat and we saw like teens. Right.
Rowdy. We would be around. We kind of get like tense and then like start sweating a little bit. That's actually our age now, too. We're not saying when we were younger.
If teens were being messing, forcing the skipper to go off script. Yeah, that would bother us. Yeah. Messing we are making so he couldn't tell which which joke, which of the nine jokes to use backside of water.
We're not there yet. But yeah, I totally loved Disneyland as a kid. I don't go a ton as an adult. I actually find myself going to Universal Studios more as an adult. It's a little bit closer. And I love to ride the movies.
Sure doesn't. And so, yeah. But yeah, definitely. We spent a lot of like fun time at Disneyland as a kid. Sure. Sure. Like maybe my my core years were like 1995 to 2000 and 2001 ish.
So, yeah, if that gives you guys a sense of what was going on in the end. Never never kicked out. Never forcibly. You know, we got we got we got we got put in the little detention area.
Really? Whoa, because I don't think your guest is a first on the podcast talking to somebody who got put in Disney jail. So we got stopped. We were like on the on the Haunted Mansion and, you know, two to a cart, two to a doom buggy.
Of course, three though. And we were doing a thing where like you can kind of see the back of the other person's doom buggy when you're going around a curve. So we were like hitting our friends.
Doom buggy. Sure. Which caused them to stop. You know, the thing plays, you know, this and the spirits are experiencing technical difficulties. Yeah. And then so somebody came and like with a flashlight and like released all our things and took us in the back and they made us empty our pockets in the back.
And the back was very clinical. I wish it was themed in some way. Sure. It was not. It was of the Haunted Mansion of the Haunted Mansion. Yeah. And you remember any it was just like, tell us some room. Tell us everything. Yeah. No, I wish it was more interesting, but it was kind of just like a break room.
Like you've ever worked at a department store or something like the break room. It just like there's a billboard up with like, you know, directions on how to do the Heimlich maneuver.
Do you remember what room you were stopped in? Did you say they miss it? I think it was the the crystal ballroom with the woman's head. Madame Leota room. Madame Leota, of course. So you got to leave the...
So in the theme part, if you're a nerd, one of the biggest things you get to do is have a what they call a walk off, which is where the ride generally would break down and you get to walk off. So you get to actually experience a little bit more of the room than you would if you're just like on the ride vehicle.
You did more of a walk of shame off. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. So you did do another. Yeah. Another dream.
Madame Leota had had sex the night before. Headed home in the same outfit I came in. Yeah. So and the something, you know, because we were such like, you know, random dipshit who loved being random. We were all carrying bubble pipes at that point because that was our thing. We all had bubble pipes.
I know. I got I want to go back in time and punch myself in the face. So like they had us empty our pockets and we all had these bubble pipes. And that was very we had to like explain to them that it was not for drugs because we were random. We love being so random.
Right. You also have like bulk bubble solution to fill up the pipes. I don't I think at I think at as at this point we had been doing it so long that we had it stopped being about the blowing bubbles and just putting it in your mouth.
I know that that smirk that rich fancy man. You know, go random. There was a comment on society. Sure. I still never had a beer. Were you the were you the kind of like were you the kind of like tough edgy teen who would like you get in a little bit of trouble and it all falls apart.
Or or could you stand up to a security guard slightly older than you. We all like we all like bent the knee so quick when this happened. Yeah. And then I remember them like feel you know them like deeming that we were OK to go.
And I think something somebody had mentioned that we were all we all had passes. We were all season pass holders. And I remember on our way out the guy said hey season passes are a great way to enjoy the park. And what. Yeah. So that was our like he's not wrong. Those were our parting words.
It is a great way to enjoy the park. What a lesson to impart on the way. Yeah. Threaten to take your yeah. I wish it was a little more interesting. I wish there was like an animatronic like you know British Bobby there who's wagging his finger at us.
But it's like a fake out of a guy with a big axe who and they like put you in the way they lay down. Yeah. He's going to cut your head. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That would be nice. I mean honestly I think yeah. Does he like and step up. And right. Because I know that like Disneyland jail is kind of a fabled thing. Right. There's even like a name for it which I've always heard has a big Mickey making it like a tisk tisk finger.
Wow. Wow. But I've never. That's that's pretty like barely sourced. But if anybody if any listeners out there know and have been to Disney jail stop listening to this podcast. You're a jerk and you don't deserve the magic of the good boys. Yeah.
I mean the first piece of advice I got before going into Disneyland jail is just immediately on your first day there you have to beat up Stitch. Everyone will respect you. Which is bold ask because Stitch is a killing machine. Yeah. It kind of glossed over after the first hour of the movie.
But Stitch has a bunch of arms. He's been trained for war. Yeah. That's why he's the he's the he's the king of the prison. You got to go after the alpha certainly. It makes like Elvis. That's why he's dressed like Elvis because Elvis did his time. He did his duty in the services.
He was a karate and a killing machine. Andy Nook. Yeah. It was karate and foodie enthusiast killing machine. It was an infoodiest later in life. Oh yes certainly. Because he got so fat. It became his primary duty. Yes.
Okay. Now when you so fast forwarding past your no good nick days in more more more civil adult times recently at Universal Studios when I threw yes read the movies and in some cases see a live spectacular based on the movies.
So when I gave you a list of topics you did mention Universal Studios and you chose Waterworld a live sea war spectacular which I would like to be very I want to lay down the law right now I'm going to make you all live under the rule that I had to live by when I worked there which is that full title had to be intact.
It is Waterworld a live sea war spectacular. A live sea war spectacular? Yeah. Sea war. No it's like it's a notion it's a reference to the notion of sea war that we're all so familiar with. Hey I'm on a sea war diet. I sea war and I eat it.
You know the word Navy is more popularized or calling things naval but the true term is sea war and if you have a friend or loved one in the Navy you should say they are at sea war. So I'll be policing that. Waterworld a live sea war spectacular.
Alright fair enough. This is probably in the history because it replaced the Miami Vice action spectacular which ran for six years. Uh huh. Uh huh. There's got to be a lot of superlatives or it's not a solid theme park attraction.
There was an A-Team show there before Miami Vice which also had a very cumbersome title that's name I'm escaping now. The A-Team show just seemed like a lot of jeeps driving around. A-Team pulling a land war spectacular. Here we are on land. Here we are on land. We're driving a lot of cars. Just a couple of humans on land.
That guy clearly is dressed like Mr. T. The Miami Vice one seemed really intense though. There's like twice as many guns. I mean Crockett and Tubbs are in the suits and they slowly get less and less dressed as it goes on. One of them definitely ends up in like a tank top by the end. And there's like cars and boats and it's wild.
So this isn't the same facility. They built a water stunt show area. Yes. It used to have a lot more land in it and then when they redid it for Waterworld like I think they kept some of the set dressing and then expanded the water.
Maybe the stands were the same I'm not totally sure. But yes some of the facility but also they must have had to make it a lot more water and probably deeper because there's such gigantic dives that occur in the show. I'm not totally sure. But anyway in narrowing down this topic why Waterworld Alive Sea War Spectacular?
Well I mean when we're talking about Waterworld Alive Sea War Spectacular. I mean it is you know I think it's an interesting mix of like actually very cool like cool things happen in it. You know a seaplane jumps a ramp and explodes.
There's you know there's stunt performers falling off ledges into vats of toxic waste. Yeah you know all kinds of explosions. Fire dives. Yeah yeah a guy gets set on fire and like you know dives off a high area. Yeah a guy hangs on to a thing for a long time which takes up her body strength. That's impressive.
Oh yeah there's a long hang. I don't know what the proper stunt term is. So you're watching this thing and it's actually it's actually very cool. There are talented people doing cool things. Yeah. But just every few seconds you're reminded this is about Waterworld that movie from 1995 or whatever where Kevin Costner is the Gill man.
It's like this long forgotten movie. I heard a statistic that I don't know if it's true but I like that more people have now seen that show than have seen the movie. Probably. It probably makes sense that this thing has been around for 20 years. 23 years. Yeah and you know sure five shows a day and yeah.
Sometimes more I think. I was looking I like I ended up on the employment site for if you if you wanted to be in this show. I found it on backstage.com and the I think they could they say you're kind of on the hook for maybe as many as nine I think.
Really. I guess. Well I guess one person I think they maybe do nine and I don't think one person maybe you could only fit in five as an employee. I'll confirm that fact. But yeah there's a lot of shows and it's been going for a lot of years. And one of the oddest things about this attraction.
Okay so the stunt show was done in conjunction with the release of the film in the sure to be blockbuster success. Of course. Yeah. Spotted around many real quickly. For sure. Yeah. Yeah. Well apparently the people from the team and the people who would build the sets for the show went to Hawaii where they were filming Waterworld and it was much like the Jurassic Park ride very much done in coordination with the making of the film.
So you can understand why it stuck around and why it just became awkward like oh it's this notorious bomb because the trades were all against it and reviewers didn't like it and now they're stuck with the with this live show. Yeah. The only reason anyone talks about Waterworld anymore is to like short hand for a bomb. You know. Yeah.
Yeah. Of Waterworld in the postman like kind of like oh that was the weird. Costner. Costner is like leading man. Sure. There for a while after like all the hits he had like before that I feel like. Yeah. Yeah. And I also you know I was under the misconception that this that Waterworld was a think until today I thought it was written directed and starring Costner.
But directed by somebody else script existed without him. I think he was like I think if you got him at that point you got a lot of him. You got a lot of. He's very involved. He's on kind of actor. Yeah. Yeah. I was under that impression too. But the postman was him. Yeah. Yeah. I was confusing those. Anyway just to get to my roundabout point.
You can understand why this one stuck around like well we spent the money we got to do it also people really like the show. Sure. But then Universal Studios Japan opens and they build it again. Yeah. Yeah. Universal Singapore opens in 2010 and they build Waterworld again. Yeah. And the company that ran the two Asian productions eventually took over the Hollywood one.
Like it went backwards. It's kind of 2014 they redid the show when the production company changed. It's called Action Horizons and it's a company founded by actual stunt people and they took over production in 2014. So that's when you saw like 19 years after it opened.
You saw some like slight changes to the show like just like like stunt blocking changes and like the seaplane comes a little later in the show and like there's one other like set piece that they did lately different. They didn't change that when the Deacon holds up a golf ball that he says I'm Tiger Woods.
And there's no further joke there. Yeah. Even though they don't refer to the affair they don't update the golf. No it's the only like topical reference in the whole thing at least in. Yeah.
Unless there's different versions and people ad lib or whatever. But I in the video that I watched and as far as I know it's not a topical show. When it opened it wasn't like I'm Jack Nicklaus.
I guess it was around in 96. He was just starting to break on the scene. I'm really not a reference. Yeah. Yeah. I'm so a ballesteros. That's a Spanish golfer I know about because of my dad. He says look at me. I'm playing golf.
I'm a famous man. Tiger Woods broke out. We should you know. Well we can get it more specific. He said look at me. I'm playing golf. You know devils in the details. I don't like nothing. Well I'm glad we can spice it up.
I gotta say still hits. There's like three things. Anytime I see the show there's like three things that always gets a big pop from the crowd. The Tiger Woods thing. The thing about like this floating piece of sheet metal that always gets a laugh which is wild.
And then the seaplane thing always. Yeah. Get that and it's amazing. It's genuinely amazing. It's amazing. The fire dive to the lake however many feet in the air fire dive which they think we talked about many many moons ago they replicated for the eighth voyage of
Sindbad stunt show in Island of Adventure Florida. Sindbad. Sindbad with an infuriated D. The Sindbad trick was taken from Waterworld a live sea war spectacular. Yeah. Nothing better than correcting minutiae like this. Also to correct my own minutiae if you're a performer in the show you are expected to perform two to five shows a day.
But they say that there could be anywhere from two to eleven performances. Eleven. That's crazy. There's like a marathon day or something like an all day. They just had the park open. Yeah I don't know. That seems dangerous. If I can correct some minutiae. Impressions de France is shown across five screens in 200 degrees so you were right. Not official circle vision but often mistaken for it.
You know what I though that's a that's a good correction because I thought it was just a regular movie. I didn't know it was a super wide movie. So we met in the middle. I like the creators of the French New Wave demand more further.
How do we even. Something I love about it is that that there's like a story to it and it references the like fiction of that movie so heavily like so people are like it's the Mariner and like and in a way that yeah it expects people to feel something about that. It's like and like just 16 year old dirtbags were at Universal Studios now like don't like what do they care that it's the Mariner.
They know the Mariner from this show. Right. Yeah exactly. Yeah. And they're like it's the smokers which was like the name for the bad guys because they you know smoked the water world had an anti smoking message I remember. They just are the smokers. Yeah that's the name of the like you know the evil Dennis Hopper crew of pirates. They're the smokers.
Oh well and the whole thing I mean obviously there's you know it's just it's global warming and pollution and stuff but I was reading how it was really heavily stemming from the Exxon Valdez.
That's where that which is so that's another odd thing that that's another thing that makes the movie strange now is that it's like a it's a movie kind of railing for a current event. Yeah yeah yeah very long time. I think there's a chance that like another water world comes out based on the show.
Right. Because they're keeping it they didn't like change the name of it at all like they could have changed the name of it and no one would have cared no one would care that the smokers isn't reference that they changed the name of the bad guys or that they changed the characters.
They've kept the characters exactly the same. They want that sweet IP. They know because they were looking for dry land. We all have to find dry land. I like when they all yell dry land. Yeah. That works on me.
So the people who seeing this who don't know water world is this all just nonsense or do they even care. I don't know. They don't care. Set it up pretty well. I think this is one of my theories about theme parks is sometimes like just OK movies are pretty like dumb movies make for good rides because you have to condense it down to like in this case 16 minutes 20 minutes or like the Transformers ride is really fun. I also like that.
But like those movies are just I mean they're great for like a five minute experience. Sure. Just like this like condensed down. It's like oh it's yeah it's a post apocalyptic action thing. There's lots of water stunts. There might be more water stunts in this show than in the movie itself.
I remember watching it on cable a long time ago when I was like young this in the postman Saturday afternoon cable TV with commercial breaks perfectly enjoyable experiences. You don't get to see gene triple horns but from behind but probably not.
That's one of my memories about water world Mr. Skin classic. Oh yeah. Definitely. Yeah. Definitely a place you're going to go to Mr. Skin. Good parts from I in postman and water world back to back. Wow. Yeah. This is a that's that's a full Saturday. Yeah. And you know I wasn't even thinking back to back.
I just want to say for Pizza Hut. Oh man. Go to town. I'd like to do that today. That's actually so good. Sure. Except for the once when you had 11 minutes into water world you'd go what have I done. I thought about watching it for in preparation for this.
You know just kind of got away from me. But yeah I wonder if I like come in here mad at you guys because I had watched a water world. Oh yeah. You made me. Yeah I didn't get a chance to do it either. Didn't get a chance. You know I tried real hard but I did watch clips from that site that YouTube account that has clips numbered one through 10 and then like too loud of chimes come in at the end. You know what I'm talking about. Yeah.
And then you they also encourage you to watch a clip from the frighteners. Yeah. Some utterly. Now that you've watched. Do you like minutes of water like actors. You want to see another movie with actors. Is that like the account is like Blu Ray account or something like it's some weird generic thing that puts all these movie clips up. I guess it's called movie clips. It's called the Vivo of movies. But it annoys me because when that when it ends. Oh I think this. Oh you know what people were mad. I looked at one of the top.
Waterworlds viewed videos on YouTube and one of them was a scene that must have been heading for Jean Triple Horn nudity because it cuts and those famous chimes come in. Yes. Right as she's disrobing and the comments are furious.
So but there's all that was an important scene to a lot of people.
So the message the Exxon Valdez message didn't get through. Yeah. Change your foreign did. It's what did. What else did I see in the clips because there's some weird business going on with Dennis Hopper gets it. I think he gets his eye ripped out and then he gets a new eye installed and he's surrounded by sycophants and they're all like it looks it looks good boss. Yeah.
Oh it better than the last one. And then just one like smart alecky teen a young Jordan Esk teen is like it looks like shit. And he's the one who's willing to stand out and then he pops it out. But that's all referenced in the show because the show is a sequel to the movie.
Yeah. Like it extends and there's some line about you're the one who poked out my eye. So it does. There is continuity between the film and the show because Deacon is the character from the movie. But Kevin Costner's character is not in the show.
What. Yes he is. He's the Mariner. Oh my god. Really. Yeah. I don't I don't blame you because one of my was so confused watching the video is that they don't they don't really hit the Mariner hard enough. Like I like if you ask me what are the qualities of the Mariner. Right. I would have zero answer. I'm not sure I could even after the show point out which one was the Mariner. I don't know. I watched the whole thing literally an hour ago. I watched it on YouTube.
I didn't watch it on the TV. I did not pick up that that was supposed to be. Yeah. That's Kevin Costner saying the only thing to me. So my big memory from watching it is the like closing shot when they do make it to dry land. But also there the Mariner can breathe underwater. Right. And there is one sequence where like he there's like a very crude submersible thing where he like you'll be able to breathe in here Helen and like the heat they go down to the depth.
And he pulls it along because he can be his gills. He can breathe underwater. And he he's like this is what the world used to be. And they go deep deep underwater. And it's clearly New York City. The ruins of New York City. Like some movies show the ruins of Atlantis. I think the only allusion to it in the show is when he jet skis his way underwater. Like he just skis under the wall and comes out of the water which apparently the Mariner is not.
The Mariner can ride a jet ski underwater. Breathe and ride. Yeah. Underwater and also not use a gun or like a night like all the good guys are using water cannons and their wits in this show. Sure. All the bad guys have like Colt 45s and shotguns.
So he's he relies on his cunning alone. I you know for I that's another thing when I found this casting site how I was I had no impression of the Mariner so I can completely relate to where you're going from Mike. And I but then to juxtapose that with when you look at the casting site what they how they describe the Mariner heroic capable and deliberate highly athletic and moves with the confidence of a man who doesn't know defeat has learned to drink own piss.
Oh that's a big yeah that's a big part of the audition. Can you take that a pint of your own piss. Does it happen in the show. It might someday do it. Drink your piss buddy. You have to have a secret as an actor. You have to have a secret. I roll my own piss. Yeah.
I don't I just I mean it goes on and on honestly but that it's he's sure built up for somebody who doesn't like rate. Yeah at all. Now when you were watching it and you didn't I thought it was just a hero. I must I missed the name because I just thought it was like oh this is a hero guy. Yeah. They're focusing more on the girl. Sure.
They're focusing focusing more on the deacon. I like well I'm not entirely sure that the Mariner is mentioned in the opening narration. I think he might not be referenced at all. Now they reference him during the show. The Mariners coming. But I'm not.
Correct me if I'm wrong. But what they do this is what jamming that information in and like telling teens quickly what this decades old movie was. I find it really weird that they devote audio real estate to tell you that the survivors live on floating fortresses known as atolls.
They write and then they keep saying atolls. I think they name check everyone in the open. I think they name check Helen the deacon and the Mariner. Is there a very quickly. So the deacon is very very often telling you that he has a sea plane. They say sea plane so much in this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I think I know who played who piloted that sea plane in the movie because he's credited as pilot a young Jack Black. Oh yeah.
That is pilot in Waterworld. So that famous plane is it like kind of the same model of plane. I think so. Yeah. Because there is like a plane crash in the movie I think. Oh it looks like the tailspin plane. Yeah. Yeah. That's a traditional sea plane. Yeah. Everyone knows. You know I
know spinner. I read a a oral history of making a water world today and they don't show or the movie the movie and they interview Jean Triple Horn and Tina Majorino was the young girl in it and the director and they also interviewed Jack Black.
And it's funny because they all talk about like how difficult it was and you know how trying but I think Jack Black was just there real quick and probably it's four minutes of his day to fill out an email about Waterworld.
So whereas the other answers are like do you do people ask you about the movie 20 years later. Yeah well you know it's weird because the movie has this tortured history. Jack Black's answer. We crushed it bro. I'm still trying to shake it. That's what it's going to say on my tombstone.
Jack post apocalyptic sea plane pilot black. I like imagining him flippantly writing this email that is all involved with Waterworld. My career has turned out the best. He really won Waterworld. I mean 1995 Jack Black like as an actor I'd go like are you kidding me.
Like you don't come on man just say it was a get that would have been a get for you. This is pre Mr. Sure pre tenacious. That's not what Jack Black is about. Tenacious might have been on HBO at this point right. Is that right. 1995 maybe not.
Cable guy he's in cable guy in 96. Oh yeah. What's another Mars attacks too. He's those all ball pop a lot when he when he showed. Oh he was I think it was him right that I just saw on the the Golden Girls spin off the Golden Palace.
Oh yeah. Comes in for a second. But the I I don't think he did. I think he truly does appreciate getting to be part of this film is then later in the interview the script was badass. It was like a wet road warrior and it was shooting in Hawaii.
I think he absolutely wanted to be more humble about it in the oral history. No I think it's OK to go like yeah it was cool when I was it was 1995 and I got to go work in Hawaii and a plus five lines role. You know sound like you're really breaking this thing.
I guess I don't know. I just think I would be jazzed. I would be jazzed. I would be charmed by how much she's got loved and Jason is put off by his cockiness. I don't know. Yeah.
He did say we crushed it but then he said it'll haunt me to the grave. Like he said he's making a joke about dumb exaggerating. Oh OK. I think I guess we did it. Shallow Hal is going to haunt him to the grave.
We're doing we did our podcast inside info. We talked about plus fives and I'm reading from backstage dot com. This is a post Barry world. People know all this stuff now. OK. Very exclusively as popular as well.
So Jack Plectra of the plane that plane is yeah actually genuinely remarkable part of that show. And I think it was probably difficult for them to pitch and to pull off because that is a that is a big prop with pyrotechnics on it that shoot off once they land.
And it has to do it many times a day and it is flying right at the audience. No cable with nothing nothing that could pull it back in case of an emergency. But it's been decades of this and nothing has happened.
It sounds like a universal world related death. No I don't believe so. They've kept it secret if they have. It does seem like one time it would have like like caught wind and flown out onto the one to one or something.
Yeah. Like right into the right into the hills and to stay right into the G.B. Buffett's Margaritaville. Oh God no. I mean that would be a turn that would be a nightmare. We're describing a scenario where a city walk restaurant has a vehicle that crash lands in the wrong.
On the outside of it on the side. It just makes city walk better. Yeah there's already plenty of vehicles bursting out. You know of all the deaths I think that's the one I want. I am in Margaritaville and the plane from sea plane flies over the over the ramp and yeah.
And it would it would it soften the blow to your parents if they if they just describe while he died in a plane crash. Oh God. But if they said he was in Jimmy Buffett's Margaritaville on the plane from water world alive seawars.
Right. He was he was getting drunk at four on a Thursday. What song was playing. Back where I come from. She's written Paradise actually. I was gonna say fruitcakes by Jimmy Buffett. No fruitcakes. Well I'm not a huge Buffett fan.
Well it's about a 12 minute song where he really tells you all about what life is like. I like what life is about. He's got a lot of lessons. Sample lyric from fruitcakes. Oh fruitcakes. There's a part where he let's see he's he says he has all these ideas about religion.
Yeah. Here's the church. Here's the steeple. Religion's in the hands of some crazy ass people. There's also the music video of what you shot at Universal Studios Florida. Yes. And you could see the sun in the background and it is very clearly incredibly early in the morning.
Like well before the park opened. Yeah. They had that they could have the run of the play hours. Yeah. I got to wake up early for the video. Well I'll do it anyway.
He. What what what aspects of this do we need to hit. There's the the plane is amazing. Yeah. The fire dive is amazing and they make a point of shouting out that guy at the end of the show specifically right. Rightfully so.
We watched a lot of these stunt show. We did an episode early on about stunt shows and we watched a lot of videos of stunt shows and the video of water world that I watched today by far had the most legit like who like noise where people are blown.
That was not really the accurate noise. That was more like a woman in the 1920s being offended by something or seeing a mouse and jumping on a chair lifting up her petticoats.
People are always into it. I mean this is one I mean it won like a Theo Ward the themed entertainment association in 1996 also winning awards in 1996. Mike the Rainforest Cafe in Schomburg Illinois won a real.
Wow. That was also with that mall for most rain. We've talked about that. There was a Rainforest Cafe in Woodfield. Boy. And yeah. Let's see the India. Oh Indiana Jones at Disneyland and Waterworld won awards the same year.
There's a question better because I think clearly Waterworld Alive Seaward Spectacular has a chance at being the the finest theme park stunt show but I think probably the biggest competitor and put another one on this list if you want but it would have to be the Indiana Jones.
It's done spectacular in Florida. If you had to if you guys were great and they're giving the out the ultimate the award. We were giving out our own the award. First you call it a real word or a thea.
Thea. OK. Sorry. It's the right. Yeah. OK. I don't know. I think it's taking your Jordan. You would know. Thea. Thea. Thea. Let's call the whole thing off. I think that you would have to probably give it to Waterworld as you are spectacular.
The plane I think tips it over the edge. Yeah. The plane is so crazy which if sometimes it doesn't run sometimes there's just an extra explosion. I have seen Waterworld without the plane effect like there is sometimes and it's sort of like like a guardians of the galaxy.
There's a rocket animatronic but they can also do that if something's wrong with that animatronic and one of the rooms. There's a video they can play in lieu of it. So I'm on video now. Sorry I'm not there in person.
Kids.
We're with my.
Started bleeding hydraulic fluid out my eyes.
You're watching this video rocket is dead.
I filmed this to prepare for my own death. I bequeath my fortune to my aunt my uncle.
Lean out that window at Universal Studios and yell at Taurus. They're humans. Yeah.
Not like me. Not getting any of.
No no no. He's a family first. I mean you know the guardians are a family now of sorts. They're a family unit. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. A couple more movies and he'll put them in the in the will. Okay. More adventures.
I saw the show once with the seaplane missing and then the Deacon just has to shout oh no my plane crashed.
So cool.
Oh boy. What an exciting fiery array back there behind the atoll.
Good thing no one else can see.
Right now we're up high at the top of the floating atoll.
Something I started talking like rocket. I was going to say it's a single voice now in waterworld.
Damn my seaplane. My little paws are screaming to the heavens with anger.
Something that I think that I think is probably very you know a reason why it's so popular is because you know before you go into waterworld the sea war spectacular you see all the headshots of the actors.
And it says what they're from and it gives all their credit. So you know I think if you're a vacationing you know tourists and you want to see some stars you know.
And usually I think I think while we were watching the video you someone made the correct joke that everyone has been on CSI.
Everyone's credit is CSI something CSI something CSI Ghost Whisperer.
I mean these are real like union stump performance. I've heard this is like a good gig to get like in between like movie job.
Like it's like totally solid work and like you get to do your craft.
12 or 13 times a day. Well let me shout out Greg Dolph who is a performer I worked with on a bunch of Conan sketches and who I didn't know till I went to I guess I'd heard that he was in waterworld but I was watching the show one morning.
And and I'm like wait a minute I think I know the Deacon and then at the end he said and from Conan I'm Greg Dolph.
Wow. Oh my god and they they kind of it was clear they might have even said like stick around you can meet some of the cast and I did.
And he like he'd be like gave us some I don't think he took he couldn't take us backstage but he like gave us you know a lot of inside info about the show and he like he clearly loving it stuck there since 1995.
Wow. And I think other Deacons have stuck around but he said super flexible I can call it something like Conan where it's a bit that like we need you in a couple hours he can they can really get Deacon.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Understudy Deacons.
Mm hmm. It is always Deacons in some kind of Deacon waiting room. Wow. So yeah they treat their people right they let them go get those outside credits and Greg Dolph a good dude. Great sketch.
The only other this isn't a stunt show but the only other theme park live show that I would say putting contention for this is of course Disney's Aladdin at the California California Adventure.
I mean I've seen you know right before it closed I saw Q&A with the cast. Oh you did. Yeah yeah I had to sign up for it and I did it early enough and I signed up and the Jasmine and that within that show ran for forever and it was the same Jasmine too.
So I bet maybe it's a similar I always was like oh this seems like it would be terrible for an actor because you have to work so much but yeah maybe that's a flexible.
Yeah I mean understudies for all these parts. And also to have an acting gig that extends for so long and Greg seemed to indicate that like he can try new things he can improvise he can slide in jokes he seemed to be very positive reports.
And I give credit to the people who play like all the characters like all the performers as stunt performers are amazing like it's incredible to see this live. It's incredible to think about them doing this multiple times a day a week a month.
The guys who play the Deacon like they a lot of that show is resting on their shoulders I feel like they are steering the ship in a lot of that and I think literally at the beginning and I think he I think the Deacon the Deacon is why people like this because even I think if you're a pure if you're purely
honest if you're a 10 year old with no cynicism and levels or if you're or if you've got some snark like no matter what you have a way in on the Deacon and the theme park villain is just so fun.
The guy the guy really hamming it up and you know like puffing out that chest and yes sometimes making topical jokes. It's just like I find the level to be confusing sometimes you're sometimes you're kind of laughing at a show like this and then you realize why I'm like enjoying it earnestly to in the way they intended.
Well, yeah like Jean like there's always this character has to exist in every stunt show or live show to theme park it's the genie in that cow in the Disney in the Aladdin he's a funny guy that all the show is this quick the show doesn't start until the genie shows up and then also sometimes on
the Broadway Spider-Man turn off the dark screen Goblin that's a very similar character. He makes topical jokes. He's a heel. He's a heel. But he's yeah he's a he's like an NWO heel. He's likable people would buy a shirt of his. He's not a true heel where the audience fully hates him. They're enjoying his fun 60s Batman style villainry.
The other thing that I found interesting reading about the show. So the Deacon and Helen have mics. They have headset mics. They're saying their lines. Some of the other lines are just like like people just yelling them real loud or they're like like what I think used to be called carts like a radio thing where you would plug in.
And then you play a sound of which eventually replaced by sound boards. But it's like programs like the when someone gets hit by the gut there's a sound effect they can program or if there's like oh there's a line just yelled here and we can hit a button to do that.
And I think at some point with that that sort of refresh in 2014 there is an ATOLer who introduces himself as Sage who was also given a mic and he gets to help drive the action a little of like oh shoot the cannon over there like run get out of there.
You know like avoid the ATOL. Yeah. Don't let the ATOL blow up at any cost. Remember the Mariner has gills so he'll be underwater sometimes because of the gills. You're you in the back are too far away to see if we peeled his ears back.
You'd see a gill there. The world building on this is successful even if the worldwide gross was not.
Did very well internationally. Yeah. He's just sticking up for the movie. They have water everywhere you know. I also didn't realize like some of the ATOL some of the people at the beginning like have to do stuff later in the show like after they fall in a thing.
They might be the guy who does the water they get changed get in the nomic stuff and do the fire fall. So like that's probably also why they aren't live mic'd because they're constantly falling in deep water and changing clothes quickly.
Yeah. This is a weird thing I noticed and I just realized this. So the characters in this I'm looking at the movie IMDB it's like Mariner, Drifter, Gatesman, Forcer, Elder and then Helen.
And it's like Helen's sort of a name. Right. And here's Game of Thrones so there's just a guy named John. Yeah exactly right. It's like kind of weird why wouldn't she have a fun like cool old name or whatever.
The thing I'm now thinking also is that in the Chuck E. Cheese universe it's Chuck E. Cheese, Jasper T. Jowls, Munch, Pasquale and Helen.
Helen is the bird. And Helen has the least fun name of all the characters. Is this a sexism thing maybe? And I'm only being half serious.
I mean this seems like a classic Hollywood thing where like you know it certainly comes up in comedy a lot. Like I had a lot of teachers coming up making sure to go like and make sure to write jokes for the women in the scene.
Sure. Like they do not just make women in your sketches or your scripts wife, mom, girlfriend. Helen. Helen is kind of like that.
So like Helen is a real plain name. It's not as fun as the other names and both Waterworld and Chuck E. Cheese have the same Helen problem.
But very dynamic Helens, the kids in the hall running bit 30 Helens agree. Sure that is a difference. Should we change the name of the Bechdel test to the Helen problem? That's what I'm thinking.
That's what I'm thinking. All the men have fun names except for the one woman. Helen problem might just be the four guys to hash this out. Yeah. Oh yeah. Yeah. For sure. Ladies, we're changing the name of the Bechdel test.
Okay. Well, wait, we all love Alec Bechdel's classic graphic novel. But we have something about Chuck E. Cheese. Helen test could be just applied to themed entertainment. Chuck E. Cheese, the Waterworld. Sure. Yeah. I mean, well, let's look up other.
I mean, if it's not an IP. But also then from there, the character Helen in Waterworld is not helpless. That's true. She is mainly referring to the Mariner and when he is coming. But she's still kind of an ass kick in heroine.
But you're you're referring primarily eight 90% of this issue is name creativity. Oh yeah. That's what I'm talking about. And also, I'm not trying to discount what Helen brings to munches make believe band because she's a force.
She's like just kind of stands there and sings. She's like backup singer. Well, okay. Here. So if you go through old Helen from the original has a guitar. But then you're showing a picture where she's like Joni Mitchell. Yes. She's like she's a folky. But then like later Helen is kind of standing on stage and sings because she's a song.
Like a four year old girl from the 80s is aerobics jumper. Yeah. So yeah. Helen is a big part of the band. And again, but yeah, name wise, she should just have a more fun name is all I'm saying. Let's apply the Helen test to some other stuff. The Country Bear Jamboree. What's her name? Well, Trixie. Trixie is a fun name. Okay. Passes. And the three. What's the what's the word of the three girls named the little girls.
Better look that up. People are going to be mad. I'm going to be mad. I'm going to be Helen. The part. No, I'll say this. I think it's you know, just as an old time sailor, their life, their love and their lady was the sea. Helen's heart belongs to dry land. So I think it's kind of a progressive or at least progressive for a dystopian hellscape where water covers everything.
She just wants to be a regular woman on dry land again. She doesn't want to have this. She doesn't adopt this Mad Max crazy warrior name. Well, I feel like it's kind of the end of water world. It's kind of like the end of Wally where they get back and it's like, well, what will we do with the future now? I guess in the credits, you get the cave painting kind of slides the end of the postman.
They kind of half rebuild society like there's a press conference at the end where they dedicate a statue to the postman and someone has like a television camera on a tripod like a 90s television camera on the tripod.
And it's kind of a little dinged up or like kind of pieced together. And then everyone has either weird lapels or weird ties. That's how you make a sci fi movie. Sure. To know this is not our time. The ties are weird or the lapels are weird.
Blade Runner, Looper, Back to the Future 2, Double Ties, or just a guy is wearing 3D glasses for some reason. Oh yeah. Well, that's how you know he's a goon. Yeah, right. Yeah, he's a lackey to the bully. He's a lackey. The Sun Bonadry. I'm embarrassed that I didn't know. I couldn't remember that.
The Sun Bonadry. Bunny, Bubbles, and Bula. And of course the Swing and Teddy Bear who comes down from the ceiling. Sure. Oh. They all have great names, all fun characters. Yeah, Pass. So that Pass is the Hellen test. Yeah.
Leota Passes. Cool name. Madame Leota. Birds in the Tiki Room. Are there any Hellens there? I don't think this Pass is the Hellen test because there's only four main birds are men in the Tiki Room. And then they bring up all the background singers, but none of them have Jason is smiling.
But they're all like they're just like sort of a big chorus of singers. Sure. They all sing like the birdies. Bird one, bird two. They all sing like the nightingale tweet tweet tweet. But no one has a distinct. Yes, Jason, what are you about to say here? I think a new attraction.
I don't want to tip this too much. Go ahead. But I feel like the Incredicoaster doesn't pass. The Hellen test? Because all the women are just like, we got to get Jack Jack.
We got to help Jack Jack. You say you're saying. But it's her baby. But it is just women talking about men, right? That's the test. The test is an interesting name. It's a names only, Jason.
Oh, it's a names only. And her name is Elastigirl. Elastigirl. That's a pretty good name. Yeah. Wait, wait. What is her first name? Maybe her first name is Helen. Is it? Oh, God. If it is. Listeners might know already. No, the people are freaking out. Her voice's name is Holly.
Holly Hunter. OK, let's see here. Mrs. or Elastigirl. Her first name is Helen Parr. Wow. Prestige. Oh, my God. You were right to bring this up. Oh, my God. This is the craziest moment in our podcast.
Well, can I say something about the Incredi in credit coaster? Go for it. I have not ridden the Incredi. Yeah. OK. I do know that they changed the whole, you know, Carnival Zone to Pixar Pier. Yeah, that's correct.
That's correct. Yes. Was there not a huge opportunity to make that the inside out emotional roller coaster? Well, you bring this up because there's they're bringing they're taking a Bugs Life land ride.
I forget which was the balloon ride and they're just reskinning it and moving it over and they're making an inside out emotional something. It's I don't know what the name of it is yet. It's emotional. But roller coaster is a better title.
I don't know. It just seemed like it's sitting right there. Yeah, it is sitting right there. The inside out emotional whirlwind. Oh, there it is. Pretty good. Pretty good. But roller coaster is fine. But yeah, that's a reach. OK.
Is the girl is the daughter's name Violet? Yeah, Violet. Yes. Yes. Does the name Violet pass? Violet. Yeah, that's a good. Cool. Helen does not pass the Helen test. Wow. Helen. That was really something we walked into. And I guess maybe now.
Well, I don't I didn't catch any names in this thing. So I don't I'm not sure how we can grade it on the Helen test. But there's a there are a lot of females in the alternate version of Waterworld Alive Sea War Spectacular.
I was honestly not aware of until Jordan brought it to my attention. And please do the honors of the name. So I I am a big fan of Universal's Halloween Horror Nights experience. This is a you know, after the park closes down around Halloween, there are all these kind of themed mazes.
Something I really like about Universal is that they get the rights to all the movies if they don't own them already. And so, you know, you're not just going through, you know, creepy hockey mask land. You are going through, you know, you are going through Friday the 13th.
And like it seems from the movies, they recreate things from the movies. It's they do a great job. But they also have like, Rybald adults only shows. And one of them that I guess they don't do anymore was they would change Waterworld to Slaughterworld.
It is a lot of the same stunts, a lot of the same cues, but with like body, you know, adults only humor and burlesque in a way. The man I didn't catch the name of the I'll just I'll call her the Deaconatrix.
Yeah, she's Dark Helen. Dark Helen. Yeah, the Dark Helen saga. Yeah, instead of the bald male Dennis Hopper Deacon, there's kind of like a like a leather girl. Yeah.
And who, you know, who who has I think her mission and she has a like a male slave, but also a sexy schoolgirl dancer. She comes out with a little monologue about creating a female utopia.
So, I mean, I don't know. I mean, I think there may be something problematic about making that our villain, someone who wants, you know, of the female only society and that's rooting against that.
Well, it's just the walking problematic. Yes. Yeah. So we looked it up. It ran 2006 to 2008 three years. We watched it right before this. I feel like I still haven't processed it because there is so much going on in this.
Can I ask, did it say is it Slaughter World a Sea War spectacular still? I just I think I thought of the fix. This wasn't what they did, but I think we should call it Slaughter World a live slay gore spectacular.
Okay. Yeah. Slay gore. Thank you. A dead slay gore spooktacular. Great, did it. I think they also numbered it. It was like Slaughter World 2, Slaughter World 3, but I don't know that they changed anything.
It is bizarre. There's a lot of the same effects, a lot of the same stunts and set pieces, but the music is all like stock, like generic rock. And for whatever reason, the delivery is so stilted of the dialogue.
Like I said, it was like watching like a college sketch comedy group who is not rehearsed enough. It was like a half speed step through. Right. Let's make sure you know you're blocking for when we do the real thing.
And you do get a couple of pop hits. There was a prodigy's fire starter. Yeah, that's true. At some point. And Nellie Furtado's man eater when the deaconatrix comes out. Yes. I really hope that is what she was called, but I'm not totally sure.
But the main thing about it is that, well, there's a lot of warning at the top to let you know that this show, it's even self aware. They say the show is gore and swearing and bad jokes. So they even know that much.
And and it does. So you got you got people you got decapitations. You got people getting shot and spraying blood. Three people die in the narration.
Like someone starts doing the pre show narration. Yes. And then there's a gunshot and a different voice does it. And then there's a gunshot and then a different voice.
So that's a joke. And then right after that, a guy comes out sort of dressed like Tommy Dreamer, like wrestling professional wrestling, hardcore legend Tommy Dreamer.
Yes, I had like track pants on and kind of a loose shirt. And I believe he was the one who yelled the line, the louder you are, the nastier we get. I know it's so funny, like hearing that line out of just like a punchy 35 year old guy in track pants.
You know, I can see getting hyped by that if it's, you know, a jacked stud with no shirt on or, oh, yeah, but it's like it's just some dude.
I'm like, you want me to get nasty, right? Yeah, that's the other thing. It's not explained.
Who is he? Oh, that's the he's walking around with an M16 over his arm. So we just looks like a man who's about to go full falling down.
He's an early in cell. Yeah, the in cell movement. Yeah, but there's no one's dress like the eight colors. There's a zombie, but the zombie doesn't make any sense.
A lot of bodies hanging off of all the body's lines of the atoll. Oh, we were saying someone shot a try shot the zombie and then he started to barf. But it was like the SNL kind of like, oh, yeah, I love that.
Shooting bar. That was actually kind of cool. Bright yellow. I admired the color because I think it's hard to get. I think vomit can just be real olive and and blood.
It reads real. The vomit reads great. It was lit great. That was pulled off well.
But other than that, all of the gore moments, like up at the top of the atoll, somebody gets kind of their arm severed, I guess is what they're conveying and with the chainsaw and blood is spraying up against the metal wall.
And the audience is not the only thing that's pleased.
It's uncomfortable and like not enjoying anything. Also seems like they're watching an under rehearsed college sketch comedy crew as excited as they would be. When are they going to get nasty?
You would expect this crowd and look, there's a lot of blood. There's a lot. I think the blood effects are kind of cool. If you like gore like that, like it sprays a lot and it's crazy.
One man gets his genitals ripped off by a chainsaw. And like if you like all this, which the three of us don't really care for it, it's a little too much if you ask me.
You could tone it down. But if you were into that sort of thing, I could see this being very exciting.
And you would think a drunk crowd for Halloween horror nights would be hooting and hollering during this whole thing. But we watched this video and the audience was like silent.
No, if they had just ran the regular show, like I feel like you can feel the audience leaning forward at that show sometimes.
Like it is not a show. I don't think it's ever a show where I've been like, this guy won't stop talking behind me.
People are into it.
Yeah. I'm sorry. I have a thought as to why this is the case. We have discussed that there is possible confusion in general, though the show is though the daytime show is very well pulled off.
There's still confusion as to what's this and who's the deacon and what's the A toll because this is because it's based on a decades old bombed film.
Now you are going in fresh and seeing Slaughter World. I'm seeing the show called Slaughter World and I don't know about Waterworld.
As far as I knew, as far as I know, this is a new thing. And the plot of it is that there's like a big barracks and leather lady in a boat and she's commanding people to cut dicks off.
I just I think people are not is not enough to pull people into the deep mythology of Slaughter World.
The good guys are these guys like ones wearing a janitor's jumpsuit with no sleeves and the other guy looks like I don't know a backyard bear knuckle brawler.
I get it still. The narration explains we are still in a in a world with no dry land. We are still post global warming, but then there are post leather or not post Nelly Furtado.
Right. So we are we are post sexy schoolgirl. Yeah, no, no, we're not supposed to post like Carmen Electra style like 90s burlesque.
I think if you're experiencing this as a new narrative and you're drunk as fuck, maybe there's some confusion going on.
I have a different theory. I feel that there are not enough topical jokes and I think that they literally need to put a topical joke every 10 seconds to keep the drunk person's focus.
And that would keep them engaged. I my feeling is that if you were to quiz dads after the regular show, they don't know what happened. They can't tell you a name of the character.
They just know it was awesome when it looked like they were going to die when a plane was coming at them. They knew it was cool when a man on fire fell in the water.
So I think the stunts are good. But I think if you're going to do a body show, you got to do it up more. More more fun. More references to 2007.
I think you might be right because this somehow makes less sense than a lot of those Bill and Ted shows, which usually don't make a lick of sense.
No, it's for full context in case you don't know this. There was a Bill and Ted Halloween show also as part of Halloween Horror Nights.
The the the Keanu Reeves film Bill and Ted and that which was full of topical references and very homophobic jokes.
And this was shut down due a Vice magazine article every kind of phobic, not just homophobic.
There was so much so much so much phobia is on transphobic, helenphobic.
Yeah, the the sense of humor of the Bill and Ted shows, it kind of amounts to look, it's Miley Cyrus.
And then someone in kind of a Miley Cyrus outfit will come out and then do a dance and then get killed somehow.
Yeah, like a book of diarrhea. Look, it's Jaden Smith.
And then they'll come out and do 10 seconds of a dance.
I don't think it's even an exaggeration that there would you would see a look.
It's Dr. Evil and then everyone would dance to Gangnam Style.
Yeah, Dr. Evil was in at least one, if not all three.
Perhaps if all every one of them.
If not all three years when Austin Powers movies came out.
Wait, were there only three years? Oh, you mean like the years?
Probably course, because they correspond with what was big in the year leading up to October.
Or in some cases, the three years prior.
That's true. Yeah, there were some wells they went back to.
We will certainly cover the Bill and Ted show.
But when this thing started, I wondered if the topicality would be a thing that would help connect people to the to the world building of Slaughter World.
But in fact, no. So you're looking for now. Let's go back to 2007. So like Paris Hilton's fair game.
Yeah, the movie Juno, for instance.
Look, it's Juno. The impending election.
I was surprised when we made one in 2006 one.
I was thinking like, oh, there's going to be a line of like, this is a worst fight than the Democratic Brimer, the Hillary versus Barack.
Or John McCain versus whatever dirtbag.
This is a worst fight.
Which is when I think of bad fights, I of course think of one of the worst fights.
Hillary versus Barack. Yeah. Yeah.
The lowest moment in politics.
So you're well, so you you know, you've got the guy on fire and you could wish that that was someone you wanted to catch on fire.
Right. Like Sarah Palin or like, yes, I swear there's going to be a Sarah Palin thing.
I guess that would have had to have been 2000.
The 2008 show, she would have been on the national scene for a few months.
Maybe that. But it's like Kardashians are kind of open season at that point still.
Maybe it seems a little ghost to make fun of the Kardashians.
But I think then, you know, they were still kind of a punch line.
If a vehicle crashed behind the atoll with a big crash sound and an explosion, you could say, look out, Lindsay Lohan's driving.
Yeah, exactly.
Oh, Charlie Sheen. I wonder, could you do Tiger Blood? Tiger Blood.
That's a little early, right? No, not until later. That's 2009 or 10, I think.
A little later still. Still at 12, I don't know.
Yeah. 2011.
Here's a 2007 one. My C-plane. This is going to be so expensive to fix.
What is it? An iPhone?
Or someone could yell. The Marvel movies will stop being popular soon.
Little did they know.
I enjoyed Iron Man and I don't need to see him again.
Probably be the last we see of these Marvel Comics characters.
I feel satiated.
Made no sense at the time.
That Samuel L. Jackson scene, that won't come into play at all.
I mean, if we're still doing joke pitches.
That was a bigger bomb than Norbit.
Are you looking at the box office?
I'm just looking at movies. Hey, look, it's the Wild Hogs.
Here come the Wild Hogs.
It's getting jet skis.
When the guy's dick is cut off, you could say, well, you just neutered him
in the manner popularized by recently switched out Price is Right host Bob Barker.
I just neutered him in the manner of recently switched out Price is Right.
The secret of good joke telling is word economy.
Economy works.
Another Seaplane joke.
Who is flying that thing? Sky Captain?
Doesn't he know this is Slaughter World and not the world of tomorrow?
And then when there's a big mess, somebody has to go, oh, we better call in Michael Clayton to clean everything up.
This is all great. This would have been perfect.
You're making me really miss the glory days of 2007 to 2008.
Someone in the crowd holding up their T-shirt, like standing up and pulling on their T-shirt like I got a Clayton shirt on.
I got a Clayton shirt on.
He's talking about me. I love Clayton.
Oh, somebody's got a bucket and they throw the bucket like it's going to be water and like a big thing of paper comes out.
And then two old men come on. They say that's my bucket list.
And they look like Morgan Freeman and Jack Nicholson.
That's great. That would be perfect.
That's good.
Oh, if only we could mail jokes.
Slaughter World.
All right. This is another.
That's genuinely true.
If like, you know how we would work for too little and no pride if to be the alt writers for Slaughter World.
Alt right writers.
Yeah.
Listen, we want all our alternate writers to also be part of the alt right.
That's fine.
Alt writers. Yeah.
Alt writers. No, yeah, we will do it.
We give a lot of sincere please on this show.
And this is one of them.
Let us write Slaughter World or any version of Halloween Horror Nights send up of pop culture, please.
Yeah, I think as we've demonstrated on this show, we're very sensitive.
So you're not going to run into any controversy. Right.
We, you know, by creating the Hellen test, perhaps the most woke metric by which to judge fiction.
Yes. You can count on these fellas not to do anything controversial.
We would never.
Good fun. And people saying, look, it's Michael Clayton.
No ruffling like a fascist hair.
You get dragged for years.
Yeah. And joy. Look, it's Michael Clayton.
And the references will just be 2007 references.
We are not doing any tough thing.
Yeah. Comedy stuff.
Because current topical stuff. Yeah.
People don't want to think about right now.
They want to go back and think about Anton Sugar.
Everyone says I'm bad yells the deaconatrix.
But really, I'm super bad.
Boy, this fight is really out of control.
I need to hide my kids, hide my wife.
When was that? That was around then.
Yeah. What was that man's name?
You want to remember Antoine Dodson and Antoine Dodson?
Yeah. All right.
That would kill today. That joke actually would probably still work.
That would work.
I think Jeannie. Oh, Jeannie did that at the California Adventure Aladdin show.
I see it. I can't hide your wife. He absolutely did it.
Really? Yes.
Daniel. Maybe this show will do two hours on this show because I'll rewatch.
I've seen that show 10 times and Jeannie would do, he would cycle in and out topical reference.
Jeannie did some Gangnam style. Jeannie did the horsey dance.
Yeah. So we won't give away too much of it.
But yeah, I remember now he for sure did that joke and it killed.
I don't think this is the last we're going to talk about Slaughterworld either.
This one's going to stick in my craw. This one's going to stick with me.
Well, maybe one day you'll be listening to a regular episode about, that you think is about some boring shit like the, you know,
you're listening to the Mike Fink keelboat episode and then all of a sudden, and the Deaconatrix rolls in.
Hello boys.
Have you guys thought about maybe making her a recurring character?
Maybe. Not a bad idea.
I think we should soften the music a little more like Steve Miller band or sort of thing.
Well, we got a lot of great options for the future.
I mean, I guess we've already, we figured out our plus up as is, which is to keep it Slaughterworld what during the day as well, I guess.
Oh, forever you mean? Just barely be Slaughterworld all the time.
Much kinder, but much kinder. If you want to know Slaughterworld is a play on anything.
No, no, no. Yeah, because we look, they've already, Waterworld is already kind of irrelevant.
So let's let's build on the promise. The promise of Slaughterworld is like like the promise of dry land.
I'm sure we all need to navigate our ships towards it.
Any any closing thoughts on this this this great franchise or or for some godforsaken reason you want to talk about boring old Waterworld again?
Waterworld the Life, Sea, War spectacular.
Well, I mean, Slaughterworld is obviously the better show for so many reasons.
Big time.
Just because I, you know, no, that's just a joke because of course I don't like the language and I don't like the sexual content of it.
But I do think that it's I like, you know, something that's been around so long.
I would like them to change it up a little bit once in a while.
So I just like the idea that it would be changed up because it has been pretty similar for 20 years from what I'm understanding about it.
And it would be nice, you know, for not that it has to be a Christmas overlay or anything, but that might be fun.
Yeah. Oh, sure. I sure is Santa captured like in the same manner as the pirates dinner adventure.
Sometimes captures Santa because the pirates dinner adventure.
Save me, Mariner. You're my only hope.
I must escape this asshole.
Excuse me.
That is very fun.
And get back to the North Pole.
And they shoot Santa's sleigh out instead of the seaplane.
Oh, that's good.
My sleigh. Thank you.
And he's also voiced by Dom Pardo.
Thank you.
Dom Pardo's ghost.
Good boys and girls.
Yeah. So, I mean, the show is great.
I guess I didn't make this point earlier.
The water itself makes a stunt show 10 times better.
So I do think that like this thing is going to be able to go for another 20 years, 30 years until they truly like don't have anything else to remake because everything's being remade and they will remake Waterworld.
They will happen.
Oh, for sure.
I mean, Westworld is not like a movie people hold and hide.
The Yule Brenner version is not like, oh, yeah, great.
That's cool.
But they like totally remade it for like a hit TV show.
So I don't see any reason why they wouldn't.
Other than the fact that shooting on everything on open sea is incredibly expensive.
Yeah.
Like a straightforward like Waterworld TV show I could see working.
Well, let's do it.
It's all digital.
It looks like crap.
People love it.
Well, I'll say this not to be a downer, but there was an accident at the I forget whether it was Japan or Singapore recently.
I guess I remember this.
Yeah.
I think it was there because I had trouble finding.
I don't know that there were that many articles about it.
There are a bunch of videos of it, which is kind of ghoulish, but the guy on the water skis, I think, like fell or jumped too soon and like banged his head on something.
And it seemed like he was fine.
And another guy jumped.
He's getting a good lawyer.
Let's see.
Who could we get?
Lawyer.
Who's proven great lawyer since 2007?
Yeah, but I think the plus up, I think everyone let's all just have a big safety meeting.
Let's walk through all the stunts.
You know, you don't want to go on autopilot.
You never want to go.
I think just a refresher.
Just because there was an incident.
When was the incident?
It was like a month ago.
Oh, was that recent?
Yeah.
It seems like everyone's OK.
So your plus up is no more accidents.
Well, you know, it's safety first.
You know, you can never be too safe.
You know, even if you're doing these stunts again and again every day, it has to be very meticulous, very precise.
That's why they can cue the sound effect with buttons.
You know, you got to do everything.
You got to replicate it the same way.
And that's hard.
I think it's all I think this is some like backseat driving on your part to accuse the show of not doing safety meetings.
Yeah.
I'm sure they do.
I'm just saying when there is an incident, it's good to just like, all right, everyone, let's go back.
Let's just check in.
How's everyone feeling?
From here on out now, there won't be an accident for the next two years and you will take credit like Trump taking credit for no plane crashes during his presidency.
Did that happen?
Are you making?
He tweeted about like no plane crashes, which Obama also had a good run of no plane crashes.
Bad record of plane crashes in Waterworld every day up to 11 times a day.
That's what finally sunk George H.W. Bush's reelection campaign is they start calling him President Plane Crash.
Never got the stink off him.
Never got it off him.
I was trying to think about I was looking at like universal films since 1995 on which like hasn't there been anything that they could have turned this into?
And I couldn't really find a good answer.
I can see why they kept this.
There is not a good water based property, but I was trying to think of universal films that I'd like to see incorporated.
Maybe just in an overlay sense and it's a good opportunity for new movies coming out.
And I had an idea of to heighten the stakes of it and make it more relevant for a couple of months.
Maybe now the window is passed.
Well, then everybody's seen this film and they really enjoyed it.
Imagine if this time if the Deacon had a different plan this time and he kidnapped a group of horny high school students, the children of the blockers.
The blockers had to break into the atoll to get their horny teens back.
And I guess you would have to call this show blocker world.
So they really missed an opportunity.
Blocker war.
A horny high school adventure.
Horny high school.
That's great.
I would love that.
At least as I was saying, a temporary overlay.
Yeah.
Doesn't have to be skin.
We've been a new is the non joke answer.
Why isn't it a Fast and Furious thing?
That's a universal movie.
It's big explosions.
I mean, yeah, I mean, I mean, that would be awesome.
In Florida, Hollywood Studios at Disney World used to have a show called like Lights Motor Action.
And it was cool to see live stunt driving and like years we did this crazy thing.
Now we're going to show you how we did it.
The only thing is you need so much room to drive the cars in and out, store them, have a backstage area where they go.
So I don't know that there is enough space.
I know that's like, yeah.
And Fast and Furious is covered now with this tram attraction.
Yeah, sure.
But that's that.
What's that?
We have not discussed the Fast and Furious tram.
No, no, no, no.
I don't think I'm not even sure I've been on it yet.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
But the also you wonder about a about Jurassic World that like it's I guess it's certainly covered with the ride.
But you know that you could do that.
Yeah.
I don't know if they have enough space to build that giant robot of the giant fish thing, which was not a robot in the movie.
But that that's a potential.
I don't know.
You're getting we're getting down there with franchises, though.
I can see why it hasn't been replaced.
But also, the capacity has always been hot.
Like people have been like filling up that arena for 20 years.
Like it hasn't as soon as it dipped, I bet people they would have been like, yeah, let's put Fast and Furious in.
But there's like there's no reason to do it.
It we don't see financial people to like it eats up so get so many people out of other areas of park into that arena.
And when they do polls like internal polls or like audience award, like vote online sort of things, Waterworld always like wins those polls.
Yep. Even in 2006 and seven, when the tram tour was plussed up by the excellent barbs and quips of Scott Gardner, still the surveys did not climb and defeat Waterworld alive.
See where spectacular.
That's wild.
I was always a chip on my shoulder.
I was trying to turn the enterprise around.
Oh really?
Oh, his bridesmaid never a blocker.
Never a blocker.
But you these weren't comments just specifically on your tour.
You were thinking that just because you were doing tours, you were going to knock the whole the average up.
I was hoping to dethrone the deacon entirely.
But that's a that's a high goal for a minimum wage employee.
Do you ever think about maybe leaving the tram and go into the atoll?
Did it, you know?
Yeah, I mean, that's the city on the hill.
Putting in a transfer.
That's the dream.
And if I guess, I don't know, I don't know how I could get in stunt shape.
Why not?
Yeah, sure.
Light me on fire.
Push me off the water.
Be like jacked.
Probably.
It's probably just, you know, being I'm not sure.
It's just jet ski comfortability, according to the casting site.
And I have never been on one, but I'm sure I would ace it out of the gate.
Yeah, that's an easy long weekend of training.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Give me give me an afternoon.
Put me on the night show.
Put me in.
Put me in Slaughter World.
Yeah.
Make me make me the deaconatrix is a dick victim.
Yeah, you usually pay good money for that, right?
So to be to have it for a paid to do it instead.
Everyone watching.
Oh, boy, the ultimate.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Well, who's nasty now?
Hey, we didn't get loud enough for you to get this.
Yeah, we did.
Too nasty, even how loud we got.
They didn't deserve this.
I don't know.
A quiet whisper is nasty enough for me.
Jordan, final verdict on on Waterworld Alive, Seaworth Spectacular.
Yeah, I mean, I love it.
I mean, it's baffling that it's there.
It's great that this like, you know, because so many movies kind of come and go and, you know, they just kind of fade into obscurity if they don't, you know, become part of the canon.
And it's nice that this weird disaster of a movie with a crazy backstory kind of lives on through this stunt show.
Maybe the one of the worst or most maligned movies becomes one of the best, if not the best.
Yeah, it's kind of an inspiring, you know, Cinderella story in its own way.
And yeah, I'm sure that whoever it was who made Waterworld, whose name no one remembers and probably was banned from movies after that, could probably still walk by the old, you know,
the old stunt arena and and think, you know, I did it.
I did. Yeah, I created permanent real estate at the entertainment capital of L.A.
Yes, ride the movies.
I'm going to I'm going to wrap up the show here, but I'm going to do it in a slightly different way.
I'm going to give you guys a heads up just to prepare something.
I think in tribute to Waterworld, I think it's only right that we should credit.
We should give our favorite credits that we have from our our that work.
Oh, yeah. The world of TV or Web.
Sure. Go ahead. Get it. Get one.
You get a choice credit in your head.
And I think let's do a rousing full cast now at the end of this this spectacular episode.
So I'm going to kick it off. All right.
Jordan Morris, you survived podcast the ride. Ladies and gentlemen, you may recognize some of our podcasters
from their work in television or branded Web content from the Nissan Juke guy missions on funnier.com.
I'm Scott Gardner. Hey. Oh, you introduce yourself.
Oh, sorry. Yeah, I'm Jordan Morris. It's so great to be here.
Of course, you might remember me as surfer dude from the NBC for weather commercial featuring Fritz Coleman.
Hey, I do. I certainly. Yeah. Hey, I.
Hey, I'm Mike Carlson from the hit Spike TV show Mansers from the segment.
Why you should never get a hand job from a British chick.
I have also been on Mansers to make the CSI of podcast the ride.
And last but not least, I'm Jason Sheridan from Hannah, Montana.
Oh, yeah. That's not a joke. What? Yeah.
I was like Hannah, Montana featured extra in the Hannah, Montana in 2009.
I mean, you got a line. No, I was going to I was going to get hit checked into a vending machine by Miley Cyrus.
And then they're like, you know what? Hey, you picked a cool thing.
But then but then they took it over there like, you know what?
Just stand next to the vending machine. We're going to she's going to hit check this other beautiful woman.
Look at Jason over here bragging about his cool heart.
You're a regular Jack Black over here. Yeah.
Hockey actor about. So yeah, that's the part you're going to be remembered by.
Right. You fell right into my my toxic pits like that.
Yeah. Jordan Morris, an actual thanks for being here.
No, this was great. This is so much fun. Oh, great.
And yes. And then where can people find you or anything?
Yeah, I'm at Jordan underscore Morris on Twitter.
I've got the chat podcast Jordan, Jesse Goh, but also something I'm doing the rounds for is called bubble.
It's a scripted sci fi comedy podcast.
I think if you like Buffy the Vampire Slayer, if you like Portlandia, it's kind of a little mashup between those two things.
Eight episodes, all your comedy favorites doing voices.
You got your Cristela Alonso's.
You got your Keith Powles from 30 Rock, your Mike Mitchell's from Doughboy.
There are all your faves.
John Hodgman, Judy Greer, Need I Go On?
I need it. Wow. Yeah, it's kind of a cool experiment.
I don't know if the scripted podcasts are going to fly, but I sure hope they do.
So bubble to try and cool way to tell a story. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It seems like you had fun doing it. It was a hoot.
Yeah. So yeah, that is it's called bubble and it's wherever you get podcasts.
And if you were in its success, hopefully it could be turned into bubble, a live.
A live. Well, you fill it in because you know the details.
I don't know if there's a war in bubble. It's a there's a sea war.
So it would be a sea war. Maybe that's the new skin we need for this thing.
Hey, OK. It's all tying together. Yeah.
Hey, as long as there's some as long as there's some dick sawing off.
Yeah, there's a son of dick and actually three characters named Helen.
Now that I think about it. Oh, no.
We all need to evaluate our own work.
The film is what do we promote?
All the things we put on Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, all podcasts, the ride.
Find us there. Talk. Give us the rate and review us on the Apple Podcasts app.
What else? I you know, if you if you know the location of dry land, please.
Yeah. Share with us. Hashtag dirt.
I would like to end. Are we all done?
Because I would like to end with one thing real quick. Please.
All right. Let's hope that this works.
The Chimes. Wow. Podcast clips.com.
See you on dry land, everybody.