Good evening podcast listeners. Terrorist Solomon Lane and his group of apostles have stolen plutonium for a nuclear attack.
In response, your three hosts have decided to watch this from fancy leather chairs that jostle them around.
Your mission, should you choose to accept it, is to listen to the boys talk about the chairs.
If you're caught listening to this by significant other or someone you respect, the host will disavow any knowledge of your actions.
This podcast will self-destruct in odds are verging on two hours. Good luck.
This is Podcast The Ride, 4DX edition.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, hosted by three guys who will tear you a new asshole if you call it the Main Street Electrical Parade song
instead of Baroque Hoedown. The song has a name, show some respect and learn it.
That's an edict from me, Scott Gardner, and hopefully you guys agree, Mike Carlson.
I do agree and I think I'm upset. Let me take a look here. Is that in my Apple Music, I don't know if it says Baroque. I think it might list it incorrectly.
Tsk, tsk. Well, I mean, if it's on a Disney album, then it is what it is, I guess. I just know that the original song that it's based on, the meat of it, and I won't do any more, we have to pay for it.
Baroque Hoedown is the main thing by Electronic Music Pioneers, Perry and Kingsley.
Yeah, look at this. Disney's Electrical Parade is what it's listed as here and it's bullshit, you're right. It should say Baroque Hoedown.
Great, I'm mad at the album too. Disney also in the wrong. Jason Sheridan is here.
Yeah, so how long is that track though that you pulled up?
Nine minutes, 57 seconds.
So that's the full loop though. That's the full...
Yes, yes, that's the whole thing you can hear.
Which does not, of which Baroque Hoedown is a piece, but also obviously it goes into, you know, Alice in Wonderland music and Cinderella music and what have you.
So I guess that is an accurate title and all is forgiven with this album.
Man, that was a close... I was really upset there for two minutes, but now we're okay, now everything's fine.
Hey, we're on Disney's side. Hey, in multiple ways, guys, the union issue worked out.
Yes, congratulations to Disney employees getting $15 an hour by next year.
They get an immediate raise and then they get $15 an hour, which is going to be beating, I guess, the minimum wage in California, which is going to be $15 by 2020.
Yes.
So they're ahead of the curve. And all it took was some of the employees threatening to build a shantytown outside of Disneyland. That's all it took.
And the most popular politician in the country coming to Disneyland, coming to Anaheim, shaming them and then dragging them on Twitter for months.
Arassing Bob Iger specifically. Hey, these things make a difference.
I don't think anybody wants to be mean and angry right now, but I think it's what you have to do to...
Yes, get attention.
...change, which I guess, which is also true of installing you as the mayor.
Maybe we got to get Bernie on our side and he needs to endorse you.
Oh, Bernie Ocasio. I want everyone on board.
A Bernie Ocasio dual event to endorse Jason as the mayor.
And let the record show. This is Mayor Disneyland. A friend of mine, future potential guest, Avery Monson, texted me today.
He's like, hey, you know, in the current Golden Horseshoe show, there is a mayor frontier land.
I have no beef with him, but I will be rat fucking him.
But just for fun, just Nixon style rat fucking, but just for kicks.
Just to assert your dominance and that frontier land certainly is within your jurisdiction.
Will he let you use the Golden Horseshoe for a campaign event with the Bernie event?
Like where would the Bernie event take place?
Oh, that's a good question.
In Disneyland, like what's the best venue for it?
You get him on your side. I mean, the biggest is Lincoln.
But maybe you have to appeal to Lincoln himself in order to get permission.
Yeah, I don't know. I mean, there's a venue, obviously, like the where they do the Mickey and the Magical Map show.
That's a pretty big venue, but maybe not the intimacy you're looking for.
You know what? Maybe it's a handshake that maybe it's at the country bear, you know, maybe it's at the restaurant.
You're asking, you're saying the hungry bear.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah. The hungry bear.
Yeah, yeah. Country bear. All they can picture is them on the restroom sides.
The politician in Ohio or I'm sorry, Iowa, kind of like, you know, on the stump shaking hands in the diner is what you're thinking.
Oh, OK. Well, that's fair.
But you want the event to take place. Could it be in the dining room on Haunted Mansion?
Oh, how about this? OK, go ahead.
The phantasmic stage. The phantasmic stage and everyone surrounds the rivers of America.
And then you take the little raft over at the end when everyone's clapping and then you start shaking hands.
So you get off the dock. OK. But then like, does the Maleficent Dragon come out and it says like bad policy or bad government?
And then you and Mickey like slay the dragon?
No, obviously we want the Maleficent Dragon under. It's a big tent. We want the Maleficent Dragon on our side.
You don't slayer, you convert her. Oh, that's good.
You use rules and rationale to get her in the tent.
With policies that appeal to people and their daily lives.
That's a much less exciting phantasmic show, but I get why you're got your point.
Yeah. And if hopefully we can get if somebody who looks kind of like you can pop up in a different place
and then you appear like closer to the river bank, like like a little magic switch out like Mickey does.
And you pop up at the very end and say some policies, huh?
Absolutely. Yeah. I mean, some platform, eh?
No one said you can't have a little fun in politics, you know, little razzle dazzle razzle dazzle.
Well, I'm looking forward to the fan.
Well, no, you'd replace Mick Fantas. Jay Jay has Jay Sherwood.
Let's just go the other way. Jay's Tasmic.
Jay's Tasmic. Jay's Tasmic. Yeah, it represents Mickey and you.
Hey, well, you know, today we're talking about we're going to we're going to have just a little fun,
casual episode here and talk about what we consider the the thrill ride of the summer.
Mission Impossible 4DX, Mission Impossible Fallout 4DX.
I don't know where the colons and dashes go exactly. No idea.
And this is not don't worry about spoilers in this episode because this is really, you know,
I think in my mind, we're less talking about the film and more talking about what the chairs do.
There is one moment that is a spoiler that I would like to talk about, but I will indicate ahead of time.
I'm just saying I don't think it's a episode chock full of spoilers. Yes.
I say I say tune in even if you haven't seen the film and we will certainly convince you to go enjoy this 4DX experience.
If it's in your town, which it is, if you live in Korea or Japan and possibly not unless you're in or one place in Slovenia.
Is that right? I think it's Slovenia. There's a 4DX in Slovenia.
Hey, it's very weird spot. Melania's parents go, go chill.
Go take your mind off everything going on with your daughter.
Melania's dad who looks just like Trump. Yes. Google it. That's not a joke.
Google Melania's father. And it's a big man with a red tie with a stern face.
And it's shocking. It's a very funny thing that cuts through the clutter and explains it.
I'm going to warn right now, though. I'm probably going to fuck it up.
They just start dropping spoilers. Oh, that's fine.
Yeah. Feel free to razzle. I'm sorry. It's Slovakia. Slovakia. Oh, no.
I don't know what's close to where, but they can check it out.
But before we get into all that, I thought this might be a nice place to tell you guys about something that I came across.
A couple episodes ago in the 20,000 Leagues episode with Stony Sharp, something spilled out of the backlog of my brain,
which is that when I was about 10 years old, I did an assignment for school,
in which I made up an imaginary theme park based on then topical events.
And the theme park was OJ land. And the reason this came up, well, I forget which.
Maybe that came up first. And then we specifically talked about one of the attractions in the show,
which was Captain Edo, a Judge Lance Edo themed redo of Michael Jackson's Captain Edo,
which, by the way, since we talked about that, incredibly, we were all together when this was discovered.
We were sent fan art of Captain Edo on Instagram, which was fantastic. I don't have his info in front of me, but fantastic.
Oh, and also me as a centaur. Oh, that's right. Interactive from my experience volunteering at a show. Whoa.
OK, well, yeah, let's give him a shout out if you don't mind looking it up. It's amazing.
CJ Word, Christopher James Warrington. Thank you very much. Check out his Instagram.
There's a lot of really fun art on there. Yeah, indeed. Great work. Thank you so much for that.
Seeing this, you know, this new well rendered art made me think I need to go back into the archives and find the real deal.
All right. So what I have to present to you now is the original.
I mean, photocopies of it, but I have this school assignment and I will hand it out to you guys now.
Now, I haven't like vetted this. So this is a photo copy. I'm allowed to mark up.
Yeah, although I spilled a little water on all the but you can grade it like a like a teacher.
I have a ballpoint pen here that is a promotional pen from the movie After Earth.
Beautiful. I stole it from a restaurant when I found it and I said, I don't steal pens. I'm a good boy.
But after Earth, I must have it. Yeah. You appreciate it more. Appreciate it more than other people.
So I all right. I I strive on the show to not put find myself in a vulnerable position, but I feel like I needed to throw this out and not look at it too carefully, not vetted right before you guys took a look.
And I'm not saying we need to read the whole thing. I don't want to. We shouldn't spend a ton of time on it.
I'm just I would just like if you guys rifled through and just like noted any right details that jump out the front page is kind of the drive into OJ land, seemingly Florida inspired this trees.
It's clearly kind of a swampy vibe and and OJ is up at the top of the sign in a prison uniform like the Hamburglar right would wear, though he certainly almost did not wear that uniform.
I have a question. I don't think I mentioned this on the show. Was this inspired by all the like Jay Leno OJ jokes at the time?
Because you were a big Leno fan as a child. My friends. Oh, is it in here? I'm you since you I was kind of hoping you wouldn't find it.
Well, I have some just set up. Hold on, hold on, hold on. What is he was about to say something?
Well, there's no set order to go through this. OK, you describe it. I wanted more context, but go ahead. No, no, no. Let's let's get into it. You'll hear it.
You'll hear it. All right. All right. Fine. How what grade was this and how old would that I want to say fifth grade, though it could be four.
I'm pretty sure it was fifth grade. OK. And this is the thing that my parents thought was so clever and the teacher.
This is Moldovan and it was it was talked about for a long time. And when I started expressing desire to get into comedy writing as a field, they were all like, well, you'll be a natural.
Right. You did OJ land. And by the way, on the front, a extremely creative and that's a two underlines, two underlines, not the two lines did not form a plus to make an A plus.
But I do consider the underlines a great compliment. It's funny because this does really speak to the climate of the 90s because this is obviously very creative and you would go on to be a very creative adult.
But if you really think about this, it's ghastly. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Crazy. Yeah. But like that.
But that's why I asked the Jay Leno thing, because like it was sort of commonplace for him just to be like, and then OJ Simpson, he chopping up people like he would just say stuff like that.
And that was a joke, even though it was a horrible thing that had happened. I think it reflects a really in the dark time and that I, you know, I blame Leno for making me feel like this wasn't like this.
This was fair game to make fun of. I mean, you know, what I will say is the circus surrounding the event. Oh, I get why.
It was a fair game. But I think I'm not even sure I was totally clued in until that great documentary made in America as to how ghastly the actual murder was.
And I think it's something a lot of people overlooked. And with that, and now that I've said that, let's read. Yeah, no, we have to read it.
We're all did about it right out right out the gate. The first sentence come to OJ land, the most politically correct place on earth. Now, let's unpack that. I don't. I've been trying to myself and I thought about leaving that page out.
We've been giving it to you guys, but I thought I have to just throw it all out there. What feels like a turn, an event of its era and a term that came into the public conscious just kind of mushed together.
It's really unclear. And what I think it is, is something that my dad was railing against. I think it might refer to the fact that racial politics took over the trial. And I think maybe my dad possibly was ranting about political correctness as it pertained to the to the event.
And then I combined it with the Disneyland phrase, the happiest place on earth. You know, there's other things in this document where I do feel like I grasped more of the complexities of the trial. Yeah.
How, but that is certainly not one of them. And I'd like to apologize for it. But with that said, I think it gets less less embarrassed. Well, no, that's not true.
Well, I just saw juice in the ears, a combination of a juice and imagine and engineers. Oh my goodness. And this is all written in like, I think, fourth and fifth grade was in there really like you have to write in cursive.
Which is, I think, for most people, although not everyone in my family, I as soon as I didn't have to write in cursive anymore. I'm like, great. Failed. Yeah. My signature now is a squiggle.
Yeah, I am. Although I'm sure if I did cursive right now, it would look exactly like the curse of doing cursive right now to see if I remember to do it.
There was like a weird kind of do the SATs. There's like a statement you have to transcribe as like a legal thing and you have to do it in cursive. Geez. And it's hook forever.
Was there like a cursive lobby at a certain point or a person in the government or an education that was really trying to push the cursive is like a really like sophisticated way to communicate.
My dad went to Catholic school, like K through 12, and I know the nuns and priests were very much like curse. I feel like people who went to Catholic schools where I grew up stuck with cursive.
Yeah. And my parents seem to find it like a moral imperative to keep cursive alive. But I'm not sure why. Is it something to do with like politeness or with the decorum? It's all decorum stuff.
Same reason they want you to know the right fork for the right knife for butter or, we're not talking about knives, back to OJ. Printing was just the commoners way to write.
Lazy is what it is. They claim that they have common rights and protections.
Feel free to just call it anything. There's also a narrative going on here too. Wait until you just, it's pretty, this is the worst thing I've had to reveal on the show. I didn't have to. I volunteered it and you'll see what it is.
Also the creative team got Jay Leno, host of The Tonight Show. This way we could play his songs and use the dancing eetos.
The dancing eetos. Oh, so they get a corporate, you didn't make your own new version. This is a corporate partnership with the Jay Leno Tonight Show.
Scott, I love how you figured out licensing agreements. Yeah, yeah, yeah. I was funny. Hey, I went to Disneyland. I knew that things said copyright Lucasfilm and I knew we had to work with the Leno film.
Let me back up and just volunteer and say, okay, the whole idea was born from a young boy from a San Fernando Valley. 10 year old Scott Gardner is this boy. He said that OJ land will never be completed as long as.
Well, boy, you felt that way sometimes. I swear that trial just kept going. As long as OJ is still in civil court. That's something to note is that I think this was done in the lead up to the civil trial and the criminal trial was already over.
The die was cast. So if you connect those pieces, and I will in this next part, that tells you my involvement, me a 10 year old boy, then we partner with Jay Leno.
Jay and Scott created the attractions and shows. They also created the layout of the park. I like if a listener could make some fan art of you as a 10 year old boy and Jay Leno working together over like drafting papers or in like what models working models that would be.
I am in a little denim suit. The way that Dustin Hoffman as hook made the kid be in a miniature hook costume Leno dressed me as him. I'm under his control.
So this is this is like a fan fiction right of me a boy working working alongside Jay Leno made all the stranger by the fact that I, I went and worked for ostensibly the enemy of the, of the, of the, of the Leno show what became the Conan, you know, what was briefly the, the tonight show I guess 10 year old me would have been disappointed.
But what I wanted to dream. Yeah, I was the land. So it says OJ's adventure land adventures land I guess there's an S at the end of that. Maybe that's a typo. Yeah, we're now you're into the attract the list of attractions.
Oh, sorry. Yeah. So, so, Enchanted living room is one of the rides. I mean this does for a 10 year old this is obviously a high level of being able to do parody and combining two things. It's a very you can tell that is why people were reacting to it so much Mike and something that I think about a lot is that I am specifically in my writing career a little lacking in the area of topical comedy, and I think I peeked at 10 years old I think if I could get some of this mojo back.
Maybe I could maybe they'd take my packet at cordon. I don't even know that you need to get the mojo back I think you're just bringing that I think we're selling limited run chat books of this right that's what they, it's not quite a book it's not quite a magazine right that's what they call.
I'm not sure nice pamphlet sort of thing I think we're some form this can live in army man we're going to sell like a few hundred of these and this will be the next generation comedy, the self distributed magazine that predated the Simpsons and other shows yeah I think this will be just as influential.
So pirates of the dream team as Jason said that one may be a little less like clever title wise, but it had to get moved down it wasn't in the right. I foolishly listed it as part of OJ's adventures land, and not, is there a New Orleans Square.
Oh it gets classified oh it's in dream team land. It's in. Oh, I see I see I see. Yeah, I think today I would do like dream team square USA I'd get it a little more right, because it shouldn't always be land obviously they they change it up.
Oh, but yeah maybe I'll just list the lands OJ's adventures land, land of mystery. Hmm, not sure that I'd X that that's, that's off the list firm it firm and land from land is what I wanted to talk about next.
Yeah, so Mark Furman. What does it say your monthly show.
Show here, like, you know, Elvira knots they look he's a celebrity. We know we're not getting Mark Furman right. There's nothing about the racism here though.
I think that's a part of it. That's the thing that I maybe wouldn't have grasped back then and thank God because I think 10 year old me is racial politics might have to be deleted from the podcast, not I wasn't a blue I wasn't a racist kid.
Even though the mark for most not really a nuance he was just super racist. But see I didn't all that I know what the time see my collector, my parents were not of you know what I caught was, I saw the dancing egos, and I knew that Johnny Cochran went on these rants that people found
funny and put on costumes, I didn't. My parents I think shielded me from the fact that there was a tape where he said the N word it's gonna time. Oh yeah I mean this is the like God this all of this is the Leno fide. Yes, cartoon version of this.
Which is sort of a good way to say like whitewashing or like covering up the more difficult end of the thing I consider myself, having been brainwashed by Leno, as you as as will be evident in this art of me in the little denim suit.
It is interesting because like people are always like well you know we need to laugh we didn't make jokes about all this stuff but to a kid, it really makes it into like this like not vicious thing at all.
Yeah, maybe no more jokes about anything.
That is kind of horrifying in our current reality where everything is speeding up, everything is just getting odder and odder all like what do kids joke about Trump what do God help me what do kids joke about me to Jesus Christ.
That one's just impossible there's no fun characters everybody's just bad. I think though the the the OJ trial in the way it was presented it was just so much more of an innocent time despite it being about this horrible thing.
And what I like about Trump is that no one stays in the administration long enough really to be this like colorful character I mean I guess Sean Spicer and Sarah Sanders or Perry never but the way that these attorneys right just kind of have like these imagine that the lawyers had this kind of grip on pop culture that they didn't really ask for.
Yeah.
And for me for months for you for years even.
That's crazy. And I loved I soaked up every part of it and cleaning great with great parodies like Darden rail is as Marsha in legal land and Darden rail Darden rail.
I gave Darden the monorail is am I missing I probably am missing it. Where is Cato in all of this.
Is Cato in the back anywhere I'm not sure Cato.
That's crazy. Yeah it was the most kid friendly cartoon character in my mind at the time I knew Cato joke oh Cato is that silly silly guy in the back.
Shaggy from Scooby Doo zoinks OG.
Well, easy fix the Cato cell and it's all the all the vehicles are all different it's all him sleeping at different minutes of the night it's him sleeping to 34 it's like 45 the Cato you could have the hotel rooms like the Cato suite and it's just like this tiny room in the back of the hotel.
Yeah.
I approve you if it was like a Star Wars immersive style hotel like they're going to build like you would have a teenager playing Cato and he'd like kind of come over and try to hang out with you during the day.
Uh huh. And your window with a window be blacked out and you would have a view of OJ's Brentwood. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It would be digital screens instead of windows. I like all this I like these ideas, I would say, I do have to run everything by Jay. Sure final. Yeah, yeah.
But in the but in theory, I looking at yeah he may have an issue.
Looking at the OJ Simpson story featuring a moment with Mr Simpson. Now, I'm hoping it's not the moment I'm thinking of.
But I do admire fourth grade Scott's commitment of using the full official like just referenced in an episode very recently the convoluted nature of the title. Yeah. And now. Yeah. Yeah, I knew it. I knew it then.
Al Cowling reference here California Cowling. I mean, this is great. Like I will say like if you and I met and I was what 11 and you were 10 or whatever you had much more you had more names than I did.
I knew Cato I think I probably knew Johnny Cocker and knew OJ knew the gist of it. I don't think I knew as deep as I don't think Al Cowling's was in my brain at that point.
Let alone to make the leap that him driving the Jeep is like you driving the Jeep in the Indiana Jones. Right.
Him avoiding obstacles and the other people with signs on the freeway are like the dart blowers.
OJ's Haunted Mansion and the tagline here is when the court took a field trip to OJ's house, it was decorated so nicely. Could it be haunted?
This is a reference to when they revamped the decor. Oh, right. To make him a more appealing and to sort of nod to his heritage and stuff. They did a little they like dressed up the house.
I don't think I was very cognizant of this all at the time, but I watched religiously the people versus OJ Simpson on FX like a year and a half, two years ago.
So this is all Al Cowling's took me a second. Yeah. So, OK, so there's a drawing which I assume is Johnny Cochran and it says the Lion King Parade. Yes.
There's also a Lion King parking garage. Did I see that right? Possibly. This is another combination of topical thing of the time. The hit movie The Lion King.
Well, it's spell lion, though. Oh, yes. Sorry. It's L.Y.I.N. King. Apostrophe King. He's Johnny Carrey's telling lies. He's the lion. You were anti-Johnny. I like that still.
Was that that seems like that could have easily you could have worked in the Leno writers room with that.
This is coming on here. You know, it's kind of like, you know, it's like, yeah, that's not the joke, obviously. But you like that would be a joke that I could see being on.
Yeah, there's a way. There's a way to frame that as a way to do it to make it a lot of joke.
I yeah, look, this has a packet. I think I have a packet ready to go. It's probably for the Jalen O'car show.
It's your point. Yeah, maybe that's still a job. Do you think you'd have OJ on the car show?
I think. Whoa, that's an idea. Hey, smile, Bronco.
Jett juice. You like this? Bring back memories.
I mean, wouldn't that that would be a ratings event and all ratings events that Leno and OJ in a car together in a Bronco together.
We're going to try to judge each other's grave in Paris.
Did he did he pass away? I think Judge Edo passed away.
He didn't. I think he did.
If that's not true, then Jason, you're the lion king.
Oh, no, he is still alive. Jason. All right.
Who passed away? You're thinking of Judge Edo's brother.
What? And as I said that, I went, what are you talking about, Michael?
But why would you know that he is dead? I feel like there was some I mean, I'll look it up later, but there's some you're talking about his brother, Captain Edo.
Captain Edo has passed away.
Yes, somebody has some somebody told me some story about Captain Captain about Judge Edo's brother.
And maybe they think that's who you're thinking of. Judge Wopner died.
I just judge has died in the last 20 years or so. Larry passed away.
Yes, Judge Wopner is let's see.
Judge Reinhold is doing great. Judge Wopner dead in 2017 at age 97.
You were thinking of a different celebrity judge. Did they do an autopsy?
There could have been foul play. He was 97. He was posing as I know.
I just think Judge Wopner probably put a lot of people away, you know, I see.
That was a show where you prosecute criminal like murdering criminals on it.
I think he had some small claims court enemies, you know. Well, that's true.
Evil stay mad. So somebody who he forced to pay five hundred fifty dollars tracked him down. Yeah, had him murdered.
Well, let me also let me say the thing that started all this, Captain Edo, of the things in here, I'm I genuinely like the Lion King.
I'm spelled that way and I like Captain Edo and he is the the oh and the in Edo.
Oh, yeah. It's his rotund body, which was he large? Maybe I just think he was because he was in a Captain Edo.
That's replace judge Edo in my brain. I was Captain Edo. No, I don't think so. I think he was a moderately sized man.
I'm trying to think what Captain Edo would have done. What is his journey of transformation?
Maybe he took all of the hate and discord within Los Angeles around that time, the potential riot about to bubble over and turn the city into a peaceful dance party
and made everybody dressed in white and made everyone's vehicles white and magic and glimmering and full of rainbows.
Yeah, he would have just met like put his hand in the air and an angry man would turn into like a wild, buffon haired, crazy backup dancer.
That would have been to burst out of the wall with that's Alan Dershowitz Alan Dershowitz.
Oh, hang on. Dershowitz. There was not a lot of Dershowitz in here, right? No, I kind of missed him. Yeah.
And the other guys who's a Barry Sheck. Oh, yeah. Sheck not represented. That's another one. Sheck tours. Sheck Mountain. There we go. Sheck Mountain. Sheck Mountain is good.
Will be. Yeah. Dershowitz is the oh, sorry. Sheck Mountain is the you are going through the wild strands of a DNA sample because that's like the track of a roller coaster.
You're going through a big helix. Oh, yeah. Sorry. I just had I had to jump on it. You were saying about Dershowitz.
Oh, Dershowitz is sort of like, you know, if there's a Soren type ride where he's welcoming you aboard the Epstein.
But you're like, oh, there's no way for that. And every even the cast members are like, don't don't go. No, no, don't don't go on that.
It's full of famous people that haven't faced repercussions for it. There's all these animatronics of very famous people. Yeah, you don't want to just don't. In the fan art, Leno is whispering into my ear and telling me about this plane.
Don't go near that plane. I know there's a lot of famous people.
And I guess, Scott, also check in your favor. There is a Vanity Fair article from two years ago. Mark Furman slams the people versus OJ Simpson for political correctness.
Wow. So old Furman and 10 year old Scott. Same page.
Wonderful. I think that this I will say that this again for a 10 year old, very impressive. I will say it's not as it already. Excuse me. It is much better than the of course, second gate.
OJ's Vegas robbery adventure. It's much better than that. That one was much less exciting. It was cheap. They didn't have enough money. They didn't have, you know, the vision or the money.
Nobody wanted photos with the nine would be thugs. Yes. Tried to help them bring in. They had to put a lot more money into the Vegas robbery adventure years later.
Plus all those attractions that like quickly opened and then quickly closed. You know, the if I did it experience the celebrity boxing, the prank show, Juiced.
Like, you know, they converted juiced to 3D. You could watch it in 3D at the second gate. Oh, OK. It's the whole maybe this is the second gate is like all it's the entire last chapter.
It's everything post trial and any store where you go in and try to get merch and OJ animatronic bursts out and says, hey, that's my stuff.
Oh, man. Man, we're doing we're continuing the thing you started at 10 years old on a podcast. We're 20. Yeah. Twenty three years later. Yeah.
Who knew this was just the first chapter and who would have known that I would add two friends eventually.
That would have been the biggest shock. Twenty plus years to find it.
Hey, you know, to bring this out and have you guys not just tear it apart and to to find some fun in it, it's I appreciated.
Genuinely, I'm going to give it an A. Whoa. I wrote an A on it. Jason, would you like to grade Scott's on your own?
Of course, I use my after his fingers crossed. I'm nervous. That is also a detail that seems like something I would have like a promotional after Earth pen stolen from a restaurant.
I think I was I with you when I got it. Scott, your your wife, when we were at Pirates Dinner Adventure, she realized we were like either leaving or something.
She still had the pen for what is it called? What is the sexy cabaret show called?
Oh, what? T-Tro Martin. Yeah.
And she like very quietly leaned over to me and was like, you want this? And I was like, OK. And it was you. You're right. Yes, I do want that.
I'm sure it was an emphatic. Yes. What's your thought there?
Was it just like was she just like it seems like Jason would appreciate a free pen? I think so.
Also, it starts working immediately. It felt very dirty. I'm going to write a first off a plus. Oh, my God.
And I'm going to put it so very grateful, funny and underline that because sometimes I, you know, depending on the teacher, you probably knew the better.
I found extremely creative, either very sincere or very condescending.
Yeah. Hey, you know what? This was a very good teacher, Mrs.
Great. That's very nice. And, you know, you might actually say that the encouragement that I felt from this project made me think that maybe I could move forward in a creative fashion.
So, you know, honestly, this this was a an important piece.
I think the next step you guys having seen it is for me to then to send it to the Conan office and to have them revoke my former employment there and have all of my sketches deleted permanently from the server.
Yeah, they were talking about getting a full archive of all the Conan shows up online and your but your stuff is might just be wiped.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. If this if this comes out, they'll realize what a grave mistake they made.
So, folks, rip Wes Anderson Star Wars now.
Oh, hey, thanks for naming one. Look at that. That's a that was a mashup of two properties.
Oh, yeah. Much like OJ land. Yeah, I did a couple of theme park sketches, too.
There was a fan correction. People would send in, you know, ways to the mistakes that Conan had made.
And he had he had said seven flags instead of six, which was a very odd mistake. But it gave me license to run around the back lot where that the Gilmore Girls set was the famous Gilmore Girls gazebo.
And I got to turn it into a miniature Conan amusement park. It was like a Conan endorsed.
I was still using the logic there where it's seven flags, but Conan was the property they licensed all our bugs.
But if you look at all my theme park related comedy, all of the logic I made, I wasted a lot of time adding that up time that could have been used to make the thing funnier.
The licensing had to be clean so people would get it.
Yeah, well, and that's my promise for all future theme park related comedy, of which there is much more to come.
Although not today because we're not talking about a theme park. Not today.
But it's a theme park of the mind and body and spirit. Yeah.
And it employs tricks. There's similar tricks or identical tricks, in fact.
Yeah. It honestly we were going to record something else tonight, which we will likely do that thing we had planned at the future.
But we all walked out of this going like this is can we tomorrow? Yeah, let's do this tomorrow.
We all knew us all watching the movie together.
For the second time.
In a row. Yes. In a row of people from other podcasts who were all segregated by their podcast.
We had to sit with our podcast. You got to show team unity.
And we, you know, that's how the magic happens. You see a movie and you know what? This could be an episode.
I think this is an episode. This is an episode. I think this is thin enough to spin an episode out of.
We're talking just to clarify about Mission Impossible, Fallout, 40X, the 40X experience.
Now, we saw this film opening night. You bought a bunch of tickets and for the IMAX experience.
At City Walk. At City Walk, a place where we're going to be spending a lot of time in very soon.
Very soon you're going to be hearing a lot about that. Start learning.
Bone up on City Walk now if you want to know what the hell we're talking about.
So on a Thursday night we had already seen this film in an elevated setting.
And I think really enjoyed it in that.
But then people were going to see it, how many? Four days later?
Yeah, Monday. So yeah, that's four days.
At IMAX. Now, if you're not in Los Angeles, in downtown LA, there is a place called LA Live,
which is one of the fakier malls ever to spring up.
Yeah, LA Live is right by the Staples Center. It's like, I don't know what the boundaries of LA Live are,
but it's mostly like this couple block swath of land that has, you know, like a yard house.
It has a Carl's Urban. It has like a Smash Burger. It's like...
Formerly an ESPN zone. One of the only other ESPN zones around.
There's a bowling alley. There's a Ritz Carlton right next to it.
Yeah, a couple hotels around in the area. It's like...
Near the Staples Center, near the Microsoft Theater and Club Nokia.
Right.
Maybe it's not called that anymore. I've seen a lot of fun concerts there.
This is the first time I've really spent any time down there.
I was there at LA Live. Really?
Yeah. I really haven't gotten down there.
Boy, missing out.
Yeah, well, I go down for wrestling events to Staples Center and then you go to yard house afterward
and you hope you see Randy Orton eating a steak.
Did you see that?
Yeah, of course. And then a friend of ours, Tim Chang, yelled at him out the window
when we were driving away. And Tim didn't have like a very good thing.
He just was like, Randy Orton! It wasn't like a funny quip or anything.
Well, relevant to Disney interests, a couple weeks ago, my wife and I got a little too drunk
at a Pebo Bryson concert. Did he do one of the...
I don't know if he did one of the Disney songs. I want to say that he didn't.
So, sorry to tell you, Beauty and the Beast is out of the set.
Get that fixed, people.
Should I look at the set list?
I guess if you can.
Refresh my memory.
Excellent. If ever you're in my arms again.
Yeah, yeah.
If ever you're in my arms again.
What are the Disney songs that he did?
Oh, I'm sorry. Pebo Bryson was the adult contemporary R&B type artist
who was the male part of the duets of Beauty and the Beast and Whole New World.
Oh, wow.
Yes. Beauty and the Beast, Celine Dion, and Aladdin.
Whole New World was Regina Bell.
Huh.
Yeah. Which are things that I didn't like as a kid.
I remember thinking, play the one from the movie. Don't play this lame grown-up version.
Oh, the singles version. Yeah.
Yes. Then those always, they topped the adult contemporary charts and in the Oscars,
they all performed together like Angela Lansbury performed with Celine and Pebo.
And it's a very moving moment.
I feel like in elementary school, like they, as soon as those movies hit,
the music teachers bought the sheet music immediately and then like taught us to sing it.
And I feel like they were teaching the arrangements of the adult contemporary versions,
not the movie one. And I would just be like, why don't we sound like the movie?
I want to do the voice of Cogsworth.
I want to do the movie. Yeah.
It's just full of kind of like chimes and like.
I cannot find, for whatever reason, Pebo Bryson does not have like recent set lists on setlist.fm.
Okay. Nobody's, that's on me to do.
Yeah. You have to update it. But I have a December 7th setlist.
And it's 22. He ends with Joy to the World. This was maybe a holiday. Oh, no, this is holiday.
These are all holiday songs. Nevermind.
Not a good sample.
This is, if you wanted to hear anything about Mission Impossible, you've now heard about OJ for 35 minutes.
You've heard about Randy Orton and Pebo Bryson.
Our three favorite people.
Our three other dream guests, Randy, Pebo and OJ.
Yep. So yeah, look, there's a magical place down in LA Live.
So much entertainment. It's not as fun as City Walk or Downtown Disney, but it's similar.
Just that's what you know. It's similar to that. A lot of lights, a lot of stimulation.
Family friendly-ish.
And a very nice movie theater, which I'm not sure when, but in the last couple years,
they have started this innovation of, oh, well, the place being.
Well, it is an innovation center.
Regal LA Live Barco Innovation Center is the name of the theater.
The theater is called Barco Innovation Center, which, again, it's so elementally.
I hope nobody really wants to hear anything juicy about Mission Impossible.
If you do see the movie, which is jaw dropping stunts rather than three guys blathering on.
Yeah. But Barco Innovation Center does sound like, oh, is that one of the names in the big short?
Was that one of the shell companies? Like margin call or something?
It's very possible that it is. Greenovation.
It's like, well, I went to the Barco website to try to get more information,
and it will not negate your opinion, Jason, because the way it is about Barco.
Imagine a way to see, sense, and share the intangible.
It's what happens when big data becomes knowledge, when images become insight,
and when experiences come to life. That's what Barco is all about.
Barco.
It is? What do you mean?
So if you're somewhere and you see images become insight, that was Barco.
That sounds a lot like the Cambridge Analytica website.
I mean, these sound like companies that would be like fronts that the IMF force would be combating.
When we were in the movie, Barco was using these special chairs to scan all of our phones,
get all of our contacts, places we've been, interests.
Oh, we scared our faces for the mask.
Mr. Hunt, you will never defeat Barco. Barco is on your trail.
That sounds like Gollum, but that is sort of what that guy's voice is like.
Yeah.
It's pretty the villain.
Lane.
Lane, right? Not Lurk.
They've gotten really good at finding sleazy villains.
You will find, as we discuss this film, that I remember no characters, names in the film,
and once again, I think that's OK because we're mainly talking about the chairs.
It is, but just for the fun of it, let's see how many you can name.
What's the main character's name? Who does Tom Cruise play?
Ethan Hunt.
Yes. Who does Ving Rhames play?
The old Jamie.
No, it's not for you, Jason. I know you know.
Oh, yeah.
Simon.
No, but you should correct me.
Simon Pegg.
Oh, you said it a little bit. Benji.
Yes, he plays Benji.
Rebecca Ferguson.
Oh, it's Ilsa.
That's right. Ilsa Faust.
Yeah, there you go. You had the last name, too.
I got no last names.
How about the...
I know the name of the theater. It's the Barco Innovation Center, but Ilsa Faust.
How about Cavill, Henry Cavill's character?
Didn't catch it.
I'm trying to remember it.
Do we even know his name?
He's a plumber.
He's the CIA's Lee Plumber.
The bad guy's name is... what's his first name?
I was going to say Jackal Lane, but that's not right.
It's Lane, though, right?
His name isn't Lane.
I don't know.
He talks like a this, though.
Yeah.
All right. Well, I know the name of the band that did the theme song in part two.
That's Limp Bizkit, motherfucker.
Sure.
I started watching part two the other night, and it is an amazing time capsule of the year 2000.
Like Scott's OJ thing. OJ.
Yes, very similar.
So, yeah. So the movie... I had never done 40X. None of us, right?
I had gone to see Valerian and the Keeper of the 19 Clouds.
That's the correct...
City of the Thousand Planets.
All right. Okay. And I was having fun. I was enjoying it, but I was particularly tired that day.
That's something to do in the morning. And I was like, think I got it. Think I got my fill.
And I left 40 minutes in. It was not meant to be a big protest.
I since have finished the film of Valerian and the 19 Astro Dungeons.
So I had experienced it, and that was enough to know some of not only what the chairs do, but what the room does.
And I was impressed. And I've been thinking about 40X ever since. And I'm glad that I did a full experience.
Yeah. I was going to say, I was a little... I don't know if they do this...
So before the movie starts, they do a little demonstration of the room, which scares the shit out of me.
Because I actually didn't know how invasive 4DX was. I knew it would jump you around, but I was like...
I didn't either. So you get like a full themed entertainment experience. You get a pre-show.
Yes.
You get a pre-show.
It's a minute long.
It's a minute long, but it fires off all of the different triggers and stuff.
Which is almost a cool thing about that, that it's all 20 of the stuff.
Yeah. The strobe lights, the spray.
The gas.
The spray, the gas.
So that was the most shocking thing to me. So the seats jostle you around a lot.
You get hit in the back by different rollers or different little fists. I don't know what they are.
Yeah.
There's air guns. But in the front of the theater and in the front of each seat, they can spray fog at you or gas.
It reminded me of a Batman villain trapping Batman in the 60s show where gas comes out and everyone just passes out.
So like there would be the start of a Batman 66 and it's like, we're in a normal movie theater in Gotham.
And then everyone passes out and it's like, it's the Riddler and he's capturing all these movie patrons.
This is what, in this case, it would be the Barkler.
The evil head of Barko.
John Barko by day, the Barkler by night.
Will Batman defeat the Barkler? Find out.
Will the gas spray keep our heroes knocked out for 24 hours so they can't record an episode?
I found the gas spray woke me right up because it was startling for one thing.
But the other thing, and I don't know if I've talked about this before, I have a very sensitive sense of smell.
Like if something does not agree with me, I cannot stop thinking about it.
The spray, the water spray, I think there was one or two moments where it did have fragrance in it,
but the rest of the time it just smelled like old water color like a dead basement.
When all the effects started in that little pre-show, I think, and this is maybe not a quote,
but it is certainly the sentiment that you were giving off, is all of a sudden the chairs start going crazy
and the gas starts coming out and you just go, oh my God.
You were just like freaked out a little bit.
They don't warn you.
There's also strobes in the theater, strobes shooting at the ceiling.
Kind of as lightning usually is what it's representing,
which then during Mission Impossible, during the crazy halo jump where it's a stormy sky, you do get lightning going.
That is fun. I like that.
How do we tackle this in an orderly fashion?
The 40X chair. We hadn't talked about the D-Box company.
Okay.
This is the company, it's a Canadian company, and they installed these D-Boxes at movie theaters around the world.
But this is a different, D-Box is different than 40X.
I believe D-Box is like the chair technology.
Is that right? But it's not 40X.
I think 40X is, yes, so it's a different branding.
But D-Box is like the chair motion and you can get D-Box stuff at home.
So Batman would be in his back cave and he'd be like, D-Box is this, is this 40X, Robin?
They're the same thing. It's all part of...
I'm Googling is 40X D-Box because I'm not totally sure.
I think it's the D-Box motion feedback track.
Okay.
Is what I'm saying.
I have a list of feature films that have been synced.
But I'm looking at websites that say D-Box versus 40X.
Whoa.
Is this different?
I think they're different.
Jason, after my tiki room fuck up, this podcast cannot sustain another error like this.
We cannot screw up.
And also because 40X, maybe there is some similar technology going,
but 40X, which is certainly what we saw, is a Korean company, I believe.
Wait, I'm on the Wikipedia doing all my research.
There's a different... Oh my God.
South Korea. Yeah.
I am a fool.
There's similar ideas.
Oh my God.
But I believe they are competitors.
Wow.
Can you find out when D-Box began?
Well, so I know this.
I think the company dates back to like the 1992, I think I saw.
The first movie that was coded and synced for D-Box was Fast and Furious in 2009.
Okay.
And then they have...
This list only goes up to like 2016, but there was like a ton of movies that have been coded for D-Box.
That's the thing.
I think this is a Blu-ray HDDVD situation.
I think they snuffed them out or something.
Wow.
Or if not entirely, then...
This is like a Tissues Kleenex sort of thing.
I was associating... I was calling the whole thing D-Box.
I was like calling it Kleenex.
I would like it if you issued your apology now.
I'm very sorry.
Okay, but I apologize to D-Box.
I'm glad we've gotten ahead of this sooner.
I apologize to D-Box if they are not out of business.
And I'm falsely claiming that.
Like we claimed that Edo's brother was... that Edo was dead.
A lot of mistakes.
One more.
Is there some punishment for Jason?
Also, yeah.
All coming from Jason tonight.
We'll make him go back to the theater and like really press his face up into the gas spray.
There has to be a D-Box setting that would be torture.
Like you could interrogate a terrorist.
Absolutely.
And you could hang them in and there's the punches, set punches to highest punch level.
And it really pummels you in there.
You could waterboard someone with a drip from the ceiling.
Yeah.
That's possible.
And have the lightning going in kind of a strobe fashion so you start to seizure.
And the gas of course is like...
Serin gas or something.
Maybe less toxic because you don't want to kill them.
You want to get information from them.
Okay, this is very funny.
So 4DX also launched with the first movie in 2009 in South Korea.
Journey to the Center of the Earth.
Okay.
Kicking it off with a bang.
So something about that film inspired...
It's not enough to sit still and go on a journey to the center of the earth.
You got to be shaking around and jostled and sprayed at.
We got to really pull you into the center.
And they kept going with looking at some of the other earlier films.
You got Maze Runner, Ice Age, Continental Drift, The Cruise.
The 4DX technology premiered in Hungary with The Cruise.
Oh, The Cruise.
I thought you were saying The Cruise.
What's The Cruise?
What are you talking about?
What do you think is that documentary about Speed LeVitch, the New York City tour guide?
The Cruise is what I call all the Mission Impossible films.
I like the idea of that cruise documentary.
Like you're on a bus in New York City and the seats are jostling around like experiencing those New York potholes and stuff.
That wouldn't be the worst.
That would be fun.
It's a race through New York with Speed LeVitch.
A lot of kids movie.
I was surprised.
My mistake in research about D-Box also kind of carries over to 4DX, which also has 4DX, Rise of the Guardians, Despicable Me 2, Ice Age, Continental Drift.
I would think this would be very jarring for a child.
Yeah.
Well, I think here's how I believe they play it.
Did you guys come across information about the levels that you can set for your 4DX experience?
I knew that there were levels, but are we allowed to set them?
No, no, no.
By the way, the chairs are programmed by somebody probably in a very audio animatronic fashion.
Somehow, which I think is pretty neat and odd and magical that this chair programming is distributed along with the movie all over the world to all these different countries.
Yeah.
So, no, you don't get to set it, but apparently it's on a scale of one to nine.
And my guess is that an Ice Age or such has just a little bit of motion, enough to make it fun, something akin to your tough to be a bug, your Disney kind of stuff.
But what we experienced, and no wonder you were all so jostled and stressed out, that was level nine.
Do you think or you know?
I know.
You do.
Level nine.
This is a very spinal tap kind of situation.
This arbitrary measuring.
Level nine.
But it's all the way up.
And one thing, I like the social media for DX because there's something about it.
I mean, the company is not headquartered in America, and it's just something, there's like odd little words that are wrong or it's just kind of off here and there that make you think that it's translated.
But I saw a strange tweet that was just kind of like, remember level nine?
Do you recall it?
Did you miss it?
You have not seen it in some time.
That is because it has not been seen since Fast and Furious, and now it is back.
Oh.
And their copy off the website is interesting and odd as well.
Oh, I'm so okay.
I'm not sure what level one through nine starts to classify it as 40x extreme, but nine certainly is 40x extreme.
The most amped up level of intensity in 40x motion design.
40x eliminates the boundary between the audience and the film with motion chairs that move in perfect synchronicity with the movie being shown.
Eliminates.
Do you agree with this or not?
Look, that might be a bit hyperbolic as far as eliminating the, like that's essentially saying you'll forget you're in the theater.
You'll be racing in the streets with Ethan Hunt, which is, look, I did not, I had a coke with me in a cup holder.
Yeah, I was looking at my phone.
And it was still like jostling the coke, but like I could still handle the coke for most of the movie.
Maybe if I had finished it by the point, by the end of the movie when you really get like fucked around with, like, so maybe that would have been crazy.
But no, I don't think this is a bit hyperbolic, but all theme park materials and advertising it.
You have to juice it up.
No, but no seat belts and stuff.
So you're saying we were at level nine last night.
We were all the way at level nine.
I mean, we were certainly, again, there really wasn't much of like warning level nine is starting or like there are certainly no seat belts.
Oh, I do the crank up.
The picture is true.
No, no, no. That's what I want.
I want to dial taking you to nine.
Yeah, they should have a pre video where like there's like some teenagers who are like, man, this isn't that this isn't that scary or this isn't that intense.
And then it's like, oh, yeah, and then there's like, you know, a commercial actor, not me, but a different one like yourself.
All right, I'm in it.
And it's it pays very well.
And he's like got a dialing like turns the giant dial up and then like the teenagers like their hair like shoots up like they were electrocuted.
And then like it jostles them for a while.
But then maybe like the commercial would like merge them into you.
So like they're driving along the road with Ethan and they're like, it's like whatever that marketing slogan was.
That would be a good like warning to really like you would feel what two is like and then you would feel what nine is like you would you could see and you could be prepared for like so Jason wouldn't have had a heart attack like he did last night.
I would like to see Ferdinand 20th Century Fox animated movie about a bull.
I would like to see that at nine.
Is that a 40 X option?
It was one of the 20.
I know.
I wonder if there's so every Mission Impossible screening is nine.
They don't have like a kid's matinee.
That's two or three.
I don't think so.
I think you're I think they deny their one their one sync pass and there's no age limit.
So you could put hypothetically you could bring a two year old in there.
Yeah.
Sit them down in a chair.
I mean I think probably somebody at the ticket counter would say but maybe not maybe you bought your tickets online.
I think maybe you got an age.
Oh okay you have to be at least three and a half feet tall and four years of age interesting to experience 40 X and that's any level but you can pull a four year old down for an afternoon screening of Dunkirk.
As soon on their fourth birthday.
You can go straight to it. Mother mother I want to see Dunkirk.
I want to see those brave boys mother.
If you were a little boy now that is verbatim what you would have been saying to your mom.
Probably.
Done the school project.
Dunkirk land.
They fought impossible odds mother.
You know I think that there are these age limits and everything you know recently you've seen our president Donald Trump talk again about how with all the violence and everything going on probably it's because of the movies and if we how we need a movie.
Rating system and I couldn't agree more I think you know morality is just out the window in this country and I think it's because I think people are getting ideas from the odd vibrations happening in their seats and these 40 X movies and we do you know I think it's distinctly possible that you could be.
I mean certainly that he feeling the bullets on the back of your neck could make you thirst for you know trying out some gunfire yourself.
I think like maybe some of those rumbles could you know do a little rumble on your junk and you know kind of arouse you a little bit.
So we need 40 X rating levels.
Yeah go ahead.
Unrealistic Hollywood expectations I mean you're going to see the final maze runner you think you're getting a death cure.
You think you're going to come out of this movie like I got a death cure I don't need to worry about the mortal morality.
You know I'm going to be immortal I'm going to live forever I have the death cure I got it from the maze.
Because it's broken down the line between reality and when you eliminate the gap between the screen and your reality you get all kinds of crazy ideas.
I was like the chair does vibrate like crazy like that's another thing it does like it shakes like it's big shakes and big movements but there is like a vibration like either like a sharper image chair or like a dirty hotels vibrating bed.
Like that sort of the feeling because all of a sudden and it would come it would sneak up on me too because also like I feel my teeth vibrating or something.
Oh okay.
There were some weird vibrations I think though the most unnerving thing was the occasional punch like where there were certain punches where you would get all of the back but then there was one level where it would just hit the shoulder blades and it was only like every 20 minutes and I found that very startling.
That was awful.
I had to sit up.
I enjoyed this experience. I noticed you doing what I did as a child during Honey I Shrunk the Kids or like you were up at the front of the seat because you did not want to be touched by these invisible robot hands.
No and I would have done the same thing I die get up when all the insects leave and tough to be a bug.
I don't want that experience.
This I wouldn't quantify it. I'll defend myself and say I wouldn't quantify it as being afraid. I just it's like you're getting punched in the shoulder.
That's not a good feeling. I'd hang out with Nick Mundy if I wanted that.
I mean I sympathize with because I do have that feeling but then I think what happened was when the first when the chair first punched me in the back I was thinking hmm you know what does lean into it really let's do this.
So like when that happened to me I was like I'm in it. I'm going to get over my eye because I did I flashback to Honey I Shrunk the Audience and even the Bugs Life and then any other 3D movies that would like kind of fuck with your legs or your back or touch you.
And I was just like I'm in for it. I'm in for I was trying to position. So this is another thing we haven't talked about.
It shoots air blasts. There's two holes by your head and it shoots air blasts constantly especially in a movie with guns. So I was trying to like position my head in the perfect way like I wanted to try to get the optimum experience because I noticed I was leaning sort of in my seat and I got hit right in the back of the head with a blast of air because I was leaning sort of toward the right.
And then I was kind of leaning up and I wasn't getting punched as much so I was like no I'm going to sit and put my head right back in between the two holes and I'm going to let my back be brutalized during this whole movie.
My head was if I was sitting up straight along the back my head was getting like bounced around like yeah the all these descriptions make it sound like we did not like this.
Yeah. First time those air blasts happened I found those very invasive. I was like oh that's like what would happen if you were being publicly executed like it was a like these giant.
I was like I was really not prepared for that. That was one thing I did not like the most.
After like the first 10 15 minutes I was like there's another two hours and 40 minutes of this movie like.
Yeah I would I also like I would think like OK because we knew we've suddenly seen the movie before which honestly it might have been more fun or crazy if we hadn't seen the movie because then I'd be like oh there's going to be a lot of guns in this scene and then it was like.
So I would know at least that I was about to be shot in the head with a bunch of air.
We could prep for all the major sequences and get ready for what we knew was was coming which which you can't do and I think it's what makes that opening demonstration so fun is that you don't you really don't know what's coming and it's so much immediately more intense than what you think it's going to be.
The chairs really rise up and also what a visual when you I'm glad we're further back than the one that I did before.
So getting to see a whole room of chairs getting jostled around is very crazy and a neat visual for sure.
Yeah I think we were all looking at each other just like giggling because we're like yeah we were seeing a lot because I really I truly didn't think I thought like the bugs life movie doesn't do the chairs aren't that crazy like.
And honey I shrunk the audience the chairs don't move like that so I was expecting a standard sort of theme park experience but this was a yes much more aggressive.
There's a lot. There's a lot of stuff and it's not just action as you guys know there are parts where you're you like tilts along with a camera pan.
Yes you're drifting to the left you can have this little drift.
There's a thing and I was one like I wanted to know I'd love to get the guy who or a girl who programs this because it's not a set like it's not a set sometimes the thing moves with the vehicle sometimes it moves with the person running sometimes it moves with the camera.
Sometimes it moves sort of to the music or the score but it's not uniform. Yes the whole way around there is a constantly shifting narrative voice of the chair and you are not the same POV for even two seconds in a row and is an anal theme park consistency person like myself I was like well that's not now we're just imitating the camera but we're not there's no action on the screen.
I found that however consistent with attractions like the new Kung Fu Panda or Shrek 4D 2 it's like you're feeling the bump as the donkeys run along a bridge.
Yeah or or now you're in this now you're feeling what Shrek is feeling that I think that I think all of these kinds of things jump or it's more Shrek 4D than it is star tours where you have a consistent vision and where you are.
Yes I think one of you were very quick to remark like these chairs are like the amped up version of the Kung Fu Panda chairs. Uh huh. Uh huh. Because that had some like there was a lot of floating on water stuff there. Yeah.
And you had that in this too there's a few boat sequences or there's one boat sequence there's a long helicopter thing where you're kind of like following the helicopter and I thought that was very cool the like drifting.
Yeah without spoiling I mean if you've already seen the film there is a there is a ton of I mean we could say that this the helicopter scene is like one of the best things you've seen in a movie theater in the recent past. It's wild.
And the nine was amped up all the way to like nine plus. Yes. I at that point like there's a ton like I remember when I was young and I went to my first like concert which is cool it was Green Day and I was so stressed out because I was raised to be fearful of everything.
So when I went I was going alone with my friends to the Aragon in Chicago to see Green Day in a mosh pit and I was stressed out about actually now to think about it that might have been my second concert.
How old are you?
Foo Fighters. I don't know too old 15 some 14 I mean I had seen like the Monkeys or something but going alone to what was like a modern band.
You sure you would actually quantify it as a mosh pit?
Green Day I would.
Really?
So Foo Fighters there was a little moshing going on. This is Foo Fighters. This is after color and the shape this has learned to fly era. But Dave Grohl is still a young man he climbed the balcony of the of the Riviera.
But so Green Day. So I knew the crowd was like kind of like you know it's sometimes mosh. Green Day even back then during the warning tour there were still a lot of punks. It was before American Idiot and they had refreshed the audience with a bunch of young kids.
So there were a lot of punks still wanting to mosh pit and we were up front and I was just so stressed out about the thought of it happening that I remember feeling like beat up for days even though I hadn't moshed or whatever.
So I've tried over the years to like not be stressed out in situations where I feel like I've lost control.
So what I'm getting to is that once this started like beating me up I feel like now as a 34 year old man I get comfortable in it and then I start to go well can't this thing go any faster or harder? I start going the other way with it.
I see.
Where now finally I'm like I don't know I don't really know exactly what I'm saying.
You wanted level 19.
That's what I'm saying. I wanted level 19 so I think it's all just like making up for me being a scared youth. So once I get jostled around.
This is still the pattern though is that you begin experiences with fear and once you're in it you just want more.
Yes.
Which is what like a sitcom scene would tell you about getting on a roller coaster.
That's true.
Or whatever.
So yeah.
What a nice lesson.
It was a nice lesson that sitcoms teach but yeah it was fun. I liked nine. I liked that nine level. It was insane.
Oh you know what I'm thinking. This is the this is the moral of the film parenthood is what you have learned.
That life is like a roller coaster and you just enjoy it.
You have a lesson I need to learn too. Not about life. OK. The actual roller coaster part is what I need to learn.
I got to say the way you guys think like looking at the list of 4DX movies what do you think is the funniest example like movies that have been 4DX.
Oh I get it. I got to find it. I got to know one is Grimsby.
The other. Oh God. Where did it go.
Now you see me too.
Now you see me.
There too. I would love to see. I love that. Now you see me movies. I would love to see them in this.
Frank and Weenie less so kind of a weird one. Yeah there's also some weird like like you were saying Valyrian.
There's also some weird bombs. Independence Day resurgence. Awful. I would have liked if that 4DX chair propelled me through the ceiling out of the theater.
Yeah there's a lot of movies that were like genre action movies with like a lot of subtitles or colons in them like the Mortal Instruments colon city of bones or Percy Jackson colon sea of monsters.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Amazer under the death cure. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. It's perfect for and 4DX itself adds a colon to a colon movie.
They should have they done old movies that they've like re put like that use the technology for like yes that would be a good they have.
I think I saw episode one maybe Star Wars Jurassic Park 3D. Pod race.
Yeah. Yeah. That's the way to turn the tide back. Yeah.
Towards the prequels that would get everybody convinced the peanuts movie cranked to nine or the Angry Birds movie.
Oh man if the chair can make you feel like you're being pulled back and launched like one of the birds.
Incredible legend of Tarzan is a pretty funny one.
Yeah. These films that aren't and they aren't remembered by anyone and you get to learn from this list about Chinese films that you've missed like the White Haired Witch of Lunar Kingdom.
Wait that's the subtitle of Valerian isn't it.
Hmm. Valerian and the White Haired Witch of the Lunar Kingdom.
And the four realms.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean so I was thinking like I was thinking because the camera moves like is there is there a movie that's not an action movie that just has amazing cinematography that all it is is just we're experiencing the camera moves like Koyana Scrooge.
Sure touch of evil. Yes.
Or the player Children of Men is a nice long tracking shot that's very like not action never use the chairs for the action just use it to experience with like Chiva the DP of Children of Men or Gravity how he places the camera and moves it along with the shot.
Yeah. Another Orson Welles project one of my very the third man you could be in the Ferris wheel with Joseph Cotton and Orson Welles.
I think this is a good. Well 40 X for film buffs is clearly a very I need to innovate. That's that would be lucrative. Yeah. Doing all of Barry Lyndon.
Yes.
I gotta say though I think one of the weaker parts of it is the glass of the 3D glasses. I thought there was some decent like depth in this one of the 3D. But and there's a lot of very brightly lit sequences in fallout.
But there's a lot of stuff in catacombs or tunnels or garages and it does look a lot darker. Here's what they should do because because the best 3D as far as movie wise is is the city walk IMAX.
Okay. If you're seeing a 3D movie which is still not like the optimum way there's no they haven't perfected yet but some some of the movies we've seen are pretty good like Guardians of the Galaxy 2 I thought for whatever reason looked great in 3D.
Yeah a lot of bright colors a lot of fluorescent colors. Maybe that helps. So I think that screen is very bright and it's very big. Yeah. Dr. Strange looked good too. Yes. A lot of that a lot of that Marvel has a lot of CGI goop in all these movies and that plays well in 3D on a giant screen.
But it's very well lit and it would be nice if you could get that screen but with 4D technology if they could combine IMAX and 4DX. Yeah. That might be the optimum movie going experience. There must be places where that is the case.
This was kind of a smaller theater maybe but I bet where I bet it would where this is taken wing a little more like in Thailand or Vietnam or South Korea or whatever. I'm sure there's like oh I even saw on the website there are sizes of the of the theaters.
So you could do premium level 9 extreme. They have it all the way up to the top. That's what I want. How long. I've never turned it off and we're at one thirty three and how long were we doing tickets 15 minutes. Yeah. So we're an hour 15. Okay.
I'll jump back in here. So I'm going to make a bold statement about this. Oh okay. I have to say I think this is if not one of the if not the best one of the best like screen attractions I have ever experienced.
Now that is tempered by the fact that is I saw a full movie but honestly if you went to Universal there was an original like movie with like the cast of whatever like let's say they did a mission impossible like an original five minute thing with the seats cranked to eight or nine and you're whipping around and all of this stuff.
This was so much more satisfying than like the fast and furious ride or whatever fury. Yeah. That part of the studio tour or the King Kong studio tour part that is the solo you know its own attraction in Orlando.
Like I honestly kind of I don't want to see everything like this but this is like a next level to me. Yeah I think maybe I feel like I've heard that the Fast and Furious also released in level nine was was really well done.
I didn't see that this mission impossible was fantastic. We saw with people who were complaining a little about ready player one. I didn't love Valerian this way but I think a great movie that's perfectly equipped for this with a lot of car chases or motorcycle chases or
whatever it is. I think the right combo. I was surprised how much I loved it and how much it's teetering on that fun theme park line where it's a little stupid. You're maybe looking for the word stupid. Do I not like it. No I think this is stupid in the way I like. I think this is the worst. I totally agree. I feel like we've been like slamming or complaining because those moments are more fun to talk about than really. I mean that that helicopter sequence was like they die.
I'm not kidding. That was like better than any like new theme park thing I've done in a little while. Yeah. By the time we got to the helicopter because like there were certain points when I went this is OK. I like this but for sure I think we crossed paths and going to the bathroom and I was like this is so I didn't know what I say stupid. I said something along those lines. Yeah.
Or whole layer. I said this is hilarious. That's the word more than stupid. Yeah. We were laughing so funny. Yeah. Like getting sprayed in the head and like shot with air and like I kept saying theater loud. Oh my God. You keep you laughing so much. Yeah. Everyone was to like everyone was there was a couple next to Mike and I.
That's the other thing you're paired off in seats and on the website they refer to it as the love seats like tiny couches the couple next to us. I feel like we're also like having a blast. Yeah. We're also startled when like stuff. Yeah. And they had not seen the movie.
They had not seen the movie. Every joke hit with them and they loved it. Yeah. Yeah. Do you think seeing Mission Impossible fall out the first time would work. I think for sure it would work but I feel like I would have won like now let's go see it so I can look at it a little more. Yeah. And not get beaten up while it was happening. I was glad because I mean I think this easily my favorite movie this summer. Yeah. Oh yeah. I think that is in a while. It's like hitting me in a dark night.
Yeah fashion probably because they have a similar vibe with that some scenes are IMAX and it's all very real and he's on the top of a very tall places and and I don't I haven't the I didn't like love the last Mission Impossible as much. I like this. I don't know. It feels this this franchise feels like the Dark Knight series and that like you know some are really pretty good and then others are like masterpieces.
Yeah I mean I I was just this is how annoying I am. Yesterday I was just probably yelling but I was saying to Lindsay I go do you remember seven years ago I kept talking about how good Mission Impossible is and how everyone's saying how good Mission Impossible.
She's like yeah it's true you did. I remember you were confused when I was like Mission Impossible 4 is coming on. She was like why do you. OK that's fine we'll go see that but why. And she's like yeah you're right. Everyone now is saying all the Mission Impossibles are great.
So I do think that hit like snobs and elitists a little more lately which I might even include myself in. You're saying I'm more of a common man who enjoyed working class Midwest.
Well you you I think you like you like passionately love a lot of pop entertainment and comic that's true worlds. You're like a head of things that other that everybody else starts to love. Thank you. I think so. Wrestling too. I think like that's true too.
The wrestling you've been going to is like having like I feel like is building in cool cred and you've been out of the game. I'll say this. I was a fan of Jason too ten years ago and now everyone is. You beat me too.
Yes an early adopter of me. And now I am like a mummy's curse that you cannot shink. You set me up for the joke. Yeah. What was I. Oh I think like looking back on the Mission Impossible I thought like number four.
I feel like they were that one had the added bonus of oh Brad Bird is directing this and that has a lot of crazy stunt pieces in it. I think but there was also like the vibe of the movie. They're like well they're setting up Renner to take it over.
They're setting up Renner and then they're like we're going to make another one with Tom Cruise and that one I was like well how are they going to top the last one then rogue nation was also very satisfying and then this this is just like next level.
I think again I don't want to spoil anything but there this picks up a lot of characters and then some threads from the other movies and it nails it so much better than Spectre did because Spectre tried to do that too and did not stick the landing.
That's fair. I mean it's the best spy franchise to certainly been more consistent than James Bond.
And and more than born and I like both of those franchises too. I'll say this I also felt like just building up like the characters and the motivations and this. I thought this was a better payoff that Avengers Infinity War and maybe it's because they weren't selling it like that.
That's a different I can't know I wanted it. We can't just review movies on this podcast right now because I we could have an argument about Avengers Infinity War but Jason your biggest problem with Avengers Infinity War is that it made you too sad.
It's upsetting. You were too sad by it and you don't like to feel sad. I'm just a viewer of a film who can that can that's a valid opinion if that's how it made you feel.
But I'm just saying you know what didn't we if you don't think that being sad should be part of that experience. If I wanted to be sad I'd watch that god awful looking Aquaman we saw a trailer for. Hell yeah.
My man that's from Justice League though. I just a couple of quick things I had written down. There's a couple on occasion something would happen that was different like like we're talking about effects and a con occasion like and this is a spoiler but something would happen where just let's just say a character got a jolt a sudden jolt.
And all of a sudden I get like a like on one side of my back I get just like a like a prolonged like punch essentially and like it lingers there for a while like whoa and there's a section where somebody somebody gets hit by something and like it feels like the corpse the body not corpse rolls over my back essentially.
Like there's a couple like interesting very under that was a nervous and I like that but then for the rest of the movie I was also going like what other tricks do you have for DX. So then like there's a scene where somebody is getting choked and I was like kind of like no I hope nothing like pops out around my neck during this because it was like surprised me on occasion with something.
So then I was thinking like maybe it's got one more like leg shackles or something like oh they did the snakes they did the snakes like honey I shrunk the audience they did like they got your legs at one point you may have stepped out there were I was at your legs.
For what that was the thing I was most scared at it with honey I shrunk the audience.
I did it I forget what oh wow it was I left during the talking a lot. Yeah you guys supposed to say oh my gosh I missed I literally missed the one thing that maybe would have like brought back a horrible memory of me being at Epcot Center when I was six and go yeah I don't like the mice around my feet.
Thank God there's no PlayStation one looking lion popping out of the screen. Yeah right.
What is this. There's no snakes in the film. Oh it's that scene where the professor releases all the mice into the theater in the Mission Impossible when Benji releases all the mice.
Ethan Hunt is at the Spy of the Year awards. Save old Ethan.
Oh man. The flubber got loose.
I will you're you're also there is there specifically that somebody gets stabbed and then you know that's what I was saying earlier I was trying to make me say out loud why we get stabbed.
Yeah I was thinking so yeah I was trying to figure out like what what else is going to come up that nothing really did but I was like there's got to be something they're hidden like another surprise they have well he of course Tom Cruise does a stunt he jumped from building to building and he broke his ankle
doing it and I was a little worried that a sledgehammer would pop out of the chair inspector gadget style smash my ankle into pieces.
When he did that jump in when we saw the first time I feel like people went huh and this time I think everyone went huh but also because you you feel it.
Yeah you got jostled so hard. Yeah I feel like as much of a daredevil as Tom because I got I was in a chair that tilted when he did the jump.
I was in a chair that shifted forward and wind was blowing at me when he did the jump from the plane. I feel covered in terms of skydiving parkour say okay here let this is the hypothetical though and I was thinking about this and this is only tangentially related but it is we're talking about.
Like say you were now cast in Mission Impossible 7 and you're on the IMF team and you have to do like would you ever be able to do any of the things this 56 year old man is doing.
I would get thrown through a plate glass window. Would you seriously want that? I'm being saying like. If I could have the proper training and safety people and all that stuff.
And let's remember the training for most stunt men is you just do it. There's not a lot. You go through the glass. I think because adrenaline kicks in when you're performing anyways and just knowing I'm going to get to go through I'm going to be able to tell people I went through a window.
I think that's a double shot of adrenaline. I just want I'm just wanting to clarify with you specifically because when that thing started I was worried about your health during that in the chair.
I think I there was a lot of shock but there was delight. It's just hard to convey delight and oh my God.
I think I can do the running. I think I could do like a very small building to building jump.
Really if I have the wire on, which he did, which he did. Mike does this thing where I don't know very low cement walls.
I do. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Go like I think I could make this jump and I do. I see says please don't. I do that in Indiana Jones when we're leaving the exit. There's like a set of six stairs.
I go you think I can go get up all these stairs in one jump and she's like do not do that and then I will and then I'll be like I can still jump pretty good.
This is the most like kid and mom discussion. Yeah. Oh yeah. I mean I'd be willing to try a number of things but I think I'd be terrible at it and most of my workout stuff is low impact and yoga ish because of like I get very red in the face.
It's kind of a red. It's not as bad as it used to be when I was a kid but like running laps in middle school or whatever I'd get just flush red which is very uncomfortable and I know that's what would happen to me.
There is a I have a vague feeling of for some reason mentioned this on the podcast before but there is a video a Funny or Die video called the Prairie Children.
One of the best funny die videos done by Ryan Perez our past guest and I also another past guest Dave Ferguson. He and I are like tussling in it like we're like little house on the prairie kind of like rough and tumble brothers and we're in like a dry patch and we're like we're like
tussling and this shot went on for a pair of approximately 25 seconds and I was beat red sweaty out of breath by the end of it and if you look up this video and you see what caused what what made me be like dead deaths door.
Yeah, it makes me think I couldn't do the bathroom stunt scene. I couldn't burst through a mirror. I was when you were saying that I was like if you had to do the helicopter with like Tom so like it's you so imagine the helicopter scene but it's like Tom on one of the legs and you on the other.
Your face would be like so bright red like they'd have to digitally take the red out of it and post. Yeah, it'd be like yes absolutely. It'd be pretty clean and they could just select one color right right form as a green screen, just be bright, the brightest pink possible on a man's face
that had been nice precedent when Justice League had to CGI Henry Cavill's mustache. Was it for this mustache so maybe why do we have to have a mustache for this people bring up because he's a because he's a prick in the movie.
And I think he looks kind of like a prick like they may actively make him look like a dick. My theory is that Tom wanted to make sure he looked different than him, and now that they look so similar but like they're both handsome guys.
So I feel like Tom was like he's got to have a mustache because I will differentiate. I think okay so Mission Impossible seven, we usually pitch rides but let's pitch an idea.
Maybe Ethan Hunt has three sons that he just found out about. And he has to take the three sons that he separated from the IMF. He has to take his three sons on vacation but the vacation turns into a whole mission, and maybe he takes them on vacation to, you know,
a theme park of some kind. Maybe we have to rescue the IMF team, sort of like a new x men old x men. Okay, that's fine. That would be good.
Because they went to see a movie at the Barco Innovation Center, and they were gassed. And the Barkler released his gas that you thought was just a gas simulation but it's real gas.
I mean the apostles are still out there and God knows what sort of twisted plans they have.
And we have to do the halo jump into to get into Epcot Center undetected. And then Jason has to do the halo jump but it's the halo top ice cream that he got.
I've never had that. Is it good? It's okay. I mean some people have a problem with like kind of diet stuff because it tastes a little off but I always think as long as it tastes 80% like the other thing, it's pretty good and obviously low calorie.
We get captured by Lane Jr. and he's gonna execute us all but then he hears that fun conversation about ice cream and he's like these guys are alright. And we all share ice cream together.
That's a good finish. I was gonna say like he also. We eat ice cream for 70 to pad out the rest of the run time. 70 straight minutes.
I was gonna say he tortures each of us with our worst fear and of course he puts you on a log flume ride with a big drop.
Or a 50 foot drop. Like a mid tier.
He puts me in a mosh pit with teens. With rowdy teens.
And he would also, for me he would take a giant animatronic that doesn't belong and have been closed to space. What's the biggest animatronic?
Maybe that's why, in Jurassic Park you're in include. How big was the old Kong?
Well but I saw old Kong every day and I had no problem. I loved seeing him. Yeah.
I did my soul well every time I smelled that banana breath. Really a precursor to 40X technology. The King Kong banana breath. Much respect.
Jason what don't you want to encounter when you've been recruited on the IMF team?
An empty cupboard.
No! Punches everyone open.
Jason I've emptied your cupboard of treats.
God fuck. That joke threw me off because I was trying to think of a joke about emotional openness with no irony attached or something.
And now you've knocked you. You'll watch me eat the treats that could have been yours. Oh but there's lots you can share. I'm little. I don't need that much.
Your mission should you choose to watch. No he wouldn't. That was just him being a jerk.
Oh yes that's fun. That's a fun thing. Actually they were right on the line using that gag. I feel like a couple characters said.
Oh a lot of characters say your mission should you choose to accept it.
The movie also they started shooting with 33 pages of a script and I feel like you could tell with some of the dialogue that it wasn't.
I didn't say it didn't work. I'm just saying some of them some of the lines felt like well this is this is a good first draft for this line.
This conveys the emotion or the plot necessity. But I found Alec Baldwin and Tom Cruise on the runway very moving.
I was shocked. Moving? Yeah.
I'm trying to think of a here I don't know if you said your worst fear. I said a mosh pit when I was 60. But yeah that's not I've gotten over that. I love that now.
Help me out with the end of this but I think we haven't talked about the masks being deployed as possible against you.
What if you when you got dropped into Epcot Center and you met your best gal Minnie and pure per usual she's hugging you grabbing at you pawing at you.
And then she takes off the mask and is something else as another big character. Oh like the bad one.
The alien from Alien Encounter. Sure. Minnie's actually the alien. I don't know what's a similar size. If it's Ursula or I like Ursula I wouldn't mind a hug from her.
You wouldn't mind being pawed at by having all tentacles. I would kick her out of bed.
What if the Eric Idle journey into your imagination took off the mask and it had been Dreamfinder this whole time. Well that's a good thing.
No we're all just like what have you been doing for 20 years. Why were you lying. Why. What.
He walks away. He does like the walk away from camera and the mission impossible theme comes on and you're like what what is happening.
Why do you just describe the confusing thing. Maybe not a terrifying thing. Guys what we're doing right now is mashing up a franchise with theme park lore which once again if you told me
that's what I'd be doing with a couple other weirdos. If you told 10 year old me that feverishly working on OJ land that the fan fiction would never continue or never cease rather and that people would be listening to it for some reason.
Although in this case maybe they bailed. They might have bailed 10 minutes ago when we said what if we were on the IMF team. Yeah that was a self indulgent idea from me. What if it was us as the stars.
Although we do that a lot. We try to inject ourselves into most things on this podcast. So it's a pretty I mean what podcast is not about the host. Sure. Podcast. Maybe there are some and maybe they're better.
But this one is lazier and that's the way it is. That's true. I'm gonna bet there's some religious podcasts that are primarily about numero uno Mr. J.C. Someone takes a backseat. I feel like you're doing a Christianity podcast. You're like well sure.
I'm always gonna be number two on the Patreon to Jesus Christ. But what if Jesus Christ took a mask off and he was Lane the whole time. That is just like Lane.
What cursed to be you not blessed. Why does he sound like a troll or a pirate. He sounds like Emperor Palpatine or Senator like he sounds like Darth Sidious. He's him too. Then he takes off the lame mask and he's another villain and golem. He sounds like a little bit. He's all and then he's golem. He was wearing three masks.
And the top one was Jesus Christ. He was lying. If we were doing plus it up our scale with the 40 X. What do we think as far as what do we keep it exactly as is would we plus it up or would we burn the whole 40 X down for insurance money.
Certainly not that I was thinking plus it up. I think we're probably we might all have ideas for it. I was thinking like put some restraints and give me a seat belt and like let's drop the floor out like let's. Yeah. Yeah. Like like as I was saying I wanted more earlier like like really like much like Ethan Hunt does to the Philip Seymour Hoffman character Mission Impossible 3 and dangles him out of like the back of a plane.
Like I want to be down. I want to be on like dangling from the movie theater seats. I guess it's not practical as far as drinks or popcorn are concerned because it would just dump it all over. But they have to give you a warning. Maybe you're not allowed to have it in there.
But you get a little like just suddenly there's a quick little intermission like popcorn time. Yes.
And then you're back to it. Yeah. Or there's like a little warning logo that's like secure popcorn now and you have to put it in like a little case. Yeah. And it like there's like a little robot.
And then put the popcorn seat belt on it. Like if you could really like if they could rotate you 360 in those chairs I would love it. I would love more just more jostling.
More jostling. Rotating is good. Oh Jason's yelling. I don't need the 3D. Yeah I don't need the glasses. I have thick plastic glasses. I find them very awkward to wear over my glasses and then also my eyes kind of hurt at the end or a little achy.
I agree with that. You know we were saying how fun the opening the demonstration of the 4DX technology is. That is a blast. And also before the movie you get to see one of the best things you can see in a movie theater.
The Regal Coca-Cola Refreshing Filmmakers contest. So I want the 4DX to extend to that. I want the Refreshing Filmmakers to also program a perfect chair experience for me to watch their their film that is Coke centric.
The little the little story where like you know the guy like spills Coke in the projection booth but then it makes the people on the screen be cheers in a Coke together. Yeah that would be great.
I want to I want to experience every tilt and the spill of Coke in my face. And the water should be Coke at that point. Yeah. So it makes it longer the whole time and I should get to taste it all.
Oh I think we forgot one thing that happened to us when we were there and this this is before the movie we were walking down the hallway and we walked through what appeared to be some sort of media event or interviews or something for death of a nation.
And he's the newest Dinesh D'Souza joint. And if you're not familiar with him he's a right wing documentarian to stretch. He's a real con man. He's a real huckster who makes these dog shit documentaries.
He was pardoned by the president. He served some time for illegal campaign contributions because he was so fucking dumb he couldn't figure out how to give an excessive amount of money. And so we had to do time for that.
And he was like pardoned like a president wasted out an hour in the day to pardon this fucking moron and this movie is called Death of a Nation and it's about how like what if the left the real Nazis and it's just yes it's called Death of a Nation.
But then the poster has a giant picture of Trump and under it says Death of a Nation. So he's too dumb shit to even like put that in.
My favorite is that the premiere of the movie appeared to be at a 9 p.m. showing in like theater 3 at the Regal Cinema in LA Live on a Monday night.
In the middle of a city full of people who would fucking despise this man if you said like hey you know who this is. We were all we all walked by and we were like we all made noise and interviews.
Yeah there were interviews happening like there's a PR person that was like a PR person there. She's like looking and I was like she knows we know like I would think.
Well once we got like about six feet away I went did you just walk through a fucking Dinesh D'Souza movie premiere. I'll tell you this I would have seen it if it was in 4DX.
Yeah. Hell yeah. Absolutely. You know that's probably the out but really fast I just have to say. Oh yeah. We forgot about in that pre thing how the you're in the motorcycle chase and then the audience it cuts to the audience watching the 4DX motorcycle chase and they're all so into it
that they all pretend to be holding handlebars. That's the funniest thing I've seen in a movie theater in years. And that everyone 20 people all agreed to hold up fake handlebars something that's never happened in all of time.
And that was I will say that that like that played well as a joke to everybody in the theater not just snarky podcaster Roe that we were in. Yeah that was a huge laugh of everyone laughing at these idiots on the screen pretending to be on the motorcycle room like that.
Everyone was laughing at that. Everyone laughed. That wasn't just cynical dicks doing. And I want the you know what that's my other plus up I want full I want a full refreshing Coke filmmakers thing and I want a full I want the people in the theater
I want the people who made that to make an entire movie but it's a movie where half of it is cutting to the audience who are all like if the scenes in a truck they're all pulling a truck horn.
Or if it's like a train if it's a romantic scene they're all grabbing they're all grabbing air and smooching with it. Or like if they're like loading coal into a cold coal train whatever you would call that train and then shoveling in. Oh what a hard life.
I'll see in here. Yeah that'd be great. I want to see more of this 40 X space work you guys did improv you could appreciate. Oh yeah. Could you feel the the physics of the motorcycles they were holding on to. Yeah I mean that's you really got to commit to it and that's how you get an audience on board.
I thought the space work was a little broad but still it was effective and that's your plus up. Yes folks you survived podcast the ride 40 X edition. Thanks so much for listening. Hey the next time you hear us.
No that's not true. Very soon you'll be hearing our very exciting live episode with Tony Baxter done live from an abandoned sports 30 in Sherman Oaks. Check that out it's coming up and all kinds of great. There's a lot going on in podcast the ride world I feel and to check it all out.
You can hit us up on Twitter or Instagram or email us at podcast the ride at Gmail. We've started to talk about doing mailbag segments or as I call it podcast the ride post office.
So you know if you want to send a little letter to the podcast right post office email podcast right at Gmail dot com we'll start incorporating your we're eliminating the boundary between the podcast and you.
So we're going to go to level nine 40 X of email.
Again that's podcast the ride at Gmail dot com we've gotten a couple Twitter DMS recently that made me laugh saying what's the email for the show and I'm like are we mushmousing it on the end of the show so podcast the ride at Gmail dot com.
Should maybe our old friend Lane give them the email address.
The ride at Gmail dot com. It's good to see you again Ethan.
Little Lori Peter Lori in there.
There's some Lori in there.
He's back.
That was Elsa. Very interesting.
Well on that great Lane impression we should take off.
I guess that'll do it.
See you soon.