You all know me. You all know what I do on this podcast. But this isn't my usual bullshit,
our treats and three hour naps. This is Jaws, the universal classic attraction, the one filled
with lawsuits, leaking hydraulic fluid, rowboat rescues, and dead birds. Justin Michael joins
us on the best, and only, scene a cruise of Amity Island. Show me the way to go home. I'm
tired and I want to go to bed. Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show that can make your two hour wait for Slinky Dog Dash
feel like a three hour wait. I'm Jason Sheridan, here as always with Mike Carlson.
Hi, yes. We want to make it worse when you're waiting in the Orlando sun, so you have to
listen to us talk about fake rocks and different treats that we like. So sorry about that, I
guess.
That was it, yeah. And Scott Carragher.
Hi. Yeah. How is the line? What do we know about the ride?
We know the line has been bad since the start, since the opening of it.
Shaded. Yes, there's a big problem with shading into the new Toy Story Land in Disney's Hollywood
Studios. We know that they've changed the menu on Andy's lunchbox, I believe.
Yes, they dropped the Monte Cristo.
Yeah, they do. This usually happens with theme park food, is that when like a new stand or
new restaurant opens, they're very ambitious with the food. And then after a couple weeks
of operation, they realize that everyone just wants a chicken sandwich, a cheeseburger,
or a hot dog. And then they start taking stuff off. So like they probably had like filet
mignon bites or something, something crazy. And then now it's just like Andy's chicken
sandwich. It's like they downgrade it because no one wants that fancy crap.
Only food shaped in slinky shapes? Like just spirals, curly fries and zucchini swirls?
I think that would do very well. I'm not sure the full menu. We'll have to look into that.
Yeah. Joining us today, a very special guest. He's a writer on Infinity Train, the new Cartoon
Network show coming soon and Bad Reception, a new narrative podcast from the good people
at Audible. Justin Michael.
Hello.
Hi Justin.
The good people at Audible.
I'm glad you clarified that they're good people because you wouldn't want to listen to some
projects made by a bunch of real fans.
No, thank you.
Yeah. So excited to have you. You're a friend of all of ours for a while and I think a theme
park nerd equal.
This is just what we talk about anyway whenever I see you guys.
Yeah, that's true.
It has been for a long time. Yeah, that's what we plug it. So let's just pick up the
conversation where it left off. Where's the last theme park you've been or like internationally?
You did a Tokyo recently.
Yes.
We should ask him.
Tokyo Disneyland ride.
We got to ask Justin.
Good point.
What's your question?
The question. Okay. So here's the thing. We've been having this discussion over several
episodes. How many days for your first time going to Tokyo, how many days? Now we each
have a different day. So maybe we don't. I don't know if you don't know, we shouldn't
sway you by saying which one we think. So you tell us first time going to Tokyo, how
many days do you need to do at the Tokyo Disney Resort?
Okay. So obviously did a lot of research.
Sure. Of course.
Because half the reason I was like very excited about going to Tokyo was pretty much this
going to Tokyo Disney Sea.
Of course.
So you go to the, there's this website that I went to and they were like, you need five
to six days.
Right.
Which seemed like a lot.
Yeah.
Yes.
But depends on how much you really want to spend there. And you're like, I'm never going
to go here again. Maybe you just want to keep going on the rides over and over.
Right.
We did two days, one day at each park. We went during an off season.
So that made it easier. But the thing about Tokyo Disney is that they only let you go
to one, there's no park hopper. You can't go to two parks in one day. You have to choose
which park you go to.
And then on day three, I've been told it's a park hopper.
Exactly. Yes.
Oh, if you do a third.
Right.
That tilts it over. Then you, it's the visitor's choice.
You can buy separate tickets.
Right.
Like they do a thing called the starlight pass. So what we did, I, we went twice, which
is insane because we got a real good deal. But the first time we went to Disney, I think
Disney sea first, just cause I like couldn't contain myself.
Yeah.
I was just like, this is what I've been waiting for since I looked at pictures on the internet
in like 2001, three. When did it open?
Mind blowing. And when we're getting all of these low rent parks, your early California
adventures and seeing what is, what Japan has, uh, yeah, yeah. You couldn't even like,
this is not what the company does now. They still do this. Oh my God.
It's insane.
And then the second time we did like a Disneyland for most of the day and then did Disney sea.
We did that starlight pass after 6pm from six to 10. We went to Disney sea, but it was
dead the second time.
Well, I mean, that's good, but it would be beautiful at night. It's, I mean, it looks
beautiful in the day, but especially night.
So for our level, the three of us level of nerd about theme parks, first time going,
how many days do you recommend?
I'd say minimum three.
Hey baby.
I didn't go more than three days because of my girlfriend, Marissa Strickland for podcast.
She likes theme parks enough to indulge me on international trips, but not enough that
she would go if I wasn't there.
Right.
Which will come up in a later part of this episode. There's another detail about Japan
that I want to get to.
Yes.
Okay. So Mike said three.
Mine was three. We're going to do three when we go there, hopefully next month. Jason said
four. Scott said two. Yeah. Well, everyone is fucking made their voices heard on this.
We had a great time doing two. I did every single ride.
This is what the idea that it is like unreasonable that you are an enemy of the state. Somebody
sent an all a cat on all caps email and the title was Scott has made a big mistake. I'm
sorry if you're a fan of this podcast, maybe don't send us threats. I mean, I did research
how like what the best way to like your plan of attack. So it was like, nobody goes in
single rider lines there. It's crazy. It's just like a two and a half, three hour line
for splash mountain there. And we were the only people in the single rider line. Wow.
Indiana Jones at Disney. See, so like, no, the rides that are single rider. If you're
doing that. Okay, sure. And you started a very helpful email, which thank you. It's
very, it was not asked for. It was not asked for, but it was very much appreciated. Well,
did we say all of it you're going? Well, I'm going. I mean, there's a chance work stuff.
Something might come up. But yeah, as of right now, I feel like I are going and I'm going
evidently in April, but I also, you never know. Sure. We shouldn't start. I don't want
to wet the audience's appetite for my trip to Tokyo and then disappoint them. That's
what I'm saying. People would be crushed. It would be so upset. So, but the fingers
crossed wheels are starting to turn for both of us to get there. So anything else you can
actually really like we don't want anything spoiled. I understand. I didn't watch any
ride throughs beforehand. I know very little. Yeah. I haven't watched them either. I did
end up for 20,000 leagues. I know about it because we did an episode about it. Um, but
I still, I try to not let it really register in the brain too much. I'll read about stuff
and I'll look at concept art. If I know I'm going there soon, like with this one, I just
didn't want to see, cause that's the most fun you can, you can never get back that first
time you go on a ride. I accidentally, I was watching something on YouTube the other day
and Tokyo came up. I forget the ride. I'm not even going to say or no, I remember the
rider, but I, I won't say, uh, exactly what it was in reference to, but I like sat up
and I went, it uses what ride system? Like I was like, it revealed a little too. I was
like, Oh, I, I didn't realize this about like, you know, this Tokyo Disney sea ride. And
I was like, Oh, I think I can kind of picture it now. Damn it. I'm so curious. I had a similar
thing. And I also won't say the ride, but I was looking at a look for this episode because
we're dealing with an attraction with a, with big giant animatronics. And I was like, what's,
what do people consider like the best animatronics or the, you know, in terms of those, especially
those giant, you know, the Yeti or King Kong or whatever. And this list that I read, the
number one was a Tokyo sea giant animatronic. I feel like we all know which ride I don't
know. I didn't know that this ride. I suspect, but I don't want to even say because I don't
want to get it. I already luckily because my short term memory is dying steadily. I already
don't remember the name. Okay. Then I don't want to, I know which ride, but I don't know
the name of the cars right now, screaming the name of the ride at the podcast. And they'll
be like, they'll write an email like Scott better remember what the name of the ride
is or else he's dead. They'll find a way to make email subject lines being red and dripping
with blood. Well, some of the best giant monster animatronic rides I found out after the fact
were concept designed by the same guy. Like I realized like there's like an a tour of
like, you know, you know, like a Tony Baxter. I feel like you could sort of see like what
kind of rides he makes. And I feel like it's hard to like figure out who makes rides. Cause
there isn't like an IMDb for, or maybe there is. I park rides. Yeah. And there's this guy
and I won't say the ride that we're talking about, but I found out this ride that I think
you're talking about. He was the lead concept designer on that ride in Tokyo. Right. He
did his first jobs were for making jaws and confrontation. Wow. And he did Jurassic park,
the ride. And he did a private, he can't, he hasn't revealed what the ride is, but there's
one piece of concept art from beastly kingdom, that lost land and animal kingdom. And it
looks like a, like a mine cart ride with a big dinosaur. My gosh. And I'm like, Oh, so
I like this guy's ride. Right. Who is that? Do you know his name? Tom Thoradson. Okay.
I think. And he goes by Thor and he's like big in the Tiki community. Oh, actually our
local Tiki joint in Hollywood. Sorry, Margaritaville at city. Oh, wait a different one. Okay. Tiki
T the tiny shack that is right. Nestled next to the Scientology center that used to be
a KCET, which is the saddest thing. Oh yeah. Brought to you by Lucky Strikes. Tiki T brought
to you by Lucky Strikes, Marlboro, whatever brand you prefer. Hey, they don't, they don't
allow you to smoke in there anymore. Oh, is that right? No, for like the last six years,
seven years. Okay. It's much better. Cause I hated it then, but I'd be like, all right,
well I like this decorated shack. But now. Whatever for decor. He made their anniversary
mug. Like he designs mugs and stuff. And so he did, it's like shaped kind of like the
right building. Oh man. He gave us a new guy to heroify on this podcast. Yeah. He's great.
Yeah. We'll check out Thor. Yeah. Hey neat. I was just going to say if the, oh, if you
haven't heard of beastly kingdom, there was going to be a whole other section of animal
kingdom with like mythical characters, like a castle with a dragon and a roller coaster,
I think. And there was a hedge maze where you'd find a unicorn at the end, which had
some amazing technology where the unicorn would speak to you telepathically. That's
not a, this is not a joke. They were going to do it where they were going to have it
like the dialogue being base tones. So you would literally feel the vibration as opposed
to hear it. So like you'd go up to the unicorn at the end of finally, like you would find
different mythical creatures in the maze, but then you'd finally get to the unicorn
and he would like, or he or she would tell you something, but it would, you wouldn't,
it would be like, feel like it was in your mind. Wow. Like base tones, like, like vibrating
words to you. So you'd like feel it in your body as opposed to hear it. There's nothing
I want more than that land, that world to exist. Oh, I know. So sad. It's in the spot
that I ever tar went though. So I mean, they're going to have to figure out a different place
for it, but now it's not IP based. So it'll never happen. The dragon coaster in, uh, the
islands of adventure lost continents, I think was like the dueling. Oh, oh, oh, the concept
I believe was born kingdom. And then when it got canceled, the universal, that makes
sense. Yeah. The concept and the person people who are working on it, right. I think so some
vestiges of it, right. Because he was popping back and forth, I guess, or maybe he started
at universal and then he moved to Disney. I think he just helped with like concept illustration
and storyboarding for jaws and those ride and confrontation. But then he was like the
designer of this ride at Tokyo Disney sea, which is probably one of my favorite rides.
But we all ride that we're all think we know the name of that. We won't say it spoiler
eluding we are. I understand that. Yeah. There's a magic to it. And there's, there's rides.
I've, I've, yeah, I ended up seeing what 20,000 leagues was, but I'm still, now it makes me
so excited to go on it. It doesn't ruin it for me. And there's never a line. Nobody likes
that. Really? The two times I've been, it's like people are like, yeah, you can skip this.
Even on the, like the, the websites that say like, here are the best ones to visit it.
Uh, yeah, it's really great. It's really just a dark ride and it's, it's with all, all physical
practical props, which is cool. Cool. Um, one more thing before we get done with this commercial
for Tokyo Disney. I am looking forward to the Teddy Roosevelt lounge. Maybe the most
of everything. Some coasters from it. And what does it say? Teddy rode Roosevelt lounge
on it or it's got the logo of it. Yeah, it's beautiful. Everything there has their own.
So every dining facility, we thought about taking another thing, but we couldn't fit.
I mean, also the coasters were cardboard, so it wasn't like a, I don't know if I real
thievery thing. I mean, we, we might not do that because I also just asked at, uh, uh,
jock Lindsay's in Orlando. Like, could I take something? They like, just push the stack
over like, yeah, take as many as you want. They did not seem to care. I mean, we like
gave them or anything, but they have those, you know, like cafeteria trays. Uh, every
restaurant has a themed tray. There is a country bear tray. Michael R Carlson. Uh, just cause
I mean, we all love the country bears. Yeah. They're like alive and well in Tokyo Disneyland
in a way that like, yes, people go to different shows. We went to the Christmas one. We went
to the regular one. It's very weird because it switches between English and Japanese.
I don't know. That won't spoil it. Hey, I'm very excited, but I wish I could have those
trays. Like they have a Duffy tray. Oh yeah. Well, we'll get to that. That's tough to sneak
out and that feels like more of stealing. I mean, it's definitely, it's a hundred percent
stealing for sure. Stealing. I just really fast. Also the, I don't, I have no idea and
just tell me you're just give me your like guttural reaction to these rides, which I
don't think we've talked about on the show. Uh, poos honey hunt. It's nothing about. Okay.
It's absolutely incredible. It puts every other one of those rides to shame. Wow. Wow.
And the Disneyland one isn't bad. It's fine. It's just kind of like it's not monsters ink
bad. Right. It's like, I feel like it's a little, little mermaid level to me, which
I rather have than not have. Yes, certainly. Yeah. But honey hunt is like, well, they're
all plush too. So they look like stuffed animals. You're going to gasp yourself. I know. I won't
spoil it. Yeah. That it's, it's great. It's the best ride. Go there early. That's the
one that, okay. Interesting. Monsters ink. Uh, also really, yeah. I'm very excited about
that. Yeah. I've avoided knowing anything. I'm just, I'm glad to hear they're cool. Let
me ask, uh, have you spent, did you spend much time exploring their hotels? Like their
official Disney? Not at all. Cause that is a thing I like to, I like to, you know, explore
the grounds and the lobbies and stuff. Yeah. Even at the hotels, like I'm not staying in.
Do they have toiletries that Jason could possibly put in a giant garbage bag? Uh, probably. We
didn't go into any hotels. Okay. I don't, I think that's the, like my theme park nerd
level is not as interested in like the hotels and even the restaurants or that kind of,
like I really just love the rides and the theming and then just being immersed in the
world. But it looks like Japan and like, I mean, their hotels look like they're as nice
as the theme parks. Sure. Yeah. Um, Teddy Roosevelt thing is in a huge cruise ship or
something, you know? So it's like, it's just an icon in the park and inside is a restaurant.
And then it is a, just a, just one of the things in this park is a full ship. It's just,
you know, among the dozens of the attractions to check out. Crazy. Oh boy. One more tip.
You think you, we have blinders on. Oh, sorry. No, no, I didn't mean to. Oh, I was going
to say, uh, uh, we recognize too that like in one of the most amazing countries in the
world, like just full of cool stuff. What is this? An apology to Japan for us only caring
about the theme parks? No, no. Only Japan and the good people at audible need to be called
out in this podcast. We're going to Japan too, but this isn't in a podcast about Japan.
It's a theme park podcast. It's not Japan, right? It's wait, no, nevermind. That joke
fell apart immediately. That's okay. That's fine. That's fine. That's what matters. Um,
uh, oh, my tip was for English speakers, like yourselves who want cool theme park memorabilia,
you know, there's a tower of terror at Disney scene with custom story. It's, it's, it's
amazing. It's great. Uh, they have a handout for people in other languages that you have
to ask for. And I think we just happened on it and it's themed and it's like a history
of the hair, like the high tower hotel, right? And it has like the legend of Shariki, you
tuned to like this evil Tiki idol is the theme of the thing. So even if you don't like spooky
drop rides or just go in the line, it's cool. And they'll give you a thing so you can follow
along. Cool. And it's better than anything you can buy. Right. Jeez. But it's, but that's
a little secret menu. It's just, yeah, we never want to know that. English speaking
stuff and like the design is really beautiful and it just go all out. That's great. I think
Tokyo is the only place where I'd be tempted to sit and watch a show. I, I skipped shows
everywhere, but shows are like awesome. There we watched phantasmic there. It was different.
Okay. Yeah. All I will say. Oh neat. And it's a Disney C. Oh yeah. In the main lagoon.
Yeah. Cool. I'm excited to see Duffy and all of his friends. He's got all the people dressed
as Duffy. Well, that's true too. But I'm just like Duffy and just his friend, Shelly May
and his friend, Jelotoni and his friend, Stella Lu and their bird mailman. Marissa and I waited
in line to get you guys plush when we were there. Yeah. You guys got me Tippi Blue, the
bird mailman. It was Tippi was almost sold out. Well, Tippi is a very popular character.
Yeah. I feel like they're not pushing Tippi as hard as they used to. I agree. I think
Tippi has gotten lost in the new, cause there's new characters like Stella Lu and what's the
new character? Oh, Cookie. But Cookie's Hong Kong exclusive. And Ulo? Ule? Ulo is an exclusive
to Alani. Yeah. So Duffy has friends that are exclusive to other parks, but I think
that they are overshadowing Duffy's bird mailman, Tippi Blue. You think some news is going to
break about Tippi? You think he's about to be Me Too'd? You know what I mean? That's
what I'm saying. Possibly. They're downplaying their association with him. That makes sense.
Yeah, they're trying to distance themselves. I get it. What did you do, Tippi Blue? Oh,
me Blue. That's better. I said me Tippi. It wasn't a pun. I really thought if somebody's
getting Me Too'd, it would have been Jelotoni, the Italian painter cat. He just seems like
he's very vivacious and maybe, you know, gives a little bit too of foreword. But he restricts
boundaries and that's a good thing about Jelotoni. I guess that's a good point about Jelotoni.
Anyway. He's a good cat. What is he? He's a cat. He's an Italian painting cat. He uses
his tail to paintbrush. All right. A good cat, Jelotoni. With his good tail. We're talking
about a different critter today. Different, a critter of the deep. Yeah. We're talking
about old Spielberg's old pal Jaws. I find it very fun when we throw out, when somebody
who I'm like, I know you're a big theme park nerd, throwing out an open-ended assignment
of topic. I'm always excited to see what's going to come back. This is a great one. But
I think it's interesting that this is opposed to all the Disney stuff. I'm curious about
your personal associations with Jaws. Yeah, I think it was very hard to pick because it
was between like Jaws and just Efteling in general. Yeah. Oh yeah. But that's a whole
separate conversation. We'll do that. We'll do that. Oh boy. Great. But Jaws. So I grew
up like loving giant monsters like Godzilla and then like King Kong and Jaws. And I think
it wasn't until recently that I realized that I think I went on the Universal Studios tram
tour first and that's why I liked Jaws. And so I used to watch Jaws and at the time when
I was younger, I was like, Jaws 2 is better because there's more shark. I guess a kid,
I was like, there's more shark. That's why it's a better movie. That feels like you could
write an article right now on the internet and people will lose their mind. Like why
Jaws 2 is better than Jaws 1. And then people would get really mad and then you get a lot
of like hate, but it would get a lot of clicks because it's like an outrageous view. So I
think maybe do that. I mean, earnestly, I think Jaws is a much better movie than Jaws
2. Yeah. But I'm saying for clicks. Yeah. And I want the clicks. I'm looking for the
clicks. So if you find me, click me. A whole very angry political movements will stem from
this article. It's the most important thing politically going on right now. Yeah. Is the
Jaws versus Jaws 2 debate. It could be like the revisionist history about the Star Wars
prequels is what I'm saying. You could start that movement. Okay. I got to go guys. Immediately.
Just bail on this altogether. This has been great. And thank you for having me, but I
got to go anywhere near this. But I like that your child brain just like is on effect. You
aren't nobody's you haven't bought into the greater narrative. You just, you that that
was just like a pure kid opinion you have. That's very nice. Yeah. Yeah. And as a kid,
you know, like I really was into just sharks in general. I have like a cassette tape of
like different types of sharks being described to me that I fall asleep to, which makes me
sound like a sociopath. Like you're trying to like get their power somehow subliminally
into your brain. Yeah. I would stare at it with my eyes wider than you can imagine just
holding fingers to temples. Repeating some words backwards. Did you remember like, do
you like remember what was on the tape? Did you listen to it so much that you kind of
have like an encyclopedic, pedic shark knowledge? Now it looks like you don't. I know. I mean,
I remember there were tiger sharks and hammerheads and they were just described and that, you
know, like what they stopped swimming, they sink. They're attracted to blood. They have
like a good sense of smell. But also, no, not really. It sounds like you retain some
of it. Yeah. I got some of it hanging out. Do you like street sharks? I did, but they
creeped me out. Yes. There was a weird vibe about those guys. Just roided out screaming.
Like they were just too gross for me. Rollerblading. Yeah. Pick a lane. Too aggressive. Yeah. Turtles
much more laid back than the street sharks. Street sharks looked like they would beat
the shit out of you. A lot of like biker mice from Mars also too aggressive. I was going
to say yeah, biker mice from Mars. Well, after all, Tamant, the biker mice from Mars. When
the biker mice from Mars were hired by the Rolling Stones to police their concert. Yeah.
Yeah. We all remember that. Anyway, sharks back to sharks. Did you see my eye? Because
I didn't see like jaws until I was like around like end of high school, start of college,
but I would have ridden the ride about a dozen times before that. I saw the movie probably
when I was too young to see the movie. Okay. If I were like a parent now, I'd be like,
no, you're not allowed to see that. People get bitten in half. There's like a leg that
floats by a kid dies. So probably it was like at least like 10 or maybe eight. But I was
so into the ride that I think it wasn't that scary to me. Yeah. And so it was first the
tram tour because I grew up in Los Angeles, which feels like, you know, instant access
to theme parks. But as I grew up and like in high school, I would because universal off
season, especially then there were no rides really compared to Disneyland. It feels like
I mean, there was that. Yeah. It really was the tour. I mean, the universal slowly transitioned
from the tour was a three hour experience. I remember it was most of my guy. Yeah. You
would eat lunch and I remember there was the incredibly shrinking telephone set. Oh yeah.
They did that. You, you basically halfway through the tour, you would stop and then
there was like, you could get lunch or just sit around and then you would get back on
the tram and then go around and see other stuff. There's a little like cart, like you'd
go down to the lower area where there's limited stuff to do. So you would eventually have
to get back on and do. I want to say it was by like the horror movie sets. Oh yeah. You
were at studio. I did it. Oh yeah. Uh huh. I auditioned for it. Really? Did not get it.
Didn't get it. Yeah. Same year. When did you do it? Around the same time? I, 2005. OK.
So it was like after freshman year of college in the summer, I wanted, I wanted a really
fun summer job. I auditioned, went to, I think it was like a Radisson. Uh, it would have
been the Garland. Possibly the Garland. Yeah. The Beverly Garland. Yeah. And you know, it
was like a bad improv audition. So it was like, I mean, you talk about it. Yeah. I remember
there was a, yeah, I had to like, uh, uh, which I was not super improv comfortable,
but like for this job, I swear to God, I will, I will own this moment. You only have to do,
you know, you only had to improvise for like 30 seconds or something. But I was like, whatever,
I don't know. There were like three auditions maybe. And I got to one where you had to memorize
a block of dialogue and go do it for one person in an office, just like in front of their
desk. Yeah. And I got to that stage and I beefed it. Whoa, really? And that specifically,
and you could feel it like disappear. Cause I was so afraid. Like they gave you, they
handed you something to memorize there. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So you had to memorize it.
Like audition style. How long did you have to memorize it? How long, like an hour or
less? Much less. Less. Yeah. And I memorized it cold. Yeah. Cause that was the, it was
meant to convey, this is the gig. We're going to hand you new stuff. You'll have no time
to prepare. You're just going to have to do it on the fly. And I remember mine was, it
involved me having to know the names of all five of the desperate housewives, which I,
again, I had like, I, I still don't know it. And I remember on the tour being so slow and
like Nicolette Sheridan, Terry Hatcher. I like, cause I truly, I've never seen that
show. I truly don't care. But I like if, all right, if this is what it takes, I, I want
this so bad. It was about the war of the worlds 2005 Spielberg movie. Oh, cause that would
have been like new. The set opened and they drive through it and stuff. So I had to memorize
like something about that. And I choked for later. I I'll just bring it out. I have the
studio tour guide manual. Wow. I think I can find the part that you probably would have
had to do. And I have so many, it's a lot of pages. I have instant sympathy for you here
because what I recall is that that stretch was one of the stretches that you had to do
word for word because it had been signed off on by some Spielberg lawyer. And there was
like this verbiage that was like, it was, you know, you had to remember, is it heart
pounding? Yes. Bone rattling. This is, is this why you didn't get the job? I mean, yes.
This was the audition that I failed. And I also just didn't memorize it well. Like I
think I just forgot a lot of it and I was so nervous. Yeah. Yeah. Um, here. Okay. I
got it. It's a, I'm like, should you read it to make up for it? Yeah. So let's see if
you can handle it now. I hear yourself of your say, take it from, right? It's, it's
this paragraph and then, and then the next would be this amazing set. Do you think they'll
hire me if I do a job? Anyone's listening from universal, uh, from the university, you
need a job. So one of your, one of your former, one of your best, a former valedictorian is
recommending this exciting new voice, Justin Michael. And I think you should hear this.
All right guys. Uh, imagine that we are, uh, you know, heading up, we're making our way
up the hill toward the psycho house for some reason it says that, but then now coming up
one of the most impressive movie sets ever created the spectacular crash site from Steven
Spielberg's war of the worlds. We're going to take you right into the heart of this colossal
set, stopping our tram for a few moments to allow you to get some amazing pictures. So
hang on tight and have your cameras ready. Wow. You zoom into this carnage plane crash
in the neighborhood. Yeah. This is clip 83 or 84. Yeah. Either way I have a dealer's
choice. I, I'm assuming though, the only difference would be that the script now says, what do
you think Jimmy? And then we cut to Jimmy Fallon and he says like, Whoa, the plane crash.
That's crazy. And then he's in a leather jacket screaming my kids or he's doing the risky
business cruise dance. Can I say what's in here in between? There's some direction. Do
not underlined bolded, point out mother and do not mention the psycho houses you drive
by. What you make your way around the house. And as the were the world sets, W O T W, uh,
that's coming to view. The only sound should be that of the music, nothing more. All caps.
See, this is that legal shit. I think, I think the script had been approved by team Spielberg
and you could not, but now I don't remember what my problem with what you just read was,
but it was something like, is it amazing pictures or is it eye popping pictures? Like the adjectives
were so hard to keep straight in my head. And I was worried. They told you, you could
be secret shopped any time that you're doing this to me. And so you were always afraid
at this point, these, this startling experience will allow you to get some dazzling photos.
No wrong fire. You just get thrown off the tram in the middle and it careens into the
earthquakes. Share is an ejector chair. You fall into falls. Like, okay, I have a couple
with the first off, um, that were the world's movie is not very good. Second off, uh, okay.
Until like the last 40 minutes. Sure. Yeah. Well engineered engine of terror. Okay. Um,
do you think that Spielberg, uh, and his cohorts were like, do not talk about psycho house
or mother because of there's that famous anecdote where Hitchcock was too embarrassed, did not
want to meet Spielberg. Do you know, this is a jaws thing. Hitchcock did a voice in
the original version of like the jaws portion of the studio tour and Spielberg wanted to
meet Hitchcock when he was still alive. And Hitchcock said, I am too embarrassed. They
paid me a million dollars to do a voice on the studio tour ride and I feel like a whore.
What? Yeah. I even know what is this story. I don't know how these things connect. He
was too embarrassed to meet Spielberg. What? Because he felt like a sellout for like being
paid so much money to do a chunk of Spielberg's all over the tour. Why would that be a problem?
Ron Howard later was the host of it. Uh, those, those, uh, those walls have been knocked down.
Directors can be all over the tram. Even if you're Steven Summers writer, director of
the mummy, who I remember my joke on the tram was always to he like, he's putting the finishing
touch on a model and uh, of like a tomb or something. And then he comes at hi, I'm Steven
Summers, writer, director of the mummy. And then I would stop it right there as if that's
what the entire clip was. I'd set it up like, and now right, Steven Summers writer, director
of the mummy. Hi, I'm Steven Summers writer, director of the mummy. The end. We're live
remixing like a YouTube clip. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Essentially. Yeah. You could
create your own cues that you had a lot of flexibility as a, as a guide, but here I am
making you jealous of the, the, the, the so many fun audio visual opportunities. I went
on that ride so much as a kid, I wet, cause I had a season pass in between every, so I
went on it over and over and over and over. So I think I was so, it was this lofty thing
to me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Like, like SNL, like the ultimate stage. That was my SNL.
I found the story. Jason's correct. It's a crazy story. He says, uh, Spielberg tried
to meet with Hitchcock many times over the years. And then, uh, according to Bruce Dern,
who like had tried to make the meeting happen, Hitchcock was like, isn't that the boy who
made the fish movie? I could never sit down and talk to him. Uh, because I look at him
and I feel like such a whore replied Hitchcock because he's the voice at the universal studios
theme park. They paid him a million dollars. I took it and I did it. I'm such a whore.
I can't sit down and talk to the boy who did the fish movie. I couldn't even touch his
hand. I don't know. Really even know why. British manner, like weird, you know, it's
crazy. I don't even quite understand what he's talking about. I kind of don't either,
but then he's being passive aggressive too. It sounds like he's calling it the fish movie.
You were the name of the movie. This was the most popular movie when it came out. This
was the time where when movie actors would do TV shows, they were slumming it. Right.
It was true. That's true. He was an old creep. Yes. Yeah. He was a weird man. Yeah. Oh, no,
we definitely had some, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's some creepy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Just I think, you know, the good people at audible, the good man, Alfred Hitchcock. What
more does it want to offend people of Japan and doesn't want to offend Alfred Hitchcock?
It's understandable. It was something else in the script. Oh, just that you did write
down in pencil, amazing and incredible. It looked like the words were. I did. It looked
like you wanted to remember. That's right. This is a real problem I had was remembering
that it's an amazing set for an incredible scene. This you fell into the worst trap in
it possible in a tour guide audition. I feel like this is like this is some like this is
Marin failing his Lauren meeting because of the so there was some monkey comments. Sit
down with the Lauren of Universal Studios. Yes. Mike Sington, head of the tour, Mike
Sington, if you're listening, we may have to sit down, repair, repair the damage. Jason,
what's all this about then? He'll say, how far did you get in the process of the audition?
Oh, I waited the three hours for the first round. Yeah. They really treat you like garbage.
Well, this was also 2008, 2008, 2009. I think I tried two years like recession time. So
there were they said there was three times more than they normally was. And that's a
fun job to have. So yeah. And I got to the like, all right, we're going to start the
timer at a minute. When you hear a ding, you're done and you have to just pitch yourself.
Whoa. And they didn't prep you for that moment at all. They told us that's what it was going
to be. Okay. But they're like, by the way, we'll let you finish the sentence. But like
the ding is the ding. You know, they weren't giving you a lot of leeway. Ding is the ding
thing. So you did. So you made it to that and that was it. Yeah, I did. Do you remember
how you pitched yourself? I just talked about like, because I had done a bunch of UCB classes
and some shows at that point. And I talked a little bit about that. I talked about going
to Orlando. You lost him. You wasted valuable time. UCB. Berkeley. That applies. Interesting.
Yeah, that is probably. You just got done explaining the curriculum of UCB 201 and they
were like, Ding, I'm up. Save it for your therapist in 10 years, buddy. I was about to tell you
about who also times you and says times. Don't you want to hear about group games? Well,
all right. I'm going to vouch for both of y'all. Let's get let's get Justin and Jason
some jobs. You now and now in your mid thirties. I'm sure this is a perfect job to have and
not a depressing. I would happily do it once. Yeah, that's why I always say that if I could
do it like once the once a summer, I'd be so happy. What a what a fun thing. Yeah, I'm
trying to figure out how to also to put it in SNL terms because truly, you know, the
tour is the you know, it's it's the the ultimate stage. Yeah, I could come back and host quote
unquote. That's what I want. You know, I did my time like, you know, I'm not. You could
become a recurring host. You'd be like a Baldwin or yeah, Tom. I want to be the Alec Baldwin
of the Universal Tram Tour. You can quote me on that. Well, anyway, I'm sorry. Yeah,
you really you fell into such a trap here. But I well, I also I imagine another job you
might have enjoyed that we all might have enjoyed is being a skipper in the yes in the Florida.
I wanted to have that job so bad. Yeah, yeah. I know a friend of the show, a friend of the
show, Bugman, also a long aspiring guide. I'm not sure why he didn't. He was down in
the Florida area. That seems like an easy slam dunk for him. I'd love to see him do
it now. Oh, yeah. Oh, gosh, I would. Oh, man. Maybe he'll do it on the show. Maybe it's
only simulation. But anyways, well, how do we how do we tackle this thing in general?
I mean, well, like to touch on the universe, to touch on the Hollywood version, first of
all, you might have the same thing as me where you go to Disney for the cutesy stuff. But
if you want to get scared, you go to Hollywood. Yeah, I was like even by the time I was brave
enough to do it, I still was very scared of the main tour attractions of King Kong of
Jaws and of earthquake. Yeah. What if I were to tell you I have a quote about that exact
topic? Let's hear it from a book. So I pulled a bunch of quotes from the book Universal
versus Disney, the unofficial guide to American theme parks, greatest rivalry by Sam Genoway.
And there's a large portion of this book about Universal Orlando being opened. And one of
the designers let me find this here. So there are a lot of designers talking about how,
you know, Universal Orlando opening was a disaster on a lot of levels. But they they
were really jacked up to work on it. This is Peter Alexander, former Universal head
creative. Alexander had worked at Disney and had learned quote, The thing about Disney
was it was very soft and family, but it was big production value. It is kind of nice,
but it doesn't have any edge. Finding that edge was how Universal was going to win. Terry
Winnick was confident. He said the Pirates of the Caribbean is for wimps. Climbing the
treehouse. That's for wimps. Space Mountain. No big deal. We got King Kong. We got earthquake.
We got back to the future. We got jaws. We are going to terrorize these people. These
are going to be rides that are going to scare the it just says expletive. I'm assuming it
means shit or fuck. We're going to scare the shit out of people. This is not for wimps.
Wow. We bullied into going to this party. I was a nerd for sure. Still am. Technically
the definition glasses. It's true. That's the full definition. Then you know, excitedly
about a thing that I love. That's more geek territory. I feel like this is how in the
early days of Universal doing more themed entertainment, at least internally they were
like, yeah, we're fucking jacked. Yeah. That guy seemed like he just did a bunch of cocaine
and ran up to a podium or something. A lot of this seems like, so much of this, and the
story is about trying to open to MGM to a lesser extent. Like it seems like, oh yeah,
1980s cocaine. Okay. So everybody involved, you were, or at least the leads of the Disney
MGM, Universal turf war, uh, that cocaine was a major player. I mean, I, I, it could
have helped. It seemed like a lot of long nights. Like Saturday night live. Some of
the material in the early days was fueled by coke. Oh, it's aged so well. It's aged
so well. What if there was a ride where there was an earthquake, man, you can't come up
with that stuff without being on drugs. We are going to terrorize these people. I love
that. That's so funny. That's something. Um, well, and I also, it seems like the Universal
strategy also became like, what if a, what if a big thing jumps out at you? And Jaws
is the first one of those which led to King Kong, which proceeded the T-Rex and in Jurassic
park. Uh, um, I think the, I think the, the jaws on the Hollywood tram tour is like a
crucial moment in the development of, of universal because it's the free, it's the first Spielberg
property. It's really the first like original thing based on a specific blockbuster, uh,
a film. Uh, they, I think they, I was looking up, what did the tram have up until then they
had the flash flood and they had the avalanche, but those were not a property and jaws is
this, this massive game changing. So their first IP kind of based. Yeah. Yeah. And now
Disney is kind of equally IP. I mean, always was cause it's the, you know, they're all
the rides are based on the animated films, but like, you know, yeah, uh, the current
seventies, eighties blockbusters jaws is kind of the first strike in that, that world being
having a presence in the park. It did seem cool. Like universal, like it was cool that
they had all of these IPs at the time, whereas now I'm bummed that everything is completely
IP riddled. Yeah. And I miss the days of having just a generic, you know, expedition Everest
or something. Right. Like when will we get that again? Right. Oh, well that the answer
to that is maybe never or when there's like a giant new park and they can like make one
of the rides in the new park, a non-specific thing, but probably like a new ride, one off
for a new land. It's always going to be IP early for like the next 20 years. I mean,
that seems like two, when, when is universal going to dial back on screen rides? The answer
is, oh, when they have to make a whole new park and they got to switch up the tricks
at least a little. Hopefully that's coming soon. The rumors say, you know, a couple of
years. Yeah. But that's the thing really about jaws. That's so cool is that, I mean, the,
the, the tram originally, and then the Florida one, uh, that you're in physical environments.
And in the case of Florida, a huge physical environment that lake is massive and twists
and turns. And there's the indoor section and several outdoor sections. Um, just like
the, the, the place making there is very impressive. Uh, it's, it's really, it's kind of like
universal's answer to the jungle cruise. Yeah. That's what I love about it is that it feels
like a theme park ride, a theme park nerds twist on a, like an old favorite. Uh, it's
like, let's do the scary version of the jungle cruise. It's going to basically look like
the same kind of boat start as innocuously, but then things will go wrong and the animals
will actually attack, which I love. I mean, it's just like a series of like horror movie
set pieces. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it gets genuinely scary. Yeah. Uh, the heat is very
hot. Uh, I don't want to, I don't want to go out of order here, I guess, but, uh, but
the, you know, the, the final state of jaws is so crazy. Yeah. Um, well, the stories about
making the heat are crazy where they would like, all right, I'm going to get in the boat,
turn the fire up as high as it can go. We read the same article. Yeah. And then dial
it back just a little. And it's so hot. Like my brother came off once, like very upset
at how hot it was. And people were convinced for years. I got burned. I got hair, like
it seems my hair, which is like partially a mental trick. And then one thing I read
was like, you also have to remember a lot of people don't put on enough sun tan lotion.
So a lot of people were sunburned and then had intense heat thrown at them. So their
brain thinks they've got like third degree burns, right? Like, yeah, it was crazy. Oh,
I'm sorry. I just also the, the, uh, the petroleum used to make these fires, uh, apparently cost
universal studios, $2 million a year. Wow. And they shut it down. I, in 2005 to like
2007, it only ran seasonally, like when it had the most crowds because Florida had hit,
been hit by hurricanes and gas was so expensive down there. It was just not, it didn't make
financial sense for them to ride jaws. But everyone got mad at them because they're like,
we like jaws, we're on jaws. We want to be burned alive. I went, it's to leave the Marines,
but bring back the gasoline. Like, I think that was the first time I went on that ride
was when they had no fire effects. Oh, interesting. I read about it because I was like a rabid
little theme park nerd and I was like, I can't wait for this part because it's supposedly
like the largest still largest controlled fire and a theme park ride. Really? Is that
like that moment? That's like the, I dunno, like it's right before the climax of the ride,
but it feels like the biggest effect is, you know, like whenever the sharks bumps into
some like gas tanks or something and then he attacks it and it like, there's a ring
of fire that looks like it surrounds your exit essentially. Yes. Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I was always under the impression that fire is caused by the, uh, skipper firing
a grenade at it. And that might be it. I don't remember, but it was always hard to tell.
It was always, it was a lot going on a lot of commotion, even in like the videos I watched.
It was hard to tell. Um, can I read one other little part of the, the, to talk about Hollywood
again? I should say in our group texts the other day, I was debated cause Scott was like,
Oh, we're including Hollywood. And I didn't even think about the studio guide stuff, but
I was like, well, there's so much with Orlando. I don't, we have the time. I think one leads
into the other. And I also think I have a big book of green loosely paper that I've
been waiting to bust out for a long time. And you're right, some is blue and some is
salmon. Um, you know, among the other things in the, uh, I forget what all the colors are,
but some of the other things they give you as a guide is just a list of all of Universal's
movies and TV shows, which I don't know what a horror has transpired on your tram where
you are stuck somewhere and having to resort to. Well, um, you may also remember, uh, semi
tough from may 1980 with Bruce McGill and David Hasselhoff. Uh, that's of course they're
on the same time as stone with Dennis Weaver. Also one season. Oh, good. Okay. Stone fan.
Uh, more stone info, please. I don't think I have any, uh, throws a cup at my head. How
did you make it from so far away? That was three cars back. They passed it up to you.
I'm car by car. Um, so I also have in front of me, the script of the experience. And one
odd thing about it is that really both of them, the interaction of, of the shark and
fire, however it happens, is it a gas tank that dips into the water? Is it a gun being
fed? The idea and in the films, the idea that the shark can trigger explosions and stuff
is so odd and forced, but so delightful. And just from the actual script, um, you watch
the guy. So, so you pull up, there's a police diver in the water, making sure that there
are no more sharks and that you can pass through and view this empty lake without incident.
But he gets eaten and blood gurgles up. Uh, so you were supposed to say, I have an idea.
Why don't we just pull up next to that gasoline tank stage direction with approved sarcasm?
I'm sure we'll be safe there. Um, I really like that. Like the lack of edginess of the
scripts to where that has to, we do, we will allow it. You can comment on it. Um, but then,
then what transpires is the strange. He takes a yellow barrel, which then triggers like
a gas pump to start spraying everywhere and explosions go off and, uh, you tilt towards
it, right? Like, yeah. Kind of like breaks a little bit and you slide down. Yes. Although
I've heard that that has been, it's been on tilt a five, which is a complaint apparently
because it was serious part. Yeah. Cause like the shark would jump at you as you were like
much closer to it. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And it brings everybody closer down into it
and gives people on the other side, a better view. But I used to pick my best seat, uh,
based on King Kong and jaws. You gotta go on the right side. Second car. Okay. Why second
car? I don't know. It's just where it would stop. So you'd be right with Kong. Like if
you were in the first car, you were too far. Might be a little ahead of it. Second car
was at least like the first half. This is when it King Kong was, uh, the big animatronic
Kong that they ended up turning into confrontation before they burned down mysteriously for insurance.
Right. Exactly. Example of finding if there were like where the rumors from that started.
Cause I remember hearing about them burning it down for insurance or that like even that
the Kong ride was too expensive. Well, there's a joke on 30 rock about it. Uh, and then there
are, I forget there's web websites, bumper car boys and a Ferris wheel.net. And I think,
I mean, stuff like that, I think is when I was, I was, I was still looking for an original
original print of what dreams may come that that burned in the fire. Yes. I just remember
there was a list of like half a dozen original prints they lost. And the only one I remember
is what dreams may come down in the back plot fire. Was it an, cause it's, it's singed like
one of the warehouses to like one of the storage warehouses to film vault. Yes. The original
real will walk through the underworld looking for its way back to the land of the living
so it can be viewed again. The joke was on 30 rock that that theme park fire didn't destroy
the stuff we wanted it to. Um, but then also like within a year they were like, oh, we
got a new King Kong ride ready to go, which is I think a big reason everyone was very
suspicious about that. Well, that's pretty coincidental that King Kong burned down. Oh,
but Peter Jackson's here to introduce a new skull Island. Y'all like screens. Yeah. Sure.
How many y'all like screens? Oh yeah. Look, stone and screens. Uh, yeah. Also that like
that there was a property that burnt down where there was a new one recently as opposed
to earthquake burning down or what have you. Interesting. Right. Suspicious. We don't know.
I don't know. We don't know. We don't know. It's rumors. We're not necessarily, we're
not typically a conspiracy theorists. I guess the fact that I said bug main is making us
go to the last time phony enough. The last time I was on this tram tour, I was sitting
next to bug main. Yeah. Interesting. And we, right before the jaws section, we both kept
going up. The shark isn't working. The shark is cause they keep doing, they keep playing
that over and over again about how the shark isn't working. I'm looking right now at clip
number 67. The shark isn't working. Which Richard Dreyfuss, the shark isn't working.
He gets even more nasally because he's, he's already nasally Richard Dreyfuss and then
he goes more nasally to be an intercom. He's not working. And then at the end, well, one
of my favorite things to say on the tram, in case you're wondering, Bruce, the ferocious
man eating shark was named after Steven Spielberg's attorney. I remember they had been saying
that since the early nineties. Oh yeah. I went on it as a kid and that is how I learned
that fact. I remember like telling people at school that, and I was like, you know,
it's named after the lawyer. Isn't that funny? We all like lawyer jokes, right? Very little
evergreen comedy, but one of the top ones is, ugh, lawyers. Yeah. Yeah. Works for kids,
works for adults. Yeah. So, so you've got this attraction, which is still, I feel like
for a long time was Universal's primary iconic attraction. Having that shark pop out at you
used in the ending of mall rats. Oh, right. We all, yeah. No, they get married. The Kong
was in the wizard and this was in mall rats. Hmm. Interesting. Our two finest films in
all of cinema. Double feature at the Egyptian. I also like to say that the shark, the jaws
lake played into what I consider one of the greatest cinematic moments. The murder she
wrote. That's what I was thinking. Her bike and Cabot Cove. That's another one. They love
that moment on the tram getting. I know it's one of the greatest generation. They were
also, but how much of that, that zone of the back lot is like three buildings. Right. There's
a way nine seasons of murder. She wrote where it was just the theme song. Yeah. I was going
to say it's the opening video of opening the intro and maybe that's it. Yeah. You just
see the shark pop out in the background. She tumbles in and there's a big explosion and
then that's the end of the murder. She wrote. There's also an episode where Jessica's trying
to solve a murder on the back lot. If you were a drama made by universal at any point
in the seventies and eighties, for some reason they found, uh, they would find a reason for
the characters like, um, you're going to the back lot this episode. Oh, what part of the
back lot are we using? Oh no, you're using all of it. The back lots playing the back
lot. They were MCA was sheepish shit. But also I loved those episodes. Like they also, like
the fans love them anyway. Uh, yeah. Miss Jeff on a back lot. Knight Rider did it twice.
They did one that I watched before this where, uh, the Hasselhoffs punching somebody and
he rips their mask off. And I think it was Robert England, the, uh, doing a cameo on
Knight Rider 18 to 18. Oh yes. You're right. Did like 18 ever go to the green planet or
anything and maybe tease teacher botanical ride wasn't there yet. It'll be later than
nothing ever used that practically. I don't think that's a couple of times. And one of
my favorite moments in all of film and television happened in the jaws Lake, which is from the,
the feature film, the Harlem globe trotters on Gilligan's Island. Has anyone seen this?
I've never seen it. I want to, I want to give maybe Doug Jones credit or a friend, Doug
Jones for possibly having found this, uh, this clip or made me aware of it. But the,
there is a part where the Harlem globe trotters plane has crashed, which eventually I assume
leads to them getting to Gilligan's Island and they are stuck in a raft and all they
have with them are a bunch of basketballs and they're questioning how will they survive?
Especially if something bigger goes awry and then the shark pops out and they're all like,
what do we do? And then curly or one of them goes fear, follow my lead. And he shoots a
free throw into the shark's mouth and then they all do. And the shark's mouth full fills
with basketballs and then it subsides and then you hear it burp. So, you know that it
doesn't desire people. It doesn't choke on basketballs. It just, so they didn't kill
it. They just made him know the burp. Let's you know that they did not choke a shark to
death with basketballs with leather in its mouth, but it is like, that's one of my favorite
kinds of things is like tortured. How you creating a problem that can only be solved
by basketball players. It used to be good. What happened? That's how I felt. I was like
all this like mopey ass dramedy about standups being sad or whatever. Like give me a show
where basketball players have to shoot baskets into the mouth of a shark. Why can't things
be fun anymore? We can all agree on that. Yeah. I agree. I am more sharks full of basketballs.
I think it is. You can draw a direct line of like, Oh, that Shaw's attraction was a
big hit and that led to get them getting Spielberg on board for like, Hey, we want to build a
theme park. Like that is the only reason Orlando happened was Spielberg signed on. And then,
you know, they had to figure out like, you know, they had earthquake at that point. They
had Kong on the tram tour. How do we expand these like two minute experiences into five
minute experiences? Yeah. I remember that, like that idea blowing my mind having been
to Hollywood first and going there. Okay. So there's, so jaws and an earthquake and
King Kong are just these like stops are just part of the tram tour and that they all now
are fully fleshed out, uh, uh, full experiences. I was so excited because you know, living
so far away, I guess I did go to Florida when I was really young and I was excited about
like Nickelodeon. I don't think we went on the jaws ride and maybe it was shut down.
It happened. Maybe it was like close to when it opened because there's, you know, famously
like how jaws was, you know, riddled with problems. That opening jaws is crazy. The
1990 version that only ran for like five or six months and was mostly broken down. But
the two effects that I wish still existed. I mean, they never worked or only one of them
is the, I guess the finale was the shark would come bite your boat and drag it. And there's
some footage of it attempting to do it online. It looks bad in theory. Amazing. Yes. Which
is such a cool, like immersive way of pulling you in. And then they blew them up like the
end of jaws with like big meaty chunks. Yeah. Yeah. And the chunks all had to get collected
into some pipe and then, and then, and so that they can be recycled and re-use. Why
didn't this work? Anytime there's these, right? Like this is similar to like the Indiana Jones
effect that doesn't work, which lasted for like a month, which is where, well, it was,
it was when the temple's collapsing, all of a sudden all this rock, like old rock would
fall in front of the car and it would explode because it was ice for, but they like dyed
it with tea or something. And it only lasted for like a month or two. So anytime they tried
to do these cool things, like things that'll blow up and separate, then they have to collect
it or whatever. They just, it never works for some reason. Like they haven't, I can't
think of one application on a modern ride like this. Did they do that on the ride? Like
was that in a like audience open ride for a couple, a month or two, maybe or a couple
weeks. And somebody there's like one, there's a very, very conspiracy conspiracy theory
type video where like their paws circle there. That is that silhouette that you see is ice
falling, simulating a grumbling temple. Yeah. Cause it was a giant like crazy industrial
sized ice machine that would dump ice every whatever 10 minutes or something could fat
like freeze ice. It was for vegetables. It was for freezing like stuff on a farm. Like
if you had a flash freeze vegetables, it was just a giant freezer or a giant ice maker
essentially. So like, yeah, another situation where it was like, it just at a certain point,
the water pooled and it was a big problem for them to come in and like dig it out after
a while. There was a rumor that when we were kids, that people would say that you could
go through one of the three doors in the beginning and they were like, I went through the right
door and I was like always look at, and so like to this day I'm like, so did they ever
use the other doors? It seems like they obviously don't use the other doors. Well, they shift
them over. They shift them over. Don't they? Can you go through any? It's all the same
entrance. Yeah. It's all the same entrance, but they shift the door over to make it look
like it's a different door. They haven't done it in a while. I feel like I always go centered
in the last so many years. They might have retired. The Jaws, the show director, Adam
Biesark summed it up this way. You can imagine how complex it must be to get one giant mechanical
watercraft to swim up and bite another mechanical watercraft, which is moving with absolute
precision hundreds of times a day. That was a thinking, but they tried it. They tried.
God bless the ambition and that it's going to be the sheer acreage and amount of physical
space that you're wandering through and multiple water vehicles. I was going to say, doing
it in water especially. I'm no engineer, but that to me seems like an extra hard thing
to do. That was the problem with the movie. I mean, it wasn't salt water in the ride,
but it's just like, it feels like a very funny thing that should have been obvious. Like,
hey, remember this movie that had horrible set problems? Right. You're going to make
a ride where there are multiple versions of the shark and it has to do it over and over
again, but you didn't learn. Also, we have never built water rides before. Universal
MCA design, whatever it was called at the time, this was their first attempt at building,
not just a theme park, but rides of this caliber. Very ambitious. Wow. It really does mirror
the film in a lot of ways. Probably the people you're accusing of being coked up are the
people in charge or they're like the mayor. The park doesn't shut down. It got open. We
got summer visitors. Another Terry Winnick had been designing MCA attractions longer than
anybody and he said it was never going to be ready. That was the same story that Jay,
in this case, Jay Stein, former head of Universal, that Jay heard from me every year when I was
all by myself. You are approving it in January. You want me to open it in June and I'm sleeping
in a motor home. My crews are working 24 hours a day. They were all on cocaine. That's for
sure. Jay's attitude was we're going to open it because we said we are going to open it
and we need to open it and we will fix it afterward. At least Adderall, if not. Was
Adderall around in the 80s? They crushed it up and they just mixed it all together. Lutes?
Were Lutes still around? I guess they would chill you out. Well, the Coke would get you
out of the Adderall. That's how you would go to sleep in your motor home in a dirt field.
After being up for 72 straight hours, you would take a lute and calm down in your motor
home. What we're saying is the people at the top were concerted active Cokeheads, but the
employees who were good people were only forced to do a lot of cocaine in Adderall. I don't
say that if you're a Cokehead, you're a bad person. No, that's a good point. It was just
a necessity. They don't have to be an 80s businessman or evil businessman from a movie.
They were contractually obliged to do Coke. Yeah. It's just part of keeping up. It's like
having a nice car if you're a major executive. You also have to have a nice Coke habit. You
got to do this. Apparently, the original show writer was Steven Spielberg's roommate, old
roommate. Whoa. Which is insane. Yeah. The failed version of it. He was heavily designed
in getting Universal Florida open. It's wild. It's crazy. So, all right. Universal opens
in 1990 or was it 91? It's 1990. Time magazine called the park Universal Swamp of Dreams.
The Orlando Sentinel reported they came, they stood, they left mad. Wow. Wow. So, the big
three, which are all, this is something I find interesting too, that it's these three
attractions that are based on components of the tram tour, all of which you get on essentially
a tram-esque vehicle. In the case of Jaws, a big multi-robe, kind of pontoon boat earthquake,
just kind of literally a tram. Then you're on an elevated train in King Kong. All three
of them had gigantic problems. Right. Jaws was the worst by far. The other ones ended
up looking better, but still. There was, by the way, to give the whole history, I think,
if I'm correct, Universal Orlando, they had broken ground. They had started planting seeds.
Then Eisner rushed in and said, ah, us too, we're also doing a studio park. And theirs
was less ambitious. They obviously have done this stuff more, so they got it open quicker.
It was probably chintzier, original MGM Studios. And they tried to do that two and a half hour
tram with lunch in the middle, and it lasted hardly, barely lasted at all. Did they have
Catastrophe Canyon open at launch or no? I think they did. Because that was the only
exciting part of that. Exactly. There was an earthquake-esque. But I think they walked you
through the costume warehouse. I think they took you around a little more. Maybe. Because
I remember always being on the tram. They made it last. All they had was the tram experience
and the great movie ride. And that was what the park opened with. Maybe the animation
building. Muppets came later. No, honey, I shrunk the kids. Star Tours? Is that open?
Not a park opening. There was nothing there. I don't think about that. We went pretty quickly
when it opened, but there's nothing there. But the important thing is they got it open
first and Universal was dilly dallying around with these $25 million attractions that were
going to be better and are better than a lot of what Disney ended up having. But they opened
late and then they opened full of problems. The PR was really bad. And then they had to
shut down Jaws very quickly. Yeah, confrontation and earthquake. They managed to fix the problems
within a few months. Jaws then shut down until like 93. It lasted like five or six months.
So wild that that's how long it had to be shut down. Justin, you think you might have
been there in that time? I think so. And there was no Jaws. I remember Terminator 2 was there
at the time and not in Hollywood. Oh, interesting. So that's like a key memory, but I was such
a little kid. I remember going on the World of Hanna Barbera ride, which was like a simulator
with like a crossover of all the Hanna Barbera characters. You can watch it on YouTube now.
Yeah, that's a fine one. Yeah. But yeah, I don't remember going on Jaws as a kid and
I love Jaws so much. So I must. I probably went on for the first time in college. Yeah.
And it was it blew my mind. Yeah, it truly lived up because the new version of it, I
think, is an incredible ride. It's great. And that first version, the bones are there,
like the grenade launcher is there, but the skipper is barely saying anything. And the
sets are like so not there. They got so much more built out. Like, yeah, by the time I
went on it, yeah, they were built out. I guess there's a larger point, though. Like it feels
kind of real. Like a lot of things that makes all of these rides kind of scary is that they're
like in the real world. So like kind of the feeling of like your brain kind of going,
this just looks like a town or like even I mean, not as much on Kong where it's a city,
but it kind of like you kind of feel like it's a city. Yeah. So like there's like there's
a feeling of it's a real world, which does make it scarier because your brain is kind
of just like taking in information like if you were in really just on a boat. That's
kind of what I love about Universal is that they do it with Jaws and they do it with the
mummy ride in Florida where they they spoiler, I guess we've we we just talked about this.
Yeah, I think we've talked about it. I think the fake out and it's like the fake. Yeah.
Tendon like, you know, they're going to let you off the ride and then you dive down for
more roller coaster. We didn't know that until we talked about it a few weeks ago. No, no,
it's fine. It's a launch coaster. Yeah, probably. Yeah, it's really like a very cool, really
replicated on anything else that I can think of. No, the other mummy is garbage compared
to that one. Yeah, that's that's truly one of the big theme park disappointments I feel.
But now it looks cool to me going to Universal Studios Hollywood because it's like some of
the only practical effects they have. Yeah, right. Even even though it was disappointing
when it came out. But it is an actual it is a ride that where you move and go places.
Yeah, not not screens. Yeah. I mean, the way that those like big whatever warrior mummies
jump down on the side of the ride anyway, we're talking about a different ride. Yeah,
the original. This is a ride that lets you know why they went so screen heavy because
like, OK, Universal opening day. I mean, it's it's also these big three attractions and
their shows. But there's also they opened with ET and they did. And that was the only
thing that worked flawlessly. They said, yeah, yeah, right. So you can understand why they
stopped trying things of this nature that cost two million dollars a year in petroleum.
So they shut down until 1993 when they reopened. Jaws no longer yanked the boat around, although
he maybe never did correctly, according to the history. And that to make up for that,
I think that's when they boosted the fire. I think there was less. I think there were
not the tanks and everything. No, you don't do their tanks aren't even built like you
don't even say I think there's one or two fire or mortar effects. But like it's amped
up in the newer version. And instead of him exploding into blood and guts, now he bites
on an electrical wire and electrocutes himself and then descends down and then right on the
way out, you get one last burst of a Jaws who is charred and just black burnt flesh,
which is truly disturbing. Yeah, it's like one last. It's like the horror movie final
jump scare like you killed the monster and then it like jerks to life, but then dies.
And that's it. Really, it's and it's the ending of Jaws 2. OK, he gets electrocuted. And so
the story of the ride takes place around when Jaws 2 is supposed like originally when it
opened again. The idea was that you're revisiting Amity and it was like when we had that fateful
shark attack a few years ago. Yeah. And so it's like timed around. I don't know if they
got rid of that later, but so I was excited because I was like, that's the Jaws I grew
up on more than the original. There's also a self-awareness because they're like there's
Chief Brody's house. He was played by Rush Snyder in the movie, which I always thought
was very funny. And rewatching the video now, they said there's there's the mayor's house,
which that means the mayor stayed in office even after Jaws. But there's a very funny
visual gag where there's Brody's house is like a reasonably sized home and then the
mayor's house is a giant mansion right next to it. Like it's like, oh, yeah, of course,
the fucking Larry would have that house. Is the what is there an official timeline for
when the Jaws ride? Is it after the first movie for sure? Is that good? That good? Says
that right? And then they when they're talking. Yes. But not before Jaws 2. I don't think
they acknowledge the other movies. They keep up with real time because in the last few
videos I watched the last year of operating, they say there hasn't been a shark around
here in 30 years. Oh, I see. OK, so so they only are acknowledging that the first movie
it's a Superman Returns type timeline. Yeah, it cuts out some of the films, all of the
films Kevin Spacey as Luthor is on this ride for some reason. He does make an appearance
and he goes right after you see Jaws chart. He's like, I'm fine. The final, final scare
is Kevin Spacey is able to work in Hollywood, but he is working at the end of Florida ride.
So yeah, he's demoted at least a little bit. So and that yeah, that final that chart Jaws
is truly that is the kind of thing that really separates Universal from Disney. I don't think
Disney would do anything. There's no chart. Corpses. They want to show the whale chart
in the Pinocchio ride. Yeah, they won't even show Ursula being run through by the mast
of a dirty, a dirty mast from a ship. Truly all I wanted was a giant Ursula and the little
mermaid ride that version that they have of like Tony Baxter. Was he involved in making
it? Yeah, or something. There's the you know, the 3D ride through like the previous version.
We talked a little bit about this. Yeah, the little mermaid episode. Yeah, it's crazy.
So good. There's a giant Ursula at the end. Yeah, yeah. Gets her what for, you know. So
I think, well, just to have a little, you know, this is not the plus up of this ride,
but let's I'll say a plus up of every Disney ride as with Jaws with this cool Jaws as the
precedent, whoever the villain of the ride was, I want to see them charred and burnt
and breathing their last gasp like like the Queen Evil Queen on the Snow White ride. We
should see her fall. Yeah, she should get electrocuted and then we should run over her
with the vehicle. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's see her like that in the fall that her limbs
are all like gnarled. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Twisted in painful directions. Captain Hook and Smee.
Smee was an accomplice. He was. He should have spoken up. Yeah. Yes, he was. Was Smee
the Gervals or the Himmler maybe? Huh? That might be for another podcast. Yeah. We'll
see. Gervals or Himmler. With Jason shared. The the alligator is France, a villain early
on, but then once it's once Vichy France is defeated, it's three joins the allies at the
very end of the war. I think that works. Is the alligator ever? I thought he was always
bad. Well, the alligator chases after Hook and Smee at the end. Right. Oh, OK, that's
right. But he always has the ticking time. He's always scaring Hook. Oh, that's true.
Yeah, he's kind of an antagonist. He's like in comic books where like Black Cat shows
up and it's like, you know, you just. She's on. Yeah, it's just like, well, you just route
the museum, but you helped defeat Sandman. Right. Right. He's very scantily clad, that
alligator. Yes, very sexy. He's portrayed in a way that's inappropriate. He's a thought.
Yeah, that alligator is a thought. Well, anytime you want to map a ride and its components
onto a war or vice versa, they're all metaphors secretly, which is what you'll keep revealing
through. Yeah, sure. Yeah, it's all history lessons. Jaws is the Kaiser. The shark is
the Kaiser. Chief Brody is the Americans finally getting into World War One at the very end.
Well, what have we what have we not talked about? Oh, the lawsuit. Oh, yeah, that's right.
Oh, that was another thing that happened in the first several months of being opened before
it closed for several years. So it's a universal sued ride and show engineering ink who built
the first version of the ride and had done work for them before. But it seemed like the
lawsuit went back and forth between Universal and this ride show and engineering ink of
like they didn't use waterproof parts. It's like we did use waterproof parts. We didn't.
You didn't test it enough. And I think it's the problem in the movie. Yeah. Right. They
weren't able to test it enough. So like the skin kept falling apart anyway. Wow. It perfectly
overlays even more perfectly than the Hitler stuff. I don't know. I think they're on equal
ground. It seems like, though, it did rule in Universal's favor and there was a good
thing the little man one. Yeah, that was an argument. That was an argument of the defense
was that like it's just this big corporation taken on. We're just two little guys in Orlando
and they're coming after us. So it sounds like a disaster all around. Don't forget the
other lawsuit, the lawsuit by the man. Yes. Yes. By truly a little guy who fell into the
water. I don't know about this. Yeah. Someone was leaning against the boat rail, which fell
off and he fell into the water in front of his children who started screaming, the shark's
going to eat daddy. And sure enough, he fell off in most of the ride. It's about four to
five feet deep of water. The parts with the shark are 10 feet deep to hide the animatronics.
He fell off in the 10 foot section, turned around to see this shark coming at him and
they did get him back in the boat and everyone clapped because they thought it was part of
the ride. But then he slipped and fell again. He fell back in a second time. There was a
banana peel that they forgot to take off of the boat. Why did universal insist on this
banana stand? Okay. And bananas. It's like a cartoon like Mr. Magoo goes to Universal
Studios. Size will pay out to that family. And not not the only size will pay out. The
duck stops. Did you guys come across the duck stops? No. Okay. So did you there was an AMA
with a former skipper on Reddit a few years ago and he would he told stories. He posted
pictures of the ride controls. Here are the ride controls. It looks like an ancient ATM.
Okay. Crazy what they used to run. Oh, like right off of your phone is probably as powerful
as like these consoles. Okay. The duck stops. You know, they talked a lot about like there's
a lot of emergency stuff involved. Like all these skippers had a line on them where if
they fell out of the boat or something happened, there's an emergency stop hooked to their
back of their belts. So they fell in the water. Everything would shut down. But the duck stop.
Here's what happens. Okay. In the spring, the lake could be filled with duck families
for whatever reason, ducks and ducklings would always hang out in this body water despite
the loud noise and the explosions and stuff. One time a duck swam right over a mortar as
it went off, sending the duck flying into the boat, bouncing off the canopy and falling
dead and mangled in the lap of a little girl. With the girl thinking the skipper shot the
duck with that 40 millimeter grenade launcher. Separately. He's also getting some hunting
gun. Yeah. The family was compensated greatly by guest relations and we were thus authorized
to perform duck stops or e-stops for duck safety to avoid a similar incident for occurring.
Oh my gosh. The story was thereafter included when training new skippers about emergency
stop procedures. There's a Pixar movie about a family of ducks that grows up on a horrifying
Universal Studios ride. Oh yeah. Where like they believe this to be like part of the ecosystem.
And then one gets murdered? Yeah. Yeah. Like, you know, in every Pixar movie you see a brutal
murder. Oh, okay. Mangled corpse. It's like kind of like the first 10 minutes of up, but
worse. Yeah. Oh, or the scene in the, uh, the good dinosaur where the father dinosaur
gets washed away by a flash flood. That was a brutal movie. It was, uh, not good. The
closest I've ever gone to walking out of a movie. Was the good dinosaur? Was the good
dinosaur? Yeah. It's bad. It's rough. I haven't seen it. I walk out of movies all the time.
It's great. It's a lot of fun. I buy a ticket just so I can walk out. It gives me power,
a sense of it at least in this crumbling world. It was honestly- He's telling me what to do.
Get out of here. I kept saying like, well, it's Pixar. It'll get better. It's Pixar.
It'll get better. And it just never got better. Man. Yeah. You wish you had a, uh, a rifle
to take your anger out at the movie. Or a grenade launcher. Or a duck stop. I mean,
look, if anyone thinks I'm wrong, look how much good dinosaur stuff is in Pixar Pier.
Try and find any. Case closed. Drop the mic. Lock the gates. I'll add a dry mic sound
effect there for you. Um, well, is there more about that? There's also the fact that the,
uh, the company got an anonymous tip from the department of environmental protection
because they were not disposing of pollutants properly from the ride. You know, like the
oil was leaking in a improper way. I would doubt it. That's why they had to, they would
drain it every year in the winter for like a month and shut it down. Cause they would
have to clean up the lagoon and then refill it. And dye the water, which apparently they
did so you could mask the shark being seen underneath. Right. They had to make it darker.
Yeah. Wow. Uh, so there's like kind of, you can sort of see a layer of where like the
dye is and like where like the density changes. Oh man. So I have some sympathy for the screen
ride thing. They're easier. I understand. There was so many catastrophes of like hydraulic
fluid, like shot out one, like they had to drain the lay. They had to try and scrub the
lake because like it made it look electric. Uh, it was like white looking hydraulic fluid
that then made the lake look electric green for like a week. And they, they was like,
okay, I think we can run it anyway. It's not hazardous. And they said like after the first
few guests got their clothes ruined when water splashed on them, they're like, all right,
we got to filter it more. We got to take a few days and just drain this mess. I was reading
here that the, uh, in June, 1995, following anonymous tip, the company was ordered by
the department of environmental protection to fix its improper disposal of pollutants
from the ride during those drainages. Yeah. So they would get rid of all that crap, but
they would have been like dumping them or whatever doing something wrong. Yeah. And
there were, there were all those jaws figures that came to life because of the pollutants
who walked out of the water and like started taking hostages in the park. Walk around characters
at first and then they willingly walked up and started taking pictures. And that's how
they got the idea for the street sharks. Oh, they were walking, talking sharks. Yeah. He
was there. Yeah. He was there and he was like, you know what? This would make a great show.
It was incredible. The coincidence that brought us the magic of street sharks. He just took
a photo and presented it as, this is just some, uh, drawing I made. It looks great.
Yeah. And universal got no money for that either. And that's the biggest shame. Yeah.
I'm on the side of the little guy. So much money on this. I didn't realize this though,
a positive about the ride, the ride at full capacity, 2,500 people an hour. So that was
a lot. It was a people leader. They call it. It was a people leader. The average theme
park ride, 1800 people an hour. So significantly more people. Bring it back. Bring it back.
Get rid of the Harry Potter stuff. Get rid of it. Down. Bringing it back. There is one
still exists. Yeah. Japan. You have been Justin. Yes. In the recent past. As we alluded to
earlier. Yes. I believe you left your girlfriend in Japan to go to this alone.
Yes. So, so John still exists at universal, you know, universal studios, Osaka or universal
studios, Japan, which is one of the weirdest theme park experiences. Cause it is, it's
like not, not like, uh, what a Euro, Euro Disney, the second park, whatever the second
game is Disney studios, studios bad, but it's like weird. It just is a mishmash. Like their
kitty land is like Sanrio, Sesame street and Snoopy Snoopy. Even though it's not here,
famously universal. Yeah. And so they, and they have like, they used to be, I feel like
I wish I would've gone a few years ago because it was like a haven for all the dead rides.
Like back to the future was still there. ET was still there. I mean, he's in Florida,
right. But ET was still there. Backdraft is still there. What? Yes. And it has, it's like
the nicest looking backdraft you ever will see. I'm like, why? I it's insane. So I went
on that and T2 3d. Cause I was like, well, when else am I going to go? Which watching
the intro for terminator two, I don't know if you remember how long and joke filled it
is. Yeah. There is watching somebody do it entirely in Japanese is weird to say the least
hour of stuff. Cause it's like a very like chipper, cheery, like woman going like super
in, in the American version. So I was like, I have a vague recollection of what this is.
But anyway, Marissa was going to something called the golden temple on game for her.
Yeah. Well it's like beautiful and you get to take like a maple, uh, I called it maple
tree way. Cause I think that's a Mario Kart level, but it was like a hanging tram through
like a beautiful maple forest. Wow. Like it's like a real life experience. And then she
went to like a spa and like, just like the things you do that are culturally appropriate
in Japan, actual good experiences to have non trash. Yeah, exactly. I was like, this
is the only remaining jobs ride. So I tried to convince her. I was like, you gotta go
on this. Like we have to go like just, we'll go to Osaka for a day or like half a day.
Like just come with me. We'll go there and I'll do the thing. Like, but we'll fit it
in. She's like, no, I have no desire to go there. We're here for like 10 days. We did
two days in Disney parks. I had a good time. So we split off and I took a bullet train
to Osaka, which was like their side of the country. It was about an hour and a half on
the bullet train. So we've taken many more hours, uh, not, but we, and I went, I timed
it so they had like a cheaper, like $40 to get in after like 4pm sort of thing. And so
I got there and it was, I went alone to universal studios, Osaka. Uh, they did have a cool macha
churros there. Um, but I went on the jaws ride. I don't know how many times, like maybe
like I rushed to it. Nobody was trying to get to the jaws. No, I mean it was like, you
know, there was a line, but it was barely full. Like people wanted to go on Jurassic
park there or, or, you know, like any of the other rides, I went on it maybe seven times
and like five of them were in a row because I was like, I got to get a good Instagram
video of the shark jumping out of the water. Like the perfect, I'll never see this ride
again. Yeah. Uh, and it got to the point where like I was requesting where to sit. Like I
was testing where the bed, like there's nothing sadder than having to like explain why you
want, like getting a video is like, like when people have cool videos, it feels very cool.
Cause you don't know the behind the scenes of it was like, of course, like you're a tool.
It was like the lamest thing. And to the point where they were like laughing at me. Cause
I was the same guy going on the job. And you still don't need a second seat. No, no, no,
no, no. I'm here alone. I'm very much alone. I mean, look, you gotta pick cause I'm, I
believe the Japan version is the same way. It's identical. So the shark pops up five
times on the one side, two times on the other. So you gotta figure it out. What side, what
side, what's your side? Well, I wanted to get my favorite scene in the ride is the boat
house. Yeah. I think it's like, it's a perfect horror movie ride. Cause first it's happy.
Then you turn a corner and you basically see a sinking like jungle cruise asco, one of
your boats that you're in, you see the fin and it's like the first kind of like spotting
of the shark. Yeah. The two C's. Yeah. That's great. And then you go into the boat house
and you get locked in a boat house with the shark, but it's like to hide from it. And
it's one of the coolest moments, horror moments in any theme park ride, I think, because you
know, there is the suspense of like, okay, I think we're okay. Let's just like hang tight
and then things start rattling. It's like the shark is clearly in this small enclosed
space with you and then does jump out and there's like a lightning effect and it looks
so cool. And you escape and there's the fire stuff. And then the ending, you really have
no idea within that room where even in watching the video, I didn't recall, I could not have
guessed which side, where he was going to come from. It doesn't feel like it should be big enough to hold the shark,
which is what makes it scary. It's still a little claustrophobic, especially for a boat
ride, which very rarely do you get like stuck in a tiny spot on a boat ride. And so they
have that and I kept trying to get a shot in there, but I didn't have a good enough
camera. I just had my iPhone that barely worked. It was a few years old. So it was just like,
I was like, I didn't want to ruin the ride and like film it with like a flash on for
other people. Cause also everybody was very scared on this ride. You watch the videos
for Florida, I think a lot of the time and people are either the skippers aren't into
it or if it was like at the end of the rides life, it was, people were just like chanting
shark. Right. Uh, but in Japan, at least the day I went, everybody was very much affected.
Like it was a day one opening of the ride. Also like they keep their rides in impeccable
condition. So like just was perfect. Uh, and so one of the cool things was watching people
get scared every time. That is fun. Which is, I don't know if you guys get, this is
maybe the saddest thing to say, but I'm like, I really like seeing things that I love with
somebody who's never been on it. Oh, I love it. It's the closest you can get from like
to experiencing this for the first time. This is what would happen if any of us had children.
I, that's part of why I'm like, I maybe I'll have children. But that is in place of that.
I just be like, I started like begging friends of mine, like don't go to Disneyland. I go,
come on down. And like, I like, I like that. I like taking people to wrestling for the
first time. Yeah. I went to wrestling for the first time with you. Yes. And it was crazy.
Great. Yeah. Uh, so yes, of course I understand that. So that also, you know what? I'll say
this. I don't care for like the flippant people in Haunted Mansion, like not being, not that
everyone has to be scared or pretend they're scared, but everyone does that faux scream
while they're, when they're in the stretching room, you know, I don't need that. I don't
need people talking along with the narration. I agree with that too. I hate all of this.
You were saying let's official podcast the right edict. If you're listening to this and
you do that shit, cut it out. Cut it out. If you're legit screaming, great. That's,
I love that. That's fun. If it's your first time, if you're a kid, but I don't like the
adults pretending to scream when the lights go out in the stretching room. It's usually
teenagers. Yeah, probably. We're anti-teen on this podcast. Definitely. Sorry. Except
for our teen fans. I'll give this, I think I do think is funny in like less concentration
needed parts of the queue, like as you're loading into doom buggies or any dark ride
where the queue's a little dark. If I think it's very funny to see someone with someone
else and they go like, bah, and they scare and someone gets legitimately scared. I think
that is very funny watching strangers scare each other. Little scares. Yeah. That's actually,
yeah. Let's hear that scare sound. I will tell I vow right now and I hope you forget
that. Next time you and I are on the Haunted Mansion, I will scare you with that noise.
No, I don't want it done to me. I want to witness it. I vow. God damn it. Then maybe
it's not the next time. Maybe it's not the time after that. Maybe it's in two years.
It's unpredictable. But what's going to happen is we're going to be getting out of the elevator
and I'm going to go, ah, and then you're going to get scared. This is like an Anton Sugar.
Like if he doesn't find you to death tomorrow, he will find you years from now. You will
not know when it will happen, but I will do it to you. I will scare you after the elevator.
No, God damn it. If you derive pleasure from it, you got to allow somebody to do it to
you. I suppose that's true. We should mention the Jaws ride in Japan is also in Japanese.
Yes. And they were committed. I was going to ask how are they performing? Because I,
yeah, you see some of these videos of the ride toward the end too. And I'm like, I don't
love their commitment to it. I want commitment, commitment, commitment. I can only speak to
the day I was there, but I think there is, I don't know if it's a cultural thing or cause
I don't know, but it feels like there's an attention to detail in the parks from the
way they're impeccably clean to upkeeping the rides and caring for things to like commitment
to the world that you're living in. And they were every single time, every skipper was
like so intense about it. Like it didn't feel, and also there was a language barrier. I don't
speak the language. So maybe I probably wasn't get it. Like maybe there were bad actors,
but the general language you would have known your Roy Scheider or Brody maybe, I don't
know if they say Roy Scheider, but I think like Brody and Jaws when Steven Spielberg,
those were the English words that appeared at some point, but they were very committed.
And it just felt like, I don't know, I can't imagine that ride is going to last much longer
there. I should go. Oh, the problem is we're only like doing like a seven ish day trip.
And it's like what you're saying, it's six of them are going to be in Tokyo Disney. Right.
Six have to be at Tokyo Disney. So how are we going to find that extra day to go to Osaka?
You can skip that stupid ass Marissa Kyoto tram. Obviously nobody's doing that. Natural
beauty. She was like, it turned down a ride to do other rides. I mean, it was beautiful.
When you came back, she was like, Oh my gosh, I should have gone with you. The thing I went
to today was such a bust. I wish I saw that robot shark. Yeah. I hate it. It was so relaxing.
I really, yeah. It was no fake chard flesh on what I did. I did. I asked her to please
watch the ride through video today before I came here. Cause we were just sitting there
and I was like, Hey, will you at least watch it? Like you've never seen it. You've never,
and you know, I love this ride. It's a reasonable request. Do me this favor. Don't you love me?
Yeah. Well, she likes horror movies a lot. Right. And I think she would really like this ride,
but is it worth it just for that ride for her? Probably not. But for this and like that space
fantasy ride, they have an original coaster. It is great. I get nauseous on spinning things
and it is a spinning coaster. But it's like, I didn't actually, cause I got nauseous on that
crushes coaster. Oh, we skipped that. That line was too crazy. We didn't do it. I felt horrible.
Like it knocked out half of my day, but it has like an animatronic shark in it. It has, you know,
I think Bruce the shark in finding Nemo. That's right. He's Bruce. Yep. As a nod,
a little holly that inside knowledge attorney. I wish you were, I wish you went on the crushes
coaster at the in Paris, but did you feel for jaws while you were spinning around?
I have to do that on every vehicle that goes through well spinning just to,
just because I deliver that joke better than anyone else in, I'd believe it. And on any
continent between you and Steve Slaga, uh, the two people I know, I'll do it. I'll do a Bruce
attorney off with him any day of the week. Let's get him on the show. Let's see who nails it better.
The joke about, uh, jaws is the only fish that can do the backstroke, but
that attorney one that's mine. I've been doing that one for years. I've like, that just conjured
a sense memory. I always wanted to deliver. Yeah. I always wanted to be a skipper wearing that light
blue tee in those jeans shorts. First off, gotta be the most comfortable cast member outfits.
The outfit was something you were like dreaming of wearing. It looked nice. I wanted to, I want it to
look nice. I wouldn't do that. I wanted to say, you know, the best and only boat tours,
Mamity Island, like, you know, you're protected by this 40 millimeter. I tried to get you a couple
years ago. I saw that there was Osaka, Japan, um, like there were auditions for characters
and I tried to get you to audition for Austin powers. They did at least a couple of years ago.
I hate it. I hate it. But maybe that would have been your in, if you would have been Austin over
there for like a couple months, then you could have transitioned to the actual jaws boat ride.
Although I guess maybe they weren't looking for Americans for the jaws boat ride, but you
could have convinced them. I could have, I could have learned just the spiel in Japanese. Oh,
oh yeah. Only those words. Only those words. Yeah. Um, you might be a superstar in Japan by now.
Had you tried to get that. I think that you made a big mistake by not applying for that.
Maybe I am already a stoop superstar in Japan. How do you figure? I mean, I will say when you
come back, when you come back, if people recognize you in Japan, and they only want to ask about
the analytics, we are not that popular in Japan. We have some listeners in Japan. I didn't see a
walk around Sheridan at Universal Studios. I would have rejected him for that. We already got one
Sheridan type already. It was like Ernie Hudson not being allowed to play himself in the Ghost
Busters cartoon. Well, if you're a listener in Japan, please tweet us. Please approach Mike,
but only talk about me. Approach Mike in real life. Jason, if you dreamed of doing that job,
then you got to deliver what apparently is regarded as the most popular line from the ride.
Hey, how many more minutes should we be doing this podcast for?
You aren't taking the bait. You don't know the line. Oh my God. Here it is. Right here.
There it is. I'm making everybody read scripts today. Oh, well yeah. Chief Brody. Well,
I have my favorites. I frankly like the end where they say Chief Brody, you know. Oh, okay. Sure.
He's touching his heart right now just so you know. Do that. He might be having a heart attack.
Chief Brody, clearly not Roy Schneider. Scheider. Scheider. Scheider, excuse me.
He says he'll be there in, hold tight, I'll be there in 10 minutes. And then the skipper always
says 10 minutes, we're going to be shark bait in 10 minutes. Which is they're already shark bait
right now. They're currently shark bait. Yeah, yeah, yeah. True. But there you go. Very good.
Thank you. Some universal property, please hire Jason and Justin. Please hire me while you're at
it. And starting salary for both of you, $35 an hour minimum. That's a great starting salary.
I'm declaring it. Oh, never mind. No, no, no. This is my level. Okay, cool. And I get 10% of that
because I declare it. Finders fee. So universal, call me and I will call Jason and Justin.
And my comment, I guess maybe actually belongs in the section where we talk about plussing it up.
But we're about there. We're about there, I guess. My one complaint is that there's a lot of fresh
faced teens as the skipper on these boats. And if I was planning it out, I would want a very
quint-like boat guy. Yeah. I would want a crusty old man with stories piloting the boat or whatever
you would say driving the boat and then doing all the lines, but it's like, is this guy who's seen
it all or whatever. And he's lost an eye or something to a shark. We need more of that,
I think, if we were going to bring the ride back or let's get some grizzled Japanese,
since there's only one ride left, let's get a grizzled Japanese guy or girl to do it.
I would love that. Because I couldn't think of how I would plus this. I was like, this is a
perfect ride to me. But having a quint-esque, just USS Indianapolis drunk. Oh, yeah. Sure. And you
could have a little sip before each ride. So if you get too close, you smell the whiskey on their
breath. That would be a nice extra touch. I wish they could get eaten or something. That would
be... That would never happen. But seeing somebody get taken out of the boat. That was a rumor that
was going to happen on the new Kong ride that was in the blue skies days. The drivers were going to
be automated? Yeah, there's going to be a robot or something and the Kong would reach in and pull
them out. I haven't been on that ride, but I was excited about it. And then it was mostly screens,
right? It's mostly screens. It's a nice Kong at the end. It's exactly the same. There's one or two
more screens. But the only reason anyone is excited about it is that there is a real... There's a head
of a monkey at the end and it's big. I feel like this is the old screen versus practical debate,
but nothing... The screen technology you'll constantly have to update. I feel like there
is something... I feel like Tony Baxter talks about it. There's something impressive about
seeing something in person and the size that it is. A special effect can't beat that.
And there's something about seeing a giant King Kong robot that will always trump whatever screen
version of it. Right. Because it makes you a little uncomfortable. It makes Scott very
uncomfortable because it's a giant robot in a tiny space. But yes, it's like your brain...
I don't have that problem though. I yelled at Kong every day.
Happily. That's a good point.
That was the highlight.
Yeah, you like the banana breath.
Oh yeah, you know it. Yeah, I got high on that.
Did you catch that difference in Japan? When you go in the boathouse in America,
it just says like boat house or like fish and tackle. In Japan, it says quince.
Yes. Which is great. Which is a little morbid because in the real world
of the ride... So did Quint die in this Amity? Like he dies in the movie?
Well, he... Wait.
Because remember, in this world, you are in Amity. Chief Brody's real.
Right. Maybe it's a memorial boathouse.
Mayor Larry Vaughn. Yeah, that's what I think it was probably like...
Because Quint's dead. Are you saying is Quint not dead or like he would have to be dead if it's
after the first movie? I'm assuming he's dead.
Like why does he have a boathouse there?
Yeah, why is there still a boathouse with his dead man's name on it?
Well, it's Martha Quint. His wife, Martha.
Oh, that's true.
Okay. Yeah.
Yeah.
Was his first name Quint or last name Quint?
Is this the... Last name Quint?
Amity from the book where Richard Dreyfus' character...
Does he sleep with Brody's wife or does he try to sleep with Brody's wife?
Yeah, in the book, he's a lot more of a son of a bitch.
There's a lot more... Yeah, Brody is much less likable also, I think.
Like both... Like there's a lot of like family drama.
Yeah.
The name of the character is Bartholomew Marion Quint.
Bartholomew?
Yep.
That's an insane name.
Grim, seasoned shark hunter.
So you want to hear that full name get said in an otherwise Japanese...
Bartholomew Marion Quint.
Yeah, get on the boat.
If they had him in the queue talking to you instead of WJWS Channel 13,
the local Amity TV station that played in the queue?
Yeah.
Oh, the queue did have a lot... I don't know.
I don't remember the queue for Florida,
but the queue here had a lot of Jaws memorabilia.
Oh, interesting.
So like there was like all the posters.
So like it looked like old stuff that was like passed out,
like movie lobby cards and stuff.
Like the crew jacket?
Yeah, like truly stuff like that.
But then the world of the ride was like what Jason was saying earlier,
like the movie was made based on real events.
The Scream 2 of Jaws, right?
Yeah, you're in real Amity and this is where the movie was filmed
and where the events it was based on took place.
But now the shark is dead and they're aware of the movie and the success of the movie.
Those... every one of those old Universal rides was something like that.
Something like that.
It was convoluted.
And I'm here for it.
I loved it.
And was this the first appearance of a fictional local media company like in Twister?
The storm chasing radio host?
The station that's only within this attraction.
Yeah, could be.
Yeah, those pre-ride videos, they were like real cheapo public access looking...
Hey there Amity.
The morning show.
Yeah, I could not find it.
No one stopped and filmed those and put them on YouTube.
Or if they did, I didn't find them.
Send us some Hey there Amity if you have it.
Yeah, they have them in Japan, I think, but the line was moving so quickly every time.
I think I lingered once and people were like, why are you stopping? What are you doing?
This is a boring line.
What was the merch like at Jaws in Japan?
It was a bummer because I wanted like a cool shirt or...
They had a plush shark.
That was the only thing and it had like Jaws embroidered on it.
But then they had like a Lego knockoff shark.
They didn't even have like a cool keychain or anything.
Like it really... there wasn't much...
I was kind of disappointed in general with merch across... like that and the Disney parks.
Like really?
Disney parks... I mean, I think I care much less about like Mickey and Minnie and that kind of stuff.
I want like ride specific things.
Sure.
So I wanted like, you know, Shurikyu Tundu or whatever.
I wanted like the characters, this unnamed animatronic from a very cool ride in Disney Sea.
Oh boy.
I wanted something of that.
There's not that.
They do have a ride vehicle for the ride in question that we're not...
Oh, interesting.
If you go... and it's hard to find.
So we'll talk about it.
Maybe...
Do you have it?
We don't.
Yes, I did buy it.
Okay.
That was like the coolest piece of merch that they had.
Everything else is just very generic Disney, but like better designed than out here.
That's what I've noticed.
I have... there's an Instagram account I follow that's just Tokyo Disney Sea merchandise.
And they just post there because this person I think has a business where they go to Japan
and sell it and bring it back.
And then send it to America.
Yeah.
But they... what I like, and we mentioned it earlier, they have a lot of country bear plush.
They do.
A lot of good country bear stuff, which they do not have in Florida and it drives me nuts.
They have so much.
I think I got Lindsay... the point was to be shared as a pad.
Yes, yes, yes.
As a country bear.
I've seen it.
She didn't take it.
She would never be so cruel to keep country bear merch from me.
Yeah.
So then they have like a little country bear monogram.
Not monogram, whatever.
They have like a logo pad that you can write on, which was kind of cool.
I think in Japan, the way I understand it, culturally, when people go on vacation,
they bring back a lot for friends and relatives and coworkers and stuff.
So there's a lot of broad merchandise, t-shirts and boxes of candy and office supplies and stuff.
Like stuff that's like broad appeal and you would bring back for people.
They have cookie boxes.
Like cookie boxes and chocolate boxes.
Just like big kind of gift packs.
Yeah.
Like you would give to you like popcorn tin type stuff.
Sure.
Yeah.
And is it like a custom there to if you go get a bunch of stuff for the host of a podcast
that you've been listening to?
Cheaper as I hope so.
Toiletries from the hotel or various...
A robe from the hotel or just several towels with a monogram.
Skeleton key from the hotel.
They just have those lying around.
Yeah.
You have skeleton.
How many skeleton keys?
You have just like a Sheraton skeleton key.
I got a lot, but the skeletons on them scare me.
So I don't open up that drawer that much.
This is a very quick tangent.
Professional wrestler Terry Funk used to have several skeleton keys.
And in the old days, he would just go to hotels and find an empty room and sleep in them.
And he would save money on hotels by not paying for them and sleeping in empty rooms
because he had skeleton keys.
Smart.
Tip for you, Jace.
Yep.
You and Terry Funk, two birds of a feather.
Bring those keys.
Get less afraid of them.
Yeah.
What else we got?
Any plus it up key businesses?
Yeah.
Burn to the...
Eventually, the Jaws in a second will burn, perhaps not for insurance money.
It'll just will, given the ecological issues this riot has had, it will just burn to the
ground at some point in time.
Of course.
Well, first of all, it should still be there.
We've talked about this a lot.
It should still be there.
Universal doesn't have a sense of history.
And I think that the core few rides that they had when they opened in the first few years,
I think that would have been important to the park.
It would have been a nice thing to like Pirates of the Caribbean or Haunted Mansion.
It would have been a nice...
These are still movies that people know and like.
It's not like these movies have faded into obscurity.
This is an awesome movie.
Faded into obscurity.
This is an odd one in that like it did.
Obviously, this was a problematic ride to have open.
It created a ton of issues for them.
But in terms, yeah, obviously, Jaws is still plenty relevant.
And of all the things to...
You totally understand putting Diagon Alley in there.
Of course.
It's amazing.
It makes all the sense in the world.
But yeah, what a bummer that this of all things had to go.
But I guess it's such a big footprint.
And it was the calculation also like where it is as opposed to the first Harry Potter land
so that they can line up the train correctly.
Yes, probably.
That certainly plays a role in it.
But it's still at the expense of our great history.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah, we don't say that a lot.
No, right.
We're not talking about a Confederate statue.
We're talking about the Jaws.
No, I'm at like in terms of the...
Yeah, I know.
I agree.
We're very progressive when it comes to the theme park stuff.
PC culture, we got sharks getting ripped out left and right.
We got to preserve history.
I love this ride.
Yeah, this one for me is...
This is up there with Alien Encounter.
Fuck, what a lost.
In terms of my favorites that I still think about a lot.
Because you're edgy, you're extreme.
I am extreme.
You are the bad boy of the three of us good boys.
That's for sure.
Yeah, that's scale.
It's like if you were to Disneyland and it's like all the cool rides from the first 10 to 20 years
were gone, except for maybe one.
It would feel less special.
Even if it was the coolest rides, it would be awesome.
But it would still, there would be a little bit of something missing from the nostalgia factor,
which I understand Universal isn't going for that as much.
But it is nice to have a couple rides that were like at the opening of a park
to give the park some sense of history.
If you were them, where else does Diagon go?
Well, it's tough because I don't know the boundaries.
I don't know what they have backstage wise.
I don't know.
Like I for sure, you could have lost the Men in Black over, you could have lost...
I do like Men in Black.
Fear factor live.
Sure.
It's a waste of space.
Is it still there?
It's still there.
It doesn't run as well.
It's cheaper.
Is it on the outskirts?
I can't remember.
Where is it on the streets?
It's around the curve.
So it's sort of like next to Men in Black.
It's what's being eyed for the Ministry of Magic, supposedly.
Oh, OK.
I see what you're saying.
Yeah, maybe.
Get Disaster out of there, which got replaced by Fast and Furious, but nobody likes that.
I say I think they should have, if there was a possible way to do it,
they should have killed San Francisco instead of Amity.
Yeah, sure.
Or like...
Much better.
Switch out.
Switch out or take out all the...
I understand they're like it's going through a lot of things.
There's the rocket roller coaster.
What is it called?
Rip ride.
Yeah, yeah.
That's a lot of real estate that that's taken up.
Just disassemble that, put it somewhere else.
I think it's cool, but I don't know.
Put it like hide it right there.
I don't know.
It seems like there was something could have been done.
I'm sure they were also thinking, oh good, this new land won't be as hard to maintain
and we'll make a ton more money.
I'm sure both things...
Expensive water ride.
Yeah, I'm sure they could have put it somewhere else, but they were also very excited to get
this albatross off.
I'm interested that there was a new movie because I feel like that's the only way it
would stay around.
It's like a Jurassic Park, the ride Jurassic World redeco.
Same with Back to the Future, which by the way, when these guys are dead, Spielberg and
Zemeckis, there will be a new Jaws when these guys are dead.
Oh yeah, it's all coming back.
It's all coming back.
A new Jaws could be no worse than the last couple Jaws movies that were already made.
And it could be your child self's favorite movie.
Yeah.
A new Jaws with like multiple sharks.
Great, update it.
Add a couple shark attacks at once in that boathouse.
The shark is neon green.
I don't care.
Just keep it.
It's an alien shark.
That's the new version of Jaws.
Whatever you need to keep this thing around.
Indominus shark.
Left shark from Katy Perry's Super Bowl show.
There it is.
Can't make it cast yet.
There we go.
Better yet, hosting it.
They're just hosting it.
It's left shark but a grizzled old man in the outfit.
Richard Dragoste's character is no longer an oceanographer.
He's a Snapchat star.
Well, and you know what?
It's in Japan and if we're trying to keep this thing hip for millennials,
what better tour guide of anything going on in Japan than Logan Paul?
I thought Logan Paul'd take your hand.
I thought you were going to say another famous American in Japan, Jason Sheridan.
Well sure, that too.
I am welcome in Japan unlike Logan Paul.
That's a good point.
I have done nothing yet to anger the people of Japan.
Oh shit, did this shark kill himself on this electrical line?
Logan Paul, yeah, Logan Paul is selfie videoing himself next to the hanging up Jaws,
hanging up Bruce at the entrance.
Oh man, he hung himself.
Oh shit, he fucking hung himself, dude.
There's the shark.
There's the tie in.
That's how he salvaged it.
You listening, Osaka?
Yeah, call Logan Paul.
Let him back in.
This is his chance to make things right and do what he does the best.
Well folks, I think that might be it.
I think we might have made it.
Justin Michael, you survived Podcast The Ride and thank you for helping us
conquer the menace of Jaws.
Yes, thank you for having me, you guys.
Yeah, it's a real treat.
Where can people find you?
Plug your projects a little bit.
You can find me on Twitter and Instagram at HeyJustin.
I also do a podcast called Batman The Animated Podcast,
which I'd love to have the three of you on to talk about a theme park episode.
Oh yeah, sure.
What did I do?
I did the trial.
The trial, yes.
All the villains putting Batman on trial.
Team up, I love a team up.
Is there some crossover situation?
Was there ever a theme park in the show?
Kind of.
Truly, I saved it and then my podcast just went on a indefinite hiatus.
I was like, this is too much and we all suffered the same fallout.
The fallout of all our good intentions.
Very fun.
So I was like, well, when it comes back, there's an episode called Deep Freeze,
which is Mr. Freeze's return.
There's a Walt Disney-esque villain.
Oh yeah.
The one that created Oceania, which is like an Epcot-esque.
Yeah.
Like Perfect Society.
Yes, and he wants to turn immortal because it's kind of like a play on Disney's head,
whatever, being frozen, but it's really fun.
Every time you would mention your show and I would think of an episode, I double check
and I'd be like, oh, a famous person did that one already.
Oh, the voice of Batman, Paul Dini did that one.
Okay.
Well, this one is one of my true favorite episodes and I've been saving it for years
at this point for the three of you.
Oh boy.
We love it.
Yes.
Down.
And what are you doing on Audible?
The Good Folks at Audible.
Hired me and my buddy, Eric Martin, to make like an improvised narrative.
It's called Bad Reception.
It comes out on August 21st.
Maybe it's out by the time you've heard this.
Yeah.
Audible.com slash Bad Reception.
It's got Paul F. Tompkins and Darcy Carden and Nicole Byer and Lauren Lapkus.
You know, all your favorite pods.
Star-studded cast.
Charmed people.
Darcy Carden, a good person from the good place.
Yes.
On the Good People at Audible.
That's why she's working with us.
Lots of other people who, you know, are great improvisers, you know, as well.
So please.
Do you ever like fit in a joke about like how a lawyer is kind of like a shark?
Do you ever do like funny stuff like that?
Honestly, we could use one for season two.
You know who to call.
Not that other guy, Steve.
But yeah, those are all the things.
Thank you.
This is my dream is to talk to you guys about what we talk about already.
What we already have done many times in person.
We'll continue talking after we turn this off.
We'll start recording the after show, but like more casually somehow.
We'll periscope it.
We'll figure out some way to monetize this too.
And every bit of our conversation.
Yeah, well, we're certainly getting to the point where our whole lives will be documented
and we'll try to make a profit off of them.
I've already had instances of like, oh, remember when we talked about that?
And it was like, oh, we weren't at dinner or anything.
We were on the podcast.
Well, it's all blurring the line, really.
We're all always doing it.
But the official actual podcast can be while you're listening to it and you know where to
find it, but Twitter for it is podcast, the ride and the Instagram is podcast, the ride and
podcast, the ride at Gmail and Facebook.
We have a Facebook group you can join.
And that's fun.
That's a nice little community.
People posting cool stuff sharing tips and Tokyo Disney Day advice, you know,
so do that.
Join that.
What are they up to?
Minimum nine.
Well, they're all very upset with Scott.
Yeah, they all want more than two days for sure.
Someday I shall atone for my huge mistake.
I will say one person just said that I'm going to Tokyo Disney for the very controversial
amount of two days.
That is what someone just posted.
Wow.
I made a controversial choice.
Yeah, it worked out.
I went on every single attraction.
It was definitely an open day.
I would have preferred three, but you know, it was somebody else's trip as well as mine.
Well, this is an important point.
Yes.
Empathy is a bitch.
I'm glad you want that recorded.
Thank you.
Empathy is a bitch.
Thank you for listening.
Thanks again.