FOREVER! DOG!
The place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and bill of bong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight
Podcast The Ride presents
The City Walk Saga
A 19 part, extremely necessary series
Exploring the stores, restaurants, and wonderful magic that make up
Universal City Walk Hollywood
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The City Walk Saga, Sector 2
We're here, we're very early in the run of this
Great endeavor
And I want to say, because I don't think we said it in the first one, our theme song
For this saga, music and lyrics by our very own music maestro
Mike Carlson, who is here today
Vocalz, sung by the great Zach Reno
Our dear friend from the Off Book Podcast
And of course, Scott Gairdner
Am I looking sharp today?
You are looking sharp, and you're
The finder, Scott, you always impress me with
Oh, now we're just being nice to each other, that's nice
You find these amazing oddities of rides and theme parks and you're very good at searching archives
The research is very good
That has been a nice thing about this podcast, I have always had this weird
Wanting to dig and find some little off
Find one thing that's not on the Wikipedia of the rides
I think we owe the audience that
There's some fun odd stuff in this sector and throughout this whole
Series, I'm looking forward to it, and in case people didn't realize, this is the proof
That we really are, we've never done two days in a row of episodes
And we've certainly never done 19 days in a row, here we are
It's really happening, and the other thing that's really happening is that we are joined once again by
The great spirit who overlooks City Walk and guides
Us into these sectors, it's the Sector Keeper
Hello Sector Keeper, very good
Good to see you, your strength brings me strength
Wonderful, we have a long way to go, we have to rebuild you
All the way up to being alive again
Yes, being alive and then allowing me to die and go to heaven
I guess that is what we're doing
And I thank you, you're on this journey
This journey is exciting, yes?
You already look a little better since the first one
I can feel the blood coming back to my face
I can feel that as you
Go into more sectors, I will grow more into my soul
And also on top of that, color is coming back
To your face, and you're also becoming less translucent like a Back to the Future
Photo, and we can see you much more clearly
Now, I think your opacity levels have raised at least 3%
Yes, check out my shirt
Oh, that was one of your favorites back in 1993
When you left this mortal coil
Yeah, don't read
Well, we don't want to get into it
Billy West, on the other hand, still a prolific great
Voiceover actor, and he ended up taking over
For Ren, and in some ways was even better
Yeah, absolutely, very nice
So there's still good men out there, and I hope we're among them
Oh, then we can help you
We're in Sector 2 today, great Sector Keeper
Boys, gather round, gather round, in order to attain the Sector 2 Stone
Please discuss Dodgers Clubhouse Store
The Crepe Cafe, Sock Market
Future Italian Restaurant, and
The now retired Upstart Crow
Okay, can do, we are ready, willing, and able, yes?
Sephora also part of this
He was testing us to make sure
Well, I can understand why you wouldn't want to
Bring it up, but sorry, we have to do the accounting
In case you're joining us for Episode 2, Sector Keeper Perish in the City Walk
Fountain, which we'll cover in a few sectors, and that one might be a dark one for you
We'll try to keep things light, and we can keep things light right now by talking about
The Dodgers Clubhouse Store
Go Dodgers! They're one of the great LA teams represented at
City Walk, well the only great LA team as the Raiders Store
Has not been an LA team for some time
But the Dodgers certainly are the pride of LA
And it's a great store. I can recognize, look, I'm a guy who likes
Like collecting crap, you can see it in the apartment, I have a lot of toys
There are graphic novels, which by the way
Right as I was talking, I got a little distracted, because I was looking at your Leonardo
Over there, does he have a penis? No, no, no, that's his tail
His tail, let me see if I can actually move it, so you're right, it does look like it's just got
A little dangly penis happening here
It's kind of just stuck there
We're going to have to pose it very much like his penis
Yeah, give it a tug until it's clearly not a penis
There was a limited run
Dynamic forces, limited run of ones where you did see
Leonardo's hog, but no, that's definitely supposed to be a tail
It's supposed to be a tail, and it's probably anatomically correct as far as a turtle is concerned
If a turtle was standing upright, his tail would just be dangling there right between his legs
Why did they need to represent this? Because that's not on a suit or anything
This is a mondo turtle, mondo is a company that makes posters and
Different toys, and there's two different heads, one is the red bandanna
For Leonardo, because they all had red in the original Mirage comic, they did not have
The color bandannas, so I believe this is more of a gritty
Ninja turtle, a more original design, and I think the original designs
Had the little tails, had the penises, had the little penises dangling
Not Fort Shildren
It probably says that on the box, adult collectors
You keep it out and open, you display penis
Well I think it's cool, because it's a nice design for the toy
In future, all adult men have Ninja Turtles with penises
Okay, let's get back to the dodger story
Kind of a mic specific
I have just some collectibles, I call them collectibles is what happens
They're not toys necessarily, that's your euphemism for your sex toys
Adults buy toys
It's a lot to explain, in a future sector there's a store
That sells collectibles like this, things from another world
So we can probably talk more about adult collectibles then
This is how much we're avoiding
Talking about sports stuff, I was just trying to talk about turtle dicks
I steered it right into stuff I liked when I was six
This is you getting in the head of a sports freak
That's what I was trying to do
Right, I was imagining, say this was a Ninja Turtles store
And it was at City Walk, if they had the amount
And different types of merchandise and clothing, I would be in heaven
If it was just multiple different Michelangelo toys and t-shirts with Casey Jones
And every version of Casey Jones, it was movie Casey, an early cartoon Casey
And Mirage Comic Casey, but also Archie Comics Casey
Which is a different set of turtle comics that were running at the same time
I would have been, oh my gosh, it would have been heaven for me
So I'm saying it's a good store because I imagined my interest being the Ninja Turtles thing that I liked
When I was a little boy
This metaphor would apply to anything though, Sephora, imagine if Sephora instead of makeup
You have Ninja Turtles things and you've got every type of
Well now you're making all the stores sound really great to me, so you're right about that
I'm just saying the amount and the quantity of things even more so than even
Like if we're talking about Billabong
Which I felt didn't have as much merchandise and didn't have as many options
For whatever, their board shorts and their skateboard decks or whatever
I'm talking about Dodger's, the place was packed, it's a crowded store
I don't have any merchandise, that's sort of especially what I'm saying and that's why I'm trying to pay it a compliment
Do I care about any of it? No, I don't give a shit, it's the Dodgers, it's baseball
I like going to the game, I like all that stuff, but if we're talking
If it was a Ninja Turtles store
Here's a fun fact about the Dodgers, the name comes from, the Dodgers were originally from Brooklyn
Yes, yeah, another fun fact in and of itself
Yeah, and once when I was in New York I took one of those double decker bus tours
And the real New York guy giving the bus tour was very
Adamant about, the Dodgers should have never left Brooklyn
Even the name is Brooklyn, because there used to be these very cumbersome
Trolleys that would come down the avenues in Brooklyn and that's how people
Would get around in the early 20th century
And they would spark, they were constantly sparking from the top
But then they also didn't have great braking systems, so people would dodge out
Of the way when the trolleys were like coming down
That's a weird, so they named the baseball team after like, getting out of the way
Of public transit, that's weird, that's very weird
And those were the days man, leaping away from fires
And giant gnarling mechanisms that might smash into me
You used to name baseball teams after avoiding accidents
Yeah, can't believe they kept that name when they moved to Chavez Ravine
Texas duckers, you would have to duck out of the way of gunfire
Oh the gunfire, they're always shooting those guns down in Texas
The duckers should have stayed in Texas, okay, the Baltimore
Maymes, I guess they're Maymes because they aren't the
Maymers, if you're getting the maimers, the collateral damages
The collateral damages, damages, damages
Oh yeah, I guess that works too, collateral damages, maybe, correct, yes
I'm sure there are in all sports teams related to the hurricane
Avoiders, the punch blockers
Local maladies should always be the source of team names
That is interesting, that is fun, I agree
Can you imagine being a sports fan listening to this, we can't name one player
People punching their radio or their phone
Stop it, feeding up their own podcast
You wanna hear about Pweeg, you fucking nerd
You seal Pweeg
So yeah, I gotta say, it's a great store, I thought it was cool
It's a lot, if you're a Dodgers fan, you'll find something there
It's packed, it's like everything they have at Dodgers Stadium, all in one tiny
city walk location, you can make a custom jersey which I think is cool
You used to be able to get Dodgers dogs up there, oh is that true, in that store
There was like a hot dog stand next to it, or outside of it, but it's gone
They did used to have Dodger dogs within the park, and I would get those
on my lunch breaks as a tour guide, and then I remembered
that hot dogs are not good to have many
times a week, no yeah, nitrates, too many nitrates
I love hot dogs, you and me both sector keepers
You are a child, we miss the days when we could eat
this way, although for Jason those days persist
How many hot dogs a week are you eating, 5, 6?
Well here's the thing with hot dogs, when you're a single man and you buy a pack of hot dogs
You're gonna want to freeze some, because you're gonna get sick of them quick
Cause like, you know, if I buy hot dogs, I'm gonna be eating hot dogs
for a few meals that week, you still buy hot dogs in the store?
How often other than a cookout are you buying hot dogs?
Once every 6 weeks or so?
You buy hot dogs once at home? Every sector keeper, you look shocked
Like what? You eat hot dogs at home?
That's interesting, cause I haven't bought hot dogs for a while, maybe I did it once
like 7 or 8 years ago, I'm not anti-hot dog
If I go to a baseball game I have a hot dog, but I haven't bought hot dogs other than for a cookout
in years. Well sometimes they'll switch it up and do like a kielbasa
Or like, if that week, if it's like, oh I'll make
pasta, you know, pasta with sauce and sausage
You could buy a sausage. Cause like a hot dog really is just bologna
It's the exact same thing as bologna really, it's just like this weird
processed meat. You get the good ones, you get like the kosher, you know, the Nathan's
Well of course there's quality to bologna as well, I'm just saying if you get an Oscar Meyer hot dog or Oscar Meyer
bologna, it's basically the same thing. You've really turned me off with that, I've never been a bologna
guy. Oh so now I've put you off of hot dogs even more
See we weren't a bologna household, but we were a hot dog household, we always had hot dogs
I'll say we were a bologna household and a liver sausage household, which is insane
Oscar Meyer liver sausage in that like tube, sector keeper
you know what I'm talking about? Did you have that when you were alive? Yes, my father would
eat liver sausage sandwiches and you spread it
Yes it's a spread. So this is different than liverwurst, which is similar
We would have liverwurst, scrapple, east coast we would have
I've heard of scrapple. I've never had that. This is all like, I don't know why we were eating like depression
era food in the 1980s and 1990s, but we were. And in the 2010s
Well for Jason, yes, he's still eating scrapple
I, look, I still, my baby boomer parents, you know, I still like
go to the grocery store, it's like alright, need bread milk eggs, you know
I'll often be like, mom why were we eating liver
sausage? Like it's crazy, it's like what even was it?
My family eats very traditionally and I'll get text messages
from my younger sister who's, I think
prone to misspellings and the autocorrects don't always work out and she was complaining
about the poor quality of the meal they had, ham over rice
but also, which is a horrible. Ham over rice? Over. I was
like, why was it dressed up with over? Did my mom tonight
have ham over rice? And you would not have that as a child growing up. No, that was not a common
that's apparently new in the Gairdner household, but the other thing was
she was complaining about the smell of the food that was being prepared all day
in the cock pot. This was a text message
I see, I see. That's good, that's funny. So funny, seeing cock pot
in print. Leonardo cooks in a cock pot. He's a walking
cock pot. See, a nice ham dinner, I would, I feel like we
defaulted to all gratin potatoes. Yeah, that makes sense
That's a fancy potato. Rice is not a thing anyone does. Were you a ham family?
We were not. Oh yeah, ham, pork loins. Pork loins, really?
Yeah, pork chops, I feel like we stopped, we used to be
a lot of pork chops, but I think as we got older, we were all like, these are
dry and kind of like, and then we switched to pork loins, which tend to be a lot
juicier and flavorful. Interesting. If you're just joining us, this is Podcast
the Ride, the podcast about theme parks and rides
and amusement parks. And processed meats. And processed meats.
We ate as children. And facts about, oh no. Oh, sector keeper, we have to keep moving.
Boys, boys, please continue with
the crepe cafe. Well, this is, I mean, this is all me, cause I
This ties right back into food. Yeah, this ties right back into food. So I went to the crepe
cafe. I had a caramel crepe
and I thought it was good. I really like crepes.
I don't get them often. I feel like it's not a thing you get
like on the go or out and about in America a lot. It's not like
an everyday, it's not like a hot dog. Yeah, it's not like my beloved hot
dogs, but I do like crepes. I mean, this one was essentially like, you know,
caramel syrup or spread in the kind of thin
crepey pancake. My big complaint about this
crepe cafe though is they served it to you on a styrofoam plate. If you had
a crepe before, you kind of got to saw through it like a crepe. You got
to saw through it a bit, but like when you're doing that, when you're putting that
extra oomph into like cutting it, if you hit the plate, it's
styrofoam, like that, you don't want bits of styrofoam
like flying everywhere. When you were trying to cut the crepe, did you ever like meet the
metal of the table with the plastic knife?
Well, no, because I had the plate was on a tray
and I never cut through the plate, but I like, you know,
ding the styrofoam a bit. I scored it.
So I would say like crepe cafe, switch to paper plates. Come on, what are you
doing? Also styrofoam in this day and age, like we know it's bad. But paper plates look so,
so cheap. Don't you think the presentation would suffer if you weren't?
No, you can get nice higher quality paper plates.
Stock paper plate. I think styrofoam looks cheaper. I can help.
Oh, yes. Yes, I'll put in a word. With the distributors?
Yes, yes, yes. I think that's smart. It seems like it's a
maybe a profit margins situation. It's, I'm sure
styrofoam is cheaper than like heavy duty paper. Do you think the crepe
cafe is having financial troubles and all crepe
restaurant outside of the... It's been there a while though. This is hanging on.
It's survived a few generations of city walk. Was there a crepe craze?
At some point? I feel like there's been attempts at it
but like... It's been in fits and starts with the crepe craze. It never hit like frozen yogurt did.
It never hit like donuts did. Which is interesting that you bring that up because
the other thing about the crepe cafe is they have a whole side of the menu
that is like European style, like Belgian fries with
a variety of dipping sauces. Which is
interesting because it's like there are savory crepes.
Question mark, not me. I don't, it seems like they're like
the crepes aren't cutting it. We need something else. And fries are
I mean that's a profit. Do we know is that, is there anywhere in the world where
a crepe in a Belgian fry is a meal? Maybe in Europe
I guess. Perhaps in Europe. But like Jason's Kitchen
Oh, I'm not, these are labor intensive foods.
He doesn't have a fryer. I don't have a fryer. An oven fryer, I don't know about oven fries.
Like that's a dicey proposition. You don't buy oven fries ever? Not usually, no.
A bag of oven fries? Not, yeah I don't think. You're making a face like I'm making you sick.
No, I mean I like to like slice up a sweet potato
and dress it with olive oil and bake that a little. That's real good. So it's like
it's kind of like a fry. It's kind of, but like I find oven fries like those
orida oven fries in a bag. I hear what you're saying. Very dry. You just gave
a clue if any young eligible podcast the ride
fans out there want to seduce old Jason Sheridan. I made you
your favorite sweet potato drizzled in olive oil.
With hot dogs. With hot dogs as a side. And a scrapple
in a glass. A scrapple is like a loaf, it's kind of a loaf
a meat, meat-ish loaf. What a first word
to describe to make something attractive. This is a breakfast meat. So you cut slices
and you grill it up so the inside is soft and the outside is crispy. If you go to
a diner outside of Philadelphia or in South Jersey and you look at the breakfast section
your meat choices are many and various. You're talking
bacon, sausage, hot Italian sausage, sweet Italian sausage
scrapple, pork roll. Keep going. Leonardo
dick. Leonardo dick. You're a ghost
too? No, I'm very much alive. I'm
a 32 going on 33 year old band. You talk like from the 1930s.
I don't, you know, you just, you watch enough
like Nick at Night and syndicated like Colgate
variety hour shows that should have burned up in fires
but were somehow preserved. I like that by the end of this we'll realize that Jason is
truly a child ghost from the 1930s and is beginning like hard
tack. Who was diving out of the way of a
cable car careening down the hill and maybe the spark
created kind of a lightning bolt back to the future thing. And he wanted to be a
Pittsburgh diver, a baseball player when he was older. Pittsburgh diver.
Anyway, I liked crepe cafe fine.
I think that $8.50 caramel crepe was okay. I
thought my popcornopolis experience was a lot more fun so
I didn't try any of the savory crepes. You like popcornopolis sector keeper? So many
flavors. It's great. Very fun. It's a fun name. Fun. Yeah.
Well, you know, there's right next door there's a lot of flavors
of socks at, well it's not right next door never mind. Fuck.
I want to talk about the sock market. That's what I'm saying. Sure, yeah.
The Los Angeles sock market, not to be confused with the
Las Vegas sock market or the San Francisco
sock market. So this is a, there's three of them all told and the name
changes depending on where you are. Obviously it's a great pun.
Did you guys clock it as
a stock market? Like
something about removing the T, like the pun was not cleared in the end until I thought
about it for a while. I, like many people that
pass through City Walk for the first so many years of living in Los Angeles and going to City Walk
I didn't even register that it was there. But then when I was aware of the
name, the sock market, I think I did not think about it until
maybe we started doing this series, we talked about doing this saga
and then it was like, oh the sock market, oh
okay, oh stock, okay. Like it was truly not a
like I didn't, the first time I saw it I didn't like stand there looking at it and laughing and going oh my
god that's the greatest. The best jokes take years to hit you.
The logo makes it kind of obvious but they really should have gone
harder with like a graph of arrows pointing up and there's a little of it
but it should be like. Like a picture of Ben Bernanke or something. There should be Ben Bernanke
there should be Alan Greenspan. Well on the
website of the sock market there is
some literature in the About Us about the head of the Federal Reserve
Board, I'm not sure why that's changed. Why there's a D at the end of that.
Don't know, but the head of the Federal Reserve Board is Alan
Seem Span. So they did Sockify
I'm getting all these but I don't care for them. Like I don't
Yeah getting does not equal approval. Yeah it's that, that bugs me
when like you can tell when a company is putting a joke or something out
there but it's like god it's making my skin crawl how this is like
was approved but it's not landing. Uh huh. Well
I think the sock market itself is full of things that might hit that same
criteria. Oh for sure. There's a lot of great sock
comedy going on. Oh my gosh. I mean everybody feel free to
call stuff out. What I think this if you had to ballpark
it does this it's not a bit it's a retail spa that is
not any bigger than this this living room and I think there are I think there are
seven thousand types of socks. Yeah it's like more almost as
packed as the Dodger's store. And it's split between like novelty
and like porno socks. Like sexy
socks. Mike I can see on your computer. Well they call it X-rated is what they have.
If you go on the website there's different categories and they have men's, women's and kids
and then there's shop by design and that says like you can shop by age, animal
argyle, comic, fashion, name socks, novelty patterns, sports and there's collections
flag, artist, photo, NFL player, sports team and then
X-rated. And of course you gotta go right to
X-rated and I'll just start with my favorite sector keeper.
So we're gonna do some bad language here. So if I
get I have some allowance would you boys
go in and buy me some? Oh cause you can't go in and
buy it cause it's too it's X-rated so I wouldn't feel right.
I feel like I could go to jail if I buy you some of these socks. I'll buy you some Homer Simpson socks or
like some Batman socks but not that. I'll say
this though sector keeper you're not aware is that now in this
modern age a lot of things are online so if you can get your hands on
a credit card. Online? Computer, computer like in the lab
at school. People have those in their homes now. Where you play Oregon Trail on?
Yes. So they're like much more advanced now and you can buy things on
the computer so I would say if you can find a credit card
you could buy socks and just pretend you're an adult.
Oh well I'm dead so. That might be dicey.
It might be hard. But maybe maybe. Can you pick pocket
like a person at city walk and get their credit card?
It says you have that ability? Yes well yes I could do
that. I have to continue my training much like Patrick Swayze in the
movie Ghost where. Oh right. So I'm still working
on this. Your ability to manipulate the real world. Yeah my abilities my abilities.
You can appear on podcasts and hold microphones but reaching into somebody's
pocket is a little complicated. It might be a little complicated. So there's like a Vincent Schiavelli
type at city walk also that you've been training with? Another ghost
man I guess? City walk is
filled with ghosts. Oh wow
really? Yes. Really? They walk amongst the entire city yes.
So dimensionally you'll never see them. But you
will never see them. But I see them yes. That sounds horrible. Yeah that's like a scary thing. That's like part of your burden
to bear. Um yeah it's awful.
They just took out the upstart crow which is in this sector
in the crow's nest and that had a big scary crow on the
outside. I mean it was for children but it scared me. Is that crow
stomping around city walk and only you see him? That crow is
the devil's best friend is what we call him. Oh my gosh. Yes yes.
Are you afraid of him like snapping your head off
or something with his giant ghost beak? Sometimes yes but other times
I'll cut deals with him and I'll feed him Menchies and he'll leave
me alone. Oh okay you know how to distract him. Yes. This is your
smart for a little one. Oh thank you. Yeah you can manipulate
ghost birds. I would just be careful of that like ghost artful dodger
that's training orphan ghosts at city walk to pick pocket
nests. Boys boys boys this is why it's so important to
rescue me. Oh okay right right. We're not even close to okay let's talk about these
X-rated socks to save your soul. X-rated socks alright. My
favorite sock and the X-rated sock section is
a sock that has like clouds and like stars maybe and it
says carpe the fuck out of this DM.
Uh. Yeah so sorry for
swearing and cursing. That's hurting my spirit.
Yeah so that's like the first sock you see when you're on the X-rated section
the next sock. When I thought you said wine.
The next sock is as aggressive
and it just says but it's less clever even which the other one wasn't clever
it just says don't let anyone fuck with you and that's
it. What? It just says don't let anyone fuck with you. I don't
know if you're a person who needs that reminder on their socks if you really get
strength from that and you're going to your job and you know some supervisor
is gonna give you a flack. You're like yeah cause like
there's a big or yeah you're like I gotta talk to the boss today and you're like I'm gonna put on my
don't let anyone fuck with you socks. Put on my agro socks
my encouragement socks. No one's gonna fuck with you today. You're the
star. Are you trying to distribute that information to someone else
because it's facing out so other people will read it. Well no it's not facing out
it's on your feet. It says don't let anyone fuck with you like on
this part of your sock. Oh okay. So it's just for you. It's just a little special surprise
for you. If you take your shoes off. Yes. Or if you're wearing
sandals. Sandals with garish printed socks? Yeah
which case you're probably a great candidate for someone to fuck with you.
Yeah. Those are the two
I would say from X when they're calling them X-rated
those are the only two with like F's fucks in them on the website.
Okay good. But then when we were in the store I noticed there are
actual like lingerie and fishnet stocking
but there is actual like sexy stuff for sale. That's one of a few places you can get stockings
Hot Topic being the other one although they're of course deemed to Harley Quinn
at Hot Topic. Sure. But yeah you can get stuff like that
Yeah they call them X-rated. Oh you know I take that
back there's an F word on a woman's sock and it just says I gave a fuck
once. That's one of them.
So cynical. These socks are so cynical. Sorry sector keeper.
I'm just going to run. I'm going to read a bunch of them real quick.
Alright these are the women's socks. Get shit done later.
Don't judge me. Good slash bad weed.
Hellraiser. I don't care. I'm high.
I hate everyone. Kick this day in its
sunshiny ass. Love you weirdo.
My favorite salad is wine. And then stay away
from assholes. My favorite salad
is wine? Yes. This doesn't make any more sense to us
the adults who are a lot. Future weird? Future weird.
Future Winter is like random. It's like seriously random.
If you knew how random it was in 2018. Random equal
funny? It does. For some people. Yes it does.
Commercials think they're funny and they do a lot
of random humor and then people will say like oh that's
so random. So that's like what it's like in 2018.
That's a random punchline? Well
sometimes not. Yeah these are all socks
for someone who you would describe as like lot going on or
coming in hot. But there's other
there's other socks. There's other socks. There's lots of
cute like dogs and cat socks. Well and socks through which you can
proudly represent your sexual preferences
like the sock with an arrow pointing up at you
that says under that I think he's gay.
Really? What? He must feel while wearing that. Or the sorges
talk about pride. The sock that just says proud with rainbow letters.
I mean that's nice. That's good. Next to which and proud is stacked
between bitch and boobies.
This is quite an array. Lesson. And just a couple of notches
over from bacon. Yes I see on the website there's a lot of bacon stuff.
Oh so that's another 2018 comedy thing? Bacon and stuff being described
as epi- bacon. It's hopefully on its way out. People love
bacon. Again tiring. Things being called the pizza of other things.
Beyonce is the pizza of music. I thought you were going to say pizza of bacon.
Beyonce is the pizza of bacon. Jason is trying to push
Beyonce is the scrapple of bacon. Yeah I think it's
time. I think it's time we moved on to bacon and I tried to do pork
roll a few years ago but the north jersey people got very upset because they call it Taylor Ham.
It's a whole thing. It's a whole regional fight. But now we have an audience so if our audience would
please say instead of like bacon or pizza say scrapple
please. Well scrapple is the new thing. And
beseech the- go to the- find the official Twitter of the
sock maker gumball poodle and demand that they
put next to their bacon sock. A sock that says
scrapple. And then maybe Jason you could get one of those and another one that says proud.
So you could have proud and scrapple. Sure. So you could show your pride for your
scrapple. Elon Musk will like tweet scrapple when he's talking about
like a cool thing. That's when we all will have made it as a podcast. Elon Musk is a
cool man in the future. He's good and not at all bad.
Oh yeah if you were curious who the coolest man is in 2018. He's
a bounty hunter?
Well I mean he certainly is a company he's gonna set up to do
that. But it's gonna be in 20 years it's gonna be made. Only hunting rabble rousing
union drive organizers. That's true. No as far
as I know I think he's just like hanging out with the Rick and Morty
staff. But he's not a writer. He doesn't help with Rick and
Morty but he's with them a lot. Funding like
real shady comedy endeavor or is he-
we don't know. There's a lot going on in Southern California. He's stealing
the staff of the onion. Right stealing the staff. There's some juxtaposition
that I noticed in the sock market. There was
a weed leaf socks but they were
right next to the NYPD socks so
that's a lot. That's a trap. That is
a trap. And also
my favorite juxtaposition in the store a sock
with a screaming Donald Trump on it placed next to
a sock with Vladimir Putin.
Which to me is like I do think if I posted this
on the Donald's reddit it might create a furor
like what are they doing? They're trying to at
you know at these Hollywood these liberal locations they're trying to
you know marry these two figures in people's heads via
socks but there's no collusion. So like yeah Trump would go on
a tweet storm railing against the sock market. I think Trump might tweet
about this if he saw it. Or he might say why can't
we why can't I be on a sock next to a sock of one of our so-called
enemies? What bad does that do for us? I think we should do this. We should post
this on reddit. We have people we know who are on reddit a lot. Maybe today
yeah let's see how far it goes. We will get this going on the
day of this episode and see if we can will will Trump tweet about
it by you know four hours later. And I will make
a sock puppet account no pun intended. Oh I see. For like
our the resistance and say like the sock market is clearly
a Kremlin backed psy-op. The sock
market and clearly Wolfgang Puck
had early knowledge about it because Wolfgang Puck Express or
Wolfgang Puck dining got out of there. They got out of the next door location.
He got out of it. Yep. Mueller knows all this
or Mueller is daddy or 76 year old. And Mueller is
dressed as Rocket Raccoon in a meme that you post. Yeah.
I want to how about the proud you wear one sock that says proud and
another sock that says QAnon. Why aren't they appealing to the QAnon crowd?
You know we could also just go back and like start to
make our own juxtaposition. Like you could just take the Trump sock and put it
next to different ones and then be like look what they're stocking next to. Like we could
create our own narrative. Oh yeah. Via the socks
and create maybe a whole like conspiracy theory web of
like a narrative that the sock market is trying to push. Yeah. And really get this thing going.
The sock market is creating a narrative and planning clues. A real number
23 sort of. We could also make
our own socks and like put them in there. Like try to
like add them to the show. Like so like make a Stormy Daniels sock
and just add it to the like the pin next to the Donald Trump
sock. We could do a whole. I mean that's maybe a bit too ambitious
but it's a good idea I think. We can do the low five version of this.
Yeah. We might be able to imply that Trump is interested in seizing the fuck
out of this DM. You know he'd say what you want
about Trump. He seizes the fuck out of every DM. Yeah. From like 11 to
3 PM. He seizes the fuck out of a
small percentage of each DM. He's on a European work day.
Oh. Oh yeah. We've been at this extra
for a while. Boys please move on to future
Italian restaurants. It's okay. Future Italian restaurants. Is it going to be open by the time
we. I don't know when the opening date is. So it's
called Il Vino and this is an Italian restaurant concept that Universal
first introduced. Universal Orlando CityWalk is coming here.
It seems like it's well reviewed in Orlando so I'm excited to have a new food
option at CityWalk. It used to be a Wolfgang Puck. I
don't know that a full spot more like a. Are you going to keep going to restaurants
at CityWalk when this is done? Well it's new.
But not a full spago level
Wolfgang Puck experience. I'm just saying I've consumed my body's weight
and sodium while doing all this. Yeah I mean I went to. We're only two
sectors in. I went to Margaritaville. You've got to drink some water.
Drink some electrolyte water. For not the CityWalk saga I
went to just Margaritaville the other day just with my friend to eat. How dare you.
So like I'm just saying I'm still going casually. Yeah.
Oh boy. I think I might be. I might need a break.
But we'll see. You know things are still. We've got a long ways to go.
That's a long and short of the Italian restaurant. That place is replacing
Wolfgang Puck. Yeah. Again kind of a more like
casual Wolfgang Puck. I never really ate there. It didn't
seem like the full Wolfgang Puck experience. It seemed closer to like the Wolfgang Pucks
that are like at LAX. Hey guess what. I've got a
yeah it was okay. I mean by CityWalk standards it was decent. I've actually got a fact
about one of the neon signs that is above. I'm not sure if it's above
this restaurant but it's in this sector and it's restaurant related.
So all of the neon signs at CityWalk were all bought by the Museum of
Neon Art and Universal cut a deal to bring up all of their
you know their biggest signs and display them.
Make it as you know kinetic street art up there and there is a sign
for a place called Condi's which I think was maybe in like Altadena or in the
San Gabriel Valley somewhere and there's two where there's a face
of a chef on it and apparently there was two
brothers and they would switch off who was facing the public and
seating people and who was back in the kitchen making the food so they would change the sign
every six months based on which brother was going to be cooking. Oh my
god that's so fun. Yeah. The Museum of Neon Art if you're ever in
Los Angeles very cool. Which is now in Glendale. Now in Glendale. It has moved
to a different mall, the mall where Bug Main lives.
There's several attractions, the Museum of Neon Art
and omnipresence of Bug Main and Susan Lucci?
Yes that is the rumor that Susan Lucci. Oh. Are we allowed to say
that? Is this a dox? Well I think that's more public I think than the spirit
of Bug Main. I mean Bug Main is all around us. It's part of the mythology
of the mountain. Oh okay. He lives there I think. Alright as long as that's public. Yeah
but anyway much like Bug Main and his
multiple identities this Conde sign would change
and shift shapes. That's cool. Yeah that's just a fun fact. That is a fun fact.
I'm not sure which, like is it
well he's got a chef's hat so I guess it would be the chef one
who they would portray. But anyway next time you're up there appreciate
that Conde sign and in fact all of the great neon art. The neon art
yeah terrific. And okay Wolfgang Puck we talked about Sephora
I don't know what I got to say about Sephora. It's a
yeah it seems nice. It's one of the new locations at both downtown
Disney and City Walk. Present at both the other being Starbucks. Both sides of
the line. Yeah. I hate to be such like a little boy about it but like Lindsey
goes in there and I like kind of wander around and be like oh well I'm gonna go to another store
oh I'll meet up with you later mom. Like that's basically the feeling of like my mom would go into
like the you know what I'm saying? Right on. I know we're talking about
something you can relate to. Yeah yeah. Go to a fun place. Yeah
I run over to Hot Topic and I look and see if they have any Ninja Turtle
or Harley Quinn stuff that I'm interested in or toys or something. Well you know it's a store with
some fun stuff. Well it's no longer there but the Upstart Crow. Yes.
Which I forget is which is the Italian restaurant replacing that or which
I don't know I'm all discombobulated. Fallen Brothers. Yeah. Fallen Brothers. That's right.
We call them Fallen Brothers the former stores and the Upstart Crow
is there for a long time. It's a
some article that I found where they were talking about you know what
residents want. There was a minute where Universal had to pretend that this was a real city
and they had to talk to locals about what would you want to see in a
thriving shopping living dining community
and apparently quote this article, Residents wanted a bookstore
which explains the presence of the Upstart Crow bookstore and coffee shop. A tiny
intellectual oasis with a big black bird perched on it.
There he is. Sorry he haunts you this day. Yeah yeah.
Look what they, I blame the residents for this. Yeah. That's why that
Crow's wash is in now. Especially the 1990s resident because bookstore with a little cafe
one of my favorite kind of shops because I was a child of the 1990s
like that is a 1990s ass-wrapped store. And every
because every sitcom Friends is a little bookstore
coffee shop. Frasier, Ellen, this was
the 90s. Coffee was new and books were
briefly popular again. You've got Mail is about a big bookstore with a coffee shop in it.
And also, Rest in Tea, I'm sorry to tell you this, Sector Keeper, Borders has since gone under.
Barnes and Noble is still going strong.
And there is a Crown Books, even though that company like went
under, there's a Crown Books in a weird mall over on the other side of the 405.
Yeah there's a couple of those. There's like just like Outliers but they're still exist
Borders gone? Yeah I know it's hard. I always thought
Borders was the cooler one. I always liked Borders more.
How do I buy Lethal Weapon
for $30? On VHS is that where you would go
pick up because they had that big media section. Well now everything
All the books are, now you buy books from a guy
named Jeff Bezos who's even cooler than Elon Musk.
Jeff Bezos, he's a race car
driver? He's probably driven a race, when you have that much money
you can do whatever the fuck you want. He owns the books and the
markets. Yeah he's telling groceries. Buying stuff online, he
sort of like figured out a way to do that and figured out how to like
cripple local economies and pay people
low money wages. We found a new way for just 10 people to be in charge of everything.
That's back in a big, that wasn't
in your childhood. Yeah that's in Jason's childhood.
Yes, your Carnegie's, your Melons, your
Rockefellers. Pre-New Deal stuff, you know, stuff Jason knows from his child.
You like this one new Boss Tweed?
I thankfully was a nemesis of Boss Tweed.
Me and FDR took him down. So he's confirming that he was a child, he is a child
from the 30's. Wow, you guys have so much in common.
Yes, brothers. Both are so ghost. From different eras but
with a big commonality, your ghosthood. So yeah the Upstart Crow
like it was a bookstore but then it also sort of has a section
well much more so than a bookstore. It became
it's like Hollywood junk. Yeah so I'd like to read this Yelp review to show you
what exactly. Yeah. Oh this illustrates the transition.
Well yeah so this is from, I won't say the user, but this is a
person who posts a lot on Yelp. It just says no more books
just a bunch of the same old plastic crap they sell on Hollywood Boulevard.
Who needs another fake Oscar statue anyways? With the S at the end.
Upstart Crow died in the flames of tourism and the bird that rose from
the ashes is a real turkey. The great coffee house and bookstore is
long gone. City Walk needs to take down the sign or change the name to Store
Full of Crap. And then there's a William Shakespeare quote. I must be cruel
only to be kind. Thus bad begins and worse remains behind.
That's an interesting choice because the term Upstart Crow
comes from Shakespeare's rival Robert Greene
in his groats worth
of wit. He describes Shakespeare as an Upstart Crow
beautified with our feathers. So
bodied, owned, Shakespeare eat it. So this was
a good quote to put into this Yelp review of the Upstart Crow at City Walk.
Apropro. Apropo? I still don't know. Did you say
Aprocrow? Oh I wish I did. Oh I wish I said Aprocrow.
You can from now on. Yeah but an Upstart Crow beautified
with our feathers I guess because people would throw feather, tarzan feathers.
I don't quite understand this bird. You aren't that old
of a bird. No I'm not that old. But you know
in the defense of the Upstart Crow there is some excellent
culture going on there which specifically
they sell a very cool item which is
driver's licenses of some of your favorite
stars. This was a big loss.
I have a pile of photos of this nature and
you know, well first of all if you're in the fake ID
market, if you're a youngster like yourself actually if you wanted to
get a drink you could get one of these and you could pose as John Lennon.
People might believe that you're John Lennon. I could use John Lennon's ID
to get naughty socks. Ah yes. It's true. Go straight next
door. Well you gotta get this from a different location now. I think now
your only option for novelty driver's licenses is
35 stores on Hollywood Boulevard. But if you get that head up the hill
and get some rainy socks. Yeah once we free you, once we release you.
The first place I'm going Hollywood Boulevard. Hurray for Hollywood.
This ghost boy is getting a prostitute.
You're making up for lost time.
Let's learn. But let me read
there's a lot of great details about all of these driver's
licenses because like a real driver's license it has a lot of different stats.
You know birth date, the day that it expires and then an area
called restriction. So let me read some of John Lennon's stats
here. You get just height, weight, regular stuff. But then you get license number
FAB4. That's fun. His birth date, his real date
in 1940 and then expires 12-8-1980.
That's insane. That's the most morbid thing I've ever seen.
Real date of John Lennon's murder. I cannot believe they would do that. Why would they do that?
On this fun thing where we remember old cool John Lennon. We have
to remember the date he was shot. Wait what is his address on it too?
Is it the Dakota? It's the Dakota apartment. Jesus Christ.
That is so crazy.
It may as well be covered in blood. Like let's be honest.
What's his name? Chapman. He would love this thing. When it was a
bookstore was this next to a rack of the catcher of the ride?
You could use this as a bookmark. And then this odd
kind of freestyle section, restriction, where in all of these they kind of do
whatever there. His restriction is listed as Yoko Ono.
That's fucked up too. What does that even mean? Yeah very odd.
There's a license, if you keep going there's a license plate for
a driver's license for Jack Bauer. A.K.A. Keith or Sutherland.
Keith or Sutherland. His restriction is
terrorists and he expires never. And of course his license
number 24. If we keep going down the line
Carlos Santana
his class is smooth.
Well that's for sure. I would only buy that if I could
buy the Rob Thomas one. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Restriction. Give me your
heart class. Make it real. Address or else forget
about it. The driver's license
for Halle Berry. She is
a license number, this is very appropriate, license number 34
2236. Upsetting. Yeah, her class is
Oscar, that's true, good for her and her
restriction is diabetes. Does she have
diabetes? Evidently, I sense of Google. God damn it. But that's a fact
you learn from this novelty driver's license. And then
yeah this is, these are incredible. And then one more right under
that, Megan Fuchs whose restriction is Decepticons.
And her across the top says smoking hot.
This is a great area of
merchandise. I would have bought all of them except
I realized why spend $45 when I could take photos
and talk about them on a podcast two years later. If the place was open it would
that is worth investigating like what company made that to really figure out
like to dig deep and figure out like and same with the stock market figure out who is
there's different companies that do it but like figure out the joke writers
maybe like I think one or two big companies own a lot of those
sock lines and just sell them as different like
it's like a Jeff Bezos style scam where it's like
all the same company but they have like different shell companies and they name it different things
yeah or how like Old Navy Gap, Banana Repo
that's all like one umbrella with different lines. Yeah those licenses
the Lenin one is the craziest. It expires. It's insane
yeah if they did that for Princess Diana
and Prince and restriction
fentanyl. Opiates. Like what?
Why is that a fun? Yeah maybe Christian Science
maybe Jehovah's Witness
maybe Good The Store Clothes
maybe Good. Could be true. Alright so not every fallen brother
is a bad fallen brother. Justified. Yeah yeah
ran its course. Stop insulting the dead. Was mine? Aren't you
offended as a dead person? Yes. If they listed if you if they made that
for you and your restriction was disease filled fountains. Yeah if my restriction
was staph infection. And it listed your
expiration the day that the accident happened? Yes and I expired
a week before Mighty Ducks came out
on that sale right? Yeah. You were looking forward to the Mighty Ducks. Yes
oh man. Well you know what under class for you sector keeper
I put first. I think you're a first class kid. Yeah. Boys
thank you boys boys you give me strength. Hey
and by giving me strength I give you this
stone. It's the sector 2 stone. Go ahead hold it
and take a look. Oh wow. Beautiful. Wow it's shaped like the Dakota
apartment. That's right. And John Lennon's body is lying outside of it.
On the back side of it it says Carpe the Fuck out of this DM. Yes.
Wow. You know what that's a more beautiful piece of poetry than anything
that idiot John Lennon ever thought of. Yeah so I mean
thank you for the stone and I feel good about this journey like I really do
I think we're gonna do. I'm so excited to see where it takes us. Your opacity
has increased I think 2 more percent since we started. Yes you brought me great strength and
I thank you so much and just remember to keep on the journey
and to obey the sector scrolls.
Okay. Yes. We'll make sure there's no deviation from
these sector borders that have been set up. Right if it's sector 7
and it's 4 different places we'll stick to those 4 places
and that's what we'll do. Be real firm about this. Yeah. Alright we'll come
back tomorrow for more fun. Uh for more
city walking. Okay. And a lot of fun stuff tomorrow and for the
next 17 days beyond this. I'm going
back to purgatory I'll talk to you later. Okay.
I'll be in every now and then. Take care. See you. Bye bye.
Thank you. See you tomorrow. Good guy. Alright. You guys we'll see you tomorrow.
Forever.
This has been a Forever Dog production. Executive produced
by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gairdner,
Brett Boehm, Joe Cillio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts. Keep up with the latest
Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.