Forever...
Dog.
When your town has let you down
When your port has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll, a place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and bill of bond
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight, tonight...
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gairdner, and our very special guest, Nick Mundy, returning to Podcast the Ride.
Thanks for having me back.
Returning champion.
I always assumed that we would go on some rides on Podcast the Ride.
I feel like I've been bamboozled.
Yet here I am.
Look, it's not necessarily... though Ride is in the title, if you read the full bio, if there is such a thing,
we are about all themed experiences of which Bucatubepo counts, of which stomach rattling restaurants like that count.
Well, it was a ride because I got to pay parking and go on a terrible trip through Universal's valet and parking system.
Oh boy. Well, wait.
Let's save that gold.
That gold is going to have to be for another episode because we have very precise as far as sectors are concerned and there's another parking episode coming up.
Yeah, okay. Real quick. I will come back for that.
Okay. Yes.
Who is the Sector Master?
It's the Sector Keeper, first of all.
And the Sector Keeper is the person who's making sure that we cover all of the areas of CityWalk expeditiously.
He helped us set the boundaries, which are very clear.
Who is this piece of shit?
Hey, hey, don't call him a piece of shit.
He's the ghost of a child who died from a staph infection in the dancing fountains. And he's also simultaneously an ageless being.
Like the Holy Trinity.
The Sector Keeper has been very good to us.
And for you to come in here guns blazing, especially when there's already been some issues about you not adhering to the Sector Keeper's rules.
In fact, I think...
Batman!
There he is!
The Sector Keeper!
He's here!
Batman!
Oh, look! He's grabbed the hidden microphone.
The Sector Keeper has appeared.
You have no idea the Hornet's Nest that you've walked in here.
I didn't even expect that you would insult the Sector Keeper right off the bat, but I'm glad he's here to defend himself.
Boys, boys, it's cold in here.
Oh no, we're making a week.
Sector Keeper, tell us, as you do every episode, please tell us what is in this Sector.
Sector 11. Bukit Abebo.
The Raider image.
Yes, certainly.
And Shoe Palace.
Yes.
Shoe Palace. And Raider store in Bukit Abebo. Is there something in that list that you don't hear?
Yeah, Lids. Superstore.
That's correct.
Not the Lids hat exclusives, but the Lids with the jerseys and the pennants and the t-shirts.
That's okay.
Locker room.
Why? Why?
Oh my god, he's disappearing.
Scott, explain to him.
Why do you want to send my soul to hell?
We're trying to keep him out of hell, Monday.
Here's what happened.
Yesterday, we recorded the episode about Lids.
And Mike dropped the bombshell on us that you have been trying to annex Lids into this Sector, even though we set the rules very clearly.
I have one hobby.
It's Houston Astros.
Fuck you, Sheridan.
He remembers. Monday remembers.
He's got a long memory.
Dodger.
We beat the...
Thank you. And I have two hobbies, Houston Astros and the worst hobby in the world, I admit it, yet I'm in Mike Carlson's place.
I collect Astros hats.
So I frequent Lids a lot.
I have a membership.
Right.
Wait, you're a member of Lids?
Yeah.
What?
I have a membership where I get discounted prices for a yearly fee.
No kidding.
How much is the annual fee on that?
I get like 20% off.
Wow.
But how much is the fee that you pay?
Oh, like $29.95.
Wow.
Worth it?
For this many hats and stuff, yes.
You haven't...
The Sector Keeper went into kind of a purgatory in the mid-90s, so by inflation, that price isn't actually that bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If we made you a chart of how inflation works.
But anyway, are you even...
Sector Keeper, are you even okay with this amount that we've talked about, Lids?
I feel I'm growing weaker.
This is what I was worried about.
Yeah.
We have to...the whole thing here...
I did a nice thing at Lids though.
We'll get to...
Well, yeah.
Here's the thing.
Between yesterday and today, we went to locker room by Lids with you, and you bought us all
hats and presents.
And as I was preparing to come in here and bum rush you, my wife, Erin, wanted me to
issue a statement, which is, I am not part of this, and I love my hat.
So let's be very clear, Erin.
Carlson's wearing the hat.
I got him.
I'd like to say...
Whoa, whoa.
That's where you got that fucking hat from?
Yes.
Nick Nolany bought me a hat.
Michael.
Well, look, Sector Keeper, I'm so sorry.
Hold on.
I'm so sorry.
I just want to say yesterday, I was talking about the fact that the sacred scrolls that
are written on the back of Popcornopolis wrappers say you cannot speak of different sectors
when you're not in the right sector episode.
But I'd like to say I like this hat.
I think this hat is great.
You look like a Beastie Boy.
I look like a Beastie Boy, which is the best compliment you can get.
And Sector Keeper, I'd love to...
I wouldn't mind talking about lids, to be very honest with you.
Hold on.
Mike, you got a hat?
I did get a hat, yeah.
Scott got a hat.
Erin got a hat, my wife got a hat.
Erin got a hat.
Okay.
What'd you say about Yuli?
Huh?
Oh, that he, you know, he said he's racist.
He did a racist thing.
He did.
And he paid for it.
And he apologized.
And he went through and then it was unnecessary to bring it up in the context of the conversation.
Okay?
I think it was good.
Look, here's the thing.
So you don't get a hat.
I'm going to heighten it.
Most baseball players are racist.
That's why there's a lot of good old boys in baseball.
There's a lot of good old boys in baseball.
You don't see baseball players.
There are a lot of racist places and malls.
You don't see a lot of baseball players kneeling for the anthem.
African American children are out all the time.
Okay?
So he, you know what he got in trouble for though?
He said the quiet stuff.
Okay.
What's the second thing?
He said the quiet stuff loud.
Oh boy.
Too far.
All bets are off now.
Your, your boy, Yuli, he said the quiet stuff loud, just like Donald Trump.
And that's why I don't, Republicans don't like him.
And just like Trump, Michael Cohen and Paul Manafort getting these hats, you know, you're
bringing hats in general.
I'm just saying, it seems like a bribe.
It seems like a bribe.
It seems like a drug.
Okay.
A bribe.
I'm issuing.
I want a trash ad hat.
I'm issuing, I'm issuing a ruling.
The sector keeper just came from a dimensional portal, which was outside your apartment.
And now you're inside.
I think for that outburst, I think Jason gets two minutes in the outdoor penalty box.
How does the sector keeper rule out that?
The sector keeper will have the ultimate, that's my proposal to you sector keeper.
It's look, that's tough.
But wait, wait, what does he think?
Yes.
Jason, please think about your sins outside.
What are my sins?
Outside.
You are the man.
I stuck up for you.
I stuck up for you when he was bullying you about not buying a buffet lunch.
And Lundy, think about your sins outside as well.
Lundy goes outside?
You're sending them both together?
Oh yeah, this rules.
What if they never come out of the...
Well, it's two minutes, so we'll set the timer for two minutes.
Two minutes here.
Wait, you're sending them to two minutes in heaven.
They're going to end up making out.
Yeah, they're going to start kissing.
Wait, they have to, wait, they will have no podcast if they go at the same time.
Well, we can, the three of us can talk.
Okay, okay, but I think this will help us deal with one thing at a time.
Okay, so Jason is gone and we can bring him back in.
He'll serve his time and then...
Okay, okay, great.
So, I bought ads, I did a nice thing.
Yeah, I agree.
And that's why Aaron wanted to steer way clear of this.
What's he doing?
All right, he's dealing with other things.
He's on it, but this will help us sort out this conflict.
Now, the Jason conflict may never be settled, but let's talk about your conflict with us.
I may have said some strong words yesterday.
I may have said you were bullying our podcast and the Sector Keeper into submission,
and that you were acting like a biff trying to pull lids into your sector.
But after the events of the last day and what you did for Mike and for my wife,
I feel better about the situation and I feel like the power of friendship is maybe overriding.
Friendship.
Yes, you believe in friendship.
You can feel the power of friendship even in your existential hell.
Good deeds.
Yeah, I think you maybe have reversed some of the things I was mad about.
Lids is a magical place.
Locker room by Lids is an even more magical place because it has jerseys.
Mm-hmm.
All right, look.
And it has famous jerseys such as Goldberg's jersey from The Mighty Ducks.
From The Mighty Ducks.
And it all turned around.
They had The Mighty Ducks jersey from Disney.
Yes, and from the Disney property, which you know I like.
And then they also have the Semi Pro jersey, Jackie Moon's famous jersey from that movie Semi Pro.
You remember that?
Oh, you sucked it.
Sorry.
I don't know that.
I'm sorry.
That's more of a modern movie.
It's a 2000s thing.
You'll get to Semi Pro.
Did he die before Mighty Ducks?
Yes.
Yeah, right before probably.
You were probably looking forward to it coming.
You saw the trailer, I think.
I saw the preview, but I never saw the movie.
And the character, Averman, seemed hilarious.
He certainly was, and I can't wait for you to see his full effect.
But anyway, I guess what I'm...
Josh, did you see Free Willy?
Because Joshua Jackson kind of looks like the kid from Free Willy, but it's not, despite confusion.
Yes, I did see that.
So here's also a full disclosure.
We did an episode two days ago about locker room by Lids, and it's possible that none of us actually went into locker room by Lids.
So now that you've...
Two minutes is up.
All right.
Jason's back in.
Fair enough.
Okay, so here's my thing.
This is my case.
Yes.
Okay, now that I have all the info.
Yeah.
Okay, one, you didn't even talk about locker room by Lids.
You're right.
The most important...
Yes, we did, because it was covered in Uncle Drew stuff.
I spent a significant amount of time at locker room.
Oh, you did.
Talking about Uncle Drew stuff.
A hilarious movie.
And the plethora of World Cup paraphernalia.
Well, look, you found a point of agreement.
You both agree Uncle Drew was great.
But they didn't even go in.
No, I didn't say Uncle Drew.
Okay.
I think I walked by the first time, but I certainly spent more time in it last night when we were there, and you were so nice to buy me this wonderful hat that I like a lot.
Yeah.
Pay off.
And then also, Sheridan didn't even bother to show up to our sector.
That's true.
I don't know if you know this sector keeper.
Absent boys.
Whoa, whoa.
I went to move into Pepo Solo and enjoyed the lunch menu on the cart.
But he called it the wrong name.
He called it Pepo.
I feel like he should maybe go back in the penalty box, but that's too much.
We've lost Jason for too long.
Yeah, we can't have him in more penalty.
The Jason Stans would be furious if I was in the penalty box too much.
Did you calm down in your time in the penalty box?
Did you learn anything?
Do you have a different perspective as we all do?
I mean, as calm as I ever get.
I'm like Bruce Banner.
I'm always angry.
Sure.
Okay.
Well, I guess I think we have to go backwards and do the chronology of this.
I don't know.
I'm not even sure why you didn't end up with Lids in your sector.
There is only.
Okay.
I've been a universal.
We've established the only times I've been a universal city walk is with Mike Carlson.
That's true.
When he's like, Hey, I bought eight tickets for a thing.
Do you want to go instead of the movie theater down the street and pay more money for 3D movies?
I'm like, I'm money you could pay for IMAX.
And then I'm like, uh, and then my wife, the law is like, yeah, let's go be social.
I'm like, fine.
And then I had a theory about how it works and then do the worst version of, uh, parking
and valet.
Yes.
So my experience is with, well, I guess I'm not going to invite you ever.
No, I enjoy it.
We're going to find a new theater.
I thought this whole Burbank thing would change things.
Yeah.
But none of them especially since my movie theater has a Buffalo Wild Wings.
I thought that would entice you more.
Well, but there's a Margaritaville now by the city walk.
God damn it.
And you know, that's good.
Yeah.
But we're not going to talk about it.
It's a different one.
Yeah.
Different sector.
And we certainly can't talk.
So my experiences with city walk are completely, um, based on Mike Carlson.
Okay.
And then what, every time I go, I'm like, I always go to the locker room.
Yeah.
Locker room lids.
Okay.
That's my place.
And then when I was like, Hey, we're doing sectors.
I assumed maybe that was presumptuous by me that I would get the locker room lids and
not the imitation Italian food.
Uh, sir, it was very important to us that you go in a Raiders store for four minutes
and that you eat food that may.
Well, I think we should start from the get-go.
I engaged with the patrons of the Raider image.
Oh, that's true.
Because you, well, I guess we can talk about things in the sector, but I want the official
ruling from the sector keeper.
If we veer into discussion of lids or locker room by lids, does the power of friendship
make this okay?
The power of friendship gives me strength.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Well, look, I'm sorry.
We.
We are the final judge of this whole saga.
Much like Christian God.
Yes.
Much like our beloved Christian God.
We'll get to some of that when we start talking about a certain restaurant.
Oh, that's true.
Okay.
Well, do we go in order of what we did?
Perhaps.
Yeah, let's do that.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, um, Bucca di Beppo.
Yeah.
You ended up with this and this was not really by choice.
I feel like we were giving you, I think we were excited to give you the Raiders, the Raider
image.
That's the strangest things that city walk and this whole lids kerfuffle.
Sure.
I understand that.
Yeah.
But you're a big Raiders.
The Raiders are still here.
Right.
Well, um, they're about to leave to Las Vegas, but they haven't been in LA for a very long
time.
Sector Key.
Yeah.
Actually, when he died, they would have been Oakland again.
Uh huh.
I think so.
What?
Ninety three, 94.
Yeah.
But yeah.
So as far as you know, no, that's the strange thing.
The Raiders are not in LA and haven't been for decades and decades.
Raiders store in it's like Chicago bear store in Indianapolis.
Yeah.
We have that.
They might have that, but it wouldn't make much sense.
Well, here's what I learned is that by going to Raider image.com, I didn't know.
In my mind, that was the only Raider image store.
Would you guys like to guess how many there are in total?
Um, three.
Um, it's a, it's a little few, uh, subtract yours by yours.
It's a, uh, uh, 13.
Wow.
Really?
That's not right.
Um, I don't think any, but there's a fee.
They just opened a couple in Vegas.
Well, yeah.
Preparation for their move.
But one of them is in Moreno Valley, which is, oh, there's a Portillo is a Moreno Valley.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Where Lucasfilm is?
No, no, that's up North.
Okay.
No, this is, this is like weird.
On the way to Palm Springs.
Yeah.
I looked it up.
Um, I take notes.
I have notes with me and we always have notes.
Um, the, uh, I worked far too hard on them and still get accused of not doing research.
Um, you know, you never can win the sector keepers on Twitter, by the way, that's, that's
his right.
He's never experienced it.
And while he's on this mortal coil, as he's going through the series, he's getting stronger
and stronger.
Yes. Yeah. Trying to track down my family.
Yeah. He's missed a lot.
Just getting city walk for his life.
Of all the wonderful things that the sector keeper has missed out on Twitter is certainly
high on the list.
Yeah.
It's a magical world over there.
Seems fun and friendly.
Yeah.
Everybody's great.
It's a real online community.
Big party.
Um, as I was saying, Moreno Valley is 429 miles away from Oakland.
That is the furthest Raiders store.
The Raiders travel, man.
The Raiders travel.
It's one of those teams.
It was like, uh, it wasn't just a team.
It was a fashion icon.
Yeah.
I had a Raiders airbrushed varsity jacket.
Whoa.
As a child.
Yeah.
Airbrushed with what?
I had Raiders for one Christmas.
I got Raiders Zuba's pants.
Wow.
Uh, Raiders turtleneck and a Raiders airbrushed varsity jacket.
I cause I wasn't a Raiders fan.
I was a Bo Jackson fan.
Oh, Jackson to me is, you know, he's my Walt Disney minus the, minus the, oh boy day.
Don't get up in the penalty box.
Sure.
Watch your words.
Actually, isn't he due two minutes in the pen?
No, I, I'm not getting up.
Can't argue with that.
My impression, the way I've always understood it is a Raiders nation.
The Raiders fan base is very intense.
Is that right?
Like it's like it's almost to a cartoonish level.
They're kind of like the bears there.
They don't or the, sorry, the cubs, they were, they just will show up all the time.
They don't demand greatness.
You're saying cause like the cubs famously have like a fan base.
That's like full of like, they're kind of like Jason Mraz listening to guys that dress
like college boys and like are annoying to some people.
Yeah.
Raiders fans are like, it's like if there was a company that had movies and movies and
theme parks, um, and they could not admit any wrongdoing by this company, no matter
if they did wrong and they would still show up in their garish costumes.
Interesting.
Look, we landed that metaphor like a 747 coming in on a runaway.
So smooth.
Look, we've, we've held Disney's feet to the fire on some of the labor issues and we're
very happy with some of that has played out.
We're willing to see wrongdoing.
And with that in mind, I'd like you to say one bad thing about Bo Jackson.
No, fair enough.
Not getting up, not saying no.
He didn't get to like him getting hurt was the worst thing that ever happened to me as
a kid.
He was out for a while.
Oh, he's got his like hip and leg ripped out of his, uh, during like a tackle in 1991 because
my understanding of Bo Jackson from what little I know is that he was playing two sports at
the same time, which is a terrible idea.
It's reeks havoc on your body.
No, it's the greatest thing.
Like he like within 24 hours he hit a home run and scored a touchdown.
I know it's cool.
I agree with you.
It's cool.
It is cool as hell, but it's not like it's bad for you to like just be pushing yourself
that much.
He was beyond human until he got hurt, but he got hurt very clearly.
Also baseball is much easier on the body, right?
We can agree on that.
Yeah, no, not for 162 games.
You're hitting dingers out of the park, your shoulder, your, your knees.
Come on, you're running.
But Bo Jackson was the greatest athlete ever and no one will ever be better.
And the phrase was bow nose.
Yes.
It was like, it was, do you remember that sector key?
Bo knows, those baseball bonus laundry.
He did everything.
He was a great marketer, which you guys would appreciate.
I have a fondness for Bo Jackson because I liked baseball 25 years ago.
So I walked into the Raiders store.
Like, look, I'll play along.
I went to the Raiders store and I, unlike you guys, I made eye contact with the customers,
service people, the employees, the employees.
And I asked them directly, do you have a Bo Jackson Jersey?
And they did, which, okay, that was my main test for this place for the quality, for the
quality of the place.
But it was at the bottom shelf.
I mean, the Raiders have had other players, but Bo Jackson was transcendent.
He was the guy who got me into, I don't know if you remember Zuba's pants, but there was
a big baggie hammer pants with, you know, I had the Zuba's football.
I had the jacket, turtleneck.
I wore it to my brother's birthday and Mr. Gattie's.
It was wonderful.
Is there a photo of you as a child with all of the Raiders stuff on?
I would have to check.
Sure.
Most of my parents, most of our children, childhood photos got thrown out because my
parents stopped caring.
I mean, or they're in a big box.
No one cares.
Maybe in a big box somewhere.
You keep moving forward.
That happened to my photos.
No, no sector keeper.
No, absolutely not.
Your family still loves you.
They still remember.
Oh, now he's kissing up to the sector keeper.
There's a lot of shifting politics in this room.
This, this.
Oh, I know.
I remember the shifting politics because when he stopped Carlson from bullying him about
food and then all of a sudden all the rules get thrown out.
Well, there's no loyalty.
These episodes with you, you just, I don't know, they're testy.
For some reason you bring controversy to the show.
You ignite Jason to accuse all athletes of being racists.
I'm just saying.
What was that?
He said all.
Oh no, not all.
A lot of baseball players.
Nothing you said most.
Well, there's a lot of good old boys.
What was your memory of that?
I said there's a lot of good old boys in baseball.
You know, you don't see a lot of baseball players kneeling for the anthem or making
big political statements like the NFL players or NBA players.
There's articles about this.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, I don't even know what to say.
Sandy walk.
Let's talk about Raiders and Bo Jackson.
Yeah.
So they, so a point for, you know, having a Bo Jackson Jersey, but it wasn't the authentic
Jersey.
It was the replica Jersey, which cost more.
Okay.
What is the distinction?
What quality of the, like the quality of the build and the cut, like the replica jerseys
are, you know, what most people get, but like for the professional collector, which you'll
appreciate it's the, the cut, the same material, you know, the better stitching.
So if you were to like take it, like go back in time with the authentic Jersey and put
it on Bo, the coach and everybody would be like, that looks perfect.
That's right.
Is that what you're saying?
It's exactly the same thing he wore as opposed to a cheaper version of it.
Yes.
I see.
I see that you took it a long time and posed as the team dresser.
Very good.
I believe this.
You're clearly a staff member here and not a time traveler.
And clearly the positions team dresser.
All teams have and have always had.
Bo Jackson, you got a wardrobe right now and get your uniform fixed.
One time I was at a baseball game with my dad and one of his friends and I, and one
of the players had just slid and, uh, you know, gotten a dirt all over their pants.
And I was like, do you think it takes them a long time to wash their uniforms?
Like I thought that the players wash their own uniforms and my dad and his friend laughed
and laughed at me for so long.
Maybe that's maybe that seed of a memory is why I get defensive when we're talking about
sports and strong arm opinions involving sports and sports stores.
I think maybe that's why I lash out at you about things like this.
Why'd you, you never lash out at me.
I well, I did.
Well, you should listen to your list and you'll hear, you'll hear him lashing at you.
The notion of this sector annexing, I don't know.
It just put me in a state.
I, nothing, nothing too bad was said.
You know, Carlson hit me with this and that you guys were texting about the sectors without
me and you know, what can I say?
He got jealous maybe texting.
Uh huh.
Are you corrupt?
Let's finish the story.
Most professional sports are there's rampant corruption.
Oh boy.
Well, I would say corporate, every corporate structure is rampant with.
Governments that just give away, you know, tax bonds, just give away to build a stadium,
the rampant corruption.
It's just, God knows what's going to come out about that LA stadium in a few years.
Are you pulling your phone out for Monday?
Are you going to throw it at Jason?
Are you going to, are you going to do a release embarrassing information?
You should, I was expecting to pull out a handful of pennies and just throw them at
him like you did at the kids at Astroworld.
Disneyland to Anaheim.
These tax agreements are divisive.
So let's rip them up.
Yeah, it's awful.
They're trying to do that because if you take city tax incentives, then you have to, you're
going to have to pay an $18 minimum wage down the line.
So Disney, what Disney is doing is they're trying to say, we'll get rid of the tax breaks
we're getting, but covertly then they won't have to pay the $18 minimum wage into a couple
of years.
So we're on that side.
Look, we straddle both sides of the line.
We're aware of the labor issues and that Disneyland does dirty ball with the, with everyone's
bad.
Yeah.
But have you seen the fake rocks that are going up at Star Wars land because they are
beautiful and I am so excited about them.
They look like just from the movies.
They look like they're from the movies.
Oh man, look like just like last Jedi.
All right.
I'm trying to talk about my sector.
Yeah, all right.
So they didn't have the, the, and I just thought someone of a Bo Jackson stature, right.
Should have not only the full quality Jersey, but granted it wasn't Mitchell and Ness.
And so those are the quote, like better quality replicas.
Right.
But the placement of it was in the bottom, right behind a bunch of stuff instead of right
up front.
Like it was all the way in the back and you could not see it when you entered the store.
Yeah.
I mean, you had to ask.
Yeah, I had to ask.
I couldn't find it.
You would think, Hey man, right.
You want Bo Jackson's Jersey to be held aloft in the rafters as though it were retired.
I want, I want soft lights focusing on it.
Yeah.
Shining upon and constantly like shifting and then refocusing your attention on the
Jackson.
Also is Kansas city Royals Jersey.
I know, I know it's a Raiders image.
You're annexing other teams now into the, this is what I do.
This is all I object to is the forcible annexing.
He was a two sport athlete.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, the reggae, it's all bets are off.
Here's the two.
We got celebrate history.
We should celebrate it.
I also, my memory now of Bo Jackson is that he had one of those handheld LCD games and
it was two.
Do you remember this sector keeper?
Like the tiger electronics.
Yeah.
Like tiger electronics.
It was two sided.
One was baseball, one was football and you'd flip it around.
So you have two screens.
But the radar image is probably just chopping in half and selling an incomplete product.
They're not honoring the true history of Mr. Jackson.
You think that back room at the Raider image, they're destroying Bo Jackson merchandise.
Hmm.
Who's front and center?
Who is displayed?
Oh, they're new players.
Like I saw bobble heads.
I can look up the NFL is too corrupt for me now.
I'll agree with Jason there.
Hey, hey, hey, great.
I can't wait to, I get thrown back in my face.
Yeah.
I, I was looking at the Yelp reviews for Raider Nation.
I walked through it and well, for one thing, much better Yelp, much more positive Yelp
reviews than Shoe Palace.
But Raider, there's some five star reviews for Raider Nation.
Like there's some diehard Raiders fans.
It's like, you know, we, every time we come up here from San Diego, we go to Raider.
I will say this, if I was a Raiders fan, which I am not, I'm a Bo Jackson fan.
Not a bad store.
It's not a bad, it's not a bad store.
We were the only people inside.
I will say that.
Sure.
But there were two employees and they were helpful.
Yeah.
Great customer service.
I appreciated their gusto.
I don't like their planograms.
Their what?
What is that word?
Didn't anyone not work retail?
I worked retail.
That's the...
We didn't have that term at the container store though.
Diagram of product placement.
It was called what?
Planograms.
A planogram?
That was Best Buy.
Oh yeah.
That's what.
Okay.
This is interesting.
I'm surprised this word has not come up in city.
Yeah.
We'll continue to talk about the planograms of the other sectors.
There's no planograms?
Did you not work when you were a kid?
He was a child.
I died in fourth grade.
What do you want?
Child labor laws to be overturned too?
I mow lawns.
That's true.
Oh, when I was fourth grade, I mow lawns all summer so I could buy a Bo Jackson rookie
card.
Really?
It cost me all the money I made, like a couple hundred bucks, and now it's not even listed
in the Beckett Monthly because everything fucking sucks.
Wow.
Yeah.
Are cards not worth what they used to be worth?
Did the card industrial index...
That all collapsed.
Yeah.
In the 90s, everything that was collectible collapsed.
Oh no.
The comic books, oh, Detective Giver, do you have a collection of all this stuff?
Yes.
Do you have all the Jim Lee, you have all the number one X-Men covers that connect it?
Yes, all of the cards.
Those aren't worth shit either?
No, those aren't worth very much.
No, they made a million of them.
My Kenny Lofton rookie card isn't worth anything.
I don't know.
I'm so afraid to say, probably not.
And your college fund made entirely of rare beanie babies might not work out for you.
Oh.
Oh no, he's losing strength.
And your Image Comic Chromium Cover Rob Liefeld's Youngblood comic is for sure not worth anything
anymore.
Is my Luke Skywalker ripped Power of the Force figure still worth something?
No, I don't think so.
But he's super strong.
He is strong and I know exactly what you're talking about.
It doesn't make any sense, but I don't think that's worth very much money.
I could eBay.
That might, the figures can sometimes be worth some money, but I'll say this, all the Force,
excuse me, the Force, the Phantom Menace figures I have in the package, worthless.
God damn it.
Oh, that was a Star Wars.
They made a fourth Star Wars in 1999.
Is this the Star Wars?
Yeah, they were bad, but now they're retroactively good for some reason.
Everyone decided that they're good now.
Oh boy.
Let's not open this can.
It won't work.
Anyway, please move on to Shoe Palace.
This was a thing I came across.
Shoe Palace and Raider Image brought up this fact that neither of the stores at CityWalk
don't validate for parking or the valet, only the table service restaurants.
So there's people mad.
There was a person on the Raider Image page going, I came up here and bought over $300
of Raider merch, some of which started dissolving immediately.
And I paid the $25 parking.
He did buy the good jersey.
Yeah, like after you washed it, it just started wearing away.
And then they got screwed.
Because he didn't get the authentic jersey.
Didn't get the authentic jersey.
That's a better investment.
Shoe Palace only had two Yelp reviews, both one star, but they were those kind of unhinged
Yelp reviews.
So I don't want to chalk that up.
That's a lot to be mad at for Shoe Palace.
Like it's not.
It reminded me of the gas store where it's like very limited stock on display, I felt
like.
The gas store?
Yes.
There's a gas.
Jason calls the gas station the gas store.
Yeah, I go to the gas store.
Anyone need anything at the gas store?
Give me a gallon of unleaded, please.
You got it.
You got an empty milk jug to fill up.
They love when you do that.
Sure do.
Oh man.
So the Shoe Palace.
Shoe Palace.
What do you think?
They have socks there as well as the sock market.
Yeah, there's a small collection of socks.
Now is that the sock store that you pointed out?
We like, ah?
Yeah, we were walking through City Walk and I pointed, I go, look, and it was sock market
and you just like barely acknowledged what I said and we kept walking.
There wasn't enough for you to latch onto with, hey, look.
No, no, he did.
No, like Willy Wonka.
Yeah.
Like, look, look upon these socks.
And then I did what he said.
And you were like, oh, and then we kept walking.
That's a metaphor for how the world treats you and us.
That's true.
Sorry.
No, it's okay.
I understand what my, my lot in life.
So the shoe palace was like, okay, so I'm a big guy.
So I judge it by cross trainers, like new balances, uh, shoes for husky boys, Reebok
cross trainer pumps.
Cause those are that, I mean, those are what you get.
But I mean, if I was in a Michael Jordan shoes, the Jordans, right.
They have a whole giant display of them.
Yeah.
That seemed to be their main.
So that's not a collection I, uh, in engaging.
So both shoes and you're in, there were no Bo Jackson's, uh, there were no Bo Jackson.
Did Bo ever have a shoe?
Oh yeah.
No, he had them.
They were great.
And then Nike doesn't release them or still continuing to make them.
There's no, the Bo Jackson's 15 or 16 that sell out.
Where is Bo been?
Cause Bo has not been culturally as relevant.
We'll get there.
Oh, okay.
When we get to this is, this is, I think is another point of common ground we have.
Cause I am the opposite of spectrum.
I'm a little guy and I find buying shoes a little difficult.
I wear smaller shoes, but I also have like wide feet towards the end.
So it's like, it's a pain in the ass.
What shoes do you wear?
I usually just wear Vans or Converse, but then they, they wear pretty quickly.
Uh, right where like my toes start.
That's the widest.
I like the underarmors too.
Hmm.
That's a good, good rec.
I'm a Converse lately.
That's what I've been wearing in the last couple of years.
I have some Nike though upstairs.
Uh, but Converse fit the best cause I, I have wide feet as well and it's, it's tough sometimes
because not a lot of shoes fit.
These wide feet.
Yep.
So, you know, no bow Jackson's no white feet shoes for smallies or biggies or, or, or tallies.
Um, sorry about the white feet gang.
Yeah.
I was in a room full of lights.
I guess, I guess the shoe palace keeps a certain part of people out.
Hmm.
The wides.
Um, the other thing is I, I'm, I'm having a child.
No wides.
Oh really?
Yeah.
If this were the first time I was hearing it.
That would be so funny if you.
What?
That was the last time I was here.
The last time I was here that was the episode.
Oh yeah.
Right after we recorded.
Yeah.
The extra one episode.
Don't mention having a baby.
Yeah.
But how beautiful if I had found out on air, what a magical real moment that would have
been just like when we, just like this whole sector, uh, inquisition that we did to you.
Real organic moments.
The next baby.
The next baby you have, if you could break it on our show, we would really appreciate
it.
Oh yeah.
It would be so great.
The content would be perfect.
Give us the name.
Well, you're announcing officially Bow Mundy.
Bow Mundy is great.
Little Bow Mundy expectant.
I didn't push that name.
Or even like a world event.
If you happen to see a world event happen on a phone, like when John Cena revealed that
uh, Osama Bin Laden had been eliminated or whatever.
That was Dwayne Johnson.
That was compromised.
No, no.
It was Cena.
Cena announced to a WWF.
To a permanent end.
Cena, Cena learned that Osama Bin Laden had been killed at a WWF house show while he was
out there and somebody whispered it to him and he got on the mic at the show and he said
that he's like, I'd like to make an announcement to the crowd.
We have Osama Bin Laden has been compromised to what was it?
A permanent end.
To a permanent end.
And the audience like roared with approval as if he just won the world title.
There was a festival going on at UCB in LA that day and the person who revealed it there
on stage during our set with Sarah Silverman.
Oh yeah, I remember that.
To like a crowd of 150.
And I revealed it to you.
To us.
Yes, when we were at an improv practice, you and then our friend Anthony Geo, wherever
he is, I remember I ran back in because I was running late.
I was running late to a meeting with a manager that's no longer I'm with.
And I was like, guys, we killed Osama Bin Laden.
We.
But Jwayne Johnson tweeted like two hours before, hey, like American flags.
He knew somehow before the news knew.
Why did the wrestlers know?
The wrestlers know all.
Bizarre.
John Cena and The Rock are essentially troops at this point.
That's true.
Cena still salutes when he comes out as if he was in the military, which he was not.
He just played a man in the military in a movie.
Scott and I were at a bachelor party that weekend and we got so black out drunk.
We all got on a text chain and we were like, did we do it?
Oh, yeah.
Did we done it that Saturday night in Palm Springs?
You forgot.
Like, yeah, we couldn't we couldn't say where what we happened that night.
Like it was the hangover and you were in a hotel room and there was a tiger and then
a dead Osama Bin Laden.
Let's not give this gold away.
This is Hangover 4.
We're rebooting the series.
Yeah.
So shoe pallets.
I'm having a baby.
I had to look at the baby shoes and they were like, OK, this is just a baby thing.
Baby stuff is either really, really cheap or really expensive.
And then if you put a Michael Jordan Jumpman on it, a shoe this big can be ninety nine
dollars.
Like I'm holding.
Yeah.
It's weird that any item that's that small, no matter what it is, could be that much money.
I don't know if that's shoe pallets fault or Michael Jordan's gambling greed.
But I also think it was very inappropriate of shoe pallets to have like the display of
baby shoes, like the big sign at the top say for sale.
Baby shoes never worn.
What?
What was that?
I can get you there.
Yes.
Someone challenged Hemingway to write like a sad six word short story.
And he came up with the phrase for sale.
Baby shoes never worn.
Sectorkeeper, you were in the Hemingway as a little boy.
Yeah, Hemingway rules.
Well, he is getting wiser.
But man, you'll be father.
Yeah.
And I'm not.
And I'm going to teach my kid not to stick to the parameters.
Some bullshit arbitrary child.
Oh, sets down on me.
My kid is going to make his own life.
All right.
Fatherhood lesson number one, fourth grade.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
A staff infection.
Whoa.
He did it to himself.
He's weak.
Fatherhood lesson number one.
Don't yell at children, especially long deceased ones.
I think we've established that I'll yell at children or children's dads if we have to.
You're going to there's going to be your your your child.
I don't know how public you are about the your child will have a.
Bizarre memory of really early on you screaming, no sectors, sectors don't apply to you.
What was dad yelling about?
It haunts me to this day.
I would like to see you get into a little league dad fight with the sector keepers dad,
wherever he may be.
I think that would be.
I played baseball.
I want you to find my dad.
See what I could do.
I'll go through the little league.
You would have played baseball right at the height of like a nightline news stories of
like unhinged baseball parents.
Yes, yes.
I I watched those.
I loved those.
You never knew it would be your dad, though.
What if his dad is Bo?
Oh, my.
And where Bo has been for the last few decades is processing the guilt of I'll get to where
Bo's been.
I'll get to where he's been.
I'm not sold.
And this is a cliffhanger.
Well, let's get to Bucco Di Beppo.
Bo Jackson ties into Bucco Di Beppo.
All right, then I guess we have to.
Bucco Di Beppo.
Let's go.
Yeah, we ate there.
Jason, you did a separate lunch.
I did.
Wait, they only serve family size.
They do not.
They have a smaller lunch menu that is available from 11 a.m. to 3 p.m.
And I left Mike's the other day after working on podcast stuff around two fifteen.
And I called and I said, do you still offer you still offering your lunch menu?
And they're like, yes, until three.
And I went up there and I had a lovely lunch because I'm very interested in a thing I've
seen at CityWalk a number of times now of like either workers from Universal or like
business travelers from the hotels having a solo lunch at the bars at the restaurant.
So I was like, let's see what this experience is like.
And I can have some authentic Italiano food.
So I had a real authentic Italian chicken BLT with garlic fries and sweetened iced tea.
And Saturday, then my dad, you got to write it.
And Monday's voluntarily go into the penalty box to get a break.
I was pretty good.
I thought it was fine.
I had some more stuff to do that thing.
So I didn't want to get a big lasagna.
You know, you miss the entire experience of what Buko De Beppo, a terrible restaurant
is, it's multiple people figure out two dishes that would be the least offensive to them
because it's family style.
Yeah.
Right.
And no one wanted any, no one exactly wanted what we got.
No at the restaurant.
My wife's a vegetarian.
We eat like birds.
You're on a health kick.
You're trying to work out.
None of us wanted to be eating massive Italian food.
And we all got the, no one was happy with the meal.
No.
But no one was, but it was all something someone could eat a little bit of.
Yeah.
We had red wine and that was the best part of the meal probably.
But it was like, there's no entree under $30 that you can get.
It's all family style and it's like 29.99 or higher.
So you must have just ribbon him the whole time about, are you going to spend $30 for
one meal?
Well, I spent $11.
Well, he again, it was a lunch menu.
I mean, for sure.
If, look, if Jason Sheridan went into a Bocca di Beppo alone, especially, and he had to
pay over $20 for a meal, he would have walked right out.
He would have said, no, thank you, sirs and madams.
So what did you guys get?
Because like that's the Italian food you can make in such large quantities and like the
cost of the ingredients is so low.
Everything is expensive there.
But like if you ordered chicken Parmesan, you got like eight of them.
There was no taste.
When you got to the when you got to the crust, you started tasting like something bad.
I don't know what it was, but you would get to the crust and I would be like, how did
it get worse?
And then the crust, like it tasted like the pan or like the oven and not like the fun
or not the cool like, wow, all the ingredients for 20 years, the height of the dinner was
the height.
Yeah, still.
It's like the 15th best cheese bread I've ever had.
So what was on the pizza?
To mushrooms.
That was the one ingredient we could agree with.
Yeah.
Besides nothing vegetarians.
OK.
And then what was the second dish?
It was a spicy chicken reggaeton.
Yeah.
And I actually a solid.
That was much better than the pizza.
Mm hmm.
Sure.
Much better.
You wouldn't give it much.
I'm saying the pizza is an F C minus for the chicken.
It was all just nothing.
Yeah, it existed.
It was kind of a neat environment to eat.
But it's the trick of like no one wanted to be rude or, you know, and everyone wanted
to eat.
So we're just like, OK, what's the bare minimum of food we could all share together?
Because it's like bartering feelings.
Yeah.
And we and we had like a lot to catch up on.
We're good friends.
And I wanted to hear how the baby stuff's coming.
Sure.
It was an enjoyable meal.
It was an enjoyable evening with terrible food.
Yeah.
And we had to like sit through 10 minutes of food decisions and all this negotiation
before we could actually talk.
And no one wanted to be a jerk about it.
So it was all very gingerly.
I wanted to say being a jerk until you were here.
But sector borders.
Yeah.
I saved it up.
We all know to save the best stuff for the year.
So it's like we were all having we were like formulating what we're going to say, what
like snarky things we'll say on the podcast.
No, but the dinner was nice.
Yeah.
Dinner was terrible food, but it was real nice.
I had a great time.
I have some nice things to say about Bucatubeppo.
When my taste was worse in high school, I'd go up there with groups of dorks and we'd
have a good time and spend pretty little because if you're splitting it with six people and
I like how sprawling that campus is, how it's multiple stories and multiple rooms that all
have different vibes.
There's a booth in the kitchen.
Did you see that?
If you walked by there, yeah.
That was very cute.
I think there's a standard of things that are at all Bucatubeppos and that is one of
them.
They have a kitchen of a chef's table.
Do they have a pope room in every book?
They do all have a pope room.
We share a photograph in the pope room.
In the pope room, there is a round table.
Is that offensive to Catholics?
Which I grew up being a Catholic.
I think they got some other issues to worry about as we mentioned it fast.
Bigger fish to fry.
Back in my home state of Pennsylvania, a lot going on there right now with the old Catholics.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
There sure is.
Were you an altar boy, sector keeper?
Oh, no.
I was up for it the week before I died.
Oh, no, you were about to be.
That might have been.
Probably the last act is preferable.
It was good that that happened.
There's a table on what's the lazy Susan.
There's a lazy Susan on top of the round table and there is a the pope's head is trapped
in a cube in the center and taking up valuable food space unless they put the pizzas on top
of the pope's head.
But yeah, every book of De Beppo has the pope room and we have a nice photo.
You can only set me free, but he's buying the picture at the end of the meal.
Is that the pope?
Yes, the pope.
He's like an Italian pizza maker.
Yeah, it's a me, the young pope, Lenny Ballardo, smoke and a young pope.
You love young.
Ten hours of my plus up for Bucca De Beppo is put the young pope in there and then you'll
never have to change it again.
You don't have to keep updating for new popes.
And you know what?
I'm not a food review person.
Maybe people like Bucca De Beppo.
That's just I have this weird expression.
I don't like Italian.
I grew up.
I'm Italian.
So I know eating Italian food.
What is this?
I don't know.
He was racially profiling Jason like you were like the baseball industry.
What were you saying?
I was talking about my culture before I was marginalized.
Represent your people, Mundy.
Yeah, so I don't love Italian restaurants, especially chain restaurants.
Olive Garden, Crab, Macaroni Girl, Crab.
You don't like the chain Italian.
I don't really like Italian restaurants.
I prefer home.
So we were starting in a deficit here just going to an Italian restaurant.
Yeah, the sector I was put in was ill advised, which I said from the get go.
No, you can't say that.
He was very careful setting these rules.
But I did respect the.
Sure, sure.
Also Bo Jackson, his new career is custom making.
He became a chef and he makes like really good meals for school children.
So I'm assuming Bo Jackson food is better than Bucca De Beppo.
Do you think he feeds with Jamie Oliver?
Because that was one of his crusades for a while.
Or are they like allies in that fight?
He's an English chef.
He's that English chef.
He used to have a bunch of TV shows.
I don't know what he's doing now.
I'll answer for Mundy.
No, they're good friends.
OK, great.
Yeah, they're buds.
I think Tiger should make a third tier part of that LCD game.
They should bring it back.
It should be baseball, football.
And on the side, it's a little cooking game.
Yeah, and he has many trays as you can.
Yeah, flip it around.
I mean, it could be an app game and you could just.
This was a sector I wanted to go in with like a kind of a good attitude.
And I tried and the food sucked.
But it was a cool, weird restaurant.
I like, yes, the atmosphere of Bucca De Beppo, which I say I never was in before, is like
kind of awesome.
Yeah, it's another like, some machos, machos where you like it's actually themed very well.
It's highly themed.
If we're talking theme park experience where you do feel like you're in sort of an old
weird restaurant, there's so many rooms.
There's so many photos on the wall.
We were finding many very strange photos.
Bathroom, there's a picture of a bunch of statues with their dicks just flopping out.
Yeah.
There's also like a fake medicine cabinet of like old timey, like, you know, shaving
cream around anymore.
Like, yeah, there's a picture.
Did you shave?
I use the hair mane, the horse mane, like shampoo that was in there for some reason.
I do like the idea that you would take a shower at a Bucca De Beppo.
Yeah.
Like in the VIP lounge.
Don't you come down to dinner looking like that, Jason.
There really should be some more like Italian street characters, street-mosphere characters
at Bucca De Beppo.
I mean, they're universal.
They're busy, you know.
Yeah, Jason, keep marginalizing my culture.
Hey, look, the area I grew up in was all Italian and Irish.
So I've eaten a lot of Italian food.
So he's one of you, is what he's saying.
Oh, so it's OK.
Just like the good old boys who grew up a certain way and maybe didn't understand, changed
cultures.
There's the truth.
We all shared the boats over, you know.
So it's kind of like Yuli, who grew up in Cuba and maybe didn't understand things and
then then apologized, yet it's still brought up.
And then he and then he was suspended for five games and, you know, apologized to him
now.
All right.
But I do agree with what you're saying.
Ignore it.
Not happy he didn't do it.
But, you know, I especially when there are like there's McKelley's right down the road
on Cuenca Ventura, like a solid Italian restaurant.
There's Pinocchio's right here in Burbank.
I also prefer home Italian cooking.
But like there are better cheap, like better decent Italian places around.
If you're going to make a point that there's better restaurants than city, why are we talking
about restaurants outside the sector?
I would interject, but your corruption drained my strength.
Oh, no.
So Monday, I feel like Monday's been turning leaves and Jason has become more villainous.
All of us.
All right.
The friendship has a blast.
You're not being boys.
You're being bad.
Oh, no.
Well, then let me let me reach out a hand of friendship.
Me and I both went in with skepticism of this, you know, cartoon Italian restaurant.
So we went in with skepticism and agree the food was not the most amazing.
The skepticism.
Yeah.
And that's the way that that's common ground.
So you're friends now.
I don't think we were ever not friends.
What do you what's your rule?
What do you feel about afterwards?
I work with my friends to OK, we went through our sectors and I was like, OK.
OK, as friends, let's go to Lids locker room because two sectors back.
Well, it's not about sectors when it's about friendship.
We're going to a baseball game tonight.
Yeah.
And Scott's wife, Erin, doesn't exactly love baseball, but she wants to go because, you
know, my wife's there and other people are there.
And I wanted to make her feel comfortable.
So while while there and we were looking around, by the way, Lids locker room had both a Bo
Jackson Raiders jersey and a Bo Jackson Kansas City jersey.
And they even had multiple both way more bows than the Raiders store.
Yes.
Whoa.
Well, that's something that real that notches down the Raider image.
You were very impressed by that.
Wow.
And then so I wanted Erin to feel comfortable because we're going with a bunch of Astros
fans.
So I got Erin and Astros had had nothing to do with my friendship with Erin has nothing
to do with the sectors or this podcast.
It hasn't been clouded by bullshit like what we all do to each other's friendships.
We rip each other apart.
Yeah.
And create barriers.
Maybe that's what you know, with Erin and I'm doing my friend's husband's podcast right
now.
So that doesn't illustrate the power of friendship.
You made me see.
I'm not done.
Then Mike Carlson is a man who enjoys many pursuits and he has it within his heart that
he wants to get become a baseball fan.
And he went to a Cubs game and he keeps talking about the Cubs game because he got the best
tickets from an old crazy millionaire.
And he got to experience that with his dad and his dad, me and his dad have never met,
but we're good friends because how did that happen?
Oh, your dad's your friend to dad every day at dad's everywhere.
There's something about you.
There's there's like a genealogy or something that dad's latch onto.
And out of all the people my dad knows exist that I'm friends with you, that he's never
of all the people he knows that I'm friends with that he's never met.
You were the one he's latched onto and he gave you some cards.
He said baseball cards during the World Series.
He was very supportive.
He gave me some baseball cards.
He's a big baseball fan.
So I wanted to repay him the favor of the baseball cards by getting his son a Cubs hat
of his favorite team.
So maybe their strength of baseball and father and son relationship can grow even more.
So that's the right way because his dad already has a Cubs hat.
Now his son has a Cubs hat.
My first Cubs had in probably 15, 20 years.
And also you look like a beastie boy.
And I look like a beastie boy.
So I was not trying to bribe anyone about sectors.
I was not trying to, you know, corrupt the system.
What I was trying to do was bring friendship to my friend, my friend and his son's podcast
and my friend and her husband's podcast.
Are you serious to the rumor that the receipt for those hats is in that National Enquirer
safe?
The second thing, I don't know what you're talking about.
Are you talking about Geraldo's vault?
No, the safe with all the Trump dirt.
There's a safe with Trump dirt?
Oh yeah, the National Enquirer head has like a safe with Trump dirt.
There's a joke about Topical News story.
Okay, you know what?
The guy was granted immunity.
Get in there.
You should just get in the box.
No, this is my show.
You should say Trump.
Oh, Donald Trump.
He's a business man.
From this pizza commercial.
You know what I'm talking about.
Trump's so funny with Kevin McAllister.
Yeah, he is pretty.
Things went a little awry with old Trump and you'll, you'll hope, maybe hopefully you won't
have to catch up on all of it.
Maybe it'll be solved by the time your soul is free.
For a sector that includes Bukita Beppo, bad man made the experience family style.
Oh yeah, you're very right.
And I think what I was, I would thought this might end up being a combative episode and
I guess at times it was, but I think it's ended up being extremely heartwarming.
And you know what you bring up Donald Trump, just to catch you up, Donald Trump is talking
about building walls between the US and Mexico and splitting up families and that kind of
thing.
Yeah.
And, and you know, maybe I'm learning a lesson here, which is that division and putting stores
into different arbitrary boxes.
Maybe it only splits us up and makes us fight and hurts friendship bonds and family bonds.
Maybe I don't know, maybe sectors are what's truly bad.
Am I bad man?
Are you the devil?
Yes.
Oh my God.
But as we've learned, I think there's, I think there's hope for you.
Yes.
We've, we've all, this has been such a transformative experience.
And if we have in fact learned that you were the devil, I think you can become all the
way good once more.
Thank you.
Boys, boys, thank you.
Look what it is.
It's the stone.
It's a sector 11 stone.
We unlock the sector stone.
We always get a stone at the end.
It's half Bo Jackson Royals Jersey, half Bo Jackson Raiders Jersey, Zubas pants, Raiders
hats, and a big bowl of pasta with a wide shoe in it.
Well, what a shoe.
Wow.
That's a complicated, complicated stone.
These are all things I'll wear.
Yeah.
You've never been so represented in one sector.
Thank you sector boy.
Keeper, oh keeper.
I think we all are going to have to hug it out after this.
Yeah.
This, I'm so happy that this ended on such an uplifting note.
And while we will continue to go through city walk sector by sector, I don't know.
I do.
I kind of, when this is done, I think, uh, I don't think we should, I think, I think
maybe the sector system has to be dismantled once and for all.
Well, I think this, this is a story of, of, you know, saving the sector keeper soul and
it's redemption.
So to go back to Christian iconography, it's like the reverse story of Lucifer.
Lucifer was an angel who fell from heaven.
You are getting out of hell and being elevated to a high point.
City walk is on a tall hill and soon you will ascend from city walk when we finally free
you.
I died when I was in fourth grade, but I think I understand what you said.
Yes.
City walk is kind of a Holy land and maybe all of these sector talks are like the disputes
between the borders, but we've found peace here today.
I like to think of city walk is like a rainbow bridge sort of as a conduit to different worlds
and different realities.
Mundy, what do you like to think of city walk?
Can we do an appitow style, uh, alt run on what we think city walk is like?
It's that bullshit place where they screwed you out of your valet ticket and they said
we got there early.
Talk about that.
That's in a different sector.
That's sector 19.
Sector 19.
Okay.
Look, before this all unravels again.
I'm hiding out there.
What do you do?
Sector 19.
Oh no, he's going to punch through the screen door.
No.
Um, Mundy, thanks for being on podcast.
Thank you.
Thank you for having me again.
I can't.
Can we talk about some rides next time?
No.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I appreciate on that.
Uh, all right.
We'll see at the baseball game tonight.
Yeah.
We'll try to put all this behind us.
Um, and set sector keeper.
Do you want to?
By the way, the dizzy used to own the angel stadium.
So there's, uh, and I was going to say, maybe if you want to have a little fun, like from
a popular movie, if you wanted to swing down to the angel stadium and maybe help some of
the players, uh, make some catches and do some batting, Danny Glover, he, there's, uh,
he might be there.
I'm not sure.
He knows angels in the outfield, but he doesn't know mighty ducks.
I think it's about rec a city walk opened in 93 and then, and that was when as you give
me strength, I remember pop culture.
Yeah.
It's all he would be.
Hey, if you help the angels tonight, I swear to God, I will go the news.
I will, if you help the angels, I will, I will bring the whole thing down.
Okay, great.
So we are ending on threatening our ghost child.
Uh, he's a devil.
He just said he might angels in the outfield, the Astros are playing the angels.
I'm not going to like, we're in a pen race.
Okay.
The angels are shit right now.
I'm not going to let some angel, like he helped the team might try to catch more balls.
First of all, he's actually kind of established.
He's more of a little devil.
Let's be honest.
So like a little devil, you know, who likes little devils, little stinkers.
Are you calling yourself a little stinker?
All right.
Fair enough.
So we'll stinker.
Thank you, bad man.
Hopefully tonight at the angels game, there are no devils in the outfield.
See you tomorrow.
Everyone.
Bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett bomb, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows
on apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.