Forever...
Dog!
When your town has let you down
When your porch has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll, a place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight, tonight
Hello, we're cresting the hill, we've almost made it.
We're so close to the end of this.
Joining us today, writer on People of Earth and the upcoming NBC show, I Feel Bad, Nick Mondernock.
Hey, thanks for having me.
Hello.
Thank you for being here.
I'm so excited to talk about this sector with you guys.
I think you got a great one.
I got a great one.
And it's an interesting one because this one is entirely Fallen Brothers.
Yes.
It's all things that aren't there anymore, including one that was very recently demolished.
Now, the building of one is still around.
So there's remnants of all of it, but it's all experiences you can no longer have.
And we're relying on your memories here today.
It's a haunted episode.
It's a haunting, haunted episode.
Speaking of haunted.
Oh!
Boys, boys, boys.
He's with us.
Hello.
You never know when these start.
It's the sector clipper.
He's back.
Boys, how are you?
Good.
Wow.
You came in and your iconic way of no sound or interesting ghostly way of appearing, we
just turn and you're there.
Yes.
My soul is feeling fulfilled.
Thank you.
You're at sector 17.
Oh, great.
Yeah.
You're feeling good because we're almost there.
So many stones have been...
You give us the stones.
Yes.
I send them USPS because sometimes I can't make it.
You know I have a job, right?
Oh, really?
You mentioned your job.
I'm still working at the admissions gate in heaven or in hell.
Oh, that's right.
Okay.
But hopefully my skills apply in heaven when you save my soul.
I'm glad you remembered from three days ago because I've been...
Look, the last three days have been a fog.
Of course.
When you escape, are you going to try to get our job at City Walk?
If you'll give me a reference.
Oh, cool.
Oh, yeah.
I can actually...
I do have a connection.
My older brother used to sell light up swords there at City Walk.
I'd love to put...
I can totally look that up.
No higher praise.
Yeah.
Wow.
No kidding.
How long did he hold that down for?
I think...
Again, this is an easy summer.
I think he did this like a summer of it and yeah, you just had like just a bag of those
like neon glow swords.
I think he had a blast.
Excellent.
You've given me so much strength that being at sector 17.
Banjo-Kazooie.
White 2K bug.
Oh.
All these things you missed.
They're coming to you now.
Winter Olympics in Salt Lake City.
Thank you, boys.
Thank you.
Oh, you're seeing all the pop culture you missed.
Wonderful.
Yes.
You're giving me great strength.
Is it...
And it's give...
You're enjoying it?
It's giving you joy?
Yes.
And it would bring me greater joy.
The sector 17 stone.
Would you like your assignment?
Oh, of course.
Well, yes.
Yes.
Give us the places and we'll get you that stone or we'll get it from you rather.
You remember how it works.
Yes, of course we all remember.
Sector 17.
Gibson Amplitheater.
Saddle Ranch.
And Marvel Mania.
And some ghostly phlegm in your throat there.
It's an amphitheater.
I think you put an L in there.
Yes, I was...
Wow, even human flaws are coming back to you.
Yes, it's very nice.
Thank you.
That's why you're becoming so human.
Yeah.
I can't wait to sprain my ankle again.
You wouldn't think that's something you would miss.
No, but you do as a ghost.
You sprained your ankle and that's how you drowned in the fountain.
No, I didn't drown.
I died of a staph infection.
Oh, right.
But it forced you to fall down.
Yes.
I think that's why I was thinking of it.
It forced you to fall down and you were like, you couldn't get up for a while.
So you're exposed to more water than the average child in the fountain.
Yes, you're right.
You're right.
The water filled my lungs inducing the coma.
But boys, boys, let's focus.
Let's focus.
Yeah.
I mean, where do we begin?
I guess, well, let's kick it off with the Gibson amphitheater.
Yeah.
So this was the concert venue that was at Universal for many years, I believe, opened
in the 70s.
And it apparently was part of the tour.
It was like the slope and the seats.
It was outdoors, first of all, to begin with.
And it was for stunt shows, I think.
But that didn't, you know, those are only used during the day.
And supposedly some employee who was probably not compensated properly for the idea was,
he said, why don't we have bands come play at night?
And with the kickoff of Jesus Christ Superstar in, I want to say 1972, though I could be
wrong, it became one of LA's great concert destinations until it closed down for the
Harry Potter experience to be opened up.
It's funny, when I started going through it, like, I think by the end, the acts kind of
like whittled down a little bit.
And I was like, so ready to laugh, but they actually had huge like radiohead toward there.
I think they had like they had like some pretty massive acts.
Oh, here's one that I thought was so interesting.
The Dalai Lama was really the Dalai Lama came and did like and did like, you know, a talk
or whatever that is.
So I love the idea that the Dalai Lama was at City Walk for like a day, a night or so
that walking around and were people like scalping tickets.
Who opened for him?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Right, right.
I well, stemming from that, you might have found in the same list is similar area.
Pope John Paul II also spoke at the Gibson Amphitheater, at that time, the Universal
Amphitheater.
He was doing a tour of LA and did mass at Dodger Stadium.
Yeah.
And he did this special event at the Universal Amphitheater.
Really glad I came across this right before we recorded.
It was an event where you could be there in person and see the pontiff with your own eyes.
But also, this event was simulcast to similar sized venues all across the country in St.
Louis and Denver.
And using satellite technology, all these cities were, you know, uplinked and able to
experience the pope all at the same time.
And the name of this event was Papal Space Bridge 87.
That's one way of describing like internet technology and broadcast.
What essentially is a conference call today was regarded as a space bridge.
Space bridge.
That's like Thor's Rainbow Bridge that two realms are connected by.
Heimdall is the one responsible for guarding.
And space bridge.
That's crazy.
It's such a fun name, too.
The Sector Stones will open the space bridge for me to go to heaven.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's what will take you back off of the love radiating from Pope John Paul II,
who's left this mortal coil.
But he's in heaven.
You'll meet him.
He'll be my guide.
Wow.
And you'll be it'll as you cross the bridge, it'll be playing the anthem of city walk,
Gasolina.
I believe we established also John Paul II's favorite song.
Daddy Yankee will drive me in a golf cart.
There was a part of it.
I bet now it's his favorite song, but I bet as of Papal Space Bridge 87, his favorite
song was the song played for him on guitar by a man with no arms who played with his
feet.
That happened at Papal Space Bridge 87 at the Universal Amphitheater.
That happened at Papal Space Bridge 87, but also happened at Hoover School, the elementary
school I went to when in 1993.
Hoover School 93.
Is it the same guitarist?
It had to be.
Right.
There could have been so many.
Maybe he's the space bridge.
Maybe he's really what is uniting us all.
His music and his guitar is like Heimdall's sword that unlocks the bridge.
So there's hardly any events more special than Papal Space Bridge, but did you guys
get to...
I grew up in LA, so I saw some stuff there and Nick, I imagine you did too.
I'm a Valley kid, so I was there.
I'm actually shocked that I didn't.
I looked through these.
Really?
I was like, how did I miss...
All American Reject seems to have been there every other weekend for years.
And I loved so many pop punk, which is totally what I was into.
I can't believe I missed that.
Oh, gotcha.
I have a friend, my friend Perry's I think snuck backstage and we had a Weezer thing.
Yeah.
And got to land like Meta, like got pictures of it.
It might have been Weezer, Antonacious D touring together possibly.
Yeah, there were great concerts there.
I saw Weezer there.
Not on that tour, but on the, when they were touring their famous albums, their classic
albums Blue and Pinkerton.
First night they would do Blue album, second night they would do Pinkerton.
I only went to Pinkerton.
I was trying to save money at the time and Pinkerton being my favorite album of theirs.
Oh, gotcha.
And it was very, they did half of the new Weezer and then half old Weezer where Rivers
dressed up like he did when he was 22.
And he dressed up.
Oh wow.
So the first, yeah.
So Weezer was going through a phase where they had Josh Fries, who was like a famous
kind of drummer who played with like everyone from like Nine Inch Nails to I forget, he
was playing with the replacements a couple years ago.
Was he in with like the Queens of the Stone Age world?
Maybe.
Yeah, he's played with everybody.
He was playing drums.
They took Pat from Weezer off the drums.
He was playing guitar.
Rivers was not playing any guitar.
He was just being a slick front man and he had a trampoline on stage and he would jump
up and down and like to the point where you would be like, he's going to, excuse me, he's
going to fall and hurt himself.
Like he was like kind of this like guy like very stilted with his arms in the air and
like you're like, what is this?
I don't think coordinated when I think of Rurik's call.
I'm not thinking like, yeah.
I saw him do Jimmy Kimmel Live and he had like a ukulele for no reason and he like started
smashing it and you're like getting the sense that he's out of control.
But the first part of it, he's so he's just on the mic and he played, they played stuff
like Suzanne, which is one of the best songs, which is great.
And then there was like an intermission and he came out and he was old and now Pat was
back on the drums.
He was wearing his like sweater vest again, like he was in the mid nineties and then they
just did Pinkerton all the way through, which was great.
But it was very weird that he played Rivers like cosplay.
He played as himself on the show.
My theory, I've said this to you, not on the podcast, is that Weezer is our Beach Boys.
They're the band like he's going to be, he will dye his hair black.
He will be doing the, he will still be wearing sweaters progressively bigger and bigger as
he gains age and weight.
We like, we will be, Rivers is not going anywhere until he's 87 years old and they'll start
doing, it'll be the Christmas album.
We do the, we do Pinkerton again, but with an orchestra.
They have like a cruise ship, but like, we're already in a cruise, there's a Weezer cruise
to like, just absolutely light up your point.
Like yeah, that's, they're in the, they're in the cruise world.
This is a, here's a bit of Weezer trivia.
I don't know if you know this, you know, they're, they're, they're big hit, they're smash hit
new song, Africa.
You know, that the public has embraced so thoroughly.
Africa actually, they didn't write Africa.
Africa was this older band called Toto in the eighties and my, and my parents saw them
at the, the Gibson.
Oh really?
In, in 82, but one of the first concerts with the enclosed, with the roof.
Right.
Which it was outdoor before.
That was the year it got enclosed.
82.
Yeah.
And I'm very jealous of my parents for having seen prime Toto 82 for free apparently.
Cause I forgot, I haven't brought this up in any of these sectors yet that my mom worked
at, at universal in the early eighties.
She was a, she was an accountant in what was like the big towering black skyscraper there
at the Ted.
That's now like the smallest building on the property.
But yeah, but everybody, everybody went for free.
And they also went to one other concert.
I think maybe the first concert my parents saw together at all, possibly while dating
was the first concert with a roof, Frank Sinatra.
And, and there was a moment that my dad's reminded me of my whole life from this concert
where he, Sinatra is setting up a song and he says, all right, there's this one's one
of the classics.
This is some real music.
You're about to hear not like that Betty Davis.
I shit furious, which I developed the theory that maybe he's mad at Kim Karns cause he
like tried to roofie her or something.
And then, but she like put a coaster on top of the glass just the time and he didn't get
to like a buddy took her away when he wasn't looking like it was like, okay, you gotta
get out of here.
Save yourself.
And then Frank's camp betrayed him and like, I know things you can't know.
Get out of here, Kim.
The first few years of gambling being legal in Atlantic city and Jersey, Frank Sinatra
kind of had the run of the place.
Like Steve Wynn, the exclusive contract and stuff.
And they would just let him gamble at all hours.
There's a story.
I think that there's a Dean Martin book.
There's a story of the two of them wanting to play cards and like going to the tables
in Atlantic city where one of them was doing a residency and demand it.
Like we want the dealer to deal by hand, which is like very illegal.
It's why you gotta do the machines and like the dealers like, uh, and the pit bosses like,
oh, it's Frank Sinatra.
You gotta do it.
And he was an asshole about it.
Roommate.
Oh, really?
You know him up there?
Sinatra is my roommate in hell.
You get him?
Yes.
We, we, we room together.
It's weird that he has to share the space, but I guess it's hell and you're being punished.
So, um, has he changed his ways?
Is he, uh, no, he's still a son of a bitch.
This is, this is total.
This is absolutely true.
Also in my, my family history.
I don't think I've said this on the podcast before.
One of the stranger stories in my family's history, my, uh, grandfather wrote for, um,
as you know, modern screen magazine or some like a fifties entertainment magazine.
And he wrote something unflattering about Frank Sinatra and Sinatra sent thugs to his
residence to dangle him over a window.
And he said nothing happened.
He got, he, he wriggled out of it, but one day he opened the door and Sinatra's guys
were there.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
My grandfather, uh, um, and which I've, so I've always thought like if that had gone
the other way, maybe my mom isn't born.
Maybe I'm not born.
Maybe I'm a lost soul, just like the sector keeper.
If Sinatra had gotten.
So you have a, you want to send Frank a message via the sector keeper?
Oh yeah.
Sure.
I can pass it.
Yeah.
Now's my whiteboard on her fridge.
Hmm.
What, what?
I mean, I, Hey, I guess just, Hey, fuck off chairman.
That should get the job done.
You gotta be careful when there's no more room in hell, the dead will walk the earth.
Oh God.
I'm going to run into him.
What if the sector keeper, you wouldn't, I mean, let's cut a deal here.
Just please promise you won't like introduce us if I end up in hell and if we don't get
you out, I mean, I have every intention of getting you out.
Of course.
If you get all of the sector stones, I won't send the ghost of Frank Sinatra after you.
Oh my God.
I think we really have cause to do this right because now my soul is at stake.
He's going to get like, I didn't get my, my boys didn't get their hands on your grandpa.
It's Frankie's revenge.
You know what's so funny to me?
I was just like, I was just reading someone like posted like a tweet or something about
like these rap music, we're worshiping these thugs.
It's so funny.
Cause I guarantee you that guy would be like, not like Frank Sinatra.
These days.
Frank Sinatra is a man bankrolled by the mob.
Yeah.
By the outfit itself.
What are you talking about?
Like what is your...
A man, a man that I heard Donald Trump tell a story that he was horrified by.
Trump was like, yeah, I was hanging out with...
The man with no shame.
He was, I was like, I was hanging out with Sinatra and a man, this is on an old Howard
Stern show.
He goes, yeah.
And a guy, we were in Vegas and a guy came up to him and was like, Mr. Sinatra, I just
got married to your music.
We danced to your music as the first, like the first song.
And Sinatra goes, get him boys.
And he just had the shit kicked out of the sky.
And Trump, and Trump is telling a story.
Trump's like, yeah.
Like you can tell Trump is put off by this.
One of the most terrible men.
Vile.
Vile man is like, that guy was a little crazy, huh?
Oh my God.
Sector keeper, has he hurt you?
Boys, boys.
No, no, no.
That means yes.
Tell me about the Gibson.
I think that sticks out in my mind.
And I don't think I went to this, but this was where Conan, when Conan did his live tour
before he had his TBS show.
But after the Tonight Show, he played the Gibson amphitheater, which is spitting distance
from the sound stage built for him to host the Tonight Show.
So like it's probably his first time back on universal property and he is doing like
a sold, like a packed show, like around the corner from where he had just been fired.
Zucker is clenching his fists.
How dare he?
I thought I exiled him.
He was banished and now he's spitting on my very turf.
Yeah.
Jeff Zucker, who now is at CNN and Trump is like, shit and all.
He's calling him like little Jeff.
Right.
He's getting, he's getting the Trump business.
So in this case, I as little Jeff or little, little, little, he was using the D's.
Oh, he was calling him little.
What's his name?
Corker.
Oh, really?
Right.
He was using condescending.
He wasn't just writing little.
He would write LIDD like, wasn't a Bob Corker he was goofing on.
Oh, maybe he was like little Bob Corker.
He was calling him.
I'll find it.
That's so confusing.
Wasn't it little like, wasn't like Marco Rubio?
Yeah.
He's the same.
What the?
He's gone out of really great.
Conan.
Oh yeah.
There you go.
He just cycles through.
If he ever decides to have like a punch up room of name generators, though I don't support
the man.
That'd be a fun gig.
Yeah.
If you could think of mean names.
It's you and Dennis Miller and Dan Manin.
The millennial, the millennial comedian.
Yeah, Gavin Mcginnis.
The old from a Fred boys.
Oh, the Gibson was also the home for a long time of the MTV movie.
Was it the movie awards and the Teen Choice Awards?
Mm hmm.
This is famously, we've mentioned him before, Sasha Baron Cohen.
His friend Bruno was there.
His associate Bruno fell on Eminem.
Oh, the second mention of this on our podcast.
That's where that famous accident occurred.
That famous accident.
Yes.
The butt to face, wasn't it?
Wasn't it like.
Yes.
And all of D12 got mad and left.
All of D12.
In a totally spontaneous moment.
Headed for the Purple Hills.
Jason, did you ever see a concert at Gibson?
No, never.
I never was.
Never saw it at the MTV.
Real brief, the only other thing I saw there, a free concert that I, well it wasn't free,
I saw it for free, put on by The Shins.
Hey, second Shins mention.
Another return.
Oh, that's funny.
We talked about the Garden State earlier.
Oh, wait, the Sector Keeper, Sector Keeper, you should listen to this band, they're called
The Shins, they change your life, I swear.
The Shins?
The Shins.
Do you remember?
Yeah, do you remember how body parts work?
That's a thing you could injure, you could twist your shin.
It's also the name of a band, and they are so good that they could change your life,
I swear.
Oh, excellent.
I'll check them out when I ascend to heaven.
When you get all your memories back.
Thank you.
I think they'll give you strength.
The other things I saw there, in 2005 I saw Beck Two Nights in a Row, a Guero tour, that
was fantastic.
Oh, sure.
And my dad dragged me to a concert in 1998 that I was all harumphy about, and probably
like a real jerk during it.
Like, I have to go with my dad, this lame concert instead of the rap I like, instead
of Busta Rhymes.
And this concert that I frowned and crossed my arms through the whole time in 1998 was
Chicago and Hall & Oates.
Oh my God.
Wow.
This is my exact wheelhouse today.
I've seen both of them multiple times.
I made a video with Chicago.
Wow.
I'm bored and mad in a Chicago concert in 1998, and then how many years later?
Thirteen years later, I did a video with the band for Funny or Die, and I got to say,
hey, Chicago, meet my dad.
Oh, great.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's awesome.
That's how many years after the fact.
I feel like that made up for what a little jerk ass I was, but I'd love to see that
concert.
I have a Chicago story.
Why?
Now we're talking.
The Toronto player from Chicago went to my church, and I used to basically like-
Wait, can I name it?
Can I name it Trumpet is Pankow?
That might, that might, I literally do not remember.
You were in school, Nick Pascot.
Scott fucking taking me to task.
This is my dream.
What was it, Perizator, Loftney, or Pankow?
Pankow.
Let's go Pankow.
I only, I learned their names because I had to block them.
Oh yeah.
I had to arrange them in as it was very, it's very hard to move eight people around.
But what happened, I was playing, I did like half ass trumpet through, through middle school
and high school.
I would just like pretend to play a lot of the time because it hurt my teeth.
And I played, I did play at the church and it became clear that my mom had like, was
friends with the, or like talked to the trumpet player and wanted him to come and encourage
me to continue to play.
So he, so I played, but I blew it.
I mean, I could, I forgot the solo.
I just like, I like, I like fucked up.
I was like, my armchair was all fucked up.
It was like, like it was all, so he came up after us.
He's like, and clearly like wanting to like support me, but knowing that it would never
happen and he just was kind of dancing around and like playing trumpet.
All right.
Wow.
Nice.
But he had nowhere to go.
They didn't know.
Just honestly, it is the most honest thing, but it was just him like clearly like being
asked to bolster me and not being able to in good faith.
Oh my God.
It sounds like he didn't like force a compliment.
No, he didn't force a compliment again.
And I respect, this is a, this is a story of respect.
We just like, yeah, all right.
But there's nothing else to say.
Like what else could you talk about?
So it was just, I just had an awkward like three minutes of him just going like, right
on.
Whoa.
I think it, I think it's Loftney, this blonde guy.
Yes.
That's it.
Lee Loftney.
He was one of the nicest guys in the shoot.
They were all very nice, but those horn guys, especially, and you're like, wow, I can't
believe you guys are here.
You guys are legends.
Hey, it's been a crazy ride.
That kind of just wasn't, it was, I honestly, I'm so, my Chicago day was very special to
me.
I feel like mine went, went better than yours.
Yeah, definitely.
But no, but I, you know something, even at the time I was like, this is the right thing
to do.
You should not, do not, do not encourage my talent, my lack of talent.
Don't do it.
Yeah.
He say, well, yeah, if you, I, and you know, you're a, you're a working successful comedy
writer now as opposed to a, like a twice divorced trumpeter in a, in like a garage ska band
or something.
Just failing out.
Yeah.
Well, congrats.
You, you made it out of that alive.
Yes.
Any other memories of the amphitheater?
Oh, you know, we mentioned this because it was replaced by Harry Potter and I think some
of the foundation stayed.
I think they kept some of the infrastructure of the building.
Right.
I'm not totally sure, but you know, I said this in the Harry Potter episode, but I think
it's a shame that they had to tear down the place where the greatest album of all time
was recorded, the blues brothers briefcase full of blues.
I feel like it should stay up as a historic monument.
And so I'm, I'm mad at the Harry Potter ride.
I go on it, but I, I shout, what about the blues brothers?
Oh, and also the, the last, the last blues brothers concert was there.
Oh, right.
It's every year's later.
Yeah.
So blues heads, a lot of history here.
Should I maybe keep talking about the blues brothers for way longer?
Okay.
Why don't we continue the music discussion though and jump on over to saddle ranch.
Yes, please boys.
Saddle ranch.
I mean, saddle ranch was the final restaurant occupying this space, but certainly not the
first.
No, this is a very exciting area.
Now the building is gone entirely and I'm not sure why and I don't know what's going
in there.
Well, I know the rumors about it.
Oh really?
Do you have anything you can say?
Sure.
But there's a message board rumors that the tooth some chocolate factory is going right
where the saddle ranch, the giant rip off Willy Wonka dessert restaurant that's in Orlando
already might be going where saddle ranch is.
Very popular chocolate, chocolate emporium and also like savory, savory treats.
There are sweets and savory.
Anything you would want.
Yeah.
The whole thing smells like chocolate.
So when you order a plate of mozzarella sticks or wanton nachos or something, you will not
stop smelling that chocolate odor.
Yeah.
So just like, I like that they're keeping up the tradition of that space, which is just
quick closures.
Just like, just, just, just a, you're spending millions of dollars creating a brief anecdote.
It heads up to being mentioned on a podcast briefly.
Okay.
So I have a full list here.
Uh, uh, it, when it initially opened, it was called a Whompomper's wagon works restaurant.
That was, and the backstory of this, do you know the backstory?
Yeah, it was about a flim flam man who, uh, uh, found a good, a good, uh, line that's
selling people wagon pieces and build a giant factory on top of this hill at the Cuyenga
pass.
And now they had converted it to a restaurant.
This way I didn't, I just copy and pasted the bio and hadn't read it till right now.
My, my little thing says CL Whompomper.
I was going to ask what the name was.
CL Whompomper, a legendary slick talking wagon salesman who invented wheeling and dealing.
This character invented the general notion of wheeling and deal while dealing.
Great grandfather.
You have so many connections to this place.
Wow.
Yes.
He, I, I'm with him right now.
I'm so proud of the, uh, he was an entrepreneur in this chocolate place is piss on his grave.
So you want him like remembered and I want him honored.
Yeah.
Yes.
Boys boys.
Promise me one day you'll reopen the Whompomper.
Promise.
You were quick to make that promise.
Okay.
You can do it.
Yeah, I can do it.
I mean, there's an old saying in LA, you know, when the Piz that if you want an easy go of
it for a little while, try to open a restaurant now.
I feel like CL Whompomper.
Am I getting the name right?
It's actually it's Hopper.
Well, Hopper, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Whomp Hopper.
CL Whomp Hopper.
I feel like he probably is related to like other deceased characters from different,
you know, shopping and dining experience, centers like Merryweather Pleasure or even
TGI Friday, TGI Friday or even just because I want to say the name Marvel McFay from Astral
World.
Yeah.
And do you find are you looking at a photo of him from somewhere?
Because there are photos of him.
I'm bringing him up.
I have not seen the photo.
I'll do it all the time.
You're right on the money because would you believe that he is a bearded man in a top
hat?
Of course I believe that.
Which is this him?
Yeah.
And who else does he remind you of?
Imagine you're Joe Roady.
Are you going to say Stan Lee from the Marvel medium?
I'm still not.
You're all wrong.
The original top hat, old timey beardo in theme park.
Yeah.
And when this restaurant opened, who was hired to play CL Whomp Hopper?
But Ron Schneider, the original actor who played Dream Finder.
Wow.
Literally the same man.
He's just playing him.
He isn't CL Whomp Hopper who obviously was a real man who you the sector keeper.
Yes.
But he did him justice.
Oh, that's good.
So he did him justice.
He played him well.
His portrayal was not piss on the grave.
No.
Here's a photo of Ron Schneider that also came up in the search results.
He's holding Figment the Dream Finder.
He's a whimsical guy.
Wow.
So yeah, I really wish I could have experienced this place.
A restaurant with a plot, obviously, always up my alley.
Aesthetically, like it's this like fake rusted out tin shack, but then you go in there and
it's nine rooms.
It's huge.
It's so massive.
It's so big.
Also, they made a point of using reclaimed barn wood to construct it, I read, and corrugated
tin roofs just like back in the day.
I'm looking at the picture.
I love a shack.
And it looks like they're tin roofs, but the roof is made to look like it's wood.
Right?
Am I wrong?
Like that's what I'm getting from the mixed materials.
Yeah, mixed materials.
But then you go inside and it's brass and it's bricks and it's dull 80s Browns and Tiffany
lamps and all the stained glass, all the shit I love to swim in.
It's beautiful.
It is amazing.
It's like if you were watching the movie version of Hello Dolly and just ran face first into
the TV screen.
That's what Whomper's Wagon Works looks like.
And so that lasted 81 to 86.
Then it became Whomps.
It's such a game.
Whomps restaurant.
I like how Hooters tried to become Hoots.
Whompers became Whomps.
Whomps lasted 86 to 88.
And then it got taken over by an old friend of ours, Tony Romas in 1988 to 1995.
As we said, one of the only establishments to make the city walk jump, to be put in a
different location.
This one's the one in my heart.
We were finally recalling it with Eva.
Yeah, that's my Tony Romas.
Did you ever make it to that one?
Or do you have like a first Universal Studios memory?
I definitely remember like Hard Rock was, I remember being young enough to be impressed
by the Hard Rock Cafe.
I was floored by that.
So that was probably my memory, like they've got all this memory.
Holy cow.
I also remember a big thing that my friends and I would do because we were in high school,
but like we didn't like like Rap Rock is we would go to BB King's House of Blues, but
to hear the music.
So we'd go there and there's like, I think we had like a substitute teacher who played
harmonica there and we fucking idolized him.
We thought it was so fucking cool.
We would go there.
We did see like the Scottlights played there, which was like fun.
We would often be at BB King's House of Blues.
Wow.
That's funny because we've covered that one and I don't, yeah, I don't even think of any
as I don't even think of it as a place anyone would have gone to.
Right.
Yeah, definitely.
But we were those kids.
You know what I mean?
We kind of appreciated good music.
Oh, so you must have gone to that baked potato down at the bottom of the hall.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We got bad expensive baked potato.
I mean, that place is so fucking expensive though.
I mean, it is.
The club, the baked potato.
I don't know anything about it.
I know it's reputation.
Yeah, it's it's it's at the base of the hill off of the Coenca Pass.
Right near by jazz place.
Yeah, but I think it's like there's like I mean, maybe this is I was in high school
and maybe the entry fee was even three dollars, which seemed prohibitive to me.
But I remember it seemed really expensive.
But we would also go to there's a place Charlie O's, which is again now a fallen brother in
the in the valley.
We would we would go there.
But there was actually like a time where there was like a pretty good amount of like jazz
and you know, if you were.
Yeah.
You were like you were a high school jazz jazz cat.
You were consciously very consciously like a Ryan Gosling, Lala Link.
Yes, exactly.
And that would be problematic.
Like, stop, like stop.
Stay away from the right at the time.
All right.
So they gave you your your your jazz fix and gave us our jazz fix.
That's nice over there.
Totally.
And yeah, this this Rome is also, I found, like aesthetically perfect.
Well, they kept a lot of the original building, but then there was also some Roman columns,
right?
Yeah.
It's like weird.
There's it's like two styles mushed together.
It somehow looks smaller than Whompomper's, but I don't think that's right.
Whomp hoppers.
This is the photo of that restaurant is something I would like just stare at for a full 16 years
and 60 seconds just to like take me back to that time.
And it reminds me of how like it's the kind of it's a lot like I took a trip to a mall
and to outside of Toronto where Mean Girls was shot like any of the mall scenes and Mean
Girls.
And I it's so locked in time, like perfect of the of this dull late 80s aesthetic.
And I showed right after I've been our friend Danny Jelinek, I showed photos of this mall
and he was I showed him like four or five and he was like, I don't know what you're
showing me.
I don't know why these are photographs worth being read display.
Like I don't know what you're seeing and I don't blame him.
I don't.
But do you do you know what I'm with this photo, that logo, that sign?
Well, you're you you actually went to this place.
I did.
So that's another element.
It's my Schomburg.
But what I this is I think what you're actually describing is what I was talking about on
the Pleasure Island episode where I was reading through people's memories and looking at their
photos of it.
I have obviously some memories of Pleasure Island, too, but I didn't live my teenage
years there or my early 20s there.
But by the end of it, I had this deep nostalgia for a place that I never was.
Yeah, I thought I was living the this youth that these people had had and they were also
like they loved it.
And you can feel it with reading the writing and looking at the photos.
So it's like the same thing.
What you're describing, I think it's similar.
There's a similar thing of like it reminds you of a place and it's like it's probably
really just like remembering being a kid or like it's really all that.
Though I bet there was less of a culture surrounding the Tony Romus if I had to guess.
But Pleasure Island seems like it had a big culture.
All that like the knots and Disney dance clubs seemed like they had it.
And people like the other these Facebook groups are crucial for everybody, like pooling their
memories and there's real community in these theme park places.
You're mentioning this is a quick Universal Studios, but off of movies.
But I remember this this time I was in middle school and we went to the the movie theater,
like the the Universal, like the AMC there or whatever.
This is one of the first times I went like I was I don't know me like like 13 or something
like that.
We wanted the group.
My crush, Ariel Fortune sat next to me and I was so floored and I was so fucking nervous
that she sat next to me.
So you would say Fortune favored you that night.
Nothing, nothing from the you make me weak.
Fortune favored me.
Airport is set next to me.
I got a large like like Mr. Pibb or something like that or like Dr. Fever or whatever.
I put it in my seat before the movie starts.
Ariel turns to me.
She goes, oh, like, can I have some of your soda?
And I just panic and I just go, it's empty.
But it wasn't empty.
It was completely full.
And so I just didn't touch it the entire.
I don't know why I panicked.
I just said no.
I don't know what I thought was going to happen.
But yeah, then at the end of the end of the she watched me as I picked up a clearly a
full through it entirely away.
Nick, that's actually a very alpha move.
And you're really good.
You're really going to turn that into something.
If I just if I'm not like lied, just bizarrely lied and denied both of us, but I just said
no.
Oh, man.
You could have you could have been married with Ariel.
For a fortune.
Yeah.
In an alternate universe.
You married Ariel Fortune.
Tour in the country in.
Yeah.
Low rent trumpet clubs.
That's tempted by trumpet heads left and right.
Trumpet groupies.
Please.
I can't.
I've Ariel at home.
Yeah.
You're you're just in Chicago.
Look, I know I'm a passable at the right.
Actually, I got her once I come home.
I'm just a little quieter.
How was your trip?
Good.
Yeah, it was good.
I'm not going to write home about it.
You're selfish to tell her.
It's like you're on the road.
That's the road.
It's like a drama playing out with your other life.
Well, you know, what wasn't in the cards for you with with your trumpet career was being
a country star.
Country star.
Probably the most interesting in my mind.
What do you know about country star?
So country star and and we alluded to this very early on in this series.
Country star was the attempt to make a Planet Hollywood ask Hard Rock Cafe ask restaurant
solely focused on country music, which is very funny because at the same time there
is Red Cross from it, which we'll get to later.
The Marvel Mania restaurant, which was an attempt to make a hard rock ask a restaurant
based on the Marvel Comics properties.
Country star was owned by a number of famous country musicians.
Does someone have the list?
I do right here.
Yeah.
Country music superstars, including Vince Gill, Winona Judd, Reba McIntyre and TV hosts
Lorraine Crook and Charlie Chase.
I know all of them.
You do.
So that's before you were.
Yes.
Oh, OK.
They were so long putting the clues together, Michael.
Thank you.
You know what?
You you've you know, Garth Brooks, right?
Oh, well, yeah, he was before you're in Chris Gaines.
Oh, you do.
I did get to experience Chris Gaines.
Oh, OK.
You went you went back the other way.
I taught him as Garth Brooks.
Chris Gaines.
I would like if in a little wing of the country star cafe, there was like the Chris Gaines
Blue Room.
It's a little like sad.
You have to request that ahead of time on your reservation.
Country started me.
The outside of the building is nearly not.
It's unrecognizable because they built giant facades that look like jukeboxes in front
of it, which I don't necessarily associate with country music.
Yeah.
Like do that might be like kind of more like a giant.
It is like, yeah, Johnny Rockets, American graffiti, like the the fifties that didn't
really exist, but we imagine in our imagination it did.
They on a roadhouse.
They probably had a jukebox, though.
I guess that's true.
But like you said, the old the the Wop Hopper Hopper Wop Hopper looks like it could be country
star.
Yeah, like that actually looks more probably like what you would think they went.
They went backwards and not to jump ahead, but then they removed the jukeboxes for Saddle
Ranch and it just went back to being a rusted out shack.
So what was the point of this?
It's weird.
I wish this.
I wish I went to this because I don't know if you have this over on your thing.
They had a menu that's fantastic.
They don't have the full one here.
But for instance, you could get Reba McIntyre's garden vegetable pasta or what known as Hickory
smoked chicken.
Very clever name or the Vince Gill cheeseburger.
You know, like that.
That is what I want from one of these restaurants.
Clever sounding cheeseburger names will come up again on this episode.
Oh, yeah.
Last hour.
I think Hard Rock seems to have less of that.
I think they used a little more, but you don't get like the Joe Perry macaroni or something.
But that's what I want.
I want everything named.
There's a few I think.
Every now and then I feel like they have a seasonal menu.
Like that's the quarterly menu or something where it's just like pit bull spicy chicken
wings.
What is the rest?
There was a restaurant.
Mr. Worldwide's wide mouth club.
Oh man.
I want to have that now.
That's one of my great theme burger.
That's when I was in Orlando last year is not buying the limited edition pit bull Mr.
Worldwide t shirt that was only being sold at Hard Rock, Orlando.
Did you say have you seen the video classic comedy clip of Pitbull and Jimmy Fallon playing
giant beer pong while the while the Sims outside of Moe's while all the Simpsons characters
including the Simpsons and Sideshow Bob standing next to each other all cheer him on and it
opens at this great little like skit in the in Moe's like you're Mr. Worldwide, huh?
Well I bet you can't do beer pong though.
No, that's where you're wrong.
All right, let's do it.
It's the most mumbled sketch I've ever seen.
I know we still have a year plus left, but I feel like that's going to be the most representative
piece of 2010s culture.
Jimmy Fallon playing giant beer pong while the silent cast of the Simpsons raise their
arms.
Yeah, raise their.
Well, Gil the salesman.
Gil the salesman became president.
At this country star they have they would have like the outfits worn by your favorite
country super.
Did you ever go by the way?
I don't know.
I missed this.
Do you remember it even being there?
I think I might vaguely remember that.
Yeah, but you could there was a monitor that you could touch and you could choose between
reading a biography of the star listening to an interview or watching the music video
that the clothes were worn in.
Biography please.
Jeremy we're being seated.
Let's go.
I want to read about the Judd family, the first family of country music.
How many pages is this?
How many?
Man, this and the premiere was the opening of this restaurant was attended by Loretta
Lynn, Charlie Pride, Hoyt Axton, Diamond Rio, Wayne Gretzky and Little Richard.
Wayne Gretzky.
Yeah.
What?
I don't know.
You know what?
Wait, that reminds me.
We didn't have time.
We somehow missed this in the Tony Roma's episode, but there was, let me pull this fact
up that the, when it was a Tony Roma's, there was an event that was like, there was a rib
eating contest that happened up here.
Just while we're talking celebrities in this location, really glad I could go backwards
and fit this in.
In this Tony Roma's, this the fifth annual celebrity rib eating contest.
Maybe we all together can participate in the, the next one, the 31st or whatever.
Yeah.
Whenever they do.
I promise to hold a rib contest.
Oh, yay, man.
We have so many incentives to give you what you want on the other side of the space bridge.
Daddy Yankee will serve you ribs.
We can wipe up the sauce with the Pope's robes.
He doesn't mind.
The winners, if you were wondering of the celebrity rib eating contest, were five stand
up comedians, Monty Hoffman, Bill Fox, Tom Tanik, Al Cleithin and Greg Goldman, who
together called themselves Comic Rib Leaf.
Oh, wow.
So many celebrities.
So it was a rib eating contest and you had a team?
Yes.
So it was the cumulative five.
How many ribs can a group of five eat?
In a nod to Comic Relief, they also gave the money to a charitable cause, but their, their
charitable cause was their family court lawyers.
Their bankruptcy lawyers from the stand up bust.
Jason roasting Comic Rib Leaf.
Take that.
Okay.
So, and then after Country Star, this became, then it became the saddle ranch, which is
a long time fixture of the, of the sunset strip.
One of the sleazy in the best ways locations on the.
Horrifying mannequins.
I don't know if you guys passed by, but the mannequins are horrifying outside of it.
They're just like, they're skin like, they're like weird, sallow skin.
Let's make sure to show the proper respect it is called the saddle ranch job house.
Oh boy.
I have one story about this, which is I was hanging out on my, in my tour guide summer,
I was hanging out at the saddle ranch one night and I was new to, I was newly 21 and
I was trying drinks I hadn't had.
And so I was somewhere where I'd had a mojito and I thought that's fun.
It's mint and you know, that's new to me.
So I went up to the saddle ranch bartender and I said, I'll have a mojito please.
And he was like, oh yeah, cool.
That's good.
That's, that's real great.
Uh, I got news for you though, buddy.
We're drinking man drinks tonight.
He rejected my order.
He mocked, which to me, a mojito while sweet still, you can taste the alcohol in it.
That to me isn't the ultimate example of a like froufy girl drink.
So like when it's hot in the middle of the summer, like that's a perfect drink.
It'll be so sweet on these parsely.
I'm sure that's what a Hemingway was drinking in cute.
Well that and rum daiquiris and yeah, you can easily kill yourself with mojito.
I remember ordering like a vodka cranberry and my friends were like a red drink.
We don't have, don't drink, don't order something with like a bright color.
That's not what you do.
That's not what a man does.
I was like, really?
This was your origin story as ever since then you've only drank the brightest color.
I scan the menu for the most neon color, the most unnatural color.
And then I want to drink as much of it as possible.
If it has five of the colors, that is the best.
Uh, yeah, good for you.
Fuck those guys and fuck this bartender and fuck Sinatra.
And then sorry to the person who complained in the iTunes reviews that we swear too much.
I never went to Saddle Ranch, but I feel like it was a few years living out here until I
realized because my knowledge of it was that it's where people went in West Hollywood to
get fucked up.
And I didn't really have a bearing on the one at Universal City.
I don't think it was still family was out visiting.
They're like, oh, we could go to this barbecue place.
Like we were up there and then we ended up somewhere else anyway.
But I feel like it was a while before I realized like other than the name chop house in the
title that it's like, oh, they have food.
You can eat there because I don't think I had ever.
And then I remember the last few years of Saddle Ranch.
They had a lot of signs about like weekend brunch, come at brunch at Saddle Ranch.
Yeah.
The one on sunset, I think a lot of people, like I had, there was people that moved out
here that I think have not maybe moved back since that I knew.
And they would be at like Saddle Ranch on sunset every week.
Wow.
Once a week or something.
So that was the place, which I think I guess I've been there once on sunset.
The one at Universal, I've only went to once and it was after Avengers Age of Ultron.
And the writing was on the wall for Saddle Ranch because there was no one there.
The mechanical bull was not working or it was not on.
They didn't plug it in maybe.
And it was like, that was actually the first time I had been in that one.
And you were like, there are over 30 empty rooms in this establishment.
So many, so many rooms.
They were not filling that space like old Whomp Hopper.
They didn't have many a wagon to wheel and deal.
And Saddle Ranch, the biggest problem is that there was no character to represent it.
There was no J.H. Saddle.
Grandpa.
Mr. J.H. Saddle.
Oh, that was a...
No, Grandpa.
Oh, Whomp Hopper.
Somebody like him.
Yeah, yeah.
But if they had had a whimsical bearded character that that guy, what's his name?
Ron could play.
Yeah.
Deserted, deserted where I sleep.
I sleep quiet.
Deserted.
Oh, so in the in the time when it was doing bad, that was OK for you because there was
a free room that you could use.
Nice and quiet.
You tried doing that at the John Lovitz comedy club, but there was just so much laughter.
It was too loud.
Too loud.
Sides hurt.
I mean, is that what we have to say about the Saddle Ranch?
I think.
Did you have a wild night there with your Universal employee?
No, it was no.
I've got disheartened.
But when the that when my drink choice was complained about.
Did that change you?
Were you then self-conscious going forward in the next couple of years of ordering a
mojito or a mojito or not beer or not whiskey or something?
I'm not sure I've ever had a mojito since then.
Oh, it's one of my favorites.
Delicious.
Yeah, I know I was really liking the drink.
And now that guy is like over my head like a specter going tisktisks.
This answers a big audience question, which is why doesn't Scott drink mojitos?
We had a breakthrough here today.
So now what we know we have to do is we have to go to Disneyland.
We have to get you nice and loaded on mojitos.
And then we go on every launch, every quarter and Splash Mountain.
Yep.
And conquer it all in one on one day.
I think I think they'll help.
I think the mojitos will give me strength just as completion of sectors does the sector
and hopefully like a one to one equivalent.
Hopefully like no like Captain Hook comes up and sees you with the mojito and he points
and you have like a flashback or something.
Well, if it was my most feared character, the big bad wolf with the big dangly tongue,
then I would never get on a ride or drink a mojito again.
He's not in California Adventure at least right now.
So you're only going to probably run into like the Incredibles, which they don't care
if you have a mojito.
Yeah, they're chill.
Dash just comes up a few million times.
And the mode could maybe sort of like give you like a tisktisk or something.
Yeah, she'll put you on blast.
So the lamp will shake its lamp head and the light will just go across your face.
I don't want the walk around looks.
It's kind of ambiguous, but Scott takes it very personally.
No, no, it's at me.
No, the light.
The light is at me.
I think it was stationary.
I don't think it moved at all.
No, no.
I can't go on this quick launch.
Just don't bring it into the pre-shofer Guardians of the Galaxy.
What's that drink you're drinking there?
Is that a mojito?
You better not bring that on the gantry lift.
I may be a raccoon, but even I know that ain't a man drink.
Yeah, we drink it.
Scott foiled from having a nice summer by toxic masculinity.
It's in every corner.
All right, well, let's talk about the...
Oh, do you have something to...
Well, what I want to hit before we get...
Yes.
He's sick, I think.
Go ahead.
I think we're all moving it along.
We're all trying to.
Really, because I know we have a lot to say about the final topic, but I want to say really
fast first that the area, the restaurant venue that this thing moved into was initially built
to be something called Victoria Station.
Yes.
I want to make sure we hit Victoria Station.
It gave me some more perspective on the creation of Steady Walk.
It's Victoria Station, which was like a trolley station themed restaurant that you can take
a little trolley to from the parking lot.
Oh, the parking lot.
It took you up the hill.
A little train.
Oh.
So that was there.
And then there was also that Chinese restaurant.
Oh, we haven't met, which I forget the name of.
I forget the name of.
Which I asked my dad today if he had any City Walk memories I should share, which is where
I remembered them going to Toto or whatever.
And he said, oh, yeah, well, I did go to that Chinese restaurant, which is real nice.
But I remember we were leaving there one time and my mom fell.
You have all these traumatic family stories attached to restaurant locations.
My dad's dad had a heart attack in what became a Bubba Gump and my dad's mom tripped and
fell outside of the Chinese restaurant.
My dad is cursed when it comes to chains.
That's why he sticks with Applebee's and Applebee's only.
So Victoria Station, the Chinese restaurant, Whompomper's, a movie theater.
So there's also.
I'm never going to say it right.
I don't know why I got in my head reading about it that there was an M in there and
had it wrong in my notes.
It's like flop flop global from the E.T. character flop global from the E.T. ride.
I'm probably thinking of the flop global.
You're confusing Whompomper's and flop global.
So there's all these disparate businesses scattered around.
Not that close to each other.
And it took them years to think like, maybe we should put up a pathway and some signs
and a couple of others.
Maybe we shouldn't just be climbing unpaved hills to get to these different restaurants.
But I do think I think City Walk Circa or what pre City Walk Circa 82 or whatever would
have been my jam because Whompomper's seems great to me.
The Chinese restaurant looks beautiful.
It was sitting there like unoccupied for decades and now they're building a hotel there.
But it was like it was beautiful from the outside.
And then and then Victoria Station, which I didn't go to, but my wife went to and I texted
her if she had any memories and she said it was the epitome of elegance in my six year
old eyes.
She loved Victoria Station.
And apparently Victoria Station, an extremely popular chain all over the country and in
Canada and specifically the Universal location, their most popular location and at one point
one of the highest grossing restaurants in the country.
It was a train themed restaurant in general, as he says, you could eat in a train car.
Aaron swears that it was superior to fellow L.A. chain or chain train train chain.
Carnes which is also a train restaurant.
So the king of the train chains.
Other than that, I don't know much about it other than I watched an ad and the prime rib
looks amazing.
The shrimp Victoria looks divine.
I bet they had excellent mojitos and Johnny Cash sang in their ads and get ready to gasp
guys at no matter what you ordered at the end of the meal, a free mini rainbow sherbet
ice cream on a mini cone.
What else would you want?
Could you have Toby Keith kebabs?
All right.
There was one.
Every restaurant has something to bring to the table.
So at one point there were two train themed restaurants.
Was Carnes that same time?
Yeah.
And there were multiple.
There was another.
There was a Carnes on Sunset too.
And then you probably grew up near the other Carnes, right?
Were you fond of that?
Uh, it was fine.
As a kid I was like, this is fine.
Don't forget the two dining cars, the Pacific dining car restaurants in LA.
Oh yeah.
Why don't maybe I didn't go to those.
Oh, yeah.
It's like a 24 hour steakhouse.
There's one downtown and I think there's one in Santa Monica.
And of course, coal mongers, my favorite.
Order that black lung hot foot sundae.
They make it with chocolate ice cream and chocolate whipped cream.
Everything's dark.
The thing about Victoria station that for some, why, why was this of interest to me?
But it still is the idea that there could be a restaurant that you could enter from
the park or from outside the park.
Why can you give me any reason why that's why I find that interesting?
But I do anything like that.
I remember thinking, oh, so you'd be able to like the rainforest cafe outside animal
kingdom.
Oh, you can go inside or outside.
That's not interesting.
Why do I think that's interesting?
Because the, I think as a kid, the walls of a theme park are the truly feel like you're
going into another dimension.
So the idea that there was some transparency that you can see through the facade.
So you know, like, oh, we get a ticket and then I go through the turnstile.
But the idea that like you would be, it would be like almost like being in two states at
once.
Oh yeah.
Being in four corners.
Sort of, you're like, oh, I'm in the park, but I'm not in the park.
Thank you.
That was a succinct way to put that.
Yeah, I agree.
It is interesting.
It's like a terminal space.
Yeah.
The zombies are neither dead nor alive.
And also much like my life.
You're trapped in a Marvel, the victory station S situation, which is also a little bit like
Tom Hanks in the terminal.
My selected movie for the city walk movie meal deal.
The terminal.
Oh, you'll, you'll get there.
I know right now you are terminal, but soon you will.
You got terminal, you got Larry crown.
So many great Hanks's and of course, forest gump, which inspired the, the, the, the restaurant
in your home.
We have a lot to talk about.
Yes.
Yeah.
Beautiful life once you're free.
But the only way to get you free is to keep blowing it.
So let's get into it.
Let's go.
A fellow astral plane splitting restaurants.
Feel free gentlemen.
What replaced Victoria's station?
Actually the, maybe the main, one of the main theme park things I am sad I didn't get to
go to the Marvel mania restaurant.
You're here for a very specific reason.
You told me this offhand at an event.
I think we had like scribbled down like, oh yeah, we should mention more many on that
sector stuff that's not there anymore.
And you, you, when I said we were doing city walk, you told us that you had direct experience
with 12th birthday party.
My twin brother and I had a 12th birthday party at Marvel mania, which was open for
like a year.
So we were maybe, maybe there may be like 15 kids on earth who are saying this.
Whoa.
Yeah.
We, we, we, we went, we gathered a group of friends.
Uh, we went, we went to Marvel mania.
It was incredible.
I had, I had a fucking blast.
That's amazing.
Now my, oh, sorry.
I was going to say my, uh, my wife was on and she talked about her, I forget, maybe
11th birthday at wizards at the magic club.
Uh, uh, and which sounded like an ideal, uh, you know, middle school age birthday, but
I would like, I'd like to hear more details about yours.
I'd like you to one up my wife as much as possible.
Let me ask you this.
Did storm serve your wife?
I mean, a, a, a wizard came out of the table, a weather wizard, uh, storm served us.
We were fucking stoked.
Um, uh, um, they're, uh, one of the things I remember that were just like a tongue for
some reason, they really thought that comic books meant like cryo chambers.
So there were just like a ton of these like cryogenic, like everywhere.
There was just a ton of them.
They housed fake memorabilia.
I think again, like kind of like hard rock cafe inspired, but unfortunately Marvel is
in a fictional universe.
And so they literally Thor's hammer.
No it's not.
This is, this is, that's not, but it was, it was with the same reverence as if it was
that like, like the, the Avengers, like, like the Avengers signed their, um, uh, their agreement
to become the Avengers that was like displayed as if it was, they all signed a contract.
There was like the five points that they agreed to Hulk signed his signature looks like shit.
What are each other's positions and how many points on the back end?
But that was displayed.
Um, uh, and here's the thing, you know, one of the things that I think when, when people
think about Marvel now, they probably think about the cinematic universe and it was, and
how hugely successful when I think of Marvel, I think of, I just instantly think of a trillion
dollars.
I think of what the pile would look like, but this was at the time where it was like
this, where Marvel was not.
This is bankruptcy Marvel.
Yes.
This is two years before X-Men, which is their first big like movie.
Yeah.
And that's, yeah.
And this is, yeah, they thought this was, they started a restaurant division.
They thought this was going to be a big hit.
We talked a little about this, I think on, on the twister episode, but when islands of
adventure was sending out preview stuff about like islands of adventure is opening city
walk is opening in Orlando, three hotels.
One of the restaurants named was Marvel media and it never happened.
It never got built there.
This was the only one ever built.
It was open for like a year and a half.
Like it kind of limped across the over the year line and it is, yeah, it's bankruptcy
era Marvel and, and Mike and I, I, this was for me.
Well, were you, Nick, were you a big Marvel comics fan?
We were reading.
I love them.
This is like a deep cut, but Maverick was my favorite.
Oh yeah.
He was like a kind of in the Wolverine kind of weapon X universe.
But yeah, we were, we were definitely reading a ton of them.
I remember one of my first memories, I remember I wanted to buy stock in Marvel at that time.
I was a kid.
I was like, you know, I was like a kid, but had some money else in my, my grandparents
had like invested in.
So I had mentioned that to my grandpa and my grandpa had said, did a bunch of research
and was in rope and sent me a letter that said, you cannot do this.
It was marvelous.
I mean, if you had held onto it for 20 years, it would have been insane.
Yeah.
This is also around the time when like Stan Lee was talking to Michael Jackson about possibly
buying Marvel together.
There was a whole thing.
Yeah.
Where they were, cause Stanley never owned Marvel.
He was always worked for hire, but there was like, they were going to dig together and
I'm sure with like mysterious sheiks like pool together all their money and buy Marvel.
Like there's Marvel is such a bizarre.
Yeah.
And like all of a sudden it became this.
But it was never like, cause Warner Brothers owned DC for so long, but Marvel was floating
around and then was owned by toy biz for a while to rescued it from toy.
It was like who Marvel hired to make their toys and then toy biz outpaced them and the
lamprey still hanging on.
It's like Perlmutter who owns Marvel.
He's a great friend of Donald Trump, CEO's who loves being with Trump and the only, there's
only two photos of mr.
I Perlmutter that exists.
One from either like the late, the early eighties, late seventies and one with Trump at Mar-a-Lago
from a year ago.
Whoa.
They only like two photos you can find.
So when that surfaced, then you're like, Oh my God, there's a, he exists and he's there.
Yes.
Yeah.
He loves Trump.
They get along very well.
He's a great piece of shit famous for saying like, we're not making girl superhero action
figures.
Girls don't like superhero.
Like girls don't buy this.
Like that's by the way, it just says a little segue there that that philosophy comes through
on the menu.
And when we, you know, when we dig into the menu, cause there's so many, like, you know,
obviously I wanted to appeal to everyone, but you know, you've got like, uh, you know,
ghost riders ribs.
That's a good, I think that's a good theme connection, but then you can see you have
storms, hurricane shrimp.
Okay.
And then you can see they've run out instantly run out of like women superheroes.
So then it goes to Mary Jane's or roasted herb chicken.
And then, and then like, like, you know, aunt May's Blake, like they they're just done.
Like, you know, like you could just see that.
Yeah.
May has, where was it?
A soup, I think.
Yeah.
Oh God.
May has, I look, there's, I have nine windows.
I should have consolidated this nine windows open with different parts of the menu.
Yes.
So much different types of menus.
It looks like they cycled out of like what the menu was for like they had one that looked
more like a comic and then they had one that looked more like.
I think there was a take home one.
So I have the adult menu, the kids menu.
And then I think there was a second generation of the menu where they tried to make it a
little nicer looking.
But yeah, this is such an odd time.
This is also wet after the bubble burst on the comic boom in the nineties.
And like after Stan, Jim Lee had left the company, after all the image founders went
and started their own companies.
So Marvel lost like a lot of A-list artists.
Jim Lee.
I mean, I think there's some great like there is it's very funny because this is kind of
like there's some standard Marvel house style in this.
But then the pages of the menu with the X-Men are clearly like the Carlos Pacheco drawings
of the time.
And there are some like Chris Bocalo.
So there's like some.
Are you sure that's not Mike Waringo art?
Of the X-Men?
I don't.
Did Waringo draw the X-Men?
I don't know.
But that looks a lot like a Waringo style to me more than a Pacheco.
I'm looking at a different page.
Can I see if I think it's Pacheco?
This is yeah, just the way you draw it.
That does look like Pacheco.
You're right.
I, Jason, I apologize.
I finally know what it would be like for a regular person to listen to any episode of
this podcast.
Classic boys, classic, classic boys.
But then there's some very weird choices.
So it's like very like late 90s Marvel art style and coloring.
But the drink page looks like the letter columns of the 1980s.
Like this was like what they would where they would print letters and print like check out
this other book featuring the characters you like.
Like it's kind of a you could get Dom Perignon.
You could get a bottle of Dom at MarlVeon.
He's probably my favorite detail.
What's it cost in you?
The bottle of Dom is one hundred and forty dollars.
Well, that's not a bad price on the Dom scale.
Ninety seven ninety eight.
Who are you trying to impress?
Who the fuck are you pressing at that table at Marvel Mania?
You're trying to impress the Wimplink Storm.
Garcon, Garcon.
Do you have to another thing about the drink menu?
All the like section headers have an exclamation point at the end.
So it says like domestic bottle beer.
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Whoever designed it thought that comic books just meant they loved fucking word bubbles.
Yes, it was plastered in the fucking things.
The gift shop, by the way, the word bubbles just said Marvel stuff.
Yeah.
And then exclamation points.
Yeah, it was those two things.
And they brag about like giant screens to watch Marvel TV and movies on.
But at the time that meant the cartoon.
Cartoon X-Men.
Yes.
So instead of sporting events, there's many TVs devoted to just looping Marvel.
I fucking loved it.
Do you have the shot list and the martini list over here?
Yeah.
OK.
I did.
Negative zone.
Trade off.
Have fun with it.
They were called web shooters, first of all, when you would get a small shot.
Cool.
Pretty good.
Which now I think they would not do that because they don't want like kid friendly characters
associated with liquor.
They want the kids ordering ice slides, which are their smoothies, alcohol free smoothies.
But the web shooters, you could get a gamma slammer.
You could get a clobber in time.
You could get an adrenaline shot.
You could get a nuclear waste or you could get a dimension distorter.
Whoa.
And they were all in a take home glass.
And this is I mean, this truly is I'm reading it is just my favorite restaurant.
I am amazed.
I've never been.
Unless I missed it, there should have been like one of those bowl fish bowl drinks that
you get like four straws in called the ultimate nullifier.
Which is like the cosmic cube, like something to get you best.
Like what are the day you sex Machina's from Marvel Comics where it's like they also.
Yeah.
I love the idea of a tram driver just like kind of just like just a fucked up day.
And he goes, you know, like it's the it's the closest place.
Just like, yeah, gamma slammer.
It's like a real sad.
Tommy, are you sure you know what happened last time?
Yeah.
All right.
You're fucking hero.
Gamma slammer.
I think that place should have been to the watcher.
But he can't interfere.
He's somebody who cannot interfere.
That's why you go do it.
But he's just sort of like the pit boss of the whole thing.
Yeah.
I'll bring it to you know what to watch.
He's going to fucking say he's going to say just let him do it.
And then like somebody has to audition for a watch.
And it's like you got to shave your head, though.
I like it.
They're not going to let you wear a bald cap.
I don't know.
It's worth it for the visibility.
Yeah.
A very 90s detail to me of like the milkshake flavors and ice cream and desserts.
There's a lot of Butterfinger crap.
Yeah.
Butterfinger crunch is kind of everywhere on this menu.
Blastar's ballistic Butterfinger bread pudding.
That's also when you're getting to Blastar, when you get into the Fantastic Four villain
Blastar, you're scraping the bottom of the barrel.
There's some obscure ones.
It's Swordsman, I think, is in here.
Oh, there's also the two gun kit.
Cheeseburger to me is going to be I'm we're thinking it's going to be like Wolverine or
like it's going to be a heavy hitter.
It's like two gun kid.
Well that's because they needed to distinguish between Caps Battle Burger, which is on the
kids menu.
There it is.
Yeah.
And they also have Vince Gill's cheeseburger.
Seemed very creative.
This is my favorite.
This is my favorite of the menu.
This is on the dessert menu.
It just sounds like absolute shit.
The thin thing from fruit fajitas.
Yeah.
Oh, fresh fruit sizzling in a vanilla rum sauce served with chocolate tortillas, vanilla ice
cream and lots of yummy condiments.
Yeah.
Those delicious dessert condiments.
They don't even specify what the condiments are.
Last meal.
I mean, it's it's very much a tour de force to have like 90s food.
I mean, Blastar's ballistic butter finger bread pudding.
We were recently up at City Walk.
I had a delicious banana bread pudding at Margaritaville.
But the idea of taking bread pudding and just cramming a bunch of butter.
Yes.
Yeah.
Butterfinger was huge.
I mean, like Simpsons crossover.
Yeah.
Like it was like, like, like, like Butterfinger BBs.
No one better.
On my Butterfinger.
What I was talking about earlier, the Michael Ringo drawn menu I'm looking at.
It says here it's like, so it looks like a comic book and it says at the top, absolutely
no broccoli, spinach or squash on this menu.
Yeah.
Kids.
Kids love that.
Kids love it.
And so like, oh, Mighty Mutant Macaroni and Cheese and the X-Men, specifically the gold
team, X-Men gold team members.
That makes sense to me.
The Champions cheese pizza.
The Champions was like a obscure like team with Ghost Rider and Iceman, a Black Widow
and Hercules.
What was the gold team on?
The gold team is on the Mac and Cheese.
Oh, because the blue X-Men on Kenny X-Men blue team is on Kenny X Pasta.
Yes.
And that's clearly Gambit, Rogue, B, Cyclops, the classic blue team from the 90s.
Nick, you know what I'm talking about.
Without a doubt.
Yeah.
And then you have the Defenders tenders, which is Dr. Strange.
Silver Surfer, Hulk, Namor.
These are also like B-list teams from the.
Even especially.
Although the Champions holds the distinction, I think, of being the first Los Angeles Marvel
superhero team.
The Champions were based out of L.A., so I kind of get that.
They have the dare dog.
That sucks.
I mean, that just sucks.
This menu is the I haven't had it in front of me till now.
It's the busiest thing I've ever seen.
There's 10 different menus.
There's multiple menus.
This was open for a year, so they must have just turned them over so fast.
I think they were letting you take home some of them because I found a lot of people like.
Because it looked like a comic book.
We need someone to copy.
Stan Lee is on the cover of the kids menu in a top hat.
This was a thing in the little corner box on Marvel Comics for a while.
There would be Stan Lee.
It's like a ringmaster figure.
That was also not to see a Wompopper, though, with a top hat.
He does.
He does look like Wompopper.
Yes.
No, no, this is Stan the man.
Some of these are so busily drawn, like some of them have like three items on an entire
page just because there's so much happening.
Yeah, but then I pulled up another one where there's I think there's like 900 words on
this menu.
It's like, yeah, boy, yeah, this is this is headache induced.
Coffee shop, supersonic shakes, love a drink called love tales.
I don't even know what would that be a reference to?
I think that is a Marvel romance title from the 50s maybe.
They also should be pointing out the mighty Marvel spice ometer.
And that is how you know how spicy hot spicy stuff is.
And it's the human torch and he's got a there's one spark of heat is a little bit of fire.
Potent is a little more and supernova is full of human fire, human torch.
But I had to keep going back to that meter because like it's so hard to distinguish between
like mild and medium.
In an unreadable font under that, a helpful guide to our taste bud tortures.
It's like so hard.
You can't read it small.
It's really straining my phone.
And it only applies to like four menu items.
It doesn't even come up that much.
How do you know that it's a oh, OK.
On elsewhere on the appetizer page, I see a little blue guy, but it's too small to see
who he is.
But he's next to the dish Gambit's sugar cane shrimp.
Oh, my God.
I don't see that.
It's a shrimp served on a sugar cane skewer.
Oh, I'm missing that one.
It's underneath the Rainbow Bridge nachos.
That's different than the space bridge.
Different than what was it called again?
The Pope, the papal space bridge.
Space bridge.
It's a Yankee space.
Daddy Yankee's papal space.
But it makes sense because he's from the Bayou.
Yes.
Rainbow Bridge to me seems like a sherbert thing.
It's crazy that on on fucking nachos is insane.
The Fantastic Four also have two menu items.
Yeah.
Which they have the fantastic fries and they have the fantastic.
Where was it?
Was it pasta?
Mm hmm.
It's like why would they?
There's more characters.
They're the first family of Marvel Comics.
I think they've earned two slots.
Did you guys read mutant chicken wings already?
I feel like we've been doing this for 19 hours.
It's also very funny that it's mutant chicken wings and the human torches next to it.
Ridiculous.
I feel like we missed 20 percent of the menu so far.
We're not even close.
One of my favorites is Submariner's Deep Sea Suggestions.
Ask your server for the market price, man.
Oh my god, deep sea suggestions.
Fucking incredible.
And of course, Doc Ock's Walk.
Doc Ock's Walk because they used Shang-Chi Chinese tacos in Sunfire Spring Rolls to actual
Asian Marvel Comics characters.
So when they got to the walk, I was like, oh, that rhymes with Doc Ock.
I'm glad they didn't go with Iron Fist, who's famously a white guy.
Oh, yeah.
Do you guys, but we haven't we were missing the main thing, which is what the sandwiches
are called.
Do you know what the sandwich is?
Let me find the thing.
The Stanwiches.
They are called Stanwiches.
Oh, Nuff said.
Nuff said.
And then the word is Nuff said.
Excelsior.
All Stanwiches are served with our marvelous baked potato salad.
In this business closed?
No, I'm confused too, Sectorkeeper.
Well, I went there for I must have got one of the Stanwiches for my birthday or whatever.
There's a little bit of drama that happened because I when they when they would come,
I think maybe because it was our birthday, but they came and they had they would also
like the there'd be like a a little like gift basket thing at the end.
It was like a bucket full of comic books.
You would get that.
I mentioned I loved Maverick, but this was the 90s.
And one of the things was if you missed an issue of something, it wasn't super clear
you would ever read it.
At least for me, it was like it like I had three comic book stores I could go to.
If it wasn't there, I was fucked.
And that was the case for Maverick number four.
What happened was we got these these buckets.
I don't know what the fuck happened, but one of my friends, Wesley, got Maverick number
four in his bucket.
Oh my gosh.
Wow.
And I was like, I could pull rank.
I had this option that I could pull rank, but I was also because of my Christian upbringing,
I would never ask anyone for anything.
I would never do it.
So I was just staring at this fucking bucket while he just like absentmindedly flipped
through it.
Didn't say anything.
The whole ride home, he was sitting next to me.
I could see it in his fucking bucket.
Didn't say shit.
I got home and I just cried.
I just could not ask for this.
Maverick number four or whatever the fuck.
And you were in an area like L.A. has always had a lot of comic shops.
Yeah.
Like that's crazy.
Maverick, the thing was, I think it was small enough.
Yeah, that didn't run.
I remember that book didn't run for a long time.
It was very small.
It just wasn't one that they were going to keep a huge back.
And you know, you might go to the there were back catalogs you could go through, but it
might be like one, six, eight.
For some reason, I just could not fucking find this.
Your Christian upbringing didn't prevent you from lying to Ariel about the soda.
Even in that, I feel like that even can be traced back to just like my complete discomfort
with any being around any like, you know, romantic situation.
That one's tricky because you did end up lying, which is against Christianity, but it was
a situation where you liked a girl, which is forbidden.
But I do hear myself in terms of getting a smooch or something like that.
Yeah.
I did myself in my chastity.
I'm just realizing there's a dessert called chocolate carnage, which is the Spider-Man
villain who is a psychopath serial killer.
Mass murderer.
Yeah.
Even before he became a supervillain, he was a killer in jail and then a venom symbiote
a little bit.
The symbiote got him and gave him on the menu anywhere.
Or is it chocolate just because they had a C at the start?
I guess it was a C. Yeah, that is surprising because venom wasn't the 90s thing.
It's not even a C-H. It's not even like a...
Right.
It doesn't make sense.
I'm looking through the video of what you were talking about, Nick.
You're talking about the different artifacts.
And I'm going to, what I'm going to do is I won't say what this artifact is.
I'm going to show it to Jason and Jason's going to announce one of the things you could
view on display at Marvel Mania.
Ah, Namor's famous conch shell.
What?
Namor's conch shell.
Oh my God.
It's a trumpet horn.
They just didn't know what was popping.
You could just see like two gun kid was held to the same standard as like Spider-Man.
They just didn't know.
They got a list.
They didn't know which was more important.
It was just alphabetized.
I mean, Spider-Man, Captain America, and then they probably could have just filled it with
the X-Men because they had the most exposure in the 90s.
Absolutely.
Which is very sad to think about now that they have taken such a backseat because of
like corporate dealings and feel like Disney owns the movie rights outright.
Then we'll probably see a renaissance of X-Men stuff.
It's all coming back now because they're good for the Fox deal though.
If this restaurant opened today, if it was a pop-up on Hollywood Boulevard, the line
would be 27 hours long.
This would be the most popular thing that has ever occurred.
You could have a job or eat there.
Yeah.
It would be like, you know, yeah.
If you trade, if you did shifts, if you traded out with friends, can you imagine this would
be like all that was Instagrammed about for the first month and a half of opening.
Yeah.
But more than any of all the things where we talk about plus it up or whatever, or an
old thing that needs to come back, if this were brought back, it generates as much money
as all of the Marvel movies do individually.
This is such a killer.
This needs to occur.
They probably would update the aesthetic and make it reflect more of the current state
of Marvel, but obviously I would love if-
Yeah.
Well, the thing is, and I hate to say this even, but I don't know that Disney would open
a tacky restaurant version of this anymore.
Maybe not.
Because the only way I think it's going to open is it opens in Disneyland or California
Adventure specifically.
It can't open in Florida because of the deals.
So Disney controls it.
So we may get a much more theme.
We might dine with Dr. Strange in the Sanctum Sanctorum.
There's rumors of a microbrewery coming to California Adventure on the Avengers-
Oh, is that right?
Well, I saw a rumor that like, because they're opening Marvel stuff in California Adventure,
that it will be an Avengers West Coast campus, which includes a microbrewery restaurant.
Whoa.
Really?
It's there on site.
Can you whisper to me, South Mike, where you got this rumor?
Disney Tourism?
Oh, I don't read that.
That's a little trustworthy though, isn't it?
A lot more than bumper car boys.
Pretty reliable.
If this were a bumper car boys, you'd get the fuck out of here.
Good instincts.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll send you the link.
I swear we had talked about that.
Fucking liars at bumper car boys.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank God it's not them.
So I mean, look, it wasn't the time, and I am grossed out by the aesthetic and many of
the things that they have, but you do a Marvel restaurant with puns and stuff today.
Forget it.
You don't even, it doesn't even know.
I'm saying that the full classy Disney version, absolutely, like in the parks, but if they
did this in that, say, by the bell, the bad version of this would be...
Yeah, it would be amazing and people would love it.
I'm just saying I don't know that Disney would let it go now.
That's my problem.
I'm just saying that they might not even allow that to happen because of the prestige of
the brand.
Well, they're letting go of $1 billion and they're making a big mistake.
That's kind of the tragedy of this place.
Because it opened kind of like just maybe a year too soon.
I really do think that those X-Men movies were huge.
Oh yeah.
It really does seem like it was just like kind of like this poorly timed thing.
And the aesthetic of it is obviously still alive in Orlando and in the Marvel superhero
island at Islands of Adventure.
And it never changes.
I know Jason wants it to not change from...
I want it to never evolve.
...being a monument to 1996.
It might not legally be allowed to.
Well there's going to be wheelings and dealings if the Fox deal goes through with maybe trading
things.
So who knows?
Well hopefully somewhere in the shuffle.
Because I think they did a bad job.
I wasn't a comic book kid if I haven't conveyed that.
And I remember seeing Marvel Mania in the parks and I just didn't know...
Nowhere had ever done a good job of letting me know why I should care about any of this.
And I just saw like horrible gaudy colors.
And there was nothing luring me in.
And yeah probably not till X-Men did they figure out how to reach out to the non-comic
reader.
My favorite thing of some of the walk around characters other than like the face characters
look like you'd expect them to look.
But like the Iron Man suit in like a display case or if he was walking around was real
puffy.
Like it was always so puffy.
Like so like yeah they're muscle guys and they're puffy.
That toxic masculinity even Captain America like he's just disgustingly buffed out.
It's nuts.
It was like this whole like Roy like the steroid obsession of these like superheroes.
The pecs that were like past their shoulder you know it was just awful.
Yeah and basically what they did was like oh okay some guys draw them like this so let's
make the costumes like this.
But even on the menu you can see the different art styles where like some of them clearly
draw them a lot leaner like runners and then some of them it's just so such caricature
exaggerated caricatures.
I want to talk to the sector keeper real quick because on display in Marvel Mania and maybe
he has more information and maybe how this relates to a set of stones.
This was the Infinity Gauntlet.
Yes.
Which also had contained six different stones.
Oh yes.
Inspired me.
My final birthday was at Marvel Mania.
You were in the same run as Nick.
Yes I remember seeing you.
You saw me.
Yes happy birthday.
Oh thanks.
You guys share the same birthday.
Thanks dude.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Wow.
My last clear memory is of Namor's shell.
It's Kong's shell.
And that's that's the stone.
The stone for the sector has appeared.
It's Namor's conch shell.
It was conch.
Boys and look closely.
It's sitting on a little mechanical bowl.
Oh wow.
I see it now.
It's holding a little guitar.
Oh neat.
Wow.
And it's all and it's signed by Chicago trumpet player Lee Lockney.
Yes.
Yes and he said something to you Nick.
He said you made the right choice.
I made the right choice.
I think I did.
Ariel would have left you no matter what.
Boys you give me great strength.
You have completed sector sector 17 Gibson Amplitheater.
And you put the L in it again.
It's OK.
It's like Womp Hopper.
You're becoming more human.
He's probably I think he has to birth the stones from his throat.
Right that makes a lot of sense.
He has two left.
Right.
And they're probably rumbling around right in there.
Marvel Mania and Saddle Ranch.
Yeah.
Yeah we did it.
And Victoria Station and Womp Hoppers.
Yeah.
And Tony Romer Star and Tony Romas.
There was a lot there.
Yeah we're not getting out of this thing.
No.
These have been jam packed sectors.
We didn't even talk Nick you've been working up around here.
That's right.
So what are like what are now your experiences before we go.
Oh sure.
Of like we're living and working and playing as Jimmy Buffa would say.
And we we write write our office looks looks down on the tram tour.
Who's are who do you mean.
Oh what's that.
Yeah.
Who do you mean.
You mean we.
Myself and writing partner Anthony Geo.
I think you're friends with him.
Oh Pascale said the show.
We haven't seen him in a while.
Yeah.
I wish.
We should get him back.
But there was just a funny instance because you know the tram stops and it's where like
they play like the like Jimmy Fallon makes a joke about how he wishes Jurassic Park was
or I don't know whatever it's like this like there's this like video section but there's
that stop is right outside and what happened is a tram stopped and they were shooting right
beside it and so the cast of SWAT came out and shakes everyone's hand on the on the tram
right there fucking stoked out of their minds.
They can't believe everyone has their cameras out.
They're shaking hands.
They're like really being really good about it.
But what happens is that tram takes off and there's the tram right behind it that I think
they think the same thing is going to happen.
They come up and SWAT.
It's like no of course this was just like one time.
The second tram who has seen everything comes up stops and it's just like the saddest.
So disappointed.
It's SWAT.
It's She-Mart Moore.
And Kenny Johnson.
Sector keeper when you're free and when these when this 19 part series is a giant award
winning smash you need to go make like the cast of SWAT and go say hi to a tram.
They'll flip out.
I don't think you're going to arrive when you are alive again you'll arrive to a world
where this was received unbelievably and where you're a household name and household face.
Oh I would be so happy as long as God allows it.
He will.
He needs you to share your joy just as as John Paul the second shared his joy across
the Papal space bridge.
You're going to bring I think you know we've been you haven't experienced this but the
last couple of years in this country have just been a mess and I think you sector keeper
might be the key to solving all of it.
Oh I would love that.
Either way you could be our savior or you could be the Antichrist and you could bring
about the Antichrist.
Either way the problem gets solved.
Well if we all have a belly full of Daddy Yankee's ribs everything's going to be okay.
All right give us a little hint about which direction it's going to go.
Grace yeah yeah maybe and you know if we live each day like it like it's the last and if
we're you know you know striving for desserts of the quality of Blastar's ballistic Butterfinger
bread pudding then I think it's I think it's all going to be all right.
Nick where can people find you?
You can find me on Twitter at Mandar Nick.
Yeah do improv with JV Friday nights at 11.
UCB Franklin.
Have you ever seen them?
Oh you can't oh I'm so I'm so sorry.
No you can't see improv anymore.
He's missed the improv boom in general.
Wait yes.
It might be over though by the time this is over.
Yes UCB Gangnam style it's all coming back to me.
You're probably seeing the the UCB TV show but and maybe one of the theaters but they
have several now.
Oh.
Yes so you'll get to experience all of those.
The target probably won't quite be done over on Western by the time he's you're alive but
a lot to look forward to no matter what.
Well we did it we're on the way out.
Only a few more left.
Yeah Nick thanks for being here.
Thanks so much.
Best of luck to you on those final two stems.
I forgot to say it.
Oh cool.
You did it.
Hell yeah.
Exclamation point lots of zigzags around it Marvel style.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
Happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Happy birthday man.
We'll be back tomorrow and we're getting we're we're near in the end.
We're working all we're working the way down and what will happen to our heroes in the
last two issues.
Odysseus has almost returned to Ithaca to claim his rightful place.
I forgot to mention another one of these desserts real quick.
Latvian strawberry shortcake.
Very good.
See you tomorrow.
Thanks for listening.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.