Forever...
Dog.
When your town has let you down
When your port has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll, a place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight, tonight
Hi. Yep, me too.
Maybe they pick it up here.
Maybe they come back, you're right.
Maybe they go, oh, 12 looks good.
Maybe hopefully they come back for Paul Scheer.
Paul Scheer is back.
I am so excited to be in Sector 12.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
I don't want to talk about 5 or 4.
I mean, 12 was the one, if I had my eye on any of the sectors, it would be this.
It's the most elusive sector of City Walk.
In my opinion, it's kind of hidden in the corner.
It doesn't, yeah, it doesn't get the,
it doesn't get the sunlight of the tourists as much as the rest, I feel like, you know.
This is a nice change of pace because our last guest, Nick Mundy,
was trying to annex things into his sector.
Oh really?
It became a whole thing.
Use the rules.
No, no, I like my sector a lot.
I mean, you know, you know, and we're going to spend, I would say what,
we agreed before the podcast, about 90 minutes on Samba, right?
The Brazilian Grill.
Is that like, we're just really going to break down that.
Well, Samba is in another, it's in another sector.
Oh, it's not in our sector?
It is not in our sector.
So you are not required to know anything about Samba.
Samba is in sector 14.
Now why? Because it's so geographically.
The Sector Keep, these have been set years and years, eons ago.
Oh no, no, as I know, and in fact, maybe this is a good time to get the reminder
from the Sector Keeper, oh, great master, what are we talking about today?
Boys, boys, Paul, today's sector is Sector 12, Margaritaville, Wetzel's Pretzels,
Hard Rock Cafe, retail store, and I fly indoor skydiving.
Good luck, boys.
So it's Margaritaville, Wetzel's Pretzels, Hard Rock Cafe, retail store only,
not the Hard Rock Cafe restaurant, and most importantly, maybe,
I fly indoor skydiving.
Yeah, so we got to build to that, I suppose.
I think that's probably last, although Margaritaville could be last as well,
but whatever, yeah, we'll build to I fly, I fly.
I will say that in recapping from the Sector Keeper,
I had forgotten about the Hard Rock store because it was such a jam-packed sector
that I feel like I'm remembering it now, but it's been a big night.
Yeah, it's been a big day, and we spent a significant amount of time
in that Hard Rock store.
We did.
I talked to the employee.
We talked to the employee, too.
Well, you want to talk about it?
Let's talk about it.
So it's removed from the, it's not, as opposed to Margaritaville,
which Margaritaville no longer has the retail location, though it still says store,
but they took it out and put tables in.
In Hard Rock Cafe, it's removed entirely.
It's outside.
It's far away from the entrance to the restaurant,
and you cannot access it from the restaurant.
Which is a bold move because, you know, someone who has visited
Bubba Gump Shrimp Company, you got to walk through that gift shop.
It's very, you know, Bank CES, right?
I mean, like, you know, you go through the gift shop.
I mean, here, you know, here you got to exit and then go to the gift shop,
which is, that means that Hard Rock is so comfortable in the appeal of their merchandise.
They're like, we don't even need you to walk inside
because you want one of these classic Hard Rock shirts.
Yeah. Do they have merchandise in the restaurant as well?
My memory is they might also have some merchandise as well.
So it's not only that. It's also just like it's an overrun,
like the embarrassment of riches.
Well, this is for the people who, like, don't want to mess with the food,
but want the t-shirt.
Now, I don't know if you guys can speak to this at all.
This is a question I've always had.
There's been so many Hard Rock shirts that you'll see
that identify Hard Rock Cafe in places that they're clearly not, right?
Is that like, that's like a thing, right?
I don't know. I think they're there.
There's a lot of locations.
There are a lot of locations.
They are everywhere and a ton of international.
Okay.
Although they've started to maybe dry up and close a little,
but not near, that's not that much.
Planet Hollywood, pretty dead in the water.
Hard Rock marches on.
I went to, like, the first Hard Rock when I was a kid
because I grew up in New York City and it was a real event to go there.
That was like when, like, you know, Dan Ackroyd would like pop in
and do like a blues set or whatever, you know, like.
Sure.
But I did ask the guy behind the counter
because the classic shirt is the white shirt with the Hard Rock,
like the most basic, the one that you would see at like souvenir stores.
Right.
And he said that is the best-selling shirt.
He's like, so much so that he sells out of them on a regular basis.
Really?
He said that a woman came in and she's like, he's like,
I don't have them and I won't get them again until next Sunday.
Wow.
When I get my delivery.
He gets a delivery every Sunday and he's like,
and it's he's he said that that shirt is the reason why people come in.
It still has the staying power.
Because people collect those.
Like, if they travel a lot, I feel like people collect.
There is, God, I got to see if I can figure out who this is.
It's either like a journalist or like a Microsoft executive,
someone who was like an early adopter on Twitter
and someone found like someone realized they every time they traveled,
they're like in Macau, got to get my Hard Rock shot glass or got my Rock shirt.
And there was just dozens of these posts.
Well, he, the person by the counter is also saying that the two things that people come in for
are the pins that are specific to Hard Rock.
He's a guest.
The regular pin like the regular shirt is always a good seller.
He said, but there's two specific ones.
And there was one I actually had my eye on.
It was a film camera that is shooting out the word Hard Rock.
He said that's only available at Universal Studios because of the specific nature of it.
And then there's a drama mask, like a happy sad drama mask.
And that is also an exclusive to the club, the Hard Rock Club, the Universal Club.
Paul, this begs the question.
Are you a pinhead?
Well, you know, we really got into it there because it seems like Hard Rock got in
on this this pin craze so much so that they have a whole pin section.
Yeah, it's a ton of black, which then delves into seemingly some double entendre.
If you're always on the lookout for new ways to poke, prick, stab and stick it to your style,
then maybe you should be a pinhead.
And this black goes on and on and on.
And I guess relevant to theme park worlds that this is, I guess,
maybe perhaps inspired by the Disney thing.
I don't know why.
Yeah, I feel like people feel like if you have exclusive pins,
you have to get them or you're missing out on something.
It's a collectible mentality of like we need to get all of these.
Yeah, it's weird. I don't know.
That's that's the thing that has stuck around almost at Disney because they've had little toy
like little vinylmation toys, but they got they seem to be phasing those out a little bit.
Yeah. But like the pins remain.
That does seem to be like a very consistent collectible item for adults.
I am often disturbed by seeing older people with their pin books at Disneyland.
You opened up on some sort of barrel and children approach garbage can garbage can.
Yeah, there's a there's a lot of trading and it feels like it's gone to a seedier side than it originally was intended.
I believe like the idea was that you were wearing a lanyard and you might have a couple on there
and then you would pass somebody and hey, I like that pin and then you would switch pins.
But now it seems like a much more of like a market.
Yeah, a dirty marketplace about the hacks.
You can buy bulk lots of pins like twenty five to one hundred pins on Amazon for like twenty five bucks or something.
Your eyes are getting all shifty when you're talking about this.
And then you just take them to the parks and you trade with cast members for ones you really want.
You get a randomized assortment of like real pins and for like a fraction of the price.
So what are you where are you buying them bulk?
You buy them on like Amazon. You buy like a lot of twenty five for maybe like twenty five dollars.
Are they real Disney pins?
Real Disney.
So then the cast members are forced into this barter.
Yeah.
Or if you go to a shop and say like, oh, do you have any pins to trade?
Sometimes I'll have a little display.
They keep behind the counter.
Interesting, interesting goal of this being combative and trying to like I think the system.
I wish I kept my original pins because when I went on one trip, I had an MGM Studios hat and I put a bunch of like Roger Rabbit pins on there.
And it was very specific to Disney.
Now, those would have been worth.
Oh, yeah. Sweet, sweet coin.
You know, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's all explode.
That's like the only consistent I feel like collectible.
Like that's still money, like everything else I feel like has its ups and downs.
But that's only been on the rise for whatever reason.
And you think that the hard rock is I mean, it's hard because you wouldn't be you wouldn't be walking around the hard rock trying to pin trade.
This is only for your own personal gratification and satisfaction that you would have like a wall of hard rock pins.
Like this is like, you know, and I could see someone who like also has like a tequila and hot sauce collection.
Sure.
And they're selling off their hard rock.
They're Mr. Worldwide 2017 Pitbull collaboration.
Do any of our listeners have a collection of Hard Rock Cafe pins?
Please post them.
I would love to see them because I used to collect the Hard Rock Cafe shirts that had original artwork by musicians on them.
Those short lived t shirt things. It was like, you know, the lead singer of Crash Test Dummies designed this Hard Rock Cafe.
Whoa, it's Stone Temple Pilots have their own shirt.
And it was sort of like in the mix of the Jerry guys and Jerry Garcia was like making ties and that nature.
But it was like, did you have I had about five or six because, you know, it just sort of like, well, this is an exclusive shirt.
I got to get on and get to get get in on this.
And do you think that the era of the Hard Rock Organization having relationships with the current rock stars has waned?
Like because I don't I feel like I walked in there and into those restaurants in the 90s and thought, well, they are clearly in league with people of that nature.
And now I don't know because like who's on the wall now is the bass player from Korn Monkey Shaffer.
Well, I looked at that. I feel I feel like the gift shop had the lower tier memorabilia.
Oh, yeah. Because it was sort of like that's not where you're going.
You know, and then I'm also like, do you feel any special anymore when like someone comes up to you?
Hey, great set tonight. Korn killed it.
Can we have that guitar for the merch store Hard Rock Cafe L.A.?
Like, do you feel like who does that? Who's collecting these things?
You know, is there a play? You know, I don't know. Is there a place you have to go?
Yeah. Who is the broker? Yeah, I would read a big like article or oral history.
Hard Rock. All that stuff comes through it because I've also heard the rumor that it is fake.
There is a Beck biography I read where he walked into a Hard Rock Cafe and something was labeled Beck and he's like, not as far as I know.
So like, yeah, some guitar and it was not even recognized.
Well, we didn't you walk we walked in a couple.
It might have been three months ago and you pointed at something on the mall.
You go, who's that? And the guy behind the counter went, I don't know.
I think that was about are you there was one is one is Chiodos, Derek Frost from Chiodos.
And I'm sorry if I'm the Chiodos might be a great band. I just don't know them.
And what's the other one? A Treyu. Don't know Treyu.
I've heard of a Treyu. Do you guys think that we should open up like the stream, the stream shack, a podcast themed restaurant?
Oh, man. Like sit under like some watercolors of Mark Maron's cats.
You could see Joe Rogan's weights, whatever it is, you know, a replica of the ear wolf table.
Everyone's eating on signed ear wolf tables. Look at that display case.
It's a collar from Bosh, Sean Clements' dog that shows up on Hollywood and book a lot.
You know, you could you could you can sit under the image of Dustin from Feral Audio and you could read his tail of woe.
Oh, the full pop. The actual manifesto.
And then at the end, you can pay with Mike Mitchell's actual credit card because it was actually stolen from him and he hasn't noticed.
That seemed like something that would happen. Sure. Stream shack.
Jason's working there.
Yes, I'm laundering, I'm waiting tables and laundering money.
When I first ate at Planet Hollywood, one of the first times again, it was in New York City was like one of the first.
I think it was the first Planet Hollywood.
I was so excited because I went there one day and Anthony Michael Hall was just eating like lunch there.
I was like, Whoa, celebrities do come here.
And I thought that was a real cool thing.
And I feel like we could all do a shift at the stream shack. Yeah, sure.
To kind of mix it up. Well, it starts the legend that, you know, the big stars like us, you know, really are.
They actually do. This is their place.
And it would be great to, you know, maybe the stream studio.
I mean, that would be like the thing or be like a studio or you have to have like live shows there so you could be munching down on burgers and listening to great interviews.
And this would all like stop happening as time went on like how ESPNZone used to do live broadcasts.
And then after two years, like, nah, nah, nah, fuck it. Yeah, let's not get out there.
But we start the. Well, we need a mascot.
And it's interesting because we learned a little bit about the Hard Rock Cafe mascot, which I did not even understand was a thing.
I Googled this right before we started a big, you thought I was just looking up the sector. I was looking up.
Oh, this is a thing that given more time, we would have researched for days. Yeah.
Just being hit with this information.
So, yeah, we're going to do our best here, but we do not have all the information on the official doll doll of Hard Rock Cafe.
She's a mascot. She's just it's I would say it's the mascot is personified by the doll.
Right. I can't find her in other media.
Oh, the top of my very quickly. Her name is Harper Ray.
Yes. And we've gone through a lot of changes over the years, apparently.
Yes. And she's different. So she's a she's in a sort of a Barbie like box.
She is very similar to Barbie. The one we saw, she was like she had a drum and she had like a cool scarf and she had a shirt that said, I'm with the band with the Hard Rock logo under it.
Can I read what the back says? Yes, please.
It says Hamburg, Cancun, Bali, Rome, Harper Ray travels the world playing to packed houses at the coolest venues from Munich to Macau, Bogota to Boston. Harper Ray rocks every Hard Rock with a uniquely signature style.
She's dressed differently at every Hard Rock, too. It says music is in her DNA.
She was raised on late 70s blues rock and 80s metal punk.
She has layers of rhythm in everything. That's a weird thing to say. And Harper Ray is a drummer.
Sorry. And Harper Ray's drummer is a true rocker, never happier when she's improvising a drum solo. Where will Harper Ray show up next?
Straight up typo. Yeah, right.
She is with the band or she is in the band? Because it should be like, and Harper, it should be like she hears a rhythm in everything. Harper Ray is a drummer.
I guess it says Harper Ray's drummer is a true rocker. That's like saying that there's somebody else that we are not familiar with.
Who's not available for purchase. Who doesn't even have a name?
And the single drum also strange for someone with such an inherent rhythm sense. Right. She doesn't have a sense you need more than one drum. Is it a snare or a tom?
It looks kind of like a tom to me. Kind of kind of thick. It's kind of a yeah. And she's got two sticks.
I will say maybe I'm maybe I'm being sexist and I really don't want to be. But she's wearing a shirt that says I'm with the band. Yeah, that's what I. She's in the band. Right.
So in. Yeah. Yeah. Like and I get like why that may be ironic. But when you look at the way that she looks, you would think, oh, she's like my first thought was, oh, is she like a groupie?
Like that's what she that's what she appears to be. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. See, there's different. OK. So this is a different Harper Ray. I found her on eBay.
And she's wearing what basically looks like a Disney bounder like outfit, you know, like a right like a rockabilly girl kind of a thing. And she's got a guitar. So this one very much makes it seem more like she's in the band. Yeah.
Versus just a fan of the band. And by the way, I guess I've read it and keep the same instrument. No, apparently. Yeah. But maybe that's the confusion. Maybe she comes with a drum.
But that's for another character in the Harper Ray verse, which I was looking I was like looking online, trying to find if like Harper Ray is like a little sister named Midge or something or like summer, which I'm looking at.
I don't know what store this is from, but I'm looking at a guitar one and totally different hair kind of black black with the street.
He said, yeah, yeah, it is. Yeah. And this one says collectible pin included. Yeah, that's one here, too. Yeah. He said that she has changed her look many a time.
I can only find two looks. I can to. So he said that, yes, she's she's changed looks either for some reason. People don't love Harper Ray like we all do immediately. Yeah. Not like putting her old dolls on eBay. Or there really are only two versions of Harper Ray.
I think there's two in this one. The one that we're looking at looks more like Katy Perry and the one that we saw. I don't even know if she has a analogous person.
Harper Ray like Barbie box reminded me of like a thing we Paul you noticed earlier. There were some L.A. specific pins. Oh, yeah.
The Harper Ray bar like box like we have very clearly skirting around like look. It looks like Barbie box. Right. Very clearly skirting copyright laws.
Just like those other pins were at the Hard Rock store of like Dodger Stadium with no Dodgers logo. That was a bizarre choice. It was like co-opting L.A. landmarks. Yeah. Not giving the due to the landmark.
Right. Because that costs money. Because there was a. What was the other was a universal one. But it was kind of it was kind of it was a large dinosaur that we hypothesize either from back to the future of the ride. Right.
Or Jurassic Park the ride we didn't know. And then a roller coaster that simply does not exist at Universal Studios which actually makes me go why doesn't Universal Studios have like a real like simple roller coaster.
I mean the hippogriff ride I guess is a version of it. But I mean it would be really smart for them to just pop in the thrill ride. They have the one in Orlando that's very generic the rip ride rocket.
I like that one. Yeah. Music. Yeah. But it's not themed or anything. It seems simple enough. It does seem like there's a real opportunity to make something that starts up on top of the hill and go down.
Yeah. Is it an easy neighbors. I think it's a neighbor. They're right on. Oh you're right. Because they're like the roller coasters are loud. That being said they're running fireworks now at night.
Like there's a they're being very lax about stuff. I mean you know you know me I'm just just waiting and hoping for that tonight show ride to get over there. I mean come on. Yeah.
That in our fingers you know. Yeah. I know the barbershop quartet. I think we should skip right to the Seth Meyers ride.
Alan. Oh yeah. Meyers. OK. Yeah. Why not. We don't want to clone. We don't want the world. Yeah right. Let's do things.
Look I'll take a morning Joe right if you want to do a meek and just garbara. Sure. In the NBC family.
We're talking about the VR experiences you could have on the VR episode where you could just do all the shows you could have a VR experience with everyone.
That would be amazing. 30 Rock. Yeah. Hard Rock Cafe where I would say that I think what I like about it is it feels or the gift shop I should say. Right.
No we can't talk about it. It feels exclusive. It feels like it feels like you're going to get some cool stuff out of there whether it's jewelry which they do sell.
Scott you look great in the leather jacket. You know I was just looking at photos. I don't think I look bad at all. Yeah.
Actually I'm a man. Maybe I should get that jacket. My question is joining an IMF team.
My question about that jacket is you have to agree on some level that you want a leather jacket right. Yeah. Which I just don't know if I'm willing to.
Right. That's a big it's a big person. But then once you've committed to that you're going like well I'm going to get a hard rock one I'm not going to get like I'm not going to commit to like just a nice leather jacket like that you can go like it's odd that you would want it on brand.
Yeah. Yeah. And if you're going to choose a brand for a leather jacket obviously Taz clearly the only way to go. Yeah of course. I think maybe a lot of hard rock merch is bought and not worn or used in any.
Yeah. I am around shocked that because this is a brand I think you was I realize now there's some crossover now between both of our episodes Scott and I episode of Doughboys.
Scott had a hard rock cafe item are redeveloped episode and I think you were saying on that episode like what is this brand. Yeah. Who loves this brand. So when you're talking about the merchant like not only is a t-shirt fine a leather jacket that really proclaims that you're a fan of the hard rock.
Well here's I'll add to this and say that I think that we all share one thing because my doughboys was Bubba gum shrimp company. Oh yes. Same idea. Who feels like I need to immortalize this meal with merch.
I bought a shirt there that I thought was hilariously funny and I wore it once. It was an election shirt. I wore it on election day and it said vote for gump and it was a special election theme shirt.
But then it looked too close to vote for Trump like if you look at it and so I felt really self-conscious about it. I put that right next to my adult swim when I was down there visiting them. They made these make fish center great again hats.
So it was just like just Trump hats but they just replaced the thing but again it requires a real fine look at the thing you can't just glance and when you glance at these right they elicit a different response than you want requires a knowledge of the daily adult swim streaming only show fish center.
Yes which is a very very niche kind of like if Decker and on cinema weren't on obscure enough for you if you want to go even deeper and streaming comedy. Have you guys seen the adult swim streaming show called like pitch session where like basically just like take callers pitches for TV shows and then they have like Walter Newman who is one of the adult swim development execs like will then like kind of give them feedback.
It's odd that you really are pitching the shows. Yeah. Would they ever do it. Probably not. Yeah. So I guess that makes it like okay. It's not like nefarious. Yeah. But it is like if you have a good idea it could be that could be just whipped away from you. Yeah right. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Well that's why we should save pitches from the show when we pitch great ideas we just throw them out into the air and like that when we just I worried about we just talked about that start to start tours this the story of Rex and star tours but it's it's sully it could be as far as you want to go it can be sully inspired could be sully shot for shot and but with Rex.
Yeah. I'm worried that's just going to get taken. Well I mean I would be freaked out if I were you guys because I know that in was it Hong Kong Disneyland. They just opened that Apple dumpling gang thing.
They announced that. Yeah. They were able to get enough kids and do the adoption thing. So it's like it and apparently they can turn over a hundred adoptions in an hour. But it is you know they want to kind of upgrade it a little more.
Yeah. And they're going to have a lot of children there and that was the key. Why are we pitching it for Anaheim man and the right I heard now that I'm now that's Paul brings it over I remember and it starts in Shanghai Disney. That's where the right connects to Hong Kong.
That's a bummer. I think I've had a breakthrough here of Mike. I've answered my own question. I think hard rock because like you're saying bubblegum and that makes a lot more sense to me to buy a bubblegum shirt really for whatever reason.
It's so strange to have more specific for us. Yes. OK. Yes. That's what I'm saying. So that's all right. I think in general because you could end up with like some some joke or his weird philosophy right. Even a stupid is a stupid does shirt makes more sense to me than what.
What is hard rock hard rock saying I think that I think the fact that it's so generic is the strength of hard rock rock is just like wearing a Nike shirt even though Nike is an athletic thing but it's just as generic it means nothing like it's for a dad to where he feels comfortable.
It's as hard rock it's nothing weird but it falls into the same category that the hard rock park fell into which is like music is not like popular music is not that anymore. Like when we look about you know our the mascot I've got her name now already.
Hey Haley Haley Ray I was going to call her Harper Lee Harper Harper Harper Ray who is like into like a blues and rock like that. It's almost like saying like Harper Ray is not of this world or of this musical like that's not.
I mean that music is slowly dying out in popularity like it will always be around but like it's not the hot music so it wouldn't. I think when hard rock first started in the 80s it was like everything was the cool hard rock but now it's different.
Yeah, yeah. And like so they had a leg in like 90s like you were like Stone Temple Pilots yeah grunge stuff and you've honored the club of classic masters because they led to this, but now what did 90s grunge lead to they lead to nothing it's gone.
I would think that people feel less connected to Jimi Hendrix now than you know than than Mo you know I think he's I think he's you know I think he's just like losing popularity I were at least my mind I grew up like the cool yeah the doors Jimi Hendrix yeah they don't think kids are like going back to Jimi Hendrix.
So what do you see on any show on the VMAs or the Tonight Show or anything that is well this guy's clearly Hendrix inspired right yeah yeah so there's more of the like current you know current R&B hip hop is more is influenced by older R&B hip hop but like there's no the rock lineage in terms of popular
scale seems like done yeah for sure I so so yeah this is this is a comfortable shirt for baby boomer dads and moms to wear but in addition I think it's such a generic brand and a generic logo that anyone can wear it and it's literally just like wearing a Hanes a blank Hanes shirt or something
that just says like music a shirt right music on it it's a place yeah you're less good like you're not comfortable wearing the band that you actually like you're like I need to just get something that represents music that I like yeah it would be like us like wearing your shirt just
said like funny comedy that would be like oh you like funny comedy like cool yeah yeah it's always like well like like funny or die almost started to feel I started feeling like what is this brand like because there's not a clear besides that will Ferrell's part of it
like anybody every like all the comedians all did funny or die videos and then what right what is it that's theirs besides sometimes will ferrell's like the thing of funny or die was so great at and and still great at is like finding humor and like the Kia or you know
ziplock bags and things like that you know and then the simple oil company I oil Gail yeah five Miller light spots I did in two days for the price of a half spot the Reds Apple ale you know that kind of stuff really you know the lighter side of all of that sure
Humor to be found in every classic Remington rifle
Boy well, did we keep marching on that we
We can we rock on well if we rocked next to it. How about we rock past?
What's what I want to just say one thing to what that we may lead right into our if we go to Margaritaville
I think there's a similar idea here, right?
We're Margaritaville I would argue is the best merch of the three Bubba Gump hard rock in this because Margaritaville
Represents I'm a Jimmy Buffett fan. This is like an out on offshoot of that, but I could at least buy
That your but your it's like another level of merch for someone you like
Like you know saying it's it's it's it has a built-in audience more than the other two. Yeah
Very specific also kind of co-opted island breezy lifestyle like somehow
I think there's probably people who like the restaurant and who are not necessarily even a too much about
Jimmy Buffett the guy and it's right really you think that that's a two
Two different sex of people people who like Margaritaville and people who like Jimmy Buffett. I think there might be there's a there's
There's people on the outliers
But like there has to be a crossover at least of people like I like the margarita mostly it's across
But I think that's the way he's made it bigger than right. Yes the brand
Yeah, you're right the brand itself now is so just insanely large like insanely huge and pervasive the restaurant
I feel like he that's how he became elevated
Yeah, but don't use these songs, but it as I get older and they understand
Things more feel like people feel really like they're cutting loose and they have like margarita, right?
And yeah, like somebody by calling your place a margarita like margarita bill sure the song obviously and but yeah
I feel like it's like let's go there. We're gonna have Margaret like it's like you you well
Like it's almost like now we're gonna cut like it's like it's a it's a perfect thing. It's not like they're like Jimmy Buffett food
It's like it's basically calling people in to get shit face like you're saying like let's have margarita
It's like I think people like always want margaritas. I don't know that like yeah, it's not a rate
It's not even like a beer is like a kind of a just thrown. Yeah a margarita
Suggests that you're somewhere that's like exotic or it's a little sugar
Having fun drinks before sipping and you're taking your time with it. It's right
In a place that names itself margarita, yeah, we're gonna probably have the best margarita
It's like that's the other thing too. It's like I can go to a bar get a margarita, but this place is I mean
It's it's on the wall. It's it's there. We know they're gonna make the best you sure
Did it deliver as promised?
Did you think well, this is my first time in a margarita Ville?
So this is you know, I was taking it all in and I was I have a couple questions. Yeah
I get to the margarita. I just want to like work up to it for one second. Yeah, of course. So
It's interesting. There's a lot of TVs there a lot of TVs that you would see like a sports center, but uh, it's all Jimmy Buffett
Mostly like once there's a Bieber song. Oh, okay real mismatchy
Modern music makes no sense. They're all read or Jimmy Buffett on the TV
There's no Bieber videos in that TV right what was playing while the Bieber song was on but some I think once every six songs
It'll be maybe to be different pretty buffett heavy rotation tonight. Yeah, it was just for the best there
Jason is falling asleep. I all right. Yeah, no, I'm good too much margarita
Oh, yeah, well the the idea that like
the the videos I was really in impressed by because
They look very much like heavy metal rock and roll parking lot videos
It's like there was one video where the average was having fun
It looks like all like back behind the scenes footage
But one video of like one of the fans like in a leg like a boot like they broke their leg or their foot
And it's just like they're just like dancing and like the cameras pans down to like a boot like you know
A corrective boot because they broke their leg. It's like oh alright
This is like it's it's just kind of showing all sides of the Jimmy Buffett's man
Yeah, this so there is a there is a documentary
I believe still on Netflix and I forget the name of it, but it's about parrot heads and it's produced parrot head
Is that what it's called?
It's on you've seen is why it's on a
Gulf what's the Gulf and Western?
Yeah, Jerry Jerry Diaz all these different trop. What do they call them chop rocks?
Do they call them chop rock guys, maybe and they're all
They're all like most of them are Buffett imitators essentially and they have I should look up some Jerry Diaz music
But the whole thing is a propaganda piece for parrot heads like they're trying my
Interpretation of it, and it's not a bad. It's interesting some of the stories or whatever
But my interpretation of it is they're trying to tell you that parrot heads are not just a bunch of drunken asshole baby boomers
You know we have a lot of diversity here. There's a lot of inclusion
And then there's a lot of like what good things for the community the parrot heads do when they put on their different concerts
So I do wonder if maybe it's like and then yeah take a picture of a guy with a cast
We don't care if you got a cast
Yeah, well, there's a good they saw Jimmy Buffett also wearing a shirt that said Hank what's the relevance of that? Oh that was um
What song came on? It was like an honky-tonk song came on. I don't know. That was like a Hank Williams shirt
Oh, hey good looking right? Yeah, right
Yeah, there was like six of them. Is that an original Jimmy Buffett song? No
No, that's a that's a
Yeah, so Jerry so just real quick so there's all these different Buffett imitators, so I highly recommend watching this
Mostly on his record label
Oh yeah, some of them are
But this I don't know that this gentleman is his name is Jerry Diaz and his his band is called Hannah's Reef
And here are just some songs that he wrote in this vein of Jimmy Buffett beer in the cooler on a beach in Mexico down in the
Cooler on a beach in Mexico down to the islands and welcome to Senorita Ville
Amazing
Just all people this is like if Harry Potter fan fiction was as popular or like
Well, it's popular as Harry Potter
It's interesting because
It's like I was watching him on stage and I had no no offense to Jimmy Buffett at all actually I but I was surprised that like
He is dressed like if you were to take it if you were to grab a random sampling of dads like like, you know
Mid 40s to 60s, right?
Just a random family across the country
I think that Jimmy Buffett would blend in if you have if you had no faces
But just like what they were wearing like he's one time like almost like wearing cargo shorts and like a little Hawaiian shirt
Like he one thing was tucked in and he's not like it's interesting. He looks like one of them
He does so here's I look I'm here just to start out. I talked a lot about this on that doughboys episode
I got very fascinated with this whole thing because it's and I follow all the social media of Jimmy Buffett
It started honestly it started when I we I could play the song. I'll play the song a second
And I'm sort of fascinated with what you're saying because I think at this point his whole life is a calculation
to maintain the appearance of
This man who surfs like every day right wears the clothes you're talking about chances are though. He sells the clothes
He's wearing as well. He's like Tommy Bahama, but another yeah. Yeah exactly
So like I think that like his instagram they just there's one day of one day a month
They go over to a beach. They have 12 different sets of clothes
They change them in and out of clothes and he's like going surfing again
Hey fans up and then like it's a different shirt
They get him in and out and it's like they post these periodically through the week
And then this is a very I have then they ran a restaurant and he's like crab legs
Go best gumbo in town
I'm they just get a lot of a lot of pictures of them doing stuff just to make you think
That this man is just always in a hammock or in the water or or eating crab legs or eating gumbo somewhere and like
He runs an empire. He's busy never alone meetings. They're always documenting him. He is busy in meetings
So like yeah when you're saying he's dressed like kevin the heart of
Trap rock. Yeah
Every second is a chance to be perpetuating the brand he lives and dies by that 12 inch ipad pro
That he is often photographed with yes, like he's always like working on it, right?
They show you behind the curtain of like look oh here's he's in the office
He is always on this ipad
So they will show you once in a while him in like a meeting
But he is there's so many videos and posts I will say this paul if you want to see him
Yeah a lot follow movie producer frank marshall
Oh, yeah, because frank marshall who's married to kathleen kennedy course is his like best friend
Okay, and I follow frank marshall and he is with jimmy buffett by the way
It says it right here when I typed in frank marshall's name followed by you
Right there at the top one like wow
With buffett
Like so much more than his wife honestly, that's calculated too. I don't know no frank. I don't think it's
Calculate brand just calibrated. That's just if you want to see pictures of jimmy buffett
I don't think frank has a handler frank just like loves jimmy and hangs out with them to see pictures of him
That's the way I want to see this
All the time. So how many followers do you think jimmy buffett has on social media versus how many margaritaville?
Is that where you're going?
just because i'm thinking of him as what we just talked about like this guy was like
You know all right, so on instagram, how many followers do you think he has probably low?
That lower than I think yeah 150 000. Okay. Anybody else?
Hmm do you get lower or higher? I don't know. I don't know. That's at 200. I'll go higher. All right, uh
300 000, okay 171
Because because part of me is like oh, you know what I bet you it's because
He's not probably doing that much on social media ultimately because his fan base is probably
Not on instagram. Yeah, that makes a lot of sense. Yeah younger
User base, I believe. Yeah, but he it was
Isn't his entire rise and fandom
social media before
Social media it was like truly the definition of viral right just person to person spreading the gospel
So does he really need to be pushing it? But he might also be splitting his fan base because he's got
His account he's got the margaritaville restaurant account the margaritaville
Clothing account, right? Aren't these? Yeah, they're all yeah margaritaville itself has less than he does. It's got like 100 000
buffet too
Wasn't even big till the 90s
Yeah, he didn't charge the 90s for parrot head was coined in the 90s
Uh, and that's when the whole thing exploded into like yeah
Became a big touring. Yeah when assholes were then this is this is record
Shitting in the parking lot and not cleaning it up, which is like a couple years ago. What was the city?
It was on the east coast somewhere where there's like the police were like, please if you make make sure do not use
Make sure toilets in our parking lot and then leave them there
It sounds like a philadelphia thing
If it was so he didn't chart until alan jackson had him on five o'clock somewhere. Wow
Yeah, by the way five o'clock somewhere. It was a great um, uh piece in margaritaville a big giant clock that is stuck perennially
Yeah, five o'clock and it kind of looks like it's moving. Yeah, but it's yeah
Yeah, also the clock's like a lime too. Yeah, we should mention that we did sit in the giant boat man
Yeah, because we were occupied with what we had a place to ourselves that was great
Parties, i've really dreamed of being in the big boat. Yeah, they give you a lot all those restaurants
I mean there's like
It's it's disappointing to be at a boring table because there are so many great other options
A lot of those tiki booths and stuff like that. Yeah, I was a little worse to be the merch store
It's not a merch store. I mean to be in that like what am I in? I mean that is such an anomaly
Yeah, i've never seen this before in any other margaritaville
they open when they open there was a little store not a huge store about the size of the bubblegum store and
You really didn't see a lot of people in there
So they yanked the store out and filled in more tables because I guess they figure they make more
But uh, but oddly kept the sign up which seems so easy to take. Oh, yeah
Very easy one of the words you have to take the whole thing. Yeah exactly sure
Yeah, there's a dude. There's a good gift shop in margarita in orlando margaritaville. Oh, it's huge
When you talk about this is like the real mecca. I mean
Well, look i've said it many times this this is the margaritaville that has jimmy's real plane real life plane
The hemisphere dancer the one that was shot at by the jamaican government. Okay. He was not on board
I believe bana was on board at the time and that's why he wrote the song jamaica mistake
Right and I believe you might have told me this because that sounds familiar to me
And there's no one else probably you're told that the musicality of you saying this. I feel like you've heard it
seven or eight of nine
Maybe you've listened to it if not been told it directly
But I and and I now fear i'm repeating myself
But to say that i'm also a fan of jimmy buffett's appearances on hawaii 5-0
Oh, yeah plays a pilot a good friend of the main character. Yeah, frank frank bam
Yeah, and they and they and they uh, and they go to north korea in an episode
He flies them into north korea. Yeah
Yeah
I was sorry about somebody who was on
Uh, hawaii 5-0 and messed up a line and then one of the regular he was just on that episode and then one of the regulars
Said hey man, forget about it. It's okay. It's a white 50
That's a little of a shit thing
It's really good. I think things are a little more chill when you film in hawaii
Yes, yeah, yeah with real money
um the uh
Uh, we wouldn't we didn't really partake in the food. You had the uh, I had the i've had
Probably nine or ten things on the menu in my lifetime. Okay
The i have a burger in paradise. I've had the cheeseburger paradise solid chain restaurant cheeseburger
Yeah, uh, i've had you know, like the turkey version of it fine. It's fine. I had the ahi
Tuna or what was it poke poke?
Okay, yeah, and those were good very salty but pretty good for you know chain restaurant
And they have regional stuff at some of these margaret because the florida one is like fresh conch fritters. Oh, okay, but that is
The most serious
I they're delicious. I've had them a number of times before what are you talking about conch?
What's a good conch? I only know that it's a shell. Yeah, it's a good conch is what's inside the shell. It's used
Yeah, oh, interesting. Oh
Yeah, it's like I would imagine like a clam consistency very similar to a clam
Very similar to a clam for the conch shell mentors. The conch
You get down there or conch stew I forget what it is. Um, I felt like this place
Uh
Definitely keeps the spirit alive. I mean, it's a big one. It's definitely a big one
They have a whole outdoor dining area with a fire pit and nice like uh, like lounge chairs
Oh, yeah in shaped fire
Oh, we see that you see it from above and the big but the big issue
I think with the with this margaret of a location is it replaced what used to be was an arcade right that place jillian's
Yeah, one of a ripoff david buster. Yeah. Yeah, and that was two stories
But which made me think this will be a sprawling that's what we were all fantasizing about that. It would be something
There's this big stairwell by the fire pit that leads up to nothing you get to a locked door
and that's a big bummer if it was a massive two story because we talked why I would have in last episode about uh,
Bucatubepo yeah about that bucatebepo
sprawling many little rooms and pockets and almost like uh, it was like a restaurant that
We got so popular. We just had to keep on expanding. But like yeah, yeah, they don't like they didn't know one out of their apartment
Yeah, there's and broken there. Yeah. Yeah, but this one. Yeah, it's and it feels a little claustrophobic
Yeah, that's the problem as opposed to the vegas
Location very high ceiling in vegas. Yeah. Yeah low ceiling in orlando
But like kind of the shack kind of porch thing is very charming and inside is
Inside it's got a high ceiling. But yeah, I like the low ceilings because I could look at the artwork on the ceiling where it's one
was a
uh a cloud in the shape of a salt shaker
Sure, that was one of those is is weed like a part of the jimmy buffett culture. Yes
It is more drinking. He's he's very much on record
Supporting legalized weed stuff. Okay on his youtube channel
Yeah, there was a video of him in like florida where he's like I want to support prop 91 like legalize bear one in florida
Like so he is sort of behind that and got it. Okay his audience is a bunch of drunken high fools
So right sure, I think that has to be a big thing. Obviously they don't sell weed yet
Legally in these places, but I have to imagine that's coming soon. Maybe yeah
I feel like it's in a again a very baby boomer way where it's like they're mostly drinking boat drinks
But a little weed when the kids go to bed
We all take a toke
Secret dad weed is very charming. Yeah. Oh, yeah
That's that's one of my old mild. I feel like they should start making like cbd infused cocktails. So like yeah
It's also like it's not gonna get me high. Right me that at margaritaville. Yeah, it should maybe like have like a cd
However, I don't think citywalk is open to that kind of thing as we talked about voodoo
Don't know. Yeah is like a in portland is very
It's like this is clearly like acknowledging weed culture and this one looks like a dick and
Where this is a gay rights themed donut. Yeah, no none of that made it to la. Oh, so I which
Why why does citywalk think we're I guess it's a family. There's so
conservative serve so many
Demographics it ended up sterilizing. Um, but a ramp but you know what?
Halloween horror nights when things get a little more adults
Maybe maybe though maybe the citywalk locations need to get into the spirit too. Well, I also feel like you are
entering at your own risk at Halloween horror nights because it's like
They put a warning. It's like now you come in here
It this is an adult night. It's an adult night
You know, like I feel like citywalk can never do like this is like citywalk is almost like independent of Halloween horror nights
Yeah, you know, it'd be no way to go warning
You if you come in this voodoo don't know it still be a donut that has two men kissing drawn on it
Yeah, like you can't do that thing that I was on so disturbing is like during Halloween horror nights
They do those like crazier shows like it was like the Shrek fucks the donkey and the 3d show. It's a really vulgar
vulgar
It's like kind of replacing that Bill and Ted kind of uh, but no liquor in the part like no one's getting fucked up in the
Part Hollywood no Hollywood no Orlando all bets are off in a way. They do some liquor though, right? Don't they have beer in uh, universal day
I probably had
I think I was maybe beer. I was just there like two weeks ago and I remember seeing like cold Heineken's in
um
A bin. Yeah, you can buy it in the day. Do they stop selling alcohol for horror?
Might stop at our nights because it's such a young populace because I never heard local populace
I've been there every year for about five or six years and gotten private guides and stuff for it
Like that's I bring in a big enough group that we get our own guide and don't do all in her. Yeah
It's the best. Wow. You have to like pack it in and you gotta like do it now. You gotta like what's
What's the highlight? The highlight is you get a good oral tour of Halloween horror nights, but then you also
Uh, they know how to I've never moved around that park in a more efficient
Uh away. It's like boom boom boom boom like you just like they start in a very weird way and they and they
They just wrap you in and out like it's
I always find that park to be a little bit of a nightmare to or move around especially with that big
You know, especially when horror nights kind of goes into like the uh
Like streets, right?
Your streets. Yeah
so they they they
Are very adept at going this is how we do the whole thing and you leave and they kind of like
Edge you out of like don't do that one. It's not that good and this is
Our waitress tonight was very helpful in that respect margaritaville was very good about like yeah
That one's a little sweet. That one's a little like there was one or two drinkers. She's like don't
Yeah, don't do it. Don't do it. So then she was her. Yeah pretty pretty
Uh
Give it giving with information but not like really dragging anything
She's like well if you like if you're that's what you're looking for try this
Like I asked her should I get a key lime pie or strawberry shot cake or shortcake and she was like
Look strawberry shortcake is good
But they put the ice cream on top of the bread and the bread gets hard and a little cold
Just so you know, wow very good honest response. Yeah the problems of the which by the I did keelin
But we both again and that was good. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I hadn't done dessert there. I like to uh, and sorry is uh, uh, they sell
alcohol at mows
Uh, just in mows, but you can't bring any alcohol into the mazes or anything
Okay, and like it seems like just at mows here. Okay. Um
So the margaritas we all had margarita. Yes a version of margarita
Yeah, I followed mike's lead and got what is it called the feeling hot hot hot margarita, right? Okay spicy
The margarita. It was spicy. Yeah, I was surprised at how much spice it had. I like the spicy drink
Yeah, I was surprised. I felt like a chain restaurant wouldn't go that spicy
It was actually a little spicier than I remember having it when I had it
Uh a week and a half ago. Okay, just on a leisure trip. I love it
So you go there not for just for journalism purposes. My friend works right over there. I said let's go to margarita. I said yes, please
um, so
Good or bad then? Oh, uh
perfectly fine not
Uh, not too sweet. Yeah, uh, not too much
And I feel like the liquor content was a little bit high or i'm becoming more of a lightweight because I did feel like I was
Like oh, yeah, yeah, I was at an empty stomach. We had just done an exciting thing too
But I I as soon as I had like three sips I was like, oh here we go. We're in margaritaville now
Yeah, I did like three fourths of that drink and I felt like that was a the right amount for me to do and then still
Drive, which that's good at that point if you you want to feel like because the drinks are a little expensive
You want to feel like the one is gonna kind of yeah, like get you take you home. Yeah
Uh fan of the shark fin, I think what I think that was a rum, uh tequila
Mambo and and uh, yeah, not too sweet rum could be a dangerous area
Oh, I had the one particular harbor, which was all rum and fruit juices
Are you reading the ingredients?
Hmm. Are you reading the ingredients? Are you all right? I was just summarizing
Yeah, I I will say that I found
I guess what my expectation of bargaritaville was was that we were gonna get
Almost an aggressive cheesecake factory like menu of drinks. I was gonna see like
What do you got here? Because this is a place where you like the goal is let's have fun, right?
Our drinks should be fun little cheeky-esque
Um, but no it was it was a fine fine menu of drink is a lot of drinks
A lot of drinks, but I I would argue that baba gump has a more interesting selection of alcoholic beverages crazier, too
Yeah, the atmosphere in there is crazier and the menu itself
Uh as like I ordered I mean, it's so crazy
I ordered a drink I thought was alcoholic and I didn't realize until I had the whole thing that it wasn't
Well, yeah, I mean look, I mean I think I think uh
Uh, baba gump was the first time ever had one of those mini carnita bottles like yeah in like shoved in the drink
Yeah, it was good. Amazing. It was great. Yeah
Um because it kind of like it actually lessened the taste it was like I think it was a margarita
with a corona stuck into the corona is kind of like
Uh like sucking out the sweet so you kind of have this like beer orita. It is i've had that before it is very good
Yeah, my city walk places
Is have a have a bottle and another bottle shoved in yeah, bless him my uh, uh, buddy richie
Uh, I I took I was like, hey, you know, let's go
Let's go to drink a margarita, but that'll be a fun
He seemed like a guy be into that and he was like
Uh pretty hard edged after and said, you know, I you know gotta be honest
I don't think this place is happening. I think it's too far
It's at the end of the right at the end of the whole thing as opposed to i'm thinking of baba gumps
As you say it's in the middle. It's in the hub of all the action margaritaville's
It is like literally you can't see it behind the hard rock
You might miss it and I don't think la is really
adopting jimmy buffett
Yeah culture could be wrong, but I think that two story thing is I I don't think I don't think uh
margaritaville's on the verge of a collapse or anything, but I don't know how if it makes I don't know
It's gonna be a gigantic. I feel like they should have stuck out with jillian's because
Because that well, I guess maybe it's hard because I would like a david busters closer
I mean, there's a david busters nearby in hollywood, but
It's that impenetrable. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's hard to get to and now it's close
Hollywood in highland. You're good. Yeah
I mean first of all what you guys are saying is heartbreaking and the idea that maybe this isn't the right spot for it
Or though like I think hollywood and highland would be a much better spot for margarita. Yeah, I think
Well, they have the cabo wabo
Yeah, tina's there. I think honestly a better place for it is third street promenade
That's right by the water. Yeah
The fear itself each yes
They were like bubble gump is there too. Yes now they should make it
There's i've been to the margaritaville at navy pier in chicago, right and it sucks
It is small and cramped and bad and it's too far from the water and it's like dirty
It's like it's so disappointing. So like if they did a full-on
Orlando style one on the pier. Oh
We'd be there all day. We we would never leave
I've been to the uh, atlantic city one which I would put on par with like the vegas one
Like it has a nice tall ceiling
It's built into the resorts casino right on the boardwalk and on the other side of the boardwalk on the beach
There's a land shark lager bar and grill
Um, sure it's got two and then there's the margaritaville casino area of resorts
Wow
so and I think the thing that that has a going because it's a casino and it's like always open or I think maybe they
close for a couple hours in jersey, but like
I remember going there around christmas one year and eating there and the place was packed
You see yeah, and that's a city walk. Yeah. Yeah, and so like casinos the vegas one's usually crowded
but uh city walk even like
you know
The end of summer ending summer, but like tuesday night. It's empty. Well, here's what I'm gonna say
it
Reads as an adult place if i'm a family which I would argue the majority of people in city walk are
If i'm a family and i'm going where are we gonna go to eat?
I think margaritaville doesn't feel like a family establishment buco di peppo feels like a family establishment far
Bump a gum feels like a fart, you know, like feel like johnny rockets
Uh old classic even saddle ranch which you know
I think like runs that gamut because it's like there's a little bit of an edge to it, especially when hollywood
But that one it was a little tamer. Yeah
You know it they're I just don't feel like it calls to families
I feel like you know it calls to the the parents even though you sit in there perfectly family oriented
But you might not know that yeah, sometimes there's stilt walkers making balloon animals. That's fun
Yeah, but not always you should see it in full swing sometime
I would love it is shut with a band that is instead why go in and just hear the recording of
margaritaville when you can hear a band playing
exact same way
Jason and I this is a video that never came out that I do have a copy of that
Maybe I will put online someday jason
I were we went to the opening of the margaritaville to cover it and saw jimmy buffett play on the stage
Wow, yeah 30 minutes there. So
We got to see the ultimate concert. I mean, that's amazing. Yeah
Yeah, and we also like that same that was last year
We went up there. I think all three of us on the day. It's soft opened
That's true
We got word that it opened then we went to the press event. Yes, that's true
Wow, we also went back for your birthday like a month or two later
People like oh hey, yeah. Yeah, so people started to we started to recognize
Waiters and still walkers staff has turned over those since because I haven't seen a lot of those folks
Yeah, let me ask one question. I don't mean to upset anybody here. Okay, go ahead the difference between kaba wabo and
and margaritaville is
Uh, I would say it's a little more of a specific what the lifestyle is at margaritaville
I see like what the vibe is what the kaba wabo is a similar vibe
But it's just feels a little more generic to me, but it's it's trying to do what margaritaville does
But I'm kind of pulling some hard rock energy
Yes, yeah, I'm letting the difference. Yeah, you're right. You're right. Also the menu is primarily
I'm sure there's burgers and steaks and stuff, but it's primarily tacos burritos
enchiladas nachos that sort of guy so it's a more mexican
Femme, yeah, right. Um, all right, so that's an interesting
I mean into when you look at the rock stars behind
Sammy hagar jimmy buffett hagar a little more aggressive a little more wild
I think I think kaba wabo is a more unpleasant
Brand, okay, so that to me, I don't know how other people I think that's right
And we've sat though with that cool that the big table at kaba wabo cantina and hollywood and highland more than once
And we sat there before a jimmy buffett concert before a jimmy buffett, which I went I went with mike to the bowl
To see just like two or three years ago already, which was
It was fun interesting
But why you went with us to wire's air as well
I was there and the it like I just by he played all the hits by half hour
And he like oddly stacked at the top and then I I was just like I am thirsty for a fourth chord
Give me one more just give me a minor. Give me a sharp
Anyway, it was gda city
For two and a half hours and then I
His guitarist do a song like two songs and he's like goes as a glass of wine off stage. Mm-hmm. Wow, it's so fantastic
Uh his show his live show. You got to listen to live recordings. He's barely singing. He's like, yeah
Like yelling this this is the noise that comes out of his mouth when he's singing now
uh
It's I can't wait till he comes back
We've been talking about it jason and I were just talking about it on the way over
I will not be joining just god is gonna be a real stick in the mud. It does not want to go. I just
Be curious to see what it would be like I just want to see what kind of
Uh, can like what kind of dancers he picks because in the videos we've seen there there's a real
mix between different shows
Um, we we we were going too long on margaret. I could do another two hours. So now we go to the main event
Well, no, I I'm so
There are two things that I must do all I was saying is that we're only going to do 10 more minutes of
Uh, I'll do you hold to it. I'll do one more. I was gonna play a little math sucks
Which is the song that math sucks on your own time. Yeah, look up the song math sucks
uk s
That's when I fell in love with jimmy buffett, uh, and it's from his album beach house on the moon
All right. Anyway, so a couple years ago, uh, I signed up for a mailing list because margarita
ville
Is gonna have like a resort in orlando called margarita village and people will be able to live there
They'll be able to buy homes
There's going to be some sort of kind of water parky part of it and I think you'll be able to rent stuff for vacations
Are available for tours at the moment, but uh, they're still doing it all in phases. So the water park is not ready
So this is 2016. So I signed up for this mailing list just to you know, be in the know
So they would like send you stuff about like hey
Do you want to put 100 grand down on a house and I'd be like, oh no
Thanks or whatever like you get emails like that. So then I get an email from a guy and he says hey
Hey mike, it's time for us to begin submitting names for the streets of margaritaville resort orlando
I would love to have your creative help in naming our streets for the resort
Feel free to use song lyrics sea sun and ocean themes or anything that screams margaritaville lifestyle below are some street suffixes
To help complete the names. I really appreciate your participation and input as we create a truly unique destination in orlando
Finn's up david
So then of course he's like alley bay boulevardie suggesting things
So this is again pre podcast
I'm texting with scott. I'm texting with jason and anthony
Geo, yeah, we should have back on we should have
We sent them a hundred
Names for a street. We we we spent a day going back and forth on text really workshop
I like mine in mine individually. I tried to like
Yeah, really like like now that one's weak. That's gotta go or that one's that one's too soft
Uh, uh, yeah, I really hyper analyze. What how do we think we should I read a hundred should we read some?
midnight
It's a night a.m. For the audience
So i'll read just uh, you know, i'll read uh
Uh picking at record it later put it at the end of the episode. I'm just gonna read 10 at random. Okay, uh
uh sunny side street
pelicans beak bay
lazy river road
working and playing way
colada cove
sand dollar drive
drunk drive
buccaneer boulevard
Skip and work circle
I'm gonna go a couple more. These are scott's damp ramp
rumble ridge
Uh margarita strida
Uh nautical mile shopping plaza
What was the one?
There was one you had this car it's just shorts street that was my favorite of yours
Why I was also proud of drinking drive. Oh, yeah, because I think I had drunk drive and you had drink and drive
And we submitted them both
When it's a hundred and jason's I think this is yours if there was a four or six way intersection port of indecision
And then I explained
I have a qualifier here because I said marshall park after jimmy's friend movie producer frank marshall
So we'll post all of these on twitter. Yeah, uh, we submitted all of these and then I got a response awesome list
Mike really appreciate your creativity and time put this put this list together. I will keep you posted on the results
Uh, so that was two and a half years ago years ago every once in a while. You get a construction update, right? But
So it's not open yet. No march 27 2018. Hey there david. Just wondering if the final street names were ever finalized
Thanks, no response. Come on david. So how do we put pressure?
on
The margarita village resort
How can we utilize our?
You're competing ardent fan base
uh
Hundreds strong to get them to make sure that we really love all streets is one of our names
And it could be any of them whatever we give them such a range such a great. Yeah
I mean, don't you feel that maybe?
it's it's just throwing like a little like uh chum
Um to like, you know their fans like go name our streets, but they have no intention of using those
Yeah, and then everyone just assumes like oh, maybe that was somebody else's cool name or whatever
Yeah, but they don't want yeah
I think we got to look up this guy on linkedin to start
Make sure he's still with the company and not with another company or in jail for financial fraud or something
There was a there was an email in between this exchange where he said mike
We submitted over 50 names, but he doesn't say our names 50 names to the county for approval
Once we finalize our site plan, we will assign street names
Probably later this summer. That's 2016. So we have a great holiday weekend
It's if it's a government issue, right people to storm this. Let's look up whatever county it's in
That's what we're saying. I mean, I feel like your audience can help
Get this together there had but but how specifically there's got to be a way
Maybe it's a dual approach of hitting the margarita village
uh
Homeowners board or whatever
um in the and the
And something in the city of orlando
But i'm worried tweeting isn't going to do I think someone has to introduce a referendum to make sure here's what we've talked about people
Oh, yeah, that's good, too
I was going to say somebody with a backpack has to hop some fences
And see if they can get a peek at them one of these urban explorer
Types that one that's look. I don't want anyone trespassing but I have already seen
footage of how this
Uh construction is progressing via
drone
Somebody needs to get a drone going over the in progress margarita village
And zoom into any signs that you see and get the footage back to us
So if you're an orlando drone owner, first of all great to meet you
And happy you're listening to the podcast. We may have a lot of other jobs for you, but thing number one
Get that drone going over margarita village
Do you think that the idea of the village has not been built and the street names have been picked?
Really are indicative of the fan and the culture of the parrot head like we'll get to it man, but first
We don't have to do construction every morning like yeah
Like this is like, you know, like they put it like you just do a drone video like footage and it's like
Like one house like kind of halfway done like like we're on island time
Hard to work with disney world down the road
so fun
We wanted to put a barbecue grill in the center of the house, so, you know, like just weird like
choices
Um, this foundation is crooked. No, it's not
What's fine to me?
now
Are we moving out of margarita village?
I would say it's hard for me to be ripped away from it. But yes, we should probably move on
pretzels as the next which you know, I I did not partake in a wet souls today. Yeah
But i've partaken in wet souls before sure
But my concern about wet souls at universal
Is that it's not going to be up to the high standards of my wet souls thing because they have to turn over too many pretzels
Yeah, I had a pretzel today. I we split a pretzel. I had a pretzel right before we did iFly
And I gotta tell you that first pretzel I thought was good. Yeah, like a mall level pretzel
It was warm. It had the salt on it. It was very good. Now we had a second. I did not like it
You didn't really know that's like a standard wet soul pretzel
Yeah, I just don't like the wet soul because I had it even like and it's because I was hungry because I didn't dinner
But I was like I could really go for some more pretzel. Like I was even like craving more pretzel once it was over
So that's always the worst because you go back for seconds and it's never as good
There was no way I mean it was because I was hungry. Yeah, like it was an amazing pretzel
What I what I appreciate and I think that the people who are listening to this obviously you're committed too because you're 12 or 14 episodes in here
You uh, you didn't just go over to voodoo donuts, which is only a mere feet away
You stayed in yeah, we actually stay in the sector. Yeah, you didn't yeah
You could have easily just broken for the second one. You already had your pretzel
You could just go over to voodoo and be like this is you know
Yeah, you know no
sector breaking anywhere
Oh really never straight
No, no
And even we had a piece of pretzel and we were in the hard rock gift shop and all of a sudden jason walks in
And he's got a big cup of like wet souls like pepperoni. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, he's rubbing his eyes
And like I will say I had one of those and those were not good
I fucked up. I was concerned about doing the skydiving on an empty stomach like
No, no, no, you have to do stuff like that on an empty stomach. I I was giving starting to fade
And I was like, well i'm gonna get a bottle of water and I was in there anyway this morning
Like eight or nine
Okay, i'm rocking a 6 a.m
Yeah, I did 7 a.m. And you're still here. Yeah
I do it. It's it's his loyalty to content. Yeah, I have to I have to place your loyalty to content
Every hour you're sleeping. No content
Yeah, they were um
They they were uh, that was I thought a good option. I thought it'd be interesting a good option
uh the pizza pretzel bites it said pizza, but it was really just like
Pepperoni baked into little bits of pretzel and it was
It was didn't look good to me
No looking at that cup that no, I don't like pretzels in the cup. I honestly after the the boat drink
And the skydive i'm starting to feel at all. You're jacked up. I can tell something is going on with you
I've keep mentioning it during the show. You're rubbing your eyes. You're yawning a lot. It's I am worried
We're gonna look over and you'll be as asleep as edwin is right now on the on the couch
Edwin nipped it me a little earlier. I think you went out he sometimes if you're if you're not me or lindsey
And you rub his little belly or his haunches. He doesn't like it on that. But yeah, my ride i'm screwed. Oh, you're no you're fine
You're gonna have to drive
You're gonna have to drop him off. You're gonna he's gonna have to know
So I can get under the cubs, you know get those covers
All right
Yeah, so
Let's also stick to the stick to the bottles of water and the regular pretzel was a was a b those
Pepperonis were a d minus you need some culpability and you really thought there was a world where a cup of pepperoni
Had those before i've had the full-size ones before and it's been fine full. What do you mean full-size?
Just a regular pretzel, but like little pepperoni baked onto the top
Really about this pretzel pepperoni
That's crazy. The thing also they were out of the hot dog pretzel
He's awake. Yeah
Masterpiece this is most awake. He's been all night. Have you noticed this? Yeah, I know
Pepperoni it looked like the thing you bought looked like a cup of discarded pizza crusts and somebody like smack
Like as we didn't eat. Yeah
Like you're cleaning out your car
We had a lot of
You know variables the the I we weren't sure if we were gonna hit the cutoff for the skydiving
So we didn't realize how much training?
Was here's what we've been talking and talking talking. We never said hey
We this is the one where we went indoor skydiving. It's the most exciting
Actual it's the only in all 19 of these fucking things. It's the only thing it's an actual
Full-themed experience and we never let's get excited about it now. It's a ride
We're building up to the end because we had to we started with it
You would not want to hear about wet's those pretzels. We got to walk
We got to walk into this like we you know, you get your this is it
This is your tom cruise find the helicopter sequence like they like
This is the moment you're gonna walk out remembering feel like you've done the halo jump now, yes, we all did it
I'm ready to be in a movie with tom. I'm feeling comfortable and with stunts. I fly
is
This experience that has alluded me but i've seen it numerous times
It's a big giant tube with a gigantic fan underneath that simulates
skydiving
and seems
Insane when you walk by it, but it gathers a large crowd
I think we all gathered a crowd in our time there
Yeah, it's interesting to see people just floating in the air and especially the instructors who are truly impressive in putting on a show
Yeah, during the day they can go real high they do flips. They do all sorts of tricks
Which now we know the system that they take in like eight at a time everybody at minimum gets to
Perhaps more and then when it's all said and done and you know how difficult it was
That here now watch what I can do and the guy does legitimately incredible like literally does a show off
Section which honestly I have to say I could do without that part
I like maybe it was because we saw about four people do show off
Minutes, but it was it was fun
but i'm also like
Well, i'm trying to get i'm trying to get up in this
Yeah, it's like it's like it's like lebron james like going like now watch me play and then you like, yeah
Like yeah, it's like, oh, yeah, you're great
Like all right that too buddy if he just got out of here cranked it all the way up and didn't mind me fucking myself up
Well, I mean like you look here's the thing. Oh, you should walk through the whole thing
But they only give you a minute at a time. Yeah, which
Seems when you're in there, it seems longer than a minute. Oh, it seems like 10 minutes. Yeah, it felt so long
But it also feels like not enough to get fully
Uh used to it. Yeah, yeah, yeah kind of as soon as you're starting to feel although, you know what happened to me. I think
It's a long minute and that and the in like 30 to 40 seconds
I was like, I think i'm really cruising and then the rest like
Nope gone. I got too cocky now i'm wobbling around then it's not working out but yeah, but then
Yeah, I found the exit kind of fun. I like the exit yourself out there
I felt a little cool doing that even though i'm sure it did not look cool. Yeah, actually there was a
When jason exited it looked like a charlie chaplin movie like when they're like if you ever seen the gold rush
Where like he opens the door there's a big wind burst and he gets knocked back the first time you did it
You went and all of a sudden you got knocked back. I real confidently went for it and fucked it up
Yeah, which is not to say by the way, that's not the most i'm sure my first one was the most embarrassing of all of us
I mean, I think I think we all had moments. I I never felt
uh
Great, but I felt or confident. I should never they never have confident, but I feel like
It's so easy what you have to do, but it's so hard when a giant fan is pushing at you. Yeah
truly insane can we talk about first of all hats off to the ifly people because
Uh, not only did they make room for us. Yeah, they hunted us down
Yeah, we had given up all hope
Uh, and they found us in margaritaville and they brought us back in so
Kudos to the ifly team at universal studios if you are 12 episodes deep and you're hearing this you guys
Yeah, I know I said the thing about the showboating but uh, you guys are all uh,
Classy great people who cared about you know, giving us uh the the experience of a lifetime
Yeah, check kept checking in. We're really monitoring everything very it none. It was not confusing
They did a good job of paring it down to just the basics. You need to know right they throw
Yeah, I find i've found laser tag tutorials to be more complicated than what they present
It's like four things. Yes, and they but they also presented it like well
You need to go to school before you do it and there was a moment. I was like, oh wow
we have to like go in here and like learn something right and uh,
It's like I was saying in there. It's like
there
The uh the introduction video to soren
Uh, it seemed to be more serious than yes, so maybe we watched about a lot of guys
But then you enter this crazy yeah, you watch kind of a pre
Ride video where they show you the the hand signals that you need to learn
Uh, which I guess if we list them off, it's like the you know, straighten your legs bend your legs
Uh, just yeah chin up and relax
Toughest thing to figure out how to do because I would relax and I would fuck up
Yeah
Well, yeah
Like I would relax and I tried to get my body so relaxed then my arms would drop down right
Head up is the trickiest thing because you always got to keep your head kind of elevated your arms are out
like it is an interesting body position because
It's a lot of things you have to be focused on at the same time. Yeah, also in the preview video
They did a smart thing which I don't I don't even think I talked about this and I there was a bachelor party
I went to where I had to drive a fast car around a track with other fast cars and the pre video
Made everyone in there terrified because it threw
50 things
All right
So what you're going to do is look at the green marker when you pass the green marker
Then you put your eye on this other marker and you you you uh pedal to the metal you put your full gas down
You try to drive and it's throwing all of this terminology at you and we left there going
Oh my god, we're never going to be able to do this. What I liked about this was
They don't over explain everything they throw everything at you like basically once and then it's just posted on things
And they basically kind of are like there's no way these people are going to remember exactly what we're saying until they're in there
Which is what I mean all you basically have to do is lay down
Because the air is poor, you know
You just lay down and then kind of just be as straight as you can be
Ultimately with your head up. I mean it weird kind of like yoga challenge. Yeah. Yeah, just being yes still and and like
Centered which is what I blame any mishaps on with you mike is like I do feel like you just didn't catch like the
The initial drifts correct and I don't feel like that was your fault you're saying that because because there is a person outside of the
I've like controlling
The speed in the wind speed of the wind
So thank you for letting me off the hook because sure it is weird because you're not quite sure what you're doing
Versus what they're doing because then there's a certain point where sometimes they'll turn it up
He'll be like, you know turn it up a little bit and then maybe that one knocked you down if you're not perfectly
Like I think my issue was I where I was told I was like leaning too much into one of one of my hips
But it was hard to kind of figure that out because you're also like on air. You can't like you can't it's hard to find
Like that yoga pose because there's no ground. Yeah, are you ever?
On your stomach. Yeah
Like it's the rarest when I
When I was at eye level the arms I had the hardest time going like oh, so yeah
They are saying eye level but it's a little above eye level
Yeah looking like and I would say like when I was on my back, which was an inadvertent moment for me
Uh, it was way more fun
Because because you're you're kind of scooped and you just kind of are letting it like
Lift you and you're in this like zone. Whereas what they're what they're making you do is kind of like lay down
lay down
Flat, I don't know
It almost seems like it would be better if you lie down on your back on the metal grate and then you were like turn it up
Yeah, like it feels like you go up a little bit and you just be like hey
This is nice like that right to me like it might be a more pleasant experience
Maybe it's harder to control your body that way tricky because like you're walking into a room where
You're gonna basically fly up right?
You know, so you have to like feel confident like that was scary to walk in and you were the first one of us to walk
In scott made me go even though he was first. He was the next one
He was in the wine thing. So we were in there with a group of children. Yes
Children and I was right that children were much better than us
It seems like and the mom was too
And the mom was good. She went up pretty high for not having like the super high thing
Uh, yeah, the kids were very good. There's like also here's the thing the eye for a little different size
Like tunnels in different places because I fly is all over the country
So some of them like we even saw on the video have these like shooting up like, you know
Cartier ship kind of things going on. I think this is a small one. This one
Yeah, it's a tiny one. It's very tiny. I could have sworn in that video. You saw somebody flying through a hole
Yeah, and then went to another thing
I have like full like full like crazy training things like that. So like especially for me
I was bumping into the wall. I'm six three
Yeah, I'm a big guy too
And I feel like I was bumping into the wall. There's a lot of like yeah
So like well, yeah
The kids were really doing well because clearly perfect for kids are tiny and
They're getting hit by the right amount the right, you know ratio of air or whatever
Yeah, so like they were that being that being said were just a bunch of adults trying to
Make excuses for why we were so bad, but I think also at the same time just give us a little bit more time
We only had two minutes. Yeah to do it and that was broken up into
Segments. Did you see the chart inside? There's a chart on the wall that you could go back there to to study
And it is as big as the periodic table of elements
Yeah, all the courses that you could and can take. Oh, oh, yes. I did take a yeah, it is so complex
You said when we want to be 40 of them, right?
It's the levels of Scientology. Yeah, they're in Roman numerals. It was crazy
I was like what is going on here because at this point if I'm gonna spend that much money at iFlight it was
Which is it's kind of like for all of us with our universal discount. It was 190 dollars. Yeah, right. So 190 bucks
Um, yeah, still that's a step down. Yeah, we know
And if you were to do a package where you get more than two, it's really good. Yeah
Yeah, that's crazy expensive flight and you can yeah, you can i'm just seeing how much that would be. Yeah, that's
I don't know. It's like if you do why don't I just jump out of a plane? I guess is what i'm saying
Yeah, especially when you there's something about seeing that chart
Maybe that's like 50 bucks a person so seeing that like knowing knowing what you paid
And then walking in and seeing oh wait, i'm level one of
200 like literally that many little mini step outs. Yeah, what is going on here?
Maybe you would hope that the class gives you a little bit more time
In the air, but again is that skill?
The transferable to jumping out of a plane if you are a skydiver, please let us know
Claim that skydivers train in these
I think tom did and I think probably did I mean no he definitely did in for the halo jump
Like he did a lot of work in the halo jump. Okay, sure
Uh, yeah, I wonder if he like did he do something where he had to restrict his oxygen because the halo jump is the is the very tall
It's very high. He was having a tank so he had the tank so he could do fine in that tank. Oh, I see
um
Erin my wife who came with us she she went skydiving years ago and she
She was passing by the sci-fi thing and saying I think it's weird because I think it's simulating like the most unpleasant. Yes, right of it
It's not the part where you're just like gliding and it's like the most you're gonna hit in the face with the most like caustic
Part, but I don't know. I also by the way to simulate skydiving indoors. I'm not gonna fault
I think it's incredible technology. They figure it and I had a good time. Well, it's doing it. It seemingly is just a giant fan
Yeah, yeah
I had the preconceived notion going into that. I would feel a little unease of the feeling of falling which I
recognize clearly is foolish because
You mean I'm into the fan?
Yeah, like I had that it was we were sitting there and I was like what if this is the one time that the metal
Grading is gonna break. I do wonder they must have an emergency generator. Like if there's a power outage
Or like an earthquake which actually happened while we were there
I was a minor. I'm just yeah, none of us noticed but like there's got to be a backup generator that kicks in like
Pretty that's it. We should eat it. You figure that out. Otherwise you're gonna hit flat on your face. Yeah, but
Well, if you're the guy if you're doing the show
Yeah, that would be a concern. But I think ultimately what you're talking about is
So a fan shutting off is still rotating around so you would go down low
I will say this I just realized it right now and never felt like I was really in the air and I was so that's
Interesting thing for skydiving. I didn't I was never like I was worried about the height and when you'd see people go up and down
It doesn't didn't feel like you had I mean we we all were off the ground
We were all right really off the ground floating in air
But didn't I never felt like I was I never felt like oh, I'm like, oh like I don't know
I never had that feeling of such a height sensation. Yeah
It's really they could he just as easily call it air swimming. Yeah
There's a real presence of that
Yeah, so much because so much of it is just trying to stabilize you
So that is why it feels more like swimming than it does because you're taking your especially at this intro level
You're trying so hard just to stay afloat
We took an intro swimming class. Yeah, yeah, does anybody think that you might have looked cool or anything?
I haven't really gotten to look at these videos. Well, I'm curious not to it won't be interesting trying to make your fun faces
Sure, you're like here. I'll just throw yours. I know your direction. See what see what you generally think
I mean, I don't think I look cool. No, ah
It's interesting watching myself in the thing I'm like, oh interesting and I'm trying to see
Where I'm oh, yeah, I'm tilting. It don't look cool. Oh, I'm there. I'm up a little bit. Yeah
It's interesting. I can't even at two seconds as a victory. It was a really hard thing to maintain states
It's interesting to see you can see yourself. You should almost get the video. Whoa. Wow
Yeah, you should almost get the video right after you see it cuz I'm like I'm looking at myself and it's a totally different
perspective and an understanding of what I
Was doing versus what it looks like I was doing. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know what you mean total disconnect, but yeah
I'm like, oh, that's what I was doing. I have downloaded my video and
The funniest part about it is just a man carrying me into the tunnel. That's very funny on Twitter, by the way
Well, yes, there's a man just carrying me like I'm a
Mannequin see that was a good that was a good fly there. Yeah, I had like good 20 sec 15
I mean probably three seconds Margaritaville sign. Oh, I love it Margarita real sign right behind
Yeah, so like I had a decent run right here and then like something hit me and I flew
Mm-hmm, and then I kind of like lost but then I'm up. I'm up. I'm up
I'm there then. Oh, yeah, so then okay, so
At this point, I wasn't holding my arms out far enough
So if you're a wrestling fan diamond Dallas page does the diamond cutter and that's kind of what they're trying to tell you
It's like this, you know, it's like right kind of like this
So they're telling us to do that so they had a talk with all the four of us in between the first and second
The children were not the children had done it perfectly the guys like all right
Here's what you gotta do
You gotta do and he's like explains it and like they're like all right cuz like they were so dissatisfied like these two dudes working
We're like I feel like they were upset at us and then we asked how did we do and they were like, uh
You know not not that bad. Yeah, you know, I think we were pretty I think what they were real
I think what they wanted to do was really toss us up in the air and they were really hoping that on that second round
they could get the
You know, and I think we were all almost there
More we could have maybe oh, I think I think yeah, we just needed like I
would pay like a hundred dollars to be like
Give me in there. Like let me just like kind of you know, you're counting down that minute. You're in a pressurized situation. Yeah
Well, you go a little I think there's ways you could get six
But I also feel like on the other hand it might have gotten boring after that, right?
Maybe I was also ready to not be in earplugs and helmet and goggles
yeah, the guy though we have a video of it the guy pulls me in the middle and
Like truly like Tom Cruise throwing that guy through the window through the mirror in
Possible he like throws me like up against the thing
It didn't hurt or anything, but it's funny the video is funny and he's like no and he's like showing me higher your arms
Have to be higher and he's like showing me like very aggressively cuz like the minute the seconds are counting down and I was like
What's going on here? I know I was a bit intense moment
Yeah, it looks like he's like screaming looks like I just did something
Don't you threaten my wife?
Green yes, it's like the first mission of house everything's like mission impossible. Let's be honest. We were just as cool
Is that we're just cool. I felt like I was more confident with how mine went than than I thought
But then I went and I have only looked at two seconds of video
Right they told us to smile and I wasn't having fun. So I did successfully smile the entire time
but what I thought
Was like kind of a gentle glide. I when I looked back the wind was blowing my face back and what I and my
Smile to me. I I think I looked exactly like Stan Laurel. I
Look like a wax figure of Stan Laurel. I'm not super proud of this video
But I'll throw it up. Anyway, I look like a good
madam to so's wax figure version of myself that just says like a
Neutral face and I don't even quite look like me because the wind is blowing
And a man is throwing you into the garden a man is literally picking up the disposal of the girls
Yeah wax figure if you yeah, you'll look at this video on Twitter and you'll be like, oh somebody put a dummy in there
That looks like Mike
Repeatability under what circumstance would you like set for some reason go do it where you could get more?
Yeah, I would go back to I fly I would I thought the people were lovely there. They treat us really well
I just think I do think it's something that you need to
The from the first and the second time I felt very
Different like I'm like, okay. I thought there's a couple of things you just get over like the idea of like I'm walking to this
Thing I'm like and it's yeah, there's like I think you just get better exponentially. Yeah, I would do it again
I would definitely do it again if I get tired imagine like making a point
But if so if a group was doing it I'd be like, oh definitely and then I can kind of get to the chase a little more
I also wouldn't mind
Like it would be more fun to be in a group where it's all our group like we were four
Mixed with four right so we don't get upstaged again. Yeah
But he's a little kids. Mm-hmm, but the price tag is a little hefty
Yeah, 50 50 bucks and that's with a discount for two minutes
The fly time the way the thing is structured price wise is that to get like I guess like you can get a whole group together
And it's so like a whole group together and you get like so many more minutes
For like twice the price or something like like it like just spending double or something gets you so much more
So it's structured to try to make you go
I'm sure package with you know pitch more pictures and more time and I stuff so like
Yeah, I think that would be the way you'd have to do it is get a big group together and like do the special
Package or potentially. I don't know if I should say who but I guess someone who's been on the show
Did it on mushrooms? Oh, no, I don't know how to handle. Yeah, I don't
Yeah, I just like
Yeah, that feels intense. But also relaxing. Maybe like, you know, if you if you got a view
I don't know. Maybe that's the way that was the missing. Let's all
Let's go back right now make the
Bang on the door make them open it back up find some mushrooms on the way
Yeah, this would be great
4 a.m. Fire up that fan and go
That's all it takes right? We're here. We're back
Get it going
We so the waiver you have to say you have to sign a waiver
Which is like, you know if anything happens bad to you, it's not our fault
Yeah
And it tells you like if you have any heart trouble back trouble or your shoulder has ever been
Dislocated and my shoulder has been dislocated. It was a casual dislocation
Right. It was a car accident and it was like
Hang in there for like a little and I was like, ah and like popped it back in
And like sometimes if I'm like leaning on it or something or weird or honestly
Sometimes if I sneeze into it, like it kind of goes like it can pop in and out a second
And I'm reading this and I'm like, oh my gosh, I'm gonna die
I'm gonna pop in and out a second and I'm reading this and I'm like, I hope this isn't a problem
But you braved it for the podcast. I mean that's it. I'm a theme park journalist
Content. Yeah
Glory to content
So yeah, so I was like I was a little worried going in and I was so tense the first minute
I think that's really more what did it but I was like, oh no, my shoulder hurts after this first round
And then I was like, does it hurt or is it in my head?
I can't tell and then that second time since I was so much more comfortable
It my shoulder felt better right after it popped back in so it well that didn't pop out during the
Yeah, so maybe but maybe it will never pop out again
So I do think like yeah that like tense like just a first a minute of like getting your but I know you scott and jason
Said they felt sued by it. Yeah, and I were saying we were tense afterward. Yeah, I felt like well
I felt this thing of like
um
Like my body was just being I mean, I guess my body was being beaten by a fan
so it's almost like my body was like hot from
Like a very like intense. Yeah thing. Yeah, it was interesting. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I wasn't relaxed
So definitely wasn't relaxed. It was like my body had to kind of like
Like chill out for a second. Yes, I felt like
There was a time when I went on like a stressful hike and like yeah
It was like it was going downhill and like I was like skidding on like dirt
And I remember just being stressed out for like 15 minutes and I got down to the I felt like
Like fucked up
15 minutes and it was because my body is warm and I was like, yeah
Yes for too long and like yeah, so it was similar to that but not as severe
But yeah, the second time I was doing good tired afterwards and then we got back to the car
I started to feel the like yeah, like I had had a massage
Yeah, but now you're a so what would you say?
Now I feel like honestly my stomach feels like I am dying
Yeah, you know
The the zen zone versus that massage. What oh, yeah sure. What what what is better experience?
I fly or the zen zone
uh
I play as a more interesting experience. Yeah
Yeah
What if it's relax massage i'm just talking about the massage after effect, uh, I think zen zone zen zone was so generous
They tossed in so much extra stuff. They were so nice. I fly they gave us free stuff too. They were also yeah
They were very nice. Yeah, which you know what which helps make up for all of the other the city walk
uh nonsense such as the
The parking I know you had a slight tail of parking. Whoa, yeah too much money
I thought it was a discount but still that only knocks off. There's a valet right and and the valet is a great
uh addition to any big theme park, uh, you know like to be able to get your car quickly and get out and it
Dumps you right into this heart of city walk. But one of the things that you have to do with that is
You pay a premium
And but you can get validated and I knew that we were going to be at margaritaville
And I knew that was going to be a validation that I could definitely use down the past
They lure you into this like idea that the movie theater can somehow validate
But it's it's not it's a very complicated process. Give you five dollars in cash
Yes, if you go up after the movie with your receipt. Yeah
which takes off, um a little bit on a very expensive thing so, um
Normally if you're there for over two hours, it's 45 dollars under two hours
It's like 25 dollars. I think that's about the ratio. Um, I could give or take
um
And so when we went to sky fly or ifly they were like hey
We can validate if you did valent as like I did he's like but you have to also make sure they see your certificate
I was like really because we got a little diploma you missed it. So I I I went there
They've already stamped it. They've rubber stamped the thing they in the valet center boom
Give it to him. He goes do you have the certificate? I'm like, yeah
so I had to unravel my certificate from my pants pocket and then put it up on the uh, you know,
Glass window like i'm
Hunter like, you know like robert denaro in the beginning of midnight run. I'm like boom. Look at those check marks
stable body got up in the air listened to the commands, you know, and and he looked at he
genuinely
looked at it
Examined it and approved it and then said okay, you've been validated. I've seen your thing
$25 and it was still
$25 with a validation like and that's the thing that I feel like back in the day
Universal when you could get validated they would give you a reasonable parking rate now
25 bucks is the most reasonable you're gonna get we did have the for I did dm you and say hey, so it's after six
general parking's 10
valet in theory will partially validate but we had a weird
We had a weird experience with our pal jason. Walter. I'm looking here and I believe our problem was
You would have gotten free parking if it was two and a half hours
Okay, so because it was probably two hours 40 minutes
Okay you which
Yeah, this all there should be this is a farce you were a great
You're a grown man showing another grown man a certificate up against a window that I'm flying
They only give it to you they only
Allow you to show your diploma on the first time flight. Did you hear what he said there?
He's like they only will they only will
Validate that first time if but meanwhile, it's more expensive than most restaurants
It's a $50 ticket to fly like why are we not validating this like and also?
What are you penalizing the students of the school, which I can only imagine are like in the dozens
Like you know, it's not like you're not like it's not like thousands of people are using this loophole of like I'm a
I fly students. Yeah, these indoor skydivers think they don't they're so entitled
They think they don't have to pay $45 for parking every time and I will say
You know and I saw that I could have parked in general parking
I could have even parked it for free because I'm an annual passport holder at Universal
But I have such an issue with their parking structure
I was like by the time I park in that thing and then walk to wherever ever you guys are
It's gonna like eat up another 15 minutes or something
You don't know what garage they'll send you to
I mean we're gonna cover this look where if you like what just happened if you want to hear more about all this
We're going to be litigating all of this in the finale
We haven't given away the full list, but the finale of all this
We're gonna go out in a glorious blaze of a ton of discussion of this nature
And we have got I here I'll start teasing it now and say I don't want to just this to be fruitless complaint
I want Universal to hear this discussion and I want these policies to change
As much as I want our street names in Margaritam
I agree
Here's what I think I'm gonna give it out to like take it into your episode
I believe that annual passport people should have the preferred parking
I feel like that should be up on the thing
Yes
At the park you're already spending X hundred
What does that cost them?
Yeah, what does that cost you and then I also believe that if you are an annual passport member
You should get a discount on valet a discount 10 percent 5 percent
Okay, yeah
Give me something because that that annual passport did really help us at iFly
Yeah
Just bringing it down bringing down the price from like 217 to 190
They really worked with us. They were great
Yeah
Yes, but this but the parking Gestapo at Universal is will is non-negotiable
I feel like it would be ridiculous to say annual pass holders should get something special at Disneyland
Because there are so many I feel like the annual pass holder for Universal is a much much smaller
You would think right?
I also think that the general I don't know your read if you tell people you're going up to city watch
I don't know if people are like really or if he'll make funny you've lived in LA for a while
It's a kind of a joke to think that City Walk Universal is actually like a vital vibrant part of LA
And I think a lot of the reason why people stay away from it up there is that parking situation is so terrible
I think they must start bending these rules and then yes and letting you like if you're parking on the right
If you're going to a restaurant on the right side get to park in the right side this thing where you have no choice
It's also I mean look there's so many big ticket items there if I'm gonna go see an IMAX you gotta go
I like that I like that IMAX
That's our movie
Yeah, that's where I hit it up all the spots so it's like I feel like let's just work out a better validation plan here
Let's see now is it still handing you cash? Grubby cash dirty money
Yeah, I think that we could not that I'm under the illusion that so many people listen to this
But I think by virtue of that we're the only people talking about this issue on any platform
I feel like we could affect change in real change and we're not negative. We're not naysayers
This is a water cannon shot over the bow of Universal
You know this is this is it yeah and also while we're at it
Look, I know we're not in a time that's appropriate for this
But uh if we're making changes at Universal we gotta bring back that Bill and Ted show I know
Oh boy
That's a whole other thing
It's something that I am conflicted about in many ways but I think you could bring it back and curb some of the overtly misogynistic and racist elements
I would say curb it entirely
This is a bizarre conflatings at the whip
The idea that vice has attacked us so now we can't do our homophobic show
We love that the pop culture characters are all meeting each other and dancing to Gangnam Style
Absolutely let's just be a little more socially sensitive
And this idea that like oh so I know everything's off limits now PC
No just don't be a jerk to these people otherwise do whatever you want
You just write something that's not so fucking base and I will say it got more and more base every year
And I think that that's competing with Nots Very Farms which has another show very similar
That's very like pushing the boundaries
When I first saw that Bill and Ted Excellent Adventure it was much more pop culture stupid like Kung Fu Panda eating
Like Kung Fu Panda eating, Panda Kitchen and then farting and all those seats shook
And I'm like that's a level of humor I'd like to see
You just want to see the Ready Player One do the backpack dance
Well you know there's this at UCB there's been a show that our friends Brad and Nick do that is the Bill and Ted show
Well I think that we might have started that because many years ago we did it for a special comedy bang bang
The Christmas comedy bang bangs
And we did it like for three or four years straight and we would call in all these dumb favors
And have Jonaham dressed as his mad man character Don Draper
And we would put like Brett Gellman and I would play Bill and Ted and we did like
Oh I didn't know all this
Yeah me and Scott Ackerman would write the scripts with Gellman too
And it was like a 15 page script and we would do it before the Christmas comedy bang bang
We did it for like three years
Gotcha wow wow
And it was really a challenge to write the stupidest thing you could possibly write
Which but also but like this other show and probably what you guys did
I imagine there were moments where like sometimes you're doing a snark version of it
But sometimes it is just a genuine
Like doing those kinds of jokes in a genuine fashion are pretty fun
We tried to write the show that we actually thought they would make
And not comment on the show that they were doing
And when and the grand like payoff would be to go see it and then see if we got close
And I remember one year we got very close to like three or four jokes and it felt really awesome
It would depend on what you were doing at a manager
But what if Universal Studios reached out and said we want you and Brett Gellman or whoever to actually do it this year
And you would hire the writers but you would have to do all the shows
Or a month and a half
Do a residency, a Universal Studios residency in the park
Take over in a genuine, in a hard comedy fashion
One night only, like Hollywood Bowl, like Willy Wonka, I'm in
Or you can have your script in front of you
I'm not going to give you a good show, I'm going to memorize it
Mild dancing, mild choreography
I'll rehearse, I'm just not going to commit to the seven shows a night for like a month and a half
I feel like, yeah I would do the seven shows in one night
Or two nights, I would do a weekend at Universal, residency as a small residency
Well maybe this is, 14 shows in two days
They should do that in exchange for an overhaul of the parking system
Oh yeah, if you, yes, look what you get
You get Paul Scheer as Bill, or I don't know who you were
I was, yeah I was always Keanu Reeves' character
Oh okay, wonderful
Yeah so it was a great, and look now they're coming back now too
So there's a chance for them to come back
This would be the time, how exciting, feel like when they did that Hell House show
Where like, where big comedians participated in this
Yeah, yeah
The original thing, yeah okay, so the carrot on the stick for Universal Studios
Falls in for 14 shows
And just give me a call, and I'll say one other thing as we're wrapping up here
If Margaritaville does close
I say, get a Void
Yeah, can they do that though?
I think Void is all up in Disney's stuff
So yeah, I don't think that they can
Do you want a Void alternative, because there are other companies now doing it
I mean look, put an escape room up there, put something, I think a Void would be
I mean yeah
There's IMAX VR too
I've done that, it's like home, I have home VR and it's the same
Void is way more
It's good
Yeah, but by the way, you know, get a Universal property in there, come on, you know, do something like that
Yeah, there's a lot of games
Kung Fu Panda
Kung Fu Panda meets Mika and
Yeah, Joe, yeah, sure, and Donny Deutsch
Well, I think on that note, Paul Scheer, you've again survived Podcast The Ride
Thank you so much
And the City Hall edition
I'm so happy to be back
Oh yes, well, thanks for spending your evening with us in this multi-destination
It was a real highlight, it was a real highlight to travel with you guys, to fly with you guys
Hey, brothers in flight
Yeah, we rocked out, we went to an island and we went up in the air, man
It was a wild ride, bro
Really did it, and oh look, the stone, the stone is descending
The stone is coming, we have done it again
It's in the shape of, oh it's Jason and he's indoor skydiving but not in a tube
He's inside a Wetzel's pretzel cup
And he's spinning around and there's pepperonis almost like air dancing around him
And somehow that Jason looks even worse than I feel
Than the Jason I'm looking at right now
Wow, well add it to the collection and you know, Paul, you also by the way, this idea was really announced and born when you were here
I know, I feel very honored that it's come full circle, you know, from Pleasure Island to City Walk
I really feel like I'm carving out a place for myself
If you ever want to talk about a ride, feel free
No, I only want to do around like, part Jason
So if there is a, if there is a
Do you want us to, we could do the Knott's gift shop where they just sell the jams and stuff
Oh yeah, I mean I'm down for that, I'm down for, you know, any of those boardwalks
Oh yeah, sure, yeah, yeah
Shop attraction adjacent to theme park
Yeah, where you get close enough but not in it
Yeah, no actual vehicle can move
If there's a sunglass hut nearby, I'm there
Lightly themed, but not too much
Thank you again
Well, see you in Sector 13
If I live
If Jason is still alive
Okay, Jason's really not doing well
Goodnight
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog Production
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook