Forever...
Dog!
When your town has let you down
When your port has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll
A place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight, tonight
There's no way of knowing
Jason Sheridan
Hi, I'm here too
Yes, and we're joined by a returning guest who is here
I think in one of our most well-received episodes
He was talking about one of the craziest things we've talked about, Hard Rock Park
And now back to talk about an area of City Walk much less interesting than that
Jason Walliner
Thanks for having me back, guys. I'm very excited to be a part of this series
Very happy to have you back
And I realized before doing this that this is your
I mean, we ended up splitting that other episode in two
So this technically is your third episode
Which makes you the top running guest of the show
You really are, I would say, the Alec Baldwin of Podcast The Rock
True insult
What do you mean?
You're good enough to be one of us
You could be one of the podcast
And if you had gone down a different path, you could have been one of those
One of the not ready for podcast players
As Scott said earlier to us before we all met up, you were in the three timers club
Am I the whole three timers club?
You are the three timers club
So stretch out, enjoy it while you got her
And Jason, you just had a baby recently
That's correct
That sounded like you were setting up for a Byron Allen comics unleashed moment
I am so officially setting myself up for a Byron Allen comics unleashed moment
So we wanted to get you a baby
Oh my god, that's so nice of you
And I think it will become apparent what it is when you take that rubber band off
It's a scroll, I'm taking the rubber band
Off, and I'm unfurling it, oh my god
It is a legit map of Hard Rock Park
This is an original opening
This is incredible
Definitely framing it and putting it in my child's room
We were hoping it would go in the nursery
So your child can see that they too can accomplish great things
I'll tell him as soon as he can talk, just every day, that one day I'll take him to Hard Rock Park
And just describe it as this wondrous place
You and me, bud
And then one day I'll tell him the truth, or I'll just play him the episode
I'll send him the link one day, we won't be speaking probably at that point
Forget him on a plane to Myrtle Beach
Yeah, I love the map, there's actually a picture of that guy from the banana splits and an arrow
These are all the hits, the life in the fast lane
Let's just do that episode again
It is an actively cumbersome piece of paper
Imagine carrying this around in 100 degrees with humidity
That's how they would just hand that out at the park
That's the park map, yeah that's the map
Because you would think it would be more like the Disneyland map
Which is just a tiny little tourist camp
It's very big
But there is, yeah, there's the bare metal families here
Winston the punk rock dog is represented
Oh man, you haven't listened to the episode guys
Go stop right now, go back and listen
There's over three hours of it
If you joined us for City Walk
I'm sick of these people who came only to listen to the City Walk series
We have a whole show, guys
Don't ignore the rest of podcasts
There's actually something we didn't cover in the episode in here
There's actually a lot
But one of them, I think we had a good hour on the hideous statues throughout the park
And the one with the, well we could have guessed this
The one with the cow with a rockabilly hairdo and all these udders
It was like really unsettling
Shoot at you and razz you
That found's name is Rock Cow Billy
Oh wow
That is such a leap
I feel like I time traveled to five months ago
We're just, we're in a temporal loop
That's a bigger leap than the roadies of the roadies stunt show
Who do get very hurt in that YouTube video
The guy leaves, that's right, he stumbles away
I have bare metal family on my phone
On occasion I will just play it
Cause I'll rip it off of
Yeah I don't know, I mean I'm not gonna play it now
We don't have to
We have to get through this
These sectors
We have to get through
The four of the most boring things
So this is only sector three
Are you gonna release this third?
Are you releasing the sectors in order?
Yes, this is only three
So we're like bright and bushy tailed right now
We don't know where this is gonna go
We don't know how tired we'll get
This might be the start of kind of a decline
Because you know sometimes we end up with guests and I say
So why'd you pick this topic?
And I feel like I know your answer on this one
Which is that others were chosen
This I, yeah I didn't find out
I didn't find out about this until too late
And I emailed you and you told me all the good ones had been taken
Was there one you would have wanted given anything?
Oh, no probably not, I don't know
What's been the best one?
What's been the most fruitful sector?
This is only the third
We don't know
Right now it's mostly crepe
So far crepes and water coffins
Do you have like if somebody were to have said like
Said like a month or two ago
Favorite city walk place
Do you have one that comes to mind?
I guess bubble gums but just like
I don't know
Yeah, I don't know
What's city walk? I've done the indoor skydiving
I've been to Margaritaville a bunch lately
Us too
Congratulations
I haven't gone to the Churrasqueria
Have I gone there?
It is crazy
I always forget that there was a full Brazilian steakhouse
Oh, that's right, yeah
Is there still a Bucat de Bepo there?
Oh yeah, there sure is
We walked by there tonight
We did a full pass even though we didn't make you stay at your sector
No, we got to walk around a little bit
You took the full tour
Anything you now
That you passed by that you wish was in your sector
No, I don't think so
I wasn't coveting any sectors
When we were walking around
I don't know, it's all city walk
This is inaccurate
This is what anyone's opinion of this would be
But you know, there's some fun stuff in this one
I guess
Do we just go in list order?
Well, let's throw it to the sector keeper
Oh, that's right
That's who will decide
We take you now to our friend the sector keeper
Boys, today's sector is sector 3
Universal Studio Store
Ludo Bird
Francesca's
Sublime Gifts and Finds
Good luck, boys
Thank you
Well, I guess we should do it in the order that he suggested
Which is I think in backwards order of interest
So let's start with the most interesting one
The Universal Studio Store
Which is the basic
I think it's cool that there's something
Like the world of Disney
At downtown Disney
There's a store that gives you some of the universal experience
And where you can go buy the merchandise
Without having to
What's the marriage metaphor
And get the milk for free
Without having to get the milk for free
Uh huh
I messed that up
So do you think a lot of people will just go there instead of the theme park?
I definitely think that, yes
And they go back to their hometowns
And they impress their friends
And this was just
I stopped in a store for a second
While doing all the rides
And just hoping to death that the lie's going okay
And they don't look cheap
How many people that are tourists just go to City Walk?
That's like
That's the weirdest thing about that
Studio store
I know it's the downtown Disney as well
Like they have the world of Disney store
But wouldn't you think every tourist
Goes to the theme park, not just to City Walk?
The locals are probably
Buying less merch
That would be a guess
I would think the only people going up there just to buy
Merch at the studio store
Who are locals are like heading for the Harry Potter stuff
Like if you got a kid
Or a family member
Or a nephew, something like that
And you know they're really into Harry Potter
You know, because half that store is Harry Potter stuff now
And that part looks pretty nice
Yeah, they redid that
They redid this whole store not too long ago
I will say, I don't think anyone
Was buying anything while we were in there
And we were in there
It was a pretty busy time at City Walk
But I felt like no one was really
I would say in all the stores we went in
The cashier was making long eye contact with me
Because she didn't have anything to do
All the different cashiers were not very busy
This studio store is also like
Spitting distance from
The studio store as you're exiting
The park, so if people are buying
Like, that was a great day, I want to get a souvenir
They may have already done it
Like, you know, 20 feet ago
Yeah
But I mean obviously
It's there, we don't know
The analytics, there must be some analytics
That show that this is a good idea
That people buy things here
Like giant donuts
I was eyeing the giant donuts
Big Simpsons looking donuts
Baked fresh daily
That kind of looks fake
Because they're so big
Grotesque mutant donut
That has been like, I don't know
Mutated at the power plant
But they bake them fresh
And then they just sit in a
Shelf in a box in a room temperature
To be bought by no one
Yeah, they are not
I'm supposing that they are bought, they are not bought
Yeah, and when you say bake them fresh
Is that, do you think they probably make them there on site?
Like a Disney type thing?
That's what the sign said, yeah
It says baked fresh daily
There's a full backstage like bakery and confectionary
To support the theme park
I would think there has to be
And you dream of it each night
I mean
Lying at the end of the conveyor belt
I guess I'm skeptical because Disney is so
Transparent with their bakery
There are people you can watch as your
Like candy cane is made or your fudge
And like with the universal
We don't get to see fudge being made
Right? Am I wrong?
Is there a live fudge
Display at universal anywhere?
I don't think being made
No
Maybe if you're lucky you get to see it
Being loaded into the case
You get to see a tray being loaded into the case
If you're lucky you get to see the fudge being loaded into the tray
A truck from Laverne, California
Unloading crates of fudge
That's close enough for you
I declared this to be the most interesting one
Are we out already?
We're still getting our sea legs in this series
Well here's an interesting thing
So the one end
The end furthest into city walk
That used to be
The things from another world
Which we'll talk about in a much later sector
The comic store
Used to be
A pretty normal
A pretty cramped comic store
And they
Had a good amount
Of comics in there
For such a tiny space
But then when universal was looking to expand
The studio store it was right next to it
So they cordially
They were like
We'll move you down to a different space
How did you know it was cordially
I feel like that was what
There was a story about
Or like we're moving
You know they seem excited
They seem excited about it
Okay, but you're speculating on the cordialness
But the sign was like we're willingly moving
Don't worry
We're moving down the block
No to our customers, we were not forced out
A very polite conversation happened
And we loved what's happening
Not gunpoint
Um
You know we caught you
I feel like I heard there was something
We got you
It's fine, we're happy about it
We get more space
So there used to be no studio store there
There was a studio store but it would stop before
They expanded over
To the comic store area
Is that what is now Harry Potter
No the other end
So we were looking at the world's best bod
And like world's greatest ad
That was like the comic store
Okay, so that's all right
Fake awards, a good amount of like
Bart Simpson
Drink receptacles
A bunch of minion heads
Um
There's like slippers that you
Potentially put your foot into Homer's mouth
That's nice
There's a wall
There's one
One high end section is about half
Back to the future memorabilia
Yes
There's a signed Mr. Fusion
Signed by all of the cast
And the creatives
Five grand, is that how much it was?
Five thousand dollars?
Above that is a signed
Leah Thompson photo
With a little photo of her
Nowadays
Looking unhappy holding
The photo that you're buying
That little photo was in the
Certificate of Authenticity
I learned this at some point
In California if you want to sell
Something that's autographed you have to have
Some sort of certificate of authenticity
But what
Any criteria for a certificate
Because can that just be forged
Just as easily as anything else?
I guess so, I feel like there's some sort of way
You have to go about it
Is taking a photo of the person with the autograph
Like the poor man's certificate of authenticity
You know like poor man's copyright
Where you have to like mail it to yourself
Just like just take a picture of the person with it
And they're giving it a thumbs up
Any piece of memorabilia as long as you have a photo of
Leah Thompson holding it with a scowl
Was that a cry for help?
Was that like when like kidnappers
Make someone take a picture holding
That day's news
She was holding the hill valley
Leah Thompson trying to send us a message
Yeah she's been kidnapped
She's in the back area
At Universal that they
The sign just says fudgery on it
But there is no fudge being made back there
Just a table and a trapped
Leah Thompson
Let's get her out, save Leah
Well there's a head of that transformer
That you told me about
Well there's a bumblebee head
But I was more interested in the
Character specific to the ride, Evac
Which is the evacuation vehicle
That everyone is in that's trying to get out
And he's trying to avoid all of the
Evil Decepticons
You're in Evac
So I was telling you guys that you're in
Evac and I guess for some reason
Nobody knew what I was talking about
Because you're in a blue car
You're not in Evac
No that's it
Are you in his back?
Or you're in his car body?
His head is above your head
Well it's kind of in the engine right?
Wherever the heads go
There's no head, you're in a blue car
But it's in the front
You do hear his voice a lot
I never even
Thought we were in that guy though
Well you hear a lot of voices
In the ride so it could be
Right I didn't know we were part of a guy
You hear an open roof
But then at the end
Remember at the end, this belongs of course
In a full length Transformer episode
At the end when you decide
That no we're going to be the heroes
We're not going to just, he says I'm sick of running
Right? Is that something like that?
And he punches the All Spark
I'm not running anymore and then we kind of
Go closer to whatever the evil
Guy's name is
Megatron, thank you
Do you remember this part, the fist comes out of
The EVAC vehicle and he gets a
Real solid punch
On the screen or like physical? On the screen
Yeah so like your car runs up to him
But then the car sprouts an arm
And it just shoves this arm into the
Chest with the All Spark in it
Oh yes yeah yeah yeah
So that's EVAC's arm, so that's the head
You never get to see EVAC fully
So no one's, you think a single person's bought that head?
No I don't
I don't think anyone's bought EVAC's head
I just liked seeing it there
Do you think they have a way to ring it up if you want to buy it?
Yeah I'll take the EVAC
Oh I don't even know, we lent
Our ladder, we lent our
Step ladder to the other store
I don't even know how to get it
Does anyone, who has the keys?
I feel like we never got that key
This is unshatterable glass also
There's no way back there, there's nothing we can do
I don't want the audience to send me
Gifts, but
I would happily accept EVAC's
Giant head
I would be so happy
Inconvenient amount of money
Someone is just going to send you
A head
Is this what you meant?
This is
When I was, I was up there
A while back when this was, when we were beginning
This series
Not realizing we would all be touring it together
I wanted to make sure I covered the studio
Store, if I didn't get the chance later
And I was in that little
It's this little hallway
And one side is a mirror and the other side is this display case
With the nice stuff, like the head of EVAC
And there was a big ET there
And I was just standing there taking pictures
And then this group of guys came up
Which my natural inclination is
Oh no, young people
They're going to bother me, they're probably
They found something to pick on me for already
Instead, these guys started roasting
Everything in the case, and it was
A delight, watching them do it
They were saying, you know
One of them said to the other
Where they pointed at ET and said, that's what you look like naked
And then they
Started talking to me
And they asked me
They just pointed at ET and EVAC
Without naming either of them
And they said, who would you be more
Upset if you went on a Tinder date
And it ended up being one of them
Who would you be more upset about
And I said
I'd be more upset about EVAC
Because he's big
And his dick might be
Like an exhaust pipe or something
And he might crush me or blow steam at me
And they instead
And they said
You'd be mad if you got catfished by
This guy
And then they'd veered away from me
Because one of the guys thought
Of a joke, he pointed at the Mr. Fusion
And he said, what's that, a new slap chop?
And
Teens are so good
At roasting
And that was so
Funny that all three of them
Went running around the store
Sprinting around the store
Saying, oh shit, oh shit
Watching these guys
They were having such a blast
It was three guys ripping on theme park stuff
It was like this alternate
Universe version of us who, I don't know
I'm sorry to say, might have been funnier
They were
For sure funnier
I thought about what's that, a new slap chop
Done since then
So whoever you guys were
You gave me a lot of laughs
And thanks for not being mean to me
Like I still assume anyone younger
Than me is going to be
That's a really nice story
Yeah, yeah
So good memories
There, I was to any good awards
Anyone noticed, there's those weird
Off-brand Oscars
I took a picture of, let me see
Oh, I just took a picture of one
That's, you know, it's like, it's best mom
And best dad, best girlfriend
And best body, that was funny
Best dog sitter
Was one of them
But then very miserably
On the bottom shelf
Bottom is best me
So you, the person who goes to
Universal
Doesn't want to pay the price to get into the store
Or get into the theme park rather
Just goes to the store
And then wants something to remember
Is non-tripped Universal
Buys himself
A best me, looks in the mirror
This, this, I mean
Universal in general
Kind of has to
Because it's like, Hollywood
Baby, you know, California
Los Angeles, like
When you're in Orlando
In Universal or Disney, there's not a lot of racks of like
Orlando!
Crap, you know
Because people are coming from all over the
World, all over America
And, you know, they want to
They inevitably will buy
Some, like, Los Angeles
Postcards, or Hollywood postcards
So they keep a lot more of that, I feel like
Than other parks
Yeah, but the thing that I really love in any of these
Hollywood sections, and this is true of
The Studio Store, it's true in Hollywood Boulevard, it's true of
Any movie theme park
The off-brand Oscars
Is a really fun thing, because the Oscars
Are really specific about their
Their golden man holding
The sword, and the way that, the exact way
That's framed, so the off-brand
Ones where it's like, well he's holding his arms
The other way, and he's holding
A big star, or
Like, or a film reel
Or, like
Or, you know, or his chest
Is like two tattoos of cameras
Or, like
Yes, we wouldn't want to dishonor
The dignity of the Oscars
The Academy Awards
But I, maybe that's a business to get into
Is designing
Rearranged
Oscar statues
What if it's just like a tiny evac painted gold
That's the ultimate gift
That's for Universal, that should be, that's what they really should do for
Universal, they should have their characters in gold
With these different things, so like
ET in gold, and it would say
Best friend
Or something
Or like Ricky Ricardo
Best band leader
Norman Bates
Everyone's favorite Universal Studios
Character
Best clerk
Best hotel operator
Cindy Lou
Least crazy guy
Like a golden
Like a golden, like buff man
But then just the head is Woody
Woodpecker's head
And he's best mischief maker
Fallon
Best host
The people who pretend to be from New York
Who yell at you on the street when you walk by
Best
Best working class couple
I walked by that
Today, because I went in there for a few minutes
And like no one
Maybe you guys have covered this already, no one pays
Attention to them
And like it looks like they might just
Live there, and the deal is they have to
Be mic'd
And like just sit at the window
They weren't even like doing New York accents
Anymore, I thought
They were real New York, you know, point, anyway
When we were
When we were there, weren't they doing a bit with Beetlejuice?
Yeah, I think they were yelling at Beetlejuice
And they were like, hey Beetlejuice, what are you doing?
And then like he'd have
Be like, ah, I'm just on the street here, and then the woman
Would be like, no, I won't
I won't go out on a date with you, Beetlejuice
And then he's like, ah, come on
Come on, and they're doing a bit, and then you're saying
No one's paying attention. I saw people taking pictures
With a Beetlejuice today, who
Knows who Beetlejuice is anymore
He's like
One of the top five of universal characters
What do people think he is?
Like, a weird guy?
Just a ghost, a crazy clown
The walker-lion
He's it, they think he's it
That is like, do you think
People know Lucy better?
Because there's still a Lucy walk-around character
Lucy versus Beetlejuice? Still on TV
Yeah, that's true
Beetlejuice, you gotta be a cinephile to know about
That's a good point
Some random kid
There's a rumor about a new Beetlejuice movie every year though
That's one of those
The AV Club, I think if you
Added up all the AV Club articles over the years
15% of them are about a
Beetlejuice reboot that I'll never have
We're Bill and Ted 3
10% are about Bill and Ted 3
Big wave
25% is every time
Arrested Development might come back
These
Stories power the blogosphere
It's what it's all
Hanging off of
It's important
Best blogger
That's good
Best pod mass
Assembler
Best
We should be nice to them, shouldn't we?
They haven't written about the show yet
Write about the show, cowards
If you want your gold instead
If you don't want a best coward statue
include us in pod mass
That'll do it
Best coward
That's the most restraint I've exercised
Doing the social media for the show
is not just tweeting after a few months
at AV Club
Go, cowards
Hey Vulture
Split sire, Vulture comedy
Whatever you're calling yourself, you're in the clear
You've mentioned us a few times
We want that 50 listener
boost
You all give us
The best boost
That's enough of that, let's move on to
Luda Bird
A restaurant that you
guys both ate at
and I had in the past
What did you think?
Let's talk about the experience of it
Because we were at the
counter for what felt like
25 minutes waiting for
someone to come
We were there right at dinner time, right as the parks
like, gliding out for the day
The kid who was working there, and I say kid because
he was a child
He seemed like he was 16
There was fear in his eyes
Did you notice this?
I felt so bad for him
because he was running and doing 10 different jobs
I think he had braces
I think there was a whole thing going on
There was also 3 people back in the kitchen
I don't know what they were doing
And he was working so hard
So it's not his fault, it's the management
at Ludo Bird
or whatever the hell it's called
So you blame Ludo
Put the fryer, put down
the serving plate at
Petit Choua
Choua Mac
Papa Monti Universal, full of chefs
He's spending most of his time at City Walk
Right?
He's gotta keep an eye on that one
Not making TV shows, which they were playing clips of
The many Netflix shows
he's made guest appearances on
Who is it? Who's the guy?
It's this very famous foodie chef
Ludo
who has some
really good restaurants in LA
but also had this truck serving this
chicken and then made it into
a few franchise-y places
that are pretty mediocre
not great
not something you would say
like, oh, you have
I remember someone telling me about
the chicken truck years ago
Oh yeah, it's the best fried chicken
You would never say that about
Ludo Bird and City Walk
It might be one of the best
quick service
options
up at City Walk
I think in terms of chicken
I would hunt out in LA, it's been laughed by
Dave's and
Hell and Rays, the hot chicken places
If we're gonna talk about hot chicken, let's get going on it
because we have had hot chicken fever for over a year now
The wait here
wasn't quite as long as a Hell and Rays
but it
was different because there was no one online
The excitement level was a little bit lower
There's no music playing
There's no fun employees
They do the fun
weight part
to build the anticipation
That also happened when I went to
Menchies, which I know is a different
sector, but I went to Menchies
Don't anger the sector, Keech and Jason
I'm just saying
I finished making my little thing
and I realized
is there a cashier
in this establishment?
Oh yeah, I never saw one
They turned out to be standing right next
to me, and that was why, but they weren't
behind the counter, I think they were cleaning up
You thought about running out with it
I mean, I was also thinking about
just doing a free sample
down the line, but it was a little crowded
You did the sample
and then you did the main
I did the sample and I liked what I had, so I just got it
Black cherry
Tart, black cherry, very good
Simple one flavor?
No idea, twist with original Tart
and then I put a lot of chocolate and peanut butter stuff on it
Best?
We're not allowed to talk about this though
Saludo
You guys both had sandwiches
How were your sandwiches? I had a spicy chicken sandwich
The ingredients
were good tasting, like the sauce
is good, and there's like a pickled
onion and stuff, the chicken was definitely
very cold
and I think it had been
sitting around a while because they had
told you that they didn't have
Well yeah, so I ordered a grilled chicken
and I gave him my credit card
He said I'll be right back
and he disappeared for five minutes
and I forgot that I had a
sign or anything, so I was just like I'll let him go
whatever, and then he very quietly
and she officially came up to the table and was like
Oh I need you to sign this, could you please sign this?
And I was like, oh yeah, sure
of course, and then I'm sorry, I forgot, no that's okay
So then he took the thing back
and then he quietly came up as if
he was a director giving me a note
or something, like he didn't want to embarrass me in front of
him, we were out of the grilled chicken sandwich
would
something else be okay? And I was like yeah
and give me anything, spicy
chicken, and I was like sure, yeah okay
And then he basically had it in his hand
and then he just handed it to me
and yes, it was like
again, the ingredients were good, but it was
pretty cold
the chicken itself was pretty cold, which I've
eaten at Ludo before and
this was by far the coldest
I've had at Ludo
It was definitely cold
And again, not this kid's fault
No, no, no
Ludo's cold chicken
Ludo's coldest chicken
You're tired of the odd chicken, Chris
We had a honey, we had a honey drenched
Which was good
We went here after
the, we did it out of order
sorry sector keeper, but I
got it, we got it after the
water coffins and
that made me
sick, this wasn't good
Yeah, this isn't a good
restaurant, or whatever is going on
they need, it's
I feel like a lot of restaurants are kind of like
sort of, what's
the, not, like bait and run
that's probably not it, but like they're
started, there's a grand opening, the guy
checks everything, alright, it looks
perfect, and he never comes
again, it's just stressed out teenagers
you never get it right, and it's not
their fault, because they aren't equipped to do so
like once you're past the opening
ceremony, it places like City Walk, nobody
ever checks in again, that's I think City Walk
you can franchise yourself out
and if it's
bad, it doesn't matter
it, you know
it's like making a TV show now, no one
sees it, it just goes
out into the ether
and you never hear about it again, who knows
how would I even look that up
no way to tell anymore
look, this is a thousand factors
that's what the teenager
would tell me about the chicken
no, this used to be
Jody Moroni Sausage Kingdom
one of the finest names
of an establishment I have
ever heard, I think I ate there once
or twice, and founded a very serviceable
sausage establishment
I liked it
I've never actually, I never had the pleasure
of eating at Jody Moroni's
I've never traveled to the kingdom
you
well, you know, you served at the pleasure
of the king
King Moroni
did you have to say my liege after you ordered my liege
it's a very cordial
pot tucker
my napkin
my napkin and my plastic
fork and my tray
to serve
Jody Moroni
there's a kind of a trend
and Jody Moroni's was part of this
I think, because this was originally
just a single restaurant
in Venice Beach, it was a Venice Beach favorite
in City Walk I think some of the idea of it
was to kind of
borrow or co-opt
you might say, LA
favorites, I think there's been a history
of that, things that maybe there's, there has not
been a second location of and they do
now it's become a place that co-ops
Portland favorites
with, I mean
Buddha Donuts is an example of that, many monster
but they did it with, there was a Tommy's
I forget if there still is one, Pink's
Gladstones, which got
replaced by Bubba Gumps, but yeah
it's kind of this like, City Walk's
like the man
like snatching up
indie bands and signing them
but then not letting them do their thing
yeah, stifling their creativity
yeah, the sausage king
the real sausage kingdom
was, they've been crazy hot dog ideas
everyone
not everyone ate there
but everyone who did started a band
started a sausage
a sausage king restaurant
so, yeah alright, that's not
good either, let's keep going
Francesca
come on, center three, I have literally
not a note about Francesca's
which one was?
Francesca's the one we went in first or second
it's really just like clothing
and it's like a little bit of
kind of, gifty nonsense
you see, Francesca started back in 1999
when we opened our first
boutique in Houston, Texas
and filled it with a winsome collection
of hand picked merchandise
women everywhere instantly fell
in love with us, so that we now
have over 700
boutiques in 48 states
across the country
and counting, and then we also
launched our online boutique
francescas.com, so you can shop
serve or play, whatever it strikes
your fancy, that's right from the Francesca's
website
did they become a sponsor?
did you, something I didn't read
it enough, it's something, it was maybe
Asian owned
it's just like an importer company
that does cute stuff
I mean, I know they have
carefully curated clothing
bright baubles, bold accessories, and playful
gifts, well you don't know that, you're just
no, he's doing it, he's doing it
all off the top of his head
he's not reading that
I mean, it was
a lot of knickknacks, it was a lot
of knickknacks, and one side
of clothing, I don't want to get ahead of
ourselves, but I spotted
some bath treats that were very
similar to the nectar bath
treats that will be coming up in a future sector
they were, you know, they were
like food shaped bath treats
bath bombs and soaps
and was not, not the first
appearance in this sector
of food based
treats, because that comes up in sublime
gifts as well, there was a lot of
oh sorry, oh no no no, go for it
I was just saying, there is a crossover with this and
sublime gifts of a lot of
stuff like a glass of
wine that says binge watching and
boozing are my favorite
stuff like that, or for a man
a beer cozy that says
this guy needs a beer
and then there is a little purse
that I, I don't know if it's
for an avocado
that you put in like a little purse
but it says time for avacardio
which I don't, is that
that means eating an avocado?
Like instead of
exercising, like the mouth workout you get from
eating an avocado, which is not like a
not strenuous, not strenuous and also
not like a crazy snack
indulgence, you'd be like
time for my cake sur-size or something
that would make more sense
and then one that we found that just a little
shot glass with a picture
of a cactus that says
feeling fan cactus
is one of the worst
versions of those kind of things
I found, I bought
an item from the store
which I don't need to unwrap on the air
because I know what it is, but I'd like to
see it again. The audience wants to feel though
you unwrapping. Yeah yeah, listen to that
binaural, binaural presentation
if you wouldn't mind. Yeah, do you feel like you're in great
moments with Mr. Lincoln?
So I bought a shot glass
that says, that has
a bird on it and it says
McCaw me maybe
and that's something I
oh now, I like it
I'm a Carly Rae Jepson fan
so I'm excited to have this
and the back of, wait I
oh yeah, on my patio I have a
sign that I bought in San Diego
that's something about like
two cans for the price
of one, I forget. So this
will go along with that, I'll drink
I'll stare at that two can
sign while I drink from this McCaw
shot glass and
I'll be very satisfied with my life
Lot of
crossover too in both stores
lot of unicorn
stuff. What have you declared the
year of the unicorn? Is that
There was a unicorn display at Ralph's
over here in Burbank, like the unicorn
everyone is doing it
Really? Yeah, I don't know why but it is
Starbucks is going on drinks
You know I like those drinks though
I haven't had one yet but it's
But you will, you know you will
Blue and purple. What do they call it?
Unicorn tears? Unicorn frappe or something
Unicorn tears
Or am I thinking of liberal
tears? You might be thinking of the new
Pixar Pier Bing Bong's candy shop because
you can eat Bing Bong's tears
What do they look like?
It's not open yet
But they are hyping the tears
The candy tears
I found a book in this
store called Book of Questions
And it says, I don't know if you guys
saw this, it says spark fun conversations
and get to know friends and family
better. So there are
maybe ten
pages in this book
And on each page there
is one question
And I will just read a couple of them
What's the best compliment you've ever been given?
I will read
a second one
What would your answer be for that one?
You know what? Good point. Let's all do this
Oh shit
Let's all do the Book of Questions. Jason, thank you so much for that suggestion
I think that
I think that podcast arrived
We could get to know each other even better
And Book of Questions
So Jason Sheridan, I would like you
to go first. What's the best compliment
you've ever been given?
I don't know
You know what? I'll say this. Anytime
someone says
that I was funny
or I did something funny, it
always means a lot
That's nice. Scott, what do you think?
You don't have to be funny. We can just say
serious things
This isn't the best one
ever, but it was
a big honor when I
performed at my high school
talent show and I won
the category of best miscellaneous
I consider that an award
compliment
I sang Kiss from a Rose
and it was
a lot of fun and I'm glad
to have been recognized but kept separate
from the rest of the singers
Jason?
I have nothing
I have blacked out any
compliment I've received in my life
Hey, nice
Lacoste shoes
That's the nicest thing anyone's ever said to me
Sweet! That's my best compliment
What about when someone
told you great imposter
syndrome?
Mike? I'm trying to think
and also could I
keep our compliments more at the front of
our brains? It'll help us get through
the times that we're getting very few
compliments or three star
reviews. Don't you feel disgusting if someone
compliments you?
It's so shameful
Yeah
You gotta land somewhere between
You can't like swat it down
hard because that
embarrasses the other person. There's no gracious way
to take a compliment
It's cruel to compliment someone
You think so?
If you're like
oh thanks it was nothing
then you hear yourself being
falsely humble. Even if you're not being
false about it, it's like
I sound like I'm being falsely
modest
You don't want to acknowledge if someone
said what you just did was very funny or
very good, you're like hell yeah it is
but you don't want to do that because that seems like you're crazy
but also if you were doing something
that you put together or you did a performance
you thought it was good or you wouldn't have done it
but you have to meet it in the middle
you have two conflicting things at once that are happening in your brain
Yeah and I've done the thing
where if someone compliments a thing
that you don't really
think is good that you were involved with
then yeah to say that to them is like
to be like you're an idiot. Why would you like that?
You're like oh yeah
that wasn't very good, yeah that didn't come out very good
but thanks. I had a lot of problems
It makes me happy if somebody compliments
something I did that I know that I had
trouble with at any point
and I think I like to tell people that
I'm like oh good I'm glad it worked out
Yes I do that too because there was this moment
where it was not good and I'd know what it
could have been. But don't you still think they're lying?
They're the person giving the call?
I'm suspicious but I don't always
think for sure. That's nice
You know what the line
this is the exact line for
me about anything I've made or an episode
of the podcast. If anyone
can name one specific
from the thing
I know that they watched it and they thought
oh you know what I should say is that I liked that
if they just say they liked the thing I think they're
then they're lying. Yeah that's true
or the thing
they did like it but it sort of
failed on some level because nothing
actually broke through. But if
I get a compliment on a line
a dialogue in something
that's a good hack moving forward
when you're complimenting someone next
I'm gonna do it right now to Jason
Milder because I just
a few days ago for the first
time watched All That Jazz and
I had a much bigger appreciation of the
finale of Eagle Heart of the
last season of Eagle Heart
having watched that. That's the nicest
compliment I've ever gotten. Thank you
even not that you appreciated
that you remember
it and acknowledge that
it was a thing that existed. I thought it was very funny
at the time and I kind of
had a vague notion I was like
oh I know All That Jazz
like I know this ID
but I didn't really remember it that well but sitting
down and watching the movie from start to finish
I was like oh now I like. It's such a good movie
no that's true anytime like anytime I have
something like that like I yeah I'm
proud of that and if someone
liked it I feel close to them
and want to talk to them for longer than
they probably want to talk to me.
Oh so it opens floodgates. Yeah
yeah yeah. No that's very nice Jason.
It was interesting to watch a legitimate
compliment exchange happen and see how you
responded to it and I think you did
well with the compliment. You know what it was actually moving to me
so I take back everything
I said before I don't think you're an
idiot for liking something that I did.
Oh god it's great.
It's also just balancing out my karma for
drunkenly accosting
you at a party nine years
ago or something when I first moved to LA. Wait when?
Which party? Was that a Funny or Die party?
Yeah. Were we together and you were like
I want to know how much I'm judging so long there.
Jason told me he was going to go
attack you. Did we know each other already?
No I mean I had only been in
the city like a year and a half. Can I remember
that? You were perfect
nice. No it was a lovely conversation. We
mostly talked about the best show. Oh
okay yeah. I remember that
that's crazy. I wasn't
I didn't see that conversation. Wait which party was it?
It was that Funny or Die party at that
what's that Sinus face
that got off of.
They must
have broken fire codes.
Oh my god. There was far too many people.
That was yeah.
Stressful. But you had a nice moment
within what is sort of a crazy
stressful party. I
took these pictures of this stupid book
thinking oh we're just going to
goof on this book. This
stupid fucking book. We're going to
oh four guys are just going to rip it up
laugh it up at this stupid
shit.
This is what we're working in the entertainment
industry does. It just destroys your mind.
You're like fucking compliments.
The nicest moment that's
ever been on the podcast. It is because I was walking
through all these stores like
both being and trying not to be like
alright what's my take to make fun
of in these fucking places. It's like
wait what are we doing? No that's like
genuinely nice. This book is good.
You should have bought the book.
It's $60.
Now let's talk about what do you meme
an adult party game for meme lovers.
That was also on sale
in this store.
Which is the exact thing funnier die did. Like
making captions for meme photos
they did funnier die the game
and you could buy that at Target.
Well honestly the worst thing about memes is that you cannot
hold them on cards in your hand
at a party with your
adult friends and talk about how much
you love memes. Do you guys do
board games with
people? I have a lot of trouble with
that. Mike has looked over at
me because he knows I despise them.
Okay.
I like
Trivial Pursuit.
I like that. I like Trivia games.
I like that or I like the version
of Celebrity where like you write names
down and toss them in a hat.
But then usually that it's like
alright now round two you can only say
three words and then round three you have
to act out the celebrity. You like get
very like worked up when
people suggest a game too. Like you get
like stressed out ahead of time. Like it feels like
you had bad game experiences as
you. I know my family would play them and
we all had a nice time. So what's the problem?
I think I like
talking more.
I think I just force myself
to become a talker at some
point. So you're with people
you like. You want to have a free
really good position. You don't want to be put in a box.
That's exactly it. Sure. Yeah.
I think I feel that bummer at
things where like okay now let's get down
to the task at hand.
But there doesn't have to be a task at hand.
Let's just hang.
I'm honestly more okay with them like
one of those board game cafes
because you kind of know that's what you're
going for and that's what you're getting in. Those
feel weird to me.
I've only been like
once or twice. That's too much of a show.
It's a lot. Let's go in public and
do this. Seems weird to me. But at
least then you know the context you're walking
into. I see. I understand what you're saying. Yeah. Maybe you should try
playing the $400 Harry Potter
chess set that they have at the Universal
Studio store that we were at tonight.
You might turn your right.
It was in a cage too.
Oh I didn't see that. Was it
the characters or was it? It's
like very ornate looking.
It was in a cage. I thought a woman
guarding it but I think she was also selling wands.
There's one woman's job which is to
guard this Harry Potter chess set.
It's not even that expensive. No.
It's less than the
Leah Thompson head or whatever you
call it. It was not a Leah Thompson head.
It was a picture. I don't remember.
So when the Transformers ride you're in Leah Thompson.
That's what you're driving
around. And then in Back to the
Future, the old Back to the Future ride,
you would constantly be looking at
a picture of Evac that would be
dissolving. Disappearing. Yeah. Disappearing.
George McFly is spying on Evac while
changing clothes in
his window. In ten
years when Back to the Future has been
remade and there are still ten more
Transformer movies and they cross over
because entertainment is a full
wasteland that will probably
happen. I mean, but that's going to be great
because Logan Paul's going to be Marty
and Jake Paul's going to be his
young father.
Are these, is this, are
these like all ready to go as soon as Zemeckis
croaks and like
next week?
We've talked about this. Yeah, we think he's
day one as soon as
he's gone. I think Gale and Zemeckis have to be
in the ground. Dead. No, no, not dead. Not in the ground.
Oh, I think Gale.
Just not breathing for ten minutes.
Have you guys seen the guy who did the video
about Back to the Future movies
predicting 9-11? No.
Just look it up. It's the best
thing. It is
fully convincing. Do you have an example
of one way that it did? No, just look it up.
Watch it on YouTube. It's one of, that's the
only thing I'll plug.
It was made, I think the guy, it was the last
video he posted was three years ago.
It is like the best edited, most beautiful
thing. It's not a crazy
person. It's someone who's like very smart.
Whoa.
It's something about like a
bigger thing of like
looking at reality in a different way.
He's not like a crazy guy who actually
thinks this, I think, but it's
a real good watch. Whoa.
Alright. Check it out. Best video.
Yeah. And then he also
starts with this disclaimer with Tiny Type that's like
I just want to say I think Robert Zemeckis
is a great man. I don't think he knew about 9-11.
Decided to do nothing.
Whoa.
Sounds like you do think that to propose.
It's worth watching. Whoa.
Alright.
Well, you're not going to find any merch for that video
at the studio store.
So do we have anything else in Francesca's?
Do we? Well, was it, was the
thing you just said from Francesca's or from
Sublime Gifts and Finds?
I think yours was from Francesca's,
right? That's the
compliment book. You're not going to be able to
compliment the store.
It was, yeah, that was the second one we went
in. Do we never get to Sublime? They're
the same store. No, we went into Sublime.
That's where all the signs were. So we went to both
but have we talked about them both? No, no.
I haven't talked about Sublime.
Alright, go for it. So, Sublime
Gifts and Finds, you know
this is the sort of, kind of
like, kitschy, it's
sort of kitschy, but then
it has like the illusions of like
a little more upscale
sort of gift shop sort of to
it. I mean, they have like
those Swell water bottles,
those airtight water bottles that are very popular
right now. They had some
patty wax candles, which is like
a higher end brand of candle.
And
this is the only, the sort of
thing that can only exist in high traffic
areas or else you're
bringing in Marcus Lobotus and he's
going to redo it because
it's like, who
else is buying this stuff besides
like foot traffic, impulse
buys. Well, speaking of, in
the store, speaking of, we
found
casery phone cases from
a recent episode of The Prophet
and with no need to explain anymore
what that means. Y'all know casery.
There was a really good episode
of the show that was a cliffhanger where
these kind of turdy guys
were, no, it was one turdy guy
and two non-turds
and they were all struggling to
make expensive cell phone cases
together. And then there's a schism
in the episode, but I don't want to spoil
it. But it was, yeah, once I realized
we were looking at honest to God casery,
I feel like we got to play to
this. We've gotten enough compliments,
the nice comps,
some of the nicest compliments I've ever received
about when we talk about The Prophet.
So I feel like we have to. Yeah. So the
casery's still going strong,
but we know there's more to this story.
There was a
rack of casery cases
in like a right, kind of
in the center of the store for sale.
For thirty dollars?
For a cell phone case? Thirty dollars.
Why would this ever be? Great margins.
They said they paid like a dollar
a case wholesale.
The margins on that are insane.
That's, The Prophet in general
really opens your eyes to whenever you
think that something costs
too much money. It's always, what do you charge
for that? Sixty. What does it cost you to make?
Forty-five cents.
I mean, that's this entire store.
That was this entire store.
It's a lot of, a lot of
wooden sign. I wrote down some of
them.
Some of my favorites.
This is
another thing that's kind of popular right
now, and it's a little befuddling to me,
is the, is Mermaids? Cause there was
like a bunch of, like,
bikinis? No, sorry.
Kind of pissed about not being a
mermaid. That was a sign.
Mermaids don't lose sleep
over the opinions of shrimp.
That is a play on lions don't
lose sleep over the opinions of
sheep. What? But about mermaids.
You never heard that saying? I don't think so.
It's like an aggro, like,
dude saying.
You can find it a lot of different, like, Instagram
photos.
It's about not losing sleep
over dudes. About
not losing, so like, the one I've
seen, the phrase I
forget where, what this is traced back to
it's lions don't lose sleep
over the opinions of sheep. Oh, but the
mermaid thing flips it. The mermaid flips it.
So like, mermaids don't lose sleep over
the opinions of shrimp.
I'd say both are true.
Yeah. Both are true.
Nature. Both are true.
No coffee, no workie.
That was surprising to see.
That is definitely a play
on no, what is it?
No tiki, no laundry, which is not
acceptable. This is a thing you would
see still at any point.
At any farm, probably.
They have like, or maybe
not anymore, but up until two recently.
I bet we can find one down there.
There's a Chinese laundry there, and I think
there's a sign. In Old West Town?
Yeah. I think it says no tiki, no laundry.
Are you guys going to do that on this show? We're doing everything
on this show. We did not.
There's one big episode. I remember.
But you gotta do Ghost Town a lot.
That's gonna be there. Oh my god.
Yeah, we have to do the whole show thing.
We're gonna go back and redo everything
in far, far more incremental
steps now that we know our real pace.
I think you should do an episode on the Calico mine.
Right. 100%.
Yeah, yeah. Now we'll start
breaking them into pieces.
This wine is making me awesome.
You're the flip to my flop.
You're a little more awesome. This one is the biggest
leap that I saw. Bikinis?
Oh, hell no. I thought you said
martinis.
Well, that's just a misunderstanding.
Yeah.
In sign form.
There's a bunch of keychains,
and they have very similar
things, like phrases and saying
pretending to be a mature adult
is exhausting, which isn't even clever.
It's just sort of a sentence. But the company
that makes these keychains is
snarkcity.com.
And I went to
snarkcity.com into the sales
section, and they have a bunch of mousepads.
And they have
primary business you should be in.
They have one that says, nope, not today.
And then they have, let me
check my give a shit-o-meter.
Nope, nothing.
Which I think they should have caught the nope,
nothing. No, I think they should have added
to it and be like, nope, nothing.
Turns out I don't give a shit.
I mean, it's already
a little crammed on here.
It didn't even go up 20%
of the way to give some of
a shit. Here's what all the way at the
bottom. Here's a mousepad.
Pull yourself together. You've
got bitches to battle and men to
destroy.
On a mousepad. On a mousepad.
These are poorly
graphic designed, too.
I feel like I could picture this person coming
into their office and swapping
out the default mousepad
and saying, oh, I don't want to deal with them.
I hope that's for a woman to
own. I hope.
Yeah, so much.
Wow, he sold a
crate to the proud
boys of Orange County.
The sale's a sale.
We could do an episode on snarkcity.com
but that's just a taste. That's another one
William. It's crammed with signs.
They have a lot of that store
sublime. Are those black
woodblock signs with like the
white text that
I don't, does anyone know what
their name is? I think it's all made by one company.
And I know
there's an, I rented an
office and it's kind of owned
by a lunatic and in the bathroom is one
of these signs and
it just says, like,
replacing the toilet paper won't cause
brain damage.
So every time I like use the bathroom
I have to like just be bummed out.
But like it's like this very aggro sign.
And so these have gotten, and it's
the same company definitely. And
the signs get so
over, like, so they're giant
some of them. And one of them is
like, live your life. Take chances.
Be crazy. Don't wait because right
now it's the oldest you've ever been and the youngest
you'll ever be again.
And that's the one with the least amount
of text. And this one
was on the wall.
And I was saying
some of these feel like, you know, on the
on an iPhone, if you
just, if you have predictive text on it, you
just tap the word to randomly
assemble like a paragraph that sounds like
human speech but isn't.
Marry your best friend.
I did not say that lightly. Really truly
find the strongest, happiest friendship in the person
you fall in love with. Someone who speaks highly
of you. Someone you can laugh with. The kind of
laughs that make your belly ache and your nose snort.
Your iris and your urn is healing. Kind of laughs.
Wit is important. Life is too short. Not to love someone
who lets you be a fool with them.
Make sure they are somebody who lets you cry to despair
will come. Find someone that
you want to be there with you through these times.
Most importantly, marry the one that makes passion, love
and madness combine and course through you.
A love that will never dilute even when the waters
get deep and dark. That's a sign.
That's so much to put on your wall.
Whatever just happened to an
Irish grandmother lives here.
Something
simple and nice. All of these signs
sound like they are being bought
by someone who says the phrase
Hey, I'm not done talking to you yet.
A lot of it.
People are walking away. Hey, where are you going?
Hey, I'm not done with you
yet. Think you are too good for me?
Yeah, each one should end with
Hey, where are you going? I'm not done with you yet.
This place is like a grandma Spencer's
gifts. Like it's got
some bawdy stuff but it's a lot of
signs and signs that are supposed
to show you what you're at. It's like
this is who I am. Read the sign.
There's a lot going on because there's also
like a full wall of jewelry
cases. Yeah. Like
affordable jewelry.
But I don't have any bearing on what jewelry is.
There's the dad Annex
2. That's the one little
bookcase.
John Wayne's guide to grilling and then
the rest of it is like shitting related.
I took a picture. There was all these like
man soaps and I took a
picture just because this one had such a crazy
name. What was it called?
Oh yeah, it's a bar of soap
enabled navel supremacy.
We just
sold a crate of 200
into the brown boys and orange.
Dude Cannon Sublico.
The one next to it says
productivity wins the day.
And then
the one behind it is old Milwaukee
big ass beer soap.
Oh, that's right up
a dad's alley.
That's the Spencer's Gifts is what I'm saying. There's elements of Spencer's
Gifts, but it's a lot of
stuff. A lot of that. A lot of phone
chargers that might spark on you
and
those cords that will fray
very easily in your car. A lot of Kierkerland sort of
like we were looking at the pen that's also a
ruler and a level and
you know, an eraser or whatever.
A lot of like gadgets
and gizmos. The specter of
cleverness has haunted this
particular retail zone because what this
was for many years and very strongly
in my memory of being younger and wandering
around CityWalk was that it was an art
gallery called Martin
Lawrence Gallery. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, if you remember that. Very
strangely and obviously
easy thing to comment on that
Martin Lawrence. Am I going to find
a painting of Shanae-Nae in there?
But not in, no, in
fact, I
found a quote from some review
of what it might have been and
the straight up quote
I think the literal art was
fun, such as a cow
standing on snow cleverly
named Cold Cream.
Clever?
Is it? I don't know what that
means exactly. Oh, because a cow makes cream.
Snow is cold.
So you got cold cream.
So these new places. Famous phrase, cold cream.
Of grain the cow. Yeah,
it's like a popsicle stick joke.
But the answer isn't something you've heard of.
Is it someone who thinks that
ice cream is called cold cream?
Shhhhhh!
Can I see the dessert, man?
What kind of cold cream you got?
It's a regional thing.
Yeah, it's a regional thing.
You guys want some cold cream?
It's like when the
Simpsons where the Flanders have ice
milk.
Yeah, flavorless, please.
Quite similar. The other one is
a Scottish terrier being
lifted up named Beam Me
Up Scotty.
Oh, that's pretty good.
But as opposed to these being like
knickknacks you could buy for $30,
I think these are paintings that cost like $2,000.
This is where
Tony Soprano commissioned that painting
of Pile by the Horse.
I'm not watching
The Sopranos, so I'm out on that
one. It's pretty much all I watch anymore.
Also, you could apparently
buy Warhols at this gallery.
Really? Yeah, you could go
to City Walk and get a rain
stick and like a giant
pencil that or a
giant toothbrush from the Giant Store
and an Andy Warhol painting.
Is the Giant Store still around?
No, that was an early... and I don't even remember
what sector that was in. That one's lost
to the... I don't know. If you know the name of the Giant
Store, please let us know.
And I have another request too, which is
some of these things that we read,
these poems that are on these signs.
I would like to see those little
like affirmations written
on top of photos of Jason.
I think that would be
a blast to see.
And those would come and they would feel like
the best compliments you've ever asked.
Love my picture with
badass bitch.
Battle some bitches today,
Jason. I would like
a picture, if we're asking more things,
I've asked so far on this podcast for
a $400 head of
the EVAC, the Transformers character.
But I'd also like
a cartoon of Jason asking for
some cold cream, please.
And probably like maybe tugging on
like his mommy's apron when he's like a child.
Like Nanny from Up at Babies.
And she... her pattern
to
acknowledge the original painting,
the apron is cowhide.
And that
keeps it in black and white so you don't have to add color
to this painting that
you're going to do at home necessarily. So that's
your assignment, black and white.
Within two to three weeks, please.
And head of EVAC.
Is that it? Do we make...
Oh, also one of these used to be a sunglass hut where you walked through
giant sunglasses to get in the store.
Oh, that's nice.
That would have been a fun homage
to that. We don't
have... we've been talking forever and ever, but I did
think that maybe one final thing to put in
this sector, why don't we annex
the universal globe,
the spinning globe itself
that's
facing the...
If you're watching Extra
where Mario Lopez broadcasts
every day, you come to LA, you can
be in the background. And the background
is the studio store.
So that's why I think it's in this
sector. Do you
know what time they film that every day?
I was looking it up. I was wondering if I could
get onto Extra.
You can.
If I could have done that on the slide
today and then surprise you with my appearance
on Extra. But I think you have to like, wait.
And then it's not just like you're standing
back there. I think you're like corralled by
like an Extras guy. So...
But I don't know. We could...
You want to go to... Why don't we make
other people do it? We keep commanding people.
Go to Extra, hold up a
sign, says podcast a ride.
We're busy. We can't go. We should get like a Stern
Show type thing. Like a Baba Booy.
Or like a real like a trademark that people
can go interrupt shots from
like a new local news or
get in the background of entertainment
tonight or whatever. Scream hashtag
Jason for DLR. Jason for
DLR. Yeah.
Cold Cream.
You know what? I kind of like to see on some
signs. I mean, we're taking other people's material
here. But what's that? A new slap
shot?
Throw that on the sign. Hold it up from
the back. Yeah. Any of your favorite references
and we'll see what stick. Yeah.
We don't want to create a Baba Booy.
But I mean,
we don't want to force one is what I'm saying.
Yeah. Yeah. It has to happen organically.
Yeah. I did watch that Dolan Brothers
clip that you sent.
The Vine Stars were interviewed
at. So that's just one of many great moments
that happened on Extra. Well, I actually
didn't watch it. It was... Oh, really?
Mari Lopez asked...
There are these twins that
started on Vine. They went to YouTube.
I guess they... Oh, cool. They made the leap.
There was a controversy
because, like, they were,
I guess, protegees of the Paul brothers.
But then kind of had a falling out.
But then... Did they get dissed in a rap?
Oh, I don't know. Mari
Lopez was like, what's
the difference between you
guys? Because they're identical twins.
He's like, what's
different about you?
What kind of defines you guys?
And they're both like, we pretty much have
the same personality.
Nothing, nothing, really.
But I did think
of
for when they die,
my eulogy
will be for them,
which is the
Dolan Brothers didn't die.
They simply became YouTube videos.
Like in Westworld.
Westworld.
Let's see, I didn't get that.
I don't get Sopranos and I don't get
Westworld.
I like it a lot, though.
Too busy getting caught up on the Dolan Brothers.
Watch the first ten hours of Westworld
and that will make sense.
Skip season two.
Well, you should print that out, put it on a
big board of piece of chalk
and give it to the Dolan Brothers when they die.
Alright.
I'll hold that sign up when they die.
At the Universal Globe.
To honor them, hold it up in the background of Extra,
which was once their domain.
That's very nice.
Well, I think with that...
Oh, the Sector Stone is appearing.
Oh yeah, it does.
Hold on, hold on.
There's a teen is telling us that
this Sector Stone is not actually ready.
They don't have it anymore.
Really?
So we're gonna have to get a replacement stone.
Oh no.
Here it comes, here's the replacement stone.
Oh, I see it. Hey, what's that? A new Slap Chop?
The stone is in the shape of a Slap Chop.
The stone is in the shape of a
of a Mr. Fusion, but it's a new Slap Chop.
And it's got
black text on it and it says
people who live at Glass Houses
should shut the fuck up.
Is that us? Who's that?
I don't know, it's for Blacksing.
All the songs are for Blacksing.
Oh yeah, the stones have been around forever.
Alright, well, Jason Warner,
you survived Podcast Thrive again.
It's such a pleasure. Thank you so much.
Do you have any projects
or any man-shops of
popular films and
major tragedies you'd like to plug?
Yeah, just check out
that Back to the Future video.
It's a good video.
Alright, check us out tomorrow
for Sector 4.
You'll see what it is.
Yeah, you'll know. Bye.
Bye bye.
Forever!
Dog!
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Bohm,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows
on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest
Forever Dog news by following us
on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam
and liking our page on Facebook.