Forever...
Dog.
When your town has let you down
When your port has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll
A place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and bill of bond
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight, tonight
I forgot what we were doing. We say, well, hello, welcome to Podcast The Ride
and then say the City Walk Saga and then were we saying...
Yeah, we were saying just the sector number.
But we don't say what it is because we're going to get that from the sector keeper when he announces.
Okay, that's how we do it.
Hi, my name is Mike Carlson. You're listening to this amazing series.
We have gone a little mad from City Walk Madness, which I guess is a disease you could possibly contract.
I don't think I fully have it. Jason Sheridan, do you have it?
City Walk Madness?
You know, been up there a lot recently. Some trips are better than others, you know?
Yes, I know what you're saying.
Just like one day at a time, one trip at a time.
Also, joining us, Scott Gairdner, how's your madness level as far as City Walk?
Well, I think on a scale of one to ten, I think it goes up with every episode.
So we're at nine right now. And on a scale of one to ten, it'll be at 19 by episode 19.
I felt ebbs and flows like going up there. Some days I'm just like having a ball.
And then some days it's like kind of a real chore because maybe I have something to do in an hour and a half.
And I feel very rushed. And then you can really feel maybe what people say when they say they don't like City Walk, which by the way, I'm not saying I still love City Walk.
One of the things that happened that factors into this episode made me say out loud, maybe I don't like City Walk.
What?
Yeah.
This is only a sector nine. We're only in the ninth.
Yeah. But we just had it. It was just a big meal fail. It was just undeniably.
And I'm not even sure it was City Walk's fault entirely, but I don't know. I'll get into it.
There's a whole... I would say I was taking somebody from out of town around and I don't think I or the walk put either of our best feet forward.
OK.
I get that.
Let's throw it to the keeper.
Oh, yes. To see what of the fine establishments are in sector nine.
Let's go to the board.
Boys, boys, today's sector is sector nine. Dong Po Kitchen, Skechers, Locker Room by Lids, and Voodoo Donuts. Good luck, boys.
OK, so we're dealing with Dong Po Kitchen, Skechers, Locker Room by Lids, which is not just the Lids store.
Not just Lids. Has led to some confusion in our text message chain, I think.
Yes.
Or confusion on my part and worrying that everyone else was confused.
And I feel like it's probably actually never been confusing to anyone that went to City Walk because no one cares about those places.
That is true.
No one goes to get a hat at City Walk.
If we didn't say any more about this, we would have already spoken about it more than anyone else.
People who work there.
And Voodoo Donuts. Last but certainly not least, what I may call the jewel of this sector.
Interesting.
Yeah, this sector.
We should do one where we could just also make these up.
People don't have... we could be like, oh, the shoe factory is in sector nine.
And people would be like, oh, oh, I remember that. Yeah, that's that shoe store called the shoe factory.
Nerf Zone.
Yeah, OK. So this obviously is the all Nerf store.
Yeah.
And it's the basic Nerf bats and guns.
Right.
But you know, you could buy a wedding cake made of Nerf.
And then I would be like, you know, the Nerf stores theming isn't so great.
I think that they should really like do something a little bit more fun and theme park style.
Like, how about like a giant Nerf gun or something that's like sitting outside or like at least a giant yellow Nerf ball that like kids could like roll around in the store.
And then people would be listening to this.
I'm exasperated by all of it.
Yes.
Jason would be like, I like it.
And did you know that they have like Nerf ball treats?
That would be basically how it works.
And they make cops that look like the yellow Nerf balls.
Oh, my God. That would be great.
That would be fun.
By the way, this is a great idea. Is there a Nerf store anywhere?
I don't think so.
I don't think there is.
And how did that not happen in the 90s when Nerf is operating at peak Nerfdom?
CityWalk is peak 90s.
There should be like a super soaker store in the 90s, too.
There should be just full super soakers, different kinds, small, large.
You would have seen Michael Jackson and Macaulay Culkin hanging out there every day of the week.
Super soaker store Macaulay.
And crowds of adults just going, oh, I don't know.
No, people, everything was fine in the 90s.
They were like, we love these two entertainers.
That's what they were thinking.
We were unconcerned by any of this.
Yes, it was the 90s.
I did see a picture from it could have been the 90s.
Maybe it was the early 2000s of the Skechers store was there, but like very close to it was also a Vans store.
Do you remember this, Scott?
Oh, into the same district?
Yeah.
Which is crazy to me because that feels like a similar, similar, but not exactly the same, I guess.
Very similar, yes.
But Vans, I think, would be competing more with Elements or Billabong sort of thing.
I see what you're saying, but I mean, they're both primarily known for shoes.
For shoes.
Let's bag that out real quick.
So Skechers.
I learned that Skechers is the, OK, what is this qualifier?
The third largest athletic footwear brand in the United States after Nike, which includes Air Jordan and Adidas.
That is kind of crazy to me.
I didn't realize Skechers was that popular.
Really?
I mean, I kind of do.
Do you have the full list of shoe company popularity?
No, I don't.
What kind of theme park journalist are you?
If you don't know the top 10 shoe companies, Jason, get the fuck out of here.
I mean, here's the, I went to the Skechers Wikipedia page.
I followed one of the links.
It had an article, which followed to an article about the top athletic footwear brands in America.
Doing the click through, I feel like is already further than most podcasters and certainly me a lot of times go.
Oh, sure.
So I'm impressed by that.
So let me not, let me actually give you journalistic credence.
I mean, I do have half of a journalism degree that I then converted to a television degree.
Hold on a second here, Jason.
I'm on a story that's from it's from success story.com and I looked up 10 most popular shoe brands and I think this is something very different.
But does it say athletic?
Hmm. Does it say no?
You know what? You're right.
It just says popular because we're looking at number six here is a Berluti, which is like a fancy dress shoe is number six on this list.
Yeah, I don't know.
Seven Johnson, of course, Johnston and Murphy shoes is number eight.
Where's Bruno Mali? The is not the name of the OJ's shoes where he said during the trial.
I wouldn't I wouldn't wear no ugly shoes like that.
Hmm. Or am I quoting something from a sketch?
I don't even know.
I don't know either.
OJ actually one of his first spots when when he was found not guilty was at the Nerf store.
Got to celebrate. I love Nerf. Naive. Funny. Right. Yeah. It's funny because I am not guilty.
Anyway, sorry to derail.
So, Sketchers, I walked through the Sketchers store.
The other I thought maybe like, oh, I know they had those ones that like the shape up Sketchers shape ups.
And I thought that was their thing.
And I thought like, oh, they're they're less expensive.
I didn't find them any less because everything was between like 50 and 70 dollars.
I feel expensive. Yeah.
And also the other thing about Sketchers, that logo is on everything.
And it's real big and it's not practically aesthetically pleasing to me, at least.
Yeah. And lack of the T is pretty irritating.
I hate the lack of a T. I was just thinking that that bothers me so much.
It should be called Sketchers, Sketchers or something.
It's weird. I don't know. I didn't even. I'm sure there's a reason for it.
I was just on autopilot and I wrote Sketchers in the notes a couple of times.
Did you use the T? I did use the T. I wasn't even thinking about that.
Wow. Gives you something else to dislike.
The other thing, in 2012, they settled a multimillion dollar lawsuit that they had misled consumers with those shape up ads.
Oh, interesting. 40 million dollars, it says here. Yeah. Whoa.
Wow. But they survived, you know. They survived.
They survived. And they of course have their beloved gang of Burger King Kids Club-esque characters, the Sketchers kids.
You, I'm sure, when you went through the store, made a real note of the gang who, you know,
I'm looking at a photo and there's like, there's the boy side.
There's like kind of a rockabilly guy with sideburns and a robot with a light up yellow face and then like a reboot,
like the 90s CGI character reboot and kind of a Deadpool ripoff ninja man and a Green Goblin ripoff man.
And then somebody, my wife, described as a courier who's just like running in a hat with an S on it.
And that's the boy side. And then there's a bunch of girls too.
There's kind of a Hannah Montana, Pink Hair, pop star and a masked girl.
It's all really strange because they aren't labeled and none of the shoes tell you who the characters are.
And you can't find it online either.
No reference to there's no Sketcher Kidopedia.
That sucks.
It's also weird because there's a photo of all these characters and you can't see any of their shoes.
They exist only to sell shoes and I don't know what shoes they are wearing.
There's one especially with just like about 1% of a flap of a shoe. Like why cut it off there?
Yeah, it's weird because you would think they would want to make the shoes very visible.
So, you know, a kid would go in and go like, I want to be like the Deadpool Sketcher kid and I want to wear whatever shoes he's got on.
No, they really. Yeah, they they've like fucked up by not just giving these kids names.
That's all you need to do because we would for free list them all.
Yes, they had right now.
I just listed vaguely what the characters look like.
We'd give them an ad for free on the show because we'd be so excited.
Yes, they have.
That would extend this part of the segment like 10 minutes if there were names for all these kids.
Yeah, they don't have to have any personality. They don't have to have any backstory.
We would fill it in, but they fucked up because we're about to end.
I'm assuming unless we have a ton more sketchers stuff like I don't really.
Well, I just think again, I'll say it's very odd to see that logo stamped on like because they also sell like casual shit like leather shoes,
kind of stuff you might wear with a more casual suit or business casual.
But then that fucking sketchers logo is stamped in the leather on the side.
It's so jarring to me. You're reminded of the poor spelling at all times.
Yeah. I have one final thing about the Sketchers store, which is there.
There is a gumball machine.
And if you work at the Sketchers store and you're listening on the back, closest to the back of the store on the left side,
there is some chewed up gum deposit on the back of the gumball machine.
So just maybe take care of that if you're a GM listening to this, you know, to get an employee on it.
But just do be aware there is some built up gum.
That's gross. Well, yeah, please. They're listening and they will probably rectify that quickly.
I don't want to get anyone fired over this. Just trying to be helpful.
So locker room by Lids. So Lids is hats.
Yeah. And locker room by Lids is everything else sports apparel related and also some hats and a lot of hats and all.
Yeah. More hats. It's just that locker room, which I guess like they were thinking like
they didn't want it to be foot locker because obviously it doesn't make sense.
Not just shoes, but like locker room suggests sports, I guess. Yeah.
But Haggis had asked this. Well, and it's a lot of jerseys and that's what's in the locker rooms. Right.
So it is an applicable name. Why didn't they just I think that there's some hubris here or some ego involved with this company
because why does it have to say by Lids? Does anyone care? I think that's a branding thing. Right.
But you know, I mean, there's so many different companies that are owned by by the same one big company
and they don't necessarily feel they need to brand it everywhere.
It feels like the Lids thing is confusing. Why didn't they just call jerseys? Yeah.
Just call it jerseys, Lids and jerseys. And people are going to be like, well, I trust the Lids brand so much
that I'll go to see what they have as far as jerseys are concerned.
This is a thing on our beloved The Prophet.
There's a lot there's been a number of cases where he kind of combines stores and then it's such and such by such.
Oh, so he likes that. Yeah. And I know that's the thing I disagree with him on.
That's a fashion label gimmick. Sure. Apparel thing.
Yeah. Yeah. He doesn't like the idea that the name of the brand is the same as the name of the store.
Actually, what you're describing with Skechers, he would like a, you know, high steppers by Skechers.
Yeah. Great idea of a shoe name. That's interesting.
I'm looking here. Lids is owned by Hat World Inc. Well, now hold on.
I don't know why there's not a Hat World establishment because that has me. That is my interest.
I mean, certainly Hat World is a better name than Lids.
Yeah. I think Lids is cool, but Hat World is so much better.
And like that's a more exciting title. Hat World is the best level on Super Mario Odyssey, right?
Let's see. There might be a Hat World's actually. Hold on. Yeah.
Do they call it that in Japan or Dubai or something? Maybe. Do they loosen the brand?
The Lids Sports Group operating within Hat World Inc comprises the Lids retail headwear store,
the Lids locker room specialty fan retail chain, the Lids clubhouse retail store,
and its internet business, www.lids.com and www.lids.ca.
You hear that and you think, oh, we don't have real jobs.
There's probably 200 people who day to day have to make sure that all of these brand names are intact and presented correctly.
Yeah. What a dull world.
Yeah. So what's interesting is that it seems like Lids is pretty self-contained.
They're not owned by some giant conglomerate.
Well, I feel like people always want sports apparel. People always want jerseys and hats and stuff.
I thought it was interesting that they had so much variety in locker room by Lids.
Certainly as soon as you walked in the door, very thoughtful.
A lot of World Cup jerseys. Sure. World Cup also playing directly on the giant big screen outside of the movie theater.
Yeah. It's your source for sports. It is. Yeah, exactly.
Maybe I'm wrong. They are owned by, this is so confusing.
They are owned by Genesco, which owns Johnston and Murphy shoewear.
Something called Deerstags.
Journeys, Journeys Kids, Underground by Journeys.
Schoetraske and She by Journeys retail of footwear for young women 20 to 35 years of age.
And they own the tender care centers at the border that the children are being insured in.
Jesus, probably. That is what happens to these horrible companies.
There is also before locker room by Lids, if you can imagine such a time, there was a store in there for a long time called Sports Avenue,
which is similarly silly to Hats World.
A thing that I liked about Sports Avenue is that there was a big shack on the outside because it must have opened when Shaq was on the Lakers,
but they did not have access to the Lakers rights. So Shaq was dunking in a red jersey, which he I don't believe ever wore in his skirlies.
He was magic in Lakers. I wouldn't be the guy to tell you, but I don't, certainly at the time he wasn't wearing red.
And I think in his jersey just said like All-Star, Team Jump.
It was like his watered down of branding as it could be the pride the L.A.
fans felt when they saw Shaq and his famous red and brown team jump.
Just represent Team Jump. Team Jump. Great, great brand names in this zone.
What a what an area. You know what I haven't said about just to backtrack what I forgot to say at the beginning is that with Sector 9,
we are moving into the CityWalk expansion zone. This whole everything passed to the Hard Rock Cafe and starting with
Skechers and the food court around there is where that's what all got added in 2000 when the when the the billion dollar expansion of somehow that little Jesus Christ
row of like the wind up toy store cost a billion dollars. The rest of CityWalk leading up to that point cost three billion dollars,
which is so weird when you think about theme park numbers, isn't it supposedly California Adventure entirely cost like seven hundred million dollars?
That's really the first. Yeah, the first unfixed version.
And when it opened was, yeah, I think seven hundred, they said something like less than the like something where the most prominent thing was Sports Avenue.
Yeah, I know it was. It wasn't the redo like a billion dollars. California Adventure. Yeah, it cost two billion.
I think just Carthage Circle area, just that street, the main drag heading up to Carthage Circle and California Adventure was like a billion dollars.
It looks the same as this history. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, point of history is. Yeah. But and that's like beautiful molding recalling classic California.
And this is a bunch of fucking gaudy crap metal and, you know, like a big helmet. I just where the money go.
This is a scam. Is that also like the cost of building on top of what essentially a tiny mountain, you know, trying to run water and power?
Maybe. And is someone without a real job? I don't know. And I hope to never know. But maybe that costs more money to construct. Yeah, I'm sure.
They also threw a little money down for the inauguration of CityWalk 2.0, which I didn't know about until the other day that this was somewhere.
I don't know if it was in this sector somewhere around this zone. There was also there was a Harley Davidson store at one point. That was one of the most exciting aspects of CityWalk 2000.
So in keeping with the motorcycle spirit, they kicked things off with a motorcycle parade led by the easy rider himself, Peter Fonda.
He led some motorcycle several feet forward and then he said, are you ready to start partying?
That's also what he said on Twitter recently. I was threatening to kill Trump or something.
Something like that. But now, I mean, it was like, I'm going to run you over with a motorcycle parade. A two mile an hour motorcycle parade.
OK, so are you ready to start partying? Then quote the LA Times. That was the cue for a fireworks display and a set by Big Bad Voodoo Daddy. God bless him.
2000, a simpler time. Big Bad Voodoo Daddy who played New Year's Eve at Disneyland like two years ago. I'm pretty sure they were the primary. Yes.
Oh, boy, I feel like the age of the good band at Disneyland is a little over. You would prefer to Cherry Poppin' Daddy's perhaps?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You got something a little more high end. A Brian Setzer Orchestra, of course.
Yeah. Then Larry Kurzweil, the president of Universal Hollywood said, who better to launch the new CityWalk than Peter Fonda?
Hmm. Yeah, I guess. A currently popular star of the year 2000.
What we're offering is a totally cool entertainment experience. So having him here fit right in. Perfect. CityWalk and CityWalk 2000 and Peter Fonda, both totally cool.
Man, that's so funny. Yeah, something, huh? I'd also like to say that I believe that 2000 was when the new CityWalk logo was introduced.
And if you can picture that in your minds, I want to say just off the top of my head that that logo contains seven fonts and 65 colors all screaming at each other.
Is that the one that's currently still up there? Where the letters are all kind of on different levels?
Yeah, there's some of them are jagged and like kicking each other in the butt and there's like electricity and it's like it's on a broken TV.
It's the logo is a big I could see if you pulled up in a cab and you look at that logo outside the book at a Beppo, maybe you go, you want to just take me back?
I don't know. I'm glad they've just stuck to their guns for 18 years. That was the only logo in Orlando because Orlando was only opened in 99 the CityWalk.
Correct. I was saying a lot of Disney World feels like it's 90s. Like you go to Blizzard Beach and it's like the 90s are back.
Yeah. And it does feel like that even though this expansion opened what year? 2000.
Which I guess is very close to 90s. So like it does feel like the 90s are alive at CityWalk still. I think they're slowly trying to get rid of that feeling that vibe.
But yeah, I think big mistake. I think keep the 90s alive forever.
The dream of the 90s is alive at CityWalk to paraphrase Portlandia. Portland, the home of one of the newest additions at CityWalk. Voodoo Donuts.
Oh yeah. I wasn't sure if we were saving that for last.
Oh whatever. No we're not.
We're not. No, that's fine.
That transition was just so good. It was good.
I just jump around. You're eating a Voodoo Donut right now.
I started eating it. I don't know why I did because I was like we're recording and you're eating.
You also said you had had that kind before so I wasn't sure that you were going to finish that way.
Well you can have the rest of the other one. Oh okay.
Here let me first start out with a negative about Voodoo Donuts. And we were very excited because we found out Voodoo was coming.
Voodoo Donuts was like the hipster-y donut place in Portland and it's like you would see pictures of lines.
Down the block. People down the block and everyone was very excited about it.
And then it feels like they were just like we're cashing out. Like let's put this thing everywhere.
We're not at a cool exclusive thing anymore. We're going to be in every tourist trap.
Well have you ever seen the owners talk?
I don't think so. Because I have now and I don't think I wouldn't apply the word cool to them.
Well they are also members of Big Bad Voodoo Daddy.
So you don't call them cool. Anyway we've got to get out. We're opening this store and now we need to get on a plane to St. Louis.
I got a trumpet to tune. So we were very I remember Jason and I at this time. This has been open for how long? Two years?
I think two years. A year and a half.
I remember we were texting about it. When's the Voodoo Donuts coming?
Very excited because I had not been to Portland but the line was far too long when I was there.
I was like I cannot. We were trying to sight see and we did not want to wait for two hours.
Jason told me of something that they do in Portland and I think you know where I'm going with this.
Oh I think I do.
They do in Portland and I was very excited for this to come to CityWalk. It makes sense that it's not there but I was disappointed.
Jason the phrase I believe you used or made me aware of was bucket of misshapens.
Yes.
And what that means is that when they're making a donut and it kind of comes out weird or wonky or looks weird.
Tastes fine. Tastes fine but it's just a little irregularly shaped.
They throw in a big white plastic bucket used for like hauling utility or paint.
Like a big orange bucket from Home Depot.
Yeah. Yeah it's a giant Home Depot style bucket. They throw a bunch of misshapen donuts in there and then you can go in there and buy them for like 20 bucks.
Something like that. Like some sort of markdown rate.
Bucket of misshapens.
Yeah.
And very early on when we were going up and trying Voodoo donuts for the first time we learned that they do not have buckets of misshapens.
No. I found out about it I think either from Kelly Sudakonic or Matt Fraction her husband.
One of them posted a picture on their blog or Instagram or something of the laid out misshapens and the bucket next to it and explaining what it was.
And I when I heard it was coming here I was like well that sounds great.
Now kind of knew that like I probably won't do that for City Walk.
I know. It doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense. You can I believe buy a coffin full of donuts though for like a hundred and thirty five dollars.
But are they misshapen?
No it's just a coffin full. It's just a you get to keep the coffin.
Just fine.
Just correctly shaped donuts.
That's fun I guess but it's less fun than getting a grab bag because like I was all excited for you to go up there and get a bucket of misshapens and bring it back down and we could all like rifle through them.
I don't know that it would have made it back down brother.
When Jason's feeling low he would just head up the hill to City Walk and get a bucket of misshapens and.
Hey the usual Matt. Put it on the tab.
Jason pulls up to the bar and he just eats.
And literally when I say this bucket the bucket is like 16 inches tall.
What isn't it? It's big right?
I think it is a repurposed home depot or Lowe's bucket that you would buy if you had a job to do.
I have to say that this isn't the full Voodoo Donuts experience that we were hoping.
Yeah.
Because the bucket of misshapens is not there.
I also had some trepidation when they were coming because one very cool thing I think about LA is there is like a culture of mom and pop donut shops.
A lot of them run by immigrant families from Asia.
And there's a great story on Eater about this and about like the signature like pink box that a lot of donut shops use.
Right.
Goes back to like one of the first immigrants from Asia.
I forget when 70s maybe late 60s 70s you know there was a lot of conflict over there at the time.
And they came over they started you know someone showed them how to run a donut shop.
And then they brought a family over and they started expanding the donut shop.
And very early on they asked for a red box because that's a good luck color.
And what something messed up at the print factory and they're like oh we're sorry the order came out as pink boxes.
And they're like well we already paid for it.
We'll just take them.
And then it was such a big hit.
It kind of spread everywhere.
I'm going to take out that segment of you talking about the donuts and I'm going to play the national anthem under it.
Segment that.
Because like you're that's so much information is very interesting.
But it also sounded like you're really giving a nice like patriotic speech about America and immigrants.
And I was nice.
Yeah.
It is a cool little thing.
I learned especially in LA.
LA only last few years got like Dunkin Donuts.
Right.
There's Winchell's there's more LA specific chains.
But we also like the last few years seen like a lot of bougier donut change bougie donuts bougie ice cream.
Kettle glazed.
So like I have to give Voodoo credit because even with city walk pricing factored in it's not that much more expensive than the donut shop I walked to up the street from my house.
We thought it was a little overpriced for what we.
Yes.
Some of the bigger ones but like your standard like I had a buttermilk bar and it was about the same as like the buttermilk donut I usually get.
Now I think I don't know that it was any better.
Honestly I think it was probably a little smaller.
I feel like some of the stuff is a little smaller.
And then I know once you start putting bacon or cereal on top of stuff it's definitely like some of the more wild donuts.
Yeah.
But they are far pricier and certainly they have the Stumptown coffee which I think is OK but like priced much higher than like a Starbucks.
And only one size.
You're stuck with a giant.
Yeah.
That's what I found.
We just we had a big big four dollar thing.
Pretty tall.
Hot coffee or iced coffee.
Hot.
OK.
Fancy hot coffee.
Some roasters taste like soup to me.
Sure.
Tastes like a a a bouillon broth almost or like a thin.
I don't know.
It's kind of like a weird taste for me.
Yeah.
And I don't mind just a burnt black bad coffee.
I don't either.
In fact that's one thing I like a lot about the Dota shops in L.A.
It's kind of like a standard coffee shop cup of coffee.
Would you would you rather be buried in a giant pink donut box or a giant bucket of misshapen or the coffin or the or the Voodoo coffee.
The Voodoo coffin.
I think that pink donut box.
Now would they have to fold up your body to make it fit in the square shape or would you would would a custom long pink donut box do.
Custom I think right.
I think custom.
Hey look.
You don't want to pay for that.
I don't want to pay now that you say that.
That's going to be expensive.
Maybe just put the ashes in a pink donut box.
The ashes in the donut box is a good solution.
Here's what I think is a good solution.
You get that acid that Walter White would use in a vats to get rid of a body and you use the plastic misshapen bucket.
That's a good idea.
And they just dissolve your body in the misshapen bucket.
Right.
Because you got to use plastic you can't use ceramics.
So it would be perfect for it.
We are misshapens when we are born and we are misshapens when we die.
One one thing I do like about Voodoo and and like I said I had a buttermilk bar.
I shared Mike and I shared some of a raised glazed raised vanilla iced with Captain Crunchberries on it.
Right.
Yes.
Both very tasty.
One thing I will say about like some of these nicer more upscale donut shops it does they do taste very clean by which I mean like at some cheaper places like you can kind of taste the oil a lot or like the doughnuts can be very greasy especially they've been sitting out for the day.
Yeah it's not a consistent flavor through the whole thing sometimes.
Yeah.
I tell me if I'm wrong.
Do all the doughnuts taste a little stale because I've had I've had to play three times in the last year and a half.
Every time I feel like this feels like it's a day old.
I think I've had a lot of cake and you had a lot of raised.
I'm a raised man and where are we all at on doughnuts cake or raised.
I don't even know the difference.
I guess wait is raised like cake is like a thicker and raised is flaky.
Yeah.
Both of the ones we have here though the Captain Crunch and then the other with a Voodoo man.
Those are raised.
I'm raised then.
Yes.
Yeah.
You like cake right.
I've grown more to like cake.
I think it's more popular in Los Angeles back East where more popular Los Angeles.
I don't I don't like that.
Certainly growing up back East eight a lot of raised a lot of Dunkin Donuts are raised.
Crispy cream is all raised.
That's raised.
Yeah.
Usually pretty much everywhere offers some sort of one or two cake options.
I think that you forget what they have over there because like I went to crispy cream a couple of weeks ago and crispy cream does taste so much fresher than this.
You think so.
I think so.
Yes.
I'm more of a fan of crispy cream.
The simplicity and yeah it is like a was it more distinct taste than what I eat with the specific things I brought today from.
I think this is I think Voodoo is honestly Voodoo's Voodoo's charm is the branding the marketing and then the insanity something that's crazy which of course you know I like like cereal and like having a lot of frosting on it and it's crazy shaped or something.
But I honestly think it's on the level of Dunkin Donuts.
I don't think the donuts themselves are anything that special.
You also I don't think I don't know if I like that crazy again I watched some videos with the owners and they're talking about how like you know honestly like I shouldn't say this but what we did is we got a little baked and we walked up and down the supermarket aisles and we were like yeah I did a doughnut with Captain Crunch on it and then bang there is and that made me like I hate that.
I like this and they're like they're they wear like pants with fruit loops on them they're all bunch of it.
Hepcat kooks.
I don't I think gravy style.
Yeah.
I haven't brought up wavy gravy gravy and pig pen of the world.
I love wavy.
I'm going to give Duncan though the edge because I think I always found them very consistent. Sure and they are cheaper than Voodoo.
Yeah.
But if we're talking city walk Voodoo is probably your cheapest snack option up at City Walk pretty easy.
Well it depends I mean we're not talking talking to sugar but you can get a nice little bag of candy for three bucks.
I guess so I guess that depends on if you find candy that filling or what sort of snack you're looking for.
Of course it depends on what kind of snack you're looking for.
Yeah so yeah I would say it's on the level of Duncan I like the Voodoo doughnuts but it certainly came in came in overhyped came in hot.
No bucket of misshapens.
So I was a little let down not that I would certainly have a doughnut there again but I was a little underwhelmed by it.
They also don't have like the edgy stuff that they have in Portland like dicks and joints that stuff didn't make it to the theme park setting.
Yes there's the bodiness is not there because they don't want to offend anybody because they're not the people with the Portland sensibility can handle vulgarity I guess but the people at the City Walk they're worried about the kids maybe being offended.
We're a PG shop.
And honestly I'm fine with that because as you know we don't like too much vulgarity especially around a family entertainment.
I wonder how the I guess we'll talk about this in that sector the things from another world also important from Portland.
Oh interesting.
Yeah what else about food oh the Voodoo mascot Voodoo mascot.
Yes we were they had the grand opening for the Voodoo doughnuts is that the City Walk in Orlando as well.
Oh yeah.
And who were we bothering on Twitter were we bothering Jim Hill on Twitter.
We were bothering asking if he was going to be a face character.
Yeah will this mascot character be there every day.
Can we meet him.
What did he say.
Did what did he answer us and he did.
I think he said he'd look into it.
I think he said he'd look into it but we never found out.
We got to get that answer from him.
Yeah I probably said that's it exactly.
I think that is probably what he said but he never said it to us so he's got a look Jim way in here way in here buddy maybe we'll just have him on to just talk about the character of the Voodoo doughnuts.
Voodoo doughnuts spirit man they named him in a video I watched but I don't remember it Voodoo but Voodoo doughnuts spirit man with Jim Hill is an episode.
Research about that character.
It's happening Jim whether you agree to do it or not.
Yeah.
If you don't know we're talking about entertainment podcaster we've talked about him before.
Listen to his podcast Disney dish.
Anybody who's in section nine probably knows.
So what if see what if you're getting into podcast for the first time and you're going like I thought this was about theme parks and they're talking about donuts and buckets of misshapens and shoes.
This is a show about shoes and donuts.
You know they say every comic book is someone's first comic book so that's exactly what I'm trying to do.
Yes.
Ahoy hoy to anyone coming in on sector nine of the city walks.
Starting right in the middle.
We are in the middle aren't we.
So I guess that brings us to the last establishment at sector nine and Scott you said you had some experience at this one.
Dong Po kitchen.
Scott's face is grimacing.
Yeah.
I had a very odd time there.
So I went up with my friend Ryan who's in town who I went to high school with and probably spent a lot of time at city walk with in high school but he hadn't been in a long time.
He was dying to see the new developments.
Sure.
The voodoo donut and you know he lives in Hong Kong currently so I thought oh well it's taking him to Dong Po kitchen and comparing the delicacies makes a lot of sense but it was very late when we were up there.
And so we went in at like 1030 and so it was not meal time and Dong Po kitchen.
So this is a space that's been occupied by several other higher ends Chinese establishments like Panda Express has tried something called Panda Inn which exists in various locations.
And I think that was the family who ran runs that company or started that company.
I think Panda Inn came first.
That was where they popularized orange chicken and then they started Panda Express.
Interesting.
I believe it was in Pasadena where the experimental kitchen is.
Oh really.
The test kitchen for Panda Express.
It's like if Chili's too was more popular than Chili's.
Yeah.
But this is a recent addition to city walk is Dong Po kitchen my friend being versed in Chinese history and culture.
Let me know that he is that is named for Sue Dong Po who is a poet and gastronome in the Song dynasty.
But he is on Wikipedia he's described as the preeminent personality of the 11th century. But now he is mainly known for having a pork dish named after him.
So we went in there and you know what I'll say the decor was very nice this kind of this calligraphy feeling these big paint brushes and actual and like poems written out in characters which are hand laid.
I think the decor is very nice in this place.
But we went in 1030 and we and I I'm worried when we go into places that and just want a drink and dessert.
I feel a little awkward about it because the guy the person doesn't get tipped as much.
So I went in and asked like hey can we just do a drink and dessert thing and the very sweet hostess who said oh yeah.
Oh of course.
No we are desserts are excellent here.
Take a look and showed us a list and oh that's this all sounds excellent.
Yes. So I'd love to. Oh and as for drinks we have many options here.
Take a look many good wine. Yes. Yes. Oh our wine is excellent.
Well here come. Yeah. Come on in.
She's very like oddly sweet and awkward and inviting and and and led us to a table and like oh OK good.
I'm really glad this is not imposing on them right in any way.
Then waiter comes up waiter a very brusk Kurt's ponytail dude who just like that.
What do you want. And like clearly at the end of a long day like immediate tension and frustration.
And I was like oh you know we're just doing kind of a drinks and desserts thing.
I roll. I order. Yeah. Yeah.
A lot of negative extremely. I just said let me do a glass of seven on block.
No drink. We don't have alcohol. The last half hour past 1030 we don't have alcohol.
That's 1030. Oh that's a cut off. I think I've encountered this.
I think I encountered this at Carl Strauss once.
My family went at 830 and they went no we already did last call.
We're like what. And they're like yeah we close at nine.
You got the last call half an hour before at the beer restaurant.
The beer restaurant. The restaurant that you walk into and there's giant beer tanks.
You get past 830. I mean it was like November.
So technically like an off season but still that's weird.
Well I think the whole like you know like City Walk is your place to drink and dance the night away.
But you know around 745 you should probably think about getting out of here.
It doesn't make sense to me. So there was no alcoholic option and all we were going to do is a dessert.
And we were like do I. I don't want no I don't like boba. I'm not going to force a boba down.
So we said you know we're just we're just doing this this rice ball thing.
And he like gave us just the thickest glare and then just snatched menus walked away.
And we're like what's happening here.
And then he comes back with water and slams it down just the loudest you could slam a glass of water down furious at us.
Then he then comes somebody comes back with the dessert.
Seems like you guys just ordered the rice balls. Yeah.
Puts it down also a little mad.
Basically what this ended up being it looks like two like soft boiled eggs floating in like a dessert version of egg drop soup.
And it was mostly like dessert broth. And there was it is not shareable in the least.
So I'm like sadly spooning some of the soup onto a plate trying to pick it up with chopsticks.
It's falling apart. Take a bite. It's bad. My friend mostly takes the broth.
The broth is bad. We have sour looks on our face.
And then ponytail man goes past my friend and he's in the middle of a conversation with another server.
And he says yeah they only got they only got rice balls.
I don't want to talk about it.
This would upset me for a month.
This this might be one of the worst service that like I you know I know the service industry very hard industry.
I I but this I this is crazy to me.
Like this is like I don't want to do this but I feel like I got our e-mail.
So like this is intense. Well luckily I have luckily as an outlet and luckily by me not remembering his name or hopefully not seeing him again.
This certainly stronger than me ponytail man cannot come back and find me.
There was there was a general. Then I started to figure out oh they're trying to close up.
They close at 11 but I didn't know that that wasn't on this.
And this poor hostess who so volatile monologued about the drinks and desserts.
Then she set a family down and it's a mom and two kids with a little iPad menus lit up.
And then I look back and they you know these innocent looking little kids and then the hostess yells well Steve told me to see them.
This whole thing was unraveling customers are being screamed about.
It was just coming apart. It was crazy. We tried to go get a drink there once after a movie because their Yelp page.
That's one complaint I have about city walk. Sometimes the Yelp hours do not line up with actual business operating hours.
And I guess that's kind of true for anywhere. But you think city walk they'd be a little more on the ball at that.
I don't know. Maybe. But again yeah I had a similar like well it seems like they're open.
The doors open and we're like hey we just want to get a drink.
And they told they but then they're like oh no sorry we're close.
But I'm like but both your doors are wide open and like that's an all literature about you says open now.
Here's the thing. I worked at the container store when I was younger.
I'm going to say I'm going to share my experience with the only real job.
I mean I was a P.A. and stuff but as far as real jobs that's what that's what I had.
If somebody walked in the door we were told we close at whatever 10 o'clock and somebody walked in the door at 9 59.
You let them browse. You let them do whatever you try to help them.
You certainly maybe could say oh yeah we're close but I'd be happy to do whatever like the customer service is that even if people are annoying
and won't and like won't leave or kind of not being so aware of what's going on is that you don't tell the fuck out of here.
That's not nice. Also this is I think like Voodoo certainly but especially Dong Po Kitchen like kind of their first volley of like a changing city walk.
Like this is an upscale. This is an international brand. It's like a chain of high end restaurants in China.
Maze Maze who don't po is like throughout Los Angeles County in very nice locations like very nice establishments.
Apparently I don't know. I've never been to them but reading about it like Santa Monica Century City.
And then the city walk one is a little more like you know for a general audience but it's still like well that's the face like that's the experience you're having.
Like I'm not expecting like you know the ritz but still like a mean man screaming about me.
I've never been yelled about in a way which just made us like yeah.
We got to get the fuck out of here. This is crazy. I think that look like probably the people that work at Dong Po will listen to this.
They will offer you a meal maybe on the house. They did not know you were an influencer coming in there.
A theme park journalist. And I also think once the voodoo people they will send multiple buckets of misshapens to Jason's house.
I mean that'd be great. And I think that they hopefully will make this right.
I'm sure you know there's sometimes you get an employee that's cranky and they don't understand exactly how other employees listen to podcasts right scanning for mention of their brands and they make it right.
Which to that to that effect I'd like anything that's coming to us from how world think as well. Oh yeah.
If that world Inc is listening please send us what do we want from them. Oh I'd love any of these sports fans that we are.
The the vintage filly scholars used to be baby blue and like kind of maroon. And I really like that pairing.
OK. I want anything that says Andre Dawson on it. My favorite cub when I was five. Scott we're taking orders. See what I think.
Wait do they own Lids locker room or do they own. No they don't own Skechers. No they don't. No that's a different. Yeah.
They do own that fancy shoe like McCormick shoe whatever. McCormick is not. I want replicas of the shoes that OJ wore. OK.
The murders. I think that's that's doable. Yeah. Perfect replicas in his size not mine. They they have cobblers that could just put a custom shoe together.
Custom cobbler on it but not some mean ponytailed one. Right. Well that's kind of getting us to the end of sector nine which is we're getting near the end of the end.
What is the halfway point. What do we pass that way point during this one. I think halfway through 10. We're almost there. Right. OK.
And I see right now we're getting our stone it is misshapen. Oh it is wonderful. Shape it. So put it with the bucket of the rest of the stone.
The sector keeper is smiling on us today and he'll also smile if you come back tomorrow to listen to is tomorrow Lids regular proper.
I don't remember. It is confusing that they're in different sectors but hey that's how the sectors go. Well there's stores in between them. Yeah.
All right. Well see you. Follow us on all the things Twitter Facebook Instagram podcast the right and we'll see you tomorrow. See you tomorrow. Thanks.
Forever. This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcast please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcast.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.