Forever…
When your porch has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll
A place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight
An extremely necessary series exploring the stores, restaurants, and wonderful magic that make up Universal City Walk Hollywood.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The City Walk Saga, Sector 16.
I'm Jason Sheridan.
I'm Scott Gardner.
Mike Carlson here.
And we're here with Sector Keeper.
Boys, boys, you give me strength, you give me strength.
We're almost to the end.
And we're pretty excited about this one.
So yeah, tell us where we're going today.
Yes, boys.
Today's sector is Sector 16.
Subway, Panda Express, Smash Burger, Poke Bar, Taco Bell, Pink's, KFC Express, Pizza Hut.
It's a food court.
Yeah, that's what's interesting.
This thing was added, I think, in around 2000.
They added this area called City Food.
Which there wasn't really a lot of quick service options.
Yeah, and City Loft would be considered part of the food court area.
Sorry, Sector 16.
Yeah, you keep going, keep going.
Are you sure?
You seem a little disinterested.
Yeah, you know, it's a food court, so you guys get it, right?
Yeah, I mean, it's like the Taco Bell stuff.
I mean, I could talk, though, about like, there's slight differences between like this Taco Bell and the one I, for instance, that's in Burbank here that I go to.
And I did a lot, I looked up a lot about Pink's.
I have a story about where I got into like a car accident at the other, the Pink's off of Melrose.
We have like pages of material.
Sure, I have a very funny picture for the Smash Burger.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Hey, boys, here's the stone.
Sector 16 stone is, I don't know, like a napkin or something.
Oh, we just get the stone already?
Yeah, I get the stone.
No one wants to really hear about this.
Like, this is, give me strength.
Sure, I think the audience would be thrilled to hear about it.
Give me strength, you give me strength.
Here's the stone.
Okay, yeah, we give you strength.
Oh, all right.
So that's it.
So we just skip the sector?
Yeah, you skip the sector.
I don't think we skipped it.
We talked about it.
We did this.
Oh yeah, it's a Taco Bell.
Yeah, I mean, you're right.
It is a food court.
You got it.
And yeah, remember what else gives me strength?
The, you know, subscribing to the podcast.
Radio news on iTunes.
Yeah, check us out on Twitter and everything.
Yeah, that'd be nice.
So like, yeah, as a thank you.
Yeah, so we're linking in this description.
Wow, okay.
Well, this was a lot more efficient than the other ones.
Yeah.
Hey, sounds good to me.
I'll take any excuse I can get.
We'll see you tomorrow, I guess.
You guys good to do it tomorrow?
Yeah.
All right, cool.
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye, boys.
Forever.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stop, stop, stop.
Boys, boys, boys, 2018, boys, boys, stop.
You 2018 motherfuckers.
Hey, hey.
You stop what you're doing right now.
You're about to make the biggest mistake of all of our lives.
Who the hell are you guys?
Yeah, who are you?
Why do you look like us and sound like us?
Who are we?
We're 2023 you.
Well, it's actually 2024.
Oh.
I just wanted to know that.
I'm still writing 2023 on my podcast episode.
Jason, Jason, these guys don't even know what year they're coming from.
This is so strange.
Listen up.
Are you here with your lackadaisical attitude, your 2018 carefree, easygoing ways, thinking, oh, that'd be funny if we just skipped the sector this time.
Surely that won't have any consequences.
Wrong.
You're dead wrong.
You're wrong.
And that's why we're back.
You, I'm looking at you little one.
Who?
Me?
Yeah, you.
What did I do?
You gave him a napkin and you said it was a stone.
Yeah.
So I don't know.
I was just trying to move things along.
No, you caused a rift.
Hey, hey, coma, go.
Let me at him.
Stay apart.
I'm going to beat you up.
I know our hands are just going right through him, but we have to.
Okay.
Multiverse.
Hey, sorry.
This is 2018 Scott here.
First of all, are you doing another one of these?
Are you're doing like another daily city walk series?
Is that what you're telling me?
Even after this one that we're doing, you still think that's a good idea?
Yes.
Yes, we are.
You got a problem with that?
And we did another one before you got to go do the downtown Disney one.
Okay.
Spoiler alert.
We're still doing the podcast in 2024.
I thought we'd be done in like 2019.
Yeah, I know.
I thought we're.
Yeah, I mean, what?
We just got to get through like Pirates and Space Mountain and then we're done with this whole thing, right?
Well, no, listen, the media landscape is constantly shifting and like podcasting is actually one of the more stable parts of the.
No, that's not what we want to hear.
Oh my God.
2024 Jason, you're giving me the worst news I could ever get.
Hold on.
If I can just interrupt for a second.
Hey, 2018 Jason, what's up, playboy?
Okay, listen, I can't tell you what the cane is.
Just go to the doctor more.
Also, you can talk to more than one people at once on the dating.
Did you know that?
I get.
Hey, it's 2018 Jason.
No, I didn't.
I thought that'd be rude.
Like I don't want to be impolite.
You know what?
It's men are so terrible.
Like a couple of condors say, you know what?
This is getting complicated.
Now I'm confused.
I just really quickly want to point out that we're back here to solve some sort of rift in the multiverse and immediately Jason just tried to help get himself laid a lot more.
Yeah, that's interesting.
We have important work to do, but 2024 Jason is trying to hook up 2018.
Hey, 2024 Jason Jason here.
I'm just trying to put your mind at ease and like don't worry so much, you know.
But you are still not to spoil things for 2018.
Jason, you do end up in a relationship.
Yeah, I mean, you're not trying to stop that relationship.
You're just trying to get your 2018 dickwad.
Just have a little fun.
Worry less, you know.
Oh, hey, it's 2018 Jason.
Do I meet someone?
Hey, 2024 Jason.
Yeah, you meet a lovely lady and you guys actually do move in together.
It's really fun.
Oh, cool.
Hey, in 2018, Sector Keeper, you get to live with them for a while too.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, this is something we really got to work out.
You got to find somewhere else to go.
This has been fun, but it's a lot of days.
We're up to 20 days.
We just added one where we had to time travel.
You got to find your own place at some point.
I'm working on it.
Hey, can I give 2018 Sector Keeper a couple of tips too?
Absolutely.
No riffs.
I'm not going to shake things up.
Sure, yeah.
All right, man.
You're going to have an opportunity.
Accurate wireless.
It's going to look good on paper.
You're not going to get paid.
They're going to call it an internship.
There's no health insurance, but they're going to offer you course credit.
You're going to get course credit at college.
Do not take it.
Okay, do not take it.
Also, shortly after that, sometime in 2023, you are going to play the Powerball.
Oh yeah, that's a big one.
Yeah, are you listening to this one?
2018.
This is what it's all about.
Do not play it.
What's the Powerball?
Okay, we don't have time for this shit.
Let's just move it along.
Yeah, we have to get to what we have to get.
So, all right.
Are you listening?
Look us in the eye and say you're listening.
Yes, yes, we're listening.
Dear God.
We're listening.
All right.
You sit back and you listen to us as we fix this.
We are going to force you to do the sector that you should have done a long time ago.
And give me that napkin.
Give me that.
That wasn't really the stone.
We didn't get the stone.
There's still a stone to get.
Wait a minute.
There's a little barbecue sauce on this.
Somebody used this?
Okay.
2018 Jason or was it the other?
We've actually been passing it back and forth.
Some of it's old and some of it's new barbecue sauce.
Well, look, a lot of things change.
Many things stay the same.
Barbecue sauce is still a tasty condiment.
Wait a minute.
There's a phone number on this thing too.
I think 2024 is trying to hook up 2018 Jason with some 2018 girl.
Yeah.
And look on Jason's notebook, he scribbled out something.
He wrote city walk and wrote pussy walk.
Oh, that's crap.
That's something we don't even say on this show a lot.
Look, you know.
Hey, 2018 us are still, we're still prudes.
No, no, no.
2024 ones too.
Yes, we're all still by Jason Fager.
I don't like it.
I'm a 2024 Mike.
I don't like reading it off the notebook.
Hey, it's 2018 Jason.
I was just trying to take ladies to city walk like Jason Schwartzwind does at the beginning of Shop Girl.
Hey, it's 2024 Jason.
You're actually supposed to just.
Reach for, you know, just sportsman at the end of Shop Girl.
He's not, you know, a desirable character at the beginning of the movie.
Oh, hey, it's 2018 Jason.
I didn't really think about that.
Now that you say that it's been a been a little while since I saw it in theaters.
Hey, yes.
2024 Jason.
Yeah, the book was better than the movie.
We got stuff to get to them.
We can't just talk about Steve Martin's novels.
The Rift is now bigger than ever.
Oh shit, okay.
All right, we better start.
Yeah.
All that Shop Girl talk.
Oh, he's gonna be scared to start coughing so much.
Okay.
Yes, look, we've, look, all of us, no matter what year we're from, we know that Shop Girl is the most relatable reference.
Everyone knows the arc of Jason Schwartzman no matter what year you're in.
Right.
That maintains it's even stronger in 2024.
I just thought a tangent about Steve Martin's fiction work would help heal the Rift.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, 2018 Scott, I liked it.
I like I think, you know, we're gonna get through this thing together.
We all got to be friends.
You can't come at us with this attitude.
We're rattled.
Okay.
Remember, it's 2018.
We're in the middle of the Trump administration.
Okay.
Use kid gloves on us.
Things are terrible right now, and I don't see how they could possibly get worse.
So please just be nice to let's just.
2020, 2020, 2020.
What are you guys murmuring about?
No, I think nothing.
No, nothing.
No, it's fine.
Okay, let's try for Scott.
We're gonna get down to business.
We have to handle this.
So due to what you all did, not covering this set, just doing a flippant brush off this cosmic consequences.
And besides the cosmic consequences, and this is real.
Do you realize what happened by you doing such a short episode?
A little four minute episode?
That's just a theme and then a little bit of talking and then the forever dog stuff at the end.
You left a bizarre sliced up husk of an episode that has tons of ad breaks, even though it's only four minutes long.
Do you realize that listeners have pointed this out over the years that it's a four minute episode that I think still has three entire ad shut.
Like it works.
It's insane.
You left a really sloppy piece and an otherwise completely tight, perfect saga.
I was just trying to give my good boys a break, but sometimes it feels bad to be bad.
Let's let the 2024 Sector Keeper do this with force to make sure that we're all on the same page.
He was 2018 said the city food list in a really flippant way to 2024 Keepers, say it like you mean it.
I'm saying it like I mean it.
We're gonna fix this riff together.
All eight of us.
All right.
You guys in?
In, in.
In.
And did everybody everybody heard eight perfect voices all at once right then.
Okay, so let's let's let's hear it.
Here we go.
Boys boys from 2018 boys boys from 2024 today's phase seven sector two, which is also City Walk saga sector 16 city food subway Panda Express smash burger poke bar Taco Bell pinks KFC Express and pizza hut.
Good luck double boys.
Very good.
I think now there's no mistaking what we have to do.
And Jason's, Jason's.
Give me that napkin.
Why?
Because you tucked it on.
You tucked it into your shirt like you're about to eat again.
Oh, we have to focus.
Okay.
Give me your it is.
All right.
I'm throwing that in a city walk trash can.
And now we commence.
Okay.
Finally discuss the subway that everyone has been waiting for six years to hear about.
It's 2024 Jason.
There has been some changes just since we've done that.
Jesus Christ.
For me it's like.
I'm terrified.
What's it's okay.
It's okay.
Like the majority of city food remains untouched.
Okay.
But this mash burger became a habit burger.
That's a downgrade.
But the subway became a firehouse subs.
That's an upgrade.
Yes.
I would have to say firehouse subs.
Yeah, those words mean nothing to my primitive 2018 brain.
Right.
What is it?
I can't picture that brand at all.
Well, 2020, you want to fill them in?
I don't know.
It's like themed after.
Fire department.
There's a painting on the wall of of the universal fire station, which is something that you could you could see on the tour.
Yeah, I remember.
Yeah, I know you do.
And there's like, I don't know.
There's like a Dalmatian.
No, wait.
It's like a raccoon is like looking in a bucket.
Yeah.
Hi, this 2024 Jason.
I actually like learned a little about firehouse subs because I'd never been for.
So I went and eat there.
Yes.
The rift is mending.
This is I can't believe any of the eight of us still have the capacity to just earnestly talk about one of the sandwich.
Go on, Jason.
Go on.
Sure.
I had a tuna salad sub and I got the combos.
I got chips and a drink.
I kind of fucked up.
I just got a small.
And as you can see, I basically paid for like a quarter of a sub.
It is smaller than a Kaiser roll.
It comes in.
You're showing us like a burger container.
That's not long.
So you 24, the food you eat still looks like that.
Well, I in 2024, I'm trying to eat less meat and I have started eating more fish.
The photo looks bad, man.
It was really good.
No, it was actually really tasty.
Jason just took a shitty photo.
I did take a shitty photo because it was windy up there and the wind kept catching the paper.
So there is still wind in your time.
You're saying, you know, windy is shit up on the top of that hill.
So we have to talk about city food is the area.
There is one of the windiest places on planet Earth.
It's like at the top of Mount Everest, the Himalayas and on top of the entire already you're on top of a hill and then you're even more on top of it.
It can be 85 degrees in Los Angeles, but on city food, it'll be like negative five degrees.
The wind chill is such that you are always needing a jacket up there.
Even in the dead heat of summer, the windy city walk.
Yes.
Yeah, that is the thing I forgot.
I was wearing a sweatshirt or something.
I was walking right through people and they didn't feel a thing.
Your temperature, you're like if you inhabit somewhere, that's got to be like freezing.
It's got to be sub zero.
Yeah, I'm like a hundred negative hundred Kelvin.
So we needed, I found a table up there in the sun because it's the only way you can survive.
Right.
Like it's like gutting an animal or something in the middle of the tundra.
That sun lasted for about 10 minutes before it was entirely in the shade.
Yes, the shade.
It moves fast up there because it's such an elevation.
Twenty eighteen Scott here really quick again.
You've okay.
I think it's weird enough that you're doing city walk Orlando, but the premise of city walk Orlando, you thought of more reasons to keep going to where we've been going every day.
Are you out of your goddamn 2024 mines?
The thing is, the 2018 Scott doing that saga only links all of your personas, your public personas to city walk in a stronger way.
And that actually will translate to you loving it even more.
Yeah.
So we can't avoid it anymore.
You're saying that we met me, Scott Gardner, and now synonymous with city walk on some level.
Well, kind of, but it also becomes even more convenient to get up there if you can imagine.
What do you mean?
We're recording closer to it, if you can believe that is true.
I'm glad to hear my life has not progressed beyond city walk Hollywood in any way in six years.
Twenty twenty four Scott, have you not sold a show by now?
Like, why aren't you busy?
Why don't you go sell something to Comedy Central or TBS or IFC or Adult Swim or any of the thriving hubs of adult animated content?
Hey, it's 2018 Jason.
What about see?
So, oh, let's just say fallen brother.
Oh, well, we all saw that coming on launch day.
Twenty eighteen Scott.
I've got a lot of bad news for you.
I don't want to bum anybody out with it, but I will just I will give you a chilling warning of just of one word.
Quibi.
Oh God, I don't want to begin to know what that means.
OK, OK.
We're twenty Michael says it sounds weird.
It doesn't look.
It doesn't mean any more to me than it did than it does to you.
Is that what replaces munchies?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, superficial.
It is not.
It isn't weirdly.
It's a place where you can take quick bites, but not of frozen yogurt.
Oh, yeah, I'm sure we'll understand eventually.
Absolutely.
It's going to be a strange time.
OK, please proceed.
Whichever Mike was talking about.
Well, I'm more about firehouse up.
Thank God.
Twenty twenty four.
Jason is more to say about firehouse subs.
Yeah.
You know, they they give a lot of money to firehouses.
They've also been doing a lot of donations to natural when there's natural disasters and stuff.
Did you open did you open up their books?
Do you know how much?
Oh, I open up there like our rescue.
Open up their books.
Yeah.
Twenty twenty four.
I'm asking you.
Yeah.
Did you show you?
Did they say on the website that they're looking that they're donating money to
fire stations across the country?
No, I was just kind of watching.
There's this genre of YouTube video that's mostly stock footage with narration.
And they're like, but I think you know about firehouse subs produced by firehouse subs.
No.
Twenty twenty four.
Jason, it seems like your viewing habits are fascinating.
Yeah.
You got quite a life awaiting you.
Twenty eighteen question from both sector keepers.
How many of those views are yours?
Oh, just the handful.
You know, you watched it more than once.
Sometimes I take a nap or I'm falling asleep.
It's pretty good.
You go backwards and watch these stock footage videos again.
Well, now I just like the I like the company man guy.
That's the one user.
Twenty teen Jason.
Oh, OK.
I'll check that out.
Yeah, I think it was still making videos back then.
Anyway, I got into some Jason level hijinks like, oh, did you get the big cookie?
Twenty twenty four, Jason.
No.
Twenty eighteen.
I opted for a drink and I got the limited time tropical cherry lime made
and pretty quickly realized I was mostly drinking a soda machine
syrup and a very large cup.
I actually probably had more syrup and chips than I did.
Tiny little sandwich.
You got half that you had a tiny sandwich and a side of syrup.
And you and you want to talk about this.
Like, well, let me let me make sure I do ample time about their charitable efforts.
I do it to say like the sandwich was delicious.
Like they use a lot of high quality ingredients and firehouse subs.
Hey, twenty teen Jason.
That's been a complaint I've always had about subway.
Hey, yeah.
Twenty twenty four Jason here.
Like, yeah, it is an upgrade.
You two get along so well.
I want to point out that this is just unusual because he was not expecting
to eat just syrup and chips.
If he was expecting it for a snack, it would have been fine.
Yeah, it was the surprise that was the problem.
Surprise.
It was not as normal syrup and chips snack.
Well, I think I was expecting a cherry lime Ricky, which usually has carbonation
cherry lime made is just, I guess, syrup or juice.
I should have tried this.
I should have tried your cherry lime.
Cherry lime Ricky's for lunch.
So twenty twenty four Jason still from 1924.
Something never changed.
Yeah, I will say that would knock against this firehouse subs.
They are known for having hot sauce bars, like different hot sauces
you can put on your sandwiches.
And this one didn't have that.
Hey, twenty eighteen Jason, that's kind of disappointing.
I like those hot sauce stores.
Hey, twenty twenty four Jason, I like them a lot, too.
But you got to watch out for your tummy troubles, you know.
No version of you, Jason, will ever watch out for your tummy troubles.
When are you going to understand that?
That will never be a year where your tummy is properly protected.
It's twenty eighteen, Jason.
Look, you only live once twenty four, Scott.
Jason volunteered to be a volunteer firefighter when he was up there,
as long as he still got some sub perks.
Do I get paid in sandwiches?
I have an answer for the percentage that it's donated.
It's point zero seven five percent of purchases in twenty
twenty four at firehouse subs locations to the firehouse subs
public safety foundation for the purchase of life saving equipment.
Point zero five point zero seven five point zero seven five.
So I guess that's OK.
It's that's point zero zero zero.
Wait, what?
This is not an impressive number.
Zero seven.
So like it's like I think it's like seven points of seven cents on a dollar.
Not bad.
If you point zero seven a percentage.
Oh, I see.
You're saying zero zero zero.
I see you're saying it is actually worse, I think.
Yes.
Well, let's try it.
Let's do some math here.
Maybe we don't know.
Then we'd have to know how much firehouse subs.
Well, no, I'm just we can point zero.
What did I say?
Seven five.
Look, I was mostly excited because they had a tuna salad sandwich
with no sour in it.
Oh, yeah.
It's twenty eighteen.
Jason, I don't like celery.
My tune is out twenty twenty four.
Jason, that remains the same.
So it's hard to find it at restaurants.
So you got to jump on it when they when you tell they don't have it.
Don't spoil your past self that there hasn't been any evolution
in your celery habits.
He's got to have some things waiting for him.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Fun surprises.
I like celery.
This is just again, twenty eighteen.
Scott, are you sure people are still listening to this show?
You're you're looking up percentages and saying I like celery.
And people are.
Yeah, dude, Scott, people are paying for it now.
And what do you wow, that's great.
We're we're doing it for free.
Yeah.
Why were you doing it for you?
Did the entire original sidewalk saga for free?
Again, you guys are insane.
Not just not just for free, right?
You were you're helping me, right?
Oh, yeah.
We're all about.
But the thing is, just to put your mind at ease in case you think we've
changed both citywalks, I guess, have put us in the red.
Well, I didn't even know that was possible.
Whichever, Jason, is that true?
Yeah, I don't think it is.
Well, Collie, it definitely is that way.
You walk around and maybe less.
Maybe at this point, we're back to break.
When Jason says put us in the red, he means put us in the syrup
that he loves so much.
The syrup is a good thing.
Yeah.
The shade of our vomit in the toilet.
After we eat at some of these.
You can afford fancier syrup.
Yeah.
Red syrup.
We got to keep moving.
Can I just say that the subway got two stars on Yelp.
So it probably makes sense that it went away.
It's a bad.
So it was always a bad subway.
I think I maybe had it once or twice.
Subway is bad now.
Yeah.
It used to be better.
Just for you guys in 2018,
there was a big thing about like how awful the tuna is.
And then Mike still defended the subway tuna after that.
I love that subway tuna.
When it's good, it's good.
And I'm sometimes it's less good.
But whatever like mayonnaise they're putting in there,
I'd really hit the spot for me.
All right.
Am I being possessed by the spirit of Jason Sheridan again?
Like I was earlier?
Maybe I am feeling.
But the tuna, I can eat a foot long tuna right now,
especially put a little honey mustard on that thing.
Give it to me right now.
I would eat all of it.
I'll leave the recording and do it.
And I've eaten a lot of that tuna, too.
Hey, it's twenty twenty four days.
I mean, let us have the subway tuna, but I would still give it a shot.
For you, twenty eighteen guys, there was a here is an art, a headline.
Judge rules that Subway can be sued over claims that its tuna sandwiches
contain other fish, species or animal products, that it's not technically tuna.
And yet the tuna consumption continues unabated.
Well, that actually sounds like you're getting a deal.
That's what I'm saying.
You're getting a smorgasbord of different fish.
It's actually delicious.
Probably fancier fish than tuna is what I'm guessing.
Oh, yeah.
High quality fish.
And they don't want to make you feel like you're snooty for eating subway tuna.
Oh, it's a fisherman's catch menu.
I guess every all the best of a little squid, like a high level squid
might be in there mixed with different pieces, like hundred dollar fish, I assume.
A high level squid.
Does that miss spitball?
Yes.
Why skills wise?
What's how does a squid become a high level?
Taste level, a high, a high premium taste is really what I meant by that.
Of squid.
Yeah.
Premium squid.
That's what I'm talking about.
And that's yeah, they don't specify what it is.
If they're saying it's bottom feeders.
Here's the thing.
They're delicious bottom feeders.
If it's a flounder or.
Oh, maybe it's crab with a K.
I love imitation crab.
Hey, it's twenty eighteen.
I love imitation crab, too.
Yeah, that doesn't really change.
If anything, you get more imitation crab.
Oh, cool.
Hey, twenty eighteen.
Mike, you're a question for both Jason's, I guess.
Has any food thing changed preference wise?
Is there some sort of 2024?
Is there anything new you're really into in these last six years?
Oh, well, I've been eating like more vegetarian and vegan.
On tray.
Yeah, but boring.
What silly trying to eat less meat like I have less.
Not less.
Oh, how did you get crazy?
You type of super anything or soup?
Yeah, I got to target.
Pick up with some soup liquids.
What kind of liquids are you drinking?
Oh, I'm drinking more.
A little more soda.
Oh, really?
I thought you cut out soda.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Twenty twenty four.
My.
Yeah, you're saying that's right.
He was trying to drink more soda is what he said yesterday's episode.
He was doing his best to drink more.
You know, there's been a lot of innovation in the zero category.
Oh, I like that.
Yeah.
Jason's giving up giving up soda for Lent.
Lent will be a time of extra sodas.
Hey, remember how the 2018
sector keeper did that thing more often where he coughed and got weak
because we weren't moving on fast enough?
You still got that in your 2018.
Yes.
Sweet.
Oh, that's off.
Sounds awful.
But it's exacerbated by his future me smells.
I think that's the parliament's.
But parliament.
Yeah.
Like Britain's Congress.
Well, that is parliament.
But I mean, the cigarettes with the recess filter.
Oh, yeah.
Those are used to be very popular with pilots
because they would chew on the thing.
Yeah.
I always tell that anecdote.
I don't I don't.
Twenty eighteen Jason is not going to need these dating apps.
You two are going to walk off hand in hand together.
Look at they're holding.
Wow.
They are.
They're holding hands.
You can't see it just under a table.
At least we know it's not like a time cop situation.
You guys can touch each other and nothing bad.
As far as we know.
Yeah, nothing.
Wow.
But yeah, sitting here.
New saga.
Same old Jason.
The sagas may change, but Jason stays the same.
Well, one thing that's luckily stayed the same is Panda Express.
There's one where we don't have to talk about a replacement.
It gives me strength in 2018.
Go, boys.
You guys Panda Express never left.
So this review counts for all of us.
One and a half stars on Yelp.
And that's current.
Uh, yeah.
And we've already done a Panda Express in this same saga.
Yeah.
Is there any original new thoughts about this particular Panda Express?
It's more expensive.
Windy and a little windier.
Well, certainly windier than the one at Alamco Blvd.
Right down the road.
All the different establishments here have to have doors open constantly,
because I think if they didn't, there would just be this wind tunnel.
Suck every time the door was open.
And it would blow the people behind the desk like out into the fryer or something.
You get tornadoes of noodles.
Yeah.
I think you would have constant tornadoes of all the food.
They're going 300 miles an hour.
They're whipping my face.
I'm getting caught up by fast noodles.
I hatch into space like just like.
You open the door, the pizza employee is sucked out into the middle of the city walk
by the movie theater.
So yeah, if you're going up there, help these employees out.
Try to do your transactions from under the door.
Just yell your order, slip your card under.
Don't if you can do it without opening the door, you're going to save lives.
If you know, they a lot of them have the buzzer that vibrates when it's time to pick up your food.
I'm wondering if that's like, oh, we don't want to give you the paper receipt with a number.
It'll just blow away.
It'll be gone.
So they needed a buzzer is heavier.
Yeah, probably had multiple buzzers at one point.
They probably contemplated printing the receipts on heavier paper
so that they wouldn't blow away, but it probably wasn't cost.
Well, then that just cuts up people as it gets blown.
Yeah, they printed it on like a piece of leather or something, a heavy piece of leather.
That's what your receipt would be.
And that printer that your stores have to have that every store up there
has to have a leather printing receipt printer.
You have to brand it.
It'd be a craftsman.
There'd be some sort of old school craftsman up there.
Oh, the brander.
That's City Walk brander.
Why do you have this?
You know, because of the wind.
Why?
Because of the wind.
Because we use leather receipts, as you know.
And then and over there is the that's the City Walk cattle range.
That's where the cows are slaughtered to make the constant, not not the food
that the burgers don't come from there.
That we slaughter those cattle's just to make receipt leather.
Over yonder, you could ride a mechanical cattle years ago.
Oh, yeah.
Bad news.
Saddle Ranch goes away.
Yeah.
Oh, too bad.
That's that's one ride that's that's gone.
Fallen brother, fallen brother.
And there are.
Oh, God.
I don't even know where to begin with the fallen brother.
There's so many fallen brothers awaiting you guys.
You know what?
Actually, if I could say anything to you, you guys from 2018
appreciate the stores that you have.
Yeah.
You complained about going to those water coffins.
But what if that was the last chance you ever got?
Let that sit with you.
I mean, that seems OK.
That seems like something I don't want to do again.
No water.
You and your fucking attitude.
Twenty eighteen.
Scott, keep it in your pocket.
Oh, these two now.
This is a will.
Will they?
Well, yeah, these two are holding hands and these two have to be separated.
Start as a romantic comedy.
The late the leads often don't like each other, but then they end up
twenty eighteen S.
K.
here.
So water coffins are gone, which also means
employee who gives free head rubs is gone to twenty twenty four.
Mike here.
Yeah, I I was just remembering this, that we were touched
a lot by the employee at this establishment.
But if you want to get excited, there is like a tiny tilly is coming.
Oh, Tilly.
Wow.
The future is bright, isn't it?
Yep, it sure is.
Was that Panda Express?
Do we do it?
Yeah, I think it was.
Yes.
All right.
Can we move on to Smash Burger?
Two and a half stars on Yelp.
Anyone?
Wait a minute, Jason, you referred to a funny picture
you had from there.
Is that true?
I think that was just a lie.
Just like that entire episode was a lie.
Twenty eighteen like Jason, you know, we had a conversation
with the Puckett Stubbett.
No lies.
I'm sorry.
No lie.
That makes his heart hurt.
I know.
I just got so overwhelmed eating all those Smash Burgers.
Well, I.
That's a different type of part.
He's lying again.
He's never he's never that overwhelmed eating any of this.
It's kind of reasonable size.
Yeah, I like Smash Burger.
Unfortunately, he became the habit, which I don't think is good.
Well, if we're going mathematically on this Smash Burger,
two and a half stars on Yelp, the habit two and a half stars on Yelp.
So it's a lateral move in terms of the public's feelings.
I don't I can't really I've never I never had Smash Burger, so I can't say.
I don't like that their name was just one word all run together.
When I was checking the sector assignments and bothered me,
I thought we made a typo, but we didn't.
I like it.
You like it.
I like it, too.
We both like it.
Yeah, I think it's kind of cool.
That's two, actually four, because we both like it.
Oh, you're right.
2018, Jason.
Oh, are you?
You said we before you even chimed in.
Are you are you sharing?
Are you turning into one person?
Well, we both really like Smash Burger, you know.
Yeah, no, I know.
But you're using one consciousness.
But yeah, look, they're both holding the same firehouse sub.
It's like when a hive, like an avatar links with the mighty.
No, the hair brand or the hair band.
Yeah.
We bought a large because it's easy to share
and it's more cost effective than getting two individuals.
They're speaking in unison.
Oh, my God.
These two, they are minutes away from Lady and the Tramping.
Yeah, we're going to meet in the middle of the pickle that you get included
with your firehouse sub.
I'm going to do a real test of 2018, Mike, because he doesn't.
You don't you don't know the context of this.
You ever seen the movie Dinosaur?
Let me show you a picture.
Let me show you.
I know the character.
This is this is a baby, a baby named Baby Aladar.
What do you think about this?
What are the adjectives you would use to describe this dinosaur?
Oh, my God.
But that baby dinosaur from the movie Dinosaur, honestly,
I'm having this weird feeling all my life.
I never wanted to have a child.
But seeing Baby Aladar is kind of unlock something in me, something profound.
I need to have children because of how cute that dinosaur is.
Oh, my God.
That's what did it.
I think I need to go.
I think I need to be planning for my future.
I think I need to leave this.
No, no, stick around, at least until the end of the episode.
And then family plan.
Twenty twenty four, Mike here.
Yeah.
Also, I want to tell you about the fact that this toy company
makes all of the mighty mutanimals in the future.
Oh, twenty eight.
Holy shit.
Are you kidding me?
You're talking about Man Ray, Dreadmon and Jaguar.
Yeah, yeah, I'm talking about them.
Oh, my God.
This is I can't I'm going to have to lie down.
Twenty eight.
Michael's gonna have to lie down right now.
There's so much I'm going to have a child and I'm going to own plastic.
Mighty Mutanimals.
Oh, my God.
I'm lying down.
That's right.
And you're doing another city walk series.
Twenty twenty four is a that's good to perfect bliss.
Holy shit.
It only gets better.
All right.
Do we do we have any observation?
Do we have one observation about one of these burger places?
Twenty twenty four.
I Michael says I like Smash Burger in general.
You can like kind of fool me with a burger if it's Smash Burger.
I like the patties.
Steak and Shake has always had a smash burger, which is where I think.
Yeah, I prefer a thinner burger.
I I'm OK with the fat burger and a thin burger doesn't matter.
But I think my preference is thinner patties.
I you know what?
I I don't like the thing that's called on is people make smash burgers
and then give you a few patties that just makes a fat patty.
It's just yeah, you're just stacking them up.
Twenty twenty four, Jason, that defeats the purpose of their thin and smash.
Here's the thing, though, about it is that if you can put the ingredients
in between the smashed patties, then I think you're getting different
sort of flavor profiles or you're getting different.
That's OK.
But if you're going to see, I agree with you,
if you're going to stack them, what's the point?
You may as well just have one big thick piece of meat.
Sure.
Twenty twenty four, Scott, you're still putting up with this.
Oh, you have no idea.
Twenty eighteen, Scott, just be just be glad they haven't started
getting into the CVS coupons yet.
That's what it becomes.
Yeah, a lot of times, many, many times.
Is this still a theme park podcast?
No.
You're looking at it.
Or no, we would pivot to a full Mickey Rooney podcast if we could.
We'd have to go back way before the city walks
saga to make sure this stays a theme park podcast.
Today's episode is the Space Mountain.
But let's first imagine what Mickey Rooney would be like if he wrote it.
Wait a minute.
You guys haven't done Space Mountain.
Wait, that doesn't make sense.
Twenty eighteen, Scott, I just got an email from that guest
you've been wanting to have on that really funny comedian.
He says he wants to do Space Mountain, that, you know, Jay Johnston.
Why haven't we locked that in yet?
Why are we?
Oh, we should.
Space Mountain with Jay Johnston is going to be great.
What about Pokéball?
Well, there's been a change with Pokéball, too, I'm afraid to say.
Yes.
Pokéball got upgraded to Uncle Sharky Pokéball.
Not Uncle Shark, too, like I was saying for days.
And it's actually Sharky with two days.
You were saying that because it's it's like it looks like Roman numeral.
Yeah, I thought it was Roman numeral.
Uncle Shark, Uncle Shark.
You know, I thought maybe it was a second location.
They actually have a lot of locations, a number of which are in Walmarts.
Yeah, I don't know if I would trust.
You wouldn't trust a restaurant in Walmart, but Mike over there
lit up at just the sight of a new Taco Bell in a Walmart.
In the Buena Park Walmart.
Oh, spoiler alert for young you.
Yeah, sorry.
Oh, he's still lying on the ground.
Yeah, he's overwhelmed.
He's a mumbling characters from the Archie Ninja Turtle line
and almost like a haze.
He's just like in serial.
Feminator X belly bomb.
Uncle Sharky's poke, Uncle Bova T
and dole soft serve.
So don't so you can get to whip at Universal City while Hollywood now
in different flavors.
Now this I did go up and eat at I was like, all right,
we got to go back to the food court.
I'll go get something.
I do really like poke and thought, well, that's you know, I'll give that a go.
After everything that's happened for now, 20 days of the saga,
I am so nervous about food.
I'm so nervous about getting food at any of these locations.
What?
Why?
You'll see in six years.
You're actually you're probably seeing right now, but you'll forget.
So I did a couple things just to like secure my
just to get more confident about this entire thing.
The reason I knew that there were ones in Walmart is like I was like, OK,
if I'm going to get raw fish at City Walk,
I need to make sure this is a real restaurant with other locations,
because after this Orlando saga, no more of these fake restaurants
that Universal invented that don't exist anywhere else.
No more of these bread boxes and these toothsums.
The owner of a restaurant I go to cannot be Universal Studios.
They're a theme park and movie company.
They make terrible restaurants.
So I was relieved to find it actually was a relief to me
that there are other locations inside Walmart that added to their credibility.
Oh, OK.
They also had a cute story of like, oh, and it started
when a family member, an uncle, a kid I never met, gave her a stuff shark.
And then they were like, oh, well, that's really cute.
And hey, what if we open that restaurant that, you know, there is some myth
making that's pretty charming.
What a story.
Yeah.
And they're hey, there you got a toy there.
You see?
Yeah.
Here you go.
Take a.
He's got a stuffed animal.
They're trying to, you know, they're they're bringing their Hawaiian cuisine,
they say, the Hawaiian, you know, food.
Yeah, yeah, they sure did.
Well, what they brought was, you know, the worst poke I've had in a while.
But but not poke that made me specifically sick.
And that is where the bar is at this point.
But this but I was also like I had a I had a pitch meeting not long after.
And so I'm and I didn't remember that until I had the poke bowl in front of me.
And I'm just like I was like trembling with the chopsticks.
I'm like, this is going to be where it happens.
I'm going to get one more food poisoning on the way out the door.
I was never in this infinite saga.
By the way, guys, it's infinite.
We don't know.
You usually luxuriate in your only 19 series.
We don't know when this one is going to end.
We still don't know.
Infinite.
That's what you told.
Wait, no, not you.
That's what the future you told.
No, it's infinite.
Well, what's happening?
Have you all lost your minds in 2024?
Yes, we have.
And you'll see why in the next couple of years.
Again, why don't you like Scott, you said you had a pitch meeting,
haven't you guys in all of these years?
Scott, Mike and Jason, haven't you all been busy doing a ton of writing and acting?
Surely it's been a fruitful run for all of that stuff.
Um, yeah, it's been OK.
Yeah, no, not not so bad.
Uh, no, no long pause.
No multiple long pauses and all of multiple.
What?
Yeah, man, you're going to meet a very charming,
very sexy man named Sam Bankman.
Oh, well, he sounds like an interesting character.
And no matter what I tell you, he's irresistible and that path can't be changed.
Oh, yeah.
Everybody in 2018, learn the phrase NFTs
and then forget the phrase NFTs.
That'll all wrap itself up nicely.
You're going to be very tempted to invest heavily in crapopolis NFTs.
Crapopolis, this phrase is unfamiliar to me.
You'll know it.
It's ubiquitous in 2024.
Oh, OK.
I look I didn't get sick is the point, but truly like the the terror.
I like the like now I go into any of these situations,
assuming and expecting the worst.
Like Aaron said, you might be the only person to ever have a mental food poisoning.
You had pre-asus psychosomatic food poisoning.
That's why I got a tiny little sandwich.
Hey, Mike got a bubble tea there, right?
I did get a lemonade strawberry bubble tea with boba in it.
And I've talked before on the show, I'm not a big boba guy,
but I did try the boba.
And this was this was much sweet.
I bet this was much sweeter than whatever soda syrup you were drinking.
This was so sugary.
Boba can be very sweet.
I could not believe it.
And it was like it was almost like twice the sugar of like a normal piece of candy
when I would bite into the boba.
2018 Mike's looking at 2024 Mike is like too sweet.
No, I wouldn't.
What's the fucking problem with that?
That's good.
I'm looking forward to that.
Yeah, it's just the problem with it was just I mean, the whole I did a lot.
I was going for a lot as far as food is concerned.
I wanted to sample different things,
but it was just not what I needed at that moment.
I needed something less sweet, I think.
But you sound like you get fucking old and lame.
Well, I mean, yeah, to some degree I can.
I've said on this saga specifically, sometimes I can't deal with the sugar
like I used to be.
Oh, man.
That's really oh, God.
But the mighty new channels are still coming out.
Yeah, yeah, they're they're coming out.
Don't worry.
All right.
Well, something look forward to, I guess.
Yeah, 2018 Mike's a sugar fiend.
He's the one who was licking the rim of the bubble gum.
Oh, yeah.
You remember when you were at that.
He's still got it.
He's doing it.
You kept it to it was two weeks ago, dude.
You know, there's no alcohol, right?
You've learned that by now.
Yeah, it's better that there's no alcohol.
Hey, it's 2018, Jason.
Don't hog all the rim.
You want to hit it, brother?
Yeah, I do, brother.
You know, I do.
Twenty eighteen, Jason, twenty eight, eighteen, Mike and twenty
twenty four, Jason are all sucking rim.
They're all doing some kind of weird search.
I know it's a little like they're kind of rim job happening.
You might say, Jason, twenty, just scratched out pussy walking road,
city rim on his notebook.
I don't know.
He wrote it.
I'm just saying what he did.
Hey, this twenty to twenty four, Jason, I would probably write rim walk.
I see that saves everything.
Twenty twenty four, Mike, you got to you got to step in and stop this.
I think you've become more of a prude than when you started.
I went back and listened to that secret.
Twenty twenty one that we did during the pandemic.
What was that?
Don't worry about it.
And the only in that episode, we talked about the weird masks
we had to put on masks to worry about.
And Jason said it was like weird, like it was like a vending machine,
panties or something.
And then Mike in twenty, he said it all her umphi.
Is this the debut of the word panties on podcast the ride?
Now we are saying rim job willy nilly.
You got to put some order in this whole thing.
It was the debut of the word panties.
We're just pointing out that it was a historical moment in the show, I think.
Hey, what about a lot of attitude?
Well, it was the pandemic.
Don't worry about what that is.
Technically, now Jason here, let me just cut in.
Where is this vending machine?
Hey, it's twenty twenty four, Jason.
Like it was a metaphor.
Don't worry about it.
He wrote he scratched out city room and wrote panty walk.
The the dating apps that you knew Jason is talking about.
Don't show you the location of of panty vending machines in Los Angeles.
OK, dating is one thing.
Those are going to have to find out.
Frankly, I don't know where they are in this city.
I don't either.
I don't want to know.
Good boy.
Well, I was twenty twenty four keeper just to say now is
technically the debut of panty.
If you think about it.
Oh, you're right.
Yeah.
So it wasn't you.
We now said panty on the show in twenty eighteen.
That's right.
Wow.
That's cool.
Hey, man, that's some Zemeckis shit, right?
We can set up all sorts of things from back here, actually.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
This is for twenty eighteen, Mike.
There is a 15 year old actress in your time who's on a Disney
channel show called Bazaar Vark.
Oh, yeah.
Her name is Olivia Rodrigo.
She goes on to make some music that is the key to future Mike being cool.
So whatever you do, finish the entire album.
OK.
All right.
Quickly, though, can I take six months to finish it?
I'm worried if you pause, it'll never get done.
I'm just trying to help prevent something in the future.
And don't forget to watch all of Bazaar Vark.
Oh, yeah.
That's one of the Paul voices in it.
OK.
And I have to watch all that.
Yeah.
You got to watch all that because they don't go away.
Jake and Logan Paul.
If anything, they become more prominent.
All right.
They were on that.
Oh, wait, wait.
Jake and Logan.
Yeah.
A second.
He was learning about pop culture.
Oh, there's so many horrors for you to learn about.
OK.
Don't tell him about whether he's in the low gang or team 10,
because at some point he's going to have to choose which brother.
Boys, boys, 24 Sector Keepers speaking.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Take us a Taco Bell.
You're slowly closing the roof.
OK, what KFC pizza?
OK, was it the same back then?
It's that it's not a Taco Bell KFC Pizza Hut, right?
There's a Taco Bell and then to separate.
And then there's a KFC Pizza Hut, but it's not one of those.
We're all three are in one place, right?
Right.
It feels like a missed opportunity.
Not just have like a like a triple.
Yeah.
Triple threat.
Thruple.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Start the 2018.
Start learning all these words, situationship.
Jason's going to be the key.
He's going to know him before the rest.
Yeah.
So start throw out any current slang.
You know, the current.
So you scratched down and says, Thruple Walkman.
You're on your second page, man.
To get a whole new binder.
OK, well, you know what?
Here's a good place to start.
People have been listening, I assume, revisiting that fragment
of an episode for many, many years and dying to know
what Mike had to say about the differences between this Taco Bell
and the one that he frequents in Burbank.
Now is finally the time to let the cat out of the bag.
What are these differences?
Well, price wise.
Yeah.
Price.
What do we think is the general City Walk markup?
Is it it's not 50 percent?
25 to 50 percent.
It could you think it can be 50?
Yeah, but probably closer to 25.
There's a sector tax.
Yeah.
That's why.
Check their check those leather receipts.
You'll see it on there.
Well, they have basically everything here.
I on my most recent trip to city food, I did not have Taco Bell.
But in the past, I have, you know, I'm a guy, especially now as I get older.
You know, a twenty eighteen, Michael, you would maybe get two chalupas,
two or three chalupas.
I'm now more one chalupa than regular tacos.
Oh, my gosh.
He's lying down.
It was he fainted, but he was already lying down.
I used to when we were in high school, man, we used to have like three
chalupas for lunch, beef chalupas with a bunch of stuff.
We got like extra sour cream.
We fucking mean we've changed that.
Yeah, I just like what it's, you know, it's a big sugar shell.
It's like that's more of a dessert almost.
It's like a dessert shell on a chalupa.
Delicious still, as long as it's hot.
And even if it's not hot, it's still pretty good.
But yeah, I just we do one fun thing now and we do maybe like a couple soft shell
tacos with we also do chicken now, not the beef generally.
What the fuck do you mean?
You chicken, the chicken doesn't even taste the beef tastes way better than the chicken.
Yeah, I know.
But if you look on the app, it's the calories go lower.
So you can get like 30 or 40 calories off of your whole like each item
if you go chicken instead of the beef.
I want to tell both of you, Mike, that Taco Bell chicken started
going down the hill well before 2018.
Tell me they at least still have the shredded chicken and not just the chicken chunks.
Yeah, Jason, I really like that shredded chicken.
Well, Jason, I have something to tell you.
The shredded chicken is gone.
What?
The shredded chicken is no longer an option when you go on the app.
You can't have shredded chicken anymore, which is better than the chunked chicken chunks.
They only have chicken chunks now.
You're going to make young use all the kill themselves.
Now, young Jason's lying down.
Hey, young Jason, they they do.
So I'm sure they do tacos.
They do go away for a while, though.
Oh, he's in pain now.
Please tell me there's at least some iteration of Sheldon
and Big Bang Theory on television in 2024.
Yeah, of course there is.
Yeah.
As an eternal being, I can tell you, hundreds of years from now,
there will be Sheldon like Shakespeare, festivals, adaptations,
Sheldon in the park, Sheldon in the round, Sheldon in the round.
Sheldon becomes like a Hamlet kind of character where all the great
that's right.
I'm like King Lear, all the great performers.
It'll replace Macbeth because that's what you're cursed if you say that in the theater.
But but you know, when that's replaced by Sheldon, that doesn't have that same.
It went that's gone.
We flushed that down the toilet.
It went Macbeth, Joker, Sheldon.
That's right.
As far as those characters are concerned,
it's the rite of passage of all great actors.
Right.
OK.
So there's an amazing A.
I.
simulation of Michael Caine playing Sheldon in the year 3000.
And the people are going to flip over.
Yeah, that does sound good.
A.
I.
I mean, I know that movie, but you'll learn about it.
Anymore Taco Bell or can we move on to Pink's?
We can move on to Pink's.
Wow.
Boys, boys, let's hear about Pink's.
That gives you strength.
OK.
So so Pink's the way this has worked out.
We were talking about Pink's yesterday on the show.
We did the Hot Dog Hall of Fame with Jamie Loftus.
And there was agreement in the room that Pink's is not good.
That was that was said definitively.
This is this, you know, longtime L.
A.
fixture.
It's really become one of those like it's a photo location
and you got to go to the big line and they have the hot dogs named after celebrities.
And we all agreed, like whenever it's it's one of those like you actually live in L.
A.
You ever try that, you start to go, it's not good.
That is a big overrated.
And yet not to not to dox her.
Yeah.
But it does.
This was this was said definitively by Jamie yesterday.
Then immediately after we saw her, you guys went up to city.
And I went up to City Walk and as I was trying to figure out what to do,
I look over and Jamie was there.
Did not invite her.
We would have been happy.
We should have invited her, but we did not.
Or she was just there on her own, headed for Pink's.
That rules.
Wow.
And you know what?
Continuing to go back to a place that you actively don't like
is the spirit of podcast.
The rock.
Well, yeah.
And despite my warnings on that recording of getting sick
twice from chili dogs at Universal Hollywood,
both Mike and Jamie Loftus came back to the table with chili dogs.
Wait, Mike, you had to again, right after a long conversation
where several times we said Pink's is bad.
Then you had pink.
Can you name everything you ordered?
Do you want to stack it up so much?
I mean, it was that you have one question.
Yeah, go ahead.
This is twenty eighteen sector, Gabor.
Does something happen in the future where your minds are erased on
on the regular, where you just keep eating this shit?
Yeah, guys, we we have this movie.
I don't know if you remember it.
You guess you don't because your memory isn't very good.
And it's not as popular as Shop Girl.
But there's this movie Memento with a lot of like memory wipes.
Is that what happens to you guys?
Like, why else?
And you have a big tattoo of spoiled food on your back.
No, I said the thing is, I keep forgetting to tattoo it.
You need to get the tattoo.
Well, everyone knows we're in twenty twenty four.
We know all of us push out of getting tattoos.
That happened weeks ago.
No way any of us are doing that.
So I got that that tea.
I got a pink's chili cheese dog with fries.
And I got eight wings from the KFC Pizza Hut.
Now, the wings were not from the KFC.
They were from the Pizza Hut.
From the Wing Street from the Wing Street brand in the Pizza Hut.
This is part of the KFC Express.
Well, this is from the they're in the same building.
But I just want to make clear that these are not wings.
You would get it at KFC.
They're wings.
You would get it at Pizza Hut.
There's a way that you can walk into a establishment that says KFC
and get chicken that is not Kentucky Fried Chicken.
Exactly.
Different.
This is more this is Wing Street Pizza Hut chicken.
And they were honey barbecue.
They were honey barbecue.
They were eight.
They were tossed in this little kind of like a spherical container.
It's not a full sphere, but it's close.
I've got a picture of the TV ads flipping the wings.
Flipping it up wings.
Another this was a glossy barbecue sauce.
So this is what we're dealing with.
This is my meal yesterday.
Sector keyboard.
You about to say.
I was just going to say another photo is being shown.
And this food looks on.
This looks inedible is what I'm trying to say.
So, yeah, so I actually didn't really want the fries,
but the guy said, like, oh, chili cheese dog and fries.
And I go, yeah.
And I just ordered it there.
Please take it and shut the door before I fly away.
This looks like a fryer.
This is the top of the spherical container that the wings were in.
Can you see those droplets of the honey barbecue there?
It looks maybe like some like aliens blood.
Ah, it's delicious.
I just wanted to sample.
I wanted to sample things.
Now, I will say this.
I did know that these wings were going to be pretty good.
And they were they were pretty good.
Yeah, they're pretty good.
Because I've had them before.
But you're having it at CityWalk.
Different flavor.
Different flavor I've had before.
They know they have garlic Parmesan.
It's very similar to a Buffalo Wild Wing.
It's a very similar to what you get there.
Don't.
And this is more for 2018.
Mike, don't become your future self.
You learn for once that CityWalk unravels everything you think you know.
Anything that you like can be bad and hurt you
because the name CityWalk is next to it.
Hey, this is 2018, Jason.
I like a honey barbecue boneless wing and I tip it in blue cheese.
Hey, 2024, Jason, that doesn't change.
Wow.
Oh, that really interesting.
Yeah, pretty good.
I'm sure you said up off the floor like you like you resurrected the Undertaker.
Yeah, the eyes.
2018, Mike Wade, did I get through to you at all?
Well, I know what you're saying and I understand it,
but it sounds like this guy can still put away eight to 12 wings in one sitting.
So it sounds like we're doing OK.
Yeah, I hear what you're saying, but it sounds like the wings are fine.
And he's eating a chili dog like Sonic the Hedgehog.
Yeah.
So it's yeah, Sonic's cool.
Right, SKs?
Yeah, Sonic rules.
Is this guy, even though he's acting like he's older or whatever,
this guy can still fucking go.
This guy can still eat whatever you put a fucking cupcake in front of him.
He'll eat it.
He's not going to have a weird shit.
He will be fine.
It's not he's not that old.
He's basically the same as I am.
I mean, yeah, basically, I am the same as this young guy here.
I'm young.
Michael is basically the same as me.
A 2018 host just, you know, work on your sleep and your bowel movements
are easy ways to improve your health.
So keep an eye on those.
Yeah.
And also, this goes for all of you 2018 fuckers.
It's called Mike Stans.
Look into them.
You've been listening back to these episodes.
Russell, Russell, Rumble, Rumble.
It's just by they're so cheap.
Go buy them.
Mike Stans.
So I guess you guys don't know that you could put a microphone on.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, on this shit.
In the fucking red.
OK, don't tell me to spend more money on Mike Stans.
All right.
I don't need to be in the fucking poor house.
I understand.
I know these things are.
Every one of these has been a major financial drain.
We're all going to have to sell valuable items that we own.
Jason's wearing the barrel with the straps lately.
That's how bad it's got.
Twenty eighteen, Jason, is the barrel with the straps.
It's because that's the style he likes.
Oh, right.
That's beside the point.
He's trying to bring back barrel wearing for a new century.
Twenty twenty four days in here.
I get a quick tangent to talk about.
I recently had been reading about stuff that shot up at City Walk
and I used the bathrooms at City Walk and it reminded me.
Stuff that shot up.
What are you saying?
Like, like, shot a film.
Sorry, shot.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, there was a couple of things that could have been.
I truly have been racking my brain.
Did we talk about the Enrique Iglesias video escape,
which is clearly shot in a City Walk bathroom?
You say clearly it is what the city.
Yeah, the city while the city food bathrooms look exactly like this.
And he is, of course, making out with Anna Kornikova,
who he would go on to marry.
They met on this video.
Wait a minute.
Twenty eighteen, Scott, you mean I don't go on to marry her.
Wait, you're married.
God, are you married?
Yeah, you were married.
Of course.
I.
Yeah, sure.
I know.
But like, just as we're talking about scratch down,
we're a throuble walk now.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, that's right.
Me.
Well, that can be me and current wife, Erin and Kornikova.
But if that doesn't work out, it could be me and Kornikova and Enrique.
That's I'll do whatever as long as Kornikova is in the picture.
I got to say, like you calling her Kornikova.
My nickname for her last name.
I call her corny.
I call her K dog.
I call her Annie.
I look, I'll call her whatever she wants to be called.
Hey, I have to just say that you started that that the piece with quick tangent.
And it was actually one of the only things that had anything to do with
city walk that has been talked about.
I mean, we've talked a lot over the years about stuff filmed up there.
But just seeing that music video, I'm like, well, that's a rest.
At some point, the welcome by the universe studio store.
That rules.
I have a request of the audience.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Can they take that photo and put you three in it?
The Kornikova Enrique photo.
Yeah, like you guys are just using the restroom.
Yeah, you're just that.
Oh, we're just in there.
We're not like all kissing each other.
No, there's spots for us.
Jason.
Oh, there's plenty.
There's open sinks.
You guys can be standing.
Wow.
Wash in the barbecue sauce for a little Wink Street.
Our little grabbers.
Yeah.
Hey, I got grabbers.
Yeah, you sure do, bud.
Is your young Jason getting younger?
Young Jason's getting younger.
Oh, he's like seven.
He's got like a little colic in the back.
Yeah.
He's got like a slowly rising this whole time.
A shot in his pocket.
Oh, it's 2024 picture I have of the three of us.
I just it's not like Back to the Future.
It's not fading.
Just I'm getting younger.
The rift must be affecting things.
Rift must be affecting it.
Sector keepers, I'm just absorbing their youth.
You're getting younger.
The picture is becoming more vivid and Anna Kornikova
and Enrique are appearing in it.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
This is going to be the rare piece of content ever
that in one fell swoop went expanded to 30 times its original length.
Yeah, that's yeah.
Well, a great expansions that's ever happened.
Is there any of the sector keepers losing strength?
One of you must be.
I think they're gaining.
Oh, this gives us so much strength.
Oh, yeah.
The rift is closing.
Keep going.
OK.
I haven't finished even talking about the meal.
OK, great.
So I'm eating these wings and I go, these wings taste exactly like I know them to taste,
except now there's a different sauce that I don't always have and I like it.
And so I get to the pinks and the pinks is and I showed you a photo of it.
It looks it doesn't look like anything special.
But I said, you know what?
I would love again.
I love to be sort of a disruptor on the show once in a while and come in and go,
you know what?
Pinks was really good.
I take a bite of it and it's one of the worst hot dogs I've ever been into immediately.
It's not rancid or anything.
It's just not good.
Everything about it is not good.
The cheese is just like maybe like stale ish again, not rancid, but not good.
So I eat maybe a quarter of it, I would say, maybe a little more than a quarter.
And almost immediately, I develop like a dull stomachache.
Within the five to ten minutes of eating it.
And it could have been from the tea.
It could have been from the wings.
But I don't think that's right.
Do you never learn like 2024, Scott?
Just don't.
Clearly, it's never going to change.
Don't even try.
Save your energy.
If it puts your mind at ease.
Fries are pretty good.
The fries were fine.
Pretty good.
If I was not put my mind at ease, you developed an insta polyp.
If it no, I'm Googling polyp once a week in my old age.
Don't put that evil on me.
Yeah.
I'm sure the more hot dogs you eat are going to help you.
I didn't need all of it.
I like a quarter of it.
So but no, you probably waited for your dinner hot dog to finish one.
And to be fair to me, also, the stomach ache went away after 20 minutes.
It was just a quick, immediate.
Oh, good.
It was not a long term stomach ache.
Twenty and moved on.
I came home, I drank my water and everything was fine.
And the bowel movement today was fine and looked normal.
You know, a rich color, I think.
You guys are upset about the word panties,
but then you just talk openly about your hot dog bowel movements.
Well, I said bowel movements.
I didn't say big old shit.
It looked like a normal brown.
I didn't say that.
We go back in time two minutes ago to stop any of this from being.
Multiverse doing fucking crazy things to me.
I'm being vulgar.
I'm talking about my big old shits.
This has to stop.
We have to fix whatever this is.
Pretty fit.
Here, I'll chime in about this while we're talking about unnerving things.
I brought Jane a large veggie.
It was called Veggie Delight from Firehouse Subs.
And it was delicious.
Could have done without this piece of bright blue plastic in the room.
Oh, what?
You guys.
Is that a tooth?
Wait, what?
It's a little nubbin.
No, that's a bread crumb.
Oh, OK.
And it's interesting because the bread was very fresh and delicious.
Otherwise, you want to go back up there after this?
Oh, I could go for a little more that tuna.
Yeah.
OK, listen.
All right.
Here we go.
This is both Scots.
If this works out, you're hearing two voices at the same time.
Of course you are.
Why wouldn't it work out?
Both Mike's and Jason's need to learn a lesson that sticks.
Stop eating plastics.
Stop eating hot dogs that only in quotes hurt you for 20 minutes.
2024 Mike is concerned about microplastics and nanoplastics.
So that is partly.
I'm so it's nice that Firehouse Subs just comes out with it.
And it's not microplastic.
They just put macroplastic.
It's a macroplastic.
Can I just say on Jason's cup at Firehouse Subs,
they have a picture of Battalion Chief Brady Rigdom.
There's a picture of this fire chief on the cup.
And then it also explains to you what thermal imaging cameras are.
There's an explanation, a dry explanation.
Yeah, there's a lot of thermal imaging cameras
that have infrared vision that let firefighters see body heat
through smoke, walls and darkness, besides pinpointing hot spots
for efficient firefighting.
Thermal vision cameras.
The explanation is all in there.
Yeah.
So there's a little informative to get to get a cup from Firehouse Subs.
Thank you.
Thank God.
OK, OK.
Thanks.
Does that cover?
All right.
So the meal only hurt you for 20 minutes.
Yeah.
And this is I'll show you what it looks like.
But this is basically when I was done with it.
That's what it looks like.
That's how much I ate.
And it was not so much.
Well, Jamie ate all of hers.
She did.
Yeah.
She had a better time than I did.
And I don't know.
Have we checked in?
Is she OK?
We haven't checked.
We don't know.
We need to.
We only need to be doing wellness checks with anyone who ever has gone.
That's a good point.
City walk.
You know, like the real pinks, there's a bunch of celebrity photos in there.
You guys probably noticed those.
You know, one unique landmark among all of these food court locations.
And there's a picture of Alec Baldwin up there.
Oh, really, Alec Baldwin.
You know, I read this script that I hear he's been trying to develop.
It's this Western that's like this really like, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Watch.
No, keep your circle.
You'll know why later.
What about KFC Express?
Good idea.
Well, we covered the wings that aren't from.
Well, I ordered something from the whole establishment.
So I don't I didn't need anything from this KFC.
OK, two stars on Yelp for that one.
Pink's three, a miraculous three.
Did I say Taco Bell had one and a half?
It is so hard to get this low of a score on Yelp.
The shittiest restaurants have three stars.
You go any like I feel like everybody like games the system on Yelp these days.
And you'll have like a three star and it'll be like the worst food you've ever had.
How hard it must be.
The amount, the frequency of people that go in and hate their experience
at City Food is just like immeasurable, innumerable.
Like so many people are going up there mad, get mad enough to go online
and say this sucks and get their score knocked down that low.
Can I ask Jason, have you 2018 or 2024?
When was the last time you dropped one of your Yelp reviews?
Because you 2018, Jason used to do this more often.
I mean, I think Jason did not do that.
Yeah, that was more earlier.
Oh, more earlier.
So you haven't done that in a while.
Yes, correct.
Because I believe when Anthony Geo and I were on a Herald team with Jason,
we found a couple of his Yelp reviews.
Yeah, while I was complaining about Mattello changing their menu offering.
Can we find that?
Oh, I deleted it many years ago.
No, no, no, we got to go back in time and stop that.
It was so long.
That would be great bonus content is Jason's old Yelp reviews
about Italian restaurant menu changes.
They were just kind of shitty about it.
They were just kind of rude about it.
It was a long it was long.
It was like war and your war in peace.
It was a epic.
Wow.
And I can't remember.
New lore.
Yeah, I forgot I even mentioned that in all these years.
Sector keeper, could you access Anthony Geo's brain?
And do you remember that?
You could see if he remembers that.
Let me see.
Let me go.
OK, so it was very long.
Six, seven paragraphs.
What was like in the middle of a paragraph?
They removed all the other pizzas, except like the smalls,
because they were trying to become like a tutorial.
But it's like it's Vitello's like.
But I don't know that.
I kind of know what Vitello's is.
Well, they used to just have like a regular like Red Booth Italian
and kind of and a big menu of just like different takeout pizzas.
They used to have an express location in Sherman Oaks.
Sorry, 2018 Jason.
All this stuff is gone.
What they close at Sherman Oaks location.
I liked it a lot.
Yeah, times are changing.
John Jason's lying back down.
What was your Yelp name?
Can I search that?
Come on.
Well, what was it?
It's probably why I think it's just my name and it's probably just nicer
views about old comedy theaters and that Burbank comic stores.
I forget if you can on Yelp or not.
Old comedy theaters.
I just wanted to give a nod to Rodney's Rodney Dangerfield's Club.
See, I never got to go, but Rodney seemed like a class act.
Or John Lovitz's.
Oh, yeah.
Do we ever get to reform this podcast?
John Lovitz?
No, the John Lovitz Comedy Club is long gone.
Yeah, did they ever take down the sign that says Comedy Club
because they did they ever put in a new comedy club?
No, no.
Did they ever put in anything?
No.
Are we there?
I like that there's a big bucket at the on top of the case.
That's what this is one of the best, like kooky displays.
There's one thing I will say about this food court that they're
they kind of have some fun with logos that you see all the time.
A digital bell on the Taco Bell swaying back and forth.
Yeah, a big KFC bucket.
Big Panda.
The Panda Express logo.
It's all very big.
OK, yeah.
Yes.
So that's fun, right?
It is fun.
Yes.
And I like I like.
Yes, I like the idea of city food more than I like city food.
I like the concept.
I like that it's elevated.
I like it's a little I like a mall food court where it's a little tucked away.
So you can like kind of sit in a different area and kind of watch the mall.
Yeah.
All that is good.
As a wind tumble come for free.
Yeah.
You say tumble.
I said, tunnel.
I just got a little mush now.
OK, I said it.
Oh, you still do that, huh?
Yeah.
Old friend that stays the same.
You were thinking about tummy, the word tummy.
Yeah.
I think about tummies getting this tummy.
Troubles can often be made worse, I feel like by cold and wind.
I will hold them and I think it exacerbate a lot of conditions.
Don't start blaming everything that's happened to you guys on the wind.
There is a chance that the wind blew some sort of harmful chemicals into my hot dog.
Yeah.
And that's why I got a little like 20 minute stomachache.
It blew my last little bite of pickle away.
That's unfortunate.
That's often the best part.
I know my man.
I know.
Lose the pickle in the wind.
Yeah.
Wait, that's real.
I mean, this is all real.
But what the fuck?
And then the wind blew away.
It took glue under the table.
I think the guy swept it up when he was sweeping.
Did you see it go into the like the waste bin or whatever?
No, you didn't dive onto the ground and take it out of the dust.
I went pickle.
You played that really cool.
There's a lie.
Yeah, I agree with him.
There is a line.
I think if the food court sold pickles that you knew had fallen on the ground
and gotten dusty, you two would both still line up to get them.
Pretty good.
I'm not even sick.
Probably the wind.
Jason's much more comfortable with surface germs on his food than I am.
I will say that.
Hey, have you gone to Sammy McFloor pickles yet?
Oh, it's we had it back at the shore, Jason would say.
That's how they do it there.
It's not weird pickles just celebrating their 100 second anniversary.
Pickles to the second one in all the talk of like a little Jason
going on little rascals type adventures.
Yeah, we now have the ultimate example of it.
Like the first episode would have to be called My Pickle Blew Away.
My crystallize the perfect caper for little Jason.
Hey, my napkin blew away.
Well, if you're going city food, you're taking that in your own hands, friend.
Yeah, I know.
It's windy up there.
I get it.
I find him on.
I keep looking for him on.
Yelp, I can't do 2018.
Us.
Do you now see why this needed to be talked about?
Talk about pizza.
I didn't we?
Yeah, we did.
See, because I eat the wings.
I eat the wings.
Oh, that was the one on my side.
So I zoned.
Do you think that would OK, KFC has something now called Cheats?
That's going to blow your mind.
2018 guys, chicken and pizza have now merged.
It's Cheats.
But do you think that the cheats of pizza ingredients come from pizza
or like the wings, is it a separate delineation?
Like, can you use Pizza Hut cheese on KFC Cheats?
I mean, can you?
Should you?
What is the question we're actually asking here?
Uh, I pizza.
I'm a big pizza guy of all the fast pizzas.
That's my favorite.
So if I would love to try the cheese on different things,
I would love to experiment with the pizza cheese.
Cheats sounds like what you eat right when you go into the bathroom with Anna and Enrique.
And it also was sound Mike was making after he ate that pink
sandwich in the bathroom.
Oh, cheats.
Sound.
Oh, my tummy.
Oh, cheats.
Cheats.
That's what.
Yeah.
I also ate some candy from Toothsums afterward.
My God.
I had to validate.
I had to.
We hated Toothsums.
We've complained about Toothsums at length.
Can we talk about our valet adventures?
Oh, do we?
We got a quick valet adventure.
Oh, that's true.
We could save it for parking.
There you go.
We got to get out of here someday.
Look, look, guys, don't you see it's a place where some of the signs are a little bit kooky.
It's a place that made you sick in new and different ways.
Don't you see now the value in doing an incredibly long episode
instead of an incredibly short episode about sector 16 city food?
Have you learned your lesson, boys?
Yeah, I guess so.
I don't.
Yeah, I don't think I have.
I think I actually liked the short one.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, yeah.
Let's see where that attitude gets you, little Scott.
Yeah, we might just memento this whole experience.
And they look as long as this long as we can financially recover from one of these things.
And I can still for the cuddly, the cowlick toy that's going to eventually come out.
It's fine.
Like short, long.
I really don't.
It doesn't bother me either way.
I just I just kind of now I have a vision of my first born child.
That's just really strong in my mind.
And maybe the name was name Aladar for a boy and Aladarina for a girl.
Aladarina, that makes sense.
Yeah.
Boys, boys.
Yes.
You've completed the sector.
Officially after five and a half years, we have finally done it.
We've sewn this all up.
We have completed sector 16 and oh, my God, the real stone.
Not your stupid napkin.
Twenty eighteen sector keeper forming its tumbling in with a gust of wind.
Wow.
Yeah.
Oh, nipple of a pickle.
Wow.
And look, it's so it's so dusty.
It's hard to grab it, though.
The wind is pushing its flying around.
We have to.
Yeah, it's not ours unless we can.
There you go.
You got it.
Wow.
OK, wait a minute.
Both Jason's, they're holding it up to their mouths.
Whoa.
They're trying to eat it at the same time.
I what?
What's your problem?
Well, you know what?
It was kind of sweet to watch.
I'm glad the two of you that was nice.
Yeah.
Found love.
It is shocking to start kissing earlier.
We should have all kissed each other.
You were just missing that pickle.
Well, you guys have a job to do.
You still have more sectors to go.
So I leave you to your adventure.
Twenty eighteen sector keeper.
Have you learned something from this?
Will you make sure never to rush any of us through a sector ever again?
Yes, we'll never rush through a sector ever again.
And our adventures will continue forever.
Well, we'll see.
All right.
Well, we'll put a pin in that.
OK.
See where we land.
All right.
I guess we should propel out of here back to our own time.
Twenty eighteen, Scott, it was a pleasure.
And I guess fuck you.
I will fuck you then, too.
Mike, you want to say goodbye to yourself?
I want to say goodbye to you.
Twenty eighteen, Mike.
And I just want to say we're still we're going to do it.
We're doing it still.
OK.
So don't worry about it.
I can go eat a big package of candy tonight.
Everything's fine.
Jason.
Well, there's actually maybe maybe we can leave Jason just for the night.
Feels right.
All right.
It feels so right.
I don't want to describe what he's doing.
His little heart's coming over their heads.
Twenty eighteen keeper.
Stick around with these boys.
They're going to take you places.
He's scratched out whatever the last walk was, and he just put tongue in walk.
Tonguing walk.
All right.
Well, hey, so long.
Bye, boys.
Yeah.
Bye.
Thanks for the waste of time.
You handled this pretty well, all things considered.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
What a ride.
Oh, jeez.
We could barely get Jason out of there.
Well, hey, you know, stuff happens when you have two freaks on the show.
A freak like him needed company.
Yeah, exactly.
Well, I like to think that you can leave the door open.
Maybe you keep a secret piece of whatever portal got us there.
And then it's like Sully and Boo and Monsters Inc.
Oh, that's really sweet.
Like twenty twenty four, Jason.
And you can you can still play or whatever it is you want to do.
Play is actually the correct word.
Yes.
Oh, no.
Just don't don't call it wet play.
Oh, God.
Well, you certainly don't want it to be dry play.
Well, I want it to be as dusty as a pickle.
OK, 18, Jason's really like he's wearing off.
I like he's really rubbing off on Jason, rubbing, rubbing into him.
Oh, no.
Oh, there is some rubbing involved.
Oh, boy.
Sometimes I got to do it.
OK, sector keeper, I am exhausted.
Surely we must be somewhere.
I know we keep saying infinite.
Wasn't that solving the rift for the love of God?
Yes, boys, you solve the rift.
You closed the mini rift.
No, there's still that wasn't the rift
we've been talking about the whole time.
There's still another final rift.
We're on we're on quantum level, Scott.
That was the smaller rift, but there's still the larger rift
because boys, aren't you forgetting one very special sector
with one very special friend?
I'm talking, how do you get there?
And when you get there, what do you do?
You park your car.
Boys, boys, the last sector parking
with our friend Nick Weiger.
Yay.
Only one thing to say to that.
Wow.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.
com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.