Forever...
Dog!
When your town has let you down
When your port has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll
A place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight, tonight
Next to a theme park
I'm Scott Gardner, one of the madmen participating in this grand experiment
The others being Mike Carlson
Hi, yes, this is a terrible idea just in general
Like, this is ill-advised to people
We say it to people and they think it's a joke
It is not a joke, we are doing this 19 days in a row
We're examining all of the stores and restaurants and water fountains for children
Signage, neon, and you know, the characters hanging off of buildings
The sidewalk, the actual bricks are up for grabs
There's things to be learned about every single detail of this place
And we'll probably still not even get through all of it
No, there's no way, I mean there's so much there at City Walk, also
Also, Jason Sheridan
Hello, you know, there's a saying that goes, fortune favors the bold
Used by either the British military or the French Foreign Legion
Or like a coffee ad or something
Or like a coffee ad as well
It's translated from Latin, I forget what the Latin term is
But you know, I feel like a grand experiment is a good way to put what we're embarking on
Yeah, but I mean, this is the type of thing we need to get into
We've done, you know, six months of podcasts about rides and stuff that everyone examines
We decided to take something that universally is regarded as like a hated thing
Most people say, oh, City Walk is terrible, this is a horrible place
I disagree with that also, I've always disagreed, I'm on record
I have tweets that go back five, six years saying, I like City Walk
We can find those tweets
Yeah, well, you know what I think I've done throughout my life is pretend I didn't like it
Made fun of it
If I wanted to do something there, I would couch it in kind of an ironic way
Wouldn't it be funny to go up to City Walk?
And now after months of this podcast, I feel free to come out of the City Walk closet
And just own that I always wanted to go there
Every time, it was genuinely what I wanted
Amen
Yeah
Amen, also
I'm scared of being persecuted on this issue of having to go up under slightly false pretenses
with friends who know actually what's going on
And let's clarify, this series is about City Walk at Universal Hollywood
Not City Walk at Universal Orlando
That is an entirely different entity
We will not speak about that at all
At all
This is only for Hollywood and yes, now
That is also lovely, it's a lovely place
Yeah, well in an endeavor like this requires rules and parameters
Right, and which is why, you know, we've carefully caged ourselves in with the 19 part system
Yes
Now where did 19 come from?
I feel like because they aren't necessarily all even in the amounts of stores and restaurants
But there's, I think 19 is a perfect number
And I don't want to question perfection, but if we had to analyze what is it about 19
Why is that the perfect amount?
You know, one of the impetuses for doing this is that like we met a guy
I think a guy almost undervalues what he is
A mentor figure maybe or a voice of authority
Boys
Oh yeah, he's here
A sector keeper?
You know who could have said it better than the man, the being himself
So yeah, joining us today on the podcast is we call him the sector keeper
He keeps the different sectors of CityWalk
Universal CityWalk sector keeper, please
Universal CityWalk Hollywood sector keeper actually if I may correct you, I'm so sorry
Yes, my spirit can't cross the country
You start to dissipate when you hit the Mississippi
I lose strength, yes
Yeah, so when we talk about 19 sectors, this is sort of a number that's been around for as long as time
Like the number 23, the significant number of the Jim Carrey film
19 is a, it exists in many different codes and it's embedded secretly all over the CityWalk property
That's fair to say, correct?
Yes, yes
That's another worldly meaning
CityWalk is a powerful place, a magical place
And so you must divide it into sectors to experience more than a sector provides would be dangerous
Yes, if we have too much fun and too much discussion about like maybe say two sectors at once
It would be too much for sort of a normal mortal man or woman to handle
So that's why we've divided it up into different sectors
Because if we were to talk about all of CityWalk at once, who knows what would happen
I don't know, we would just be exhausted, you know
Or we'd be here all day, all week
Well, and many people in this city or visiting Los Angeles from other cities have gone up to CityWalk
And I can only imagine, I mean there's no wrong way to do CityWalk, but there's also a perfect way to do it
And it seems to me, SectorKeeper, that by laying out the divine sectors, you are providing your ideal way of experiencing this mall
I would call it a perfect sort of roadmap
Yes, look at it as a roadmap, a roadmap that will provide you many things
Discoveries of popcorn, popcornopolis
Discoveries of board shorts at Billabong
Discoveries of watches at Fossil
Discoveries of water massages at ZenZone
And discoveries of well-priced women's fashion at Angel
Oh, just like scarves and stuff?
Yes, like scarves and dresses
But at a reasonable price
Fashion forward, but at a reasonable price
And that is your first sector
Sector 1, Billabong, Popcornopolis, Fossil, ZenZone, and Angel, my boys
Oh, we're your boys now?
Venture into the sector, discuss, but be careful
If you go outside of the sector, my spirit will burn in hell
Wait, what? Oh no, I spit out the drink out of my mouth
Really? That's what's at stake here?
Yes, each sector will help piece together my soul
Once you accomplish each sector, you will get a sector stone
Okay
19 sector stones make up my soul
Oh my god
So please go forth, be careful, and I'll be here watching over you as your guardian
So we're setting you free? Sorry to bring you back real quick
Yes, I'm still here
So we're setting you free? So you can hang out, but we're setting you free basically
Are you into Casper where you have unfinished business?
Yes, I have unfinished business in the city walk
I can't get into the details, I'll tell you more as you discover more
But just know that I will go to hell if you don't do this
Okay, well that's a lot to put on us
Is there a precedent for this? Was there ever a podcast that tried to analyze the King of Prussia mall in Pennsylvania
and it wasn't done correctly and the King of Prussia sector keeper is stuck in hell now?
Yes, he's there
Okay, that exactly happened
Yes
Weird
I mean that's the great puzzle of podcasting, conquering the mountain that is the King of Prussia mall
As someone who grew up going to the King of Prussia mall complex
Oh, you did
Oh yeah, it's quite a place
Are we now just declaring that we're going to have to eventually tackle this King of Prussia mall?
I wouldn't
Okay
To free him? Do you know him? Is he worth freeing?
No, not really
Oh
I mean, let's say you can find good prices on airfare maybe, but don't go out of your way
Okay, like you don't want, you know, I mean nobody is bad enough to rot in hell, but you know
You're a better guy, you're more worth saving
Yes, well I'm not just a guy, I'm a child
Whoa, what?
Hold on
What do you mean? What do you mean by that sector keeper?
You've asked us to be frank with you just as you are with us
Sure, I'll be frank, I'll be straightforward, boys, my boys
I was a child that was playing in the fountain outside of City Walk unsupervised like many children
The dancing fountains that Abercrombie
So yeah
Finch?
Fitch
Fitch, not Finch, Fitch
If you've ever been in the City Walk there are these like fountains, there's lights in the floor
And they shoot up fun little like, you know, streams of water and kids run in and play and they get soaked
And like parents laugh in delight to see their child have so much fun with what
Sometimes the parents aren't even present, it seems as if the children are just there, but this is a different sector
Yes, he's right
Keep yourself on track
But yeah, you were in the origin
So you were lost
You were in the fountain
Yes, I was in the fountain and my parents wandered over to Bubba Gum Shrimp to put their names in
And I perished
Oh my god, whoa, whoa, this is a real downer here
Is it too much?
I can't, you know, you can't question this guy's reality
This kid's reality
This child's reality
That was many years ago though, I am ancient
So I guess when I said Casper, it is literally what's going on here, Casper
Pretty similar to Casper
Because Casper was a child who was deceased and had unfinished business and
Now he's in hell
What? Casper is in hell? No, that's not good
We've established when attractions go away, they go to hell
So
Oh yes, yeah, you've made us aware of this
I've made that point multiple times
So, but Sector Keeper, I mean, I feel like, you know, not everyone listening is as familiar with your kingdom as we are
Yes
So just to reiterate for the listening audience, CityWalk is an outdoor shopping and dining complex next to Universal Studios Hollywood
I would call it a mixed use area
It's been called a faux street or a lifestyle center
A faux street and lifestyle center?
This is in an article about the history of it that Scott dug up
It's sort of a popular sort of development style that has grown in Los Angeles with the Grove or the Americana or Hollywood and Island
Many other major cities have a similar
Caruso
What's that?
Caruso, the man who builds the Grove and the Americana
Yes
Yes, this was a precursor to the Caruso properties
He was inspired
Perhaps the Grove and the Americana would not exist without CityWalk
And the original idea for malls in America were kind of a simulation of like a small town main street
You know, suburbia, planned communities in the 50s and 60s kind of inspired such a commuter culture, car culture
That we, America by and large lost that sort of main street drag
So the original architect who designed the first ideas for malls envisioned sort of an outdoor shopping and dining potentially with housing or services like a post office
But eventually that was kind of shelved in favor of like the indoor malls that are common throughout America
Many of them dying as online retailing has caught on
But those really rose up in the 60s
Yes
And supplanted genuine town squares
And malls often in suburbia and off to the sides of cities and the outskirts of cities as opposed to in the vital center of a genuine city
Yeah, and I mean this is almost a simulation of like a popular, a populous city street
Like downtown city center, small town main street
It's like a mutant version of it
I mean like Disneyland and main street, you know, is kind of a quaint, tinier scale version of a main street
The city walk version of like a main street is like giant, gaudy, you know, King Kong
It's like aggressive, it's very, like it is really, I can see, I do really, really like city walk
But I can see where people like find it nightmarish
Like, you know, my memories of it is just overwhelming it so much
It's like similar to Vegas maybe
Dystopian
Well, you could say it's dystopian
I mean I would say, what's like right before dystopian?
What's the word for that?
Mid-topia
It's mid-topian
Like it's not, like if the King Kong was like, when we finally get into like a horrible war and like King Kong is blown up and his head is off the sign and stuff
That'll be fully dystopian
Like that would be the scariest place to be, is like a dead mall or a dead theme park
Yeah
Well, this is related to the fact, I don't know if this is the same article you were pulling from
But I read a genuinely cool article from PBS about the rise of city walk in the wake of boxed-in malls
And how they were like kind of sleek and Jetsons-esque when they started
And then by the 80s they were sort of growing predictable and homogenized and kind of just dull, not fun places to be
And they brought up the, is it Dawn of the Dead?
Yeah, that takes place in a mall
Yeah, where it becomes this realm of horror where it's like a refuge for people but they end up feeling trapped
I think people started feeling like boxed-in closed, it just became like a very stale format by the 80s
And the people were looking for ways to revitalize this concept
And so that's where we enter the architect or the designer, the man behind city walk, John Jurdy
He's the, I mean the sector keeper, your...
Father
Yes, yeah, I was curious about, it's kind of a holy trinity thing
You are he and he is you, but you're separate entities as well
And one day we'll send someone in our image down to city walk
A third entity who is a combo of John Jurdy, a deceased architect, and you who are...
A deceased child who drowned in dancing fountains
And who somehow preceded the existence of the fountains
You were there before it, but it was there before you as well
Precisely, Scott
This is duality to the fountain origin story
Yes, speak of Father, please
Yes, well he's a great man
Here's where, this is so genuinely my wheelhouse because I'm a fan of architecture and a fan of malls
And let me say what this guy, what John Jurdy is behind
We're talking Glendale Galleria
Yeah
We're talking, this is for my Valley or my LA Orange County people more so
The Northridge Fashion Center mall that was savagely destroyed by the Northridge earthquake
But came back and is stronger than ever today
City Walk notably survived the Northridge earthquake
I don't think anything particularly happened up there
Yeah, congrats, it was built to last
Well it had the eternal powers on its side
You got Fashion Island which is down in Newport Beach
That was a boring boxed in mall that was starting to bum people out
And he added all of the outdoor streets and corridors all around it
All of this stuff very European, it's like trying to create little tiny European towns in boring Orange County mall areas
And then in Las Vegas, Treasure Island is this man
Wow, really?
Yeah
This is like the Tony Baxter of malls
That's absolutely correct
Not only that, he and Tony Baxter were friends
What?
Yep, I found that out this morning
I read John Jurdy's eulogy or what's an article in a newspaper
An obituary
An obituary, you are wise and all knowing, thank you Sector Keeper
I read his obituary which was written by a long time Disney Imagineer
Who talked about how John Jurdy came and spoke to them
And he spoke to them from what he truly is
A father of mixed use retail space
But I think he took Imagineers on a tour of the West Edmonton Mall
He and Tony Baxter led a walk around
And they talked about, which is another, that's one of the biggest malls in North America
And Tony Baxter learned from his teachings
Truly a Christ-like figure, it's true
He also designed the color scheme and all of the temporary, what do you call it?
The temporary stuff, I don't know what the hell is the word
Temporary stuff
I'm no architect, but temporary stuff into Olympic Village in 1984
Which in Los Angeles
Temporary modular buildings
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Things that were like a bunch of flags and peach triangles flapping around in the wind
Which is so my aesthetic
Decoration is another good word
I wish I always had somebody here to give me vocabulary words
So I didn't just say stuff and things
This is exceedingly helpful
But anyway, all of these temporary decorations for the LA Summer Olympics
Which all moved when it was done to Videopolis
So you got some John Jertie stuff intermingling with the parks
And then here's something I didn't know until today
It was pretty mind-blowing
John Jertie, years before City Walk, designed something called
And you know it, you could say it with me
Satellite Newtown
There you go, I knew you knew it
Satellite Newtown was a shopping complex
Designed by John Jertie
Which was supposed to be the mixed-use shopping development surrounding Euro Disney
Oh my god
Disney Village, which we maligned for over two hours on a recent episode
Would have been designed by the man who designed City Walk
And in fact, many of the ideas he had, he was able to finally implement in City Walk
So that, as I said, the least magical mall in all of Disney-dom
It could have been a City Walk
It could have been the first one
It's almost like we've been called to this place by the things we love
It's almost like you were with us all this time, Sector Keeper
Every time you've purchased a snack or
Validated parking
Validated parking or went to see an IMAX premiere of a Marvel movie
I've been by your side
That's actually very comforting to know
Yeah, and listeners, lest you think like a lot of
What do we care about Southern California malls?
A lot of the places we named Glendale Galleria, the Northwich Fashion Square
Are so close to the movie studios, often used as locations
In television and film
So you've likely seen or experienced these places
These places have likely implemented, implanted in your minds, excuse me
As an idea of like a mall or a retail center
The idea of somebody who's made so many malls
Like I immediately I don't know why this is
This is just some like baby boomer bullshit in my head
But like I start thinking of his malls as different albums
So like he's U2, like the Galleria might be like Joshua Tree
It's a real classic, it's good, it's very
It works very much as a standard mall
But like City Walk Hollywood is like U2's pop
And some people don't like it
It's a lot, it's a body, it's in your face
It's abrasive but it's risky
But it's risky, City Walk is more of a risk
It's a different type of it
It's a later part of his career I think
I think because of sure
How would you then rank, I left a few out
I left a major one out
The Mall of fucking America
Really, he was the Mall of America guy
So what's that in U2?
No, I said Joshua Tree Galleria
What's the biggest U2 album?
Well, Octon Baby is my favorite
But maybe that would be like a double album
U2 never really had like a double album
So I mean maybe
The Mall of America is so good
It's as good as a non-existent U2 double album done at their peak
Something they were too lazy to get around to doing
John Jertie did, it's called The Mall of America
Which album is stuck in the moment on?
That's from All That You Can't Leave Behind in 2000
That's when they came back with Beautiful Day
That's sort of your return to form album
Did he have a return to form where he made like kind of a Galleria type?
Like it was a later period but sort of a standard mall
It wasn't very risky
I don't know if this qualifies as that but
Maybe the Bellagio
Oh really?
I saw a sketch today of that main atrium
That they change out for every season in the Bellagio
And I saw this guy hand sketch what that was going to look like
So that's a good, that's like a later, an essential piece
Many years after what you might think would be the peak
And by the way, Sector Keeper, you know, you're very busy
You've had a lot going on over all these years
But there were Sam Goodies back in the 2000s at CityWalk
You know, you should have checked out U2 while you had the chance
I know, I regret it
There's digital ways
You could still listen to U2 though, the albums are available
No, I can't
Not until you free me
Oh man, you can't listen to music until we free you?
You can only hear Despacito or whatever loop they're playing up at CityWalk
I can only hear what's being played at CityWalk
So you probably know a lot of like top 40, you know, broad stage urine kind of
Yes, but don't ask me too many questions about it
Okay, sounds good, yeah, we don't want to get too off track
We have a lot to cover
You're not a music guy, you're a mall spirit
No, I'm a spirit, yes
You're a mall spirit
But you try to be aware of other topics
Right, and sometimes it just sounds like a cacophony of sounds
because many of the different buildings are playing their own music
So Margaritaville will be playing Mr. Buffett's music
And The Raiders Store will be playing its own music
The Raiders Fight Song
The Raiders Fight Song over again
And you just see how those two things mix together and it just sounds like a disaster
That's a note that I wrote down when I, this is a different sector
So I'll keep it fast, please don't punish me
But I had a brief meal at Wasabi and I jotted down that CityWalk is truly the capital, the world capital of competing music
Which on the Hard Rock, we talked on the episode and that was, and I'm forgetting the man's name, Hard Rock Park guy
Who created the park
John Binkowski, right?
John Binkowski, yes
John Binkowski was very proud of his theme park for not having music bleed
He would have a fucking fit if he went to CityWalk
Maybe he's been, maybe that's part of why he inspired it
You know, I made fun of that music bleeding thing
But now when you go to a place that is full of music bleed, it does show not that there's anything wrong with it
CityWalk is perfect
We don't want to offend you, Sectorkeeper, by saying there's too much sound bleed
But you know, if we had a minor note, that might be it, one of them
It's okay, thank you
I'm open to constructive feedback
That's very good
I thought you'd be upset about that
I'm open to it
I'm a yesander
I took, I took classes at UCB
Oh wow, really?
Still got a chance
That's good
That's great, yeah
Jason and I did a couple years ago
Okay
Well, I guess he doesn't want to talk about that anymore
I'm impressed
With, you know, that's fair
Everyone in the city says they do UCB now
So according to their resumes
If I can use sound bleed as a jumping off point into our first sector of discussion
Absolutely
Boys, I'm getting weak
Please
We have to talk
Please discuss Sector 1
Uh huh
Yeah, so we went and experienced Sector 1
Yes
May I remind you what Sector 1 is?
Yes, please
Sector 1, Billabong, Popcornopolis, Fossil, Zenzone, Angel
Yes, and the
Thank you, Sectorkeeper
The, you know, the sound bleed we definitely experienced at the Zenzone
I felt like
Oh, I see what you're saying
So we're going to start, do you want to start with Zenzone?
Do you want to start or should we build?
Is that allowed?
Or do we have to go in order?
Do we have to go in order?
That gives me strength, yes
Start with Zenzone
So we're going, yeah, we'll start with Zenzone
So yeah, so the Zenzone, we had to put a little teaser in
This is how I always start with Zenzone
Is a place we could go in a coffin and get massaged by water
That's what it looked like to me
It was like this big weird thing where they would put like a half MRI machine down on you
And then somehow water would massage you
I never went in there, I never
We were curious to go in there
We were never curious, yeah, I was like, ah, that must be just some, like
Like I never got a massage at a shopping mall
Yeah
Like, which is always like, I just, I don't know, my brain doesn't even think about it
Without even, it's just, there's no door, there's no back area of this massage place
It's just facing out to the open marketplace of CityWug
Right, so
Yeah, this is not a traditional like massage place with private rooms
Where you strip down to a level you're comfortable with and then aren't solid
It's one of the things it says, I should have, I don't have it written down
But it says like, keep your clothes on
Keep your clothes on and also you will not get wet
Yes
Because everyone thinks like, oh, I'm going to get drenched
Right, which I think you would prefer because you love to get wet at a theme park
Oh, I love to get wet, yeah
But this is not the case, it's basically like there's water jets
But there's like this like kind of tarp thing that separates you from the water
And it massages you through it
So you're basically getting hit by the tarp
Like the tarp is massaging you
Yeah
But it's using the pressure of the water that's shooting
We'll put a picture of this on because it might be confusing
Like a power washer shooting at your body
Yes, thank you, that, yes, exactly
With a tarp in between
And yes, the tarp in between is making sure that you're not wet
It's like you're driving through a car wash
Yes, right, and because it goes up and down your body
And you're on your stomach like you would be
Now we've all experienced this
We all went and did this
We all went and did it
We all went and did it, yes
And my wife came and took some photographs
Which will be up on the Twitter, you're welcome
She said before we went
Well, I got to go and get pictures of you guys in like the aqua suits
I think in her mind we were going to put on some weird like
Oh, oh
Blue tarp suits
So everyone is unclear of what before this we started
No one knew quite how this worked
Yeah, and unfortunately we don't have photos of us in aqua superhero wardrobe
We just wear our regular clothes, which is very convenient
Yes, and then obviously it's designed for somebody who's like walking away from the park or to the park
Because they don't there's no time for anything here with a massage
There's no time to put a towel on you
Like they want to make sure if there's a demand
Which we'll get to in a second
There will not be a demand
There very rarely seems to be a demand at this place
And we should mention we beat it open
We were there before it opened
We even gave them all time City Walk opened at 10
We were there at 1030
When 11 rolled around it's still not open
Just rolling up the doors
We were like lazily open around 11
We were able to
What's that?
I went recently
Oh you popped in
Michael brought me
Yeah so
What you guys were hanging out without me?
So basically so yeah so we went yesterday
The sector keeper couldn't make it yesterday
He was busy
Understandably
I'm not sure what it was he can if he wants to explain he can
But yeah so we went again today I took him today
Or he was there already excuse me
So I didn't go back in there but he experienced it again
Our associate said I'm so glad you're here
I haven't talked to anyone today
Yeah so the gentleman that was helping us there
Very nice yeah he was
He clearly wanted to talk to another human being
No one had been in there
Which is the same thing we had found yesterday
Well we were the first ones there
We were the first ones there
So yeah especially in the morning this place is a low trafficked place
And we have to give credit to the woman working there when we were there
She was very nice she gave us extra time
Yeah so we were trying
So we're breaking it down like there's different like it's you can do a seven minute version of it
You can do a ten minute version you can do fifteen
So we're trying to break down with her
Like so what's the difference like do you get an extra relaxing one if it's ten minutes and she's like no it's just longer
Like fifteen minutes is just the same thing but it's longer
And it's like okay well then we'll just do the short one
And she's like no one's here we'll give you extra time
Which I wasn't quite clear on so I was expecting a seven minute massage
Yes and then his time is dragging out it's like
Did they forget about me?
Yes I have noise cancelling headphones on has some apocalypse occurred and I'm just left here
That's funny because the sector keeper said the same thing this morning when we were there
He said he expected to come out and the whole world was different
I was like in rags or something like come on we have to go there's a there's an attack of some kind
It does feel fitting that we were all essentially baptized to begin this journey
Yes
Father was happy
Father was pleased with that
Father was pleased
Bless you John thank you John
Yeah so she opens up this like this top of this like it looks kind of like a tanning bed basically
She opens up the top and so she loads yesterday we were talking about yesterday
She loads the three of us on them
Three of the four of these and we're immediately taking up three of the four spots
Which maybe has not happened in weeks at ZenZone
Yeah this is the most anyone's ever talked about ZenZone too at this point
We've already hit the record
And no one's ever talked more about it than this
So yeah so we get face down and she puts these noise canceling headphones on
And she tells me there's two buttons
One button is to stop the jets
So say the jet hits you in the lower back and man does that feel good
You hit the button and you use a blast your lower back with water
The other button is to stop the thing if something's going wrong or you feel scared or something
And I love the fact that the button to stop it is a big comical red button
I think that which is a great design I mean it's hard to mess up
Yes but it looks like Wile E. Coyote has one of his controls
When he was trying to blow the Roadrunner up he would hit this button
Very ACME
Yeah ACME branded buttons
So the three of us load in which has to be a funny photo
Is there a picture of all three of our heads sticking out somewhere?
Yeah all of us with the headphones on face down
Because you're in the regular massage chair
Help me with vocabulary again if you can with this little donut opening
The Zen Zone
Oh that's the zone, it's the hole in the face rest
If you get like a sitting massage or like a face down massage
Yeah there's usually a hole for your face sort of thing
This is like being massaged by the ocean
By the ocean
So we're in there for a while because we all thought we were doing 7 minutes
Or when she said I'll give you a little extra I thought she would give us like maybe 10
5 minutes yeah so like extra 10, 11, 12
At a certain point I went I've been in here for 30 minutes
It feels like I've been in here for a half hour
I don't know if that's true we never actually confirmed how long it was
That would have been a good question
By the least Scott's way I said it was about 20 minutes
Oh it was 20 okay
How long was the sector keeper in?
Oh today so I think that you were in I think it was 15 minutes
15 or so
But also all eternity
But also we were supposed to be in there for 10
But yeah so I think it's just when it's running low
They will really give you a deal they'll give you a nice the nice thing
So show up at opening that's your city walk
That's a good tip
Yeah get there not at 10 it's not going to be open at 10
But when they like decide to show up for an 11
Which I you know hey I can't fault them for the late entry
Because they were so awesome once we were doing it
And also most of the other stores we tried to go to before 11 had not yet opened
Yeah I mean they obviously know the audience
They know that there's not a line forming outside ZenZone at 10am every day at City Walk
They've probably figured this out through trial and error
Even Popcornopolis I may have been the first customer of the day at like 11.30 or something
That's not the first time that's happened though
All right
Zing I got you
Sector keeper likes that
Right
He's like 10 mega clouds
Jason yelling let me in outside Popcornopolis
Yeah no no of course not no one does that
No one lines up outside City Walk they're trying to get to the park
The theme park
That's a thing you know a lot of these stores certainly at 10 in the morning
You'd have to regard as you know essentially flyover states in store form
Yes
They're being blasted through
You know what I missed by the way entirely in the history of it is that
Like they basically like needed a path that would get you from the parking garages to the park
There may have been some I forget where you parked initially in the early days of the pre City Walk days
The shameful pre City Walk days
But also the path was set up to connect the theme park to the movie theater
And the movie theater never moved
That's a strange thing about it
But like cars used to drive right out front of it
Like that was just a regular street up there
So the whole impetus of City Walk besides to create a glorious Xanadu of perfection
Was to connect the movie theater to the theme park
Much like the time lapse footage of cities growing or like the opening sequence of Up
Where a city of rises around Carl's little home
City Walk rose from the ground
I can't wait to see Up
When we say you're free you can do it
There's so much great pop culture
I'm familiar but haven't seen it
You get to see posters but not the actual films or listen to the records
So you know you pretty much know of many things
You don't know a lot of things specifically
Yeah you'll eventually
I mean what's big in the 2000s
You got a couple of those Da Vinci Code movies
Angels and Demons I think was great
Robert Langdon yes
You got a lot to look forward to there
Yeah 2000 era I mean Bruce Springsteen album The Rising
Sort of the back of the E Street band he came back with them
The White Stripes Lego music video
Ah fun
We fell in love with a girl
The Strokes I guess
Cool
They were a good band
This show called Will and Grace was on for a long time
And then they went away and then came back
It was a show not just with one actor
It was an ensemble show
You got all kinds of things
We'll try to motor through this whole series
You see how necessary it is right
We're trying to set your soul free
We're moving I think as fast as we possibly could through all of these stores
I think everyone listening would agree we're gunning it
So yeah Zenzone I guess
Yes thank you we're back
Yeah I mean I think we all two different
I think we all kind of agreed like oh that was nice
It was pretty pleasant
Yeah so yeah you're in there and you're face down and the thing is going up
And at first yeah like it's odd you get used to it
Because you're getting shot by a tarp
Like you're getting watered
Water via a tarp I don't know which better way to put it
Very repetitive
Yes it's the same up and down up and down
And it tickled my legs and feet
That was the thing that happened
But then she came by and she goes
Do you want it harder
And I said yes I do
So she cranked it up on me
As did I
And Jason also requested it harder
Scott did you ask for harder
I did not I don't remember being asked
Did she ask you
Maybe not
She may have noticed
We were also using the
I was using the button a lot
I was really focusing it on my shoulders
Were you using a button either
I tried it once and I don't think it stopped it
I don't think it stopped
On a pressure point
But I kind of wanted
I got accustomed to it but I initially
Hated it like the first few seconds
I looked up at my wife
Like oh god get me out of this thing
But by the end
After you know
500 back and forth
If you ticklish like the key
If you ticklish like the keeper
Is
The leg section is tough
Yeah yeah yeah
When it like traveled
Like you know
The up top
Midpoint the butt and the feet
I felt great but the middle
Runs I had a hard time
Not to be crass but I think it really
Tickled my bottom
Now that's not crass
Look I noticed that about myself as well
I was feeling very ticklish on the bottom
I think that it like
It was like jostling and like you could
If you I would stop it in certain
Places and one time I did like stop it right
In the middle
It's not a bad
Tickling no and I wasn't trying to do
A sex thing or anything I was just like
Trying to like stop it in places and see how
It would feel or whatever and I think I got it right
In the middle of the butt and that
Yes that is I
Probably giggled I think
My nose cancelling headphones
Didn't let me know you couldn't know how embarrassing
The noise I had made was
Now the sound bleed I had mentioned earlier
I had to say at some point they
Turned on what I can only describe as
Zen house music oh yeah and
I was hearing that and
A little bit of the city walk
Ambience
Like through
The headphones but that
May also have been because I experienced
Something I don't know that you guys did
Being a shorter man
I kept scooching backwards
To get further into the
Coffin
Because I wanted it to get my neck
But then when I got it to a spot
Where it would hit my neck and upper shoulders
It was knocking against the headphones
So I think it knocked the headphones loose
A little okay this makes a lot of sense
Because I got out first
So I got out first and you guys had a couple minutes
Left yeah because it kind of staggered us
Getting in so we all got out within a few
Minutes of each other right so I'm
Looking at both of you guys heads face down
And Scott just looks his head is face down and not
Moving I looked at you you look like
You were getting pummeled you look
Like you were rattling like I guess it's to the higher
Water pressure but I was like it looks
Like somebody's beating him up like face
Down someone's punching you in the head
I was trying to get it like on
My shoulder and I felt
Great like for much
Of the rest of the day although I woke up this morning
And a different part of my
Shoulders felt like shit now that
May have just been I was tossing and turning at night
I don't want to chalk that up entirely
To the Zen zone but
I did think like a lying
It's not the Zen zone okay
But when I got out of the coffin
I did find like where
The capsule I guess coffin is
A little it's also like a little like the photon
Torpedo when they put Spock in at the
End of search or the
End of Wrath of Khan when he dies and they put him
In the photon torpedo and shoot him out which by
The way is a crazy way to send a man
To bury a man
Is to shoot him out in a torpedo
Where do you get into the space
Shoot him into space I mean it's search
For Spock like they have to find it which is
Why don't you just keep his corpse around
Which doesn't make any sense but anyway
It's similar it felt similar to that like
I was being loaded into a torpedo I was
Buried in
In the Zen zone oh
In one of the it was used as a coffin that was
My coffin oh my god yes
Well one thing
The associate told us when
Michael and I visited is that
For a used capsule
It's sixteen thousand dollars
For a new one it is twenty five thousand
Dollars yeah we talked about
The new you found out the prices of yes
The sector keeper was the one who asked the question
I thought it was actually a very good question because the
Machines look a little old to me too it looks like
I think sector keeper pointed out this
Looked like something that would be in Barbara Streisand's house
In 1992 like
Like a rich person would be like
This is how I relax this new fangled
Piece of technology
Which I think is very accurate I think
It was an early city walk
Location I don't know if it's been there since opening
But it's been a long time through all
Of the two thousands it would seem
Yeah it's a very it's a sharper image
Kind of yes extremity
Yeah
Would
Would you get one would anyone
Get one I would
What if it cost more reasonable
What if it cost a thousand
Dollars well I'm very
So you're so you're set
I don't know
I mean I liked it
I don't know if I would do it all
The time it's got look it takes up a lot
Of room first of all a lot of room
And you need a voltage
Converter the associate told me
Is that did you ask
I did ask that yes
So they have that built
Into the side yes I would be interested
To see I would have to try
I would just go back to the Zen zone and try it a few more
Times to really see if I could get the most of it
Like I would be interested to like to see if
I could turn a little bit of my side see if I could get it
To like hit me at different angles I
Would love to see if we could crank it up even more than
What the water pressure was like let's
See how far we can take this like let's see
If it actually like if because they probably
Don't want you getting hurt in there obviously
But maybe if it was a little higher water
Pressure like it would really like work some stuff
Because I didn't feel like when I would stop it on certain
Points in my back I'd be like man that is
Like stretching me out like yeah
So I don't know I mean I
Found also I didn't think
Was outrageously priced I mean
Everywhere around here you have to
Account for like a theme park
Tax like you have to pay a little more of a
Premium yes and
And what happens is which they don't tell
You and this happened to
Me and then to you guys after you got
Out is that you're not
Only getting just the water massage
When you go in there there are some
Little add-ons perks that perks
Yes that they give you and they don't
Even ask you if you want them they just start
Doing stuff to you yeah
Little massage rollers little
Head scratchers yes are getting sprayed
Down you get sprayed down I wasn't
Marbles on you they put marbles on you
I wasn't even doing anything today I was
Just sitting and watching the sector keeper enjoying
His aqua massage and
The the gentleman came over and he
Goes I'll hold your hands on I go what and he's just
Just spraying me down and I was like oh I'm
Okay I'm doing this too I guess
So like they will just
Aromatherapy
So yeah so what happened yesterday is I was done
And I decided to spend the extra ten dollars
And do the oxygen bar as well
A real holdover from
The early to mid
2000s oxygen bars were
The hit of the Jersey Shore for a
Couple of oh really yeah did you ever
Go as a you know absolutely not okay
But the the parents no no
No no no okay it was a very
It was a trendy thing
It was a trendy thing I think
People some people maybe it made them a little
Little light headed yeah well oxygen
Makes you high I learned that from Brad
Pitt and Fight Club
Yeah I think from the plate
Right they pump in oxygen if the mass
Comes down yes Tyler Durden
Tyler Durden yeah so where's the movie
You're gonna love it sector keeper yeah
He says that you're as peaceful as you do
In the behalf of Choke as a kid but
Oh wow that's one of the things you got
Before the accident yes
Oh okay looked up shit before your
Spirit ascended yeah that's a
Bummer I'm sorry it's okay okay
So you did the Electroshock
Thing you did the oxygen bar
I got the oxygen bar I chose Bayberry
As the flavor of oxygen
Because I wanted to revitalize
It was the silly I always do that I picked the
Silliest name I wanted to revitalize which is what it
Said it would do to me and then they like
She like
She gives me basically what you
Wear when you need oxygen in the hospital
Which is scary I thought it was
Gonna be like a fun caterpillar hookah
Like I'm gonna have this long thing and I'm gonna take
Puffs and I'll be very provisorial
No it's an oxygen line
It's like a plastic oxygen line that goes into your nostrils
Yeah these two little things that go into oxygen
I sent a text to my girlfriend Lindsay
And she goes oh my god it looks like you're sick
And I was like yeah it does and it's like
It's a very weird look and I'm like
Just looking out onto all the people
That are walking to the theme park and I have this thing
Stuck in my nose and I'm just inhaling
Bayberry
But to give again to give them credit
I didn't really feel like
Upsold
They had lots of
Kitchy holistic crap
In there and they did not really
Like push that hard
So after so I'm doing this and then she comes over
And she just starts with these like weird what did you call
Marble what it like it's like a weird
Massager attached to a glove
Something my mom would have bought
In 1998 or something like
Most of the technology seems like it's a little
Old
Yes yes
They buy all their stuff from
Brookstone and she starts rubbing my back
And I was like oh okay and I'm like oh no
Is this going to be like there's
We'll see on the bill like three dollars for
Rubbing you with marbles you know two
Dollars for whatever for rubbing
Your head with that weird like I don't even
Know what to call it like these like pronged
This pronged thing that they started rubbing all of our
Heads with
That old timey
Brain and head shape science
That is not
Phrenology
Yeah it seemed like a phrenology implement
Like they were measuring us for some reason
Head scratching calipers
My mom does have that
That a head thing not the measuring thing
The actual head
Massager she didn't like make you compete
With your sister
No no no
No she was not like that
She would never do that
So yeah I thought that was all going to be
Added up and they also
Hooked electrodes to my back
This is again and they did this to me
Again today even though I wasn't buying
Anything they just hooked this
Gentleman hooked things to me again
And the sector keeper as well
So in the last 48 hours
And set it to 40 minutes
Yeah he would have let us
Sit there getting electrocuted
We excused ourselves
I almost did that when I was
Up there like I almost said like
Oh you know what I gotta use the bathroom can I
Pay can I cash out
Yeah I was getting antsy and
Aaron's plan
Was to like go into the park for a second
And go on you know one of the rides
That's 20 feet away
But she's initially like oh 7 minutes
I'll just wait around and then we're there for a full hour
She could have gone on Harry Potter twice
This was like Zen Zone
Is the equivalent of like
A lonely guy who just
Wants to hang cause like
Yesterday again they didn't say
Like oh would you like complimentary
Electrode service where we electrocute
The muscles by your neck and shoulders
All of a sudden she's just like oh hold on a second
And I'm like wait one second
Like sticking things to my back and then I go
Like this thing just like
Jolts you every couple seconds and you
Have a little thing that can
Control how strong it was
So the Sector Keeper and I today were trying to see
How hard we could go with it
And it goes up to what 10?
Yes Sector
Keeper could only handle 7 Sector
Keeper went up to 7 I tried 7 for
A second and it was like I was
Being tortured like
It was no fooling like you could
You could get information out of somebody
By using this thing also
The control looked like a Sony
MP3 player yes
We had 10 years ago oh so yesterday
Yeah so yesterday I had one that was wired
Today we had bluetooth controlled
So he used the better tech on us
And we were holding this little thing
And he set it to 40 minutes yesterday I think mine was set
To 30 minutes and I was like 30 minutes
When you're just with losers like
Us you don't get the full bluetooth treatment
But when you're hanging with the Sector Keeper
He's just trying to impress him
I think the gentleman today also liked us
A lot I think he was very interested
In the woman yesterday very friendly
Very friendly very nice guy he kind of
Clasped my hand a little bit when
He put the control in my hand yes
Yes very
Just a massage therapist
Vibe yes and he actually
I think was he targeted
So yeah so I'm sitting there waiting for the Sector Keeper
To finish and all of a sudden
He just comes over and sprays me down
And he's like oh uh uh uh uh cause then
I'm like oh is he gonna give me a charge? Did he ask if you were
Allergic cause they asked me yesterday
He just could tell
This guy's been at it so long he can tell
What my allergies are so all of a sudden
He just comes over and he goes oh turn around
And I go oh okay and then he puts I'm like oh
Fuck I'm getting electrocuted again
I'm getting more he just snuck you
Into it without your consent
He warmed up a uh
A shoulder pillow and put it on
Our shoulders we both got shoulder
Pillows and we're getting electrocuted and he's like so what do you do
And we're like oh okay
Like and we're like he's just
Like this it's like the same you heard
The trick where when you see like a person outside
A supermarket that wants to sell you something or get a donation
The trick is you put a book
In their hand cause then the book sort of
Ties you to that person so you don't
Leave them and then they can give you the whole spiel
Of whatever they're trying to sell you or something and then
At that point like hopefully you just fork over
Money or agree to something he has a different
Tactic it's put a warm heating
Pad on the shoulders and an electrocuter
On their back
And they can't go anywhere they ain't running
Into the theme park they're not going across the way
We were stuck there
It's only it's not in pursuit of more money
Cause you didn't pay more money it wasn't in
Pursuit of company yes
Cause that's what I was like oh no is he gonna like charge me
Like ten dollars now cause like yesterday
Cause like yesterday your wife
Erin did not
No one came by her and was like sit down
Here I'm putting a thing on you it was like clearly
Like oh she's not doing a service not the
Case for me I got the full
Extra treatment other than
Being in the water coffin
It was so and then not
You didn't pay a cent
I did not I mean I tipped now I had
The tip extra which is the whole thing because
If somebody does a sort of a free service
I still feel like oh I got a tip probably what the tip
Would have been if I had the service
I the sector keeper feels
He was happy
The employee was happy that
We were sober
Cause he told a tale of a
Drunk man who went into the
Water coffin and shot
Out like superman
Yeah he was drunk and he
Crawled out the front and like before
It was over before he was sober he used his
Arms to just propel himself out of
It and so I think he
Was happy yeah he was
Did he pee on his way out
He leave a trail he did not
Mention any Erin but he said that was the
Craziest thing that he had ever seen is a
Man drunk crawling his way
Out the front which if you see well you see this photo
It's a pretty small opening
And you shouldn't do it he should have just hit the
Comically large acme stop button
Right so yeah we
Were very calm he did other guys
Came in though yes and did
A quick one and he massaged their
Head and then they left
So I don't know why he didn't
I don't know why he didn't
Like give them the full service
You were with the sector keeper I guess
That you know what now it makes a lot of
Sense I they probably also
Seemed like less engaged
In what was going on
There maybe what was happening around
I gotta say I was happy to see
After we got out and we were like finishing up
The woman
Working there went around and disinfected
All the bits that we were in
I was happy to see that let me bring this
Up and this is I'm sure you
Probably noticed this sector keeper because I know
You like you germs and stuff I know
Historically that you don't love germs
Correct
I didn't drown in the fountain
I died of a staph infection
Oh really? Geez oh no
So that's why
Your urine and blood got in your eyes
Now I understand why the germs
But apparently they're in there for
Seven minutes and yet
So the gentleman today
Brought over other instruments
That hadn't been used on me
Yesterday oh and he
Started doing a thing where he would use
The same instrument on
The sector keeper than me
So he would have like a look for lack of a
Better word a buzzy dildo kind of thing
And he'd come over and he'd like
Drive it into my back a little bit which by the way he did
Know what he was doing he could find he could feel
What was happening he did a very good job then he would take
It and he'd go buzz the
Sector keepers back and I would be like
Mmm okay shouldn't you be using
Two different dildos for this
Skin to skin
Yeah and then like the same with
With the head thing too he would like
Put it on yeah your head and then my head
And I'd be like shouldn't we both have different head
Things again I wasn't worried
But like I guess he assumed we knew each other
And we were comfortable sharing
A head massager
Yeah you know each other's
Lice situation which hopefully
Is minimal. Hopefully we have a few
Lice in our hair. But if you end up in hell
You'll have nothing but lice
Yes that's been one of the threats
That's one of the things that happens to you
It's a bunch of millipedes running around
Your hair. Yes
Please please
We'll try to save you from it I mean one way
That we could help you is by
Moving on to a loose clothing store
Boys I'm getting weak
I'm getting weak I need you to move on
Oh okay okay okay
Are you sure? Please
If it pleases you we're also happy to keep talking
About ZenZone for another hour
It is time to move on
ZenZone has been an object of interest
Of all of ours for many years
It's understandable why it would linger
On it. I think we can
Let's through some of these others a little more quickly
I don't think every store will go through
For as long but probably most
Probably most. I mean we
Yeah when we were talking about doing this
I think we were like well you know some of the things
We're not going to be able to talk about a lot
We've hit the hour mark already on this episode
Ah very good
Let's keep talking about time
Let's talk about talking
Right or left?
Walk out of the store you're facing Ludo's chicken
I need you to go left to Billabong
Billabong
Billabong really is the first
Store if you're
If you were leaving the park for the day
That's the first one that you see
And it was a very
You know notable
Part of the city walk skyline
In that the roof of the building is a big surf
Board. It's the big surf board
Fin and I remember at some point
In time it was painted kind of like
Cowhide colors
So it was a big piece to let you know
This area you're going to enter is going to be
Crazy kooky
Sure and it's a little more
Tasteful in its color scheme now
And I went and poked around
This is something I want to bring up for future
Episodes I think we have to
When it's a store that's in lots of different
Types of malls we have to talk about
Well how have they
City walk a fight at? How have they stepped up
Their game on this major
Stage? Well that's an easy
Call for this one because there's a
Fucking wave pool right out front
Jason it's Jason it's
Jason it's gone
Jason I didn't even
Notice. It's gone the sector
Keeper said hey what about the water in front of Billabong
I think it's gone it's gone
They got rid of it. The wave pool
How did you not notice this yesterday?
I we were so. Sector keeper don't get angry
I'm going to leave
Okay you better not pull that
Shit every time something happens
I mean look
It was probably very
Wasteful during the drought during
The year long drought. A boring
Answer but universal is all about
Wasting of water and blasting
It into your face and giving you massages
With it. God. I want as much
Water wasted at universal as possible
And it was one of those things
Like I don't know why the first time you guys went to
City walk but I grew up with it and it was
My family and I would make a special
Trip every Christmas
To go see city walk lit
Up at Christmas time
And it was
Like it was a pretty like
Special experience you know we'd go
We'd also pop into things if we went
To universal studios but
You know city walk visits were a big deal
And I remember the first time walking through there
Thinking like well there's just like a little
Miniature beach thing
Like we stood and looked at it for a long time
I loved the wave pool. I remember the wave pool
Yeah it was cool. It's now a ledge
Where tired parents sit
Yeah they do need as much of that as
Possible universal. Makes sense
Real quick
A billabong is an Australian
Term for a lake or pond
Left behind after a river
Changes course. Really?
Very common in Australia
I thought it was like a droga like not
Bong necessarily but it felt like a hipper
Kind of that's like a real formal
Sort of name
It's a company that a surf company
A surf style company that
Originated in Australia
Billabong mentioned
In the Australian folk song Waltzing Matilda
You guys know Waltzing Matilda?
It is
It's old enough for the Sectorkeeper to know it
Yeah it's not in the 90's
I like it for Jason to know it too. My favorite song
It's about a swag man who
Can't buy a billabong. It's a song filled
With like Australian
Terms and stuff
Can you sing us the part where billabong is said?
Yeah
Down came a jump buck to drink
At the billabong
Jumped the swag man and grabbed him with
Glee. He sang as he jumped
The jump buck in his talker bag
You'll come a Waltzing Matilda
With me
Wow
And then the chorus Waltzing Matilda
Waltzing Matilda
You'll come a Waltzing Matilda
With me. He sang as he shoved
That jump buck in his talker bag
You'll come a Waltzing Matilda
With me
Jump buck is a male sheep. A talker bag
Is what like a traveling itinerant
Australian man
Carries
Scott is the sectorkeeper's
Thing
I feel weak too
Anyway I know
Of billabong
I was never like a
Skate wear
Street surf wear
Kind of kid
I've always worn Vans a lot I guess
Or Tucker pants or whatever
What would you wear when you went
Waltzing with Matilda
Like a puffy shirt
Like a peasant shirt
I was in school
With Matilda
So you waltzed with her
Yes
But it stopped there because you're
You're a gentleman
A gentleman child
Billabong the shop is
Beautiful because it's always 1996
Inside
Yeah it is
Gives you a vibe of like
Not like 90s pop punk
Even though that's not what they're going for
But that is what I associate with it
Everything was beautiful and nothing hurt
Jesus
That's what I think
Of the 90s
The child ghost
Hey well I think it's
Time to keep moving on
To
Fossil the watch store
Yes thank you thank you Scott
What is Fossil doing at City Walk
Is my question
That one of all of them is not even
That's not elevated at all
There was never a wave pool
Not a big surfboard
There should be a giant watch
Bare minimum
I feel like it's gotten more Apple story
As the years go on
I feel like Fossil stores I used to associate
With a lot of inventory on the floor
And now it feels like
There's barely anything on the shelves
A quartz watch
Yeah
And like high fashion
It's trying to go more for high fashion
I guess that is what maybe City Walk
Is trying to now do in general
Because there's a Sephora there which is a little bit of a fancier store
But like I think
There should be like
Some made up clock store
Like Clockface's watch
Watch Emporium or something
There's a Clockface man
It's not fantastical enough
Yeah and I think maybe that's probably unfortunately
The way City Walk is going is they're probably going to start putting
Maybe more high end-y stuff like this in
Although this has been there
For a while
I feel like it looks newer to me
Yeah it's maybe gotten
Blender inside but yeah I agree
We're just getting into it's just becoming
Kind of a standard mall
As all malls are getting
You know you don't have the
The mall I grew up next to
Had a food court called Chowzers
With a Z and every
Store had a toothpick
With like the little toothpick
Frilly
Confetti on the end of it
And like you know
There's no reason to have that
You know production
Value and cartoon
Silliness but it made me love
Chowzers and remember it and talk about it on
A podcast and the more City Walk
Gets bland the more it loses
Grounds to places like The Grove
And the Americana
Yeah that's true yeah I mean if this was all
Just sort of a high end like
You know Beverly Hills mall
What's the point what is it City Walk anymore?
I mean I get the idea of people
Splurging when they're on vacation
But like Fossil is like a
That's a
That's a real
Like that's a like a $200
Messenger bag
It's a lot of leather goods
It's a lot of chunky watches
Yeah
Has anyone here bought a Fossil watch ever?
My sister did in the 90s
With a
Heyday of Billabong? Yes
I hope you'll be reunited with her
When this is all set up That would be lovely
I have a Fossil wallet
Someone gave me for Christmas
A few years ago that I use every now
And then but I was
I'm not like really a leather guy or a watch
Guy
The Fossil store
I'm disappointed a lot of fans
Some people like
Leather
You're not a leather daddy?
I
We try to keep it a little cleaner
Here Sector Keeper
I try to keep my personal life off of this
I'm sorry Your child mind
Is more perverted than it should be
The Fossil store at
City Walk Universal
City Walk Hollywood
Not only lacks imagination
Michael and I noticed
It lacks watches
There's a whole empty rack
That's supposed to be like watch like display
The very first rack
It is completely empty
As if someone had
Stolen all of them
It's like a kid just running by
Collecting them all on his arm
It's interesting because they're trying to
Compete too in like the smart watch
Category so they have
Giant facimiles of their
Smartwatches in the window
The Google powered smartwatches
You can get a
Buckner NS City Bag
For $118
You can get a Nasher
Backpack for $128
So it's not so bad
That's a little expensive for people
Let's demand the fans chip in
And buy Jason one of these bags
Get him a Buckner or get him a
Rory Courier Bag
Or if you want to go high end
There's one called the Defender Portfolio
That I think would look nice
That looks sharp on Jason
Oh you know what never mind I take all that back
Get him the Estate Casual
Leather Backpack
Because he's a leather daddy
From here on out
You were too definitive that you weren't a leather daddy
Thus now you are
You didn't deny it buddy
Alright
Oh no
Oh growing weak
Boys
I think it's time to go
To a city within a city
It's time for
Popcornopolis
I'm sorry we've left you hanging for so long
You know what all comedy
Podcasts should have
A weak ghost to keep them on track
Boys, boys
Don't bring Bugsy back let him die the first time
So Popcornopolis
I did patron I went into
Popcornopolis and
I figured should sample some
Of the wares and bought a cone
Of churro corn
Tried a couple flavors
You can get free samples
They offer you free samples
Can I ask how
My feeling on samples
Is that I will never ask
For samples I only pick and
I eat I don't know what it is
I feel like I'm wasting their time
I know this is an unpopular opinion
I know you will get a sample of as many as they tell you
They'll say limit three and you will get three
So you're being a
Sweets and treats boy
Is usurped
Overridden by you being a good boy
Yes I think that is sort of what I feel
I feel like well I haven't paid for this
So I feel bad even having a little ice cream
Or a little of the popcorn and also I feel like
Maybe from being raised by my mom
Telling me that I was not a picky
Eater that I go well I'll enjoy it
So like anything I order
I will like if I order ice cream if I order
A meal I'm not I'll never see
This is horrible like I'll just enjoy it
So you're a helpful trade
In a theme park
I want to know what I'm getting into I only got two
Sample I sampled the Chicago style
Which is caramel corn and cheddar corn together
Which I liked fine but the sign outside
Add Truro corn and big
Letters I'm like oh I'm interested in that
I like a cinnamon like
I like cinnamon as a flavor
Or like roasted
Cinnamon nuts or
In this case sweet cinnamon
Popcorn and it was really tasty
I thought it was good I had a little bit of it
I've had
I've had their popcorn before
Pretty good pretty good quality
Pretty good I do think it's very funny they call it
Gourmet popcorn like every
Now and then you see gourmet blank
Right I always wonder what does that really mean
What does that really mean
I mean they have a lot of interesting they had a cupcake
Flavor of popcorn
Yes they had a lot of I mean there was no way we could
Like they didn't know we were theme park
Journalists because I think they would have rolled out the red carpet for us
If they shared and they would have had all the samples
Probably out like laid out and we would have been able to kind of come behind the counter
They were willing to give samples though
Very willing to give samples and I said oh I like
I'll take the Truro corn and
Just a small
I didn't want that much and they gave me
A like
Foot long
Cone like it's a cone
It was a giant amount of popcorn yeah
I'm still it's it's
I shared it with you guys and with people
Afterwards and I still have
A bunch left with the massage therapist
With the massage therapist
We should have gone into popcorn apples first and you could have
Eaten it while you were getting the massage
I feel like that would have been
Too distracting or we could have had someone feed it to you
Through the hole well now that sounds
Gourmet that someone had
Zenzone would have done it without being asked
I'm sure yeah if you had
Popcorn on the counter yeah they would have gone over
All of a sudden you would have felt like it being shoved
Into your mouth popcorn apples lean
Sweet yeah I would
Say so yeah they have a lot of sweet
Flavors that the sprinkles
Yeah so there's not as zebra
Oh yeah yeah yeah
I think my mom's a fan of zebra
All gluten free I found out
All varieties gluten free
Some of them kosher
A handful of them are certified kosher
And they have other things there too they have
A whole display case of candied
Apples that are like Disneyland style
Insane decorated with candy
Or confect sprinkles and stuff
You got something there you said
Yeah so I said I should
You know I should experience something different than the popcorn
And I got a
Frozen banana covered in chocolate
And sprinkles and
I forgot how big a banana can
Be because on the picture I
Thought oh a banana you know
Five inches skinny
Banana I thought
Okay this will be a nice quick little treat
It was not a tiny skinny
Banana I will show a photo of what it
Looks like and I'm in the picture
For a size comparison
Big hard raging
Banana much bigger than that buzzy
Dildo that was used on mine
And the sector keeper's neck earlier
Here's how big it was
You're making
A face
I was like oh no
Why did I do this? The sector keeper directed
Michael to smile
Because he seemed
He must be posted
Here's a picture now I'm happy
I can't zoom in but
Now I'm happy
It was very good
I mean I was not but I was just like oh no
All the calories and it was a thick
Chocolate shell
With sprinkles and it was good
Yeah it was very good
We don't do a ton
Of talking about restaurants
On the podcast but with city walk
We'll be going to a lot of restaurants
I feel like it would be helpful if we had some kind of
Like rating system to
Rank the food right
If it was rated on a scale of
1 to 4
Some sort of utensil or something
Would be good
What if we rated it on the scale of
1 to 4
Forchettas
The Italian word for fork
Oh that's nice I love Italian
First of all it's just one of the romantic languages
So I just think that and we're very like
A romantic podcast so that makes a lot of sense
I think this makes it an extremely
Original idea I think you're right
I mean I initially saw
A lawyer some sort of podcast
Lawyer coming through
Like standing at the patio door
Here and then when he heard it was
The word in Italian he like
You know tore something up and stopped
His feet in anger
I can't get him now I was checking the
Italian translation so I missed
All of that I'm so glad that this
Is in the clear I'm not sure what he would have been
Mad about but this is
This is a pretty original measure he's probably
From hell
He's trying to get me to come oh geez
Okay well we gotta keep him off your back and
Keep moving so if you guys had to wait
What are the uno
Uno due tre
Quattro do they go up to
Do we go up to five
No five would be insane cinque
No cinque how would you
Rank your banana
Can you give me the numbers again? Uno due tre
Quattro I mean as far as
What you're looking for I'll go
Quattro cause I mean look a nice frozen banana
Banana was a good quality
Is giant you get a lot for your money it's six bucks
A little expensive but it's a giant thick
Hard banana and it was
Good it's thick chocolate and the sprinkles it very
Much the shell very much
Reminded me of my favorite
Dipped cones at Disneyland so you're getting
That that's a solid treat
I've always liked it so yeah
I'll go four I'd go quattro
As well yeah
The cone of popcorn was seven
And I honestly really didn't
Want that much but
You know I respect
That you I think you are certainly getting
A shareable quantity
Worth and you're getting a lot
Worth and I respect the business
Angle I know the margins are very good
On like stuff like that popcorn that you
Can make on bulk and sell for a lot
More than it sure actually costs
And again very friendly
Good service sure everywhere we went
To up there and you guys want to put
Either the banana or the popcorn into
The club the Targa
Dioro which
Translates to Golden Plate Club
But whether we won't refer to it as that
Is coming back oh sure okay
No club it's not in the club there is no club
And I guess we should
Keep moving to the final
Store in the sector yes
Boys boys keep moving please
You'll take a right out of popcorn
Opolis and you arrive
You'll arrive not in
Heaven but in a place
Called
Angel
But not spelled with all of the
Letters A N G L
This is a shop that
Their website describes as California's
Hottest club dresses and
Trendy women's clothes
And that
Seem with what we know about women's clothing
Does it would you think it was
Trendy next to nothing
Yeah I mean I would say
So I really only peeked in it
A little and I looked at their website
But from what I know
Of the price points of
Casual women's clothes
Or evening wear that sort of thing it seems
Reasonably affordable
Price on a leather
Dress a leather
Dress oh I see
Where you're going with that
You're getting my ass
I see what you're doing there
You wouldn't know that
You're a leather daddy yeah yeah
I went in with a frozen
Banana I was eating it in
Angel today and I felt uncomfortable because Angel
A lot of honestly
A lot of clothes I have a lot of opinions on clothes
I thought a lot of the clothes looked nice I liked
A lot of the designs
But it's so close in there all the things
Like fossils very spread out because it's watches
It doesn't take up much space
Angel was very claustrophobic
I felt as a store they crammed
A lot of stuff in so I'll be honest
We didn't get the full experience because I felt uncomfortable
Wielding chocolate covered banana
In there that I would just like let
Some sprinkles fly and they would hit some women's clothing
Next to like summery crop tops and maxi
Dresses and that's what I said yes I didn't want to
Ruin the maxi dresses but it seemed very
Eclectic
Lots of options right I mean
Maybe they could
Have more of a specific style
If I was critiquing Angel
Sure sure
If you call something California it can be
Anything
California is a catch all
Avocado could be swiss cheese
You know is the California on a menu
It's a loose genre isn't it
Well this is I'm kind of disappointed
That Angel
Is the use of that location now
Because when City Walk opened
This was one of the
Landmarks City Walk stores
It was called the Nature Company
And the Nature Company
Or from their own website
At the time the Nature Company store
Features a rainforest exhibit with a replica
Of a banyan tree
Wow and if you were anybody
We've talked about that Warner Brothers studio store a little bit
Where you'd walk into a little spaceship
Or some or a little movie studio or whatever
It was if you're a kid who's
Bored in a mall if they're like a thing you can
Go into like that little
Imaginarium door
That stuff's always great and this thing
Yeah you've got to walk through a little
Rainforest which is very
Cool and very well done and the big thing
That I remember about this
I've been withholding this fact from you guys
In my recollection
This was the second location
On the Universal Studios property with
The E.T. Ride smell
Really? Oh sure
It had that same like that magical
Fake pine
Combining with that heavily
Chlorinated water
Yeah that
That magical effect
That was only on the E.T. Ride was also
In this other place so I was really happy
There was another little zone where you got a
Quick little hit of that
And you always recognized that like from
The first time you went in did you oh it's the E.T. smell
Like did you immediately it's so
No one told you oh that's the same smell
It wasn't like a
It wasn't a thing it was there was no
You know Twitter accounts
Devoted to the E.T. smell or a message
Report talking about it right I remember like
When I started when I first started talking to people
Who were also grew up around here and were fond
Of Universal that E.T. smell would come
Up so frequently and
I don't think I was the only one
Let me ask this question because you worked at the park
Did you ever see
The canisters of smells?
No no
As I'll get into
At some point I did get to see you know
Rotting botanica so I mentioned that
On the first episode
I'll bring that up again later but the
But I and one time after
The Back to the Future I closed I got to see a big
Like a stack of lots of
The DeLorean
Cars like they were they were all
Piled up in a junkyard way which
Was kind of depressing to see
And I went up there I snuck up there
To see if there was any like little piece I could break
Off like a license plate or a
Flux capacitor or something
But it wasn't really it was all like the
Big blunt pieces of it
So no no smell canister I never got
Any insight as to where the smell
Came from but I did get to experience
That King Kong banana breath on the daily
Of course well another one of the great
Universal smells that would have been a
Crazy score though if you could have like
Stolen a canister of theme park smell
And then like
Just like when you were feeling the mood
You go over and you like open the valve a
Little bit and take a big whiff
Now that's aromatherapy
I should use that at Zenzone
Oh boy what a good plus it up
Sector keeper
It really is yeah if they want to cater
To the locals and the people with
With universal nostalgia
So like Dennis Hopper's character
In blue velvet but instead of laughing
Gas you're taking a smell
Of that like
Kind of mildewy water
In plastic
Or a bromide smell
Of theme parks
Now I feel like I'm in the
Forest outside of
The Tongo
The inexplicable pine forest
I'm in Maggie Simpson's mouth
Baby powder
Smelling Shrek's farts
Those sort of like
Nature stores or
Discovery channel stores
Which eventually bought the nature
Company
That you know they all sold
A lot of educational toys
And rain sticks and that sort of thing
I was always interested in that because even as a kid
I was like how does this place make money
Like they were
Always at the most expensive malls
And you can play with everything
You could buy it was out of
Box already yeah and
It's you know it's parents walking around
With their kids going like is this the souvenir
You want for the trip is this your one souvenir
And all the kids
You just go like nah I think
I'm done I think I'm good
By the time you've already
Played with it and had time to
Decide you don't want it you probably
Dig your hand into that pile of gems
Oh my god this is great I'll stick my
Hand in this all the time to relax
Me five seconds past
You know what never mind I will leave with no gems
Yeah they didn't
Didn't stick the line I guess there's nowhere to buy
Gems anymore I don't know where you go
In Los Angeles in general if you want a rain stick
Yeah that's a good question
If you guys know of a good
Other listeners if you know a good rain stick place
Let us know
Where would you go?
I thought you were gonna have
I didn't have anything
What is Los Angeles?
Oh boy that's
Too much you're within
You're up on high on the hill
Universal city
That's how little Los Angeles
Affected you
Why would you need to know about Los Angeles?
Why do any of us if we could only be in
CityWalk?
We would maybe like to just trade places
With you I guess?
I could arrange that
So if my spirit was freed yours would be
Incarcerated
Maybe would we be willing to trade?
But would we get to be in CityWalk?
You're not in city well you can go visit
As you did because you went to the Zen Zone
Yes yes no I can stay within the bounds of it
Oh okay
You're kind of in this limbo between death and life
And you have to stay within CityWalk
And only eat CityWalk food
Yes correct
That's already where we're kind of heading
That's essentially the jail we've put ourselves in
For the next 19 days and our listeners
And in fact we're heading there
Right from this recording
Not to tip
We are going to be at CityWalk a lot
In the next 19 days
Yeah we are
We sure are
Part of it is I think maybe we'll be frustrated
But part of me thinks maybe by day 19
We're fucking energetic
And we're like riding like a cocaine high
Of CityWalk like we may not like
Limb to the finish we may dead sprint
To the finish of the series
We may evolve to another plane of existence
Yeah well I'll say this
I'm afraid of where
This is going and where my
Stamina will be by the end of it
However at the moment
I feel very optimistic
And I want to just like
Commemorate that optimism with a little
Audio presentation
For this the first part of the 19
Part series
Mike if I could ask you to hold this up
Hold my phone up to the microphone
And press play
And I will begin this little opening day
Audio presentation
CityWalk this way
Just give me some PINGS!
Ah, that was fun
That represents my frame of mind right now
I hope my musical offerings
Were to your liking SectorKeeper
It was wonderful
It gave me strength
So much strength that
I feel like boys
Sector1 is complete
We did it!
Hooray! So wait
The stone! Yes yes Sector1's
Stone is now yours
Wow, there it is
It just appeared
I'll pick it up
Can you like spray that down
Like the ZenZone people just sanitize
Before we touch it
Okay
Before it goes skin to skin I'll take it
It's as if
It's as magical as holding up
To 40 nature company gems
Yes
We're all the flavors of popcornopolis
At once
SectorKeeper you will be
Not
You will be checking in throughout our journey
I will be your guardian as you
Venture into each of the sectors
And we have some fellow travelers
Who will be joining us
Oh yes indeed
Some new favorites
Some new guests who inexplicably
Are starting
Doing a first episode
Within this series
Good luck to them
The journey is long and hard
But fruitful
May I leave you with some words of wisdom
Of course
As you walk through the city walk
Remember, it is a place of commerce
It is a place of fun
And it is a place of food
Always, boys always
Yes
Go Raiders
Go Raiders indeed
Thank you for this motto
Thanks for checking out this episode
And we're serious
Check in for the next 18 days
Yes
In a row
There will be a new episode
Maybe not all this long
Although you know us
Could be
On Twitter, on Instagram
Facebook
Is this Facebook group happening?
Sectorkeeper, anything you'd like to plug?
I just would like to maybe reiterate
The more people that follow you
Rate and subscribe
The less likely it is that my soul is in hell
Oh great
Each follower gives you wings
Like tiny ones
Not like a full set
But by the time you've got like a thousand of them
There's an aggregate of wings that can
Kind of send your spirits
So now it's up to you listeners
Help save a ghost life?
For as the British S.A.S. say
Who dares wins
See you tomorrow
Forever
Dog
This has been a Forever Dog Production
Executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner
Brett Bohm
For more original podcasts
Please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows
On Apple Podcasts
Spotify
Or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
By following us on Twitter and Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam
And liking our page on Facebook