Forever!
Is
Welcome to podcast the ride the theme park podcast hosted by three guys you just had
a rip roaring pre-show argument about who is which country bear joining us.
I'm well I'm Scott Gardner and Jason Sheridan's here.
Mike Carlson is here.
That wasn't going to be the lion but I figure we might as well acknowledge it because if
it's real you've just the episode that you've just started is a podcast the ride post office
and hopefully somewhere on our Instagram or Twitter you've seen a logo in which were depicted
in small world form and we started talking about well if we were depicted as other theme
park characters right who would we be and we were we couldn't figure out country bears
exactly but some strong opinions were had yeah I mean we've on the podcast talked about
what we would name our children if they were all country bears but we have yet to talk
about who we are as country bears so it was a little bit rendered in a t-shirt or a yeah
just art on the on the Twitter I mean the audience now is of course yelling names of
country bears that they think we are so we'll just say what like I was saying Scott should
probably be Wendell I was saying I could probably be Henry or liver lips and then Jason wants
to be big Al it feels like but I said no he should not be big Al he should be the little
bear which I can't the little bear represents my like the vibe and mental state much more
sure oh sure yeah like the desperately grasping a teddy bear yeah you're not a big Al type
in real life I would never say you're a big Al type no I mean I'm slovenly well that's
fair yes but a very clean I pride myself on being well how clear are their types in general
well I think that you for sure get a sense of their character via the song they choose
and the way they perform so like Henry is of course like a very kind of like oh he's
a little stuffy and he wants to make sure the show goes right Henry is the I don't know
the country bears that well Henry is the host Henry is the host yeah he's got the raccoon
in his hat yes his raccoon tag and he kind of like chuckles like nervously when something
goes off the rails or when something's a little blue is that is that you I guess do I chuckle
when we go a little blue as you chuckle nervously as you ask I guess I'm like Henry so there
you go there's the proof what do we know about Wendell's personality Wendell is like seems
like a madman to me oh that's Scott big time yeah I could you maybe we're all Henry really
we're all I mean I'm a nervous laffer that's for sure okay so I feel like a Henry maybe
you're that maybe I'm Henry I sort of I don't know I'm not like the host I guess but I try
to be the guy who explains things such as if I try to talk to the people in the audience
who don't know every right bear by heart well Henry's trying to keep the show on the rails
so I guess there is some truth to that that would make sense to me mm-hmm I'm trying
to think other the the Sunbonnet trio well we all secretly want to be the Sunbonnet tree
what and if that makes sense because there's a there's a it's a trio obviously and there's
three of us and really the Sunbonnet trio I'll be very honest their game is that they're
all horny they're all looking for a man we all have low t though so that's not us oh
I don't agree with that Jason is a Jason honestly has bragged to me about having a high T before
he thinks he has high testosterone I am talking about I am all three of the horny bears so
maybe you're more Sunbonnet or you have as much testosterone as the three horny girl
bears that's what you're saying I was just trying to gauge like horny don't back off
of it that's what you was horny not it was hornyness not testosterone yes okay yeah
all right it is getting confusing yeah I did I am glad you you did use that joke though
because that feels very fitting for like the the mailbag the first post office episode
because it's like a rush overnight letter we had that conversation and seconds or a
minute later sure it became odd audio content for everyone to enjoy well people's ears yes
it feels good to be to be doing material as fast as the post office can turn it out no
better speed metaphor I do like that you know sometimes we end up having episodes in the
bank for a long time and it is nice to be able to to do stuff a little bit quicker with
hot off the wire theme park news sure as well as news for us and in our in our personal
win or within the world of the show which to that end we have an announcement yeah this
is the very first episode that is being released on our new podcast network yeah we did it
guys we have a podcast network again it's forever dog forever dog we're on forever dog
about it feels like a weird announcement to make because we're it's not as if we're surrounded
by forever dog people no yeah right now we're not recording it in a new place we're still
in the living room so it's it's feels hypothetical however we we are very excited about this
and I think I think it's gonna be a great arrangement they seem very excited about having
us on board and I think they are going to help take care of some logistical things that'll
let us focus on delivering pure raw great theme park rambles yeah yeah after week that
five minutes about which of country bear are we is they're gonna it's gonna be even better
yeah we're on forever dog because we're gonna be able to focus we're really gonna be able
to pinpoint which country bear each of us are exactly what Jason's testosterone level
is and does it compare to any of the other country bears we're gonna be able to do so
much better for you guys on forever dogs all excited forever dogs forever dog also features
podcasts such as teen creeps which your girlfriend Lindsay does true yes very good and and and
and lost culture East as with past guest Matt Rogers who was a lot of fun so we're we're
in the company of some some great fun podcast yeah yeah yeah for for young Jason sake if
you had told me when I was a kid like oh you will be on a podcast network with one of the
kids in the hall Kevin McDonald has a show on forever dog my favorite kid in the hall
I love being Kevin yeah I remember like an acting class where we had to like I was when
I was a freshman in high school and they're like do all right everyone find a monologue
to bring in next week and going to is it believe kids fan org oh yeah they had transcripts
of the hall monologues and I think we had to do it and then do it again like later so
I think I started with the Kevin McDonald monologue where he talks about like hitting
his head like go falling over his bin trying to get a bunch of mail and then hitting his
head but it has so many cutaways it didn't make sense oh that's right yeah yeah oh but
you tried to do that I tried to do it on stage just me and then I ended up changing to a
letter to the guy I clotheslined as he rode by on his bicycle oh okay fully monologue
okay okay wow wow I had a did at a in front of like hundreds of people at a Boy Scout
Jamboree for like the talent show you're trying to be all subversive and prove your cool taste
well also we didn't realize we had to have something and I was like well I did this for
an acting class a few weeks ago I still remember it so your talent was a kids in the hall monologue
that's pretty fun hey let's wait let's tie it together can you can we name the kids in
the hall theme park appearances because there's a few couple of them oh well Dave Foley on
tough to be a bug right on and some other I think yeah somewhere else in the soon to
be departed bugs at California Adventure but the other one oh Kevin McDonald in Stitch
is great right I assume there was original dialogue done for that he's does sound like
his character in the right does sound like him mm-hmm yeah I think I think he did new
stuff for that so the yeah kids and all representing in the finest theme park attraction but wait
now I'm thinking about the other is there I'm thinking about mr. show and isn't there
a John Ennis appearance oh yeah John Ennis is in I think we maybe talked about this in
the shit John Ennis I think is in something in Disney Quest oh I that sounds familiar
yeah yeah yeah and obviously Tom Kenny the voice of Spongebob in all of those odd regional
Spongebob there's I think there's like 19 Spongebob theme park attractions all oh yeah
they licensed the hell out yeah yeah looking up John Ennis Disney Quest and nothing pops
up hmm what to save it for the Disney Quest I feel like this came up though yeah again
great forever dog is gonna help us create more certainty to all of these questions that
we bring up and then don't answer right you're gonna find this is never gonna happen again
and it's thanks to forever dog yes changed a number of a lot of emails with them and
they've all been very prompt responses and very professional yes as opposed to past podcasts
and other podcasts networks we haven't been on and have only heard stories about so so
far email promptness email very excited about and I hope you guys are excited about that
too polite in person great more emails no I am I think this is gonna be great and also
you know we're coming off of our first live show hopefully some people listening got to
go if you didn't get to go if you enjoyed listening to the episode but I think with
forever dog we're gonna try to do that more often yeah we won't we won't always be meeting
childhood heroes live on stage but we got some fun live show ideas and forever dogs
gonna help with that so yeah we're gonna keep this keep this show on the road very cool
yeah and also big news and podcast the right world under the forever dog banner next week
we will finally be releasing long-awaited podcast the ride event the city walk saga
the saga begins the saga begins we teased it in may whatever date that is yeah what
day are we doing it is it the fourth I believe it's it's yeah the 14th okay September 14
September 14 oh boy here we go at last I won't I mean we'll do we can tease a little bit
but we got to save it mostly for for listening yeah yeah all I can say there's a lot of there's
a lot of surprises a lot of fun guests a lot of a lot of old favorites and people venturing
into the right cast the right waters for the first time right and some very complex storytelling
awaits in the city walk saga this is it this is a 19 part series yes no joke to begin yes
that actually people laugh when I told them about it and they go haha and then I go no
we it's 19 there's 19 of them well you're the original when you first pitched it it
was if we did an episode about city walk and we said part one of 19 yes and then that was
obviously not going to be true and then it slowly just became true yeah let it wash over
us and it is true now I'm very exhausted but but happily so I mean I don't want to get
into that we're not done doing work no no no no yeah a lot and it was essentially our
summer vacation this is just may as well be called city walk saga our summer vacation
how I spent my summer vacation at the end of the day we will have done more hours on
city walk than like the best rides at any of these theme parks yeah and because there
are very few themed attractions yo very almost nothing you would quantify as an attraction
would you count Zen zone the Aqua massages as a that almost is somehow that's somehow
closer to a ride to me yeah if you were to theme Zen zone to an IP maybe I could see
it being an attraction but other than that it's just sort of us I guess a service if
it was like themed to seems like a water world seems like a missed opportunity for water
world or to me for whatever reason I first think of when they load mr. Spock's corpse
into a photon torpedo at the end of Star Trek wrath of Khan or you could pretend you're
in the you're one of the Superman villains trapped oh that's good the Phantom Zone the
Phantom Zone right or you could be young Kal-El in the rocket rocket yeah for whatever and
then you can you have to explain away why you're getting massaged by water but whatever
there's a gotta be some sort of imaginary way to justify pods Universal released the
eat prey love movie you could also go that angle what do you mean oh I see like you're
just having a nice weekend new well starting a new you're getting your age in your life
you're getting your groove back and you're relaxing and I see yeah you could do it more
on the nose like like it could be like a Stella got her groove back yeah themed extra attraction
would people on the internet be upset with the anti IP crowd be furious to see the original
story of Zen zone yeah co-opted by the monsters behind the love franchise petitions to get
rid of the you pray love overlay return it to its former glory of the Zen zone it's just
a cheap quick they just they know they slapped a coat of paint on it and they expect me to
pay more now the purity of the Zen zone experience destroyed anyway if you liked that there's
a lot more stuff like that coming up and I wonder what what do what's the response of
the audience who are not in Hollywood or LA who have not been to LA who now get to hear
19 episodes but every excruciating detail yeah I'd like to think that we brought City
Walk to life yeah in an audio fashion and there's gonna be a glut of Twitter ancillary
content during this time and that'll help you know make it a multi-dimensional experience
right but I don't know does this shut out the people not lucky enough to be within the
zone of City Walk Hollywood oh I don't think so yeah I think we're bringing it to them
you're right we're providing a service yeah we're shoving 65 stores and restaurants straight
into their ears yeah our listeners like if they're not in California or Florida they
are aware of City Walk they know what downtown Disney is they know what a weird mall is outside
these theme parks maybe they don't have as much they probably don't because they don't
live around here in Florida they don't have as much time to just waste over at a weird
mall that's right out that's hard to get to and it's expensive to park like horrible parking
situation yes we'll get into yes so yeah but we know we have a lot of time to waste we
know a lot of people who have created who who don't have time to this people with children
and children on the way who have taken important valuable time to sit around with us hours
and hours of time with us but the bonus like to all this like you know you know if you
have Amazon Prime you get all this bonus crap with you know you get like you get all the
streaming stuff and you get the the free blending books the ebooks and all that crap I don't
know anything about that continue so but the bonus with the City Walk is you get to listen
to three men in their 30s stare into the gaping mall of madness and will they come out the
other side like changed and broken or who will they just come out like a few hundred
dollars poorer each I mean that's probably true yeah I think both yeah not to no spoilers
but yes that yeah but also maybe just with a better stronger appreciation for this wonderful
place yeah that's really what I'm thinking and a desire to eat better and treat yourself
better and not jam buka de beppo and maybe what I've taken out of it so far is I need
a diet with less fried calamari and I'm gonna try to get to that as soon as we're done that's
lightly because the official flag of City Walk is just a chunk of fried calamari the
tentacles flapping in the wind yeah also the city bird bird bird city fish Jesus Christ
is the official bird and losing my mind already fried calamari which Ludo is still furious
about oh yeah Ludo of Ludo bird is still come on it's not even a bird why can it not be
my bird Ludo heavy French accent oh oh is that okay yes heavy that's so heavy I couldn't
even tell what it was yeah you need some we'll try to put subtitles on that part of the podcast
somehow well so that's that's news going on in our world but before we start getting into
some some letters that that y'all have sent there's very important news and theme park
world to report and Jason I'll throw it to you sure yeah you know you guys know me I
am probably the biggest as Matt Rogers had called himself and I would call myself the
same the biggest universal Stan among the three of us Stan about what's still like big
fans of something what does it come from what is it oh he comes from the Eminem song Stan
oh it does yeah no no the original version of it but it now just means like super like
the years about stands on the internet yeah dear Stan and Stan is an obsessive fan who
you want to be a Stan Stan kills the original etymology but now it just means more like
people who are really into like still don't care for it hearthstone or Ariana Grande and
stuff anyway this is a big tangent already no thank you I didn't know what it meant what
nice news for Ariana Grande that she's got a lot of stands waiting around yeah yeah actually
I'm Davidson looks like Stan with the dyed blonde hair is does look like Stan he looks
exactly like I would go ahead he's gonna kill her I would go and call her him the biggest
Ariana Grande Stan I'm the biggest Stan once he gets the tattoo yeah so some big news out
of Universal this summer a lot of media coverage you know a lot of people were down there for
this I think we all know what I'm talking about folks the wimpy's hamburger stand at
islands of adventure reopened this summer for the first time in years wow so now you're
probably you are probably expecting me for a long time yeah I'm sure listeners were
probably like oh he's talking about the Aventura Hotel Universal's latest move in an attempt
to slowly turn all of Orlando into hotels range hotels sure I don't think anyone was
thinking about the Aventura Hotel I was not I the host of the theme park podcast show
I have no thoughts about Aventura well that's the only other news out of universal this
summer so well there is news that they're possibly starting to build a fourth park yeah
that's true I mean it's not a track they filed some permits to expand a road down there fantastic
worlds but whatever doesn't matter let's focus on the here and now focus on this character
that wimpy's I mean everyone knows wimpy from Popeye oh everyone knows everyone knows him
and I'll gladly pay you Tuesday for a hamburger today and this is one of the seven different
old-timey cartoon characters we've compared you to on the episode of islands of adventure
yes I a dear friend that I admire and this hamburger stand it's very charming it's not
super like themed it's just a little cute cute little how long was it closed when did
they close it I am honestly not sure and I am not sure if it was ever open I believe
it you know it would have been open right when it first opened and then I'm gonna do
some may have went seasonal but it has so it's like its its origins are in question
and it's been dark for a long time for a long time it's almost like this the wimpy's hamburger
stand is the hat box ghost of islands of adventure yes long rumored long dreamed about by fans
copious fan art but only now do we finally get to experience it or like a sizable chunk
of future world and Epcot oh yeah yeah remember when I had rides and stuff in it yeah body
world what sorry what are you wife and the the restaurant right at the edge of future
world I'll see so when these hamburgers stand reopened for this summer and honestly I was
having trouble seeing if it was even still open because we're into as we record this
we've hit the slow a slower season for theme parks until the Halloween season kicks into
full gear so and I the thing I thought was interesting about this is just how if I'm
being nice I'll say unique if I'm being a little more critical how odd this menu was
so that's as mean as you get when you're talking about wimpy's hamburger stand yeah because
I don't want to hurt his feelings so brother through time what are you looking at of course
you're looking at hamburgers you got your bacon cheeseburger you got your specialty
burger which is a spinach special sauce topped with a sunny side up egg which is a very
odd combination wait repeat that again spinach special sauce surprise thousand island huh
topped with a sunny side up egg you mean this just seems excessive no it's just a lot of
disparate elements because the spinach would be weird ye spinach and thousand island and
the sunny side up egg I mean I guess the spinach Popeye you know oh oh so then it makes perfect
sense it makes sense I'm just thinking about eating that it seems like a lot going on and
then of course you got a footlong hot dog onion sauerkraut jalapenos that is an interesting
combination of hot dog toppings and then what do you want for the vegetarians of course
a grilled fish pita blackened cod lettuce caramelized onions pineapple salsa with a
vegetarian menu yeah pescatarian pescatarian there's not a vegetarian option at wimpy's
that would be insane well there is a caprese salad and a fruit plate okay and then all
of the combos are served with fries and a milkshake so like you got a milkshake coming
in oh so everything in wimpy's has a milkshake it comes with a milkshake I'm sure there
is a non milkshake suggested option it's cramped this milkshake and this is injected
into the bun this is a new menu what we yes so this is a like is the spinach egg thing
new do you know yeah I mean that that I think is like new a egg on a burger uh while a popular
regional delicacy in upstate and central New York you've never there's a plenty of burgers
with eggs on them out here yeah but yeah there is now but I feel like you see that until
a few years that that is like a food trend now you put an egg I feel like is it mcdonald's
been around for over five oh I don't know if they did one of those like I feel like
it's it's hitting critical mass like sriracha or you know cronut that sort of right um
is it like now new I don't know what your like maybe a decade ago of the egg was having
I do think the egg is not as recent as you think it is I guess so but that's like in
Los Angeles like I feel like I've got an egg on a burger at a pub like eight years ago
on Ventura somewhere yeah again but this is a major metropolitan center if you went to
the middle of the country would you see that I bet there's like diners are you more likely
to see it because it's like a big rich thing uh I think you're more likely to see it at
a boot at an LA bougie hamburger place it's not like it's kale even though kale's still
like a joke thing like for like the Midwest oh cool you're gonna put kale on it or something
like my dad also be like okay oh hummus like that's to me a little bit more even hummus
yeah yeah we're talking dads here this is dad stuff I guess my dad understands a big
fried egg on a big piece of beef he gets that that makes sense to him I don't know if he'd
have it but I don't think he's gonna go oh yuck but if I eat like pita chips with hummus
well what are you talking about what is this my dad doesn't I took him to a Thai restaurant
one time and ever since then it's been like you know if we want to go out to dinner like
well let's go get you know let's get some get some real food not no rat tail stew or
you know my dad is a pigeon-eye pie let's not do I like that they're all like witch
like witches foods he thinks that all Thai chefs are witches they've achieved this food
through voodoo yeah food you would put in a big cauldron my dad does not like the joke
when I go yeah let's just go somewhere so dad can get a grilled cheese sandwich he gets
very cranky about that joke I think if I could if I could kind of interpret in a therapist
manner and think one step ahead for you I think maybe what you're reacting to with these
menu items is that if you're taking wimpy's ideal of the perfect burger what it should
be is plain no cheese no sauce no lettuce the meat and the bun and there should be three
steam lines coming out of it and it should be unadorned well otherwise traditionally
yeah there'd probably be some horse meat in there too if we're talking real wimpy depression
error yeah the 30s okay but I actually think wimpy now a more progressive modern wimpy
would probably be open to experimental hamburgs my larger point wimpy into the 21st century
isn't he stuck sort of in his time there's been no like modern wimpy yeah that's like
making that's like a 2018 Austin Powers there's no such thing he's just a 60s guy I think
he would be interesting if we brought wimpy to the modern day and took him to like umami
burger or something he'd be like oh what interesting hamburger developments I think that's exactly
what you said when we went to umami for the first time I think that's right so I think
we're sitting here talking to the I would also like I if any of our wonderful uh artist
listeners uh which are all 2018 well wimpy dabbing that would be terrific choked on my
drink yeah I'd be curious how wimpy's clothing is changed does he just just still dress the
same or is it kind of maybe it's like skinny tie or I think yeah I don't think wimpy's
spending a lot on clothing yeah but he could be like a kind of a like a thrift store guy
who can find a nice can put a nice outfit together with cheap like with cheap clothes
oh I think that yeah that's probably accurate because like jughead like wimpy to me was
always like uh an older jughead it was a very similar character like oh just obsessed with
food pretty asexual but the cw they took jughead and jughead is sexy now and brooding and brooding
so oh so maybe what we want to see is a river daleified pop-eye universe oh just in general
I mean I don't want to make this assignment so so big that people put it off and don't
get it done let's just let's you know start with a wimpy and see where your brain goes
yeah that's that sounds smart and then if you want to move on to poop deck pappy poop
deck pappy sweepy and poppy poppies father yeah yeah yeah that's that's his name um jason
character favorite character in fiction poop deck pappy yeah uh but big picture view I
think uh when I was in universal last summer there was like a standover in lost continent
uh and the the combination there are combos one of the oddest things but I liked it that
I had ever had uh you got a euro you got a lamb and beef euro you got a side of hummus
and carrots and then you got a slice of apple pie so kind of strange or or a brookie that
was the one thing I noticed at universal last summer half uh cookie half brownie oh they
were pushing that everywhere at universal like last year uh last time I was there so
my bigger picture is I'm thinking ahead to this new universal park I think they need
to ramp up their food offerings okay like the thing I like about this menu is like there
is some variety in it more than just like basic hamburger basic hot dog veggie burger
like just throw it at you it tends to be the case at the Florida parks more than the California
parks although up until recently universal Hollywood's food offerings were pretty rough
yes so uh my my assignment to any universal creatives listening get amp on this food program
it's not for universal park but it's not universal creatives problem because we've talked about
this before what's gonna happen is they're gonna come up with some amazing dishes some
amazing cool stuff it's gonna be open for three weeks and none of it's gonna sell dads
are gonna go who's this hummus or what is this uh rat-tailed uh stew here like what
is it and then they're gonna go it's not selling we gotta just throw a chicken sandwich
on there right you say that but the harry potter menus are pretty much unchanged they
swap stuff in and out every now and then the avatar menus the avatar is the anomaly the
avatar you're right the avatar is the anomaly the new areas you know maybe give you license
to it's like part of the world's to do something a little more unusual what's um I mean presumably
it seems like the rumor is that Mario is gonna be saved for yes universal park super Nintendo
what do we get in what does Mario eat does he mushrooms of course certainly mushrooms
so you got some I mean obviously some like portobello mushroom burgers but then we want
to I want to see those bright and bold I want to see them red with white spots I think they
should have like tell you have giant turkey legs giant mushrooms that you can eat so they
have whatever antibiotics not or whatever growth hormone they put into the turkey leg
put into the mushroom fields and let's get some giant mushrooms going you order it just
at a counter but then to retrieve it you have to jump up hit a box with your head and then
catch it as it slides over to the right and they grease the bottom of the mushroom up
so it slides very easily so it's like slippery out of your hand so it takes a little while
to grab it don't catch it you don't eat doesn't matter that doesn't matter yeah yeah that's
your responsibility that's fun mm-hmm yeah so there's an idea get the figure out those
those launching boxes Star Trek would be Star Trek people eat oh my god fully whatever they
want they have a replicator that can replicate any dish that was ever made they just tell
the computer obviously there's gonna you're gonna have to get if if this is a rumor of
course more I think Nintendo land for sure is going in that third part okay Star Trek
is a rumor going in this I hadn't heard that third park huh I don't know if that would
be the case you'll have to be able to get Picard's tea order Earl Grey hot oh perfect
for your old grey hot is what Picard famously would always drink sure so you'll be able
to go up to a machine and get a hot tea in the middle of the summer you know what I saw
at the boardwalk in Jersey this summer a lot of Stan selling like stands stands oh no stay
away selling stuff with dry ice in it like drinks kind of bubbling with dry ice didn't
they Star Trek bar quarks I will quarks bar had some like dry ice they had it in Vegas
the quarks bar so yes you could do they could make like a Romulan ale or something which
is like the illegal alcohol drink in the universe it's so potent I guess is why Romulan ale
was illegal but other than that you know they all they all can eat what they want from any
time in the past because it's the 23rd or 24th century depending on what show you're
talking about hmm you think the new park will have an area devoted to Eminem and all of
the characters in his songs in the musical world you could you could visit the purple
hills oh yeah from the the D12 song picture with Stan get all his alter egos the little
all of G unit be present that's are they part of yeah I guess yeah they're related 50 cent
is sort of oh I'm sorry I'm yeah mixing it up he's the part of the expanded lineup like
the Disneyland big five or is that right it's big five they wouldn't be part of the but
on like bigger carrot photo opportunity days yeah you'd probably get G unit around big
plush headed Eminem D12 right I guess Dr. Dre yeah you have to because he's like the Walt
Disney of Eminem mm-hmm and all those characters does that make Eminem Mickey it knows well
wait what do you mean yeah he's Mickey well in this universe he's I'm thinking but though
in dr.
Dre's career the first person he produced are you thinking about opening it up to where
it's a Dre land well that's what now yes that's why I bristled at it initially and then the
Walt partners statue is dr. Dre and Jimmy Iovine of course Jimmy Ivy is absolutely then on
the statue yeah but I mean like this some ride where you get to go around in giant beats
headphones and yeah well the everything beats stamped upon everything even though they sold
to Apple though so yeah so I guess Apple has to have a presence too yeah oh maybe this
will give Eminem a chance to finally have he could turn into a themed attraction he
was supposed to start a remake of have gun will travel that's true yeah he was attached
to that I forget whether it was a TV show or a movie and it just never happened hmm
it's too bad classic Western have gone will travel so Eminem's so Eminem's going into
the fourth park and then going into the fourth yep all right Mario Star Trek Eminem the world
of Eminem the world of Eminem you'll get to see Eminem's face in a planter like Mickey
yes flowers forming Eminem's head and there'll be like a phantasmag style show called the
Eminem show oh yeah yeah the Eminem show yes yeah triumph the insult comic yeah famous
Eminem character will about Bruno will be there gotta be there oh well that's the the
phantasmag is Eminem doing battle against all his enemies oh yeah Bruno his mom yeah
and of course of course Stan Stan of course yeah giant like the Maleficent yes yeah yeah
yeah and that cues us up perfectly we know what the food offering is at the end of that
part of sure I guess you say it mom spaghetti oh yes I can't believe I forgot that's the
merch do you buy a t-shirt it's got a little yeah this purposeful stains all over it on
it wow all right so as we said big news coming out of Universal Eminem land with these wimpy's
is the opening shot of the next generation of Universal yeah yeah JK Rowling and the
visionaries like JK Rowling and Eminem will take universal into the next take a seat take
a breath stop tweeting for a little while does he tweet a lot huh no JK Rowling sure
sure sure okay well one more bit of news before we get into your question let's continue to
make this about us before we make it about the audience this has always been about us
oh yeah oh no no no certainly but what what podcast is very yeah exactly prerogative but
when it hey when it when it comes to the world of me something big news pretty big it happened
then if you follow us on on Twitter then you know about it already but in the wake of the
Tony Baxter live show interview and all of his encouragement I didn't want to let him
down I wanted to make good on the promise and I have now been on splash mountain wow
congratulations and I did it now in 18 years yeah or 17 18 something like that yeah I think
I went in high school one time I think didn't enjoy the experience and so I gave it a go
now I knew like I thought there's a couple ways to do this either I could make this podcast
content and then I'd be knee deep into Scott goes to splash mountain episode five right
which is what we wanted oh yeah yeah yeah and I and I I knew if I cut I could cut that
off at the pass with but because here's the genuinely I was freaked out enough to where
I don't think it would have been funny to record unless I'm just not aware I think I
was just like weird and sullen kind of like in the couple hours leading up to it did you
know like was it a day like you were like knew you were gonna do it or was it the day
of you were like I'm gonna do it and then you kind of got freaked out I I had a feeling
before I went down and then we had a plot look we were down at the Aaron and I were
down at the 94 7 the wave Sunday Sunday jazz brunch at Spaghetti Bar and Grill and Seal
Beach we'd spent the night in Orange County in order to catch some great live jazz and
eat some great to eat a great seafood buffet and we had a great time so I was riding high
on mimosas went to Disneyland renewed the pass I haven't been in six months and you
know so I was riding high having a nice little little morning buzz and it was you know easier
to say then than when it wears off and it because we got the max pass for the the end
of the day so as those hours are ticking up you know it the dread was forming for sure
right to where like I was enthusiastic about it at two but by seven rolling around like
oh am I actually and Aaron keeps trying to give me the outs you know you don't you don't
have to you don't know these people anything sure like no but I do this has to happen I
it just it it felt like that had to be the time post Tony right but I will I will say
it will like I truly what there there was more nervous bathroom time spent then probably
in in a day in a decade of me so more than more than like going out to perform a live
show more than any of that ever more than an audition of some kind yes that's what I'm
saying my like I feel very lucky I feel like my nerves kind of got worked out of me in
terms of like really being wrecked by stuff you know in the somewhere between 2010 and
2012 and truly I have not had this much like nervous body activity in I wasn't that nervous
to to meet Tony himself and to talk to him I was not like freaking out or nervous stomach
but to go on the fucking ride which I've been I've done it and it's not that bad right
but serious I've just built it up so I think just now the the just so much time has passed
and I do think something as we unlocked when we on our episode about it I think earnest
goes to Splash Mountain is really responsible yeah I made it more mentally terrifying which
you say you were as nervous as say like a freestyle rapper in Detroit about to take
the stage your arms are heavy palms sweaty arms are sweaty potentially sounds like yes
exactly right absolutely mom you were the white rabbit uh-huh rabbit rabbit his name
was rabbit oh his name was just right yeah the white rabbit his name was rabbit right
yeah is he called quite the white I mean he is white he's a white man yeah I'm assuming
they were that came from that nickname yeah you ever have just one moment to go on a log
flume ride to keep your arms and legs in the vehicle sir please hurry up a line is forming
you better flume yourself a little girl is clowning on your ass I'm seeing B rabbit rapper
B rabbit Eminem and eight mile mm-hmm okay anyway yeah this was my lose yourself moment
absolutely I mean the walk like walk it getting into the line was one thing to actually I
read I'm stepping in and doing it huh and then get at like being in the getting into
the vehicle and it taking off Aaron was very much like you did it you're in yours even
just getting in was it was a big deal and and I seriously do blame earnest because I
when I when you round a corner and you see that that loading zone I had all these like
these flashbacks to this was that the most stressful part of it it was like right before
you got on or was it right before the drop um no you know what by that because by then
there was no choice right obviously it's it's gonna happen you've been dropped and I and
I had fun you know what I was worried about is that if the first one would like affected
me bad if I was scared of the first little drop then I knew I was screwed but I but that's
that was a ton of fun the second one's a ton of fun and I remembered that going on that
whenever I went on it before the first one was a little much oh really weak little 15
year old me so I knew that I figured that the last one would be fine but getting in
the log is one big thing getting in the actually entering the line was one thing it was so
you you went in easily it wasn't like trying to put like a cat in a bathtub to watch like
you were like your feet were on the sides and they were trying to like two workers were
pushing you down forcing you into this log flume oh boy yeah that's too close to home
for me and Aaron has Aaron has a scar from that very oh sure that very situation bathing
Edwin the podcast ride show dog is very tough for me he doesn't have the legs with to do
that on the tub I do the same when you bathe me sure you that's just a joke you know when
I bathe you you go in very peacefully and you like it yeah I slowly lie down you actually
have to get me like my head out of the water because I'm lying down like I was like in
a coffin I just put your dish next to the tub and you have some water and you're fine
for it every time logically I know it's a trick but yeah you have enjoyed relaxing three
and a half hour tub nap mm-hmm no that it was all fine although you know this this also
another part of the reason I haven't been on it a long time is that Aaron Aaron had
not been on it in a decade either right because she she's fine with the drops but she is not
fine with theme park water dirty she does not go to water parks she's never been on
grizzly river rapids she is and she tries to avoid splash man although she likes the
ride a lot but she considers all these things giant Petri dishes sure and whereas I had
a fun experience and realized oh this is a great ride and I should have conquered my
fears long ago and made this part of my regular ride vernacular I don't think Aaron learned
anything I don't think going on the ride made her any more comfortable with being splashed
by dirty water so you know I don't know that I'm gonna be constantly going on but anyways
it was tense for both both of us were kind of grumbly right about it because she knew
what was and the first drop she got splashed so I just absolutely so so that was a real
evil okay which I did because we talked about it on the podcast I didn't get tricked by
that bear butt because that's kind of that's the idea is that you're looking up at that
and laughing going hey like Jason and then you look at that but caught off guard but
no by the time and the actual the drop was great it's fun it's fun as hell I was determined
that I'm gonna like because I was like laughing and enjoying it on the way down I went to
my laughing place and I thought well the photo will reflect that but the photo if you saw
it on her Twitter I look terrified as shit it's like me and dinosaur I thought I was
like I'm doing good and then I took a look at it and I was like cowering in fear I hate
it's so funny what's what can be in your head versus physical reality but I did I did enjoy
it a lot and I and the the feeling of euphoria after I was truly deeply excited and to get
what you had made a major step you had done nothing yeah that one that one loomed large
and it makes me think maybe there is some more room for me to try some other stuff and
to start going on rides that I did go on years ago but that you know but now I haven't been
on in a long time because of because my my wife is nice it doesn't make sure but you
know that's what's so funny about all this is like you know I should do in credit coaster
I'll do in credit coaster you've done screaming yeah I did you did I did it twice in the day
oh yeah that I did or 15 whenever my college girlfriend Jenna was you know held the bar
higher was a little more demanding sure so thus I did in that day the first time I ever
went to California venture I did do tower terror I did Malibu and I did California twice
yeah yeah I never did that was horrible that I would never I think I yeah look same as
Dr. Dooms Fearful same thing I'm not doing an ad what never done Dr. Dooms the story
about Dr. Doom needing your fear I know Dr. Dooms Fear Juice store now you're right look
now that I'm a theme park journalists maybe I got to go on these and you got to do stamp
because that is I mean that's a whole nother episode of universal needing to you know the
when they build this new park the express lines you got to make sure to get the story
in there because the kind of cut off some of the story to do a little better a little
better but not but not I'm sorry you lose a lot of the fun stuff if you go fast pass
so so yes well look I you know I'm not I'm not gonna start declaring that I'm going
on everything but I feel more open I feel I've I have not disproven no launch queen
no no I've but my own mental no splash queen I feel over I believe I am over it and next
time what I what I guess what I am right now still if you're quantifying things in queendom
I still am a no look queen because I I did close my eyes though time next time I will
look I will okay I will have a less embarrassing photograph right and I will go next time we're
all there together I will know all right I'll be excited to do it can I and this might be
putting the cart before the horse if you had a next ride to conquer we're gonna tease the
audience a little bit about that what do you think of all the rides you go well that one
less severe than the next one I'm thinking about doing a tower I'm thinking about doing
the California Screamin or I'm still not I don't know towers tough towers do you think
towers the biggest maybe could maybe that's the one to keep building although I did it
I did it one time right like I did I derive no pleasure from that which is but you know
part of the having Splash Mountain be off limits for so long was stupid because the
rest of it is such a blast I feel you can get over the one it's exactly what Tony said
it's your you're scared for 10 minutes but then you get three minutes of pure pleasure
and let me tell you he was right on I lived it that yeah I enjoyed that showboat sequence
more than any note with all of the build up now and that the man himself blessed this
journey and he was right it was great but tower terror I don't know I guess I do want
to experience guardians well because they did do at least they added like old pop songs
yes sure like they're trying to lure you a little bit like hey we got some old songs
on here we got Benatar if you want to hear some Benatar in a way besides on Jack FM there
is a way they play what they want they might not even hear it and they don't want it and
Guardians drops you how they want yeah we want how we want they I mean truly the universe
was like we'll add some pop songs and a robot mm-hmm it wasn't a robot before either in
the show I would like to see that guy you got to see that robot yeah I don't know maybe
we get to tower so boy but I'm just look we reset it no I know I'm just saying in the
future is it or is it rock and roller coaster is that the next oh I you know I think I could
do rock and roller cuz you think that might be the easiest next step yeah is this that
launch as opposed to screaming you know really this is a question for the next Florida visit
sure fair enough cuz I because there will be a lot we I should try to get more on the
table what else you know what I've never done Expedition Everest oh fantastic yeah great
no one does not seem how are the drops on that thing pretty I would like a slightly
heightened big Thunder Mountain yeah there's there's one you go backwards okay and it's
a little like you get a little in your stomach but it's not that bad and you really can't
tell it's backwards cuz it's all in the dark I though have never been I have not been in
Animal Kingdom while that's been open right so I'm not avoiding I love I'm not avoiding
expedition well I'll hit that but I don't know the I think whenever a Florida trip occurs
yeah let's try to rock and rollers is maybe a good one yeah cuz I need to I need to see
Steven Tyler's new hand first of all is his new hand and as on lewd hand and as the radio
DJ says check out his new hat check out Steven Tyler's new hat I do got to see the hat and
if enduring a roller coaster is what it takes then I will do it and that has many different
Aerosmith songs you can hear too so oh boy well now we are in Xanadu weren't but no jaded
the best there was a song we have established bummer on that I think maybe playing in the
gift shop but yeah okay thank you but not you know you know what's my bigger thing you're
I you know we I don't think we've we haven't recorded a ton since the live show with Tony
and he talks about that 12 year old self thing keeping your 12 year old self alive and I
what I what is funny to me is that I felt like with this experience I did flash right
back to 12 year old self I am as scared as a 12 year old like how often in your 30s do
you get to be like like genuinely freaked by an experience often you get to go I did
it wow I crowbarred off layers and layers of irony built up like sediment to reveal
this 12 year old that's how it felt if it was on my Instagram but I don't think I I
don't know if I put it on the Twitter but I'll post along with this I have my the photo
of me right after and it looks like me I'm in the same pose that I was in like pictures
of me at 10 years old in an Indiana Jones Halloween costume if there is zero irony in
how I looked having conquered Splash Mountain it felt great and you know what I was doing
way better than earnest was sure he was acting like it wasn't a big deal on the way up he
was kicking back he said wish I'd run a book but then after the thing he was freaked and
he fell backwards into the log not me I did it with flying colors and so I'm way better
than earnest I was not scared stupid it's got yours hashtag better than earn better
than earnest yeah let's get that no launch Queen out of here and get a much cooler hatch
that could be both yeah it can be both it can be both but I also speak it tying it all
together I need to do the I need now to do the launch coaster with the voice of earnest
oh yeah I guess it's not what he does his voice is not on it but he originated right
link dog so that'll really be the test of if I'm better than earnest hmm maybe that
is the coaster for children you mean the ultimate test will be this this coaster that looks
like a child's toy all right congratulations thank you I feel great and now that we've
talked for an hour or so all right let's get to some of your questions if we have to hey
the pod podcast the ride post office is open is open all right well let's start it off
with a letter from was a letter huh was it a letter digital oh I see a mess friend of
the show Kia Burton writes in oh hey I'm an LA local and I go to Disneyland and Universal
Studios Hollywood a lot right now I am planning my first ever trip to Orlando scheduled for
early February I have six full days there total and I'm thinking in general that means
one day for each Disney park and one day for each Universal park excluding the water parks
hmm I know this is not enough time Scott is wrong but it's the most time I can get away
from work please help me figure out how to best allocate my limited time which ride should
I structure my day around which words are potentially skippable during a short trip
should I still buy or should I still buy park hopper tickets for Disney should I go back
and forth within a day which parks should I go to on the weekdays versus which parks
are most manageable yeah one question wow this is insane first of all Jason you had
to prep us for this because this is a project for me I know I know I still have advice restaurants
that are essential should I stay on property basic stuff I know we weren't gonna hit all
of this but other listeners have also written in with itineraries I think I thought some
basic suggestions about like marquee rides at each park maybe a restaurant sure sure
well here's here's what okay so she has six days six and a half days yeah and then she's
thinking hit them four main parks and the two universal parks so I'm gonna start off
by saying I think park hoppers would be a wise investment do you oh I completely agree
park hopping is the way to do it that's one of my favorite things to do you go somewhere
at night you go somewhere in the morning yeah I'm don't go nuts with it and go to like all
four parks in a day because then you're wasting so much travel times transit transit wise
but yeah like what I will say but what's good about park hopper and if you're staying I
don't know if she's staying on site at Disney the thing to do is check the extra magic hours
of course yeah because sometimes they have the park open if you're staying on site an
hour or two early hour too late so you figure out that's how I would that's my first recommendation
if you're doing that structure your day versus like if Epcot is now open like two extra hours
just for people that are at the hotels you do Epcot that night or and then you do if
there was a in the morning Magic Kingdom was open and you do it then so like that's how
I think you first start structuring your day is just looking at the basic hours for the
park and then addition seeing what the extra magic hours are let's do I want to get into
some like into some Sophie's choices yes yeah what with that limited time frame you try
to hit all of the parks and I think you can yeah what do you condense what doesn't get
the full day in order to give time to other things I think at this point Hollywood studios
you could probably hit the marquee events and have a decent meal there and then go to
marquee rides you mean yeah marquee rides and then I eat it what do you decent meal
at mg I well they got the cafe that's okay well hold on hold on because there are a lot
of the restaurants have not closed at Hollywood Studios so like mom Melrose is like wood-fired
Italian my family always like that but also like for theme stuff you had the 50s primetime
diner you got the sci-fi dying so there's a lot of that but I think a lot of adults
really enjoy Epcot so I would give Epcot a little extra time that's why I'm saying you
try to do Hollywood Studios in half a day right down the way he a good friend of my
wife and I yeah she's she's got to do as much Epcot as possible no one her yeah it's got
to be a lot of it's here my honestly my recommendation you spend a lot of time in Epcot you spend
a lot of time in animal kingdom I think animal kingdom is great as an adult I was really
like this place is cool it's very themed it's like it's like two or three rides away from
being like killer but it's great it's fantastic and now I have a tar land is very cool those
rides are great so yeah I think you're your focus is Epcot and animal kingdom do you crunch
a magic kingdom a little bit because it's a lot of stuff you know that's yes that's
sort of that's a great point yeah you go on you go and see go on the old rickety space
mountain you go on pirate or no well yeah pirates you can but it's sort of better here
you go on jungle cruise for sure because jungle cruise is better in Florida than it is out
here there's an extra little scene and there's I like it so much more you're missing the
big two carousel of progress and people move her you don't have those if we're talking
big two country bears has to be in that the country bears is the greatest show in theme
park history you gotta see country bears I love the GD country bears and that's not
ironic at all it's fantastic I should leave a self censorship was not ironic at all no
because I was wanted to be so pure when I was making that comment so so magic kingdom
yeah there's a lot of stuff that is out here very similar yeah you know you skip for sure
you're like you know you're you're you're astro blasters yeah all that don't do even
out of you know morbid curiosity I'd say don't do a Stitch's great escape I would say train
don't do the topia but you got it yeah carousel of progress people mover country bears the
stuff we don't have any more yeah and you gotta see our president at the Hall of Presidents
oh for sure that's very and there's a great Muppet show a live Muppet show they do every
hour ish outside of that that I really think oh yeah people speak very highly of ten minutes
and you get to see real puppets and it's great mm-hmm yeah I would say I would say do you
need to eat at Magic Kingdom do you need to I mean if you're gonna eat a fast a crappy
fast service go to sunny eclipse go to cosmic oh yeah you gotta at least walk in and see
sunny and see a song or two oh you definitely do but that way can we do really quickly explain
not everybody she might not know sunny eclipse any clips a piano playing lounge lizard space
creature yes plays in this Tomorrowland restaurant it's not the restaurant isn't cosmic rays
is it cosmic rays star like okay okay stunning eclipse is the the act he's the man yeah yeah
just do a quick meal there and catch the Sony eclipse show you got to yeah or we had a drink
and just walk in and sit down in front because generally the place is not packed like I feel
it should be anytime I've been in there in the last couple years it's huge yes it is
and he's yeah so so anyway I'm saying you can get like a front row seat to see Sonny
yeah do you skip fantasy land do you skip it if you've never seen fill our magic that's
kind of fun but the screen is real blurry and like dark now but it is a fun show I think
these hours count I think seven dwarfs is great and of course if you're gonna eat a
nice meal try be our guest if you can get it or liberty tree tavern to see to do the
uh the olympic food do what I did and eat all you can eat meal um at liberty tree tavern
which is good a real solid like thanksgiving style meal so we can talk about this forever
I mean yeah but that may also be a day to investigate either a meal at the Polynesian
or the contemporary if you want a whole thing well that's so you get there needs to be a
little bit of hotel a little bit of which to which with six days you don't got a lot
of time for that but I but I think doing doing the the path and of grand floridian Polynesian
for sure contemporary walking around for six days that's the that's easily the one you
got to do because it's by magic kingdom it's on the route you know you stop in at least
trader sam's at Polynesian and you have a drink either outside or inside stopping contemporary
do something similar I would recommend since it's I mean this doesn't sound like a relaxing
vacation like you're gonna be no you're gonna be running and gunning that's okay so I would
say stay on site but like you know I am you probably do well at a mid-rate at your your
port Orleans Riverside maybe check out hard look this is a thing check out hotwire two
weeks before as long as you got your flight booked you can stay fairly cheaply if you
know where to look on hotwire tweet at me I will go into detail about this if you want
to know despite although also let me insert let me bring my wife and I's wine oriented
philosophy into this why must it be this way my why must it be a war I think that you can
like if you're willing to skip you know if you don't see a robot show you can have a
little more I was entering plenty of why I'm thinking of her husband I'm trying to give
him a little I don't want him to be exhausted and battered and now this now this now this
I'm all for that it's just that she said six days six parks uh-huh it's inevitable I'm
not saying you certainly have that Trader Sam's drink certainly stop in Epcot and drink
around the world for sure mm-hmm but it's gonna be a lot of running and gunning let's
be honest this is gonna have to pack a lot in yeah now the other question is what do
you just not do you just not do how about this what if you were to skip one of these
parks of all the universal don't back out do it all six what do you skip you don't you
sure you said you're wrong Jason has decided that he's gonna beat the Kobayashi Maru test
by just ignoring your question not acknowledging the rules of the game I don't know that you
I mean it seems like she's angling for like a blitz kind of I think because we poisoned
her mind and now she might have gone and had a relaxing time it's seen a couple things
but now this will be all-out war well she's been micro dosing arsenic by listening to
the show and once you walk off the plane at MCO that's when you drink the full thimble
of it I don't even know what to say to that I will say I will answer your question mm-hmm
and I think the answer is Universal Studios I think it is too because they have Harry
Potter out here and the new coaster is not open yet do you sing island's adventure or
main universal universal oh shoot you forgot about I got Alec yeah I mean a normal person
would probably say islands of adventure it's it's probably yeah but spider-man is there
but spider-man is there the Incredible Hulk coaster I guess it's I guess it's islands
of adventure because Diagon is so good yeah if you had to yeah skip islands of venture
even though it's a superior park to universal but Diagon is so good yeah that's the thing
you got you gotta see you gotta see you have to go to Diagon that being said it sounds
like she's doing everything so yeah I would say okay how about this you condense universal
into one day you rope drop universal you could do that original that's true you just see
ET and Diagon this is right train and then you do all the best thing you've ever said
on this podcast I totally agree with you if you I'm totally agree with you if that day
will be truly a running gun day because even your up cut day there's a few things to do
in future world and then you can have a nice leisurely stroll through world showcase by
its nature is leisurely very clearly there's not a lot yeah so just structure your day
so that you have a leisurely day stop drinking around like seven or eight don't go nuts and
then go well we're getting up early we're doing universal we're doing all of it because
you're right you can do ET don't even worry about fast and furious don't worry about the
rip ride rocket unless it's a very short wait and do Diagon and do you can do all of it
saying don't worry about a race through New York with Jimmy Fallon I didn't when do you
get the opportunity to smell pizza that's that's true the pizza smells are very realistic
all right and I'm not saying skip if you have time because maybe eating don't buy a pizza
smell the fake pizza here's how you do that when the park closes you go eat at Margaritaville
well of course and enjoy that was an I was we were assuming walk down there so but like
to weigh up it's open very late and you get to see Jimmy Buffett's plane the hemisphere
dancer which was of course famously shot up by the Jamaican government normally why he
wrote the song Jamaica mistake he was not aboard the plane at the time I believe Bono
was with some other people probably some horrible capitalist man I think Clinton had been on
the plane at the time Clinton's been on the hemisphere dancer are you thinking of Jeff
or maybe I think you Bono I think it was Bono sorry Jeffrey Epstein's plane also on display
in first floor and he's we don't know that it's not a co-ownership we don't know that
that's true that the plane is not also that's true the Epstein plane so okay so we yeah
so I think we got it I would say build in whatever in for Scott's consideration build
a swing day yeah halfway through the six days yeah just pace yourself is a good so that
way if you crash you can sleep in a little and then still hit stuff I would say have
a one meal reservation a day at a decent restaurant sure that's something that that'll help you
like slow down a little structure the day as well yeah structure the day use the max
book your fast passes ahead of time I wouldn't concern yourself too much with like weekdays
versus weekends because there's in February February is what's left of slower seasons
in Florida I don't know how much lower seasons there are I don't think it's particularly
busy no so I in the food area Kia is a big cheese aficionado runs the story at cheese
mongers of Sherman Oaks go check that out in the LA area Tom podcast the ride sent you
or do you think you're getting some quality cheese plates any at any of these properties
well I would say not universal no no Le Selye in Canada although I heard showcases probably
world showcase had some great like Canadian cheddar cheese stuff and the appetizers and
on top of a steak very delicious cheddar steak I think it was just a little where that there's
that she's soup the Canadian oh yeah it's wonderful that sounds good and France of course
in the French Pavilion there's gonna be cheese gotta be cheese probably California grill
you think you're gonna decent oh interesting oh I like that well that you can you can watch
they stop dinner service pretty much and let people out on the balcony to watch the fireworks
then you can return to your table sure so that's a nice experience yeah yeah that's
what I'm a big I'd like to vouch for the California grill atop the contemporary yeah in general
there's too much to talk about there is yeah there is a lot so but I thought this would
be a fun question talk about on the show that we have blitz through just like she's gonna
blitz through Orlando mm-hmm Kia feel free to email us follow-up question yeah true clarification
but just you know remember to breathe it's a vacation it should be fun it should be fun
and it will be fun yeah it'll be fun it'll be so fun you might need a day or so to recover
it'll be relentless though all right well that was a there was a lot for that one yeah
what else we go okay two emails Jeremiah McGuire writes specific to Disneyland what attraction
that has been reduced or eliminated do you miss the most or was the most poorly done
what or what current attraction do you know the question deserves to be eliminated everyone
said multiple questions pick one of these questions so we can get through a couple more
emails what's the most the first one what attraction has been either reduced or eliminated
that you miss the most it's country bears in Disneyland it's crazy I want that show
it would be perfect over there in critter country I the poo right I go on once in a
while and I've you know going to Tokyo and it's gonna we're gonna see the better version
of it and I'm gonna be jealous of that but country bears over there critter country I
can imagine now us going so often and just that being such a great little thing to sit
down in the middle of the day after you did hungry bears something that being like because
splash mountain is really you have to be in the mood for it has to be the right temperature
so we don't often go over to critter country unless we're sort of feeling that but if country
bears is over there we'd be over there constantly and it would be a really nice air condition
as you was it was we often talk about these shows a great place to be and I'm very sad
that it's gone people mover yeah because not that well I don't know I did I did like
the ride and with all of the 70s 80s smooth jazz that I listen to really I am chasing
the kind of music that you would hear if you were on the people mover it's just this kind
of like you know chill jet age you know zipping around a nice relaxing mod future so I did
like the word the people mover as a ride I liked the width that you could you know get
little tastes of the other rides going into other rides that's kind of disappearing and
it led a scaredy cat like me get a little taste of splash mountain good when you go
through it on the train you take a little quick trip into space mountain and star tours
before you're ready on the people mover and also just pure kinetic energy that there used
to be a time where you in your same plane of view the submarines a monorail might go
by and the skyway and the people mover and the utopia cars you could get all of and a
train potentially all of these different types very different types of transportation all
running and in your same field of view so it at you know it added to the made it this
exciting hopeful future and it was full of life and what's my other oh also just pure
capacity that the people mover would eat up you know I think internally they call it the
people eater because people are you know out on that thing for 20 minutes which reduces
the bottleneck of how many people are in tomorrowland because tomorrowland is just stroller central
now it is so awful getting in and out of there so yeah really missed that people mover and
just in anything on that track would be so wonderful to get back the one in Orlando I
was writing and I wrote it during the fireworks and I was like man this why I was I was sad
about that too and you can usually just walk right on oh yeah although the lines are getting
worse the lines are just line and Jim just talked about how the line there's now a line
for it yeah there's love for the first time in like many years now there's a regularly
a line it's not crazy but it's a line and we're gonna say oh so I was gonna say I'll
answer the current attractions you think most deserves to be eliminated and I I don't like
oh hate this hate no no this is pretty tamed but I think the Monsters Inc. ride in all
sure in California Adventure like I it will be we know it will be it will be but it's
still go every every time we say oh it's gone it's gone like that is such a huge footprint
that ride and the sound stages around it and it's just like it's fine but there's a reason
they keep using that area for like temporary pop-up stuff yeah you're saying you just want
it to go away so we can get our Marvel rides yeah get get something because also too it's
like a redress of like superstar limo like oh yeah I think it was only recently I learned
like oh all the scenes are the same they just re did everything they just put a has man
suit on Drew Carey or whatever yeah it's so funny it is funny though that it's there I
do like that about it it's funny that it's there I don't disagree with what you're saying
but it is funny that that's what it is that they just were like let's put stuff over the
bad ride yeah let's just put clothes well we'll get we'll dive into it big time for sure but
I don't think that it's not egregious to me because it creates this corner that you just
don't go to like you write sometimes happens with you and critter country if you're in
the mood for splash mountain which I now always yeah of course I now lighter day I'm not scared
of it at all but anyway candy store back there oh yeah sure yeah sure skip that but but I
think in terms of egregious get it out of here in inventions have the amount of been
in the history launch bay is it open again start launch bay yeah it's a little they closed
it for a while no no still open but that's just that whole place saying it's just been
junk for so long and fun to me Chewbacca and it's fun like it doesn't but it doesn't need
a little shed when your school needed an extra classroom they would have one of those temporary
trailers yeah wait you could have one of those for Chewbacca a little bungalow yeah little
temporary star wars and the falcon or something in the future so no you're right of course
that don't they don't need the entire entirety of interventions to meet Chewbacca I just
when I think in terms of like wasted space oh it's brutal and then that's that's kind
of all of tomorrow and but it's also you're not wrong it's not bad to have or I don't
like that there is this giant corner of what is increasingly one of the best theme parks
in the world that is kind of nothing but I think it's gonna get solved yeah I hope really
soon yes yeah spider-man soon hopefully okay one last question this this is a little long
but I think it's very funny so all right okay Sean Urie writes hey guys I'm a fellow childless
adult male who loves them who loves theming but hates big drops hashtag no launch queen
I was just good I was just recently watching a goofy movie and at two points during the
movie they are playing 20 questions both times the subject is man and the answer after only
one guess is Walt Disney this kind of metaphor for a break got me thinking about the internal
logic of a goofy movie who is Walt Disney to goofy and max do you think they recognize
him as their god and creator he must be very important to these characters if he is the
first thing that they think of every time in a game of 20 questions in one scene you
see that goofy's keychain is the Disney D logo could this be an analog for a crucifix
or something of that nature it seems it seems in the universe we only see different animal
characters and not any human characters which further points to Walt as being some sort
of entity that is outside of their known world my girlfriend thinks I am insane but I am
curious what your thoughts are on this theory thank you for your time wow I love that I
love that I just watched a goofy movie partially because we had Nick Mundy here and we were
talking about he crapped all over and I might veer on the side of crapping on it I haven't
seen it in a long time I found it to be a little rough and that was one of the things
that jumped out at me is the Walt Disney and also similarly I think maybe Max hits a Mickey
Mouse alarm clock oh yeah that's familiar that's his that's his dad's friend he's probably
like his godfather or something you would yeah if goofy paid the proper respect and
but here I just walked into godfather is that is he is Mickey like a godfather but in God
in this case being Walt Disney and are the characters baptized do they all have to enter
and commit to the faith and it's which is which it is I think it's easier for them to
do so you know I think it was easier for for people to believe in God you know closer to
the age of Christ and if Christ was a real man then there's only several generations
of people telling the story and I bet it's easier for Disney characters to believe in
the almighty Walt because some of them knew him Mickey walked with him right and when
there was only one set of footprints that's when Walt carrying him yeah and then when
it was down so they could pose for the partner statue I think that's I think he's correct
yeah I think he's a little something here yeah I think Sean is correct and I think
it's the only way to make heads or tails of that moment D being the crucifix I think it's
a pretty brilliant theory but it there's a whole other thing that this opens up to which
is was this a question we got or did I see people talking about this on Twitter once
with like what is Disneyland to the characters because there was Matt Mazzotti talking about
this like the that in some like in a goofy movie goofy lives in suburbia with his son
but in other planes of reality goofy lives at Disneyland so is it that is it that thing
that Looney Tunes gets into sometimes as well where are the are these actors playing parts
but really they live really Disneyland is their Bel Air and goofy's acting in a movie
where he lives in suburbia with his son no I see the Looney Tunes it makes more sense
other actors because like then Wiley coyote coyote would talk in a very like professorial
way and then in his in his shorts he would be like not talking at all and I feel like
it's you in different universes with the Disney I feel like goofy movie and goof troop take
place in a different universe one where goofy and Max are not part of this Disney family
because Mickey is in the alarm clock because that doesn't make any sense I don't have an
alarm clock of my dad's friend that would be insane that is my dad's friend Kent I don't
have that morning his big arms bizarre and like but I will say you know when there's
different universe there's you know people have theories about how there's you know infinite
number of different universes stuff starts to bleed over and kind of you know infect
other universes and it's it's all repurposed in different ways so maybe Disneyland just
exists in the goofy movie universe and Walt Disney exists but they weren't created by
him they're just people that enjoy his products like anyone but in the context of Disneyland
is a different universe and yes Walt Disney's there and they're all living in sort of the
Magic Kingdom and it's totally different universe I think it's different universes it's a multiverse
essentially of Disney that's what I'm saying but I think yeah in comic book terms like
goofy movie is like an else world or a what-if story yes it's like off the track of the main
continuity but then sometimes they that reality will bleed into in Marvel speak the 616 earth
yes 616 is a Marvel universe that's proper the main one there's many different ones DC
has a much even more expansive multiverse yeah okay well this is and this has its precedent
and things like Mickey's Christmas Carol yes or the Prince and the popper yes characters
are do different yeah yeah and you know obviously Mickey doesn't all unless that is the one
true world is that Mickey is Bob Cratchit that's the 616 of the Disney universe really
is that Mickey is truly Bob Cratchit yeah I mean the real wild card in this is who framed
Roger Rabbit which combines all which is our ink combines the Warner Brothers universe
the Disney universe and our reality in theory in 40s Los Angeles and whatever the hell droopy
is from just the droopy verse yeah who owns is droopy a Harvey droopy feels like Harvey
to me but let me look it up yeah where's wimpy in all this well wimpy would be the EC Seeger
is the Seeger verse yeah the Seeger verse I don't know this one that EC Seeger was creator
of Popeye Popeye years and years a popular comic strip even well before the cartoons
and so it's a very vast mythology if you're not willing to declare that Disney is Mickey's
God will you declare that EC Seeger is wimpy's God 100% great that one is unquestioned yeah
and hamburgers are his son or his son hamburgers are the sacrament of EC Seeger's son and that's
why it's that's why they're so important right wimpy is it is him receiving the body of EC
Seeger yes and that's why EC Seeger is wimpy would be a prophet but then that means everyone
who like are trying to charge him for hamburgers that are sinners like if they're pushing that
I need the money now for the hamburger and then it's him that's so him he's being defiant
by saying I will gladly pay you Tuesday right yeah but Tuesday he means like the future
he means he means the afterlife Tuesday is I will pay you when we are when we are off
of this plane because the because you should not be worth and we should not bestow worth
on these burgers they are the body yes yeah wimpy is constantly and and the the fellowed
people have who have been saved are the people who give him the hammer and say you know what
don't worry about it but often wimpy's overturning the counters like Jesus turning over the tables
and the money lenders over the shop keep right of course yeah yeah yeah absolutely of Christ
because we will all meet our reward and all of them all of the hamburger money will be
paid back when we are in Seeger's heaven when we are seated at the right hand of Seeger
so that one's wrapped up Disney I'm not sure yeah I mean that's my theory because there's
no way to know for sure I will I we do know droopy is actually Hanna Barbera Tex Avery
oh juppy dog oh yeah how about that um and yet I've never had a weird general meeting
where somebody's tried to say you know with you know what's on the table is droopy droopy
we're trying to reboot droopy oh man that's a dream meeting for Jason too droopy reboot
droopy baby Huey oh baby Huey that's Harvey yeah any of them I mean we're due for a Harvey
resurgence well the whole Harvey Harvey universe that's another podcast that weird cheap Netflix
Richie Rich hot stuff the little devil yeah little dot there's little little Audrey is
a Harvey character yeah there's a little Lada as a character as well I don't like I don't
like these characters names if I don't like the names I know I'm not gonna like the cartoons
uh well these all feel like competition for little Lulu right yeah I mean there's a lot
little yeah there were a lot of little characters in the old days so well I don't know I saw
that didn't we all right we solved it I could keep naming other Harvey characters like Jackie
Jokers or spy man or bee man or the ghostly trio or spooky the tough little ghost or Wendy
the good little witch but I don't need to do that we've said it all today I think yeah
well I mean the answer I think the I think that what I'm saying is that the Disney situation
is so much more complicated because it's such a it's such a vast and complex universe but
Sean you're on this on there and that is the precedent the other there might be something
there yeah thank you Sean and thank you in general for sending your your questions in
we've just been getting we'll do more wonderful emails like this regardless of saying we're
gonna do post office segments but I think we'll we'll keep doing this so email us at
podcast the ride at gmail.com and we may give a little bit of time to your letters after
talking about our bullshit for a while yeah and with that being said you've survived podcast
the ride the post office edition uh you know I think also I think you could ask us questions
on on twitter and that would work too and check out our twitter yeah I think one of
the things I pulled from a dm in general and and uh you know podcast the ride at twitter
and instagram and now is the time to start checking the socials because with the city
walk saga on the horizon there's there is going to be so much crucial ancillary content
you don't want to miss out you're going to want to set your twitter to send direct alerts
every time we tweet so there's that little bell icon on twitter for a podcast ride when
we start this click direct notifications yeah you guys need to as soon as we post you need
to be alerted to it so do that leave whatever meeting you're in pull to the side of the
road because when you see all three of us holding miniature dodgers bats uh you're gonna
want to get in the game comments say who looks the coolest holding them up and meanwhile
we'll be playing the game called who had that whose phone was that who took that picture
yes wait where is what's what what do we need how do we possibly begin to organize 19 uh
episodes worth of uh photos ancillary content but that's a for us vials yeah we can't burden
the listeners you don't burden them all they got to do is sit back relax and enjoy except
not really keep up the pace of a intense disney world vacation and be checking uh our socials
as much as you possibly can because this is just the beginning i mean we're coming up
on our one year anniversary on top of all this forever dog and city walk a lot going
on just getting started a lot going on in the universe yeah well so i guess now we can
say the first time thanks for listening to podcast the ride a forever dog production
and a lot more to come down the pike goodbye check us next week city walk bye forever dog
this has been a forever dog production executive produced by brett bohme joe cilio and alex
ramsey for more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to
our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest
forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking
our page on facebook.