FOREVER!
As theme park journalists, we know the value of trust. You trust us to provide accurate, up-to-date theme park news, to hold ourselves to a higher standard than pretenders like bumper car boys. Today, we've broken your trust. As we spend much of the episode praising a Mexican restaurant that has since closed, we let you down, and much more importantly, we let the Sector Keeper down.
We hope you can tolerate this episode as something of a time capsule, of an era where Camachos stood strong, and Antigitos was but a flicker of a ripple of a dream. Thank you for your anger, your criticism, your honesty. It is making us better.
With all that said, Sector Keeper, we hope you can find it in your heart to give us today's assignment.
A place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold, a sublime hot topic and billabong. A place where you can purchase a candy thong. So let's go take a walk. Let's all go to City Walk tonight.
Podcast The Ride presents The City Walk Saga, a daily 19-part, extremely necessary series exploring the stores, restaurants, and wonderful magic that make up universal city walk Hollywood.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The City Walk Saga, Sector 7. At 7, it has become clear we have actually been doing this for an entire week, a week's worth of content. Is this too much content?
No such thing.
You let us know. I feel like nobody's ever complained about too much. I haven't heard complaints about episode length, but is this pushing it?
This has to be pushing it. This is insane what we're doing.
You'd have to think. And it's probably bumping other podcasts out of people's. It's possible that people are not getting this. If you've listened to 20 podcasts, maybe there's not even room for these to show up new because you haven't cleared them out yet.
Right. People have probably unsubscribed from us for this period and will subscribe in two weeks again when we resume the normal show.
Which is fair. I wouldn't hold it against you. One reason might be if you don't live in Los Angeles and you don't know what the fuck these 19 episodes in a row are referring to.
But we've crunched the numbers and a lot of the listenership is in Los Angeles and any LA resident loves City Walk, guaranteed.
And anyone who's been at Universal Studios knows the wonderful magical shopping and dining area outside of the theme park on both coasts is called City Walk. So they know what this is.
Yeah, unless you're some sort of eccentric millionaire who can afford the valet at Universal Studios.
Oh, to skip the walk.
Is there a valet though? Oh, it is. It's in Frankenstein.
I think the valet is in Frankenstein, right?
Look, gentlemen, there are two valets, one in Frankenstein and then one in the Jurassic Park.
So you can come out in different areas depending on where you go to valet.
So do yourself a favor and do the valet that is mid City Walk to catch some of City Walk.
Not Frankenstein because Frankenstein does take you on the other side of the park.
So you will miss all of a City Walk if you go to Frankenstein.
So go to the Jurassic Park valet, which is really when you go to the closer, when you go like toward the main sort of hub where you would get dropped off in a lift at City Walk.
That's the area where you're going to want a valet to make sure that you get a good amount of City Walk in.
And that's the valet that you can get validated at a sit down establishment?
Both valets, you can get validated.
Oh, both.
For two and a half hours if you go to a sit down restaurant.
So we've said all that, but we haven't said our names, which are Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
And if that the tenor of that may let you know that some of the hosts, some of us, I imagine at some point have struggled with this, this ordeal of this series.
And, you know, it feels like a long walk through the desert.
And that's, you know, when you're going through something trying, you need the support of people you love and people who care about you.
And I'm happy to have such support today, our guest today.
She is the artist behind the logo of this podcast that is on your screen right now.
Look at your screen unless you're driving, then shut off your car and look at it later.
But and she is also engaged in holy matrimony to me, Erin Gardner is here.
Hi guys.
I say 19 days isn't enough.
Wow, man, what else could we do?
I can listen to this bullshit forever.
She's right. She's right.
There's the hills that lead up to the, there's the sidewalks that have been recently redone.
Fascinating.
The stairs that we haven't talked about the fountain, the beloved Universal Studios.
The neon sign fountain.
The elevator, the cool elevator that connects the Sheraton and the Hilton.
Well, we could talk about that.
Yeah, that's got to be.
But yeah, there's plenty more.
I think the Sector Keeper could double the sectors, perhaps.
We'll ask them.
Guess what, boys?
The grand reveal.
There are more sectors still to be done.
That's probably where this is going.
Every few years, there's another 50 Pokemon.
You can never collect them all.
That's kind of the same.
I do.
Well, I appreciate you saying that, Erin, and I know that you listen to the show, which is very nice.
And you also listen to the show in real life constantly when you hang out with us.
This is true.
It's kind of a strange paradox because I feel like this is very natural and normal.
Like I'm just hanging out with you guys, but I'm also kind of a fan.
So I'm in a weird fan.
Oh, Scott.
No, but really I am.
And I'm kind of happy to be buried in the middle.
You've had such great guests.
And now it's like Scott's wife.
Oh, come now.
No.
Look, feel at home.
Roast Jason for some reason, if you want.
Oh, I mean, that's definitely going to happen.
All right.
Come on.
But you also, you contributed to this show in such a major way by giving us our Epcot Dream logo.
Yes, thank you.
Well, thank you.
Thank you for giving me the opportunity to do that.
Absolutely.
I also, you know, you there was an alternate version of it where I was suggesting all this
extra crap roller coasters and stuff.
And you wanted to do it a lot more simple.
And then Mike wanted to do it a lot more simple.
And y'all were right.
I think.
Yeah.
It was a real mess.
When it had all the extra bells and whistles.
Add some birds flying by and Guy Pukin off a roller coaster.
And as much as you can jam into the square, it's possible.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, it's very simple.
I think it's a good good starting off point for when we have 50 t-shirts and there's 50
variations on the symbol.
So yes.
And I am down.
I think they'll be great.
Yes.
Hopefully.
Yeah.
There will be merch on the way.
A lot of reformatting to do.
Oh, yes.
Well, and do we have putting things in different, you know, in switching your CMYKs?
I don't know what shirts are printed in.
Yeah.
I'm not sure if you can see the RGB right now, guys.
Sorry to say.
So that is for screens.
Oh, no.
If you guys want it printed CMYK is going to come into play.
It's going to get real messy.
We're talking file extensions here.
Oh, yeah.
Geez.
Well, in color settings.
Oh, is that what it is?
That's what you.
I'm sorry.
That's the color format.
Interesting.
If you're going to print it.
I just hope shirts are available in the shade of purple that is close to what the current
logo is.
It'll be close, but not quite.
Oh, boy.
I could start my own dry podcast on color formatting.
Sure.
I think the logo would be the shirt wouldn't be the purple.
Well, I mean, I guess you could have a purple shirt, but I feel like the logo would be ink,
wouldn't it?
Yes, it would.
Yeah.
It's all very comfortable.
We could talk about it off the show.
Yeah.
Nah.
We don't have to do this on the listener's time.
OK.
But I don't know, we're pushing the limit of what can be considered podcast, the right
content.
That's true.
Might as well keep going with that.
Erin, the other great thing about having you here is so you're all right.
So you're a Valley kid like me.
And I think you regarded City Walk in a fairly high fashion growing up.
It was the coolest place when it first opened.
The absolute coolest.
Especially because I was like a preteen and teenager sort of in its like rise and heyday.
And it was where you kind of felt like an adult.
I remember going to the Hard Rock Cafe and buying like drumsticks for the boy that I had
a crush on.
Oh, wow.
Sorry to spring this on you.
I don't actually know this story.
Yeah, you don't.
Oh, you know that I don't.
I know.
You saved it.
I had a crush on someone before you and I bought him drumsticks.
Oh my goodness.
Did it just say how I'm easily threatened?
If you know my YouTube body of work, you know, like I did a I did this video where I'm Michael
McDonald.
And the first one I did was for your birthday, Erin.
And it was because you declared you had a crush on like 78 era Michael McDonald.
And I was like, we'll see about that.
Yeah.
I will make you think of me instead.
You served that crush.
Yeah.
Quite handily.
I think so in the minds of the whole world.
Does this mean you're going to take up drums now?
Maybe or I'm going to I need to dress up like this boy.
Well, you're going to need a mushroom haircut.
You need to 1997 it up.
Oh, boy.
Good opportunity.
I need to be like a pre makeover Nick Carter.
Yeah.
What's what?
What else about this boy?
He was just a boy that I had a crush on.
I bought drumsticks.
We don't need to dwell on this.
Did they just say hard rock on them or was it?
They didn't have like famous drummers name on them or anything.
No, no.
They just said hard rock.
Joey Kramer, Aerosmith drummer, drumsticks or anything.
No.
Just generic hard rock.
I think I got a pity dance out of him at some school dancer.
I was not very cool.
I also like that you defaulted to the hard rock gift shop and not the two block long
guitar center and Sherman Oaks on Ventura.
Is this closer to you?
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Way closer, but not as cool.
Well, certainly not.
Yeah.
Lamer logos, just actual drum companies.
Do you know the fact about the, I forget if I've told you in the lead up to this, that
the sectors are such that the hard rock retail store is in a different sector than the hard
rock cafe itself.
You did tell me this and I think it's bonkers.
I mean, I think that it makes perfect sense because that's just the way it is.
Wow.
That, that is a solid argument.
There is no debating that.
It's a Trumpian.
It's yeah.
Yeah.
It's a bureaucratic kind of a thing.
It just, it just, that's not how it falls.
You know, I respect the sectors.
I'm not going to, I'm not going to stir up trouble.
Thank you.
Yes.
I'm not sure that every guest along the way has or will respect the sectors, but thank
you for, uh, and he's not, he's not with us.
He's with us today, but we'll summon him at some point to give us the, to officially
assign our sector before we do.
I think it's worth saying, I don't think we've really said this on the podcast, but
universal studios factors so heavily into us.
Yes.
Together.
Uh, it's a 12 year relationship now with four years of, of marriage.
And it really, in some ways began at universal studios.
It did.
Um, uh, um, being that, I mean, we, we could switch on and off, jump in whenever you want,
but the, we're going to shut our mics off.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I'd love to hear some fiction in this story as well.
Interject to whatever you want, make it a fancier story.
But I got, I got the job as a universal studios tour guide.
Uh, I, I suited up and wore the ultimate uniform you could ever dream of wearing.
I love a man in uniform.
Balloon khakis and a denim button up.
Um, adjacent, uh, light blue.
Uh, but I got this job and I was kind of spreading the word that I was, that I was doing this
and we were acquaintances in high school.
Um, and you were, had just finished college and you wrote me a message on my space that
was the, where you didn't have a lot of pride in yourself.
I never do.
And it was, cause it was sort of like, you're like, I don't, I'm coming back to LA and
I realized I don't have any friends.
Are you cool?
You seem like you might be cool.
It was all true though.
All of my friends had moved from LA, you know, everybody, everybody went off to different
schools and stayed where they stayed.
And I was the one who came back to LA and I didn't have any friends left.
And I always liked Scott.
I loved his videos.
I was a big fan.
I thought he was funny and yeah, I thought that we would be good friends.
And I had heard that you've got this tour guide job and I was like, well shoot, I gotta
go see him.
That's a good excuse to hang out and make a new friend.
Sure.
And I, and I thought it was a good excuse to, uh, uh, to do that, to present myself
in the most impressive manner possible.
And so, and you came with our friends, Tyler and Kia and Andrew.
And I, I was so excited.
You guys were there that I did something.
I did probably a fireable the fence.
I forget if I talked about this in the show before, apologies if I did, but I, I was like,
you know what?
So excited to have you guys.
I'm going to take you to a place that I've not taken any, but the guests are not supposed
to go.
And I led you from the tour guide patio, uh, over to the deep backstage area and the backstage
area contained the rotting remains of ET's teacher, Botanicus.
Wow.
He took me to the Botanicus graveyard.
I screamed when I saw him and Scott, you turned around so fast and you were like, I, I can
get fired for this.
Like really, please keep it down.
The good boy jeans or in effect even while doing an illegal act.
And just then William Peterson came out of the soundstage where they shot CSI.
That's the kind of fiction.
Him and Aaron locked eyes.
It's Scott beat the shit out of it.
I stole the drumsticks Aaron bought for him.
While, while that, uh, while who are you play?
Who are you?
Um, this is weird cause when we first met, I was, you caught wind of my botanical relation
to I have to bot botanic.
That's how Spielberg says it.
Oh yeah.
Teacher Botanicus Botanicus.
And then I had been talking about this on the screen junkies.
Um, and you'd become famous for using people know me the most is talking about ET's teacher.
One of the first things you showed me a photo of this rotting botanical botanicus and my
God, it's she was horrifying looking.
Yeah.
Terrifying, but also exhilarating.
Well, sure.
Of course.
And it's kind of what you dream would be around backstage at universal studios.
Yes.
Otherwise nothing very interesting.
I think I said on another episode that one time I got to see like a bunch of the DeLorean's
from the bags of future.
I stacked up, but nothing.
I just wanted to try to like snap off a piece or something and there was nothing there,
but I'll never forget during the training, it was like, we went up a big flight of stairs
and then, Oh my God.
Yeah.
That's big.
Did you, did you ever?
He was huge.
That's right.
Yeah.
And he's because he's on this big like a pedestal that was like embedded in a stone or whatever.
How long had the ride been gone out here?
Hmm.
Mommy was in 2003.
This was 2006.
So this is like two years old just sitting out in the sun for.
Yeah.
On the rain.
It was just out in the elements.
There was no covering over it.
It was so sad.
That happened with the rocket rods too, right?
Like didn't someone say, I feel like I've heard someone say like, there was no rocket
rocket character.
No, but like the ride vehicles were just like left in a lot in Glendale or like parking
on.
I've heard that about like the parade and stuff.
Certain parades just get left out.
Spectra magic was left under like temporary tents in Florida.
It was just kind of destroyed by the elements.
I think.
But Botanica is ET's teacher from the green planet.
He doesn't deserve that.
He has a personality.
I think that's sort of the dividing line.
Some ride cars, it's like, ah, I sort of get it.
But I mean, it's like leaving a person out there.
It's like leaving your grandfather in his wheelchair just out on the patio for a few
years.
Also, surely some museum would have happily taken that for surely Universal could have
just donated that.
The Smithsonian, Natural History Museum.
Some pop culture museum.
Did you ever think about taking it?
It would have been impossible.
It was too impossible to do it.
Oh, it's giant heavy machinery and you could see all these machine parts.
I'll post this out to Twitter, which may get me, I wonder if they'll retroactively find
me.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's bit specific proof.
They'll find me one day's salary, $45.
Did you ever yell at like an older or like a more senior employee like this belongs in
a museum?
What is it doing out here?
I want to know, did you ever yell at God?
How could he let such a big botanicals?
This was the only way that like the rage that we all have every day of the Trump administration.
This is the only time I'd ever felt it before.
I was screaming at people about the poor care of botanicals.
This alien is dying out here.
He needs to get back to the green planet where he can be needs to bring joy to all the little
creatures to the to glub lock and the flop flop and the flop cloppel.
There was also a rotting like mushroom guy.
You know what?
Is that the flop?
Yeah.
One of the friends you have to find also left to die.
See, I don't remember that.
There was that.
I mean, the botanicals pulled a lot of folks.
Tragedy.
He was there too.
I put them on that scenic overlook halfway down the starway where there's like a Apollo
13 cut out.
Just put them there.
They're there.
We'll take pictures.
I don't care who the cow.
Look at this crazy guy.
I'll take a picture with him.
Oh, he looks a little like ET.
Oh, whatever.
They think he's in the movie.
Like I remember that scene when he comes.
Yeah, you get botanicals on one side, you get the Oakwood apartments in the deep background.
Yeah.
Sorry to do that.
Yeah, show some respect here.
We will do a full botanicus episode.
Yeah, that's fine.
I think we'll go back to some of the other ones and go, oh my God, we only spent an hour
and a half on the ET adventure?
Anyway, so I was riding high off of, you know, I showed that I knew my history.
I also showed that I was a real rebel, except when it came to high volume.
And then you came and took the tour and I kind of customized the tour for you and pointed
out the detail you requested, which is wherever on the lot was used for the Janet Jackson Escapade
video.
Mexico?
Yeah, that was Mexico.
It was like right before or right after the flash flood.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
That little Mexican town also used in Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull.
And Big Fat Liar?
Oh, yeah.
Yes, the flood was practically used as exactly right.
Yes.
The Frankie Muniz movie.
So I finished the tour and it felt like a particularly good one.
And then we got off and everybody was really nice.
And then you said, I have such a crush on you right now.
And I thought that was mean.
Very rude of her.
I would say bold.
I was very honest.
And I think the theme of this, I'm declaring a lot of crushes in this episode.
I think I'm quick to declare a crush, but I really meant it.
Yeah, sarcastic is what you're saying.
Yes.
Yeah, I thought it was like this moment literally happens on The Simpsons.
I think you're cool, Homer Simpson.
Stacy, that was me.
Sandra.
That was me and Sandra.
I thought it was one of those.
And unlike Homer, I didn't revel it.
Honestly, for like the for 10 minutes, I was kind of like, I don't know.
That was in a pretty.
I just don't.
Why would you do that?
Soon enough, though, you'd find it was true.
Yeah.
I just got it out and I asked you on a date to the air.
I recall calling you from the universal patio.
And then we are our first date.
You picked us up from the other from the lift.
We took this.
We were at the stop today.
What do you call that?
What it's it's the by the book of the Beppo that end the taxi.
I think that's the one that connects to the E.T. parking structure, right?
Yeah, I think.
If you look on the lift app, I think I've said this before.
If you look on the lift app and you say you say your pickup is universal, they ask if
you were by the fountain or by the other.
It's like the airport where you have multiple options at this point.
Yes.
But yeah, our for our first day, you picked me up from there from a tour guide shift and
the date went very well.
And well, I mean, I guess if we're being correct about it, are the second kiss of a long time
relationship and marriage was in the Frankenstein parking lot.
Wow.
The end of the night.
Yeah.
So I'm sorry to say that fact in advance of the ultimate parking episode.
Right.
I am.
Yeah, you should have saved it, but I'll allow it.
Yeah.
Well, Aaron, I guess because Aaron's here.
Now let's reenact it.
Well, Jason and I.
This would look more like the traditional Frankenstein burning of a windmill.
What?
Right.
Don't they chase him in a windmill at the end of that movie?
I'm not sure.
Or does he?
If we all kissed, that's what it would look like.
What are you doing?
He's on his phone.
He's still trying to find out this lift fact.
So you either you can either set your lift pickup as Universal Studios, which is by the
fountain or City Walk East, which is right between Bucca de Pepo and Lids.
Yeah.
Went to all that trouble, but then called it Bucca de Pepo.
It sounded like he said P and P.
Beppo.
Bucca de Beppo.
Oh, Bucca de Beppo.
Oh, I think the sexor keeper is suffering right now.
I think I just probably mush mouthed it.
That's just that Philly vibe.
You just mush a bunch of syllables together and sometimes it comes out a little weird.
I don't know.
I think you're leaning on Philly to hide your mistake.
Don't blame your city.
So a successful date began at City Walk East and really a successful marriage and life
began.
But that's not that has nothing to do with this sector.
No, no, no, no, you're correct.
And the sector keeper would be upset.
But it is it is it is saying that, you know, magic happens at City Walk and at Universal
Studios and that dreams come true there.
Yes.
And that's the whole you know, if if we're if some of the the the rap on City Walk is
that like, you know, it's this fake place, this fake, this artificial city.
And it's not really look at that magical life events.
Important things happen just in doing this podcast series.
We've had we've had good times with friends, of course, and some unpleasant bathroom experiences
and uncomfortable aqua massages.
A lot of city walks where it all happens.
And we still have some heavy hitters coming up.
We're going to have some great nights at Howl of the Moon coming up.
Yeah.
And Margaritaville.
Yikes.
Yeah.
And you'll be you'll be forced to join us for some of those.
It's not being forced.
We have to stay till close at all the moon.
I just want to say that now.
That I will not.
I don't know.
Even if I were to participate in that.
It's going to be me alone at Howl of the Moon.
Anyway, with all that is back storying with how much city walk has factored into into
your life and our life together.
I think we should now turn to the sector keeper and get today's assignment.
Boys, boys, Aaron, today's sector is sector seven.
Nectar bath treats, Camacho's Cantina and Walters Gate.
Good luck.
OK, and sector keeper, you are correct that those are the things that are presently in
sector seven.
But there's more to this sector than meets the eye.
There's a little bit of hidden magic because in the history of sector seven, there was
once a truly magical place indeed, a place called Wizards.
Yeah.
Oh, this is the reason that I was so excited about this sector.
Yes.
And this is why this is why you're here.
And because I consider so Wizards is well, you do you want to describe it?
Yeah.
Wizards was a very cool like like a magic club slash bar at like dinner theater type
place.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Where you just go see a magic show and you could go during the day also.
And they had like psychics sort of roaming around the bar area so you could go and get
your fortune told, even if there wasn't a show happening, it was awesome.
Right, right.
And where exactly in the city walk geography was was it?
We were trying to figure this out.
I believe the entrance is where the current American Express New Card member.
Yes.
Kiosk is.
That's where I think where you bought tickets from what I can tell.
And like the sheriff's department.
Yeah.
And I think it's of I think a lot of what's used as the sheriff's department.
I don't know if any of it got annexed into the UCLA extension.
Possibly.
Which we haven't really covered either.
I don't think that maybe didn't really turn it become a sector.
Was it one time functional class space?
Yeah.
And the sign is still there.
But I don't think they do any of it now.
Don't think so.
I looked it up a little and I think it was kind of a bone throw to residents who were
like, well, a town should have education.
And so they like, all right, here, let's jam something in here.
I don't know.
And I think it's now gone and they moved it all to Woodland Hills, to my hometown.
But so, yeah, because we were walking around the area and you were now that that bridge
that is kind of that separates kind of that middle zone, that sir, the circle court in
City Walk.
Yeah.
Was that that was part of it.
I believe that was part of the bar.
That was the bar.
I think.
Yeah.
It was extended.
It was sort of an overhang and you had it was all glass walls and you had a view of
City Walk from the bar area.
This was three stories tall.
Yes.
Three stories.
Well, you entered at the at the floor level and then you got in an elevator that I only
have the most hazy childhood memories of it and like preteen memories, but it was a black
light sort of elevator.
So you would get in and the lights would dim and there would be sort of like a black light
effect.
So you were immersed from the minute you got in the elevator, which was so cool.
And then the doors would open and let you into what I think was the bar level.
And then above that, there was a like fortune telling area.
Whoa.
And the third, the third floor is certainly isn't anything that hasn't become unless it
became maybe part of it might be the John Lovett's Comedy Club or one of those things
or space for the sheriff's.
Yeah, it might be that.
Is there like a city walk jail up there?
Maybe it's the city jail.
Oh, you three would never know.
You're such good boys.
Yeah, we'll never know.
Well, after that night at the moon, who knows what?
We've had reports that you're drinking a lot of the free fruit water at the Sheraton down
the hill.
That's what you yeah, you're going to be in jail for that.
Just wandering.
And he was referring to me.
Oh, yes.
I love you guys after we saw the Kung Fu Panda thing movie and I didn't want to pay for a
four dollar Dasani.
So I walked and got free fruit water and sat in the Sheraton lobby.
Yeah.
Well, we've established that I am the bad boy of the podcast.
What would this quiet stepping away to see botanicals?
But shush, don't tell anybody.
And this water thing.
Yeah.
So you're lucky you didn't go to city jail for that cotton candy disaster.
Yeah, that's true.
Her littering for you dumping a whole cotton candy into the garbage because I couldn't
eat.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Aaron's lucky enough to hear so many of these stories before the listeners hear it.
And then again, when you're listening to it later and then again, if we're out socially
punishment.
Yeah.
So sorry.
And what a perfect place for you to be in a city walk.
Candy thing.
Oh, let me refresh you.
No, no, no, it's good.
I heard it twice already.
There's so much cotton candy and like I couldn't eat it and like, oh my God, I can't believe
I ordered it.
And then Nick Mundy texts you and says, I'm worried about Carlson with this whole cotton
candy thing.
I'm at a point where I can't hold on to my own memories anymore.
They've all been replaced.
All that brain space is now your memories.
This is why you need to you.
You need to preserve the memories of wizards before they're knocked out of your brain by
something even stupider.
Yeah.
Diving a milkshake.
If only Philip K. Dick had lived long enough to write a story about a podcast that replaces
your own memories with anecdotes you did not live.
Duller.
Less interesting.
On par.
In the ballpark.
I have a brain.
I haven't lived a fascinating life.
Geez.
But you went to wizards.
What are you talking about?
It's three stories of magic.
Of magic.
So much magic.
It's so much.
I had my 11th birthday party there, which was a dream because I loved this place and
I couldn't wait to be 21 so that I could drink in this damn bar because there was a certain
time or certain days that they wouldn't allow kids in there.
Yeah.
And it drove me nuts because there would be days that I would look at it and think, oh,
if only I was an adult, I could go up there and have those.
They serve drinks in potion speakers.
Yes.
Well, the trailer for Wizards has these special drinks and it's potion or test tube type
drinks.
Yeah.
So this guy sent us a four minute long video package trailer for Wizards, which is first
off, I'm glad you did because I think I said to you before, if you search Wizards and City
Walk now, it's very hard to find any results that aren't Harry Potter stuff.
Right.
Actually, I was just talking about this with my mom is that this is all before Harry Potter
and for kids who were into, and for me, I was super into like David Copperfield, but
also Eureka's Castle.
So it kind of was this like wizard safe place for kids who were into like nerdy stuff.
Because there was like a Dumbledore looking wizard roaming around in addition to like
a wise, in addition to the 90s.
He's like a more of a Merlin looking.
Yeah.
Like a Merlin.
He's like got the purple or something robe.
It was a very classic take on wizardry.
Did you care about Sword and the Stone also?
A little bit.
Yeah.
Isn't there, is Sword and the Stone the one where people are attracted to the squirrel
or something?
Which one is that?
Yeah.
They're turned into squirrels, right?
Merlin turns.
They're attracted to squirrels?
People, is there a, there's a female squirrel or something, or is it the, the, the boy turns
into a squirrel.
The boy turns into a, Merlin turns the boy into a squirrel and he like experiences young
love or something with the girl squirrel.
Okay.
I don't remember it that well.
I feel like I've talked to somebody who this was an awakening for and I swear I'm not coding
myself.
All right.
We'll believe you.
This is the male equivalent of the women of a sort of Fox Robin Hood.
Yeah.
Cause many women say that they were attracted to the Robin Hood, Disney character Robin
Hood, the Fox, cause he was like a cool, handsome Fox.
Really?
Yes.
I was attracted to Ken from Street Fighter.
That was one of my first cartoons.
He was a human.
Yeah.
Man.
So that's normal.
Which one, which ones he describe him?
He's the blonde Ryu.
Okay.
Sure.
They were very, they're too boring guys.
Yeah.
Not like Blanca, not like M Bison.
I think I have a crush on Bison on Raul Julia.
Oh yeah.
Oh, well that's fair.
Sure.
Do I tame the power?
I didn't realize this is a tangent Balrog, which is the boxer character.
They were going to call him M Bison because it was Mike Tyson.
And then it was a problem and they changed that and they made that the character that's
M Bison M Bison.
So they could not even make the association.
That's why that weird name exists though.
Oh, it's rise of Tyson.
And Zangief was a real Russian wrestler.
Oh, so how about that?
So Street Fighter facts for you guys.
Hey.
Anyway, back to the three story magic.
Getting off three story magic.
You were saying that the store, because the other thing is what is now nectar bath treats
was a wizard's store.
It was a wizard store and they sold wands and you know, like wizard trinkets and it's
sort of a pre what all of Anders is that the name?
Yeah.
Yes.
Wand shop.
So I would spend, I called my mom to ask if she had any memories and she was like, yeah,
I couldn't get you and your sister out of the wizard store because you guys loved all
the magic stuff and something that I didn't remember that she did is that they had like
slight of hand magicians sort of roaming the store.
So even if you didn't go up into the bar area or see the show, the store had magic for you
and it was free.
Really?
It's funny you say that because when I last time I was in Orlando, there was a shop in
the original part of Universal Studios Florida sort of before you like hit the kids area,
that was like a magic shop and they're like, we'll have a magic show in a little while.
And I'm like, okay, what is this?
And I went in, this might've been two times ago I was there because now I think it's like
old, you know, studio props you can buy props from the theme park and stuff.
But at one point in time it was magic and it was like close up magic and little, little
stuff because you could then buy all of those tricks right around the corner, including
a wallet you could open and there would be fire.
Like it fire through the length of the wallet and somehow it like used the lighter fluid
and they're like, they were telling everyone only adults, you have to have an adult buy
this and also we're not going to, we can't sell you the lighter fluid and you can't take
lighter fluid on plates, but it uses any regular lighter fluid.
So yeah, so Universal's not above a magic association to this day.
You didn't get that trick, did you?
I didn't get the trick.
And you didn't accidentally put your money in there?
No.
Too careful for that.
Come on guys.
That's true.
But it was also weird to come out and look across the way and be staring at Diagon Alley
and be like, that's right, I don't, okay.
Huh?
Well competing with competing wand stores.
I don't want to, you know, I, I'd say, you know, however you want to take us through
the three stories, feel free.
But I did find a, a little like passage from a website or from a piece of promotional material
that kind of lists everything that you could do.
And maybe that can help guide us.
I would love to hear this because my memory is so fuzzy.
And yet I do think you were the best source of information because there is almost none.
I had to really dig in my Google searching.
I had to make the date, you know, before 2002 or whatever.
So you know, when one of these sounds familiar, if you have anything to say about it, feel
free to stop me.
My memory is like looking through a kaleidoscope.
That's just like hearts and stars.
It's just a feeling.
I just can't get over that bar on the bridge sort of, because I've always looked up at
that bridge that crosses over the walkway and been like, yeah, that is a really, that
would be a cool view.
But it's like, wait, does it just connect the office buildings?
Like, I mean, it's probably all office space up there now.
It's just a sheriff, I think.
But I remember fairly late in the game.
I forget if you were with me when I saw this, but I like, I was walking through one of those
corridors and they still like the doors were still lightning bolts from wizard's era.
Yeah.
So they left remnants of it.
So pretty late.
Okay, so, you know, here, stop me or I'll ask you about some.
Make it a magical evening check.
You did that clearly.
What, the birthday?
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
And tell us anything else from that birthday.
Good attendance, good presence that you got.
I'm thinking there's only one picture and it's from like the house after the wizard's
stuff where we had like cake and open presents.
And I was looking at the people in this picture and I was like, huh, there must've been a
minimum to fill a table because some of it was like my sister and some of her six year
old friends, my cousins, some girls that I didn't like from school.
And it's like, oh, this is sad.
I had to like really reach around.
I still had a great time.
So good you didn't take any picture.
I mean, that's, you know, that's a good time.
It's like, oh, I didn't take pictures.
Too much fun in the moment.
They might not have allowed it.
Maybe it would have ruined Magic Castle.
Magic Castle, by the way, if you don't live in Los Angeles, kind of the like the more
like traditional equivalent of Wizards that's been there for a long time and it's still
there.
That has to be where this comes from, right?
Yeah.
I would say Magic Castle.
Let's make a cheaper, gaudier city walk version of this.
Anyone can go to Wizards.
Not anyone can go to Magic Castle.
That's right, only people give you a card.
Some people, like a magician, will hand you a card that gives you access somewhere.
But other than that, yeah, it's harder to get into.
I did see this literature that they said they felt like the Magic Castle was by magicians
for magicians.
Right.
And they wanted to create a populist magic bar.
For the many, not the few.
Magic.
I have another theory also, which is that I think it's just this, we've talked about
other things, this dynamic elsewhere in theme park culture, where I wonder if they talked
to the Magic Castle and said, would you want to open a wing at City Walk?
Oh, interesting.
And they said, no, this is what Paul Scheer said about the improv.
Was it Boom Chicago or Improv Olympic or something?
Or a New York one?
Was that one?
Chicago City Limits.
Oh, okay.
Gotcha.
Disney had approached them to do the comedy warehouse.
Okay.
And they said they wanted an insane amount of money.
For the name.
And Disney went, okay, well, thankfully, improv games aren't copyrighted.
So.
Neither is magic.
And neither is magic.
There's another thing similar to this also.
Well, it didn't end up happening, but when they were looking for live entertainment for
City Walk, they approached the groundings about opening a wing in a theater at City
Walk.
Oh.
It did not happen.
What could have been and what John Lovitz ultimately made happen.
I think UCB City Walk sounds pretty good right now.
Hey.
Maybe close.
UCB Sunset opened up UCB City Walk.
And put it in that hallway.
Kick the sheriffs out.
Yeah.
So, all right.
Make it a magical evening.
Chat with a wizard.
Accomplished?
I don't remember.
I know that there was a roaming wizard, especially like at the dinner show.
I think, you know how they have like the Charlie Chaplin at the Wild, Wild, Wild West show.
Yes.
Like, you know, roams around before the show starts.
I think the wizard.
Right.
Have been that sort of.
Like the guys who do the hijinks in the Waterworld show were running around before it.
Yeah.
But I don't think Merlin had a lot of or sorry, a wizard had a lot of hijinks.
He's generic wizard.
Copywritten.
That might be public domain though.
I think Merlin is public domain.
Sounds like he would be.
It's interesting though.
I was going to there's a combination of this, which is not how the Magic Castle works, but
there's a combination of your fantastical magic and your, you know, more practical magic.
Your traditional magicians, but also there's a wizard roaming around.
So it's like it's a fan.
It's crazy.
It's very fantasy.
There's fantasy element to it.
And there's also like more normal magic type things.
And also comedy, Matt.
Like there was in the video, there's a guy doing like gag magic.
Yeah.
And a laser show.
Right.
Oh, that laser show looks cool.
Yeah.
Which I think was a pre-show element sort of thing while you were eating.
It's probably on that list, right?
It's coming up.
Yeah.
We're going to make.
I'll skip ahead.
Yeah.
The spectacular laser show creates glittering sights and exciting sounds.
Accurate.
Yes.
It's time to make your shrimp skewers appear.
Now, there's something else.
It sounds to me like the food presentation is much like the pirate's dinner adventure,
which we did an episode on and Aaron was present for.
I saw a review of Wizards, which had the following quote, the first three quarters of an hour
of the two hour show is devoted to a meal of indifferent quality served with Prussian
efficiency.
What does that mean?
I think it means how the pirates thing was, which is like it is they think those guys
are on it.
It is a delivery system.
This is not what would you like, sir?
They're grilling you.
That is likely true, but I was 11 and didn't give a shit.
I was goofing around with my friends and probably doing like silly things with the straws.
So sure.
That's the magic that you could do.
Some of the power of silly straws.
All the liquid comes in a pitcher.
It's all dumped out in a pitcher.
Your ship is in a pitcher, drinks are in a pitcher and it's just like you have one chance
to get you have to flag them down if you want it.
Your magical meal were personal pan cheese pizzas.
Sounds pretty good actually.
Yeah, this is probably on the higher end of food for your 11 year old self.
Definitely.
Yeah.
It was fancy.
Now, what you probably didn't do as an 11 year old, I hope was drink a love potion.
Oh, I would have loved to though.
That's the kind of thing that I yearned for when I was 11.
Adults.
I just wanted to be 21 so that I could go drink there and fall in love with a cute boy
who maybe looks like Ken from Street Fighter.
Be served a drink that's Midori and Midori over ice.
Have your palm read.
When you talk about the mix of types of magic, very strange.
That's not something at the Magic Castle that it's palm readers too.
Yeah.
And I did have that done.
Ah, remember anything?
No, I'm sure it was very tame because I was 11 or 12 when I had it done.
They weren't like, I see that you're with a bunch of people you don't like.
At your party.
What's that like?
Why is your cousin here?
Scraping the bottom of the barrel, are you?
Don't have enough friends at school?
That seems like too easy for a palm reader to do it for like an 11 or 12 year old.
You're going through a lot of changes right now.
Yes.
Exactly.
You feel like people don't understand.
Yes.
I remember it being a lot.
It was really focused on the palm reading itself and it was like, here's your lifeline
and you have a long lifeline and here's your wealth.
And here's it was really tech.
Like you could go on Wikipedia and say the same things that the palm readers there said.
They call this the pinky finger.
Here's the part that I wanted to ask you back because I don't, nothing I saw on the video
correlated to this exactly.
Visit Saturn, Jupiter and Mars.
No idea what that means.
Yeah.
I didn't see any equivalent of that.
Maybe that's if you drink too much.
I guess so.
If you smash your head on the way out.
Yeah.
Then you'll be seeing stars and planets.
Everything here also had a Z, a wonderful thing.
See the world's top magicians perform amazing tricks while you dine in the elegance of the
theater of illusions.
So that's the main theater.
It must be.
Yeah.
And you'd see, you know, like, yeah, there'd be, there'd be a comedy magician.
There'd be more of a sleight of hand guy.
Yeah.
It seemed like they, they had a lot of variety.
Seems like they were, they were lauded for that.
Yeah.
The laser show covered before after the show, you can sip cocktails and concoctions in the
magic potions bar as magicians perform at your table.
What a bar.
You could if you were 21.
Right.
So you didn't get to do it.
I didn't.
So by the time you turned 21.
It was gone.
Wizards is no longer.
We would be hanging out there all the time.
That's what I was thinking.
That's right.
That's why I was watching that YouTube.
Cause we go to there for city.
We were to watch the movie, go to opening night of movies.
We, and now we go to Margaritaville beforehand, but we would absolutely be at Wizards bar
every night.
The bar was beautiful too.
It had so much neon.
So much.
Yeah.
That was, those shots were blowing me away.
It's very much my aesthetic.
The and a giant Wizards hat in the main bar.
Yeah.
It was huge.
Two stories it says, and you could see that from the window.
Yeah.
And now it's an empty hallway.
It's sad.
What are you talking about?
We keep, this has been a recurring thing in the podcast in the city walk series is I've
been calling them fallen brothers, the ones that didn't make it.
And it seems like everything with personality is not really there.
Like the beloved rain stick store of the nature company, the rain sticks are the bar.
It doesn't really look like it, but it reminds me of Clark's bar from Star Trek, deep space
nine, which was apparently a bar in Vegas, which is outside of the Star Trek experience.
Oh, at the, uh, the West gate.
Yeah.
I think that's where it was, which is a thing I never went to the Hilton.
It was our first trip in Vegas.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Our first vacation.
Um, but it's like a, yeah, it looks, it looks like dreams are made of it.
We've been there a number of times and it's a really confusing mishmash of it's still
a Star Trek.
It's still a spaceship casino.
Right.
Now it's a timeshare selling place.
So you go into the Star Trek themed area and they try to sell you a time.
Wait, did you say it's West gate?
Yeah.
Is that the guy from King of Versailles or Queen of Versailles?
Yes.
Oh yeah.
That guy's the biggest piece of shit.
The guy who runs West gate.
That guy is the sleaziest guy with this giant house.
Okay.
So when you're in, um, like you're in a Star Trek themed area and on folding tables are
Queen of Versailles t-shirts that you can buy.
Get out of here.
They add like as if the Queen of Versailles presented just like, what was that?
Dumpster, the show with Paris Hilton and, uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, yeah, she's just, you know, she's the queen of, uh,
You know, like the, like the, the wealthiest ritzy, but the documentary is extremely sad.
Oh, it's depressing.
Yeah.
Dead animals and their horrible house and their palace never gets built.
And you're watching that they would like present that as like live like the Queen of Versailles
and not cover up the Star Trek stuff.
Not cover up.
So funny.
Just a space.
I mean, that was a thing that the people in that movie are so gaudy and cheap, even though
like the guy in the mo, oh God, I forget his name now, but he made so much money selling
time shares and shit.
And he got in like, it got a lot of hot water.
Cause like one either 2008 or 2012, he said like, well, if Obama wins, I don't know if
I'm going to be able to keep all these people on payroll the way this guy's going.
And it's like, what's the disease weird, like ultra rich people over like that Obama.
He sure was radical in the way that no one went to prison for the financial crisis.
And, uh, uh, uh, Obamacare was a modified Republican healthcare plan.
Well, you can relive the glory days of 2006 and the half completed.
Also remember when we got on the elevator and people had just finished a Star Trek wedding?
Yes.
Wow.
And they were in full.
Full costume.
Was there an alien?
I think so.
Yeah.
Were there Ferengi?
I don't know.
I don't know the Star Trek.
I think one was just kind of like a mod sixties girl Star Trek crew person.
The other one might've been a Ferengi though.
I hope.
I'm not totally sure.
Yeah.
For your sake.
Or a Borg.
No, no Borg though.
I hope not.
There were only two people getting married.
So how long ago was this again?
That was in 2006.
Okay.
So was the casino not necessarily still Star Trek?
I think it is.
A little of it.
No it is.
In 2006 it wasn't Westgate yet.
That was still the Las Vegas Hilton.
Yeah.
It changed over pretty in the last five or six years I want to say.
Recently.
But remember when we went a couple years ago and it still had the Star Trek logo outside
even though it doesn't stay Star Trek anywhere inside.
This thing is a mess.
They are not keeping track of what's going on.
One of my biggest regrets is not doing that Star Trek experience.
Which people theme park.
Which people go nuts about.
People said.
Did you do it?
You did it?
I loved that show.
No.
Oh you loved the show Star Trek?
No I loved the.
Oh the thing I'm talking about.
Yeah at Universal Studios right?
Oh no.
No, no, no, no, no.
This is a different thing.
Wait what?
In Vegas it's called the Star Trek Experience and you would like get beamed up and like
be on the bridge of the Enterprise and then like Borg would show up.
Like alien Borg would show up and that's a whole people describe it as incredibly immersive
to Mr. Tony Baxter I think says he was blown away by it.
Wow.
Because he thought it was like going to be a normal ripoff simulator like Star Tours
style but then you get beamed up somewhere and it was an incredibly like realistic effect
and then you're like on the bridge and it's like they have performers and it's a whole.
That sounds cool.
You're talking about the Universal Studios.
Sorry yeah yeah yeah.
The stage show at Universal Studios which I loved.
Were you ever in it?
No.
Were you in any of those?
Did you do Harry and the Hendersons of sound effects?
No.
I had a very cool friend named Astrid growing up and she got picked for everything.
Everyone I know is a friend named Astrid is like Astrid's so cool.
She was the coolest.
I mean she deserved to get picked for everything.
I was sort of quiet and weird and she was like loud and crazy.
I see they knew she could she could give them some energy.
Classic Astrid.
Yeah yeah yeah.
I think we're almost through the list but the I don't want to skip past that potions
bar that you get a little like magic potion themed drink and I love in the video when
they set down a magical overflowing potion drink next to a little bowl of Chex Mix.
Not magical but yeah we would be you love the Chex Mix.
We go have the Chex Mix at the Universal Hilton bar.
Which we will cover in a later episode.
Is that still there?
Yeah.
Cause I walked through it the other day and I don't know that I saw.
No.
The Atrium bar?
The snack dispensers yeah.
Snack dispensers oh I don't know.
They may just have it like under the counter now.
Are you saying that there's still a bar but maybe not the snacks?
Yes.
Oh well okay.
The Atrium bar is still there but I feel like they just have these giant like dispensers
for like Chex Mix and stuff.
Maybe they just scoop it out now.
Chase this is one of the times when he sat up to double check and see if the snacks were
still at the bar.
I sat up too but I thought it was because the Atrium bar was gone.
Right you scared them that the bar was gone.
No still going strong looks recently redone.
I just hope it's still like big brass bars and stuff.
That's beautiful.
We gotta go have a drink there too.
We will.
We have so many places to go.
We're gonna hit that and take the outside elevator down to the Sheraton.
Oh yeah that outside elevator that goes really slow and clunky.
Which was not working the other day so I walked down 45 degrees.
Middle of the day sun burning bright.
Next if you like walking up hills and taking long escalator rides Universal Studios the
place for you.
Yeah agreed.
Let me see the Venture of Visions psychic reading room and Spirits the fortune tellers
bar.
Wait those are different things?
Psychic readings and fortune tellers different?
I guess so I don't know.
Oh my god and you never and after all you never know what the future holds until you
ask.
So you accomplished all that.
It sounds like an incredible 11th birthday party one of the greats.
If it's 10 years later I would have loved to have a 21st there.
What a bummer.
Yeah I feel like you would have done it but you had the same thing with me where you thought
your adulthood would be full of city walk visits which I guess it has been.
It kind of is.
Just with levels that we added to it but we have spent a lot of our actually our 10th
wedding anniversary was in that Hilton Atrium bar.
We've done a lot of important events and milestones in our lives.
We'll renew our vows below the King Kong as if he is.
That would be fun.
That's a not a bad idea.
Well you know we should do it under that sign that says the most beautiful faces in the
world pass through here.
Well that would be a lie.
Just yesterday I noticed that sign like I always notice the face but I never really
process the text on it and I was just like what in the hell.
Just looking at that sign because I was like crossing above it and I like just happened
to look down and go like what what.
I always knew the sign was there and I went on an early I went on a high school date to
city walk and I remember thinking like what if I was like what if it was going really
well and if I was like bold enough maybe I could point to that sign and say yeah like
you.
Wow.
You didn't do that.
I know I did not I did not have the courage to do that.
Now we were we knew each other in high school does that make you jealous we weren't dating
then.
We it was the perfect timing together we both grew out of our thank God it was stagger awkward
phase.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Scott do you remember wizards being there and not going in.
I think I assumed it was for adults only I assume and I was never corrected on this so
I could have gone and I didn't go and I'm upset about it.
Sometimes kids could go not always though.
OK I see there's very few things you admit to being upset that you didn't go on because
usually I'll say like oh I wish I went an alien encounter you're like too scary I don't
care.
Yeah yeah and then like this might be one of the only ones where you're like I regret
yeah going in wizards.
I'm pretty sad about this of things we've talked about I'd say this not going to wizards
and that I didn't get to meet Marvelous Marvel McFay at Astro World Astro World and hear
the song ring through the through the loudspeakers.
So just just to confront so wizards open in 2000.
No no no no OK sorry.
93.
I'm not young.
I started dating Aaron at age five.
My yeah 1995 was my birthday but it was OK before then.
And how long did it last for.
I don't remember when it closed.
I figured it out finally and it took a lot of I ended up on magician message boards to
figure this out and I made it back alive.
OK it was it closed it seemed to have closed slowly in 2002 I think just the lease probably
heading for a 10 year lease and they just didn't renew it.
And sadly I had to say it I think the the it was owned by a husband and wife and the
wife passed away and I think the owner lost enthusiasm for doing it and just kind of just
sort of let it go.
Is that a bummer.
And and and now here's the thing.
Oh no this I did figure out this did open.
Here's new fact for you Aaron that I somehow kept to myself at home.
There was a.
Thank you inner monologue.
That wasn't talking for two seconds.
There for a little stretch of time there was a second wizards in Tokyo Japan.
Yeah yeah didn't know this.
And where was it you ask.
Well they were trying to build it.
It was slated to open in Jakarta Indonesia originally.
They were 95 percent completed when political upheavals there made it impractical.
So yeah the wizards were chased away and they ended up opening it in a mall called XP
Ari which means inspiring experience.
And this mall is right next to Tokyo Disney.
And now I know that there is this mall outside Tokyo Disney.
So yes perhaps the four days will need to be.
Whoa four Jason.
Jason we're all right.
And so Scott's got a really I perked up.
It's a technicality but take it.
Hey yeah I will.
I'm already imagining Scott with his like Sherlock Holmes style magnifying glass like
check it out this ball.
Trying to find remnants of wizards.
Yeah I found a W. I found a W on a pipe on a valve.
So we flash forward to 2018 because there's so much stuff in the sector now.
There is yeah we haven't done any of the current.
Can I say one more thing which is that there's the happy ending to this to that sad story
which is that the the main close up magic guy was named Warren Gibson and he left in
the mid 90s to establish he was so inspired by his time at Wizards and everything he learned
there that he opened his own magic bar in on Maui in Lahaina is a Maui area.
And that's called Warren and Annabelle's and that is that was open in 1998 and it's there
to this day.
Let's go.
Wow.
We got to go to Maui.
So this literally the spirit of Wizards transferred over to one of the most beautiful places in
the world.
So thanks Warren for Annabelle.
Wow we all got to go to Maui.
No complaints from me.
Yeah.
How many days in Maui?
I think seven is great.
Seven?
Okay.
Personally.
That one I'm not going to I'm not going to complain about.
Seven days in Maui sounds wonderful.
All right so that's that's the Wizards tale and thanks for telling us what you knew.
Thank you.
But there is other stuff in the in the sector including where we went today Camacho's Cantina
where you had been before correct?
Yeah several times.
Uh-huh.
I don't know why I hadn't had you guys.
Never.
Just yesterday.
This must be a thing like they must.
It's just because it's like hidden away a little bit.
There's something uninviting about it.
Yeah I know none of us have been there.
But it's got a lovely fountain outside.
Yes.
And I've been to the one at the airport.
Oh.
What?
In Terminal 1.
Or at least there used to be in Terminal 1.
I think that is a Camacho's like there's a McDonald's.
It used to be a Godsend.
LAX has gotten a lot nicer in the last five years or so.
But when I used to fly US Airways a lot because one of their hubs is in Philadelphia.
They got bought by American Airlines.
But I'd always be flying out of this one terminal that had like no food in it besides a McDonald's
and a Camacho's which was like a Godsend for like breakfast burritos.
Yeah.
Oh.
It sounds familiar.
I do feel like I've seen the logo in LAX.
Yeah.
It's a pretty big logo sign.
But in terms of the City Walk one had never been there besides yesterday.
And I got to say walking inside, beautiful inside.
Really nicely done.
I was shocked.
I walked out because it's like a little bit of a step.
There's like steps down.
It's kind of in the basement a little bit.
Not really.
But it's like there's you feel like you're going underground.
The bar is.
Yeah.
Sorry.
And yeah, it's very nice.
Yeah.
This might be the hidden gem.
We didn't know.
I think that's an original City Walk 93 opening.
Is it really?
And it's just, you know, whereas other City Walk trends have come and gone and burned
out in a flash.
Classic Mexican food.
Everybody always loves it.
Always in style.
And I would say 3 p.m. on a Friday packed.
Their dining room packed.
The bar a little less packed, but I had a great happy hour.
The people there at the bar for happy hour were having a great time.
What'd you get?
I got just a house margarita and then I got potato taquitos with and it came with half
mole sauce and half like avocado sauce.
Delicious.
A great mole sauce.
Got out.
I think both of those like 11, maybe 12 dollars.
Wow.
Great deal.
That's better than just regular Mexican restaurants.
Like, because usually you think City Walk like prices are usually jacked up above average.
But I thought that Camacho's was on par with just regular Mexican restaurants in the city
that aren't in a touristy area.
I thought so too.
Yeah.
And I think in terms of happy hour might be a little loud ahead of Margaritaville in terms
of like price and quality.
Well, and certainly decor.
Like when you compare those, the bathrooms in Camacho's are beautiful and fancy.
I love the bathrooms in Camacho's.
Full door stalls.
You kidding me?
Gorgeous.
Amazing doors.
Molded.
I love a full door stall.
They have one at Carthay Circle.
We'll eventually talk about that.
It feels like you got a little apartment in there.
This might be.
I'm not going to hang out that long, but I just like it.
It feels very private.
Number one with a bullet in terms of City Walk bathrooms.
Yeah.
At the moment.
I don't know that anything's going to top this.
I think we may have to like, if we have to go to the bathroom for the rest of this journey,
we'll have to like sneak into Camacho's.
Sneak into Camacho's.
Because that's a good.
It's always packed.
It would be easy to do.
Yeah, that's true.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Just slip past the crowds and yeah.
Happy with your meal, Erin?
Good skinny margaritas, both of us.
Yeah.
And nice beer too.
Well, the best thing, the thing, this is going to sound like I'm trashing City Walk, but
one of the best things about Camacho's is you forget you're in City Walk when you're
eating in there because it's very much, the theming is different.
It's not, you know, gaudy and neon in there.
It feels like you're in kind of a whole Newali Mexican restaurant and it really like atmospheric
wise, you know, you feel like you're having a different type of experience.
Yeah.
So, I mean, we all went to Camacho's.
We all were like, wow, Camacho's is great.
Are we putting it in the Golden Fort Chet?
Yeah, I would put it in the Golden Fort Chet club.
Yes.
For sure.
What's Italian for yes?
C?
Is it C?
I was in charge of learning Italian for our honeymoon and I failed.
Yeah, that's why I turned to you.
French, say it in French.
Just move it over.
We.
We're going to move it over.
Okay.
Can you give it five forks in French?
C?
That's as far as I could go.
The fork, four K's.
A, I, S. That's pretty specific.
It's probably in front of you.
You don't have to ask for one there.
Yeah.
All right.
It's in the, it's in the Golden something club.
Yeah.
Wow.
What a, like, what a pleasant surprise.
I thought that was something we might just brush by.
I know.
That's what I thought too.
Yeah.
Really good.
And that's what this series is about.
Yes.
We might've never gone.
Yeah.
That was the last thing.
It looked in the menu.
It said on Friday and Saturday, they have a mariachi band.
Oh, we saw the stage.
We sat by the stage.
So gosh.
What did everyone eat?
Oh, I had carnitas and a flour tortillas.
Great.
Vegetable enchiladas.
Salmon tropical.
A little, a little accent above the.
Oh, I felt like I took a swing.
I was like, I know they'll do just kind of some greasy tacos as well, but a salmon dish,
will they?
I thought it was excellent.
That's great.
Chips.
Good salsa.
Oh yeah.
Great chips and salsa.
A little spicy.
I liked it.
Spicy.
Yeah.
Smokey.
Yes.
I liked the green creams, stuff carved into that.
The decor of this place, it's like all of the, the, the tastefulness in city walk in 1993
went into this one spot.
Yeah.
A lot of tile work, a lot of wood stuff.
I did say I got a little bit of a kick out of watching like an old, a middle aged, a tired
white guy sitting at the bar, like a few down for me.
Just kinda like in one breath go, can I get some sour cream, gracias por favor?
Like it was one sentence.
Not attempting to pronounce.
And then finally, to wrap up the sector,
upsettingly, the former Wizards Wonders
became a lush for a long time,
and now it's something called Nectar Bath Treats.
All right.
All right, here we go.
Well.
I hate this place.
Sorry.
Well, let's ask a quick question.
How many of us bought something and tried it last night?
Let's raise our hands.
I like it, Jason.
Two of us.
Jason and I are raising our hands.
The two A students.
We got A's.
I mean, this was one that I, early on, was like,
well, I got to get something there.
You declared that you were going to get something and try it.
So then I said I have to get something and try it.
I wonder what we got.
I wonder what you got.
All right.
I guess I can go first with mine.
So first of all, I wanted to, so just in case you don't know
what Nectar Bath Treats are, most of it
is like food looking, like food shaped soap.
Yeah, it is not treats.
Yes, you cannot eat it.
There are a lot of signs on the wall
that say do not eat this stuff.
Because a lot of it looks like real treats.
It's very pretty looking.
Sit down, Edwin.
It's not treats.
Donuts, like popsicles, but there's soap.
It's all these fancy expensive soaps.
And a lot of soap where I was like, this looks cool,
but what is the practical use?
They had a three tier cake of soap.
That's like $40.
It was, I thought it was more than that.
The one that I saw was close to $100, and it was monstrous.
And I don't know what, it's fun, I guess,
but are you going to ever use the soap if it's hard to?
How do you break it up?
Do you just like kind of break off?
It was huge.
I guess you have a big cake knife,
and then you cut slices of soap off before you take a shower.
You don't ruin a knife.
It used to be, or was it next to it, a Lush store?
It was a Lush.
I feel like I know multiple women who are like,
oh, they took the Lush store away.
That was the thing I liked up there.
An actual.
I've never shopped there, but I do
know people really like Lush.
And you don't do like froufy bath stuff.
So to you, a bunch of key lime pie soaps doesn't make any sense.
I used $1.69 dial soap from the drugstore.
Yeah, that was a little bit of a change for me,
because I definitely bought a bottle of body wash for $2.50
the other day.
All right, buy like a gallon of body wash.
Welcome to my life for eight months, friend.
Eight months, friend.
But they have, yeah.
I'm looking around, and I'm like, I got to get something here.
And all the soaps just seem impractical.
That seems really more for decoration, just for the fun of it.
I'm not going to be washing myself with a fake popsicle that's a soap.
That seemed like the most practical,
because it was at least a flat, flat-ish kind of shape.
It didn't have a wooden stick in it, which is odd.
Yeah, but I mean, maybe that's kind of like the scrubber.
It actually makes sense if you were, say,
imagine you're holding a popsicle and you're
washing your back with it.
It makes sense.
Like you're Donald Duck with that big, big bath brush.
So I was walking around, and here's what happens, I think, most of the day,
is that a couple of people wander in, walk, do one quick lap.
It's a pretty small store, and they right away leave.
Because they're like, well, I would $25 for this.
This is crazy.
And there was a gentleman who was excited to talk to me, because he's like,
well, do you want to see a demonstration?
And I went, yes, I do.
Because they have a big sink.
They have a big sink in the middle, and I don't know what he's demonstrating.
It's usually kids they're doing demonstrations for.
Yeah, of course.
This time it was Michael.
It was me.
And you could tell he was like, oh, I've got something to do now.
And he was like, well, what I would go, what's a cheap kind of, I'm just
getting into this, what do I want to do?
He goes, well, you could do a bath bomb, and you could also do what they call,
hold on, let me find the name of it.
You could do a little, they call it a bubble scoop.
So the bubble adds, there's some moisture, and then the bath bomb has
Aromatherapy.
Is this the one that you buy three of them and put it in a little ice cream
container?
They can do that too for you.
So he's like, you got one bath bomb, you get one of these little bubble scoops.
And he's shown to me, and he's like, hey, put your hand in the water and feel it.
And I go, oh, OK.
So I'm putting my hand in soapy water, and I have to be like, oh, yeah.
Oh, I feel it.
And then he puts the other thing in, and then he goes, yeah, you can feel the
water if you want.
I go, oh, sure.
And I put it in.
Oh, yeah, I feel that.
And I was like, I don't know.
It's soapy water.
It feels fine to me.
Just a good public bath with a man you just met.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm on my hand.
He's like, oh, you want to like me?
I'm drying off because my hands are soaked.
So I'm looking around, and I'm like, let me get one of these bath bombs.
The bath bomb was $6, and the other one was like $5 maybe.
That's what he recommended to me.
I'm so curious what you got.
Hold on.
Don't say it yet.
OK.
And then he tells me, so I got the Calm Your Spirit bath bomb, because there's
many different kinds.
There's one that's Awaken Your Senses, which is supposed to clear up your
sinuses and stuff.
And then there's one that's like Stimulate Your Passion, which I guess
that's a horny one.
I didn't get that, which I'm like, that's weird.
I should have gotten that.
Jason should have gotten that.
I should have gotten the horny one.
And then so I get that one.
And then as far as the Bubble Scoop, that one looks like ice cream.
The other one looks like a big giant kind of hard candy.
And then the Bubble Scoop, if you guys want to see, it looks like little tiny
scoops of ice cream.
And it really looks like sherbet.
We saw those today.
It's impressive that it looks like that.
And I got that.
So he's like packaging them up.
And he goes, oh, yeah, don't worry.
The sparkles are like, I think, biodegradable.
And then I was like, oh, my god, am I going to get sparkles in my urethra?
Like, that was the first.
I'm so sorry to be vulgar like that.
But that's my first.
I got like a fear as they were like, I was like, did I buy?
Oh, shit.
What is this going to be?
Would a woman using it also have concerns about getting it?
That's what more possibility of sparkly innards.
He brought up the sparkles and I went, oh, he's saying maybe the sparkles are
OK. He brought up that concept.
Not in my urethra. No, no, no.
I was going to say that part of their marketing is like paraben free, handmade.
There's a lot of other crap that's not in it.
I'm saying I wouldn't have thought anything of it until he brought up the idea
that the sparkles should be OK.
Hey, but for a second, thanks for shopping here.
Hey, don't worry, those sparkles, they won't hurt your piss hole.
You're all good.
A couple of weeks, but it'll clear out.
Yeah, it'll be fun for a couple of weeks.
And it comes with a bottle of cranberry juice in case anything goes wrong.
And then, yes, because they're like very big on the holo, it's OK, it's fine or whatever.
So I was. But that is what he when he said it, I was like, why did you say that?
Why would you say that?
If you took your pants off and were just in your underwear, would we we wouldn't see
just a glow emanating from your crutch?
I honestly, I've been shiniest.
I've been running around all day, so I haven't even looked.
So who knows?
I looked like Spar.
At some point, Hawaiian Tropic started putting sparkles in like
their main bottle of suntan lotion. Really?
And I was just like, what the fuck is that?
Like I bought a full bottle and I'm like, well, I'm just going to be sparkly
for the summer. That's disgusting.
I had to switch to the sport brand because there weren't sparkles in it.
You don't you you do you do makeup that has like a that's a little sparkly.
Yeah, like not you wouldn't want like it in your washing sparkles.
Sparkly and something with glitter in it.
Sure. Yeah. Go away.
Right. Yeah. Those are items.
Yeah. Yeah.
So this was hopefully not glitter in the periwinkle dream bubble scoop Sunday
that I got. So what did you use?
So I use both.
So I use a bath bomb, which is a calling bath bomb in the periwinkle
dream bubble scoop Sunday.
So what you do is you put the scoop, the dream bubble in first as the bath is going.
And then you have to put in the bath bomb after when the tub has been full.
Also, I had to really scrub the hell out of the bathtub last night
because I was like, I got to get this clean if I'm going to sit in a pool.
I take a bath once every five years, maybe. Yeah. Yeah.
And I'll be I'm six, three years.
I'm six, three. I would say years old. Jesus.
Losing my mind. Six, three.
And I do not fit in that tub very well upstairs.
It is a small tub.
But I was like, I am a theme park journalist and I have to do this.
So I filled it up.
I'm a little concerned you combined items, though.
Well, he told me to. He said that was the he said that was the best way to do it.
That's why I got it.
I asked him what the what the best way to do.
That's just a hard sell.
Well, it was a hard sell.
But he was explaining to me that this part was a aromatherapy.
This part was more for moisturizing your skin.
You know, there's only two people in this group of four who fight like a married couple.
And it's not the people who are married.
Fair enough. Fair enough.
That's a good point.
Well, let's see what he did in a second.
We don't even know what he did.
Maybe he's oh, you're going to have the same reaction.
No matter what I did.
Maybe you ate the periwinkle dream bubble scoop Sunday.
So I did it.
And for the first, I hadn't taken a bath.
So really, this is mostly going to be
commenting on what the bath is like for a six, three man in a tiny bathtub.
Because it for once we will not have supplemental photos on Twitter.
I felt like Rafael in the first Ninja Turtles movie where he's like in the tub.
It's too big. He's too big for it.
Or like in The Matrix, when they get like they're just like slid out
and like it's uncomfortable and they're just like a prone body.
So like I don't feel good today from
lying in this bathtub for an hour.
This is a bath tree.
But it's not the bath treats fall because I found the bath treat very nice.
I found the aroma very pleasant.
I don't know that I'm going to do this.
Maybe once we move out of here and get a better tub,
I could see doing this once in a while.
I find it very pleasant.
The only problem, again, bath problem, not bath treat problem,
is that I cannot get to bed after a bath because my body temperature is so fucking weird.
It took takes me an hour to readjust to the outside world again.
I don't know why that is,
because it would be nice if I could go right to bed.
Did not happen. Jason is looking at me like he went right to bed after.
All right. I've said all I have to say, Jason, let's see what you did.
All right, Martha. Fine.
Jason, I should do Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf on stage.
That might be what this is like.
All right. Well, I land work.
And what's her name?
So I was concerned about not having time for a bath.
I was also concerned because I feel like I didn't see the cheaper bath item.
So I thought, well, if I'm going to spend eleven dollars,
I want to get my money's worth.
And I was also trying to find a treat that appeals to me.
You get the milkshake.
I did not get the milk. Damn it. OK.
How do I work? You pour a milk.
It's a milkshake.
It's just kind of like it's it looks like a milkshake, but inside is powder.
Yeah. So it's kind of the same.
He said it's actually very similar to what I did.
A literal nightmare.
I had a nightmare where I went for a milkshake, but it was sand.
Horrible.
So I was going back and forth between the donuts and the popsicles.
Now, I'm very picky with sense, too.
I don't like a lot of sense.
I have a sensitive nose.
So I was trying to find one.
I like I didn't want to smell particularly sweet,
but I am OK with coconut stuff.
So I got this coconut pineapple doughnut soap.
Whoa. What it is.
It's like a doughnut.
And it's just a bar of soap that looks like a doughnut.
Now, it has sprinkles on top.
The sprinkles are also soap, but they just kind of fall off
as you are, let's say, unwrapping it from the package or using it in the shower.
Also, like it's got like a little
little icing and like a little mini doughnut.
So it's like, well, you can't scrub with that side.
But then the other side is just like a flat.
Oh, my God.
And it also just like I'm not either a huge fan of bar soap to begin with.
I find it dries out my skin too much.
It is a little uncomfortable.
So it's fine. It smells.
You were cleaning yourself with a doughnut last night.
No, this morning, this morning, this morning, 9am.
You took a shower with a doughnut.
And also, I mean, this is the greatest thing that's happened on this podcast.
It's going to take me months to use this.
I feel like you feel clean.
I feel clean. I feel like fine.
But it also like you smell like coconut too.
Not really. It's kind of that generic kind of bar soapy kind of smell.
Like I kind of let down.
Yeah, I don't.
I don't think it's a let down for the next month.
Jason will be using a doughnut to clean himself.
That's terrific. That's the greatest thing I've ever heard.
I mean, I like to switch it up.
I, you know, I got a lot of hotel soaps to go to.
Oh, yeah.
Should we explain that that was tweeted about?
But somebody that somebody brought you.
Oh, yes. A couple of very nice listeners came to Mike and I show at UCB.
Yes. And they came up to me and said, we just want to say hi.
And also, we brought you something in tribute.
And it was a lovely Pixar pure bag of each two Disney hotel soaps.
And that is the nicest.
And they were so nice.
And I'd like to say to the fans out there, keep it coming.
Jason would like as much of this as you can get any hotel.
Any hotel you get.
I don't want a single thing.
If you saw me somewhere, if you knew you were going to see me for some reason,
give me a soap doughnut to give to Jason.
I want all gel fan treats to be that.
Let's see if we can keep up when this one runs out, if you can replace it
with a complimentary new doughnut.
Yeah. Anyway, the soap doughnut, I guess it's fine.
It didn't seem that much nicer than I thought.
It would be a little more moisturizing.
But again, like, did you talk to an employee at all?
Or every employee I talked to just kept saying
what I would look at something that could go like you can smell it, too.
It's just like, don't just look at it, smell it.
That's the other thing.
Like, it didn't have a ton of sense.
I feel like that one popsicle smell, though it was kind of vanilla.
But it was like, oh, this feels like it might really be overpowering. Right.
Fruity sense typically try to learn.
They tend to meld together to like, yeah, smell one.
It sort of kills your senses.
And they all just smell like a mishmash of fruit. Yeah. Right.
If you like if you smelled 20 things in a row, you'd only smell the first two.
Yeah. Or it would just all start to you forget.
Sure. Yeah.
I remember that coffee one that we smelled. That was terrible.
Yeah, that was smell like coffee.
It was like a kind of a one for boys with tobacco.
Really? Yeah.
That smelled horrible.
That was OK. Now, that's what I call a treat.
Delicious tobacco.
Yeah, I don't.
That's why I went for the ones that like seemed like they were just slightly
dressed up, traditional bath things, something that would seem practical.
Yeah, because there's a lot of nonsense in there.
I also like when I take a bath once in a blue moon, I'd like to have a beer with it.
Maybe listen to a podcast.
I had a grape diet soda while I was in the bath.
Oh, a grape diet soda. Yeah.
And maybe my girlfriend took a photo of me with it and we'll post it.
No, it's not anything indecent.
Chillin' with some diet grape.
Here's Mike's glitter filled urethra.
Here's the X-ray x-rays from Providence St. Joe's.
Mike's glitter ridded.
Well, as you know, post that x-ray on Twitter.
In the rare event that grape soda centric urine is peed from a glittery urethra
triggers an instant tumor
that blocks the pee hole forever.
Before we wrap up, we also had
Walter's Gate in this sector.
Yeah, I annexed Walter's Gate because that is that that was where I entered
for the day to do my tour guide job.
It's right between Camacho's and the
Abercrombie Fitch, which is once the Sam Goody.
And I don't.
Hey, you know what?
Let me be real corny here.
All I want to say is I started that summer being a tour guide
without an awesome girlfriend.
And by the end of the summer, I was walking through Walter's Gate
with a lot of pep in my step.
Oh, that's nice. Thanks, Aaron.
Can I ask you, was it always like really intense in terms of metal detectors?
No, got a lot crazier.
Got a lot crazier, right?
Because I think I used to use that gate when I was an intern on the back lot.
And they would send me up for like lunch orders at City Walk sometimes.
Like you take a golf cart up there.
Yeah. And you could just walk right into City Walk
and go up to the old.
What was the taco? What's that fish? Rubio's.
They're using rubio's.
You get a bunch of orders and take the golf cart back down
some very steep hills to use a golf cart on. Yeah.
That's so scary.
It's really scary.
Now it looks like a full security checkpoint, like an airport. Mm hmm.
Yeah, yeah. It got really intense.
And I'm not sure if I think there was a real Walter.
I think Walter was the guy who checked in and I'm not sure if it still is.
I hope if he's still around, he's doing well.
But yeah, you know that.
Yeah, that first summer, I felt a lot of pride walking through there.
No, and I had to all I had to do.
My only responsibility that day was to maybe come up with a new riff
on the King Kong part.
I I also remember I remember that I took a there was a thing called the ESATS,
which was an employee satisfaction evaluation kind of thing.
And I didn't I didn't take it that seriously.
And there were a lot of people I knew who had a lot of grievances.
And I'm going to I'm going to give them a piece of my mind on this survey.
And but what I did was like I just like gave fives to everything
until the comments section.
And then I said, like, you know, the job is going fine.
But I there is this thing where, you know, we went into a soundstage.
There was an open set and then an earthquake happened during the
and I read it and the entire set flooded.
And and we received no help, even though there was a power outage.
I didn't feel like anyone cared, like no supervisors came.
And then we went into another soundstage and there was a giant ape in there
who took the tram with his hands and shook it around.
And I'm just, you know, it makes me feel I love the job.
But if I don't feel safe, maybe I have to go.
And I wrote all that out.
And then I told I told a fellow tour guide that and they were like,
well, that's a little disrespectful, don't you think?
But wow, this was not a job to take seriously.
I mean, you were very good at it.
But hey, thank you.
We know what it is.
Yeah.
They some some people did.
And there was there's a lot you had to like memorize to the to the letter.
Do you remember the whole thing?
I it's possible that if I had like the keypad in front of me
and the correct clips, I could from the beginning one time,
Aaron and I, we were driving, we were stuck in like horrible
unexpected traffic on Denim Arango.
And you said, you want to just do the tour?
And I did like a lot of it.
And it passed the time.
That might be a well, Patreon exclusive.
Scott reads the tour.
Does the tour.
Scott ASMR.
Oh, I guess.
Twist my arm. Maybe.
All right. Fine. Regular episode.
But 2006 era tour.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
So we're we're hyping Evan Almighty.
We're pushing that.
We're talking Ghost Whisperers starring Jennifer Love Hewitt
and two lesser known actors I had to mention every day due to their contracts.
When would you have started?
2006 summer. Yeah.
2006. I would.
That was when I would have been out here like interning start
a fall and of summer like 2006.
Did you guys pass through Walters Gate together?
We probably passed through.
We're on the back lot.
I may have taken one of your tours.
Whoa. Although I feel like you I do remember one or two tour guides
where I was like, yeah, they were really good.
And then there would be somewhere I'd be like, how is that guy still doing?
Like people just did not care.
Yeah, yeah.
The yeah, it's it's it's possible.
It's possible that, yeah, like Walters Gate, like that sign,
all the most beautiful people passed through it.
And it's possible we were two beautiful ships.
That's right. In the night through Walters Gate.
You're going to make me cry.
I'll make you cry at that one.
The me and Jason one and not the one about you.
Nice thing.
Both in our khakis sleepily asking, hey, I'm going to go get a burger today.
Does anyone want me to pick up anything?
That is a thing by Walter.
I've realized being up there at the lunch hour on weekdays is just
how many people walking around CityWalk are people in business casual
from the offices worth a lot grabbing a quick bite to eat
with their generous employee discounts.
It's 10 percent enough for you.
Is that it?
I think that it wasn't much.
Not for me. I got I got 10 percent off of Nectar.
What? Why?
Because you are you a pass holder?
I said, actually, I had my past just ran out like a month ago.
And he was like, I can give it to you.
This was how we even got anything for a blossom.
Yeah, there's there's discounts to be had.
Are there everywhere?
Well, a lot of places.
I've been doing this entire CityWalk thing.
Yeah. Full price every time.
Passholders. Why? Mine ran out.
And we've been up there like 17 goddamn times.
Yeah. We've we'll be up 17 more.
We could have saved like $200.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Should have asked at the water coffins.
Oh, yeah, we forgot about that.
We'd have had a down payment for a house by now.
A Lude owning.
No. But what's that when you have memories?
I bet drinks aren't you don't get discounted, though.
So we shouldn't get a pass
before my pass renewed before we go to Holland, the moon and spend $300 on
the jello shots and jello shots.
Dory and Dory, please.
Were it only in a bottle of potion, then it would.
And that is that is that's going to haunt me that that's not there anymore.
Oh, boy.
Aaron, thank you for sharing your memories of Wizards past.
And I can officially say, Aaron Gardner, you survived podcast, the ride.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, thank you.
Thanks so much for doing it.
Is there is there anything you would like to plug?
I have a website, I guess.
Aaron Gardner dot com.
That's correct. Yes.
I don't do a whole I'm on Twitter, but I only follow podcast,
the ride and Pibo Bryson.
If you follow me, I follow you back.
I don't even follow.
Yeah, I don't even follow Scott.
You don't follow us individually.
You only follow podcast.
I only follow podcast.
Thanks for boosting the like signal.
It's it's much appreciated.
But wait, before we go, the stone,
the stone is appearing.
The stone's emerging.
Oh, wow. There it is.
It's beautiful.
It looks it looks like a nectar bath treat.
OK, I guess that was inevitable.
It's about the size of a stone.
It's a stone that it looks like a doughnut that is flavored for a cupcake.
But it still has the marbling of a stone.
It still is like.
Jason, are you washing yourself with it right now?
Yeah. And it's.
I'm crazy.
Yeah, the scent is dissipating as you're rubbing it on your skin.
It smells like it doesn't smell.
It smells like dip.
It doesn't smell like tobacco.
It smells like Chaw.
It's a weird one.
It's a weird stone.
I guess that's they're not all winners.
That's what the sector keepers skin is made of, I guess.
That's what post afterworld skin composition is.
Yeah, that's fair.
Well, thanks for giving it to us anyway.
Yeah. Hey, check out Aaron Gardner dot com.
You know what you got are all those you got those those cards and the pins.
The adorable animals. Oh, yeah. That stuff out.
Well, I let the Etsy lapse. Oh, no.
Yeah, let's not do that. Yeah, they hiked up the seller fees.
Oh, all right. Well, then don't go there.
All right. Well, a good decision made then.
Screw you, Etsy.
And follow Aaron Gardner for no tweets.
Yeah, I will call you back.
Oh, at friendship 500 at friendship 500.
But you'll see a nice picture of Expo Ernie, the Vancouver.
Yeah, fair robot.
Hey, and as for us, yeah, keep liking those posts on Twitter.
Like Aaron, keep keep giving us good reviews on iTunes and
join the Facebook group.
A lot of fun stuff going on in there.
Someone posted a great
it's goofy, but he's a giant golf ball.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Character.
A lot of good stuff on that Facebook.
A lot of fun stuff going on there.
All right.
Then we'll see you tomorrow for for more bullshit.
We'll cross to the other side of Walters Gate
and talk about fountains or something. Yeah.
All right. Thanks for joining us.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.