Forever...
Dog.
When your town has let you down
When your port has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll, a place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight
Podcast The Ride presents The City Walk Saga, a daily 19 part, extremely necessary series exploring the stores, restaurants, and wonderful magic that make up universal City Walk Hollywood.
Hello, welcome to Podcast The Ride The City Walk Saga, Sector 10.
It's like a Super Size Me, but with zero points.
Joining us as always, the increasingly beleaguered me, Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson.
I'm feeling good.
Oh, great.
Congrats.
Let's try to take some of your luster and Jason Sheridan.
I feel good because this is now we're a little over halfway done.
Right? 19 sectors.
Yes.
Oh, that's exactly right.
We crossed the boundary at nine and a half.
Yeah.
It's like a marathon now where we know we've hit the midpoint in the marathon and now you know, well, I did this many.
Surely I can do the same amount.
So like, I'm feeling good.
It seems like Scott has hit the part in the marathon where he went, I don't want to finish the marathon.
Well, I might have hit it in sector two.
Okay, fair enough.
I might have.
Maybe I'm a quitter.
And yeah, you're right about looking at distance, but I'm looking ahead to when we inevitably do City Walk Orlando.
Yes.
Downtown Disney.
Anaheim.
And then like Orlando.
And then like the Outranks.
Disney Springs.
Disney Springs we did, but like, oh, sorry.
Oh, I thought Disney.
I'm getting them all confused.
There's too many malls clattering around in my brain.
Yeah.
Disney Village is the Paris one, but that's we covered that plenty.
I also heard that they were going to redo Disney Village soon.
Maybe that's like part of the plans.
That's right.
So much money going into that park.
We'll have to do that again.
But somebody, oh yeah.
All right.
Well, pack your bags to France, everybody.
We're just visiting them.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's here.
The sector keeper's back.
Boys, don't go to France.
Oh no, why?
Because I need you.
Oh yeah.
You're halfway there.
You're right.
We have to focus on one set of sectors at a time.
You're looking so much better, sector keeper.
Thank you.
Yes, my color's filling in and I've put on some weight.
You were a little emaciated before, so I'm not going to say that's a bad thing.
Will you give me strength and you fill the void that was my soul.
Cool.
I have a sector assignment.
Please discuss sector 10.
Of course.
Menchies, flip-flop shop, Cinnabon, lids.
Okay.
Interesting.
Another wall heavy one.
Here's a quick thing, sector keeper.
We have a future guest coming up, Nick Mundy.
Do you know Nick Mundy?
Have you heard?
You can't watch the internet or anything.
No, I've heard of him.
Oh, you've heard of him.
Okay, well that's great.
He's coming on the show soon and he actually asked me if we can just move lids to sector
11.
Whoa.
So we're going to move.
What?
He was just saying he wanted to talk about lids because he had a sort of affection and
he said it would be great if they were both in the same.
Is that okay?
The sector keeper is looking for ways to make this okay, but I can tell right away it's
not okay with him.
He looks upset and I am indignant.
Okay.
Hang on.
So he's trying to annex it into his sector?
Nick Mundy texted me and he said, can we do lids and, because he wants to do the Raider
image, which is also part of sector 11.
And he just said, can't they both?
Why they're so close to each other?
He said, first of all, why is he communicating with both of us separately?
I gave him the list and I, and he said, I'd be into Raider store or lids, the word or
I sent him the list and he said, how about Raider store?
And now suddenly he's pulling another one.
Nick, Nick Mundy has plenty of avenues to talk about hats.
He does not need to pull his hat obsession.
I agree.
Double up.
Yes.
Does Nick Mundy want my soul in hell?
I probably, evidently.
I don't know this kind of cowboy around might work on Tiger town or whatever his show is
called, but that, that Texas cowboy stuff doesn't fly here.
That doesn't fly in the walk.
For one thing, there's a gap between the lids and the Bucatabepo.
There's an entryway.
There's not even stores there.
There's a taxi stand.
Yeah.
Are we now saying that-
This is an America Samoa.
Could he, yeah.
Well, he's still got the spirit of the, of the Texans that were, they were robbing the
land from different.
They were part of Mexico.
I don't know the history.
Some of Texas got stolen.
Yeah.
And Mundy's, uh, Mundy's operating with that level of, uh, callousness.
All right.
So, I mean, what am I going to do?
Am I going to tell him no?
You're going to tell him that there is a special boy who has laid down ground rules and that
no guest has required any changing of the rules.
Everyone has fallen in line.
And why is he special enough?
Look, he's a nice guy.
He was the best man at my wedding.
I, I look, he's fine, but that doesn't give him God powers.
Bad man.
Okay.
All right.
Well, I'm glad there is at least three way agreement, but I guess the choice isn't yours,
Mike, but I, how can you really in the face of this?
I didn't think it was a big deal, but if, look, I don't want to put a ghost boy into
an earlier grave.
Into a different type of eternal grave.
The sector keepers rules are laws.
And I'm assuming he got that plain snapback hat.
He's wearing the one that's like kind of darkish blue, but it doesn't have any logo on it.
It's like a character wears in a movie where they're trying to lay low and you're like,
where did they just find that plain baseball cap that fits them perfectly?
He's been wearing one of those this whole time.
Did you get that at Lids?
He's like the sparkies of earth.
Oh no.
You're equating Nick Mundy.
He's now one of the biggest villains of this 19 part series.
Okay.
Well, look, I don't disagree.
I hate to throw the guy under the bus.
As I said, a lot of good Marys, a good guest before, but I don't like making demands.
Here's what I'll say.
We will do everything we can to stop him from talking about Lids.
We will do our best to stop him from talking about Lids.
He is a wild man.
If he starts talking, I don't know what will happen, but we will do our best.
I think a little of what's happening.
He was on the show.
If you didn't hear his episode, he talked about Astroworld.
There was a lot of back and forth about whether or not he's a bully, he's defending himself
against charges of being a bully.
I feel like he is bullying this series and he's bullying the poor little sick, dying
sector killer.
I'm already dead.
Oh, that's right.
Dying more and more.
Dying more.
That sounds like that unstoppable force that is Nick Mundy has not yet worked.
He has met him.
I've met him, but he hasn't yet met the immovable object that is Jason Sheridan in City Walk.
Did you call yourself the immovable object?
Yeah.
Wow.
Like the blob or the junkernut.
If we're talking X-Men rules, I mean.
The blob, Jason Sheridan is the blob or the juggernaut.
Man.
Andy's Shoto, the Ready Player One key chain.
Do you remember a week ago?
Shoto is whispering in my ear right now and it is such a string of foul-mouthed vulgarity.
I don't even want to repeat it.
Shoto is peering.
Let's not put him on mic.
So here's what we're going to do.
We are going to talk about lids.
If Nick Mundy is successfully able to shush us and get in a good, I don't know, like now
I'm worried he's going to tie us all up or something, take the mics, go into another
room in your apartment and do his lids material.
I'm looking through the sacred scrolls that you showed me before we started recording
today, that say the sectors on them.
And now I'm reading sort of the language after.
They're written on Popcornopolis wrappers.
Yes, exactly.
The scrolls have been written on the Popcornopolis wrappers.
And it says that he who talks about sectors out of order or stores that are in different
sectors add length, ad nauseum can destroy the order of the sectors and throw them into
disarray, creating new sectors that would reformat CityWalk in a totally different
way.
Skewing the space-time continuum, the specter-time, sector-time continuum into an alternate tangent
where corrupt leaders run rampant.
He's a biff.
He's a biff-tan and we got to stand up to him tomorrow and get the almanac back.
Right, because God knows what would happen.
All of a sudden a sector is margaritaville and it's sugar.
They're not even anywhere close to each other.
No.
Or you would break up the sector order where the Hard Rock Cafe retail store is in a different
sector than the Hard Rock Cafe, which is very important because those are the numbers that
the official CityWalk map gave us.
You can't have the Hard Rock Cafe and the Hard Rock Cafe store together.
Yes.
Is Mundy insane?
He might be insane.
The lines were drawn with my blood.
Oh, God.
We're going to do our very best.
God, harden the blood, please.
We're going to do our very best to stand up to this bad man.
I had a choice.
Be a donor or draw the maps.
At least your blood was given to something useful.
Yes.
That's true.
Not to some guy who would have wasted it.
Please, boys, do your best.
Okay.
Well, the best thing that we can do is to do our lids material right now.
Here's what's in my list.
The hats on the outside of the lids glow.
That's the end of my lids material.
Mine just says a lot of hats.
So I'm tapped.
Lot of hats.
Let's move on.
Mike, you got anything quick?
I'd love to tell you guys that I bought 10 hats and wore them to various events.
I did not.
I walked in, I said, a lot of hats here, and I was done.
All right.
I'm going to leave this done.
Moving on.
If Monday has more to say, he better keep it to his fucking self and his cats.
Your gravity gave me strength.
He can do it on his Tiger Town podcast or whatever.
Yeah.
Do your Patreon only lids spectacle, but not here.
We also, by the way, we already did locker room by lids.
Yes.
Yeah, which is a different store.
And in a different sector, locker room by lids is in sector nine.
Covered in Uncle Drew.
And lids is in sector 10.
I think you should post a screenshot of the text and so that our fans can look at it and
see the forceful, frightening language.
I can provide a JPEG.
Oh, wow.
OK, thank you so much.
Thanks.
You can do the power of a phone screenshot.
Yes.
Wow.
You're certainly magical.
God, some people just want to watch the world burn.
Well, when things are heating up, you got to cool down with some delicious menchies.
Yes.
Menchies.
Sector keeper, is that a favorite of yours?
I love menchies.
So there's a menchie boy on the front.
There's like another kind of fun kid type character.
This one's a little more fantastical.
He feels like a candy person from like Candyland or something.
Brother.
Oh, really?
He is your literal brother, just sort of like a guy that you like pal around with and is
like a best friend of yours.
A literal brother, yes.
He was my brother.
Yes.
Menchie was.
Menchie is still alive.
The boy.
The boy Menchie is still alive.
Yes.
The boy who lived, Menchie.
Yes, the boy who lived.
In your family's lineology.
Yes.
Lineage.
And Menchie is generally, because there's a lot of Menchies around here.
There was a frozen yogurt by Craze in Los Angeles.
I feel like it started by Pinkberry a little bit.
And then Menchie's kind of emerged as maybe the more popular one.
There used to be a yogurt land.
Is that the same space?
Same space.
Yogurt land gave way to Menchie.
And if that special little boy can rise and reign triumphant, then so can you, Sector
Keeper.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah.
I believe in you.
And the Menchie, as I said, there's like a boy character and it's like his full body.
Most of the Menchies just have his head in like when the locations are on Los Angeles,
but this is a full body.
But a very small interior location.
So a great nice kind of out, excuse me, exterior of the building.
But again, a very limiting small area for you to actually go around, get frozen yogurt
and get your toppings.
Yeah.
One thing I noticed about this place, and I think this is actually most Menchies have
this available, but especially this one, it felt like they were really pushing it.
And I think I know why.
And I sent it to you guys.
There is like a giant floor to ceiling window decal that says pineapple Dole Whip Sorbet
slash float.
Oh, that's right.
And it's on the website too.
But I mean, in a theme park adjacent setting, that shot's fired.
I mean, come on, that's shots fired at Disney, right?
Like the one of the homes of the Dole Whip.
I believe they used to advertise Dole Whip is like, you can only get it at the Dole Plantation
or Disney World or Disneyland.
Now it's everywhere.
I don't know what exclusivity or licensing change, but like Dole Whip is everywhere.
But it was a little drawing for me to see like a Dole Whip advertisement at Universal,
you know?
So it's upsetting you a little bit.
I suppose.
It would be like seeing like a Butterbeer at Disney.
Oh, at Disney?
Yeah.
If it was like, what would they call it?
What would Disney's version of it be?
Like, it's just a cream soda basically.
Woody Sweet Sarsaparilla.
Oh, that's good.
Right?
I don't have a complaint if that showed up.
Hey, pretty good.
Yeah, that's good.
All right.
Yeah.
We're putting each other off.
I got no problem.
Man, that's pretty, yeah.
We should go to you for more ideas for like drinks and treats.
They should.
That's a mayor thing.
They should consult.
I would love an expensive consulting fee for minimal work.
That would be a good mayor thing though, is the mayor gets to name all the treats and
he has like his ideas get to be brought into the world.
Would you settle for being the mayor of CityWalk if Disney doesn't work out?
And I think it will, but.
I think so.
I think I would take that on.
They're good people there.
You know, they need a strong leader.
And you tell them, you know, the sector keeper when you're in.
Well, sure.
I'm happy to put a good word in.
Oh, I mean, that's a big endorsement coming from you, sector keeper.
Sure, sure.
Letter of recommendation written in your blood.
Absolutely.
If there's some left, yes.
Just a quick trip, I hope.
My last thought on Menchies is that I don't like do it yourself frozen yogurt.
I don't like putting the toppings on myself.
I want them to do it for me.
Out of laziness or out of you don't trust yourself?
I trust myself, but I feel that it's more fun when I get handed a thing that's been
sort of constructed versus something that I put together.
Because it always like, it looks worse.
I don't have the technique that someone working there might have.
Jason's looking at me very suspiciously.
No, you are wrong.
Yeah.
OK.
Because frozen yogurt is nothing more than a topping delivery mechanism.
Right?
I disagree with that.
That's a crazy statement to say.
I mean, I like frozen yogurt, but I'm never like, oh, I just want some plain frozen yogurt.
I want the toppings, baby.
That's crazy.
I want it to get real.
I want a lot of toppings.
Come on.
What do you mean come on?
You would have just a regular frozen yogurt.
I mean, if you're at a TCBY in 1994, but nowadays it's a topping world, baby.
I like toppings.
I like putting toppings on frozen yogurt, but it's crazy to say that no one would want
the regular frozen yogurt.
I want I was going to say loaded up, but again, I'm conscious that it's per weight pricing.
I want it loaded up.
You bring your own personal scale to make sure before you get to the front.
And mine is rigged.
Trust me.
That doesn't make sense because it would fuck you over.
No, it's rigged to be.
Never mind.
I see it's higher.
So you trick yourself with it.
I see.
Shaves off the bottom of the bowl, like the little extra paper part, which saves you,
which gives you like three cents off.
And you attach a tiny balloon as you put it on the scale.
So it's just a little scale, but I'm loaded up with toppings and I want it to.
I want it.
I want a soup.
It's melt and you frozen yogurt.
I find melts quickly.
So it becomes topping soup pretty quickly.
It does.
I agree with that.
But it's just toppings and you don't want the yogurt to be good.
No, I want the yogurt to be good too, but I'm there for the toppings.
Why is it either or?
It's somewhere in the middle.
I didn't say it's either or.
I said it's in the middle.
I'm just saying what he's saying is crazy.
He's calling me crazy for not wanting to do it myself, which I don't think is crazy because
I like a pink, even though pink berry has its problems.
I like somebody giving me a nice, like sort of constructed little dessert.
It's aesthetically pleasing to me.
I can't argue with the aesthetics.
Well that's all I was.
I like that too.
So all right.
You got to, I don't know what.
You control your own ratio though with, you know, you can get things in weird if I, and
if like I want just two gummy worms also, because when I don't ever buy a bag of gummy
worms, here's just a little, a little extra treat.
Like almost like a fortune cookie unrelated to the meal, but a nice little aftermath.
I like to load it up.
I mean, probably because I mean, it's hard to mess up frozen yogurt, but make design
your own burger is kind of, it can be a disaster.
What do you put on it?
What is your, what do I put on it?
Okay.
So, you know, I like the crushed up like cone pieces.
Like an ice cream cone.
Yeah.
I like a rainbow sprinkles.
Got to go for like a fudge, a little fudge, a little caramel, maybe some peanut butter
cups.
The cookie dough and brownie bites are always disappointing.
Maybe a little bit of fruit, but.
No, no.
No.
Fuck that.
Every now and then I like to get one or two of like the boba or the lychee, like, cause
I don't get those a lot, but I don't want a lot of them.
The boba I can't do after that mini monster.
I know you're still scared.
I don't think I'm ever going to do boba again.
Can you guess the weight at Menchie's?
I forget.
Wait, what do you mean?
If you guess the weight on the scale before you put it on, sometimes you get a discount
over.
Really?
I've never seen that either.
I certainly don't think a theme park one where the prices are already going to be inflated
a little would have that.
I thought you were asking Jason if just by holding it in his hand, he would know the
exact weight.
Sometimes I come pretty close.
Sometimes I more like the dollars.
Sometimes I'm like, I bet this is going to be like 250.
What is your ideal weight for a Menchie's bowl?
I guess that depends on what the price point is going to be.
Okay.
So you check the price point before you go into the Menchie's to know how much you're
loading up.
I try to be cognizant of it.
I'm not sure what the conversion rates these days.
Yeah.
What is the yogurt conversion?
Check the stocks app on the phone.
Let me check.
Has Nikkei opened yet?
No, too late.
On this coast.
Like a card counter at a casino.
They ask you to leave, but it's not illegal.
Not illegal?
What am I doing wrong?
But the winner stands to gain five extra peanut butter cups.
Whoa, that's a jackpot, those peanut butter cups are heavy.
A dollar and 10 cents of added value.
Oh, oh, oh, all right.
Really?
Were you getting tired of that?
Oh, um.
Smackdown.
You're tall.
Is that your keeper?
Which way we going next?
I need you boys to venture into Flip Flop Shop.
The Flip Flop Shop made famous on the Flex Watches episode of The Prophet.
Yeah.
The Prophet Town.
It culminates.
That's like the big grand arena, like the final place where those brothers who lost
their mom do battle.
Right?
They do like a presentation.
They do a presentation with a display case of their watches where each different design
represents a different proceeds go to a different charity.
That's right.
Yes.
And that's different charitable causes.
And if you know, if you go into the Flip Flop Shop today, do you see this display?
No.
Wow.
Geez.
It was an old flex.
That was a season one.
Yeah, that was an older one.
Flex Watches still in business, seem to be doing well, judging by their online store.
But I did not see a Flex Watches display in this Flip Flop Shop.
It's very small.
It's a very small Flip Flop Shop.
To even get retail space within the Flip Flop Shop.
Yeah, there's almost nothing to work with.
I feel like maybe businesses should avoid city walk altogether.
In a lot of cases, I think you aren't...
You know, I was just with my friend up there and he proposed the idea in general that maybe
Sephora, like that Sephora is probably not the location making the most money of all
the Sephoras, but it serves as a big ad for the other Sephoras that's seen by everybody
going into the theme park.
So maybe all of these stores are fronts in a way and advertising for the other stores
that people are more likely to actually go to.
That's fair.
I mean, a portion of the people at City Walk are tourists.
So like, I think it is good to have some...
Not just locals doing podcasts.
Not just locals doing podcasts as they slowly crack up.
I think it is like a hat shop, Flip Flops.
If you're out of town or you're staying at the Hilton or the Sheridan, oh, I forgot.
It's so sunny here.
I forgot a hat or I forgot Flip Flops.
Let me walk across the busy uphill street all the way to the end of City Walk opposite
of the hotels, the furthest away and pay $15 more than I would pay if I took a shuttle
to the CVS down the street.
Potentially, but you don't know the layout of Studio City adjacent areas.
Yeah, and I like you, you've outed yourself as living in this neck of the woods, which
narrows it down for stalkers to find you.
Please murder me.
Drink them of any podcast toast.
Oh my.
And no, I made it.
I was murdered by a stalker.
I do think Sephora, and there's probably a lot of truth to the fact that just having
a nice big store is a nice ad for it, but I do think Sephora is a practical thing that
plenty of people walk by and go, oh, I need something in there.
That makes a lot of sense.
There are stores that make less sense to me.
The guest store makes less sense to me being there because it's kind of like high end shopping
and it's like- Minimal inventory too.
Right.
It's minimal.
What are you doing in there?
Sephora actually seems a lot more practical of like, I do need something in there.
I forgot it on the trip or I ran out of something.
And people love it.
Sephora and Starbucks, the only two locations I think that are at City Walk and Downtown
Disney.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Is that right?
Because my girlfriend, Lindsay, goes in that Sephora every time we're in Downtown Disney.
She loves that Sephora.
I have been in like, I'll be like, I'll be at D Street and you'll be in Sephora.
Like sorry, mom.
I'll be over in the place where they have the superheroes and Star Wars stuff while you
look for stupid makeup.
I'll be doing the full void VR experience as soon as you just quickly pop in to get
some eyeshadow.
You know what?
You're on your way to, you're at that Sephora on your way to the parks.
You get one of those, you get like a sample makeover.
They do a makeover in the store and now you look your best for donkey in the park.
Where Maryland, if you run into, you know, a star.
If you got some competition, then you know, like if you're trying to be the prettiest
gal in the park, prettier than Marilyn.
Or the man that's from New York.
Yeah, the New York tenement couple who yell at you.
Yes, on the second floor, yes.
If you look your best post makeover, you're less likely to get razed by the Brooklyn couple
in the window that yells at you.
Oh, Marone, where are you from, idiot?
I don't think they're legally allowed to call you an idiot.
No, they're not.
I think they have to be like silly guy or something.
Yeah, that might be the worst thing they can they can call you.
Pittsburgh Pirates hat.
They're not going to be my Yankees.
That's pretty good.
Yeah, I'd love to do some work for those guys.
Where were we?
Flip flop shops.
Oh, Fallen Brothers flip flop shops was used to be the wound and wound toy company.
Oh, yeah.
It was a Melrose Avenue.
Melrose and Avenue were Boulevard Melrose place in.
Who cares?
It was on Melrose and then they moved it to City Walk Avenue.
Avenue Avenue.
The little wind up shop was a local spot.
I think so.
How about that?
I'm not sure if it's still there, but very poorly reviewed on Yelp.
Oh, I bought someone a little music box there once.
They liked it.
Yeah.
I forget the City Walk one kind of poorly reviewed as well.
But there was a review that had a great beginning, which I will read from very quickly.
The Rolling Stones once sang that you had to start them up.
It's true.
All great things need a bit of a wind up.
Incredible review.
Wow.
You had to start them up.
Webster's Dictionary defines wind as.
Also, Mick Jagger, he sings start me up, not start us up.
And he's speaking for himself.
I don't know if Charlie Watts needs to be started up.
Charlie Watts seems like he's always asleep.
So maybe he I don't think he would like to be started up in any context.
Yeah, he looks annoyed to be still playing the drums.
But I figured out something else by now.
And Mick is singing to like arouse him, right?
That's the start me up means.
I guess.
Yes.
Start me up.
I never stop.
Boy, that was a rock lyric.
Make me a lot of messages.
Make me horny and I'll be horny forever is what he's saying.
For a long time.
I mean, that's what all of it's about.
You think any wind up toys ever made anybody horny?
Well, Sector Keep, I guess I can't ask you.
You're a child.
That's inappropriate.
That's a illegal question to answer, I feel.
Just abstain.
Just abstain, please.
Don't humor.
Oh, you know what I missed?
Also Fallen Brothers.
I missed about Lids that it was once something called Shimoni Sterling Silver Jewelry, which
is still open to this day at the Planet Hollywood Shops Mall in Las Vegas, the scariest shopping
center on the strip.
It has two and a half stars and the pictures of the merchandise look shoddy at best.
Man, do you remember?
Sorry, Sector Keep, there you go.
If Nick Mundy speaks equal time about that shop, I will allow him to talk about Lids
as well.
Oh, that'll kind of balance it out by doing by bringing history into it.
Yes, yes.
But he has to know about it.
Yes, the scales must be balanced.
OK, so we'll ask him if he knows what store was there under it originally.
And that'll that'll set the universe back in balance.
50-50 he knows.
I think it's a good shot.
That only leaves Cinnabon.
Also, very poorly reviewed on Yelp.
A lot of one star people are mad at this Cinnabon in particular.
And I saw people calling out.
You talk about the City Walk Markups.
I saw a tell of eight dollar Cinnabons that don't look aesthetically pleasing from their
photos.
Get out of here to them.
To that price point.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, I don't know.
That's worse than Spark.
I mean, nothing's worse than Sparky's.
But Cinnabon's thrive on Markups as they are in airports and expensive locations.
But I think a Cinnabon also to put on my profit helmet, I think a Cinnabon probably costs
about 22 cents to manufacture.
Great margins on that.
Great margins.
Very good margins.
I think this this sector might be in the running again.
I know I mentioned others, but like this is the is this the most mall mall sector, mally
sector?
Pretty boring.
There's a food court of the city.
City food, though, is, of course, like a food court upstairs.
So that's pretty mall to that's true, which is unique.
A bad restaurant terrible.
Now made me ill before that.
Pics, pigs, not the poke place.
OK, this is the city.
The Cinnabon is one of the first things like the main entrance to City Walk.
If you're like being dropped off there by a Lyft or an Uber, this is one of the main
like things when you walk in.
It's like here's the Cinnabon.
Like that's the icon of the park if you're just walking in for the first time on Lyft.
I believe now they've built in if you're picking up or dropping off there.
There's like the Universal Studios stop.
And then this is like the City Universal East stop.
Yes.
Oh, different entry points.
Drop offs.
Yeah.
Well, I did this.
Oh, my friend Ryan, who I went up with the other day, he I was explaining the City Walk
19 part saga to him.
And to get up to have the bill that we walked from the base of the he actually went to the
taxi stop here.
He flagged a taxi down like in New York City and hopped in it and sped away when you were
done explaining it.
This person is a graduate of Harvard Law, Yale Law, and is now a on track to be a tenured
law professor at a university in Hong Kong.
So he's happy his old buddy Scott's doing great.
Just like you guys.
We have been to downtown Disney.
We have been to City Walk.
I think we're we've got a pretty impressive list of credits.
We do.
So we say stuff like this mall was bad and this mall was good.
This that's the Cinnabon price point is unacceptable.
A dollar fifty for extra icing.
No way.
So trying to deal with the myriad of like other past City Walk establishments is probably
as confusing and frustrating as dealing with the mainland Chinese government as dealing
with Chinese human rights law.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think we're providing relationship they have with Hong Kong.
Yes.
Yeah.
Just as important of a service.
Anyway, I described the series to him and then the first thing you see walking it up
to that point is like two neon Cinnabons, which I like.
I like those neon Cinnabons.
That's one of the best thing I can say about the Cinnabon is that I like the fun neon cinnamon
buns.
He was he maybe struggled to see how discussion of these things would sustain 19 episodes.
But all Ryan, if you're listening, hey, you're you're waiting in it.
Proofs in the pudding, proofs in the Cinnabon frosting, 19 parts going down real smooth.
So oh, oh, more fallen brothers.
Cinnabon used to be something called Bonitas Frites.
And this was a location specifically for Belgian fries.
And that is all that they had Belgian fries.
And this place sounded pretty good.
I screenshot it a little.
It was written about in a book and you could get malt vinegar, red wine vinegar, even catsup,
salt, pepper, cayenne, mustard.
This is interesting.
For a few extra cents.
So Jason's out.
You could get remoulade sauce spiked with tarragon, a creamy, did I say it right?
I don't know what it is.
Dijon mustard dip.
This place sounds much better than Cinnabon.
Jason, they sat up.
Jason's more color in his face.
Remoulade, often found on a po'boy sandwich, found in New Orleans.
Delicious sauce.
Preach, Jason, preach.
You had me, I mean, I was halfway out the door when you said a few extra cents.
But once you got tarragon in there, that's a bad herb.
I am not a tarragon fan.
I'm a time boy.
I love the taste of time.
Tarragon, no thank you, sir.
That is already delicious.
It does not need any pesky tarragon in it.
Laying down the law.
Wow, testify.
This is reminding me, like we mentioned on the crepe cafe, going really in on those fries
with lots of dipping sauce.
Well, it's just more, which is very European.
That's the cultured way to eat your fries.
Also from this book, apparently I screen shotted.
A fall of empire.
Same book in America.
So quote the author, not myself.
This is the author talking.
David McCullough?
I think so, probably.
Something called a sauce andalouse, which no Spaniard would recognize, is basically
the garlic mayonnaise tinted pink with peppers.
So I want to challenge this if you're listening and you're a Spaniard and you recognize sauce
andalouse before it was defined, let us know.
Hashtag Spaniards know.
Prove this author wrong.
Prove David.
David McCullough.
Prove David McCullough wrong.
There's a reason they wouldn't recognize it because it wasn't named after the region of
Spain.
It was named after the pixie song.
And the Andalusia moon.
Right.
Like we can on the loop.
Is that what the name of the song is?
The movie, the short experimental film is when Chen Andalu and and there is a song based
on that.
I don't know.
We get what comes out of the eyeball when it's cut open on.
I think that's what this is supposed to be.
It's like a cut open can of.
Frank Black's favorite sauce.
Cut the ribbon.
Good on you, Frank.
DeBaser is the song.
DeBaser.
OK, all right.
I'm sorry.
I know DeBaser.
Does this kind of take us to the end portion of the.
I think so.
Sector 10.
You've given me great strength, boys.
I hear it.
Boys, come close.
Yes, of course.
Come close.
Yes.
I want to give you the sector 10 stone.
Go ahead.
There you go.
Wow.
Spit it out.
It looks like a little flip flop.
Yeah, it's from.
Yes.
Its origins are from deep beneath the flip flop shop.
And the flip flop has a little fit, fit it, brim hat.
Yes.
And it's it says sector 10.
Sector 10.
Yes.
It knows it belongs there.
It knows that Lids belongs in sector 10.
That's right.
Yes.
Enjoy, boys.
Enjoy.
We love.
OK, we will.
I love getting these customized stones.
Yeah.
It makes me really proud every time we get one.
It's going to be quite a collection.
We'll take a picture, right, and put it up on the social media.
Yeah.
I'm sure for all of them.
That's no problem.
So up on film, we might have to.
Oh, that might be an issue.
They are.
They are supernatural.
They are sparkling magically.
Light seems to either be absorbed by them or sharply reflected off them.
So so this gets us this gets us to the end and tomorrow's episode is with Nick Mundy
and let's just say if you think man, man, man, man, and if he thinks he's going to come
around these parts and talk about a story that has been fully covered, we have said
everything there is to say about Lids.
Listen up tomorrow and listen to us.
Give this bully a piece of our mind if he dares cross the sector keeper.
We're waiting for you, Mundy.
Sharpening your sword, skirt your loins and prepare for war.
Right, gentlemen?
Right.
Absolutely.
Jason, AKA, Shoto.
May I make one last request?
A reminder.
Yes.
That not only your your journeys give me strength, but it helps me greatly when listeners
like and subscribe and leave a review.
Oh, yeah.
For us.
Yeah.
Podcasts are right at Gmail, podcasts right at Twitter and our Facebook group.
Our very yeah.
Our Facebook group.
It makes you big and strong.
It makes me strong and it keeps me out of hell.
Yeah.
I mean, it seems like you get wiser as these sectors go on.
I'm learning.
You didn't even know David McCullough.
I know.
Or you wouldn't even known something like that early on and you just came out of nowhere
a few minutes ago.
Smooth, smooth, smooth.
This is by Rob Thomas.
It just came to me.
Whoa, you're having visions of pop culture without even.
Well, that's a sign.
And I think that you that doesn't happen to you without the power of good reviews on iTunes.
So we want to see those iTunes reviews and we want them to say sector keeper sent me.
Let's start seeing those pop up in the store.
Thank you.
All right.
Well, we'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, boy.
This is it's going to be test.
Stay tuned, everybody.
It's going to be tough.
Come for the king.
You best not miss.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Baum, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.