Part of an adventure
Hauntcast is about an attraction so ghoulish,
it almost turned a young Mike Carlson off theme parks entirely.
Rest your weary bones in a scared chair next to a scared deer.
It's Snow White's Scary Adventures on Hauntcast, the fright.
["Spring Day's Theme Song"]
Welcome to Hauntcast, the Fright,
the show hosted by two men who were once
very scared of today's ride,
and one big brave boy who ain't scared of nothing.
I'm said big brave boy, Jason Sheridan.
Joined as always is Scott Gareder.
And I'm one of the little scaredies.
And the little scaredy Mike Carlson.
Jason, you were roasting me.
I'm scared, I'm scared of roasts.
You took a big leap there that is,
I can back up with evidence you were correct,
you made a good guess.
But let's be honest though,
the word scary is in the name of the ride,
so how else am I supposed to be able to guess?
For now.
Added later though.
Added later.
As we'll get into.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It wasn't always in the title.
Yeah.
But what you were listening to also
is the first episode of Hauntcast, the Fright,
which we will be for all of October.
We are out of the last themed thing
and into the next themed thing immediately.
For those of you who have not listened
since the City Walk Saga began, welcome back.
Encourage you to go back and check out highlights.
There's so, so many twists and turns,
a spectacular ending I thought.
The way I figured you can just do
like one City Walk Saga episode a month now
for the next 19 months.
So like when you're, maybe there's no podcast
or you got an extra hour to kill, catch up on it, you know?
You didn't have to do it daily.
In a lot of cases, an extra two hours.
Okay, another two hours, sure.
Also, they're not going anywhere.
They're up, you know?
Take your time.
Yeah.
They are up and accruing respect and admiration.
And within a couple of years,
we'll be considered one of the great cult podcasts,
mini-series.
Maybe it's not there yet, but.
It's not, look, we're not getting serial acclaim yet.
We're not getting Finding Richard Simmons,
whatever Richard Simmons is, what's it called?
There's something about him looking for.
Oh, Richard Simmons is missing.
I don't think it's called that.
The wrong show, the show that was wrong
about its premise.
Edward Richard Simmons was always fine.
Or the porno dad show.
My dad wrote a porno.
A lot of people seem to like My Dad Wrote a Porno.
Do you guys know this show?
What is that?
It's a show about like a guy whose father passed away
and when they were going through his things
that he found this very long, erotic novel.
Okay.
How dare you be talking about other compelling podcasts
when we're trying to hype up what we have just been through?
I mean, that's true.
Yeah, we certainly went through one of our deal.
I don't, we should all, the only thing we should be talking
about with any enthusiasm is, yeah, these guys did
this thing where they went to CityWare for 19 days in a row
and there was a little boy ghost keeper.
You gotta check it out.
If we, and if any of us have children,
which obviously very unlikely,
but if any of us have children,
they're gonna find years later, like in their 40s or 50s,
they're gonna stumble upon the fact that their dads
did 19 episodes on CityWalk
and then they'll do a podcast about it.
It'll be like, oh my, did you,
my dad did a 19 part series on a shopping mall.
We've also like lessened our chances of having children
just because of the amount of salt we have consumed.
To do the CityWalk episodes.
Because we weren't down our actual sperm count?
Possibly, I mean, we were walking a lot.
No, I just meant our longevity of life.
So yeah, we will die sooner.
I thought you meant like,
cause they would put saltpeter in like military meals
to make sure the men weren't that horny.
That's what I heard.
So I thought maybe we're, our drives are down.
I don't know.
Well, that's a different now and then.
I'm not forgetting you of course.
Of course not.
But Scott and I are way down as far as our T's.
Every now and then you hear about someone
who like lived to a hundred something
and they would eat like bacon and hardtack and whiskey.
Sure.
How much hardtack have you been eating lately?
I eat a normal amount of hardtack.
Just six times a month.
Doctor recommended it.
Just, yeah.
Have you ever had hardtack?
I don't think, I mean.
You're thinking about it.
I don't think so.
I think, cause I went to a lot of like
colonial themed shit growing up
in like the Pennsylvania area.
There's a lot of colonial themed shit.
Or going to New England.
And I'm sure we would have,
must have had some foods of the time.
But like.
Cause a hardtack is a biscuit.
It's a biscuit.
Yeah, but that was,
so that was more of a military like ration sort of thing.
Because I think it's like.
That doesn't mean you wouldn't have had it.
Yeah, that's true.
It's an old timey thing.
I don't think I've had hardtack.
Okay.
Well call your dad.
Maybe he has some information about it.
I did email him about something on today's episode.
About the topic.
Which I should say we're talking about
Snow White Scary Adventures.
It is a month of the scariest attractions on earth.
And where better to start than with the most.
The first.
Bone chilling.
Yeah.
The first attraction I ever went on at Disney World.
Oh, I see.
Wow.
I think it's seeming to me like maybe we all have
parent stories and contacts related to this episode.
I would think.
Oh.
We had to unlock memories.
Yeah, of the hidden terrors that befell us.
Yeah, well, you know,
where, yeah, where better to begin in a terrifying month.
Is there a more,
is there a scarier ride than Snow White Scary Adventures?
Soon we'll find out.
I can't imagine there would be.
Not a maze where some teenagers running at you
with a chainsaw or there's slasher like characters
from movies running at you.
No, no, no.
It's a tiny two minute ride on a tiny little car
on a little fast track where a bunch of like
static mannequins like slide out toward you.
That is what we're talking about.
And I'm saying that in jest,
but no ride scared me more.
Yeah.
As a kid.
And I think it's possible that there is not a ride
that has produced more terror
because it just sheer volume,
if you go back to the fifties
and chart all the many decades
of some iteration of this ride occurring,
and it is a ride that kids can go on in terms of,
you know, it's not a twisty tourney ride.
So all ages can go on.
I just, I just feel like more tears
have probably been produced by this ride.
Maybe than any other in the world.
Sure, more than the Haunted Mansion.
Potentially.
Yes.
I think you know what you're getting into
on the Haunted Mansion.
I think this ride pulls a bait and switch on you.
Yeah, the Haunted Mansion is downright delightful
compared to the, especially the original
Walt Disney World Snow White scary adventures.
Like.
Yes, I mean, that's true.
I went on Haunted Mansion with no problem.
I might've like squinted a little bit,
but I was not nearly as scared as I was on this thing.
So can we get into,
because you have had such a visceral reaction
to talking about this ride as a kid,
why don't we start with that?
Sure, let's explore it.
Yeah, let's explore that.
In fact, because you're holding a,
because I have a different angle.
You're holding your hand out like you're a therapist
and you're like, let's start with you.
No, I'm just curious.
I was just surprised when you brought this up
because my, the long and short of me is I never,
I liked this ride.
I always, I never gave this ride much mind.
What a brave, brave little boy.
What did you call yourself?
Oh, a big, brave boy who ain't scared of nothing.
Okay, so as long as I remember that.
I was trying to figure out something sluggo
from Nancy would call herself.
No, that is a perfect way to describe yourself.
I'm not mad about that at all.
As for us, yeah.
Yeah, no, so I think I really should
have double checked with my mom.
I could have maybe gone on like Dumbo or something first,
but my memory is when I was three years old,
we were in Florida, three or four,
and the first ride we went on was this ride.
And it's the original Walt Disney World version
of Snow White.
And it was not called Scary Adventures,
but it was the scariest of all of the versions of the ride.
Was it just called Snow White's Adventures?
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Okay, sure.
And the ride is, if you haven't been on it,
it's like all these dark rides in Fantasyland
are very claustrophobic.
So like the walls are closing on you
and all the characters are pretty close
in proximity to you.
I think that's an element that makes it scarier
than Haunted Mansion.
Yes, 100%.
Lot of room to breathe, and it's all very calm.
There's no real jump scares,
other than I guess I was freaked out by the things
that do like pop up from behind the tombstones.
Yeah, but there's a party going on at that point.
Sure, sure.
So it's a little, yeah, as a kid probably I was like,
but there's such a fun song happening
and there's a big party, ghost party happening,
that at that point those jump scares,
they feel like are lessened in their intensity.
Yeah, I did not like the things jumping up
in the Haunted Mansion, but that music is so infectious.
Of course. Like as a kid,
I was just like, I'm here, I get to hear,
what are my favorite songs?
This is before Spotify, you couldn't take it on the go.
Yeah, exactly.
Are you typically driving around
blasting Grim Grinning Ghosts?
Yeah, yeah.
It seems possible, I don't know.
It's entirely possible.
Well for me, I would certainly be blasting
the Bear Naked Ladies cover of Grim Grinning Ghosts
that exists.
Did they really?
Interesting.
We can talk about that later though.
The full episode devoted to the note by note breakdown
of the Bear Naked Ladies cover.
And here's what Ed Robertson was doing
on the verse, second verse here
that I thought was very interesting.
Yeah, so we went on the ride and I loved The Seven Dwarfs.
I was obsessed with it.
They had re-released it in theaters not long before that.
And I remember like, I remember going to see it.
I remember being so excited.
I remember taking a nap before going to see it
because I was so excited.
There was a poster on my grandmother's door
of like Seven Dwarfs.
I wanted the toys that didn't exist.
And my dad came back one day
because I was sick and I was like,
can you get me Seven Dwarfs toys?
And my dad was like, all right, I will.
My mom was like, they don't make those.
You can't promise them that.
They don't make those.
So my dad found seven like little ninja toys
and he goes, yeah, these are the Ninja Dwarfs.
Here you go.
And I was like, oh cool.
Wow, that's so sweet.
And I bought it.
Like I didn't, I was like, oh cool.
Like made them fight and I was none the wiser
that those were not really the Seven Dwarfs.
Now I didn't think about it though.
I wonder if he found like a perfect seven pack of ninjas
or he like took some out to make it.
I really should ask him about that.
No, yeah.
Anyway, so I-
So ninjas sound cool.
Yeah.
I'd like to see a ride about them.
Sure.
But the audience would be very slim for that, I suppose.
I've heard of three ninjas, but seven ninjas?
Now I've heard of everything.
Or too many.
So I was so excited to go on this ride
and immediately the ride like plunges you into darkness.
It's already very dark and claustrophobic
and very quickly your friends are not there.
The dwarves are not there immediately.
You start out in this little forest and then you go in
and immediately you're just in,
you're just with the witch and the queen.
Yeah.
Like the queen and the witch.
And immediately-
Oh, you know what?
I'd like to explain something.
And we can go, we'll go back and talk about the-
The actual ride.
The different versions and everything.
But if anyone listening is,
has in their head the Disneyland version,
which begins with,
oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like there's a pleasant scene at the beginning
before you are plunged into terror.
But the Disney World version that you went on,
not so much, not even, I don't think any pleasantness.
No, you are immediately greeted with the witch
turning around as an old hag and screaming.
Just blood curdling, like screaming.
Yeah, and I was done.
I mean, I was done at that point.
I was so scared.
I closed my eyes and looked toward the ground.
And my mom always tells the story that she was like
pointing stuff out to me on the ride to try to show me.
Cause in her mind, we drove down to Florida
from Chicago area, which-
I don't know.
This is a crazy.
I don't know why my parents insisted on doing this.
Like could flying have been that much more money than,
like an extra day of work, my dad had to take off.
Like in hindsight, now that I think about it,
like why did we drive a couple times?
Was it too young to fly in their eyes potentially?
Maybe, that's a funny thought.
My sister was-
A lot of people don't fly.
A lot of kids don't fly.
My sister was younger.
No, I didn't fly until I was like 15 or something.
But so like, I think we were thinking it was safe.
That's not how your parents chose to.
Yeah, and I don't know if my mom was like scared of flying
at that point or I don't know.
I honestly, I don't have an answer for this, but we-
I think there's a cutoff in any direction from Orlando
of eight to 10 hours where people, if they haven't done it,
they have at least considered driving to the park.
It's like 22 hours of driving from Schaumburg.
It's not that short.
So it's like a two day trip.
And I remember we like left at night
and I remember being very, oh no, this is the second time
we drove to Florida.
Sorry, I'm mixing up my stories
because I remembered having my Game Boy in the back
and we stopped at Burger King, but that's a different trip.
That sounds like a hell of a time.
That sounds like-
So yeah, so we drove down.
So my mom will say like, oh, we like drove all this way
and he's not gonna look at any of the rides.
Like that was her first thought.
So she's-
And the whole way down you were bragging about,
mommy, when you see me on the first ride we go on,
my pants are gonna come out dry.
I'm not gonna blink.
I'm gonna have big boy dry pants.
You'll be so proud of me.
My eyes-
Immediately over dirt.
My head's on a swivel.
I will be enjoying all of the animatronics.
We will get our money's worth, mother.
The money will be well spent.
Wait till you see how much I look at.
This all seems like stuff Jason may have said as a child.
The money will be well spent, mother.
Your hard earned payday will come to fruition.
I've calculated the amount of joy I'll have
for the ticket price.
So yeah, so she was like trying to get me.
She's like, look at this.
There's a evil tree or there's a this.
And I think within like 30 seconds
she said like, oh, look over here.
There's whatever, a squirrel or something.
And I looked and it was a scene
when the witch comes out on the boat.
So I opened my eyes, the witch pops up
or pops like that thing.
And that's a similar effect to the Disneyland version too
where she just kind of slowly comes out on a boat.
Ah!
Yeah, she's on a boat now.
She's turning around.
Was she on a boat in the movie?
And she shows up on a damn boat.
I can't, there's a lot of this where I'm like,
this is just the ride.
This is like the ride taking shortcuts
to try and tell the movie.
They love the witch on the ride.
They love it.
I was obsessed with the dwarves,
but this is a ride about the witch.
This is a ride about this woman chasing and stalking you.
And especially the Disney World version,
she showed up so many times in a row.
Six or seven times.
She is full on stalking your ass.
Yeah, so my mom's turning and I opened
and then that was it.
And I was not gonna open my eyes the rest of that ride.
And my mom said, open your eyes, Mike.
Oh no, she said, look at that or whatever.
And I said, I can't, my eyes are shut too tight.
That's the famous line my mom always tells that story.
I can't mommy, my eyes are shut too tight.
So like I was just.
It's your eyes fault, it's not you.
I was blaming it on my eyes.
It was like, I cannot help it.
I am so scared my eyes will not open.
And I wasn't crying or anything.
I was just like, I don't want to deal with this scariness.
And yeah, so I think we went another dark ride
and it was a similar situation.
But luckily, and we'll save that for the Peter Pan episode.
Peter Pan, a nice distance away from all the things.
And I loved Peter Pan.
Okay, so it was dicey whether or not
this trip was gonna work out at all.
It's a hell of a note to start on,
but Peter Pan turned you around.
How old would you have been?
I always forget.
I think it's 80, not 87, that's when my sister was born.
So I must've been like five.
I was probably 89.
All right, it's brave of you to share these details
to go back and remember dates and times.
I know it's hard to do so, but I'm glad you're doing it.
Are you about to do the same thing?
Well, I might as well tell mine.
The first time I went on this ride
was not the first time that I went to Disneyland in general,
which I will explain.
Basically, I told my mom that this was a topic
we were gonna do, that we were gonna kick off
this month of Haunt Cast the Fright with this ride.
And she started telling a story of
the first time I was at the ride.
And I said, you know what, here, wait, save it,
call back, leave a message,
and tell the story that way.
So that's what happened.
And I'm just gonna play the audio file.
I figured it would be,
this is the more honest way to do it,
to let my mom tell the tale.
So here now, for the first time,
actually, her voice on the podcast,
this is Kathy Gerdner.
Hi, Scott, it's mom.
I was just remembering a story
of when we first took you to Disneyland.
You were four, and we were wandering through fantasy land,
and I took you over to the Snow White ride,
and you stopped at this real cute sign
on the outside, the elbow characters,
and you looked at it and read out loud,
Snow White Scary Adventures.
Board a mine cart to travel through
the scary adventures of Snow White,
but watch out for the wicked witch.
Supervise children at all times.
Children under age seven must be accompanied
by a person age 14 years or older.
And then you turned around and said,
Mommy, I don't think I'll go on this ride.
And you maneuvered us right out of fantasy land.
Wow.
It's always been one of my favorite stories.
Love you, bye.
And then my mom said she loved me.
And so that made me feel good.
And then you added, Mommy, I'm sorry,
we will not be getting the most for our ticket today.
I apologize for you and father's earnings.
We will earn our money by looking at each planter
and the beautiful landscaping in the park, Mommy.
I think I could have just told that story,
but I knew that tale, and I wanted my mom to do,
my mom could do a better impression of me
at four years old than I could now,
because I had a very high-pitched voice.
I don't know if you know this, but I was,
I mean, my parents always said I sounded like Mickey Mouse
as a little kid.
And I probably said the full name.
Yeah, I'll find a clip at some point.
But I think I was constantly just saying,
Mommy, in falsetto, as I did in this instance.
So I made a point of reading the entire sign
very carefully out loud, showing that I could comprehend
all of the safety warnings.
And then I just made kind of an educated decision.
But what I didn't know is that I just took them out
of Fantasyland entirely, and I did it sly,
like, why don't we go see something else,
as if I was not just a...
Had you not been on any of the other dark rides
in Fantasyland at that point?
I think I, I'm not sure.
I think I must have been on one of them.
And as you said, Peter Pan is fine.
And then you go on the thing,
we're talking about the Disneyland version there,
which is not that scary,
not as much as the one that you went on.
Still kind of scary.
I might have skipped it like a bunch of times in a row.
I think I saw the word scary,
and that was enough to get me to bail entirely.
And I might have ended up going on it and thinking,
what was the problem?
What was the fuss here?
Why did I avoid this for so long?
Mommy is probably what I'd said.
And just to confirm, this was the post-New Fantasyland
83 redo?
Yes, correct.
Where they kind of softened it a little,
but it seemed like they,
that was when they added scary to the title
and put up the warning sign,
even though they had dialed back a little on the terror.
They made it less scary.
They made the rides less scary.
I mean, the redo in Florida was in the nineties,
but the one in the eighties, yeah, makes it...
But the redo they did was putting the word scary
in front of the ride.
And that is more, just that was more terrifying to me
than anything internally in the ride
that they could have done.
So if you want me to avoid something, put the word scary.
If there's a party going on, you don't want me at the party,
say my scary birthday party,
and I'll call my mommy and not go.
Well, and a big thing with these changes
is that they put more of the dwarves in
and they put Snow White in,
because for the longest time, she was not in,
besides a brief period in the seventies,
she was not in there, because you were Snow White.
You were supposed to be experiencing it
from her perspective, what she would live,
which is all the fantasy land stuff.
When it first opened, that was the concept.
And people did not get that
because theme parks didn't exist.
Like, I feel like now you can get away with a little more,
although now it's kind of like, you know,
you want to see, people want to see Optimus Prime.
They want to see Harry Potter.
Right, there's a balance between that
on all the rides that have to do,
like you want to sort of experience what they experience,
but also like if you're on the Snow White ride,
you kind of want to see Snow White do something.
And how are you a group of nine people,
one young girl?
How are you a single?
That doesn't really make sense.
Can I ask, do you have any memory of your first time
other than just some cool leather jacket boy
getting on the ride and saying, I'm scared of this?
Lighting cigarettes on it.
When we were talking about this,
I was trying to remember that
because I was a very nervous, scared child.
And now I am a very nervous man.
I was a worry wart as a kid.
Like I gave myself stomach aches just all the time,
just nonstop.
And my parents do have a story of me freaking out
in a ride, but it was Pirates of the Caribbean.
Like that was one of the first things they took me on.
And my dad just texted me because I was asking him
about this, how old would I have been on this trip?
Because this is a story my parents like to tell.
And he wrote back, it would have been like February 88.
So just under, I would have been just under
two and a half years.
My brother hadn't been born yet.
And they wanted to go when I was still young,
but they knew that if they waited for my brother to be born,
like it would be another X number of years.
So they wanted to go down.
So we went down, one of the first, if not the first ride
they took me on was Pirates of the Caribbean.
And I screened my head off.
And it wasn't because of the pirates,
because of how dark the ride was.
I did not like the darkness as a kid.
I think that factors into Snow White for me personally,
and I bet for you as well.
It's just darkness.
So my quick thinking parents similarly were like,
is he gonna do this the whole trip?
What are we gonna do?
And they were at the gift, you know,
you exit into the gift shop and they're like,
oh my God, there's a little key chain flashlight.
Let's give him the little key chain flat.
So they bought a little key chain flash and they're like,
okay, so why don't we go on another,
or why don't we go on this again?
But we got this little flashlight.
So if you get scared, just point it at the ground
and it won't be dark.
And it just worked.
It worked instantly for that and for everything else,
including Snow White.
So I emailed my dad and asked him,
was I scared of Snow White?
And he said, I don't remember you being scared on this.
I do remember the flashlight being brought out,
but you liked it.
You should ask him how bright was the flashlight
and did it ruin the ride for the people behind us?
No, because they taught me.
Don't bother other people with it.
Aim it like in your hand or aim it at the ground.
Okay.
Just to see something light at all.
Just to see some light.
And then I think I was just fine with it.
And yeah, I mean, I still have,
it's back in my mom's house somewhere.
Oh, he's actually exists.
I still have it, yeah.
I don't think it stopped working years ago.
Well, when we go to Halloween Horror Nights,
you're gonna have to bring that flashlight with you.
Wait, now, hang on, wait, that was a pretty revealing,
you just don't, now you don't do Halloween Horror Nights
is what you're saying.
Okay.
Well, I don't either.
Yeah, none of us.
But at a certain point, maybe not this year,
we're gonna have to do it.
Yeah, we should just be,
we should be calling this month Scaredy Cattober.
That's essentially what we're doing here.
We will tease, we've got a little bit of
We've got some fights coming up.
We are dealing with actually scary things.
It's not all gonna be a child's ride.
Pranks and goofs, yes.
We were scared of when we were three or five.
Yeah, but I'm just saying,
we're opening up, we're giving you
those vulnerable moments.
That's in our lives.
I'm saying, just get your flashlight ready, Jason,
because we're gonna scare the shit out of you.
I had a little MacGuffin flashlight
that solved all the problems.
And that's how it was good to go.
Although, I would still have to hype myself.
I loved the one at mansion, but I was like,
just gotta get past that hanging.
And not-
Oh, the hanging stressed you out.
Yeah, the hanging man.
I think because it's a constant narration,
it's a constant narration, the stretching room,
and then it's the sudden lightning strike.
Yeah, I don't know, that would never-
I don't have a memory of that bothering me.
I don't know why.
I think I just didn't like sudden surprises,
like the lightning strike or the heads popping up.
And you're not gonna like the sudden surprise
of a 21-year-old in a leather face mask
jumping out at you when we go to Universal.
I mean, we'll see.
You're not gonna like that either.
Okay, let's not gang up on Jason.
I'm so tough now.
I'm such a tough guy.
We are believing you.
To tell us, they are, it sounds like a chore,
but they are at the Hollywood One selling
limited alcohol refreshments at Hollywood Horror Nights now.
Orlando, I believe, is the wild, wild west,
and I don't know that they really changed their alcohol laws.
Yeah, it's like Mardi Gras down there during this thing,
which we gotta do that too one of these days.
What, the-
The Orlando Horror Nights.
Well, sure, you gotta compare the more heavily IP-based
Hollywood mazes to the more original attractions,
which are called houses in Orlando.
And we'll get to that in a future episode.
Next week or two weeks from now?
Snow White, back to Snow White.
Back to Snow White.
We're just gonna have to move to Orlando
for like three months.
Forever.
To cover all of the, well, there's an idea, yes.
Let's talk about some of the basic tenets of this ride
as it does not relate to us peeing our pants as children.
Do you realize this is the first opening day attraction
we've ever talked about?
Correct me if I'm wrong.
I don't believe we've talked about
a Disneyland opening day.
I think that's right.
That seems right.
We have not talked about any of the primary
Fantasyland rides of which this is one.
It was an opening day attraction in all of the original
Magic Kingdoms in Disneyland, in Disney World, in Tokyo,
and in Paris, and that was the last of the Snow White
adventure rides that have been built.
It is no longer in Florida, which I guess the now
Seven Dwarfs Mine Train, which is a newer ride.
And that's in Shanghai as well, I believe.
I think it is, yeah.
And Hong Kong, if you like Snow White, you're out of luck.
I believe, I don't think they have a...
Orlando became, is it called Princess Fairytale Hall?
Something like that.
Princess photo opportunity.
Fascinatingly designed, it's crazy where they have
multiple characters, but then there's switchbacks,
and so you could, they rotate the print,
but the geography of that is very interesting to me.
How they navigate it, so you don't see the other princesses,
you only see the one you're going to meet.
I did not do that.
I took many, as we know, I took many photos in Orlando
with many characters, but I did not, as a lone man,
go and take photos with the princesses.
Did you go to the princess zone?
No, I've just read about it.
Oh, okay.
There's a smaller version in Anaheim, right?
You just read about how the doors work
of the princess show.
I'd like to see you snooping around there in Orlando,
noticing that you can't see the other princesses in here,
You gotta play it a little more cool at Orlando
for inspecting this stuff.
I was down at the park recently,
and no one cares in Anaheim.
Right, but you have to bring a friend or a wife,
a person playing your wife around
to make it not suspicious if you were just going.
You have to hire an actress.
Yeah, you have to hire a local actress to play his wife
so we can go snoop around the Princess Fantasy Fair area
so we can see the different ways
that they hide the princesses.
That sounds like a very charming rom-com
that nowadays Netflix would probably make it,
it would just get buried.
That's fine, as long as you get some money.
That's true.
Your SAG minimum or your WGA minimum.
Oh yeah, sure.
He's gonna star in a movie where he hires a woman
to go around Disney World with.
He'll have to have the permission of Disney to do it,
but he's only getting SAG minimum,
even though this is his film based on his story.
It could be like Escape from Tomorrow, I guess.
It could be another gorilla.
We should reclaim the genre of secret leap shot
in theme park films.
This is the perfect place.
Well, I have to say, I mean, it's been a year now,
so I could say I thought the Florida Project
did it very well.
Well, it's not only, only a little bit of it is in the parks.
Only a little bit, and I found it so moving
the way they did it.
Yeah, that's fantastic.
Great film.
I'd like to talk, since this is an opening day attraction,
I'd like to talk about the first thing ever filmed
in a Disney park, which is the opening day special.
Have you guys watched the opening day special
in full, ever?
Like the one with, like,
Reagan, what's the guy?
Art Linkletter.
Yeah, Art Linkletter.
Yeah, I've seen that.
And like, there's a lot of weird pauses in the feed
and like, there's confusion going on.
And weird parts where Bob Cummings can see Art Linkletter
and they know that this is a part in the broadcast
where he's supposed to be talking,
but he doesn't have a microphone,
and they cut to him stomping around and loudly
gesticulating and pointing to him and his ears
and his mouth, and now he has no way of.
Right.
And due to fair airtime laws at the time,
they occasionally cut to a young Gore Vidal ranting
about the fall of society and capitalism just unwarranted.
He was sitting in the Mickey Mouse planner in the front.
His head was the Mickey's nose.
He did get to eat the very first Mickey ice cream bar.
I may be upset about a lot, but this is delicious.
That is so, I mean, cause you know,
Noam Chomsky's email is just, it's public.
It's public and you can email him, it'll write you back.
You could email Noam Chomsky and say,
hey, have you had a Mickey Mouse ice cream bar?
Do you think he'd respond?
What do you think about the whiskey?
Well, who knows?
Do you think he would respond while we're doing it?
Can you email him right now
and they'll see if he responds by the end of our recording
and by the time it airs?
He could, but we'd lose Jason for a while.
I can try, but I only have touch screen devices
and I'm trying to hold a microphone.
I could do it by,
We'll email him after this.
Let's try it by next week.
We'll find out.
By next week we'll find out.
Yeah, let's give a little Noam a little more time.
Yeah.
But so there's one little bit of the,
since we haven't talked about original Fantasyland,
there's a little thing that I'd like to play.
My favorite part of the opening day special,
which is the lowering of the drawbridge
to let kids into Fantasyland for the first time.
And boy, do I like the voice that is in this video.
Here we go.
Open the Fantasyland.
Open the Fantasyland Castle!
I love that voiceover, I love crazy old men.
The dog was really stirred by your impression.
Did it make Edwin freak out?
I used to, our cat, I used to sometimes sing like Ringo.
I'd sing that song, you don't love me anymore!
And then our cat would flip out.
That was like the exact register that she could not handle.
Edwin's tail is slightly wagging, so I don't know if he hates it.
He might like it, he just came to hear it more clearly.
No, no, no, no, I don't smoke anymore.
I like to write a little bit up on the floor.
It's the Ringo No-No song, look that one up.
That's my favorite.
Anyway, that makes me, I like that VO, and I want that to play,
I want an equivalent of that to play at every part of the park
before things open.
For example, open the Napa wine patio
for the day drunks of the world!
How much more fun would Disneyland be?
Open the women's restroom!
Let's get Scott Gander a Fess Parker winery Riesling.
He's thirsty, my man!
The Riesling lovers of the world!
Ralph Brennan's Jazz Kitchen is now serving dinner!
The finest jambalaya in the world!
Splitsville luxury bowling!
Luxury lanes.
Open the cat door for the feral cats of the world!
Well, please do that and let me do it.
I want to be that guy, hire me as the official Disneyland bellower.
Everything, the children of the world,
they repeated that when they redid Fantasyland.
Yeah.
They said the same thing, we're opening it up,
the drawbridge for the children of the world.
The second, only the second time that drawbridge was ever lowered.
Yes, because when they redid all of the rides in 1983,
Fantasyland was just closed entirely because the whole thing
kind of got got wrecked and the rides were like not just slightly altered,
but completely changed and lengthened.
By our now best friend, Tony Baxter, he redid all the facades.
So all of the more ornate versions of the rides that you see today,
the fact that it actually looks like a Bavarian town.
And he made all of the rides, including Snow White, 25% longer,
because he thought if people don't like the new versions,
at least they will get more bang for their buck, more value.
The parents of the world will get more value for their admission fees.
But yeah, but so when they do, because there just was no Fantasyland
for a couple of years, they raised the drawbridge.
And that's described by Imagineers as a very dramatic moment
and a very dramatic moment to re lowering it.
It would seem like it would be very dark.
Yeah, it would seem like it would have been better to like just put up a sheet,
like keep the bridge down, put up a sheet in there that just says,
like, don't come in here.
Like if you want, you can walk in part of the castle, but then there's
maybe not a sheet, maybe a wall, maybe an actual physical wall.
That's like, you know, we'll be back in the next year.
Hmm.
But I think it was a I think it was a bold statement.
It was indicating that big things are not even going to be able to recognize it
when it comes back, which is true.
They did a great job with that.
I have one more thing about the opening day special, which is the I watched
they kind of there's a little like opening musical number,
which is very poorly organized.
And boy, the old there's a lot of videos on YouTube that go into this.
What the characters looked like in the early days.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Mickey, they they they it was like a last minute idea on Walt's part.
And he reached out to the ice capades, which was the only thing at that point
where there had been walk around Disney characters and he got these ice costumes,
which all had these big, bizarre slices in their face.
Like said, like the Mickey mask would go mesh every
or every once in a while, like in the cheeks and in the forehead,
because the the ice dancers needed maximum visibility.
So the first couple of years of Disneyland,
you're looking at these bizarre ice uniforms for all the characters.
And that's that's true of the dwarfs.
Also, the dwarfs were super terrifying.
So in the opening day special, you get to see all of the rides
kind of one by one open and they show clips of the movie.
And you see a ton of kids all flood into the Snow White
ride when the gates lifted.
And Bob Cummings, one of the hosts of the special, is sitting
in one of the cars and like, OK, come on in, kids.
All right. Cool.
Take it easy. Slow it down.
And not all of you not to.
Hey, well, one at a time, maybe.
OK, good. Hey, get it.
Get off my cord. OK, good. Fine.
Very good. He like scolds the children for standing on his mic cord.
And it is like it is chaos.
The entire opening day special is chaos.
But this was one little sliver of a moment I enjoyed.
That's great. Yeah.
I mean, from the way anyone ever describes that opening day, it's like,
what is it? 60,000 people, something insane, like descend upon Anaheim.
And there's parts of the park unfinished and there's like paths
that lead to nothing.
And bootleg tickets.
Someone figured out how to scout tickets.
That's why there were so many more than expected.
Yeah. And then there's like just people like people describe
like cement drying still the first day and women's shoes getting stuck in cement.
And the only shoes they had to give them were the Mocketsons.
For sale and frontier.
Like they were. Is that a true thing?
Are you joking? I know.
I believe that is a thing I've heard.
Really? They were handing out Mocketsons.
They were handing out free Mocketsons because women's high heels
got stuck in the cement.
Yeah, that's that's the urban legend I always heard.
Yeah, because people are getting stuck in the cement and then their shoes
were dinged up or ruined and they had to give them something.
Really? We got to look into this.
If you guys at home have any
information about the free Mocketsons that people got opening day.
That's the old wise tale I always heard.
That's crazy. I mean, it also seems just crazy.
Disney would give something for free.
Yeah. Yeah, true.
They just marked them down.
Well, we'll give you a five percent discount for getting your high heels
stuck in the not dry cement.
Well, they gave out ice capades skates for free.
So you could.
All right. We can replace your shoes, but you will have to walk around
concrete on skates.
But if you can handle the balance, this should get you going.
It was chaos. Yeah.
Oh, no, go ahead.
I was just going to say the ride, I just both versions of the ride.
This is something I don't know if you guys have the same thing.
When we were kids, one of the most exciting aspects of getting on the ride
was seeing which car you were going to get.
Oh, yeah, sure.
And we would like, well, I let's I will go around.
Well, all once we'll say what character we want, because they have all seven
dwarves on these cars.
So what character did we all want?
And I'll say one, two, three, Dopey.
Yeah. Right.
Is there any kid who didn't want Dopey who really likes happy?
I was I mean, I was praying Jason said like Doc or Sleepy.
Doc was Doc or Sleepy would probably have been a better joke, I guess, for you.
But yeah, I was hoping he's the king or like Bashful or something
would have been a cute choice for you.
Bashful is cute. But yeah, Dopey is.
Yeah, Sneezy is maybe who's like the least popular is it?
Grumpy is popular because he's so specific and because you get a shirt
with grumpy on it for your asshole dad.
That's the tone of all those shirts is like, hey, isn't your dad a grump?
Well, get this shirt to shame him or this coffee mug to say
he's so unpleasant in the morning.
Oh, no, it's it's to embrace it.
It's the character we love about you, Dad.
Don't ever change.
But yeah, we're yeah, we're all dopey.
And he he definitely lands
heavier than the other dwarves, I suppose.
He's the he's the fun way.
Is this the only one is different doesn't have a beard.
I had a question about the dwarves in general, which is,
do they know each other because they are all dwarves?
Or did they all separately meet?
Did they like go applying for mine jobs and then meet each other
and go, we have so much in common.
We're all small.
You have a beard as well together.
Why don't we all move in?
It won't cost us much.
The space being small after all.
Like, do they know they're bringing this, you know, they're not canonically brothers.
There's nothing that says they're brothers.
No, I don't think so.
They're in all a litter together.
Yeah. Some of them.
Where do dwarves come from?
Because they could come from budding.
They could reproduce from like budding.
What? What does that mean?
Like another species like, I mean, I guess they're human.
Budding like buds.
Wait a minute. What are you talking about?
Disney dwarves are human.
I guess so, but we never meet their parents.
But a lot of movies.
You meet their parents to know they're human.
You don't meet Snow White's parents either.
There's a lot of magic shit going on.
Snow White can summon animals with singing.
Like that's some real Aquaman level shit.
That's because she has the greatest voice.
I guess so. That's just science.
There's a lot of magic.
There is a witch with spells.
There's a witch with powers.
But is your thinking that like the hobbits aren't human?
Or are they like a variety of human?
Or are they a different species altogether?
I guess humanoid.
They're humanoid.
I feel like the dwarves, the specific type of mining that they do,
this is just a guess, is that it helps if you're of a smaller stature in these mines.
So whoever is in charge of these mines decided to hire specifically little people.
And they got all the dwarves together and those are maybe they're like,
they all wear similar clothes,
which are very similar to the clothes of like David the gnome.
Like kind of a hat.
And that's my question is,
did they all have that fashion sense when they met or was like bashful in a suit?
I think that was just a dress.
Form like a unified, a group mind style.
Well, like Dopey is wearing like pajamas that are too big for him.
And then like the habit is a similar.
I think it's just the clothing of the time for like poor people.
I think, but I think they own the mine.
You think the seven dwarves own the mine?
Like this is the ideal.
This is some like socialist paradise in your brain.
I don't think that the seven dwarves own the mine.
Who are they giving those jewels?
I think they're selling those jewels direct.
Here's why you're wrong.
Here's what I think laborers own all of the, they deserve all of the fruits of their labor.
But offhand, I think, I think Jason is correct.
I think he's a hundred percent wrong because why are they living in that small ass house?
But you just said that because they're little, it feels lavish.
No, no, no, I'm saying they would be, look, they mine like big juicy jewels every day.
They have carts, mine carts full of jewels.
Like if these are legit jewels, these guys are some of the richest guys we know.
They would have a castle.
They would have had so much money that they would own a castle.
They have to be giving these diamonds and jewels to some other mysterious like person
and they're making all the money because unless the dwarves are very tight with their money,
which I guess is possible, the amount of jewels that they're bringing in on it in a day,
like it's not like they're hunting and they get a couple pieces a day.
It could be like Jay Leno.
They don't touch their tonight show money.
It's all retirement.
It's all in a fund somewhere.
Yeah.
I just think they're living a little bit higher on the hog than what they're doing in the movie
if they own everything.
I think what if they're what if it's like then they collect them and then they give it to a guy
to sell the way that like a farmer would like he picks all the crops, but then like here,
take it to market and maybe the guy taking it to market is screwing them
because what I don't think is that they are slaves.
I don't think that they're being forced to be in that mine because they enjoy it.
They say digging is what they like to do.
So I don't think they have a boss, but I think there's some.
I think the seller is screwing them and he comes back with a little a couple of coins
and they're like, oh boy, we've forage for us this week.
So they're just fucking idiots.
Yeah.
They're being taken advantage of by some slimy guy.
But they seem happy.
They sing what I learned.
I never realized this is called the silly song.
That's that Germany kind of song where like snow there were like, oh,
like Snow White's just kind of clapping along.
Yeah.
And there's a weird moment where like Dopey has a an accordion.
No, a symbol.
He has a symbol and he hits it and then he hits Snow White's knee
and then he puts it on his head.
Oh, no.
Like a hat, like a what kind of hat?
I actually don't know what kind of hat, what that is called.
Do you call that a rice paddy hat?
Yeah, but I don't know if that's an Americanized like term for it.
That's a scene in every Disney movie up until 1965.
For sure.
Yeah.
There's a pre-racist cat in the aristocats.
The crows take a break from singing and then they put those hats on in Dumbo.
They do a worse stereotype.
Yeah, they do.
They double stereotype.
Yeah, but I never knew that moment was called the silly song.
Yeah, I don't know.
I didn't know.
I don't know that.
I didn't know that.
So they're having a good time.
They're obviously very pleased.
I think they're just rubes.
I think they're getting taken advantage of.
That's sad then.
That adds a whole like a tinge of sadness to the whole thing.
Also, where is this amazing mine full of like just completely perfectly shined up diamonds?
By the way, this is a thing that I have to commend and we're not going to talk about it too much,
but the the mine train ride is that the mine train ride
takes all the scary stuff away and it focuses on what my sister and I's favorite part of the movie
was the mine with the colorful diamonds.
Yeah.
With the while you work picking up like fully perfectly like shined up diamonds somehow.
Don't like it's not a hog looking for truffles situation where you need you have to like go
like where are they?
There are so many if they like they could go all day and there would still be bright
bright diamonds and rubies and just amethysts everywhere.
They're all just open and out and ready to pluck like ripe apples.
These guys should be the richest men on earth.
Yeah.
But something's going wrong.
Maybe the seven way split screws them somehow.
I don't know.
That's true.
They may just have a bad money guy.
Yeah.
Who's their financial advisor?
The great great great great grandfather of Lou Perlman.
Oh boy.
He makes a lot of saves actually.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Lou Perlman had auditions for dwarves.
The Huntsman could also.
Yes looking for little guys to fit into mine.
I'll cut you in on so much of the profits.
The Huntsman could also be screwing that because he's the queen's like fixer.
He's like an Eddie Mannix type of like back in the day.
Right.
Because the queen sent the Huntsman to like hey go murder go murder this person.
This is another story.
So this is how a little insight into how I was raised.
I loved when my family would or my parents would read me the book the Snow White Book.
Oh sure.
And my mom used to censor that part of the story when she would read it to me.
So the thing that the evil queen says is like to the Huntsman like go
cut out Snow White's heart and bring it to me in this box.
Yes.
And then he says okay but my mom would always say go get Snow White and bring her back here.
So a kidnapping is better than a slaughtering?
I guess it is.
She didn't like the graphicness of cutting out Snow White's heart so she would change that around.
So she would change the story.
Apparently though she called my dad and she didn't tell my dad the plan and all of a sudden
overheard like go cut out Snow White's heart and she's like like she ran in and like
did a whole thing.
Yeah so that's a little bit of insight.
And you closed your eyes so tight you couldn't hear the story anymore.
The sound of my blindness.
Father of mine.
You know speaking of censorship weird facts that I learned about this film is that
this is so so what I all right I was trying to disseminate why did they make this ride so scary?
Why is it not a ride where you're going through the mine and the workshop and then there's a
little bit of witch peril?
Why did they double down on it is so just terrifying front to back?
And I guess if you were if you saw Snow White when it came out probably one of the biggest
pieces of it you're hanging on to is Snow White running through the woods sort of a psychedelic
sequence because I didn't remember how it all played out that the trees are kind of her fantasy
it's not like there are magic alive trees trying to get her she's she's having a nightmare the
the crocodiles kind of form out of logs and stuff so this is like a this is a crazy trippy
sequence for the 30s that a lot of people discouraged Walt from doing at all but he
thought he doubled down and did it in all of those movies.
I was gonna say on all the rides.
All the first ones are terrifying.
So many of the original movies and rides still have I mean Heffalumps and Woozles is a
hallucination there's so many hallucination scenes.
Ah true yeah.
Movies and rides.
Mm-hmm and Fantasia.
Fantasia.
Super trippy movie and then yeah yeah so but he thought it's an important feature of the
fairy tales that I want to make these films of that they are genuinely scary that they actually
are kind of like grotesque and weird and freak kids out so he pushed that but they had to like
really argue with film boards across the world to get this film shown the English board of censors
like after they they relented and they played Snow White without editing it but the British
public was very upset about it people people were like like honestly terrified and their their kids
freaked out and uh here's what I didn't know in England this this board banned all horror films
entirely in 1934 so to play a film with this essentially horror sequence was a really big
deal and then in Italy during the Mussolini regime all terror films were banned and the first one
after the ban was lifted was Snow White and people who had not been accustomed to seeing
scary movies of any kind for decades and who didn't know what the medium could do this is the
first animated feature film entirely it freaked the fuck out of everybody in Italy.
Worse than years of living under a fascist regime.
This scary cartoon was the worst part of living in Italy but it's whatever the article that I
read I think that's what might have all been from the site passport to dreams which were a really
cool article about Snow White's scary adventures but it's it's considered true that the specific
bizarro type of Italian horror that was popular in the 40s 50s 60s was largely influenced by Snow
White and by this weird frame of mind that Italians were in where they didn't know horror at all and
then it like shot back up in their awareness due to Snow White. This kind of makes sense because I
are and British are like very specific and strange. I don't know how to say it. Yeah like more
upsetting in some regard I wouldn't pretend to be an expert in the genre but I know what they're
saying that Italian horror is a particular freaky vibe. For sure. So I gotta say watching the
ride-throughs before the refurbishment that happened at both Anaheim and Orlando I was
this is what like boardwalk haunted houses look like. Like this I think on purpose or
inadvertently like influenced like roadside haunted house just because like there's so my just like
beach town haunted houses in amusement parks I just associate with yes so much screaming
skeletons saying help me and like fucked up trees because like all of this shit is not that
expensive to make. And there's not a good like not a good video of like what it looked like in
the first five or ten years of it being open in Disneyland. Seemed to be yeah we looked around I
didn't find anything. But the way people describe it is that you know the Disney World version is
the Disney World version is even painted differently and what you're saying about like haunted houses
the color scheme in the in the video at least I watched of the the one in from Florida the original
one that one really reminds me of some janky like haunted fun weird fun houses I went on as a kid
because like the witch even has this bizarre like green hue to her that she doesn't really have
in the movie like she seems more jacked up and weird than she does even in the movie and like
all the trees and all the different characters like really have this like like they're very
disturbing but also they have this color scheme that was almost reminiscent of like black light
haunted house even though that's not really what it is but it feels like that to me from watching
the video and I did like watching the video of the Florida one I was like in it especially after my
dad said like no you turned on your flashlight once or twice but like you did like this I'm like
watching and I'm like I do like this aesthetic like I was like this reminds me like there's a
few comic book artists that are like really scratchy or really like Wilson Kavich like I
like oh this that's weird this is like hitting the same part of my brain that those artists like
that's true you know I think you feel the concept art in the style of this ride like it doesn't feel
like a frame of a Disney movie it seems like you're inside a weird scary painting because the the
movie itself is is particularly I think striking and beautiful and I think probably they they went
so hard on it because they had so much to prove with it um yeah the backgrounds and just even just
watching the motion of the dwarves I'm like god this is so like fluid and intense well yeah dude
that's that kind of thing when you think about how little that this this genre is unprecedented
yeah oh yeah there's not been this kind of film and so they don't just they don't like cut themselves
slack and try something easy they it is seven care seven bulbous characters marching around
cresting a hill changing perspective every single second it is so crazy the uh just the you know the
level of detail and very human looking I mean Snow White and the prince very human looking totally
different from the queen and the dwarves like so many different things going on and that sequence
of her that kind of like psychedelic sequence is is different from the rest of the film it's like
its own a bizarre little sequence that the nests incited perfectly I mean I have to say a lot of
these classic Disney movies when they there was a run like five or six years ago where they were
putting them all on Netflix and I went back and watched a lot because I feel like every house
growing up bought some of the like coming out of the Disney vault tapes but I remember having like
Pinocchio and I mean all the 90s ones certainly but like I don't think we had a ton of the classic
ones but I knew I caught them like here and there at like friends houses or the Disney channel or
like after school stuff right and I was just amazed at how much I had just forgotten about
like oh this movie is only 70 minutes long we're like oh this what is this sequence like that sort
of thing yeah as a kid I watched it's weird though because I'm talking about how scared it was of the
ride but as a kid I don't recall being that scared of the movie I think I just thought it was cool
I was scared at the end with the with the rain for sure that last sequence is was very scary to me
but like for whatever reason I just thought the movie was cool and I thought the ride was the
scariest thing ever sure I'm gonna do a similar voice to what I've been doing but my favorite
part of the film still cherished to me today is when she's singing into the wishing well and the
well is singing everything back to her and then the last word is today and but her reflection
doesn't sing it back it's suddenly the prince is there and he sings today that bizarre that people
this was the accepted style of male singing yeah that era the the dwarves kind of sing like that
too even though then they talk and they're kind of like they're weird old they're weird elfie guys
but they all sing this is very warbly voice that everyone had yeah I love it I want to go back to
it if this was if you turn on new it's the instrumentation of you know Skrillex DJ Khaled
sort of music but everyone agrees that now men sing with a heavy baritone again the uh uh I
thought you were going to say something about another thing that you love that starts with today
which oh yeah that's yes yes yes the the um the Geppetto song uh from this Christmas special which
we talked about in an episode where every Shriver is crafting a puppet of himself and but today
that's a similar different different uh male baritone today but I guess I always like that
I just love crazy old man yells so much and uh there's a lot of those to talk about in the area
Snow White uh yeah uh the I was reading so yeah so the the Disneyland version apparently was
originally very scary then the Disney World version way scarier and they cite a lot of these articles
sites Claude Coates Claude Coates Tony's mentor Tony Baxter's mentor um and his first collaborator
I think he worked Tony had something to do with this like it's one of his first projects to work
with Claude is the yeah it sounds like it I don't know why I I'm a little fuzzy in the details but
some interview where he was saying I'm you know I'm 22 years old and I'm like I personally am
supervising all the you know big props that will be in the Snow White attraction uh-huh and the guy
who did the the movies yeah right crazy Claude Coates painted those backgrounds and then he's
painting he's painting them himself in Florida right on that right like that's that's what's
drawing those backgrounds and then 40 years later hand drawing them in a physical place in Florida
and Claude famously I think has a has a another uh an argument or whatever a debate with another
guy that's like this as well who works on all the movies and then it just designs a bunch of stuff
for the theme park Mark Davis which they famously I think fought about Haunted Mansion or I don't
know if there was really fighting but they Mark Davis wanted uh the fun ghost party and Claude
and Claude lost basically he got a little creepy at the start but then it ends up in a Mark Davis
fun yeah character ghost party but is that why if this is Claude Coates going full till that's what
they're that's what people say is that Claude finally got to do something that was as scary as
he wanted uh on this on this version of the ride specifically huh so like he finally got to scare
the shit out of kids like he always wanted to wow I just want to scare kids and they won't let me
Mark Davis permanently scar children I don't know that he hated whimsy but I mean
Mark Davis's whimsy won out over his uh nightmare he just wanted an area without any whimsy and he
got it and you're totally right that you it is like we'll post a video of what this was like pre
the remake in 1994 what was originally in Disney World and I don't know if it's a it's if it's a
fact that the audio is probably not that great so things are overlapping and echoing but it is just
a terrifying wall of sound from front to back that's just constant witch cackling screaming
moaning wind whistling it is it is awful it's it's insanely good sound design but well I could I can
absolutely see why this would have freaked you out as a look at it and is there no music something I
mentioned the original version original version doesn't see no music which is crazy that's the
case with a lot of these things though too like there's yeah but I can't really remember the
music for Mr Toad I remember all the songs from Snow White yeah you mean yeah in the movie yeah
yeah yeah yeah for sure there is a Mark Davis book there's a for sure there's a Mark Davis book out
somewhere Mark Davis Walt Disney's Renaissance man I forget when it came out it's supposed to be
very good but whimsical so I don't know trash it if you're holding out for terror Claude would want
you to burn it yeah um yeah but I don't know I I think I like I found it you know yeah it's a joke
that we're gonna start the scary month with Snow White's Scary Adventures but watching that
watching the ride through that thing and yeah and what are the what are the specific components that
get scarier than what was at Disneyland at the time I guess it's it's more witch appearances
yes there's there's I think there's a 10 second sequence in which she jumps out at you twice or
maybe even less yeah and it's kind of more um it's a little more caustic jump out violent than
in the Disney ride especially the Disneyland ride especially now you round a corner you see
her back she turns around or something but this has you she is not in sight at all and she kind
of slams out of you uh in a weird rickety boat and stuff like that yeah there were seven Wicked
Witch figures on the original Florida ride that's crazy which is a lot for like a new ride zero
Snow White zero Snow White ride with seven figures of the witch of the villain of a horror she may
as well have just been in the car with you like she's just that's it's her ride it should have
called the witch's adventure like Snow White's villains the witch's quest the witch's quest
to see what I feel in my head every day and it's so bombarding you with so many witches that
there's net like now you know there there's a rhythm to a lot of the haunts now where it's like
scare relax a little forget about the scare scare again relax a little you know they kind of pace
it a little yeah this is a barrage from the very beginning and then here's a component I didn't
know about that after a lot of chaos then you arrive back in a cottage I guess the dwarf's
cottage and well maybe this will be a respite but in fact all of their all of the animals and all of
their doodads and toys and pots and their you know their their organ with the faces and everything
all of the all of these faces are open and aghast and staring at you that is a stoned nightmare
yeah like imagine if you hallucinated that everything around you was staring open-mouthed
in horror of whatever is happening to you that is that is genuinely freaky
the animals in the window just look like a good harpy so and then you're just out of the cottage
and back into the into the swamp again yeah it's so quick there's no fun to be had it's it's crazy
it's crazy it's so crazy that they allowed this ride to happen like this that there wouldn't be
any fun yeah and very little I rereading the summary of the plot of this movie I'm like oh
the prince is very useless in this like they dance and then he kisses her to wake her up
and that's his two appearances and I the huntsman has a very brief appearance of course
he chickens out yeah he chickens out he doesn't stab snow white and take her heart
the guy can't do can't get his job done let's be honest but in the ride he does you watch it happen
he rips her chest open he stops you he says where are you going you're not going anywhere yet
Claude Coates wanted an actor always on the ride to reach toward your heart in the last scene
your heart please that was a crazy thing I read about and and this to me seems wild that people
did this like it reminded me of the thing about how like the great train robbery or whatever that
was where the train would be coming at the screen people saw a movie where a train was on the screen
they thought a train was going to shoot into the theater that there's anecdotes of people reaching
out to grab the poison apple at Disneyland so they made it behind a mirror so there's a like
a holographic basically apple yeah it's like a projection wait I don't think that's like the
the great train rob I think that's people wanted to steal the apple I guess so but like how often
did that happen maybe a lot I think a lot of you're saying it's bullshit I'm saying it's yeah I
disagree I think I think a prop is handed to you essentially you maybe reach out and take it and
wow I stole the apple yeah I don't think that's people not understanding what's happening to them
in the medium what he's saying no he's saying that he thinks the story is overblown I'm not saying
it's actually like he doesn't think that it's fake I'm saying the anecdotes about what you're saying
it's fake but he's not saying that people are confused Jason thinks that it's a real apple
that she was like a cafeteria lady handing him food and that they would take the apple and say
thank you and then try to take a bite and then their teeth would all break off
Jason is the head did you ever reach for the apple as a child no because I didn't think again I
don't remember paying this ride too much mind if she offered you an ice cream would you have
reached for it well I don't it may have tricked me now I will say dear oh I love butter I know you do
uh it could have also been in the early days maybe they were doing that because their brains are
just trained from riding carousels where you reach out to grab the brass ring so you get to ride the
carousel again people in early days wanted to just wanted to reach their reaching arms gotten
tingling uh yeah yeah I don't know what you're talking about oh the term grab the brass ring
I know that term that comes from in the old days of carousels there used to be a brass really
hanging out and you would try to grab it and if you won it you got to ride the carousel so only
one person would be able to win it I'm sure different uh carousels had different rules
and bylaws interesting but that's that was the prize you just got to do it again I think so
remember carousels were like amazing to people back yeah these were people startled by trains
constrained by the British and Italian governments from what they could do
everyone was so repressed it's just enjoyment of things would come out in weird ways like a
brass ring or a psychedelic sequence in the middle of a snow white we're telling
that's why all English people and Italians still want to have sex with brass rings
their brains are all scrambled um we're talking a lot about the different versions of this right
and it's very confusing because they're pretty close even though it's so there's a video
myself absolutely there's a video though I'm going to tell and we'll link to it and now it's
this is also confusing because there's so many different things theme park related yeah I know
this is called the yester world yes and it's a great 15 minute video sort of detailing the
changes to these rides and like which version was which and very highly recommended I got a
lot of information from it um but there needs to be some variations in the names for these different
parts because there's a yester world there's a yester land there's defunct land and there's
and as if if you weren't confused enough in the yester world video defunct land kevin perjurer
makes suddenly appears in the video hey it's me from defunct land here just interrupting yester
world what's going on we need some variation in the names uh or are we wrong should our
thing be called yester disney day like is our podcast title too creative
to fund yester kingdom we're gonna change it to from pocket we're well from oh yeah let's buy
that right now yester kingdom podcast yeah uh jason the yester kingdom podcast featuring jason
yeah that's good now we have a proper theme park titling system um so but anyway that is a very
good video though very good yeah it spells out a lot of stuff that i didn't know and how all the
different it's a weird they all all these attractions opened yeah all right so one in
the 50s one in the 70s uh the one in the 80s in japan one of the 90s in france but they were but
disney one the disneyland one was redone in 83 the disney world one was redone in 94 and each
time they kind of changed to become more central and similar to each other to the point where i
think probably by paris they had perfected the ideal what this ride should be and the big thing
that they did in paris that none of the other ones had was an ending they actually made the space
for instead of okay if you go on the one here in anaheim and disneyland it's a bunch of horror
the witch gets struck by lightning and through shadows is her demise is implied and then you
round a corner and just see kind of a flat sign that says they lived happily ever after
it's very abrupt i kind of like it i almost don't want them to change it but by the time they open
the paris one they actually created a little room where the dwarves are waving goodbye to snow white
and the prince and dopey's sitting on top of a bridge and wiggling his ears and so they actually
got to the by the by finally by the 90s they knew we need to do a concerted ending room well the
one you're describing where it was just which is the the thing on the wall the writing on the wall
is even better than the original disney world version which doesn't have anything like that
the witch is about to drop a giant diamond or a giant jewel on you and then you just leave you're
like thanks for riding well there's no thanks it's just you're outside like she kills you even though
though it's obviously very bizarre that you end up in hell at the end of that ride it does you're in
that room for long enough that it feels like a odd twisted ending and you've been like all right i see
the end of the story but to just you're getting a diamond pushed at you and then you're outside
there's no transition out all the light just hits you it's so strange and i guess well i guess mr
toad implies that you were yeah you're dead because you're in hell but the it's even like worse in snow
white because you were dead and there's no indication of what happens to you yeah it's bizarre
the newer version correct me if i'm wrong but there's the the implication that a lot of the
horrifying the terrifying stuff could be a dream is that right did anyone come across that yeah
i mean like they're like the stuff in the forest and stuff what do you mean because you see now
that snow white is in some of these attractions uh she's walking up the stairs to go to bed
and that's an implication that we are seeing her dreams and that's all right i see yeah interesting
but that's so slight you have to read an article for that to even occur to you the other thing that
like to take umbridge with is a giant diamond yeah that's wild in the anaheim one it's a big
boulder which is the movie makes sense absolutely but a giant diamond and once again if the dwarves
are working in a mine that has diamonds that are bigger than they are then why are they still
working they should have found that cashed out you would think never worked again a day in their
lives this is this also suggests that like they're inside the mine somehow like like this is a
different surreal ending to the ride that's different from the movie the witch is in the
mine right she get in the in the mine right we don't know so it's actually kind of interesting
it's an alternate ending to the movie uh an alternate ending to the story but it's it's
bizarre and yes we've never seen something that big it's it's yeah it's a rare disney fairy tale
that ends with the protagonist being crushed by a giant diamond you're in a scene that is not in
the film and then you don't live happily ever after i mean it's but you're you're dead it's like
kind of an inglorious bastards rewriting of history where his hillar dies in inglorious
bastards of course he did not die like that in real life in this version we know all the evil
queen meets her end in the ride from the 70s in disney world she lives she kills you with a giant
diamond she lives she goes on i think yeah that's it that's the alternate history of snow white
she probably tracks down that huntsman has him rip out the hearts of every dwarf one by one
makes them all watch as each other are slaughtered that's that's i know i'm making that up but that
is in the spirit of what this disney world attraction is in the spirit of the original
for sure
oh yeah well you always ripping people up and killing people every original fairy tale is about
rape and the eating of hearts everything in disney movie is based on they had to censor the most
horrifying things anyone's ever written or read man if you could go back and see like clod coats
his original like what is his blue sky version of this thing it has to be what 10 times weirder and
gets to put their wildest like idea so like he had a whole other narrative like seen like specific
scenes where each dwarf is tortured like you go in a room he didn't want dumbo to be built he was
one he was wanting to annex all of that territory to have the room to do individual deaths for each
yeah it's uh he's depriving sleepy of sleep it's like the clockwork orange his eyes are
a survivor's guilt that he just lives with for the rest of his days i could never mine again
dopey has to like take a test or something and he can't do it because he doesn't understand things
well that's just your nightmare oh he tests i can't take tests too much pressure i had to take the
act twice i did okay though the second yeah not the first time talk about horror yeah oh sure um
so there's there's certainly a much more nightmarish version it would be that i'm sure
clod coats will get his blueprints and get to the bottom of this and we'll see all the various ways
this sicko wanted to torture the dwarfs you guys i wonder if tim burton used any of the sick and
twisted stuff for that live action dumbo that's coming out oh yeah that would make sense because
this is all snow white stuff but maybe you know you got to look for inspiration you know where
you find it if you can get in those disney archives you're going through a lot of stuff
i think yeah i think tim burton's dumbo is going to be an incredibly challenging film
we're going to be as freaked out as the italians in 1938 we couldn't process horror
that count on it um i learned something this is a quick side note i didn't realize this maybe you
guys know this and i'm just stupid for not realizing it that when they were doing disney
where they were going to build disney world they were going to basically clone like the ride systems
for snow white mr toad and peter pan but they were not going to be those movies whoa they were
going to be sleeping beauty sword in the stone and mary poppins wow they were going to be the
same ride system was that going to be tony baxter's mary poppins ride that got him the gig
i don't believe so because i think it was just going to be a peter pan ride system and maybe i
don't know of the same track and the stuff but then roy o disney said no they got to be the same
we're not changing what the carrot what the movies are so i mean that would have cost a lot more money
to make brand new rides that they were brand new i'm saying like peter pans would have been mary
poppins i know no not brand new ride systems but it would have been more money yeah for sure more
money but it wouldn't have been like yeah as much of developing but none of them really are clones
like those fantasy land dark rides are not exactly the same from park to park maybe by the time you
have the carbon copied but as it was like all of these snow white ones are slightly different
from each other right you have no choice but to go see all of them on this earth if you want to be
a completist that's what you have to do yeah i mean that would have led to a fascinating like
two very different fantasy lands between orlando and anaheim if they had totally different awesome
yeah that would have been crazy if they set that precedent that they would change it every time
it's sort of smart though because i don't know if this is why he did it but like the famous story is
that there was not going to be a pirates in florida they're like well you have a pirates
in california and then too many people complained and then they scrapped like a cool new ride for
pirates and they just threw pirates into florida so it's almost like anticipate i mean i don't know
if that's why roy said it's probably a cost thing he was the money man so that's probably why they
didn't do something different but so they kind of i feel like the dark rides are like the primary
movies maybe that was the feeling too we gotta do snow white sleep and beauty that is a primary
that's not represented in any significant way yeah i guess the castle walk through and me can make
an argument but no ride and this was going to be that was going to be the scary one that was yes
going to be the snow white one too so then there was like versions of it that they had drawn up
and then they decided to go back to do this yeah so that was going to be scary and you'd obviously
maleficent would appear you know a hundred times on it or something would have been screaming about
maleficent instead of the witch imagine that i thought it was interesting thinking about like
when when the disneyland one first opened opening day of disneyland the movie was 18 years old at
that point right yeah yeah 18 yeah but still but i was because you know when they opened the little
mermaid ride in california adventure and what would that have been like 2000 and 11 first 10
11 yeah 11 11 i think um check uh uh the movie was over 20 years old at that point and then
similarly here but like at the time i was like oh yeah i guess you can i mean that one but little
mermaid is so beloved i'm wondering if like that did that make more sense for disney to like yeah
of course we used the little mermaid ride here did that make more sense i guess they had less
movies when they opened disneyland so i mean it's just big gaps it's interesting to think about
like oh yeah that movie has been gone for years whereas like guardians of galaxy opened the summer
guardians of the galaxy 2 was in theaters i mean i assume it's just that they were like in a similar
way to being like well 20 years later we know this one was a like classic that people still like today
i'm assuming what that's the same thing with little mermaid where it was like oh yeah this
seems to be still resonating very hard do we think i think maybe mr toad potentially was a
more odd choice it was a more recent choice film that probably correct me if i'm wrong i feel like
people know mr toad because of the ride yeah i agree more than because i don't even know
it's from the it's it's from like an anthology called adventures of icapod and mr toad
yeah because it's paired with the legend of sleepy hollow which that concept or someone
posted that concept art online recently that was going around and i think it's mary blair did concept
art whatever it is it's beautiful but terrifying sure and that always scared me as a kid i was i
was scared of that i was scared of the headless horseman sure oh i didn't like the headless
he gets him at the end yeah sure he doesn't get away there's just a new new school teacher at the
end am i imagining that the disney version yeah i'm trying to remember now i don't think there's a
while ending it's more heart rips the he rips out icabod's heart in the tim burton sleepy hollow
detective icabod crate goes back to new york with his new bride and uh wars he just kind of adopted
is it johnny depp and halena bottom carter uh johnny depp and christina ricci oh yeah christina
ricci interesting but what will happen in the will ferrell sleepy hollow when they get around
to making the comedy versions of john c reilly is the headless horseman yeah i guess that actually
sounds fun yeah into that what we know will happen is we'll all be laughing we'll all be laughing our
multiplex um are we at the are we at the plus it up point um i don't remember how this works
anymore we've been doing so many on this forever city walks how do the how do these episodes go
what is my name for this stone is the big jewels yeah no stones no stone there's no there's no
narrative there's no overarching narrative for this thank you just talk about it right and we
say what we like about it and we just have to determine when we move on nobody is coughing
tell us yeah how do we oh how do we go back i think what we used to do is we would talk about
should the ride stay as is should it be plussed up or should it be burnt to the ground for
insurance money do you have any thoughts i do sure um so yeah i mean plus it up like we usually say
there's like the problem of course is space with this stuff but amazing they found some in 83
right they found some in 83 and they made it bigger i can't imagine it being shorter a lot
these rides yeah especially um and like i do think it's the intimacy of the ride is something
cool i think the frozen ride in epcot benefits from the fact that they had to force it into this
smaller space because you kind of get closer to the robots and it's cooler and like there's a
definitely a feel like as opposed to little mermaid where i feel like it's too big there's too much
room in little mermaid for some reason for me some of those i mean i thought there was a little room
obviously but like i don't know it's something about the sea is too but that's but it's the
grandeur of that sequence then maybe there's a different problem i'm not identifying ending
though that just skips the last like 20 minutes of the movie yeah i know i'm just saying that
there's something about um the fantasyland rides that put everything closer to you that makes it
more interesting it makes it feel special or better to me um but the thing i don't love about
fantasyland rides and this is just because these tracks are so old is that like the the cars all
just run at a very similar pace the whole time and it just feels like you're getting it done with it
doesn't feel like the car itself has any character to it it doesn't feel like like it would be nice
if you stopped and started in places it would be nice if there were moments like i'm trying to
think um like you know indiana jones or something just the car vehicle changing up its speed and
changing where it's pointing or something i feel like would go a long way in making the rides feel
a little bit more memorable other than just kind of going like all right zip through this thing
all right you saw all of it all right you're gone like sure like it's not necessarily the amount of
time you spend i feel like it's the way you're sent through everything that sometimes feels like
you're not getting a full experience on it i don't know if this is impossible because these are very
like short tracks and they want to get people in and out because of the ride capacity but like if
if your car like zipped into the the house the snow white house and it spent 20 seconds sitting
there watching the little show when they're playing or something maybe 20 seconds is too long
dude at the capacity i know it's i'm talking about things that would ruin the park and there's no
room there i'm just saying i'm trying to identify why sometimes i feel like these don't give you
the feeling of a ride and i don't think it's the length of time i think it's the very i think it
standard like speed i i don't disagree with you but i also think that is what these are i know
they are just like single speed you know really like minimal not not super flowery attractions
and it's it is what it is they have an old-timey charm to them and i think it might betray what they
are to get crazy yes right betray what they are though but i know what you're saying it is what
it is too dramatic of a word but i like what they are and i guess all i'm saying is like thinking of
the other rides that are similar to this why don't i want to go on these more often like i
wonder an adult but that's beside why do we want to go on any of this crap um well like that's
beside the point i'm just saying that there's there's probably things you could do and may
and again it may be impossible but i'm blue skying here you know that's what we're doing
i'm just saying maybe that's no bad ideas in blue skying like like a like if the witch slows your
car down or something and like you have to deal with like literally deal with her as opposed to
driving by her like i love the moment in the transformers ride when optimus prime at the end
of the ride he leans down and he tells you you did a good job i love that i think that's great
you want the huntsman to lean down and tell you you did a good job uh-huh and i yes i want i want
an intimate moment with each seven dwarf i want each of them to shake my hand in a way that's
like your need for mommy approval you like want the characters to tell you you're good uh yeah
maybe i mean i think that it would be nice if some of the characters told me i was good at least a
few of them it sounds like you had a very strong bond with these characters when you were young
i did for sure yes the seven dwarfs uh for sure i was obsessed with the seven dwarfs i may have
i had all those toys i wanted to hang out with aladdin and and the carpet you wanted to be
friends with the carpet yeah the carpet was a real scam the carpet and the monkey why can't
i remember the monkey's name a poo yeah i wouldn't be friends with you want to list the characters
that i like to be friends with let's let's hit it lumiere cogsworth flounder sebastian uh the dog
from oliver and come to dodger from oliver and cogsworth well i love the dogs and alluring yeah
cogsworth and i feel like would get along just fine
yeah i could see you'd end up you'd under his influence you'd end up growing a mustache that
looks like two little handles of a clock yes even once i've turned back into a human
yeah a little thin part and then you see you turn it into you have to shape it into an arrow each
morning look good on you so i think all to somewhat what my plus up is look for moments of intimacy
on these rides that's what i'm looking for and i'm not not intimacy in a sexual way intimacy in a
in a way where you come off feeling like you had a more of a connection with the characters or the
situation as opposed to just zipping by all of them good job mike from me doc you have to give
card at the start of the ride obviously that should be in every ride it's your passport to
get to bavaria or wherever snow white is set but the thing is so fast he has to rip through four
names like great good thank you thank you i'm proud of you mike do you want to meet my friend shrek
and it's red donkey i know dodger he's not here but i have his number he knows everyone yeah we
talk sometimes that's what the magic texting makes it easier they were promising with the magic band
that's the type of thing that would happen in florida but they really didn't make good on that
the closest was that was that poster in the rock and roller coaster queue that was like future r&b
singing sensation michael and it was just a written on the thing but it wasn't like they were they
were talking about magic bands being like a character would be able to come up to you and be
hey there michael i heard you stay to port orleans in room 305 i'm proud of you
how was your meal at south segula float works
sorry your flight had a delay in talahassee
i'm noticing your smartphone is running out of space
your app your disney app another dog is now distracting me in front of this bit
anyway i was 12 yet michael want me to delete unwanted files for you
good decision i'm proud of you as long as they say they're proud of me that's all i care about uh
hey all right so tell mike you're proud of him i look i do come on i do his your house i do his
voice when he when no one's around what does he say well he said hey he kind of sounds like this
oh i want to go outside that's my dog voice that sounds like a sick mickey mouse yeah he's a little
like anxious and he's rumbling right now and he doesn't like it right now he's worried i'm gonna
do that voice again yeah don't love me anymore the children of the world today that's all i do one
voice is every every deep male bell what's funny is that the 1983 version when they yelled it
the guy seemed like he was 20 years old he was kind of hanging off the side of a castle with
the sword and barely got it out he's coughing um all right plus it up what do you guys think
i have a i have a genuine answer which is i think it's time to uh oh i think it's time to bring
seven dwarfs mine train to disneyland really how interesting would it be to i don't think people
i think people like this i think people like snow white scary adventures i think no one has allegiance
to it enough to where if it was replaced by something i don't think people would be upset
and i like what they did in florida i like that this this the florida ride seemingly embattled
too scary for its first several decades they redid it in 1994 and people thought that that kind of
the balls off of it it wasn't scary enough so they ended up getting rid of it entirely in 2012
thinking that well now we will represent snow white via seven dwarfs mine train i haven't been
on seven dwarfs mine train it seems like an awesome ride and i the area of disneyland i'm
the most interested in in terms of expansion at this point is i mean toonetown but everything
up there the fantasyland theater the former videopolis i feel like that's all prime spot for
and you've heard rumors that frozen happens there i think it'd be cool if it seems like a really
smooth transition to go from either frontier land or or star wars galaxy's edge however works
to go from that to the to the rocks of the snow white coaster and that that kind of transitions
you maybe this frozen up there too and that transitions you into whatever's left of toontown
i think they could get rid of gadgets go coaster and do uh bring this ride there and then maybe
that opens up the possibility of doing a new uh 50s style dark ride perhaps for a more recent
property i think i think it actually would be interesting to see like let's do a little frozen
ride or let's do rapunzel or let's do uh or one of these sword and stone or sleeping beauty or
i think the i feel like walt might have wanted more change over of these rides i agree with that
kind of rinky dink enough that you could update them and change them out um that'd be my i just
think i think that would all be interesting doesn't have to happen but i that seems like a cool
disneyland move of the future well how about this you take out the storybook boats you take out casey
jr no and you put the whole coaster back there i don't know if it's big enough you're a huntsman
and we'll eventually do the coaster um and you guys neither of you guys have been on it right
the snow white i wrote it oh you wrote it okay i don't want to review that but i i do find the
ending of that lacking i feel like we need a good ending for it but that's another show sure um but
okay fine you put that back there with get rid of casey jr burn it to the ground for insurance money
how dare you and uh the storybook boats uh and then how about this we combine toad and
snow white into one ride somehow i knew it doesn't have to be those properties one big toad but those
are fine one big toad those are separate sides of the castle oh wait i'm confused then no wait
no no no no i want to have you say and take out pinocchio's during journey oh so you want to keep
pinocchio's yeah yes my favorite now the allegiance has come out yeah actually i was curious about this
in general favorites favorite of the fantasy lander it's gotta i mean it has to be peter pan okay toad
i'm pinocchio now i i this will do a full toad obviously but toad as much as i love it i love
the concept you can't deny that it's a lot of flats there's a lot of flats there's no robots on it
but he's a real scamp i love those devils hopping around i don't know i feel like we need some robots
i think the flats have a lot of personality and i think the train hitting you gag is very clever
the devil's fun i agree i'm just saying that peter pan has to beat it i think unfortunately for me
i don't think it does because for me because that is not it is it is not worth the wait it is all
that is out of control the line has nothing going on i think i somehow take some of the line
if they could kick out a store or something get a little more space do something a little more
interesting with that line uh but i i think what i like i think i like snow white and pinocchio
because you can just essentially walk right on them always and are they that is peter pan that
much better than the other kind of ride system i kind of believe peter pan is that much better
yeah i think it's a whole letter grade above those rides once since the upgrade yes i think
i've written it once because the line is just always so bad unless you go first thing in the
morning yeah no i i hear you i we don't go on it a lot either it's just it's the reason is it's the
best one it's yeah that's unfortunately the reason is that it's the best one and everyone knows it
toad's weirder this is why this is i think a lot of people would vote toad over peter pan
especially since we lost especially since we lost it let's look at the app right now let's see what
the line is we don't need to look at that we're looking at the app right now i'm gonna change my
points you have no put your phone down it's loading i have a ton of let's let's put the poll up on
twitter uh although now people might have allegiances they're just wanting to spite one of us but i
would love to say toad i would love to say it it would make me happy it doesn't sound like you would
i absolutely would toad is a more obscure choice i'd love to be like cool and hip and pick the cool
underground ride next to the mainstream ride toad is liking like liking brian eno or something
saying brian eno is your favorite artist or something it's not saying it's exactly like that
and mr toad produced a lot of great stuff too he wasn't just a performer well look right now peter
put the phone down i know the no i could have guessed that michael we said no phones during podcast time but it was in the it was a disneyland app
we are not proud of you right now but i said put the phone away all right uh so i'll give mine yeah uh i'll give
my silly the skykeeper serious answer i'll give a silly nonsense answer okay um so one thing we
didn't talk about is how when they changed uh this ride in disneyland the the ride vehicles used to
be shaped like mine carts and now they are shaped like beds and each bed has yeah the dwarf's name on
it i think you know i think about watching the first lie down dark ride i think we go further i think we
think about watching these uh movies with our families on family movie night all cozied up
on the couch with lots of blankets i think you really get pampered i think they really should
pamper you like you're getting into a bed i i want some are they beds they were beds no that's the
ride vehicle that's a question is is what are these i saw an article asking that question are they really
beds i don't know they're sort of bed-ish they kind of look like where you look that's true okay but am i
in reality i'll say my my real answer is i like the little i know the i know the budget got scaled
but like the last time for the 60th anniversary it kind of gave a fresh coat of paint upgraded
some effects on all these rides i think that is the way you keep them going uh i think just every
few years you you get some you know you certainly keep a lot of the animatronics or a lot of the
figures but you you plus it up a little with rear projection or new sound cues or new
whatever uh i mean because i don't know i think people just like the fantasy land rides kind of
as they are there's a reason people are waiting 20 minutes even just 20 minutes 50 minutes
to see these things sure how about also at the end of the ride we meet the mysterious man who
takes the jewels into town and sells them for the seven i mean i would love to learn more about the
economic uh is that have they oh no well that's i was going to say did they relinquish out to
action but they haven't done a live action no they haven't have they so when the rock plays
the huntsman well there was a snow white was a huntsman that was another studio yeah but the
huntsman can't be this star and we get the live action of disney's snow white well let's just
you know if the although i don't know let's get a more interesting i don't know like steve buscemi
or somebody is the man who uh who just cheats the dwarfs out of all of their way hailey steinfeld
is the snow white yeah she's snow white and how about uh grumpy no no doc is played by the rock
that would be very funny that's like infinity war where uh what's his face is the real big
the guy from uh game of thrones oh oh peter dinklage is the giant yeah oh
that's good stuff you know all right yeah neat opposites and dealing with uh uh finances and
finding out why the dwarfs are getting screwed yeah uh well part of the film is just looking at
spreadsheets they'll just put spreadsheets up on the screen we can scan it and go oh yeah oh no
that's that's that's bad or they'll put the screens on the ride like they did on spaceship earth
and you'll be able to look at the spreadsheets while the ride's happening oh that would be great
i mean because the more we talk about this the more i realize the dwarfs are probably wealthy
enough that they could get the huntsman to turn on the queen and overthrow her yeah and they could
rule yeah wouldn't that be a good sequel yeah the dwarfs ruling the king dwarfs ruling the king
and see how power corrupts and money corrupts them yeah yeah soon enough they're all cooking up
poison apples too and trying to knock off their enemies anyone in power would be working with
the dwarfs to turn from their kingdom to kick some ass take that i dedicate this
beheading to the children of the world this ass whooping to the children of the world
um all right these are all great ideas yeah folks you survived haunt cast the fright the first
edition of haunt cast the fright and we'll be talking about other scary rides throughout
the month could they possibly get scarier than this i don't know of a scenario where a ride would
be scarier i do not know uh if you want to if you want to follow the activities of haunt cast the
fright go to podcast the ride and twitter we're not changing them right that would be yeah no
that would be literally confusing we can change the display name people that's fun yeah people do
that for october i like that that's a lot of fun fun yes um but nothing yeah we're not going to
email address or anything email us at podcast the ride at gmail um and i you know what i have a
thing to plug right now beyond the typical show stuff i really want to encourage people to check
out a themed experience that i that i watched earlier this week um you know we reviewed mission
impossible 4dx in an episode of the show and i got to experience something that makes mission
possible in 4dx seem like a puddle of piss uh this thing blows it out of the water uh and if
it's on youtube and it's a it's a thing called tiny fuppets 4dx uh this is a i've been a fan
and a proponent of this series for a long time it's a portuguese animated show it's just been
in 2d for a long time uh called tiny fuppets and it's remarkable animation i mean i'm trying to
this like you know the way you know people tout miyazaki in america and try to bring it to a new
audience uh i'm trying to do that with tiny fuppets uh which are turulima makes and a team of
great portuguese animators anyway they are they have moved to a new medium it's now being done
with with not just in in 3d but in in 4dx and it's an experience where you you actually it is
immersive you're brought into the world uh you there is a chair that shakes you around the
technology is so far beyond what that tom cruise piece of shit did and i just really want to
encourage people to check it out um it's uh it's it's a lot of fun uh just like storytelling like
you're never gonna get in dumb american cartoons uh the the portuguese are are light years ahead
so uh please check out uh tiny fuppets 40x i i encourage you guys to uh oh of course sounds
great we're big fuppets heads uh oh really oh you are aware yeah we're aware of it we got some i
used to get vhs's oh really oh you're oh gee yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah wow well i'm very impressed
by that because i feel like they i feel like people don't it's like eno or mr toad it's
something the same thing you know know about in america and i'm trying to get the word there's
also a lot of confusion about is it's that it's a little similar to muppet babies which to me is
that's a bunch of babies but i never really saw it i never really saw the connection yeah no
there okay i'm so glad you're so you guys you're people of taste you know what i'm
yeah uh your actual connoisseurs of animations you understand the differences so i just want
to encourage our entire audience to check out the for my money themed experience of the year tiny
puppets 40x just type that in on on youtube uh or follow tiny puppets on twitter um and so i'm
sorry to give you more homework assignments than usual but uh i i think you'll have a blast they'll
be glad they did i absolutely and yeah and hey and the regular stuff follow us for more at last not
sectors although really all of theme park world everything's a sector everything's a sector yeah
yeah it's a it's a thousands and thousands uh the theme world thousands of sectors strong um
all right well thanks for listening we'll catch you with more frights next week spook you later see you