Forever...
dog.
Greetings foolish subscribers.
Your cadaverous pallor betrays an aura of foreboding.
Almost as though you noticed how long this podcast is.
Is the episode actually the length of a feature film?
Or is it your imagination?
And consider this dismaying observation.
The information contained in this podcast has no practical application in the real world.
But who are we kidding?
That's nothing unusual for us.
It's Hauntcast, The Fright.
Welcome foolish mortals to Hauntcast, The Fright.
I'm not ghost-hosted by three headless men in their ghoulies.
I'm Rotscaredner, joined by Mike Snarlscum and Jason Skeleton.
That's the best I could do.
I think I got the best one.
Jason Skeleton.
I thought about it working a little harder and then I was like, you know what?
That's just the plain Jason Skeleton I feel fine about.
I think I've seen this Halloween season, I've seen filters for Instagram or Snapchat.
I don't know, with dancing skeletons.
And it always makes me laugh.
Like a skeleton going all out, having the time of his life.
I think it's so delightful.
Isn't it?
Is it because you use scare already?
Because Jason's scared in.
I like scare in mine.
You took scare.
Yeah, I carted it over.
Being that there was a whole word I could turn, I should have done like skeleton with a D.
Skeleton, okay, that's good too.
Skeleton.
Or figure out a way to put scare in mine and then we all have scare in it and then it's uniform.
Yeah.
Okay.
Because scare in is the closest thing I could think of off the top of my head.
Snarlscum is a stretch also.
But feel free to replace these as we go.
I just thought I'd throw those out and we can change them every year.
Yeah, we'll change them every year.
Yeah.
Because we are doing the Haunted Mansion every year on Halloween.
It's official.
Yes.
If you were looking at this episode title and think, first of all, hopefully you're
excited that we are covering the Haunted Mansion and we're excited to be doing it.
But if you're wondering how people who took 19 episodes to cover City Walk are going to
possibly contain the Haunted Mansion in a single episode, we are not.
This will be a tradition every Halloween week will be the Haunted Mansion because there's
so much culture to cover within the Haunted Mansion.
I don't know how many it's going to take.
It seems like a lot potentially.
Yeah.
I mean, we are going to, obviously we've all agreed to do this podcast for at least 10
to 20 years.
So we know that.
That's the handshake deal I assume we made long ago.
So I would say yes.
There's 10 episodes honestly seems maybe.
We'll see if we can be tidy and keep it in there.
We'll talk a little later about what we're taking off the table.
But basically, we're kind of calling this like the origins of the attraction.
We'll kind of talk about how it got started, all the earlier versions and how it became
one of the best theme park attractions of all time.
But before we get into that, a big exciting announcement.
Today, this moment right now is the rope drop of Podcast the Ride, the second gate, which
if you don't know, if you didn't hear our announcement of this earlier, this is our
Patreon bonus content world of wonder that we are opening up over at patreon.com slash
podcast the ride.
So it's open the second gate.
Oh, wait.
You know what I should do is open the Patreon content in the name of the Weirdo Podcast
fans of the world.
Yay.
All right.
Oh, we've already started off on the right foot calling our donors weirdos.
Oh, I consider no weirdos is a term of affection for me.
I started out with my buddy Tommy Blot just started calling me and a lot of other people
weirdos.
And I realized, oh, that means he means he likes you.
That's what I started doing.
That's true.
Yeah.
It's the line in that Spider-Man turn off the dark song.
Oh, yeah.
All the weirdos in the world.
These are just the avant-garde people, the interesting people, you know, that's what
Bono meant.
People you want to be taken over New York City, which by the way, this isn't anything
we've talked about, but I did.
I did want to propose to you guys and I'll just do it on the air, perhaps within the
Patreon an entire episode just about the Letterman performance of Spider-Man.
We should do that annually as well.
I watch that every couple of months.
All right.
Now in year three, we will cover the man made entirely out of mutant bees.
Swarm?
You're talking Swarm.
I'm talking Swarm.
That's what Green Goblin would say.
Yeah, a Swiss Miss episode.
Yeah, for sure.
So that's an example of the kind of wonder that awaits you.
But let me give a very specific example of what you can find if you go to patreon.com
slash podcast.
The ride right now available to you is our first Patreon episode, which is about Disney
Quest.
It is a full length episode that's only for you, the potential patron.
Disney Quest, which if you don't know offhand, was the five story windowless VR experience.
Enigma.
Yeah.
That lasted for a long time.
One of the most confusing things ever on Disney property, and we know this is kind of an internet
favorite, Disney Quest, and we thought that'd be a really fun way to kick it off.
But there's going to be all kinds of stuff.
We want to say the basic terms, the kind of stuff we'll be doing.
Well, let's say too, yeah, pledge five dollars a month.
You will get access to the Disney Quest episode right now.
It's available right now.
You could stop listening to this and go to Disney Quest and then come back to Haunted
Mansion.
You can park hop.
It's a Patreon park hopper.
And then starting in November, you will get three bonus episodes a month.
Yes.
And we can, there are different types of episodes we have coming.
Among others, this is not going to just be it, but right now we have three different,
or not three different.
So we were talking about we have full length episodes.
We have character meet and greets.
So we've been hearing a lot about like people want to hear about Sunny Eclipse, you know,
the Lounge Singer alien from Cosmic Rays in Disney World.
And we're going to do that.
Yeah.
Maybe I'm not going to commit to this one officially, but when we kind of stopped doing
that animatronic a month of the month a while ago, and I had a little thing written up about
the lady who works in the Spaceship Earth Computer Center, like with the cool Afro and bright
yellow.
Maybe that's a character meet and greet.
I agree.
We talk about kind of anybody with a, what's the name of that toy?
You have a bunch of them, the Vinylmation.
Yes.
The Park Stars.
Yeah.
I think if it's a Park Star, it's a good candidate to be a character meet and greet.
I agree.
I do think we can talk about the goat on Big Thunder for 45 minutes to an hour.
If we haven't proven our worth in the rambling arena at this point, if you don't believe
we can do that, we'll prove it over on the Patreon.
And if you're one of the wonderful weirdos that wants to hear us do that, please come
over to the Patreon.
Come to us, the three biggest weirdos of the ball.
In the world.
We also have, they're called Sea Tickets.
Oh yeah.
See, we haven't talked about Sea Tickets yet.
This has been our idea for a while.
Kind of taking attractions that don't really, that are kind of riffraffs, that don't really
fit into a broader discussion of a land, that are kind of their own odd thing, that don't
necessarily sustain the full two hours, although you never know.
We don't know where these will go.
But they're potentially more of mini episodes.
And what have we talked about for the Sea Ticket?
I mean, the one, we haven't done one of these yet, but we always talk about the Mike Fink
keel boats.
Right.
And as an example of that, what are those?
That's always been one of those weird, I'm not sure I ever did it.
And then one of them went to sink and then it became not an option to do it.
But we're going to talk about that.
I'm pushing for Lucy at Tribute.
I love Lucy at Tribute.
There was a Lucy Ball Museum at both Universal Studios, Hollywood and Florida.
That was among the more mundane things at Universal.
Maybe I'm mistaken.
I think a lot of it, actually, Aaron, my wife, very fond of Lucy Tribute.
I'm very fond of it too.
I think when you said that for a Sea Ticket, like a shorter episode, I said, no way.
Full length.
Oh, we're bumping that over.
We can put it on Sea.
I'm just saying you may not be able to contain me talking about I love Lucy.
Yeah, Lucille Ball was probably my first favorite comedian.
So a weird little kid.
So that could be a Sea Ticket, but that might grow and become.
Well, these might all evolve and shape.
We've got to see if we're even able to do shorter ones.
And really, I think potentially in episodes could consist just of our internal discussions
of what goes into what category.
Yes, that's true.
I guess we do this via text a lot, but maybe we need to cart it over and make it listenable.
We should really just say...
We should probably have at least a document because searching through text messages can
often be a nightmare.
Yeah, true.
Yeah, I mean, we should...
Well, let's just open up our text.
Let's make our texts and our emails available.
Let's release the archives.
That can be part of it.
It's all evolving what is the actual contents of podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
But that's some of the stuff we've talked about.
Do we miss anything?
We'll do the podcast The Ride post office there.
We've had this idea of a lost and found episodes where we go back and cover parts we've already
done before.
We're actually, speaking of which, we started this show about a year ago and the first episode
was the ET Adventure.
This very day, we're going to record a little character meet and greet with an old friend
named Botanicus.
Yes.
Botanicus.
So, yeah, November, we're announcing...
We're not always going to announce everything ahead of time with the next month is coming,
but for the month of November, the first month of The Second Gate, we're going to do Disney
Quest and we're going to do Botanicus, an episode all about ET's wise teacher from the
Green Planet.
Finally, not weighed down by the other elements of the ET Adventure we had to cover before.
We don't have to waste time with the flop-global.
We can focus right on ET's teacher.
I will say we will talk a little bit about the flop-global.
We have no choice because that book that Botanicus is in is entirely about the flop-global.
Right.
He has more page time than Botanicus does, so he will be mentioned.
But Botanicus, we got a lot of fun stuff.
I found something that was shocking to me on the internet, and I will just tease you
with that, having to do with me and Botanicus that I did not know existed on YouTube that
someone made.
Oh, wow.
Interesting.
I found this an hour ago and I went, whoa.
It blew me away.
So that's a tease.
This is a real...
For your brand, for hashtag Botanicus.
Yes, which is a real flex.
2014, yeah.
My brand.
I'm finally really taking advantage of it.
Fine, Ryan.
Right here in...
And then I guess we'll say the last episode, or the third episode in November, will be
about Club 33.
Club 33.
You may have seen on Twitter that we got lucky enough to go, invited to Club 33, and we ate
and drank and...
And why not, with this new exclusive experience that we're crafting, why not put the ultimate
theme park exclusive experience into there?
So the podcast, The Ride of the Second Gate, has private clubs that you can join.
Yes.
Yeah.
It really makes me laugh, but in the Club 33 episode there.
Makes sense.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
These are champagne episodes that you're going to get.
So yeah, that's the beginning.
That's the beginning.
As we said, we won't always know what all of them are, but if those are enticing to you,
then head to patreon.com slash podcasttheride and...
No colon in that web address.
There's never a colon in the middle of a web address anyway.
No, only after HTTP.
Yes, oh yes.
That's the only spot.
Only there.
So, but just the words, podcasts.
So our famous colon's safe.
Our famous colon, yeah, is not there, but also you can just click on the link in this
episode description or on all of our social media accounts, because Lord knows we will
be screaming about it for a while.
I mean, I don't know, screaming.
Screaming is obnoxious.
A little bit screaming.
You might be screaming.
Yes.
I'm just trying to keep it mellow.
Yeah, I'm, I'll let you be calm about it.
Yeah, but yeah.
I got worn out by my initial bellow, but I was happy to bellow about it and I'll continue
to bellow about it.
And the Disney Quest one is a lot of fun.
That one's in the can and we...
It's a real...
That's a play.
If you don't know Disney Quest offhand, one of the, truly one of the strangest things
ever on Disney property.
So hear us talk about it for, that's a pretty lengthy one too.
It is a lengthy one.
Also, full disclosure, we realize that's technically coming out on October 26th, but cut us a break.
You're getting a little early.
Just a little treat.
I don't know if anyone...
So that's technically, you were saying that's a November episode, but you're getting to
the 26th.
So there's three episodes for November.
You said the three episodes for, yeah.
Right.
So anyway, if that sounds fun...
I don't know.
Don't hold us to rules.
Yeah, don't hold us to rules.
For $5 a month, you're supporting us in the regular show and you're getting three extra
episodes.
That's the deal.
If it sounds fun, come along.
If not, we have our regular episodes that are still free.
Yeah, they're not going anywhere.
Yeah.
Which we are currently in.
And I like that after all that, where we sort of had, not like rules, but there was a lot
of mechanics to explain about podcast thread, the second gate.
And now we get to shift right over to a different type of mechanics, which is the Haunted Mansion.
As we said, we're going to break up the Haunted Mansion.
We're going to cover it bit by bit, year by year.
It'll be a Halloween tradition.
And as we said, there is so much here.
And I thought just to be very clear about what we're going to cover or not cover, we'll
take a couple of things off the table right now.
My idea to tackle it was to do it chronologically, the beginnings of the ride all the way up to
the opening in 1969.
So what I'm going to take off the table, Nightmare Before Christmas.
We're not going to talk about that yet.
Go on.
Yeah, get in the back of the bus driver before Christmas.
Maybe in 2025.
Phantom Manor in Paris, which is wonderful.
We won't cover quite yet.
Or the Tokyo version or the Disney World version.
That's how much there is in the single.
There's just there's so there's so many specifics and wonderful stories, particularly about
the creation of this ride.
And there's plenty to do right there.
What else are we?
I would go so far as to say Phantom Manor and Mystic Manor in Hong Kong, two separate
different attractions than just Haunted Mansion.
And those episodes could be done potentially not Halloween week.
It depends.
Or they could.
We'll figure it out that schedule wise later.
That's a sort of trick a gooly in the Haunted Mansion might play on you.
I would say don't count on us getting to the Hat Box Ghost today.
I don't know.
I'm not I'm not prepared for that.
No, I'm not prepared for me either.
I don't think I think that's we're looking twenty nineteen twenty twenty at least before
we get to Hat Box Ghost.
So maybe we'll talk about it.
Maybe we get to the even the hallway where there's pictures of Hat Box Ghost on the wall.
Maybe I don't.
I'm not convinced we're even going to make it into the house.
It's possible.
We won't talk about the ride today or this year.
I mean, this is also we're kind of in doing all of this rule setting.
We are also under selling how cool everything is.
Oh, yeah.
That we have to talk about.
Of course.
And that this well here I will throw I'll throw this out.
I'll I'll I want to extract some opinions from you guys.
Yeah.
Where we get going too far.
Do you think at least at the time in 1969 this ride opens?
Is it in 1969 the greatest theme park attraction in the world?
It might be now.
Yeah.
I don't know what ride looms larger in my mind than the Haunted Mansion.
And even just doing research for this, I feel like I've read as much for this as any like
any episode I could pinpoint besides maybe Hard Rock Park.
And that was a whole park.
Well, that was a we just like, you know, we thought we were going to get like a drop of
oil and instead it gushed.
It was a geyser.
That was the problem.
We all that day were like, oh, God, oh, God, oh, God, it's time we have to start.
But yeah, this way, I think we knew there was a ton here.
And I agree even like this story of how this got made is interesting enough on its own.
Like it's so big.
There's so many people involved and there's so many huge events that touch it.
And it took so long to get it off the ground.
It's part of the fabric of Disneyland before Disneyland even broke ground.
There's so much there.
It's for sure the best ride when it opens.
For sure.
Because if you're a Pirates guy, Pirates doesn't open until a few years later.
Right?
No, Pirates is first.
67.
Oh, I'm confused.
But it's close.
It's neck and neck.
If Pirates is second, it's not a distant second, certainly.
Like I'll give due to Pirates.
But how insane, what a crazy run that those attractions were relatively close together.
A lot of the same team involved and that they're in the same area of the part, the first new
land of Disneyland, New Orleans Square.
Is that level of immersiveness, of architectural accuracy.
There's such a neat vibe there.
There was all kinds of live entertainment at the time and that the first two rides are
probably still in anybody's list of the top 10 attractions ever.
Yeah, and they seem like, you can feel that they're in the same era.
You can feel there's obviously a lot of similarities because the same people worked on them and
they're both kind of follow a little bit of a same pattern in the sense that it ends with
a big party.
They both kind of end with big parties.
It starts out slow, it starts out scary.
And starts out in just kind of relatively unassuming patios and hallways.
They really save the magic.
There's no videos.
Obviously I have no problem with a video getting you into the experience of the ride.
Those are often my favorite things.
But I love the fact that these are pure analog experiences.
Yeah it's crazy.
They get lumped together still to this day.
I feel like they're inseparable when you're talking about, I don't know.
When you're talking about rides you're always lumping these two together because of the
proximity I think, but also because of the fact that they're so similar in maybe structure
is the word I'm looking for.
And they both explode the amount of audio animatronics at the park.
I think by this point you've got Small World, but some of those are more minimal.
You've got Carousel of Progress, but you're kind of following new iterations of the same
character over and over again.
There's not too many audio animatronics in that all told.
There's Tiki Room, but they're small.
The fact that there's so many grand life-size and memorable characters in both of these
rides that you could describe, oh that weird guy or that weird lady offhand.
There's so many of them.
It's part of, by the way, not to get us on a tangent, but another thing that we will
not be addressing in this episode, except maybe for right now, the Eddie Murphy film,
which I've never seen and I imagine we'll talk about it someday and I'll see it.
But from my vague knowledge of it, the fact that they don't use the characters other than
little cameos or that it's not the mansion because the mansion is so memorable.
Well, Jennifer Tilly is leota.
Yeah, that's right.
Leota's in it.
That is the only thing that really sticks out.
From what I remember.
That seems to be one we could do something with if we pop by Howl at the Moon first before
recording that if you catch my drift.
Liquid courage before dealing with the Eddie Murphy film.
You had a bucket full of blue stuff.
A bucket full of blue stuff to talk about blue Jennifer Tilly.
It's ectoplasm.
Yeah, I mean that's sort of, I've been corrected about my country bears.
I've never seen the country bears movie, but all featured prominently on the cover of country
bears that are not any of your favorite country bears.
Oh yeah.
At least they are not recognizable.
Doug Jones, of course, is like, no, they are in the movie and the movie's good.
He said that to me.
So I guess maybe I have to watch it now.
That's a debate we can have.
Yeah, maybe we talk country bears with him on the movie specifically.
But yeah, it's like that people like those characters.
Why are you running away from using that?
I mean that's what, and we won't talk about too much the Guillermo del Toro idea for the
Haunted Mansion, but he I think is so focused on the Hatbox Ghost.
But again, we're not talking about him very much.
If that film ever happens or any future Haunted Mansion property, I have a feeling that it
will be more central to the actual, like what the fans like about this ride.
Because why would you not utilize that?
People are super passionate about every single, every room, every piece of wallpaper.
I sat in one of those Van Eeden auctions and I watched just replicas of the like, is it
a raven or an owl?
What is the like the top of the line dividers?
That's a bat.
It's a bat, okay.
But there is a raven that follows you throughout the attraction.
Yes, yeah.
But okay, the bat heads of the poles that divide the line up.
I watched a replica of one of those sell for, you know, $20,000.
Wow.
Like there's so much, like people freak about every single piece of this and I hope there
one day is a film that like does the, does all this stuff in a cool, respectful way,
the way the best comic book movies do like really pull from the, from the actual culture
of the ride.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, it's, yeah, it's, it is like the whole thing has become so iconic as you're saying,
like every piece of it is iconic.
And I guess even though I'm, cause I was really struggling with Pirates versus Haunted Mansion
of like what I like better.
And I feel like maybe I often want to go on Pirates more, but if I really think about
it, the pieces that make up Haunted Mansion do feel more iconic to me and more memorable.
There's more things I think if I listed a hundred things about Haunted Mansion, I feel
like I can easily come up with that list faster than Pirates that I go, man, that's great.
That's great.
Yeah.
I mean, I think the thing about like every piece of it feels now at this point, like
it's its own thing.
You know, I also maybe this, it's really splitting hairs, but if I, I think the fact that the
Haunted Mansion is, is this smooth experience that never, only if there's a little like
slow loading or an accident or something, does it slow down.
But like it is such a dependable experience.
That's like, you know, you're getting, you know what you're getting every time and you
never get tired of it.
Pirates does have that issue of the boat backups that goes so deep into the ride at this point.
That's gotten really bad the last few years.
Yeah.
I think they're running too many at once.
Yeah, they run so many boats cause they try to get people in and out fast.
But yeah, it ends up being, it ends up like in that last scene when the Pirates are shooting
at you, you're just like sitting there forever.
That makes you a little like by the time you're off of the ride and then you get back and
it does, it ends with just kind of, you see where you came in again.
I think that ending is maybe the only thing that I have to feel like I get off of Pirates
and go, okay, well I'm ready to eat or like chill out or something.
It does feel like you get checked out of the ride like a minute before you should or at
least two minutes before you should.
You'll check your phone at the end.
But Haunted Mansion, you're in it.
Pirates you can run into, I think, cause I ran into this once.
It was like my family and then we had like the whole boat and tour to ourselves except
for a row of people, a few rows back who were hammered.
And then you're just stuck with these people for the whole ride.
Haunted Mansion, you have a little more privacy.
The only issue you really won't run into that makes me neurotic is people firing off a flash
in Leota's seance room.
Oh really?
Like trying to take a picture and forgetting to turn the flash off because it's so like,
you know, oh it's just automatic.
The flash on your phone just detects when it should go off.
That sucks.
That's like then you're like 30 seconds of the ride adjusting your vision trying to react
to that.
Devilish deeds.
Don't take those flash photos folks.
Yeah, well it's wonderful.
There's so much.
And do you want, I feel like we all probably looked into the history of the ride beat by
beat.
Let's try to move through this chronologically and then see where we're at and see if we
even have time to talk about specific rooms.
Well the earliest iteration or thinking about this ride goes all the way back right here
to beautiful Burbank, California.
When Walt wanted to build the Mickey Mouse park across from his news studios.
Which we don't talk, we haven't talked about Mickey Mouse park a lot, but sort of the original
like smaller iteration of what became Disneyland.
And if you're in LA and you drive past the Burbank Disney animation studios in that building
and a big plot of land that is still undeveloped right next to that building, that is the original
spot.
That's where Mickey Mouse park would have been built.
Right next to the studio.
Yeah.
But there are, illustrate, you know, concept art from that and there's a little, little
part of it says like, correct me if I'm wrong, it says church, graveyard, haunted house or
old house.
Oh, okay.
And it's just like, they always envisioned some sort of spooky house, some sort of haunted
house.
Sure.
Because even at, even just back in the day pre Disneyland carnivals, you know, fairs,
haunted houses were very common.
Yeah, I mean, because the famous story of course is Walt wanted a place to take his
daughters that wasn't just a shitty old carnival.
So yeah, and on his head he was like, how do we plus up this crappy like fun house, haunted
house type thing?
Yeah.
And that came up a lot in a lot of different versions of it.
Like, and this was one of the battles thought about the haunted mansion is that like some
of the design showed it as like a shitty old decrepit house.
And Walt was like, I don't want a shitty old decrepit house in my park, especially in the
another early version where it was going to be off the main drag of Main Street, which
she's kind of like, that was interesting.
Yeah, that I mean, that's a real, that's a thing I feel like you think I think about
like Americana, especially to kill a mockingbird or Winesburg, Ohio, like these little towns
with the main streets, there's always like one shitty rundown house.
And at the time, at the time it probably made sense, but to us, they all look old now.
And it's like, Oh, look at that old house from the early 1800s, as opposed to these
modern houses from the late 1800s.
Now it's just like, look at all that old crap.
Sure.
It all just blends into a much.
Yeah.
That's funny.
Yeah, so I didn't know that that the, it was initially going to be like an offshoot of
Main Street.
And there's been various things.
If you go down Main Street today, there's these little alleyways, but there's nothing
too significant down there.
But those were earmarked in the early days in the fifties and sixties as potential like
expansion zones and whatever, because it just can be like Liberty streets.
What became Liberty Square in Disney World, which is where the Haunted Mansion is in Disney
World and the Hall of Presidents, there was going to be like a little like in the past
colonial area, right?
Shitting off of Main Street.
And love Liberty and he wanted it represented, but it didn't happen until Disney World.
Edison Square was also one of those possibilities.
Oh yeah.
I don't know much about Edison Square.
Was there also international?
Was there going to be an international street?
Oh, maybe.
Yeah.
Kind of the early seeds of what became World Showcase.
So, there was going to be a little side street with the haunted house at the end.
And then they started talking about doing something as sort of an annex of adventure
land.
Like, and I think by, I might be wrong, but in 58, they were already starting to talk
about a New Orleans area, but not where it ended up per se, more along the river.
It was going to be sort of tucked into a part of adventure land.
And in 58, there was a map put out where Walt made the New Orleans announcement official,
although it was all stuff that never, it didn't quite end up getting built the way that he
said, but that included a wax museum, potentially of pirates.
Right.
That would have, then that's what turned into the ride parts of the Caribbean.
Something called a thieves market.
I know.
That's fascinating to me, I guess.
What does that mean?
Like a bazaar?
Maybe.
Like a thieves market kind of a thing.
Yeah, like you could run by and steal an apple, a vest.
Will we finally see some of that in Star Wars Galaxy's Edge?
Oh, and thieves, a proper thieves market perhaps?
Stealing from the Toydarians.
So they're called the aliens who make the waves.
Wados race is called the Toydarian.
Yes, you're correct.
So you think there's, there's bad deeds going on in the market plate?
What's it called?
Oh, well you're talking about Star Wars Galaxy's Edge, which is on the planet Batuu.
Yeah, in the outer rim.
In Black Spire Outpost.
Black Spire, okay.
So Black Spire Outpost is not, it's not a clean shopping destination like City Walk.
That's what Jason's suggesting.
Yes, of course.
Okay.
So yeah, perhaps this was the original Black Spire Outpost while I was thinking about it.
So we can see the origins of Black Spire Outpost in the Thieves Den.
Is that the same map that has like the munition depot and the burning of the town?
Like there's some that read, there's some old maps.
This is what I'm looking, oh yeah, one of the resources is something called, it's a
book called The Haunted Mansion Imagineering a Disney Classic by Jason Sorrell.
It's really great.
Great book.
Oh, the one we're talking about is in here.
A lot of pictures.
You can read it yourself.
You don't want to hear us essentially slowly read the book to you.
Try to remember what's in here.
Also, and this is another check mark in the plus column for The Haunted Mansion.
I don't know of any other attraction that has as thorough a website as DoomBuggies.com.
Like this meticulously researched fan site.
And I read the six part history.
I started to read, and there were all these offshoot articles from that six part hit.
Like I still have six tabs open on my iPad that I just didn't get around to.
Well, save it a year.
You got plenty of time.
We can always go backwards.
Unlike The Haunted Mansion itself, our DoomBuggies can go backwards and then forwards again.
Yeah.
So, well, if we're going chronologically, then the man in charge of the ride eventually
put in charge of the whole project was a guy named Ken Anderson.
And he was like the one who's making these early sketches, trying to come up with the
concepts.
And he was, I associated him offhand with, I want to say Sleeping Beauty, but he wrote
a lot of the animated.
He's like the screenwriter of the Winnie the Pooh shorts, the original ones, among many
other.
I couldn't even begin to say the whole thing.
A lot of former animation department guys working on this.
The other name, and I forgot about this.
This is how much I've read about this now.
The other name that I saw pop up with Ken Anderson's, Ken Anderson's was Harper Goff
in the early days, who went on to design the Glamour Trams, Universal's first tour trams.
Oh, really?
He was the art director on that.
And then he was also the art director of Willy Wonk and the Chocolate Factory.
Oh, right.
Okay.
Yeah.
So he was involved very, very early on in this cast of thousands that worked on The
Haunted Mansion.
Was he part of one of those other, like either Kings Island or Astroworld, do you know offhand?
I would believe that because yeah, a lot of people did go work for other places.
I wonder if that-
You might be one that's not away.
Yeah.
There really should be like an IMDB for everyone's theme park work.
I mean, that would be the greatest.
Absolutely.
Or a, yeah, I spend a lot of time on Discogs.com looking obsession musicians and that's my,
I want these things to be more easily cataloged.
But it all gets so fuzzy.
People don't get the, you know the way when we found out Tony Baxter kind of helped originate
Soarin a little bit.
You never, you have no idea.
Or Raleigh Crump making Marvel McFay and Berry Tales.
Right, right, right.
Yeah, we're gonna need that because I very much want to do an article about Six Flags
power plant in Baltimore.
Oh, absolutely.
Which I have been to that building.
It eventually became an ESPN zone, a hard rock cafe and a massive Barnes and Noble.
But it was once like Disney Quest, an indoor amusement park, but they didn't want to call
it an amusement park.
Right, because they'd had grand plans for rides and what ended up happening was that
they didn't make any rides.
It was just shows.
But all these Imagineers, it's all walkthroughs.
Which Walt became very against the Haunted Mansion being and rightfully so.
But yeah, I'm, oh, I'm 100% on Six Flags power plant.
That's a really fascinating, bizarre failure.
It was only open a couple years, right?
Yeah, it did not last very long.
And then yeah, the next generation, yeah, the restaurants and the bookstore was one
of the revitalize that whole area of the Baltimore Inner Harbor.
It has the giant Baltimore Aquarium on one side, the Science Center on the other.
It's just like a ton of tiny malls.
Okay.
That aren't connected, but there's just like four malls.
I see.
And obviously the Harbor Keeper will be joining us for an adventure, step by step adventure
through the harbor.
To give Ken Anderson is his do here.
I'm looking at his IMDB.
He has story credit on Cinderella, on Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree, The Jungle Book,
Aristocats.
And then he's just every like many different roles on many different.
Yeah, and also like storyboards and like all the art is him.
Layout art.
That's so crazy.
Like so many of these people are writing the scripts or writing the songs and also doing
the concept art.
Like the multi-talent nature of these Imagineers is mind blowing.
Yeah, like I think it's in this Haunted Mansion book where Exatencio, like Walt was like,
you're going to write the script for pirates.
And he's like, I've never written a script before in my life.
And then it was like, but then I figured it out.
Like, and Walt just told you to do something.
And then these guys were like talented enough to figure it out.
Pretty crazy.
Yeah.
Really cool.
I am so excited to tell you about a lovely meal kit delivery service that I'm obsessed
with.
It's called HelloFresh.
HelloFresh shops, plans, and delivers step-by-step recipes and pre-measured ingredients so you
can cook, eat, and enjoy.
My favorite HelloFresh meal is the balsamic fig chicken.
It's very, very awesome.
And I made it, which is pretty amazing, in the place that I live, my home.
All right, here's how it works.
There are three plants to choose from.
Classic, veggie, and family.
Forget planning dinner, spending money on takeout at 10 p.m., or worrying about gathering
ingredients week after week.
All the ingredients come pre-measured in handy labeled meal kits so you know which ingredients
go with what recipe.
It's easy.
The recipes are simple and the instructions are outlined on pictured step-by-step cards.
So it's like super hard to screw it up, which is good for me.
Spend less time meal planning and grocery shopping each week and get that time back
to do more of what you love.
Most recipes take only 30 minutes.
So you can listen to podcasts ride.
Like you can listen to one-fifth an episode of podcasts ride while you prepare your meal.
And HelloFresh is a subscription service so your meals come to you week after week, just
when you need them.
Okay, so here, we have a very special offer for all you podcasts ride listeners out there.
For a total of $60 off, that comes to $20 off your first three boxes.
Visit HelloFresh.com slash theme park 60 and enter promo code theme park 60.
For $60 off HelloFresh.
So, well, so Ken Anderson, yeah, he drew the initial concept for what became the creepy
old house and it was, I didn't know that it was so specifically a specific house in Baltimore
to bring it back.
The Shipley Leitaker house and if you look at photos side by side, it absolutely is very
much like the haunted mansion.
It was destroyed, I think not long after the real, the haunted mansion opened.
But yeah, there essentially was a real haunted mansion and he also based it a lot on the
Winchester mystery house, which is an attraction in, ooh, is it Santa Cruz?
Where is the, or San Jose?
Where's the Winchester?
Yeah, I think San Jose, San Jose.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, that was one that Walt really got, I mean that I think made him think like it should
be a walk through like the Winchester mystery house or San Simeon, I saw it mentioned a
lot.
I don't know about San Simeon.
That's the Hearst castle.
Oh, okay, okay.
And then the Winchester was the Winchester gun, like that's the family that created the
gun.
Now, of course, filled with doors and that opened the walls and stairs that go nowhere.
The Winchester widow thought the house was haunted by everyone who had been killed by
a Winchester gun and she was very much into the cult.
Wow.
Yeah.
That sounds like a good ride.
At least a good maze.
Now that I'm a big haunt fan, I feel like I could make up a good Winchester maze.
So it is the house that already exists.
But mine would be different.
It would be more theatrical.
I could really, you know, they're not going to let me do everything I want to do in the
actual house.
I have to think they must do a haunt thing, right?
The Winchester, they're smart.
Look that up.
Of course, there was that movie with Alan Mirren not too long ago playing the widow.
Right.
What was that called?
I think it was just called Winchester.
Is there a point where the people who are there, do you see ghosts who died from a bullet
from a Winchester gun and then they say, well, I'm upset that I died, but you know, price
of freedom.
Yeah.
On the other hand, I cannot question the quality of the workmanship and the fair pricing of
the Winchester munitions.
Never had a problem, never stoppage.
I didn't have to polish it very often.
Yeah.
No misfires, no clogs.
No complaints there.
Complain about the death, but not only.
I was also, when I was shot with it, I was also holding a Winchester rifle.
They have tours of the estate, daily tours, but then they also have what's called the
Halloween candlelight tour.
But I'm trying to figure out if there's like teenagers that'll scare you too.
Oh, I don't think if you're holding candle.
Did this come up before where I took, my family took the candle lantern tour of Plymouth,
Massachusetts?
No.
I'm not so fond with ghost stories and hauntings and stuff because it's so old and in the early
days of Plymouth, people were very big fans of dying all the time from diseases and lack
of medicine and food and such.
So there's a lot of spooky hauntings and going on.
There were a ton of, more ghosts per capita in the 1600s than these days.
Yes, absolutely.
And people didn't have television or movies to entertain themselves.
So even if there wasn't ghost, people would just be like, ah, there's a ghost over there.
We got to kill the time until we go to sleep, possibly forever.
We may never wake up from that sleep.
We don't have medicine.
You paint a glorious picture of the era.
I hear Salem, though, leans even hard, much harder into it.
Plymouth leans into the founding of the country more and Salem, I think, leans into the spooky,
the witch trials and the black cats and everything.
Understandably.
Gotcha.
So Ken Anderson designs this exterior.
Walt says, as you said, I don't want a decrepit old mansion ruining the skyline of my beautiful
park.
Wait, is this Walt's line or is it somebody's response to him?
We'll take care of the outside and let the ghosts take care of the inside.
I think that was one of those ones often attributed to Walt.
To Walt.
Okay, okay.
And then the other thing in terms of the like, he died before this ever opened.
Walt died before this ever opened and was to his death was like, oh, there's got to
be a walkthrough.
Oh, had they not made the switch yet?
I don't think they made the switch until after his death.
Maybe right at the end because the World's Fair kind of kickstarted that.
But we're getting ahead.
I'm getting ahead of myself.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
So they, but they at least have the idea that you're going to enter this big themed experience
through a mansion facade, but they had to settle on what the story of this was.
And Ken Anderson came up with a couple of stories and I imagine you guys came across
these.
The most fleshed out of which seems to be the story of Captain Bartholomew Gore, who
was an old sea captain who murdered his wife.
This is so great.
Like we always talk about how we want to see that Batman five, like a Joel Schumacher,
like Batman triumphant, like that Howard Stern scarecrow, Howard Stern scarecrow, like Jack
Nicholson back, whatever.
Like you imagine this when I'm looking at the legend of Captain Gore, I love this.
I imagine in the same way of like, God, what would this have been like?
Sure.
And why not do it in some regard now?
Why not do this as a like Disney's getting into the void thing and there's the horror
void, Nicodemus.
What if now we had the tale of Captain Bartholomew Gore?
I was thinking that Disney does the Mickey not so scary stuff for Halloween, but why
not throw some mazes?
Because again, I'm a big Haunt fan now.
Throw some mazes in California Adventure and make Captain Gore.
Because essentially what they're saying when the mansion was going to be a walkthrough,
they're talking about Haunts.
They're talking about what now Universal and Knotts just do for a month and a half or two
and a half months.
Yeah.
And they do literally every one of Ken Anderson's ideas in different Haunts and people will
lose their minds.
You go, oh, well, it's an old Disney thing that didn't get made.
And even if you never heard of it, you go, oh, that's amazing.
And it would sell out and they would make a shitload of money.
This is like lost demo, like weird fragments of Shakespeare plays that didn't get made.
Yeah.
Like it's these alternate what could have been.
I think that's a genuine money idea.
Yeah, it's a great idea.
And I'll go one step further and give it a modern long naming style like some modern
rights.
The Legend of Captain Gore colon another Haunted Mansion.
Oh, yeah.
No, sure.
You get the term in there.
You get the title in there.
There's not there.
There doesn't have to be the single Haunted Mansion.
Yeah, that's really cool.
Just call it the Haunted Mansions.
Yeah, like eight Haunted Mansions.
And already we're in the in case you don't know, in case you've only been to the US ones,
Phantom Manor is totally different.
Mystic Manor is totally different, but they're in similar in spirit.
It's a similar thing going on with Tower of Terror where some of those have different
stories.
And yeah, why not?
Like the idea of this being more of a franchise and sure tales of more crusty old murderers
that will tell the real Robert Dyrd's story.
Some of them can be based on facts like law and order.
Some of Haunted Mansions are factual.
And instead of coming back, hurry back, hurry back.
The little ghost at the end goes, OK, bye bye.
And there should be one based on that with the Chicago guy that you love, the killer.
Oh, H.H. Holmes?
H.H. Holmes.
Oh, yeah, H.H. Holmes castle house.
Regional Haunted, well, we, hey, once again, you can go check out our episode about Disney
Quest right now, but that was an attempt to do regional, little Disney theme parks.
This is the idea.
You do like pop up Haunted Mansions in different cities, maybe based on stories from the cities.
You go to Galveston and you build the Durst mansion on a mansion.
You go to, is it Chicago?
Where was the H.H. Holmes story?
Yeah, Chicago during the World's Fair.
Yeah, regionally, we're bringing back the Disney Quest idea, but with your favorite local murderer.
Making a murderer in Baltimore.
There's a lot to do in Baltimore.
We're going to take over that harbor.
These are great ideas.
Also looking through all this art, like Star Wars is a thing that it's been mined so thoroughly
for nerds and fans of things like every single alien in the background of a scene has been
named and there are figures and there are comics about that character.
And then there are full, like there's toys based on the concept art of characters now.
This thing has been mined so thoroughly and Disney hasn't even, they don't even know what
they're sitting on as far as I'm concerned.
With something this popular, all this art and all this crazy stuff, there's at least
something to do with it.
Because this again, so many different attempts variations.
So Captain Gore, the story there was that he was about to be married and he told his
wife don't go in the attic and she went in the attic and she found out his secret, which
was that he in another, in the past, he was a murderous pirate.
He was Black Bart.
Yeah.
I've seen Black Beard.
Is it Black Bart or Black Beard?
I see Black Bart.
Oh, he's Black Bart.
He's Black Bart.
Another famous pirate, right?
Black Beard, the most famous pirate perhaps?
Not at this point Captain Jack.
I think so.
There was probably a Black Bart.
The Black Bart was I think also a famous pirate as well.
Okay.
Which I mean, I guess it seems, I mean, this is before, wait, this is, yeah, this is in
the 50s so they didn't have pirates open yet.
So although I think that's kind of a cool thing to tie the two attractions together.
It seemed like, well, that's, yeah, that Mark Davis connecting those two.
Yeah.
So he was Black Bart.
He has a pirate secret and instead of letting the secret get out, he throws his soon to
be wife down a well.
Which here's a thing I came across.
This blew my mind and I'm going to break a rule here because this was so crazy to me.
It can be done.
Figuring this out.
When you leave the attic, you turn around and you go downhill backwards to get to the
graveyard.
And I read one, I only came across this.
I forget where that you, that is a simulation of the bride being thrown out the window.
What?
By captain.
But that was a thing.
Oh wow.
Really?
Like a holdover.
I'd never read that before.
I don't know if it's true, but now I could not get it out of my head that that is why
you go backwards.
Do you think maybe it's just sort of a holdover from a design?
Cause like you're going backwards into the party, but maybe you're dead now.
Is that the idea?
Is that the transition to you being dead potentially?
Cause we're dead.
Like you're dead at the end of the Haunted Mansion.
Is that?
Is that right though?
Cause a ghost follows you home.
Right.
Yeah, you're right.
Maybe you aren't.
So then you're not dead.
You have to come back and bring your death certificate.
Right.
So then you're not, so then it can't be that.
So you're not dead.
But it's a simulate.
It's like, you know.
Maybe the idea is come back when you're dead.
Yeah.
But I think that's an interesting example, whether it's true or not, there's so many
little things that in some way through all of these creators involved, stayed in the
Haunted Mansion.
There's so many little bits in the soup mixed in.
Fragments.
Yeah, exactly.
There's early iterations where there's a character named Madam X and that became Madam Leota
down the road.
Or like, yeah, there's all kinds of where this didn't get fully fleshed out, but it's
acknowledged in this photo on the wall.
So like all of this, the many years of development, by the way, in everything we're discussing,
as you said, Mike, we're still in the fifties, right?
Not over 69.
There's so much this thing plugged along at the slowest pace possible.
It's crazy.
Like I mean, movies still sometimes take this long to make.
And I mean, not this long, but there's like, this is like reminds me of hearing those nightmare
stories of movies that were in development hell for 20 years.
Like Walter Mitty.
But it all worked out.
Right.
Or this is about to come out.
I can't believe this.
I remember this Indiegogo four years ago and I'm finally getting the reward.
Orson Welles' final film, The Other Side of the Wind comes out on November 2nd.
And it sat unfinished for decades.
And they finally got all the footage together and got the rights cleared away.
That's farther along though.
That got farther along than what I'm saying.
Like, oh yeah, that's true.
Cause there'll be movies and then there'll be like 25 writers or like 10 story credits,
10 screenwriters.
Yeah.
And then like, which is what happened to this, what you're saying, like so many different
people.
Traded hands?
Almost like people not, I don't think people were fired off of it, but I think people like
left Disney and weren't part of it or other people got put in charge.
It almost is a similar to a big tortured blockbuster.
Right.
But that ended up working out.
And very few of those movies end up coming out as good as The Heart of Man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Really?
Yeah.
It's the rare one for sure.
So yeah, look at the, in this book, the art is really cool.
Like there's a ghost chasing a woman around and then he has like big hairy hands or something.
Yeah.
And then there was like, it was, it's interesting cause it was a walkthrough, but there's, there
was a big conveyor.
I don't know what you would even call it.
Like a big platform that would lower into the ground instead of taking you upstairs.
It looks dangerous actually to me too though, because like the way that the elevator works
in the Haunted Mansion is very safe, I feel like, but this was just like a thing in the
ground with just lower.
Oh.
And I feel like somebody was definitely gonna like hit their head on the side or-
Yeah, yeah.
It was certainly dangerous.
If you weren't like evenly on that thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Right.
Or somebody's hand-
Cushion City.
The kid would get caught in it and something like something bad.
Yeah.
I didn't worry about that.
They would have figured it out.
Well, clearly the walkthrough element had to change and that was kind of a component
of why in these early versions Walt was not totally satisfied.
And there were a lot of like, it seems like in the early versions they'd like rig up these
ideas of an effect, but they would sort of take two minutes to play out.
It sounds almost akin to like what they do now in the Harry Potter windows, the little
like things you can activate with a wand, but you'd have to like stop and look at it
and I think Walt needed something that could continuously be getting people in and out.
Were you talking specifically, there's this sea captain effect that they had.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
What was the deal with this?
Like you were saying it took two minutes to play out.
Okay.
And then the sea captain, they had like mocked up or figured out a version of it would like
appear at a certain point in the ride and then he would just turn into water.
Whoa.
And like it's described as like the Imagineers were like, oh my God, like it was amazing
effect, but it took so long to set up and do that it was scrapped.
It's not repeatable.
It's not.
They can't just run constantly for 12 hours at a time.
Because it does seem like over and over again, they are worried about like ride capacity,
which is funny because it doesn't seem like they were worried about that for Star Wars
land.
Yeah, I don't know how that's going to work out.
Because they got rid of the ride that would have eight people, which was that Bantha people
over.
But like it does seem like they're very concerned with like, there's going to be a lot of people,
we got to move them in and out.
So even in a cool effect like this, we can't do it.
It sucks because it sounds cool.
I don't even know if there's a version of it anywhere in the theme park.
One thing I want to bring up that I kept seeing referenced and I think the timing is kind
of crazy on this.
So inspirations, you know, we talked about the Winchester Mystery House.
Architecturally there's a bunch of houses that kind of inspired it.
But yeah, that Baltimore one, especially with the columns and the iron grating all the way
around the outside patio.
Antebellum style.
Yeah.
Another thing that I saw referenced that inspired it was the 60s horror movie The Haunting,
which was remade in the 90s and remade just recently as the Netflix original series, The
Haunting on Hill House.
Is that all the same thing?
Yeah.
The Haunting of Hill House.
It's based on a book which is supposedly like one of the scariest books like horror books
ever written.
I mean, just look at, so here's a Haunted Mansion.
This is an ad for the Disney World one.
And this is the poster for The Haunting.
Oh, whoa.
Pretty similar.
Pretty, pretty close.
Sure.
There were specific gags to use kind of an off word, but that were kind of borrowed from
The Haunting.
For instance, it was a movie in 63.
Yeah.
Featuring Russ Tamblyn.
Russ Tamblyn was the name I read.
There was like four main characters.
That's the name of the actor or the character?
The actor.
Related to the number?
Tamblyn's father, I think.
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like I've heard that name before.
Oh, interesting.
So, but especially the door sequence, like the third or fourth thing in the ride where
there's like doors kind of pounding and one seems like it's breathing or that the knockers
are going of their own accord.
It seems like all that was very haunting influenced.
Yeah.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Although not to be confused with The House on Haunted Hill, a very fun campy horror movie
where Vincent Price lures people to spend the night in a house and if they can do it
and survive, they will get a large amount of money and everyone is given a little coffin
when they get their little hand held coffin.
They open the coffin and there's a gun inside and the house used in that is the Hollyhock
House in Barnsdale Art Park, right?
Oh, interesting.
In Los Angeles, the Los Alis neighborhood of Los Angeles.
Is this the, somebody had posed a question to me, where does the trope of spending the
night in the haunted house to get some reward come from?
And I wonder if it's from that movie.
I think in popular modern pop culture, I would say yes, that is the thing that is parodied
a lot.
Is there probably an example of it in Gothic horror?
Yeah, sure.
I don't know.
I don't have time for that stuff.
I can't read.
I read very slow and there's a lot of those books and it's hard to tell them apart.
And is there, does this happen in real life?
Is it, can anyone listening hook us up with an old man who will challenge us to spend
the night in a haunted house?
Which is essentially the plot of the Eddie Murphy movie also.
Oh yeah.
There is something like that.
Similar to that, I think.
I have not seen the whole thing.
Yeah, if you know an old character actor who's willing to take in a few boys to see a challenge
to them, yeah, please let us know.
Or if you are that old character actor, I was disappointed because I watched some of
that Netflix show and I thought it was a new version of the Vincent Price thing.
Oh, yeah.
I was like, here we go.
What new old character actor do they have to invite?
Oh, what?
It's a family.
It's a family drama.
Oh, what?
No, but the House on Haunted Hill and The Haunting were both remade in the 90s too, like within
a few years of each other.
I think one of them has Jon Stewart in it, I could be wrong about that.
Or somebody, or Chris Catan is in one of these.
Yeah, there's something like that.
I know, I remember that.
Jon Stewart's in the faculty.
Maybe I'm thinking of the faculty.
Yeah, but Catan could be right.
Also obviously we'll cover the Jon Stewart filmography beat by beat in the Patreon for
no reason, why not?
Big Daddy.
Death, Death, Death to Spoochie.
Oh boy, what a lineup.
So, where are we?
I mean, we're still-
We're still poking around here.
We're still in the middle of the movie.
So, where are we?
We're still poking around these-
Ken Anderson.
Oh my God.
We're still poking around these walkthroughs.
And this was one of the things that delayed the development of this.
Walt was committed to doing it, but just didn't like some of these stories, found some of
the stories too dark.
Oh, also Ken Anderson in his multiple propositions proposed a thing that would have culminated
in The Headless Horseman from The Sleepy.
It's Adventures of Ichabod.
The Adventures of Ichabod and Mistreat.
I forget what you call just the Ichabod part, but yeah.
So there would have been a pre-standing Disney character in it, but Walt wasn't totally happy
with everything, but they still- I'm not sure the mechanics of how this worked out, but
they built the house.
They were committed enough to this is going to work out, and they had the plan of it'll
be a small house that you enter with elevators that take you down and below the berm, and
then there's a bigger show building behind the train tracks, which is how it works at
Disneyland.
That's part of what's happened.
They have to get you, as with pirates, they got to get you behind the train tracks.
And it's in this big, it's funny, you guys look at those on Google Earth or whatever.
Those show buildings are so weird and boring.
Oh yeah.
Those big clunky industrial warehouses.
Which I forget, if I'm really into it, if I'm in a great mood at the park having fun,
like, oh yeah, I'm excited to go on the Haunted Mansion.
I forget like, oh yeah, this all has to exist in space somewhere, in physical space.
You get sucked in the illusion, especially as a kid, that you're in the house.
The house, yeah.
And that it's all happening in the- but that house is so small.
Similar to down the road, the Indiana Jones adventure, where you enter the temple, but
the temple is the smallest thing ever.
Yeah, a quarter of a mile away.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, it was like when I was on pirates, and I was with a guide in April, and he was like,
you know, we're not going underground.
That's just sea level is the whole ride.
The train is elevated.
For pirates, yeah.
Everything that when you load and everything, it's elevated.
And the restaurant is all of New Orleans Square is built up.
But always just your brain is like, well, we're going underground.
That's where the pirates live.
We're going- but it's like, that's all just built up.
It's like so effective.
You're going to ground level.
You're just growing to, yeah, ground level and everything else is just- because it makes
sense when you think about how like everything is like built up.
Huh.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
So you're not actually, yeah, you're not going into it.
But anyway, those basics were established.
And this, until I started doing research for this, I didn't realize, I knew that there
was a delay between the building getting built and the ride opening.
But I didn't know it was that that building was there in 63 and the ride was not open
until 69.
Until 69.
And for a good amount of time, it was this mansion that was just unlabeled with no reference
to what it was.
Which ended up making like free, what we would now call viral marketing because then people
just started making up their own stories or urban legends.
And it's like, it's too scary.
Or someone died in there or there's actual like, oh, they can't open it yet because they
got to make it less scary.
There was a ride that was to not unlike Alien Encounter later, all of these like, what's
happening in there?
Yeah.
I think that's so crazy.
And then it was just up there for six years, partially because story problems, partially
because Walt, without a lot of heads up, got pulled into this 64 World's Fair thing where
he built all these attractions in New York, small world, carousel of progress, the prime
evil world thing.
So a lot of people got pulled off and the place just sat vacant.
Yeah.
And I feel like I saw something, were they giving out flyers for it in 61?
Wow.
Like CN 63 or CN 60.
Yeah, really.
Really?
They really thought like this thing got delayed so much, but they were, yeah.
The marketing people are like, well, if past rides are any indication, it will take this
long to build it.
And I guess at the time, the biggest expansion had been Matterhorn Monorail subs came in
at the end of the fifties.
Yeah.
I'm trying to imagine like a modern equivalent of this.
Like if the temple in Indiana Jones just was there for, and you could like see it very
clearly for five years.
They did it for a year.
And I remember walking around and they did open just that little zone.
Right.
And that was the coolest.
Sure.
And it did make you wonder what the hell's going on.
It was like a teaser trailer.
Did you not know it was Indiana Jones?
No, they told you that.
But there was no indication.
Maybe there was one piece of concept art of what the ride was going to be, but it sure
let you spin your wheels and go, what the hell is this thing?
These aren't perfect one to one comparisons, but it would be like, say, releasing concept
art for a couple possible hotels in a parking garage and never fucking building them.
I mean, it's not it's certainly a cruel tease, but it's not quite one to one.
It would be if they just built if they built the outs, they built like part of the hotel.
No, this doesn't work.
It'd be well if they if they built the Haunted Mansion and then demolished it and put back
in the sandwich restaurant.
Holiday World is back for a limited time, depending on how these local elections go.
This is totally out of order, but I have to say it before I forget.
There was and I don't remember what era this was.
There was a plan at a certain point for a restaurant.
Yeah.
I mean, they did like Blue Bayou and then they were going to do Haunted Mansion restaurant
and that obviously got cut.
So crazy.
So yes, there was a Haunted Mansion sandwich shop at least.
That seems like a good spot to bring in the next couple of people who worked on this,
right?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Yale Greasy and Raleigh Crump.
Yeah, sure.
So yeah, Raleigh Crump has come up before probably.
Well, we just mentioned Marvel McFay, but probably mainly associated with the sort of
kooky art style and the tower that was outside of Small World in the World's Fair.
Forget all the Raleigh Crump specifics.
Power of the Four Winds.
A lot of another animation guy, right?
Another guy pulled over from animation.
All of these guys did backgrounds or character design, something for animation.
Yeah.
But his thing was that there was talk of some kind of pre-show, which potentially was a
restaurant the way the Blue Bayou gets you into the world of pirates.
And then when that got cut, there was this other idea, the Museum of the Weird.
And I have to admit, I'm not the biggest Museum of the Weird expert, so somebody feel free
to take it from here.
But it was kind of this, and again, another facet of developing this ride that Raleigh
Crump had collected all of these oddities and designed all this weird stuff, like a
clock with a face and a gypsy cart.
And it was like, how do we fit all this in?
And Walt figured out this potential pre-show area before your walkthrough experience began.
Yeah.
I mean, I haven't...
Diven, that's not the right word.
Diven.
Diven to the Museum of the Weird yet.
But Raleigh Crump, there was an article about him in a newspaper, like what, a month ago?
And he very much is like, he's like, if this name means anything to you, the wavy, gravy
kind of guy.
He's like a very hippie, kooky kind of guy who likes...
He kept talking in that article about like, we got to make Disneyland weird again.
He's very much up on like a lot of psychedelic stuff, colors.
Oh yeah, concept art is very much, yeah, like minimal and stylized.
Yeah.
Colorful.
Yeah, at least the color wise, there's a Jack Kirby vibe I kind of almost get from it.
Kind of, yeah, around the same time too.
And he seems like, he is such a specific type.
And I don't know that there's any other Imagineers I've read about that are so specifically like...
I don't know that he got high a lot, but like a Sid and Marty Croft aesthetic almost, coming
from like another Imagineer more than Raleigh Crump.
Yeah.
Well, he wrote a book called, I think it's called, It's Kind of a Funny Story.
There was just a gallery show exhibiting his work, I think here in California.
I went to...
God, what was it called?
I think it just closed.
There used to be a store, a collectible store here in Burbank where I've bought Disney merchandise
before, but they did a Museum of the Weird inspired art show a few years ago.
And so was people's interpretation of his models or art from the Museum of the Weird.
Oh, what it could have been.
Okay.
Yeah.
Of like the chair with a face in it or the candle wax man.
The candle wax man, the man made of candle wax is very unnerving to me.
Sure.
That picture and the cat going around.
Yeah.
Right, right.
It's weird.
It's kooky.
It is weird stuff.
It's surrealist.
I assume he would like Pee-Wee's Playhouse.
In my head would probably like talking furniture.
And this stuff has gotten revit.
There was talk of a Museum of the Weird movie at some point in the 2000s.
Really?
Probably didn't get that far along.
Eventually made into a comic book called Seekers of the Weird by Marvel in Disney's theme park
Disney Kingdoms line with the Haunted Mansion comic and the Big Thunder comic.
You're sitting on just making another haunted maze, the Museum of the Weird and everyone
lose their minds and pay them $100 extra on top of the Disney admission to go to it.
This is all really, the fact that there's like these subcultures and it also reminds
me of weird like the bands that the guy you like played with before it became the Elvis
Costello hung out with Brinsley Schwartz and these weird like Proto, the Cory men and that's
what all these things feel like to me.
I just started listening to Brinsley Schwartz the other day.
Oh, that's Brinsley Schwartz.
Good, very good.
Nick Lowe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He writes a great song.
It's a good band.
You should listen to it.
Yeah, you got your Rockpile stemming off.
It's before Rockpile, right?
Yeah, no, that was way later.
But I did.
Yeah, that's what this feels like to me.
Weird little like, you know, that didn't become the main thing, but you know, it was part
of the DNA and also, and I think it might be true that the first notion of a seance
room came out of the Museum of the Weird.
You know, and I think that was eventually if they hadn't done this development, it might
not have been in the Haunted Mansion.
Yeah, in the book, there's like a very colorful version of a seance room and it looks more
like I want to say gypsy, but that's probably like a very lame way to describe it.
But it's very colorful.
It doesn't seem like spooky at all, but it seems like a cool place.
Like it seems more like what I've seen from Mystic Manor than Haunted Mansion.
Oh, sure.
And the drawing of the cart, forget what exactly the term for that cart, but that there is
a cart like that outside of the Disney Disney World Haunted Mansion in Florida.
Oh, gotcha.
Kind of a little, you know, a little steps removed because, you know, all of these ideas
change the north.
There's a little cart in Disneyland.
And there's a little cart, but the Florida one is more colorful like that.
Yeah.
You're looking at this stuff, it all reminds me of like, it's his style is like so individual,
so individualistic and it's been clearly done in the 60s and so bold.
And it reminds me of like the point, like the Harry Nilsson scored animated feature
or like, or like what's that?
It's the French movie.
Is it fantastic?
It's not Fantastic Voyage.
What's the like weirdo psychedelic?
I apologize for blinking on this name, but it like his stuff just like feels like, it's
like cool, crazy counter or Lord or more obvious reference.
Yellow submarine like, yeah, definitely fits in that.
Yeah.
Yellow submarine is a good, is a good example of something where like, I bet that's his
completely is aesthetic and the art doesn't, it looks very similar to it.
The way that years later you end that they've that every once a year you get this wonderful
mashup of the, what became the Haunted Mansion aesthetic and the Tim Burton aesthetic.
It would be so cool to like walk around Raleigh Crump world.
Oh yeah.
Specifically.
Cause within just, yeah, there's so much character and specific choices within his, his art and
yeah, they got to start.
I'm upset.
I know it was an idea we just had right now.
Yeah.
I hope someone somewhere is thinking about doing these, these, these spinoffs.
The company in general does not know what they've got.
They know this stuff makes a lot of money and it's currently like maybe one of their
more consistent businesses, but I don't think they have any clue really what they're sitting
on as far as material that's already there.
That's what they own.
A thing that impressed me it's talking to, and you, you can hear this on the season pass
podcast episode about not scary farm, but talking to their merchandise guy down there
and he was just like, anytime we were to bring up an old knots thing that we don't even,
I mean, we're not the most knowledgeable about knots.
He's like, yeah, we're working on that.
Yeah.
We're working on some pins for that.
We're working on this or that or stuff like they are like mining their full a hundred
year history.
Yeah.
And I mean, they obviously probably have less, um, less stuff, but they still have a ton
of stuff because it's been around for so long and Disney does some version of it, but they
still only do the very bare minimum.
Like I would think that if they sold like, like we're recording this a couple of days
before what's kind of come out and this Tiki, this hat box goes Tiki mug sold out, which
I went down to try to get it and I was too late.
I was hours late and it's just shattered me and I've been depressed about it for a few
days.
Um, but like stuff like just merchandise stuff of all this old design or, or that, uh, just
like a little toy of this cart and be like, well, it's the original Rolly Crump haunted
mansion cart from the promo art.
People will lose their mind.
People go nuts.
Like people would love that shit.
And it's not just us.
There are thousands, as you can see the people lined up for the hat.
I know hat box ghost is a little mainstream now, but he's not that mainstream.
Right.
He really only became, he only got put on the ride a few years ago.
And it didn't, it grew out of people keeping this legend alive and being like there was
a much, it was a, again, in a music way, it was like a little like cult audience that,
uh, that grew and grew and grew and now can sell out of stadium.
The story of the hat box ghost again, probably its own episode.
I think it might be.
Yeah.
Well, here we're talking, we're talking about artists and their influence on this ride.
And maybe now we can start getting into the primary people who the, the haunted mansion
story comes from.
Uh, unless you want to go backwards.
Well, I think we got to talk about Yale Gracie before who, oh, sure.
So Yale Gracie, uh, was the guy who was tasked with, you know, Rolly Crump's doing all these
designs and Ken Anderson, uh, plenty of design work and, and a lot of the early storyline
development I think went to Ken came from Ken, but Yale Gracie was the one who came
up with all, he was tasked with the illusions.
How do you make it look like there's ghosts in this damn building?
And, oh yeah.
So, uh, and him and Crump, uh, uh, happened upon the, uh, old theater technique of pepper's
ghost.
Okay.
So you credit them for bringing that into the red.
Uh, yes.
Yeah.
I mean, it goes back to the 1800s and it's where you, you have an object or a person
like out of view of people, but there is a piece of glass.
So we're in modern times, plexiglass and the way it reflects light off of it, it makes
the object looks transparent in the audience.
There's probably, if you saw a spooky play in the 1800s and you saw pepper's ghost thing,
I bet you lost your fucking mind.
Probably started for life.
Yeah.
It's just people going like, we still don't have medicine yet, but we can do this.
We die less, but like, look at that.
There's a ghost.
You can see through that thing.
You can see how does that work?
How possible?
Yeah.
Funds to this.
There's a less from keeping my child alive.
How many church outings do I have to go to to balance out the seeing this creation?
I've been bedeviled.
I, yeah.
And then there's, there's a story.
I think this was all in this haunted mansion book about that.
Crump and Gracie just got to have this room of madness where they were just experimenting
with different illusions, some of which ended up in the ride, some of which didn't.
And that there, and there was a story in there about how they, uh, they were asked to turn
the light on, keep the light on at the end of the day because the janitors were getting
spooked.
Yeah.
Janitors did not want to walk in there and have to clean the object, clean the office
and find all of this crazy stuff.
And they were like, oh sure.
We'll leave the light on.
But they also rigged up the wind, a motion sensor.
And when you entered the room that a black light would, would turn on and now all of
the illusions would be operational and lit in the scariest way possible.
That's great.
And they came back in the next day and all of the effects were running and there was
a broom dropped on the ground.
So clearly the janitors fled in horror and said, you're going to have to clean your own
office from now on.
We're not doing it.
This is one of the fun urban legends associated with, with the haunted mansion.
I, I, I saw other stuff in there too, that Raleigh said he had drawn the original stretching
portraits and then Mark Davis said, I'm going to redraw these.
Oh, or that he drew the original wallpaper design, which that I kind of believe more
with all the, with the eye.
Yes, the purple wallpaper with black, which is incredibly popular on merchandise now.
Lots of apocryphal stuff around the reading about a lot of imagineering stuff.
It doesn't sound fun, but it does.
Reading that in the book, that sounded fun to me.
Yeah.
I'm just like trying to figure out effects and it just seemed like, yeah, that like oftentimes
it's just like, it seems like, Oh my God, how are we going to do this?
Yeah.
Especially in the early days.
But these, it seems like these guys were cut loose to just drive stuff.
And this is going a little out of order, but I might as well say it.
You guys might've come across, come across this.
The, the busts that follow you that, that as you move, the perspective changes and they're
always staring at you.
Yes.
Still spooks me.
Yeah, absolutely.
And I, here's a, here's a bigger thing about the haunted mansion.
This will apply to the episodes we do in the next five years, all of them that they're,
I'm so impressed that there are so many effects in this ride that I didn't really know off
hand.
And they, I think they've done a good job of keeping some of this stuff.
If not totally secret, then like it's still, you, you gotta wrap your head around.
How do they literally, how do they do that?
And this, and the bus is one of them and feel free to skip a minute ahead if you don't want
to hear how they do it.
You're talking about the bus in the line or at the end?
Yeah, before you, before you board.
Yes.
Thank you.
That, that is not a regular bust.
It is a little window box and you were seeing into, like it's like a cut open bust essentially
and you're seeing into the inside of it and it's lit in such a way that it looks like
the front of a, of a bust, but in fact it's the hollow inside of one.
And it's, and so it's just like this optical illusion thing and Gracie and Crump stumbled
upon this because they were also working on the Lincoln animatronic and there was a bust
of Lincoln's head that was like open at the back and they passed by it and it was like,
Hey, look at that.
Doesn't it look like Lincoln's looking at you?
Like here, go back and forth and Lincoln followed the whole way.
Wow.
So that's a hollowed out, it's not a real bust.
It's a hollowed out.
Yeah.
Reverse of a bust.
That's crazy.
You're looking into like a sculpture of a face.
That's interesting.
And it was, and it was originally Lincoln.
It was because Lincoln was just lying around.
I can kind of see it now in my head because I always have kind of thought that there was
a dementia.
I could kind of like, I always kind of could tell it felt like it was maybe an inverse,
but that's very interesting.
There's something that bugs you and it doesn't feel like tangible.
I'm sorry.
It doesn't feel tangible.
It doesn't feel like a, like, but like, is it a some weird proto hologram?
But no, in fact, there's no, which again, analog effects.
So this is all pre-digital on top of the fact, it's all these like very clever, like magician
inspired effects like Pepper's ghost.
And then also that I'm sure a lot is digitized now, but that all of the animatronics are
run by this gigantic server room.
That's all punch cards and everything to pull this right off in 69.
It's so fun, not that computers like help make a ride easy.
Now every, all the biggest, best rides in the world are the most complicated things
to wrap your head around ever.
The processing power of the Falcon ride is going to be mind numbing, but like that it's
just computer rooms.
It's just big crazy banks of how would they do this thing?
It's so, it's crazy.
It is why it's crying a bunch of like three, much of like animators and story guys.
And then some of these people had engineering backgrounds too, but like just, yeah, hey,
figure this out.
Yeah.
And then they went off of Cinderella and onto figuring out how to make ghosts come alive.
Which it seems like there was a lot of tinkerers too.
Like Trump was like a tinker and Gracie and like the way they talked about Yale, Gracie
is like, he would just be in his, and he would just come up with stuff and he'd just have
stuff sitting around on the shelf.
And even if it wasn't used on a ride or a movie, they're like, oh, we can actually use
that on a different ride or movie.
Oh, gotcha.
Right.
And the other thing to think about that all these guys doing this, like this is a very
funny picture of Yale.
Great.
And probably most famous.
You're going to talk about the picture.
There are so many good pictures of Yale, Gracie with ghosts.
With ghosts.
It is so, it is a treasure trove.
Like I, that, this is a very similar picture to what you will post to these.
You just Google image Yale, Gracie ghosts.
This picture of him pouring like champagne or booze or something into a glass of one
of the ghosts is fantastic.
I like this one.
He just looks like somebody's cranky grandpa or dad.
All these guys too.
Like a pipe firmly in his mouth.
He's the pipe guy.
Yeah.
Cause there's a, there's a video you can watch also from a special called Disneyland Showtime
and Kurt Russell narrates kind of what we've been describing, like these offices and who
knows if they were set up for the cameras or not, but like, you know, here's a workshop,
your ideal image of what imaginary could be where there's just ghosts everywhere.
And yeah, you watch a guy with a pipe go and like make an adjustment and he's smoking a
pipe while working on the, he said, that's real.
He just was this short sleeve workman guy with a pipe.
All these guys, even the pictures of Raleigh Crump in the miniature of the tower, the four
wind he's like in a short sleeve, like sure.
It looks like, you know, Johnny all American.
Yeah.
Well, they're all very, I mean, this is the same exact time as, you know, the moon, the
moon landing in Apollo 13.
And yeah, it looks like the, it's all a bunch of Clint Howard's.
They're all,
Yeah.
Even the psychedelic artwork guys look like that.
And that's the same thing of Jack, he's in pictures of Jack Kirby sitting at his desk
working.
It's like sleeves rolled up smoking a cigar.
Right.
Cause that's what you wore to work.
There's a picture of Raleigh with a yellow shirt, which is I think scandalous maybe for
the time.
Oh, shows what a, yeah.
Yeah.
What a wild man.
Kind of a handsome,
He's kind of a quarterback.
Yeah.
Pretty, pretty built dude.
I mean, he's, he's in some of these videos too.
There's one where he and Walt have really kind of got this poor woman corner or in,
Oh, that I think that is the Miss Tencenio of Disney.
She was the ambassador for the,
That's another word.
Do we have a name of that special?
Oh yeah.
It's so great.
I mean, I'm sure you could find it.
That's the one where like Walt is, seems a little lit.
I feel like I heard someone talking about this recently where he seems like a little,
like he's like in our spook how or so scary how.
And he's like, and then Gracie is like, Haunted Mansion.
Walt like he's,
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And he keeps going like Haunted Mansion and oddities from,
Oh yeah.
Beyond the mind.
There's something, they see Ramble like that's not, no, that's not the name of the thing.
It does seem like colloquially around the lot around Wed, they would call them, the
people working on this, the illusioneers, because they were coming up with so many tricks
and stuff.
Right.
And they're called, and it's Wed.
This is, all this is pre it becoming called Imagineering.
They keep saying Wed illusioneers.
Yeah.
Illusioneers cool.
That's not a, that's not the worst altering name for sure.
I get Imagineers is a bit, I guess a better catch all, but still.
When does, do the universal ones, are they universal ears or they,
Universal creative?
Yeah.
I feel like that's the term.
There's not a fun, they really should have come up with a fun name.
We should borrow from a upcoming topic, the Bill and Ted show, borrow a joke from them
and call the universal Imagineers Harry potheads.
Hey, hey, don't tip the appearance of Harry pothead on an upcoming spoiler.
Harry pothead coming.
But anyways, well, so more, more in the parade of wonderful, the wonderful short sleeve stiff
shirts.
Yeah.
We're finally getting into Mark Davis, Claude Coates and a lot of the ride, a lot of the
story of what fine now we're finally getting into what the actual, the actual automation
23 minutes into the podcast and we're finally getting, I knew it.
I knew we weren't going to get in the door, but there's so much there.
Also, you know, we're not doing too much as like jokes.
We're so like, there's some topics when there's not anything to rail on.
I'm worried about beginning stuff wrong too, in this episode.
And I already got the pirates wrong because I Googled pirates and it popped 73 up because
it's when magic kingdom opened and I went, oh, it must be 73.
And I'm like, so worried now that we're going to get like, there's going to be like haunted
mansion.
What opened in 73?
Pirates, pirates in Florida.
Oh, in Florida.
I'm saying I already got something wrong and I started sweating because I did it.
Because I, so I'm saying like, we're just like, not a lot of jokes, but we're going
here and we're just trying to like, tell, talk about what's interesting.
But I'm worried there's going to be a ton of haunted mansion driven episode where there's
more room for error.
Right.
We're going to talk, but there's going to be 50 haunted mansion nerds frothing at the
mouth.
If you, well, we haven't even talked about the blood mirror family yet.
I know.
But I don't know where they show up in the timeline.
Honestly, I think it was a Ken Anderson alt version.
That was a Ken Anderson version.
Yeah.
That was going to be this family who all like killed each other in comical ways and they're
the ghosts singing.
That sounds great too.
That should be one of the haunted mansions.
And also there's this like picture of like 11 that, that image, the marketing image from
the haunted mansion in Orlando had all of these pictures of weird family members.
And I think they were the blood or maybe not again, there's so much.
Yeah.
Weird.
And let's, so let's get blood mirror manor going.
All of them.
But so, but okay, let's get into, we're finally, we're stepping up to the main general concept
and the, just to break down the real basics of how the story ends up being told is that
Claude Coats was kind of the, we talked about him with Snow White, Snow White of Florida,
his primary doing.
He was, he was more, he was a master of like locations and setting and mood and feel and
environments.
Mark Davis, more of a character guy down the road, worked on country bears, America sings.
Jungle Cruise.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
So like.
He's the guy with the, he's the responsible for the jokes on the Jungle Cruise too, like
in addition to characters and stuff.
It's his like whims, he's a whimsical guy.
So many America scenes.
Yeah.
So many, which is many of the tableaus on Splash Mountain now.
So so many of the like famous, oh, that little animatronic scene is Mark Davis.
And so being a character person, he's probably more about personality and more about comedy.
And the big breakdown of this ride is, or was, should it be scary?
Should it be funny?
And the arbiter of this at some point in time might have been Walt Disney himself, but Walt
Disney passed away in 1966.
So these imaginaries were left to, left to fight it out, scrap it out themselves.
And I think it's interesting because Coats and Davis did work together on Pirates.
And, but you never hear about the war from Pirates.
Maybe Walt was helping with that.
Cause that's what they're saying.
Like he would, like the difference is that Walt would just make a decision.
They'd go, here's what I want.
Claude would say, I want to do this.
Mark would say, I want to do this.
And Walt would go, okay, we're doing the, he would pick one.
Cause Mark was characters and Coats was sets or like.
Yeah.
I mean, there's that breakdown.
But also clearly with that, there's also, I think the, the, the horror versus comedy
breakdown.
And, and, uh, which, which Coats is pushing more for, for scary environments.
And we, you know, we'll explain how it, how it kind of ended up working out.
But to me, it seems like Mark Davis, his attractions have a lot of character.
Like Claude Coats is Tony Baxter's mentor.
From what we can tell, Tony does seem to like a ride where you're the person on the ride.
Maybe all of his rides don't have a ton of animatronics.
You're sort of experiencing something.
Whereas Mark Davis is seem like you're going to go and watch a bunch of fun characters
do something a little bit more.
He's more about that's the, for my eye, my untrained eye, that's what I see when I look
at the different rides.
There's exceptions to the rule.
But there's, you know, it has a lot of personality, obviously.
There's this general, if you think about the flow of Haunted Mansion and the ride that
we may or may not talk specifics about, but the, the, that for a while it is a character
free ride and you sort of just like get, you know, or you hear the ghost host, but you
don't or you see, or you hear dead men telling the tales in, in, in pirates.
But it's so much of that.
That's another very long drawn out.
A lot is happening before you see specific characters and they're, they're kind of luring
you into this world.
Not unlike Indy in a way also that until you whip around that corner, you don't, that there's
this big sudden reveal of, oh, there's Indiana Jones, but it's been all about going through
this tunnel and a long, long, long buildup, which is a pretty cool way to do a ride.
I find it a little strange that Harry Potter and the gang are in the line.
Is that how we do them?
They do make an appearance.
Yeah.
You mean they're not on the ride?
Or just in general?
I mean, they're in the ride, but the, like, that they aren't saved for the ride.
I think it's kind of a, when you end up in that room and they're there, you're like,
oh, oh.
It's like a ghost almost too.
Yeah.
Which is cool.
It's not a big complaint, but it feels like a kind of like underselling, oh, we're going
to go see Harry Potter and then he's just in the.
The specialness of it.
Yes.
I see what you're saying.
I think I know the justification.
I know the justification I think is that Hogwarts is so special that of course they're there.
Like of course the characters would be in Hogwarts.
Because I would argue also that like the Harry Potter ride is great.
I think that there should be a full on Hogwarts dark ride.
I would argue that there should be something that really lets you explore Hogwarts even
more to a degree than it is going through the line.
More like gangs and stuff happening than like just, it's on the way to other stuff.
Yeah.
So I feel like maybe that's, you're right, but I do get what they're thinking is of like,
you're in the school.
You should see the students.
Like I would like to see a full Hogwarts ride where it's like the students are there and
like stuff is going on and like it's a bustle.
I just feel like you're saying Harry.
I think you're right.
I'm just saying that's probably their justification is that it is a working school and all you're
really seeing are a couple of people in robes and then there's a bunch of tourists.
Mine was more practical and I'd have to go back.
I have to get maps from when I first went and like now, but I feel like when I was first
there, there was a line on the map about take the castle tour and there was a separate one
of the queue lines was just, you could just walk through Hogwarts and not get on the ride.
And I feel like they were trying to pitch that as like a separate, like, Hey, if you
don't want to ride the ride, it's a little ride is a little intense.
We just want to walk through.
You can do that.
I can't really tell the last times I've been there if they were pushing that.
Cause I feel like they use it for express now or they just also anyone I've ever tried
to warn that the ride is intense laughs at me after they get off of it.
It's happened like five times now where I go, that's a pretty scary ride.
And then like they come on there and be like, what are you talking about?
And like, this is anywhere from our friend Marissa to my mom.
Like I went on with my mom and I was like, it's going to be pretty scary.
My mom's like, it's not that scary.
I would give the motion sickness warning like, cause I don't feel motion sickness on a lot.
I don't have that.
So it's the one rare theme or problem I don't have.
But I do.
I feel it on that.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
I don't have that problem, but yeah.
So we're almost going upside down.
Like that was the thing that always struck me is with like, as a kid, I was scared to
death of rides that went upside down.
This goes like 70% of the way there.
I was scared of the Dementors.
Yes.
No, I especially don't like them.
Yeah.
They get close to you.
Especially the Dementors count in Hollywood.
There's like 12 more.
Yeah.
But now that again, now that I'm a Haunt fan, maybe I'll go back and I won't be so scared
of the Dementors.
You also became a real big fan recently of laying it on thick.
I think to be fair, I think I've always been a fan of that.
That's you and I both.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's keep, I think we can get to the door.
All right.
Let's try to get to the door.
Well, anything more about Dave?
Well, oh, we can't.
We can't.
Davis and Coates is still going.
Because the peacemaker eventually arrives.
Yes.
Ex Atencio.
Uncle of Hollywood director, Peter Atencio.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And a guy who was like around the church that I went to growing up and my mom knew his daughter
and I ran it.
I got to meet him in the church parking lot one time and he drew a Mickey for me and I
still have that.
That's great.
It's a very treasured thing.
Yeah.
And that thought also when you talk about why Pirates and Haunted Mansion feel like two
parts of a whole, that it's Coates, it's Davis and it's Ex Atencio.
Ex Atencio wrote the script, also wrote the song and had never written songs in his life.
Green, Green and Ghosts.
But he could wrap his head around the fact that in both Yo Ho, Pirates of the Night for
Me and Green, Green and Ghosts, that it has to be kind of in the round.
It has to be a circular song.
It cannot be a live and let die with all these different sections and changes of tempo.
It has to be one flood.
It's the best example I could think of.
I love live and let die.
That's perfect.
That is opposed to Bohemian Rhapsody.
Live and let die.
It has to be this like, that's I think how he could wrap his head around doing a song
having not done one is that like, okay, well I know from rides how this has to function.
It has to loop like animatronics.
And music by the music part of that by Buddy Baker.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
And they were, I think he like both of both of those people, both Baker and Atencio were
surprised that they got the assignment.
They were like, I think, fill around with an idea and then we're like, and then Walt
will give it to the Sherman Brothers.
But in this case, they did not.
So it's actually strangely two of the most, you know, even though they did so many of
the famous Park songs, it was this was both, both of these were Atencio and and he, yeah,
beyond doing the song also like had to make heads or tails of all the stuff we've been
talking about for an hour and a half.
All of the various show elements, the different directions that Coates and Davis wanted to
go these weird scraps of here's an idea Raleigh Crump had, here's an illusion that Gracie
thought of.
He had to tie it all together.
And also at this point, he was stuck with the general notion of, okay, what the fans
are going to expect now is that this is a retirement home for ghosts.
We're backed into that because when the mansion was just sitting with no attraction inside,
Walt's tasked new, imaginary hire Marty Sklar, who became eventually the head of the whole
thing and worked there for decades and decades and decades.
One of the first things he ever did was write this big note that was left on the gate explaining
the backstory of it.
The gist of which is and as Walt Disney had said in various media, this will be a place
for homeless ghosts to stay.
The first time Walter talked about it on record, he was for the BBC and he talked about how
he had sympathy for all of the ghosts in England that have nowhere to go because London got
bombed during World War II.
I read that too.
That was the most bizarre thing.
What a bizarre thing to say.
Can you imagine if a head of a company said that now?
Referred to, yeah.
Like, and not that long after because we now are about the same distance of time from 9-11.
So like, we're a place for the 9-11 ghosts to go.
Bob Iger announcing that the 9-11 ghosts are free to come to Disneyland.
Like what?
They've been swirling around the skies of Manhattan, but now, yeah.
He'd have to resign.
I mean that's, well.
If he tweeted it, yeah, he'd be done in an hour.
If James Gunn has to go away for like lame, bad, dirty, gross jokes from 10 years ago,
Bob Iger inviting the 9-11 ghosts.
He needs to be punished for this thing we made up that he did.
I agree.
You know what?
In all fairness though, Walt's famous last words of course were, I will be ghost number
a thousand.
Change the script.
Yeah, one of those.
He's not one of the impressive, he's just like the third knocking door.
That's Walt.
I used to think when I was a kid that he was one of, we shouldn't be talking about this,
but the end of the ride with the heads that are singing, I used to think one of the heads
was him.
I did too.
I think I went for that too.
I don't know if it was, it's not Thorol, I don't think.
Thorol Ravenscroft.
I don't think that's who I was mistaking for Walt, but it might've been.
It's just the vibe.
Like a mustacheed man.
Those heads, you can't see it, but all those heads underneath the neck are wearing short
sleeve dress shirts with pocket protectors and somehow a full carton of cigarettes.
Bushy.
If all of those heads were smoking cigarettes, that would be the best.
Oh God.
Can you imagine how exhausting that would have been on message boards?
It was like, I think they should always be smoking cigarettes.
I can't believe they took out the smoking bus.
Walt wanted it, he's rolling it in his grave.
All the ghosts were smoking in the graveyard and they should have been smoking forever.
Smoking's okay, but drinking is not.
Those people would, if there was a Taunton Mansion bar, they would shut the fuck up.
Let's be honest, these anti Disneyland drinking people.
If you get the drink and then you get, I was going to say a real tiny glit, a fancy hat
box shaped shot glass that you put into, like if you get a Margherita Cadillac style, you
put the little.
Oh, and he like dumps it himself if that was possible.
Everything's dry ice everywhere.
There we go.
Again, it's crazy that that doesn't exist.
They were going to do that Tower of Terror bar in Florida and they didn't for some weird
reason.
But Mike Carlson would draw the line if they served wine.
An alcoholic's drink.
Yeah, well that's an alcoholic's drink.
Margherita is a fun drink or a colorful drink.
This to me, one of the strangest things ever said out loud by anyone or been certainly
on the podcast itself.
Well, I mean, in full disclosure, we're recording this on the 20th of October, which is our
one year anniversary and I picked up a bottle of sparkling wine for us to enjoy at this
episode and Scott has been like licking his lips and salivating this whole time.
So in Mike's defense.
If you haven't heard Mike said that it out beat by beat all of the all of my smacks.
And also people probably and a lot of episodes, though, my neighbor has a window.
So with a pie on it and Jason oftentimes is licking his lips and salivating.
So I have to edit that out often as well.
This is a cherry pie cooling on a window.
So you know what you were getting into when you moved here and I have to oftentimes as
you're floating off the couch toward it, I have to pull you back down and I have an
anchor around my ankle now to prevent that.
But when you close the blinds, then you can't see your neighbor who is a burlesque model
in a 40s bathing suit.
Get her away.
No.
In decent.
All right.
So where are we?
We're getting there.
We're 40 minutes into the Haunted Mansion and we haven't talked about.
I love OK.
Well, I think the divide is becoming clear.
I think you come back next year and we'll talk about, you know, the stuff inside.
We'll talk about the room.
So how about the so we have the war.
We have exsitio making peace.
I think like the it seems to me like how it ended up working out is that the beginning
of the ride pre characters is like that's the scary zone.
Spooky.
And it's and it's kind of keeping this this tone of OK, like there's going to be there's
going to be a wake.
Ghosts are going to start appearing.
But is that going to be OK or is that going to be terrifying?
And you get to live in that for a little while.
And then probably the leotis scene starts to transition.
She's not funny, but she's like making you comfortable with the idea.
We're going to start seeing goes.
And then when the ballroom starting to get a little funnier and then by the final by
the graveyard party now, oh, ghosts are fun.
Actually, I like ghosts.
I want to I like a ghost ghost.
That's scary to me.
I was going to ask, where do you guys personally think the line where where does where is the
brackish water between the fresh water and the salt water?
Where is like the delta?
I think it's the my very my favorite thing in the ride is the the dual.
The two ghosts and the pain, yes, we're facing apart from each other and then they turn and
they say, I agree.
And that to me is where it starts.
That's exactly what I want to say.
Yes, because it's like it's still kind of scary.
That whole room.
Yeah, that scares me as a kid.
I was like, I like this, but I'm happy I'm on the second floor.
Like, I'm happy I'm above like above them because they don't have like and I don't know
this.
We didn't need to research this because we won't do this until 2020 2021.
But I didn't like the feeling you get because I think it's a little bit farther away than
the graveyard ghosts is that those people aren't as full of life, even though they're
moving.
They don't have as much character to them.
I don't see them as friendly.
I see them as like having a party and I'm intruding upon it.
Whereas when you're in the graveyard, you're enjoying you're there happy that you're there.
Well, and they're part of like a very formal functional, like if you went to like a royal
banquet order to that here now is the dancing part.
And now we sit at the table and we use this knife.
We but the by the graveyard party, all bets are off.
Everybody's hanging everywhere.
There's lampshades on here.
And people have broken out into different clusters.
There's no order left.
And that's my so my view of how this that's the story works is that yeah, that you're
like nervous about ghosts.
Am I going to like ghosts?
So wait, they're having a fun party.
I actually I shouldn't have been afraid the whole time.
So then you're accustomed to like, I guess I'm I guess I'm a fan of ghosts.
All right.
Well, very good.
One's going to follow you home.
It's like, well, wait on a second.
I didn't agree.
Let's not go nuts here.
Yeah, that's that's my that's that's how I perceive the story.
And I think I so I think you get this gradient from Coates into.
Yeah.
Into Davis in a very fun way.
But as we talked about a little bit in Snow White, you know, Coates didn't get to do his
full on hit like trapping people in a scary, stressful environment, which is why when he
he got his dream in Florida and did the Snow White ride, it was super scary, not character
oriented.
So somebody's just yelling in the other room.
Goose.
But that's that's like where so to tie our whole spooky month together.
Yeah.
So, you know, Snow White probably doesn't happen as terrifying as it is.
And as a friend of the show pointed out recently, like we said, Claude Coates was Tony Baxter
psyched him as a mentor figure.
So when it came time to do Haunted Mansion in Paris, Phantom Manor definitely leans more
towards the scary.
Yeah.
And the whimsical.
Although there is also competing stories about that, that, you know, the French, they they
get scary.
They Tony always said they get scary.
They get funny.
They don't get them together.
So they have to go in one direction or the other.
This is I'm sure this excuse me.
This point has been made before, but the Haunted Mansion and pirates are structured like Wilco
front man Jeff Tweedy talks about putting a concert together.
He's like he likes to start out with like maybe like a challenging like moody or stuff.
And by the end, it's a celebration and it made a lot of sense to me when I heard him
talk about what a concert structure like that you want to end on a very fun, triumphant
note, but you start out kind of wading into something that's a little bit more like dark
or challenging.
So it really is kind of a perfect structure for a show in general.
Like just to you.
So, you know, you start out with ashes of American flags, but then by the end you're
playing Monday, you're playing, I got you, you know, all your fun Wilco rockers.
It like makes a lot of sense to me when we're talking about like the way they transition
out and then the way this stuff ends.
And in this case you get scary version of Grim Grinning Ghosts into mid step waltz version
of Grim Grinning Ghosts into fun, kooky ragtime Grim Grinning Ghosts.
And I'm describing Jason's dream, a concert that is all Grim Grinning Ghosts front to
back 70 minutes.
And I'm going to do you one better on that, Mike.
The Wilco Alhom Yankee Hotel Foxtrot, very labored creative process.
Yes, very labor.
Much like the Haunted Mansion, an album that in my mind looms very large.
Also probably think, did like Pitchfork give that like a perfect 10, like the year that
came out.
It was like the album of the year.
So do we give the Haunted Mansion a perfect 10?
A perfect 10, yeah.
Are we the snobbier end of Pitchfork and it's just 7.8?
Fine.
It's pretty good.
Why did they give the rafts to Thompson Island at 7.9?
I don't understand.
Maybe instead of the whole scale plus it up, we should just start doing the Pitchfork rating
on these rides.
Oh yeah.
For all the rides will give a very precise amount.
And then like strangely, like to make a point, we give 10 out of 10 to the Jimmy Fallon.
Right.
And we're like, you know, pop art.
It's what's the problem with that?
All right.
What to them had a job interview those people this week?
They're trying to get more mainstream.
I'm heading to MTV.com.
Well where are we and how do we how do we proceed?
We keep trying to get into the queue and we keep getting spooked by curveballs and I've
got another one, the World's Fair, the 64, 65 World's Fair.
Yes.
Probably.
I mean, the second big event that affected this ride in addition to the other being Walt
Disney's passing.
But the World's Fair, a lot of imagineering, a lot of wed and presumably MAPO, which is
the manufacturing arm of wed diverted to making World's Fair sort of stuff.
But greatly the work done for that and the research done for that greatly influenced
this ride.
All the animatronics work done for the World's Fair attractions and the rides is the early,
early pre-omnimover ride system for the Ford Magic Skyway.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Of a continuously moving ride vehicle that was refined into the omnimover used in Adventures
Through Interspace and other Claude Coats.
Yes.
So if you don't know about, if you don't know the mechanics of Adventures Through Interspace,
those were what became the Doom Buggies.
It's these pods with the high backs, the best vehicles in which to make out at Disneyland,
thus leading to Haunted Mansion being the best ride in which to make out.
Have you, didn't you make out in a Doom Buggy?
Oh, you know it.
Or like you kissed.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
What was the story?
Oh, no, I did.
Well, there was, I like, knowing that, you know, knowing that I like, this was, if I
was going to get it done.
Right, that's the time.
That's, yeah, yeah.
I think I talked about, this is the same one where I had some of this mischief with the
Matterhorn.
Oh, yes, yes.
And we were like, the whole day at Disneyland, we were trying to evade the very overprotective
mom, me and my long distance girlfriend who I only saw once a week.
So we had to make out at Disneyland because there was no other option.
So did you say once a week?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I only saw her a week a year.
That's what I meant.
That was how I spent my high school years for you, the listener.
I was, had a girlfriend I only saw one week a year.
So I had any, any exploration I wanted to do, I had to do at family friendly, theme park
destinations.
So once again, if you've been listening for a year, that's just a reminder that things
like that are why we are the way we are.
A crucial backstory, just like all this crap about Raleigh Crump and led to the iconic
podcast, The Ride Boys, We Are Today.
So iconic.
No, no, no.
So we like knowing the layout of it, we were like always trying to, we were always trying
to escape the overprotective, you know, just, you know, like very much like in a movie,
like the Katie Holmes's first daughter trying to escape from the prying eyes of the Secret
Service.
I swore you were going to go with Amanda Bynes and Frankie Muniz trying to escape movie executive
Paul Giovanni.
Big fat liar.
By hiding in the costume department?
And then having a wild romp through all the costumes and props?
Oh yeah, yeah.
That's another, that's a big theme park movie.
Well we can, maybe that's a Patreon.
That sounds like a Patreon.
Patreon commentary on Big Fat Liar.
So anyways, I like, I had to like, when the elevator doors opened, I like broke off and
like we got away from her mom and I could see her like getting lost in the crowd and
pushed back.
Oh wow.
And we're getting steps ahead and we're, you know, now we're like seven doom buggies ahead
of her.
Oh wow.
So we can do, we can do whatever we want.
Oh yeah, she was furious.
Absolutely.
They're going to enjoy this attraction on their own.
He might lightly graze her boob over the shirt without me watching.
That pale wet boy, who knows what he'll do.
He's wet?
Yeah, he's sweating.
It's just constantly damp.
I see, you're not incorrect.
Also keep in mind, I had, if you've seen a photograph of me, I had hair twice as long.
Oh yeah, I think I've seen something.
So that's my, that's my, hey, worked out great.
I was the happiest haunt in the whole mansion.
I will be back with my death certificate.
Did you just run to get back in the line then after that?
That would have been smart.
No, then we were, we were good beyond that.
Yeah, no cell phones.
You don't want to get too lost, you know.
No there, yeah.
So I'm not sure we all had, so this, we're talking like 2001 or so, which is two.
Anyway, so we've obviously covered all the important stuff.
My make out adventures in the year 2001.
We've talked about first daughter and Wilco.
What, what can we, how can we wrap this up for this, this chapter?
I mean, we've, I actually, I think the entire origins episode makes a lot of sense.
Yeah.
I feel good about it, but what's, what's anything big that we haven't, oh, you were starting
to say the, the doom buggies.
Yeah, the doom buggies as they call them in the Haunted Mansion.
A couple of interesting things about that.
One, the only time doom buggies is said in the Haunted Mansion is when they come to a
stop and that recording that says like, you know, spirits have, you know, interrupted
your journey.
Please stay in your doom buggy.
That is Exitencio.
Oh.
Saying it.
No kidding.
I know that.
That is his voice.
Who's also the skull in Pirates.
Pirates, yeah.
Yeah.
Wow.
And the same guy does the safety announcement, wrote the song, wrote the dialogue.
Yeah.
And here, look, we've talked about this.
We've talked about everything, any and everything, except for the, besides these specific stuff
in the ride, but the dialogue, indelible, famous people quoted with the exact intonation.
So many lines from this are so quotable that it was all from this same guy.
That's a, that's totally bonkers and I'm sure we'll get into our, our favorite stuff, you
know, next year.
But that's also a, I remember that being one of the like early, oh, let me try to impress
people I'm taking here with my little, you know, my odd little knowledge.
You know, these are called Omni Movers.
I remember knowing maybe Erin was, the early sign Erin was the one is that she, I told
her about Omni Movers and she thought that was neat.
Other people, I'm like, this is called an Omni Mover.
What?
Who cares?
Could the difference have been she just smiled and was like, cool.
When you say neat or was she literally like, oh, that's very cool.
Like you believed it.
Oh yeah, no, I should know.
Oh no, a very, a very earnest smile and the word neat.
And she still likes to use the word Omni Move.
She likes to point out Omni Movers to others.
It's a match made and that's right.
And Omni Mover Evan.
I mean, I all, I, I wasn't saying she wasn't actually interested.
I was just saying that the difference between some, the average person when they hear Omni
Mover, they, their eyes glaze over and they go, who cares a shit?
And then just the difference between somebody going, oh, cool.
Yeah.
Seems like, yeah, that's a, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's all though.
That's all.
You're the one marrying me now.
Uh, yeah, absolutely agree.
I, uh, is a mild interest in what you're saying.
But the ride system is like, uh, and there's not a ton of rides that are this, but you
wish there were more rides that were this that you never, that it's, it's one, it's
not individual cars.
It is a trail of cars that is never stopping.
That's continuous.
And that's what Little Mermaid is.
And that's how they solved the, that was one of the big problems with the walkthrough ideas
is you weren't going to get enough people through.
The Omni Mover pretty much doubled how many people could get through this thing.
There really should be in each theme park, there should be like three versions of this.
Yeah.
Like there should be, like, cause People Mover is a version of this, especially the one in
Florida.
I think Florida moves more, whatever.
It's a bigger, longer thing.
Yeah, yeah.
You can eat up more people.
Yeah.
Like People Mover version of this is your, like, Inner Space was, uh, what was it?
Little Mermaid, sorry.
Um, it, because like it's practical.
It wasn't like a dream flight or isn't, um, I guess you'd call it's not the pod, but Buzz
Lightyear is.
That's true.
Yes.
Good point.
Yeah.
Dream flight and if you would have wings.
There's just something you can literally get people off the ground.
And the Imagineers liked it because they could control the speed and what your perspective
would be and what you were going to look at.
Oh, I think the idea when you see the early discussion of this ride that we can make you,
we can spin you around that you can go backwards.
Right.
That, that I think is a mind blowing, uh, mechanism that they got to put in.
Yeah.
The amount of control they suddenly added really is like one of the most ingenious,
uh, uh, very, and it seems like it would have been a version of this is that third ride
that got canceled from Star Wars land.
Is that, is that you think that's the deal?
They supposedly it was like a people mover Bantha ride and Bantha is a big like furry
creature.
I don't know how they're going to make it look like you were on the back of it, but
like it was just a people mover type thing where it would just be a continuous and you
just zip around above the whole land.
Yeah.
And colloquially called people eaters because they take so many people out of the park.
Um, this was interesting to me.
This is concept art of the doom buggies going down the portrait hallway.
Ah, oh yeah.
Yeah.
Isn't some of that stuff or the bus or something saved for when you're on the ride in Disney
world, I think some of the, some of the elements are different.
Like it's not in the line.
It's on the ride.
The line is a little shorter when you're, when you get off the elevator.
Uh huh.
It's like, it's, it's a different line and it's not, it's, it's a better line after the
elevator to the ride in Disneyland.
Okay.
Oh, interesting.
But some of it's yeah, some of it's on the wall a little bit.
This is stuff we will, uh, we'll get into also the differences between, which I thought
there were just a few, but as you go through this book that we've pulled all, a lot of
this info from, there are a ton of different, a ton of differences between all of these
places.
And you'll be hearing this in a few years when president Michael Avenatti, uh, made
every mistake, right?
President con man the second, uh, is in charge.
He's our con man though.
He's our con man.
I've gotten more on board the Avenatti train day by day only because I've lost all hope,
but I don't, do I think he'd be a good president?
Of course not.
But we need a guy who can like, you know, who would like smack Trump in a debate.
Well, look, Scott, the residents of river city were very fond of professor Harold Hill
when he rolled into town to save them from the ills of billiards.
He was a nice man.
The boys band.
He seemed nice.
Yeah.
It kept being nice, right?
So, uh, uh, by and large in the end, actually, yes, I've fucked myself with that point because
everyone likes him at the end.
Uh,
Wile Langley would have been better.
Oh yeah.
He does actually, yeah, that's a good point.
Um, so I mean, we're at the game.
We got the climax.
We talked about what Omni movers are.
Yep.
Um, what else do you see that?
What's a good, like, how do we lead when what and, and how do we, so I guess we'll pick
it up next time in a year.
Yeah, any year.
By going room by room because I truly, and I think going room by room, do we even get
to the end of the ride?
No.
I don't know.
Cause there's so much just in each of, there's so much personality.
There's so many, uh, wonderful gags.
I have a lot of thoughts about the employees working and I like, we all have, I think our
own taste of what we would do if we were working the haunted mansion.
That's sort of a dream.
Everybody kind of fantasizes.
What everyone's favorite stretching portrait is.
Yeah.
What people fantasize about working, I think haunted, whenever you go, Hey, if you worked
at Disney, where would you want to work?
I think most people say haunted mansion.
That seems like a num, probably the number one or, or I guess tower of terror.
Usually people like to say, Oh, I could be like creepy to people.
Something where you get to do stuff or like the late great movie ride.
You know?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
Interact with people.
Oh, after all that bunks, he materializes.
Yeah.
I'm bad.
I'm not a actor scene.
Yeah.
I, I guess you're right.
I, I'd have to think about that where I would want to, did you guys, I didn't know until
there's a little tease of stuff to talk about that there were live actors briefly in the
80s.
Yes.
That's crazy.
Uh huh.
People hated it.
Scared me as a kid.
I would love it because I'm a big one fan.
Jersey Shore haunted houses.
Like I would go to the person working the line like, excuse me, are there real people
in this or is it just the robots?
And if they said there's real people that jumped out, I'd be like, no, no, thank you.
I think it's somehow might be worse than haunts because at least haunts you are, you are moving
and you can look away.
Like if you're in a little car, you're trapped.
I mean, we've all been on this ride so many times, but I thought now, since I know that
fact, I've thought about it being on the ride.
So especially going down the hallway, I'm like, what would be a really, what would scare
the shit out of me right now?
I guess if somebody actually came through the door, like very fast, if somebody's popped
through the door, you lose your mind.
Uh huh.
But yeah, if you, if a person was just like, I'll ask you some questions about record
Ralph, Ralph breaks the internet.
You have a couple of minutes to answer a survey.
Uh, if like the, if the omnimover like turns around and there's just a person like, like
staring at you, like it, right.
I guess maybe after I'm trying to think like maybe when you enter the attic, cause the
attic is so claustrophobic.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Like stuff like that.
I've thought about, I think if Leo, if Leota shattered and like hopped into my car and
not the others, only my, like her, like her decrepit, uh, like, you know, her, her, her
pale hardened, uh, uh, rigor mortis face, uh, uh, you know, and there's like little squishes
with each pounce and then she's in my, yeah.
Yeah.
If it shattered like a fish bowl and Leota was in my lap, I'd be, uh, that's the worst
thing I could think of.
That's a rolly crump idea.
That's a weird idea.
I think it's a little weird, but I think it's good.
I think you can make it work with, with some finessing.
Um, but it's not, yeah, it's scary, but it's hard to development.
Uh, and we'll, yeah, we'll keep perfecting.
Let's see if, let's see if we were, let's say a crump crump coats and Davis, who of
the three of us, like which of us are, which guy?
Hmm.
Uh, who do you think?
Who's the weirdest?
We're all a little, uh, uh, I don't know.
I mean, we're all parts of all of them, but for the fun exercise, we should, we all go
a little mad sometimes.
I'm obviously a little, I'm Claude now because of how much I like scary stuff.
So I'm Claude.
I'm, I'm crump because of how I trip out on psychedelic wine.
That's true.
And Jason is clearly Mark Davis.
I guess I'm Davis.
He's a whimsical, yeah.
He's a whimsical, a lot of character, very specific character.
I mean, certainly the most memorable of the three of us, you know?
Oh, well, I'll take that compliment.
Put that in my pocket for later.
You were designed, if we could have, you know, I really don't want to call for fan art, but
if you could draw a picture of Mark Davis creating Jason on an animation desk, that
would be really great.
Remember it all began with a Jason.
Um, I like that.
With a nice call for fan.
Okay.
Well, then I think I can say you survived a haunt cast, the fright in which the ride
in question was not discussed.
But I hope you found all of this information interesting.
I think it's all crucial backstory and crucial development for what, what became the iconic
ride that we will get into next year.
Yes.
We hope you'll meet us at the wrought iron gates this Halloween season next October.
And if you're only listening, if you, if you only intend on listening to our haunted mansion
episodes, then I would say don't hurry back because you got a while to wait.
Uh, we were going to be waiting as long as people waited for the actual ride to be built
in Disneyland.
That's a good idea.
We get it done.
Can we get it done in six years?
We'll try.
We'll do our best.
Uh, we'll, we'll give it a go.
So for me, for a, a guess what?
Uh, next week we're going to be covering a, a, a, a spooky theme park attraction that
I think is every bit as iconic clean and perfect as the haunted mansion.
So come back to find out what that is.
We're as positive about it as we have about this.
You will find us glowing about all of the incredible writing and detail in this attraction.
In the meantime, please go to patreon.com.
It's how you can do it right now.
It's so exciting to say we will waste two more hours of your time.
Totally different attraction for building full of attraction for only five little dollars
a month.
You can barely get a McDonald's meal at that.
You can, if you use the app like I do, I can get a $2 to $3 meal and it's actually very
satisfying.
But like you barely get a comic book for that price nowadays.
And we'll give you hours of entertainment.
And you know what's funny is that like the haunted mansion today, the first Patreon topic
Disney quest is a building with no windows and no doors.
Very good point.
It's all together.
So yeah, head to patreon.com slash podcast.
All right.
I'm so excited.
It's open and thanks people for encouraging us to do this and thanks in advance for checking
it out if you're going to do it.
And for our regular hijinks, head to Twitter at podcast the right, Instagram podcast the
right, our podcast the right Facebook group, podcast the right at gmail.com.
And which again, I'll keep saying it, send us ideas, stuff that you want to see as Patreon
content or any kind of content or write us letters or complain about the very slow speed,
almost Omni mover like pace at which we're moving through the haunted mansion.
Yes.
Well, you've survived haunt cast the right.
I did say that already.
Hurry back.
I think this is the second time you forgot that we said it already.
Or Scott said it already.
I honestly this time I did not.
You zoned out.
That's okay.
Well, I just wanted to do the hurry back voice.
See you over on the second gate.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex
Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us.