Five, four, three, two, one.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Podcast the Ride,
the second gate, historic moment,
the show hosted by three guys who know two hours a week
just isn't enough.
Those guys are me, Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson,
and Jason Sheridan.
Hey fellas, we made it.
We have landed at a, it's a historic opening day.
And I just wanna say this,
to all who come behind this paywall, welcome.
Podcast the Ride, the second gate is dedicated
to the dreamers, the optimists,
the people willing to pay for an hour of rambling
about Edwin.
May it be a source of time wasting or distraction
during a jog or commute for all the world,
dedicated by Scott, Mike, and Jason, October 2018.
Do you feel the magic in the air,
this historic opening day?
That's beautiful and I also like in that,
that's obviously gonna be a plaque.
They'll put that on various merchandise.
Only the people who subscribe to the Patreon
will be given access to be able to buy the plaque.
I was, look, the gold itself will cost about $10,000.
So we're gonna have to mark it up.
I like that it's also a tease to the Edwin episode.
There's a very specific.
I figured I'd plant that flag now.
That's, look, we have a ton of fun ideas for this,
for the tried and true people who are down
to hear more stuff.
That's one of them.
We wanna talk about all these crazy weirdos
who we like who are part of old Disney rides
and attractions and films, your thorough Ravenscrofts
and what have you.
Mike, as you've alluded to, we wanna pay tribute
for longer stretches of time to some
of our favorite animatronics.
Our favorite alien animatronics.
You might hear us over here talking about a guy
named Botanicus.
I bet old Sonny Eclipse will be discussed
in the near future as well.
What's really great is that a lot of these animatronics,
not Botanicus, Botanicus has a rich backstory,
but many of their animatronics will do an hour on,
have no backstory.
There's nothing to talk about other than pictures
and maybe the songs that they sing in a restaurant.
Because we have thought about these things
for longer than the people who invented them,
who invented the mythology.
Because often this was some author or copywriter
who was just like, I don't know, scribble something down.
But the tossed off nature of the mythology
that it's half committed to, I think,
is what makes it so fun.
Like how a little of a shred of any actual info
we have to go off of.
You gotta use your imagination.
Fill in the blanks.
That's the fun of it.
And anything, anything.
And because we're taking the time and thinking about it,
you know, why can't what we say be canon?
I say it is canon.
It is now.
Sure.
A lot of canon will be made here.
All podcasts are canon.
We're building a whole new universe of mythology.
All of us together.
That is, that's a thing we've talked about off mic before
that every now and then someone will go like,
oh, you gotta have this person on.
I bet they're gonna have this person on for this topic.
And we're like, we didn't know that person
is obsessed with X topic.
We just know them as a person we know.
Or don't know.
Or possibly don't know.
That's a funny thing because we have had some guests
who are on a bunch of other podcasts.
So we are plugged into some of the podcast
industrial network, but complex rather.
That's what I meant to say.
Podcast industrial complex.
That's the name of the mythology.
But there's a lot of folks we don't know.
Sure.
A podcast elder statesman.
And that's the thing we need your help on.
If you're a frequent podcast listener
and we have failed to have a guest on
who has asserted themselves on some podcasts
we've never heard as a big theme park guy
or even a slight theme park guy, let us know.
We'll try to get to hold of them.
That's a bold claim that we're gonna do that.
That seems like a little- Also, you're really opening
the floodgates.
That was not my intent.
I'm not saying that.
Yeah, Joe, we're gonna end up with Terry Gross.
If she ever said- Well, that's fine.
If she enjoyed a ride or something.
That would be a coup if we got Terry Gross.
It certainly would.
But I wouldn't feel comfortable making the ask
unless in some deep, fresh air she referred to enjoying,
I don't know, the-
Tilt-a-whirl.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The primeval tilt-a-whirl.
I'm just saying like just a regular tilt-a-whirl.
Just any tilt-a-whirl.
And she'll come on to talk about the tilt-a-whirl.
Because she seems like she might not like
the corporate stuff as much,
but she loves an old-fashioned fare or something like that.
And then she just kind of quietly speaks
about the tilt-a-whirl and what fun it was.
If we could do- Spinning around and round.
If we could do tilt-a-whirl, the episode tilt-a-whirls.
That actually is a very gross.
That is a pretty good idea.
But we're making a lot of leaps to say
that that could happen.
But oh, but maybe I shouldn't say that.
Maybe I should just be confident and commit.
With your Patreon pledges, you make it more possible
every day that we will do the episode
tilt-a-whirls with Terry Gross.
That's a podcast, The Right Promise.
Which is to say made up.
Here's something we, this is a type of episode
that I'd like to propose and talk about a little bit.
This is something I wanna do within the Patreon.
A type of episode called Lost and Found.
I've talked to you about this,
you guys about this a little bit.
But here's what I'm thinking.
Every, I want by the end of this whole podcast,
The Right Journey, that we have covered every square inch
of anything that is currently or has ever been
at a theme park.
And we've talked about a lot so far.
But I do feel things have slipped through the cracks.
Even in attractions and places that we have covered.
And that is why in a Lost and Found episode,
I want the listeners to write us and say,
is there a topic or a ride that we've covered already
that we missed something big about?
If there was a coaster at Kennywood or a slide
at Schlitterbahn or if you just think we didn't
spend enough time talking about,
if there's a Dilophosaurus you're really fond of
on the Jurassic Park ride or something,
please just write us and let us know.
Podcasts are at a Gmail with the subject line,
Lost and Found.
But what I'm proposing basically is just
revisiting prior topics to make sure we covered
every inch of it, got it all totally covered.
Here's an example of the kind of thing.
We just finished the City Walk saga.
And during the City Walk saga, it was too late
to address this because we'd recorded all of them.
But somebody wrote us on Twitter to let us know
that several episodes of the television series Sliders
had been shot at City Walk.
And they gave us the episode names and descriptions
and stills and they used the universal starway
to as a, the starway played in the episode,
the big escalators universal, they played as like
escalators going all the way up to the sky
to a cloud mall in the sky, which City Walk stood in for.
They used the Jody Maroney's.
This was all news to me.
I didn't know about any of this and we couldn't cover it
in the saga.
That's the kind of thing we can talk about
in the Lost and Found.
But we need you, the audience, to let us know what we lost.
Someone sent us a report that they had seen Prince perform
at City Walk.
We obviously didn't know that happened.
So like that, we would have talked about that for an hour.
That's exactly the kind of thing.
So anything like that, that's been,
if this has been burning a hole in your brain,
they talked about Knott's Berry Farm, but they missed when.
Well, we missed a lot of Knott's.
Oh yeah, yeah, no, that would not.
I'm sure like that we covered it all in a single episode.
Nine more Knott's episodes.
But if you're aware that there was like a,
who was like a super conservative, you know,
like if Spiro Agnew held a campaign rally
that turned violent in the 60s at Knott's Berry Farm
and you were there and you know stuff about it
and you have photos, write us.
We'll put it in the Lost and Found.
You do the legwork for these episodes
that you are also paying for.
I was gonna say.
We're gonna do the legwork.
I just want the prompts.
I want like the. Oh, I see.
Give us a shred of info and then we'll go do our research.
We'll find out about stuff.
And I would just feel terrible if we, there's,
if we know somebody's yelling at their iPhone
during the Astroworld episode about, you know,
friend of Marvel McPhaze, we failed the name check.
Oh my God, we need to know that.
Let me just, this is bad podcasting,
but let me throw it back to that joke pitch.
Lee Atwater is the sheriff in Ghost Town.
If that happens. Pretty good.
Pretty good. Pretty good, right?
I like that. Yeah, that's good with me.
Anyway, back to what you were gonna say.
Oh, I was gonna say,
I think that's a fitting lead in to today's topic.
Absolutely. Because this is a,
an area of, well, I don't know.
It is documented,
but I felt like I hit a city limits at a certain point
in researching this.
There's stuff I would like to know more about
that I never will because it's been bulldozed.
Yeah. Can I tell you what,
just my reaction is what you're saying,
what happened to me after doing some research.
I had a visceral reaction to this place
and I started to feel it by the end
of looking at all these photos.
What I, the note that I wrote down is that
I think that tonight I will have nightmares
that are full of limited polygons.
That is how I will dream tonight.
I will dream as if I am watching a,
a pre-PlayStation 2 video game all night.
The graphics then aren't even as good
as that cartoon reboot.
Yeah, no, no.
Because reboot is finished and rendered and shaded.
Reboot is great.
No, all of these attractions are,
look, but you have to cut them some slack.
They were, you know,
these things were having to render in real time
in one review. Right.
But you, there's less slack to be cut
because this attraction was open until 2017.
And we're still looking at 1998 graphics.
19 years, baby.
And, God, wow.
Well, and, and just to say it,
you know it because you're,
you're staring at the file right now.
We are talking about Disney Quest.
But let me put this on, on you guys.
I'm going to put you to the test.
I like to, even though I think probably behind the,
with the, with the Patreon episodes,
we're getting a lot of people who don't need Disney Quest
explained to them.
However, if you had to explain Disney Quest
to someone who didn't know what Disney Quest was,
how would you even begin?
Sure. I'll take the lead on this.
I would describe it as an indoor interactive theme park.
That's exactly right.
That's how any reasonable person would describe it.
And that's a very reasonable choice.
Michael, do you have an objection to that?
Well, I was going to say you might be,
that sounds like company speak to me.
Are you saying that because it's the first item in my notes
and it's in quotation marks?
Yeah. I have it too, Jason.
I have the same thing.
I was right.
I listened to like a,
I think probably the president of Disney
regional entertainment explain what this thing was.
I'm calling this shot now,
Disney regional entertainment episode.
Oh, just the whole thing.
Just the whole thing.
Well, they only had three enterprises, right?
Yes.
I guess, I guess we can just break up the enterprises,
but this, I feel like-
Although I'd be more than happy to hit them in two birds
with one stone and to cover what it's ESPN zone
and club Disney.
Disney's Chuck E. Cheese.
I think I said Disney play,
which is the new streaming service that's coming soon.
Sorry.
Club Disney.
How dare you not keep this corporate speak
and you're straight in your brain.
We'll do Disney play when it launches
and it'll be a lot of us going, oh.
When I read about this Disney Quest,
I was so excited.
I couldn't have been more excited because in my mind,
the easiest way to describe it was it's Disney,
but it's all virtual reality games.
That's, and to me at the time,
I was very excited about that.
Like when you first heard about it.
When I first heard about it and it was,
it seemed very simple in concept to me as a kid.
Sure.
It was virtual reality, but it was Disney.
I feel like I'm jealous that you got that breakdown.
I feel like I learned about it for the first time
being at Downtown Disney where it was built.
And I don't think, I remember asking people
and them saying, yeah, it's kind of this indoor.
It's like video games, but it's bigger than that.
It's not a nose in arcade.
No, it's more complicated than that.
Like I don't think I understood what it was
until I got into the building.
And still, I don't know if I understood.
And then having to explain to my dad
why we needed to go in there, I don't think he got it.
And I don't think he lasted more than an hour.
Can I ask, so who here went to Disney Quest?
I did. You did?
Me.
Oh, so I'm the only one who never did.
I never went to Disney Quest.
And I knew all about it,
because 1998 was like the height of my family's
vacation club membership.
So we got mailings about every,
because for whatever reason, in the late 90s,
they were pushing stuff not in the parks.
They were pushing La Nuba,
they were pushing Downtown Disney real big,
and they were pushing Disney Quest.
And I think we just never went because
we were probably already spending enough money.
And then I think also we kind of came to the consensus of
like, we kind of do Downtown Disney in like half a day.
Do we want to give up another half a day in the parks?
I was adamant that we were going to Disney Quest.
We went the opening summer.
I read about it probably in a Disney,
man, I don't know if we were still doing Disney Adventure
at that point, but I read about it somewhere.
I was obsessed.
I love virtual reality.
That virtual boy that I did not,
my parents would not buy me,
but anytime I played it, even though it sucked,
I was like, this is pretty good.
Like, do you guys ever play virtual boy?
You were trying to like it.
I never got a seizure, so that's good news.
Yeah, I did not get a seizure though.
I did, as we'll find out,
it was not pleased with what happened to me at Disney Quest.
Oh boy.
What a tease.
Yeah, so I was obsessed with it.
I was obsessed with like,
this reminds me of the time in my life
when I was obsessed with like going inside the computer.
There was a UPN show called Deadly Games that I loved
that has Christopher Lloyd starring
as a character named Sebastian Jackle.
Well, I like that already.
I loved any Christopher Lloyd stuff.
And it was a UPN show about Brent Spiner,
who was data on Star Trek was on it
as like this like wacky jokery kind of like guy,
but it was all like, you're going inside the computer.
And I was for some reason obsessed with that idea.
So when Disney Quest came out, I was like virtual reality
and I made it, I was like telling my parent,
like we gotta go, we gotta do this.
And on the last day of our trip in 98, we did it.
Oh man, you fucked up.
I was so excited.
This is like just as excited for maybe more
in anticipation of this than Tower of Terror,
Rock and Roller Coaster, any of the big rides
I got to go on later.
Like that we were like going down
to see what the new thing was.
You built this up as big in your brain as possible,
which is certainly not the set up to any sort of.
No, yeah.
The end of the story will be that you loved it very much.
Yeah.
I feel like we may have missed a little bit
of fundamentals about this.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, June, 1998, I believe was the opening.
We have previously talked about Pleasure Island,
which is this.
So in the 70s, there's this Disney Village marketplace
that opens up, but it's kind of separate
from the theme parks at Disney World.
Just like mellow little shopping zone.
They add the hip 80s nightlife to that zone
with Pleasure Island in 87,
and then they keep expanding it
and rename the whole area Downtown Disney.
And as part of that rebrand in 1998,
they opened the West Side.
The West Side, baby.
We're talking Virgin Megastore.
We're talking Disney Quest.
We're talking an original Cirque du Soleil production
called La Nuba in a brand new arena built just for La Nuba.
Have you seen La Nuba?
I did not see La Nuba.
I did not see.
My dad always wanted to see La Nuba.
We always wanted to see Cirque du Soleil down there.
And again, we were just like, but that's a night.
We're not going out to dinner or going to the parks.
And I think we just never got it together.
My mom also very thrifty.
I think that's why I kind of gave up on virtual reality
at one point, because I like,
I'm going to have to fight to get money for the,
I'm going to have to argue to get money
for virtual reality stuff.
Free up the funds.
To, yes, free up the funds.
Give a little like PowerPoint presentation
showing why this is a good investment.
I'd like to use your money wisely, mother.
And let me explain why.
And I knew it would be a less than satisfying experience
for me because of one thing, baby, glasses.
Glass, a little kid with big glasses,
virtual reality helmets, not exactly.
Even the void, the void was pretty good.
The void had the best headset for glass.
I think they're a little better design nowadays.
And although maybe I would have had a better luck
at Disney Quest because they had some pretty innovative
for the time kind of VR headsets.
You're like, evening at the improv style,
the standup set about like the perils of wearing glasses
under VR.
I just remember.
Where my dude's at, who are trying to fit glasses
under a VR helmet.
I remember trying to do it at, and I talked about this.
I, on another episode at Funscape,
which for this episode, I went back,
I did find proof that Funscape existed.
This was the family entertainment.
I thought you were a liar.
Play zone.
I swear you were making this up.
I mean, it did feel like you were.
Funscape does feel like a fake name.
It does feel like a fake name.
Turns out it was not just connected to Regal.
Regal Cinemas was an endeavor that they funded
as like these entertainment centers in Wilmington, Delaware,
Fort Lauderdale, Rochester, New York.
And there were these giant centers and they lasted
about as long as the Chicago Disney Quest,
which is to say two to three years.
Which I never went to.
Which you never went to.
That's odd.
That's very odd.
Because I'm from there.
You know, my father-in-law, a Regal executive.
Really?
In that era.
And he's never opened up about Funscape.
He's never talked about Funscape?
I need to, I bet he has no idea what that is.
Yeah.
Probably a different division.
But I did find out that Wilmington, Delaware one,
which may have been the biggest judging from it,
did introduce stadium seating in movie theaters
to the state of Delaware.
Wait, not to America?
Not to America.
To Delaware only.
To Delaware.
Or at least a region.
There was a lot of buildup.
That was the first place I remember stadium seating.
A little puff of fart at the end.
Yeah, kind of.
To Delaware.
To Delaware, yeah.
They all had to sit on a level.
Just a lot of smaller, kind of jankier theaters
or beat up AMCs, a number of which are still in business
and remain pretty beat up.
But Regals were always nicer.
Once they started coming to my area,
Regals were usually nicer than AMCs.
I would love to delve into various movie theater locations
and our feelings about the brands
and which who had the best videos that played before.
We talk about, is his name Front Row Joe?
The, who I believe is the Cinemark mascot.
I think that's, he's kind of a Texas character.
So I didn't grow up with him,
but I know about Front Row Joe,
which is a weird name to give a big movie fan character
because why would you willingly happily sit
in the front row?
No, I sat in the front row for the first Avengers movie
and it was one of the most uncomfortable
movie going experiences of my life.
I sat in front row for Mission Impossible 2.
Did you?
Yeah, not great.
Yeah.
Not a great experience.
It's very extreme.
Never great.
I would, I'll just, I'd leave the film before I think
I'd sit through that.
So more episodes coming down the pipe.
We'll hand, let's get into the arguments of Regal versus.
Yeah.
This is connected enough to think about world.
A world history of the fundscape endeavor.
That Regal was also bankrupt and,
or it caused them to go through bankruptcy proceedings.
I forget which, but yeah, it wasn't a good call.
Apparently the go-karts would rattle the building.
Also indoor go-karts,
you gotta really make sure your ventilation is good.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Gas is not, that shouldn't be in the atmosphere.
There's one here like over by the airport in Burbank
in like a giant old warehouse and it's just the go-karts
and they had to redo the building
to make sure it ventilated and.
How do you know so much about this?
I mean, you can kind of see it,
but it's also, it's just go-karts.
Have you done it though?
I have done it.
Oh, okay.
It's crazy.
You can get up to like 35 miles per hour in there.
Really?
Yeah.
Should we do it?
Should we review this on the Patreon too?
Potentially.
Is that a theme park?
Burbank local go-kart attraction.
Local go-karts.
Actually just the episode title,
go-kart, indoor go-kart ventilation with Jason Sheridan.
I'll put you in there as the guest.
You will like elevate you above most for that episode.
Also, maybe I'm giving them too much credit
cause also they were trying to add laser tag
and we're doing a Kickstarter campaign to add laser tag.
So that's not a great.
No, not a great sign.
Vote of business confidence.
Can I add one more, I'll make another problem.
We're making a lot of promises about the Patreon.
If we get to a certain amount
where we're like doing very well,
we will go out in the desert and review that
racing cars bachelor party I took
where we all drive cars very fast
to like 125 miles an hour on a track
with two other maniacs.
Oh, I would consider that.
So let's all do that too.
Goes, oh, that's another thing
that Disney was pushing in the nineties,
the wide world of sports.
I'm sure it was a similar.
It was a similar thing to this.
So well, except so they're famously
one of the incidents of the wide world of sports.
Someone died in the race car there.
The reason being they weren't going the wrong way
on the track.
The track had been designed to drive either clockwise
or counterclockwise and they had been running the cars
the wrong way for a while, I guess.
I don't know this.
We got it.
We got into the whole thing.
All right.
Anyway, I brought up Funscape
because that is my first memory of doing like a,
like $5, $10 VR thing.
And then go and like, yeah, glasses will fit.
Having to put this headset on and like squinting
while doing V of like zapping, yeah, polygons.
You've never had an experience to your liking fully.
No, not, not really.
Maybe not until the void.
That was better.
Even, even as a glasses.
The void I thought was very good.
They've done a much better job lately.
Like with just 3D glasses in general,
even if it's not virtual reality,
cause Lindsay hates all 3D things.
But then Flight of Passage was great,
which is the Orlando Avatar ride.
So that, like that worked perfectly.
And then we did VR in Japan and they make enough room now
for glasses for most of these different places.
So, and she loved that stuff.
Not all of it.
So there was a time when Flight of Passage was,
Flight of Passage was open at the same time as
Disney Quest. This building full of 1998, you know,
watching a like, you know, a video game rendered
like Sultan's Guard in an Aladdin ride.
Oh. You could go,
you could do both of these experiences.
Graphics. A couple hours.
Your phone.
You could play higher graphic games on your phone.
Kids were probably sick of it.
And it's like, hey, we gotta hang out here for another hour.
This is playing Fortnite on their phone.
How many Disney quests?
How many like tricked parents over the years
where they were not on Disney and somebody was like,
like, oh, Disney Quest is down there and they walked in
and they paid their money upfront and then they were stuck.
Like they were like, oh shit.
Like this is what it was.
That was my term.
My dad wanted out of there as quick as possible.
And I didn't necessarily argue with him.
I think my dad, now that I think about it,
didn't even go in.
Good call.
I think he stayed out and hung around.
I could be wrong about, I have to check.
What fun is a dad gonna have?
Also the video games are hard to play.
I think my dad would have enjoyed it
and my mom would have done like the jungle,
the paddling one or one of the,
yeah, we did the paddling one.
And then she would have pulled a paperback book
out of her purse and found a well lit spot,
which is not easy, I feel like, in the videos of this.
Dude, depressing, I might even say,
like atmosphere and lighting.
Well, just dark.
It's like a children's entertainment center
and it's so dark.
Really claustrophobic.
So okay, if you were at the Downtown Disney West Side
starting in 1998, there's a lot of,
I like that skyline when you're looking over,
when you're looking at maps
or like the hotel informational videos
and you're sweeping over this skyline
that has the big globe of the planet Hollywood
and the big pineapple of the bongos, Cuban cafe
and the tent of Cirque du Soleil
and then the centerpiece of it all, a big blue box,
which is Disney Quest.
A big windowless building.
So yeah, what this was was a,
it's a five story windowless building
that is covered, that is full of video games,
but also kind of more fleshed out VR experiences.
And the idea was to use this starting location
as a way to do, okay, look, building an entire theme park
at various spots in America is pretty cost prohibitive
for Disney at this point.
And they can't exactly go build a Disneyland
outside of Chicago or Philadelphia or any of these places,
but what they can do potentially is go into a city center,
take over some space and do kind of a more compact
indoor theme park experience.
So they opened Disney Quest in Orlando
with the intent of opening it up in different cities
across America.
And across the world, I think,
because specifically they wanted to open 20 to 30 of these
within 10 years.
Eisner's talking about in that,
there's an opening video from Chicago
and he's talking about what Philadelphia was next
on their plan.
So Philadelphia, they broke ground on.
Right, yeah, yeah.
They were doing construction at Athe and Market,
like right in Center City, Philadelphia.
What blew my mind is that I didn't know,
I don't know Philadelphia very well,
so the fact that it is like,
it is a five minute walk away from the Liberty Bell.
From all of it, Independence Hall,
yeah, the Liberty Bell, the Convention Center,
the Reading Terminal Market,
which is sort of like Grand Central Market in LA.
And it's right next to a regional transit hub,
trains, subway trains, regional trains.
There's a Greyhound station in that area,
so like high traffic area.
And still a parking lot,
still they started construction
and then they stopped when the Chicago one failed.
They dug a hole.
Yeah.
That was going to be the basis
for this five story video game place
and didn't get past the hole.
And the hole was there for many, many years
and was referred to as the Disney Hole.
It has now been paved over and is a parking lot.
It's a parking lot.
But there's supposed to be apartment towers
being built in the Market East neighborhood
that they call this.
I don't know if it's going on top of that,
but that would seemingly make the right place.
Building towers in cities takes years.
Disney doesn't own the land still, do they?
I don't think so.
I don't think so, no.
Or they never maybe owned it.
They were just gonna.
But you know the idea there, so yeah,
so as I said, the first one opened in Orlando in 98,
followed by Chicago in 99, I believe.
Yeah, in June 99.
And then they were going to open Philadelphia in 2000
and they were trying to get this location open
in time for the Republican National Convention.
Yes, the Republican National Convention.
For the event at which George W. Bush
was confirmed as the Republican nominee
and the gates of hell opened.
Oh yeah.
All of these people were all going to,
Strom Thurmond was gonna be hanging out at Disney Quest.
He was gonna be strapping on a helmet.
He was gonna be designing his own roller coaster.
Oh yeah, Dick Shady.
Dick Shady exploring, riding the comics.
Riding the comics.
My memory of the Republican Convention in Philadelphia
is that I wasn't there.
I was at Boy Scout camp for the week.
Why would you?
I'm sure you would have been there.
Were you invited?
No, but I remember being very mad
because I was like. You wanted to go?
No, I wanted to watch the Daily Show
without the Republican Convention.
So I made my dad take the Daily Show all week
and he was like, yeah, I went down.
At the time, you could just walk around the convention.
He was like, yeah, I went down.
I walked around.
Whatever.
You're sure your dad went to the Republican National Convention
and hung around?
Yeah, because you could just do that back then, I guess.
Before 9-11, you could just walk through.
Or they had like, maybe they had an area,
the visitor center area or something set up for it.
But he like went around and walked around.
I think he bought a companion.
But you were very much a, you were very much a liberal.
No, none of us were like jazz for George W. Bush.
So he was going to be like,
I'm going to check out the opposition
just because it was a historical moment in the city.
I don't really know how either of my parents
felt about George W. Bush.
I think pretty quickly we're like, oh, this guy's an idiot.
Yeah, it was a thing to do because me and my brother
were out of town.
So it was like it was a thing.
As if a fair rolled into town.
He'd be like, go check out that fair over there.
Oh, there's a bunch of evil people in a convention center.
Go check out the evil people in the convention center.
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
I mean, I guess it was close.
I guess it was in the Burbank.
It was over here in the Burbank Hotel.
I'd go check out the Republican National Convention.
Yeah, I think they were like at the time,
I think people really didn't give a shit about politics.
And it was just kind of like, oh, look,
it's something to do.
It was a different time, you're right.
Yeah.
So the Disney Quest.
The Disney Quest, yeah.
That's the thing we were talking about.
The, okay, so first things first, as we said,
big, tall, it's essentially just a blue box.
There is the big words Disney Quest on it.
And there's kind of Mickey ears,
but done kind of a little more,
little more hip, a little bit.
It's like a big scribble.
And that's the only decor on the outside of this thing.
Otherwise it is such a kind of murky, unpleasant behemoth.
I find that building to be hideous.
And to me, Disney Quest typifies
what I'm going to call the Disney 90s aesthetic dive.
In the 80s, especially Epcot Center,
I think Disney was like leading the charge of cool design
and stuff that I think still is neat
and what people's vision of the future is.
And then you start around the 90s.
I mean, I think a lot of design got shitty in the 90s,
but this entire place and all the signage within it,
it just reminds me of,
I remember my yearbooks around that time.
Oh yeah.
Starting to become this weird where everything's
in lowercase for no reason.
And every letter is in a different font
and a different color and things are scribbly.
And an O is a CD.
And Disney starts getting into this kind of thing.
And I think in the lead up you have
when they switched from Epcot,
which was sleek and cool and I'm biased
because I love that aesthetic so much.
But when it became Epcot 94
and all the signage got you.
And in inventions, I find really aesthetically unpleasant.
Yeah.
Oh, I loved all of this shit as a kid.
Really, really?
Well, as a kid I did.
But I see that it looks gaudy as shit now.
It is not aged super well.
I regret not going to Disney Quest a couple of times
the last few years that I was in Florida.
I was like, oh, I could have still gone.
It's crazy, I couldn't wrap my head around
that it was still there until last year.
Really strange.
It seems like such a product of its time.
And it would have been exactly what I liked at the time.
And it is a way, I mean, there's a lot of things.
There's corners of Epcot Center
that haven't changed since 82
and it's a little time travel you get to do.
But especially that in 2017,
you could have really literally taken a leap into 1998
and some of the worst aesthetic indulgences,
the exact same computer technology
that was powering everything in 98.
You see just compact computers.
Oh yeah.
It's so out of date and they made no effort to keep it up.
And aesthetics are a big part of that.
I hate every sign that I saw delving into all this stuff.
There's like 12 circles in the queue,
the Disney Quest queue.
It's like this like just squiggly circle
and his ears are squiggly circles.
And it's like, ugh.
You know what's another aesthetic
I wanna bring up really fast?
Do you remember when ABC switched to that yellow,
the black on yellow?
This isn't something that struck you or didn't bother you.
They were all, I mean, I just like.
Let me look.
There was this particular campaign they did around like 96,
97 when they would have been promoting like two guys,
a girl in a pizza place and these kinds of shots.
I just, I find it like hideous.
Look at maybe see yellow.
That might give it to you.
That's the one now.
Oh yeah.
And that's fairly clear.
It was just like bad.
I don't know why everything became like hideous,
scratchy fonts and all lowercase with a lot of attitude.
Yeah, you're in that neck of the woods.
Anyway, I don't.
Something like that.
I'll post what I'm talking about.
I just remember seeing these awful ABC posters
starting to go up around Disneyland.
Aesthetics just got so off.
Red Rockets pizza port.
That's an aesthetic nightmare.
Yeah.
All of Tomorrowland 98 in general.
I just don't know what happened.
Everything just got so sloppy and like kooky
and in your face.
I mean, the city walk Lego is kind of an example of that too.
So like the map, the map of Disney Quest.
That's pretty icky.
Yes, what you're showing me right there is pretty icky.
And the score zone, the replay zone,
the create zone and food quest.
Food Quest is my favorite.
Like there's no way the food quest was good.
What a lazy.
Food Quest is so lazy.
I, god, there's so much.
This is a lot.
I loved the research for this.
It reminded me of researching for Hard Rock Park
where I would just peel back one layer of the onion.
Yeah, this might be.
And find a new layer of the onion.
This might not be the only Disney Quest.
Yeah, we might not get to.
Well, but here to keep us on track
and to help us get through it all is the zone keeper.
All right, I'm gonna.
No, absolutely not.
I think we could use that.
I think that's the only way.
I think we need somebody to guide us through this.
Okay, so let me, then let's take it a little orderly.
Let's at least, you know, once you're inside Disney Quest,
you can go to any of the four zones that you want.
But the first, but to get in,
there's an experience that you have to have.
You have to walk in to this rotunda.
And I'm looking at this photo.
When I talk about crazy,
I actually don't mind this that much.
I'm looking at a room that is a bunch of gold pillars
that have gold busts of Disney characters,
all your favorite characters, like, you know,
Pinocchio, Pocahontas, and one of the Mighty Ducks
from the 90s Mighty Ducks cartoon.
And then there's a black and white zebra striped ring
above that that shows a fake indoor sky rotunda,
like the Caesar's Palace Mall.
And then around the ring,
it says the full word supercalifragilistic ex-fialidocious.
The vibe of this room is extremely 90s cyber lawnmower man
disclosure.
This is a 90s ass endeavor.
All of this is a 90s ass endeavor.
It feels like you were, especially this room,
it feels like you were entering a CD-ROM
and walking around a CD-ROM.
Any listeners who are into that CD-ROM aesthetic,
please look up some Disney Quest photos.
You won't be disappointed.
I remember going into, like, this may be,
maybe I'm misremembering or I'm trying to, like,
act like I knew what I was doing,
or act like I knew something was good or not
by just seeing it.
But I remember walking into there and knowing,
feeling, it didn't feel good to me.
I just remember the feeling of the place.
It immediately let me down a little bit.
There was no way I would express that when I was that age,
but I do remember the feeling that I did not have on,
as this is like Tower of Terror, all that stuff.
You would see the building go,
oh my God, this looks great.
There was a vibe in there from the start
that you are not going to like this.
You feel like you're walking into some weird sex club
or something. Yes.
It's something shady, for sure.
It's like, there's a cheapness to it.
Absolutely.
I bet there was a big old-lunch crunch
during the building of this thing.
Because even if you're not a nerd for this,
you can feel when something's cheap.
Have you guys seen, there was a rendering of the,
what the outdoor, what the exterior of DisneyQuest
was going to look like that is a lot more impressive
than what it ended up being,
which is kind of like four walls,
sorta painted on and scribbled on.
But the concept art was so much better.
And I think there's a lot of things in DisneyQuest
on the inside as well that, with infinite budget,
could have been cool as hell,
but I bet it got stepped down.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here's my thing.
I know aesthetically, a lot of this is not great design,
but I associate it with a very happy childhood.
And happy, I have a hard time untangling, like-
But you never went.
I never went, but I liked the brochures about it.
In your head, it's like the blue sky version of it.
And you'll never get to go there, so you can imagine-
But also, I mean, that's kind of an appeal
of Hard Rock Park, too.
You know what this reminds me of now to think about?
This whole aesthetic reminds me of when they introduced
those Pop Tarts that had the blue and purple frosting on them.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Like just the like-
Oh yes, the Wild Berry?
Thank you, Wild Berry Pop Tarts, which I do like,
but it's an ugly look.
It doesn't look attract, it doesn't look appealing.
It looks like it's for-
I think part of it, too, is, and Mike,
I know you will get this,
and it actually comes up in DisneyQuest,
but when digital coloring really started to catch on in comics-
Like when you saw the change from like the dots,
the colored dots where you'd have to lay on,
I honestly don't know how they-
It's still very confusing to me how they used to color comics.
But in the way that it was brighter and more pastel-y,
and then it just got a lot more sleek.
And you're saying you're comparing this how to DisneyQuest?
That trend in the 90s runs concurrent with this trend
of everything getting digitally colored
or digitally designed, like all of that.
And I think a lot of things have,
like obviously most things are done digitally these days,
and I think people have figured out
cool aesthetics within that.
But I think what DisneyQuest in general suffers from
is the awkward slide into digital,
and especially Disney having no idea
how to play it or work within that.
Because you used to just have like red, what was it?
Black, yellow, red, blue.
And that's how you would color the newspaper comics.
And you could combine them to make greens
and purples and stuff, but you were limited.
I will say, I feel like there was a,
people loved teal and purple specifically.
I don't know why those colors seem like in the late 90s.
GameCube was purple in 2001, which I guess is now 90s,
but around that same time.
Tomorrowland 94.
I know what you're saying is as far as just like
the colors of it, it does feel like of a time.
And it's not that I hate the color scheme of it,
but when you look at the pictures inside,
I remember feeling just let down, I felt sad.
It was very dark, it was very, well here, let's get inside.
But how do we get inside, guys?
We're on the bottom floor, how do we get up to the top?
Is there a special type of device that would take you up
to the top floor? Is there like a fucking
cyberlater, do they got a cyberlater?
Oh, do they have a cyberlater?
They have a cyberlater?
Wait, it wasn't just a regular elevator,
it was like a, it was a full on cyberlater.
It was a full cyberlater, yeah.
Seeing the sign, cyberlater, cyberlater,
cyberlater two venture port is what the sign says.
Cyberlater for sure has to have appeared on Deadly Games
as a villain or something, like that seems like such a cheap
name. Oh, a man named the cyberlater?
Yeah, like a bad game, cyberlater played by, you know,
I was gonna say Jean-Claude Van Damme,
but that's, they didn't have the money for him in the 90s.
Robert Davi. Okay.
I forget who he is, but he was in a,
he was an 80s actor who was in a Funny or Die video once
who was very mean and very bad to the women
and promoted his, relentlessly promoted his
Davi Singh Sinatra album.
All right, Robert Davi played cyberlater on the UPN show
Deadly Games starring Christopher Loy as Sebastian Jackal.
That's a fact, that's canon now.
Yep, yeah, as far as I know.
So you get into the cyberlater, which even once you're inside
still feels like a regular elevator and you're looking at a
mirror of yourself.
Yeah, it's me, what's, I see me all the time,
what's the big deal?
Then the doors close, the lights short out and you are gone.
You are in pure black and replay it, the mirror is replaced
with a big animated digital presentation starring the Genie.
Our friend, the Genie. From Aladdin.
Who of course famously is voiced by beloved comedian.
Dan Castellana.
Who although a lot of the articles and videos about
Disney Quest fail to acknowledge it is not Robin Williams.
For sure you can listen, Dan Castellana, the voice of Homer
was the alternate Robin Williams in all of the other things,
Return of Jafar.
But not the third one where he returned.
Oh, he came back.
He sorted out his Disney issues, which is why he's also
the timekeeper in whatever that was called.
Why is that not coming to me?
Oh boy, I'm losing it.
I know what you're talking about.
The visionary or something.
Something like that.
Sure, the cypher later.
So a little thing and he impersonates,
he does all his Genie hijinks and then lets you out.
He does Mo, he does Barney Gumbel,
he does all the impressions that we know the Genie loves to do.
And then you land.
I said Mo by the way, that's Castellana.
I screwed up that's Anka's area.
Oh right.
Barney is Castellana.
Strike it from the dad is not canon.
Grandpa.
See, yes, there you go.
So you arrive at Ventureport and you walk into another
big rotunda that has a big telescope or something.
Here's something I want to say.
A lot of, especially people were tweeting this at us,
I think earlier in the year when this was going around,
there was a fantastic Twitter thread explaining Disney Quest
beat by beat done by a real video game expert named
Max Krieger.
And his Twitter handle is at MaxKriegerVG.
And I think it just Googled Disney Quest Twitter thread
and it's excellent and it breaks down a lot of this stuff
in a very concise way that doesn't take two and a half hours.
It's a really good Twitter thread.
But I do disagree with him on one point,
which I think he's maybe more into this place aesthetically
than me and he shows a picture of the Ventureport
and it says,
guests would disembark at the heart of this massive
five floor complex Ventureport.
It was breathtaking all caps.
What?
Full of design flourishes often overlooked.
I don't know.
I'm gonna show you guys a photo.
Does this take your breath away?
Do you still have breath?
That's a picture.
Okay, so I was looking at the picture of this
and then the picture, I go, that's okay.
I don't hate that.
No, that's like interventions.
But it's like interventions.
And I have no memory of being wowed.
I didn't walk in and go, now I've arrived at Disney Quest.
I remember just like being not being able to see it.
It's not lit.
I feel like that is just a well lit photo of it too.
Yeah.
My memory of it is like, it was much murkier.
All of this was a dark place.
It was so dark.
It was bizarre.
This is depressing and scary.
I think the Ventureport is good.
But you, it's not a great experience.
But I've only experienced these well lit pictures.
In theory, the Cyberlator is a magical elevator.
That's true.
In theory, the Ventureport is unbelievable.
The Walt Disney Family Museum has a great themed elevator.
And I don't wanna tip it.
But it's not a Cyberlator.
It's not a Cyberlator, but it's a very cool experience.
Pretty disappointing.
I'll say this, I think I'm a sucker for color delighting.
Sure, who isn't?
Yeah, I know all the videos,
but all the walkthroughs of Disney Quest,
I'm like, do you like how much colored lighting is in here?
But there's a whole course of darkness.
It was not enough light.
It is so much, I think it is so much like
Disneyland interventions.
And they opened around the same time.
I think that's some of my problem with it.
I actually, Disney World interventions,
I'm more okay with.
It's kind of kooky or more open air.
The attractions I remember and enjoy.
Still, this is the only other thing I can remember
from going to Disney World that I was very let down by
was interventions.
Because I remember reading all about interventions,
so excited about it.
And you get down there and it's like,
you can play Sonic the Hedgehog.
Yeah, but there's a lot of them.
There were so many.
You loved interventions in Florida.
I loved those free video games, I sure did.
Here's another weird Disney Quest thing.
This is a quote from the Orlando Sentinel.
Each year, 20% to 30% of Disney Quest attractions
will be replaced with something new.
So that was never going to fucking happen.
Never, and whenever Disney says that, it is a trap.
It is not.
There will never be the change of order.
Except it's only happened with the new Star Tours.
Sure, because that is a high profile.
That's true.
There's multiple properties.
There's a lot of financial incentive, I feel,
to keep updating that.
But why would they change up interventions every year?
Plus, the Illuminati's given them extra funding
to get the multiculturalism in there.
Because of Star Wars?
Because of Star Wars.
It's all propaganda now.
I'm worried Russian bots are gonna hack
Star Tours at some point.
They're the ones that are sending us off
on that horrible collision course
with the evil First Order and Crait.
That's true.
Hey, did you guys know they did a study
and 51% of people who did not like the City Walk saga
turned out to be Russian bots.
I had a feeling.
I had a feeling, yeah.
Because what reasonable American would not have loved
every step of that.
So we've now arrived at Ventureport,
and it's in our hands.
We can go wherever we want.
We can go to the replay zone.
We can go to the score zone.
We can go to the create zone.
We can go to the explore zone.
Those are all completely different,
as different as Tomorrowland and Frontierland.
Very clear delineations.
So, I don't know, guys, where do you wanna go?
Pick a zone.
Well, I think when you have five levels of entertainment
and four worlds without limits, it's hard to choose.
It's hard to choose.
So already, yeah, that is a helpful thing to remember.
So it's five levels, but four.
Five levels, four zones.
And the Cyberlator's not one of the zones.
That just gets you to the Ventureport.
Did the Cyberlator would take you to the fifth,
to the score zone first, right?
Well, no, it would take you to the third.
It would take you into the middle of the bay.
It would, is that right?
Yes.
And it's a 45 second elevator line
that takes you from floor one to, well, floor three.
Oh, you're right, you're right.
It's the world's slowest elevator.
Well, you wanna go to the fifth floor
if you got hungry for FoodQuest.
I might just kill it.
Okay, let's just go to FoodQuest.
Yeah.
So why wouldn't you start on four?
I don't know.
Why wouldn't you start on five
and work down like the Sid and Marty Croft?
But what was, oh, it is like Sid and Marty Croft.
Except they deliver you to the middle.
You know what I'd like to say really fast?
If you're, this is all, I'm confused
as we're saying all this out loud.
I don't know if I know where I am.
And if you're feeling a little lost to the listener,
a way to get acquainted with all of the zones
and with DisneyQuest in general might be
to go to YouTube and type in DisneyQuest B-roll.
And once you do, you will find 18 minutes
of raw footage that was shot to be condensed
into an ad, into a shorter ad for DisneyQuest.
Which you can also find
if you search DisneyQuest commercial.
You can also see it edited down
or you can watch all of the raw footage
in which an overacting family runs around
and explores DisneyQuest.
And this is a notable video
because the daughter of said overacting family
is a young Mandy Moore.
What?
Yes, did you realize that watching it?
No.
That was Mandy Moore.
I really got my reaction, I did not.
Uh-huh, I wasn't sure if you guys knew
when I brought it up.
I didn't know.
So you get to see Mandy Moore running around.
You know, a lot of people,
I know people are fond of her work on This Is Us,
but to me, her most crucial work was saying,
whoa, wow, and I want that slice
at the Cheesecake Factory Express at FoodQuest.
I think she peaked a long time ago.
Well, while we're talking about that,
one of my favorite things in that commercial,
which I was a little disappointed
there wasn't more of in the B-roll,
is the family picking out their cheesecake treats
and the mother who is experiencing agony
and ecstasy simultaneously at this quarter.
And then like two shots later,
she's in the butt of your bumper car things
and she is similar look.
And I can't tell if she's experiencing pleasure or pain.
It's amazing gesticulating and acting.
And throughout this, as we cover the individual things,
I have written down what the father of the family said
while going into the attraction.
So I'll throw those in.
I will say this in general,
that at the start of the B-roll,
we were zooming into DisneyQuest
and the families pointed the wrong way,
looking around to see if they can find it.
Then they turn around and see it was right behind them
the whole time.
And the dad goes, there it is, woo!
It's fantastic, just improvised dialogue
by people including Mandy Moore.
What's fascinating too is about that B-roll,
they use it in one of the commercials for,
I don't know if you guys saw this,
there's a commercial for DisneyQuest
and they use some of the footage, it's only two minutes.
And they first like use some like Disney-ish music
and then all of a sudden 15 seconds in,
semi-charm life by the third eye blind starts playing.
A song about heroin addiction or something, right?
Something like that.
Isn't it?
Well, there's like bump again and then a bump again.
I've heard a lot of theories about what it is.
Yeah, so yeah, probably heroin, let's say heroin.
And then a hard cut to Zero to Hero from Hercules.
Yes, yes, yes.
That also, when I talk about unpleasant aesthetics,
that this place, because of when it opened,
had to be hyping Hercules,
which is sort of rough in general.
We got to remember Hercules came out in 95 or 96.
So it's hyping.
97 a little later.
Wait, 97?
I'm pretty sure.
Yeah, it's 97.
Really?
I think Tarzan's 98.
Tarzan's 98.
And I, no, Tarzan's 99, Mulan is 98.
Oh, Hercules in 96.
It was Hunchback of Notre Dame.
I know all this because these are the only things
I had to think about or do in these years.
Yeah, it is, okay.
Yeah, I must have transposed it with the other.
I guess you went from Hero to Zero.
I guess so.
I liked the Disney, the brief action,
action animated Hercules, Mulan,
and I really don't have much memories of it.
It's not like you liked everything
at this period of your life.
I think you did.
No, I did not.
I think you would have been a better,
you had a better late 90s than we did, I wanna say.
Yeah, probably.
I was pretty sure we'll look around then.
I was getting grumpier.
Yeah, I didn't like Hunchback.
I did not at all.
No one likes Hunchback.
Yeah, hell fire, hell fire.
Unpleasant.
Very depressing song.
They're too mean to that poor Hunchback.
Why don't we start here?
Let's go to floor five and work our way down
as Sid and Marty Croft intended, and on floor five,
I don't know, what is floor five?
Well, it's Food Quest.
Can I ask a question?
It's Food Quest.
Let's get, let's lead up our journey.
Food Quest is, from what I can tell,
maybe you guys did better research.
The only Cheesecake Factory Express that ever existed
was in Food Quest.
Potentially, it was mostly a freezer case
of Cheesecake Factory.
But they also had cheese steaks, I read.
It was also a cheese steak factory?
There was a cheese steak factory as well.
They could just take the cheese from the cake
and put it over on a sandwich.
There was food and people, like, there were,
I mean, you know, the Cheesecake Factory
has a bevy of options.
A giant menu. A giant menu.
As did this place.
There was also something called the Wonderland Cafe.
Well, the Wonderland Cafe was the Cheesecake Factory.
Oh, it changed.
Or I think, I saw a picture that said
the Cheesecake Factory Express logo
and then it said Wonderland Cafe.
And there was another thing too.
Here's one thing I know is that the Wonderland Cafe
had a big blocky font that says Cafe
and then on top of that, hand scribbled Cafe
on top, writing on top of the other.
So where Cafe is written twice, one on top of the other,
that's that kind of aesthetic shit that makes me upset.
It gives me a headache as we talk about it.
No good. But Cheesecake Factory Express.
Did it look good from the, I don't know,
from your vague catching of it in B-roll?
You think, I mean, is it a good spot?
It looked like that probably the cheesecake
was probably delicious.
It probably was. Yeah, everything else,
whatever it was, whether it was connected
to the Wonderland Cafe.
What was the other thing called?
There was like, it was a food court,
essentially a food court.
So it was like two or three stalls that you went up to.
And then eventually it all got.
Steamer trays of pizza and pasta and that sort of stuff.
Yeah, then it all just got named Burgers, Dogs and Raps
and Pizza, Pasta and Panini.
And whenever the deal with the Cheesecake Factory was done,
the food apparently got markedly worse.
So this miserable arcade is rotting and losing games
and the food has gotten much, much more unpleasant.
So that's where we're starting.
But from there, what zone is, I think,
I think it's the score zone.
Yeah, let's go to the score zone.
Because the top floor of this building had exactly,
it's crazy that I did not go there
because it had my two interests in the late 90s exactly.
Comic books and alien encounter shit.
All right, let's go in the order you said.
Ride the comics with an X. Ride the comics.
This one is the, this is the one I'm so interested, like.
I want. I didn't do this, actually.
What was it?
It was a VR, this was one of the VR things.
So you're putting on the big blocky helmet
and in it you are doing battle with comic book characters.
And it seems like you have like a little rod
that ends up serving as a sword.
It was a laser sword.
It's a laser sword. It's a laser sword.
And you're fighting against not Disney character.
They're kind of like a made up,
they feel like the villains from Nick Arcade,
where they're reminiscent of what real characters
from a comic or video game would be,
but you've never heard of them until right now.
Yeah, you're fighting against, you know,
Miss Skinner and the devil dogs.
You're fighting against the Toymaker.
You're fighting against Mistress Khan and Z-Bub.
So play on BLZubub.
It's weird that they would call it like comics,
but these aren't comics.
Oh, I beg to differ, Michael.
This was a popular 90s thing.
Don't you remember?
Oh, you mean like Comic Zone and stuff?
Yeah, like Comic Zone and the.
That's dumb too, though, I'm saying.
Yeah, it was just.
But you know what makes that different
is that that had a whole aesthetic in the,
we're talking about Comic Zone, a Sega Genesis game.
Oh. Available for iOS.
Is that right? Yeah, I have it on my phone.
Oh, that's fun.
But that used, that had a whole mechanism
that you would go to different levels
by turning the page, and it was like a whole,
it set the whole thing up.
You're inside a comic book,
and that's a big part of the play mechanics.
This, yeah, all this stuff is just like
they made up characters and they're like,
this is a comic, but it's not a comic.
It's just aesthetics.
It's just the aesthetics of 90s,
like hyper stylized, hyper violent comics.
What if you were, what if you strapped on a helmet
and you got to do battle with the X-Men except unbranded
and rendered in a less memorable fashion?
And also they are not comics, they are not flat.
They are CGI characters.
So the characters you saw on the sign on the way in
are not who you are fighting.
That's what Ride the Comics is.
I Ride the Comics follows the find
early video game tradition of the box art
being more interesting than the game itself.
Oh yeah, yeah.
The ET video game tradition.
I'm trying to figure out,
because I was trying to zoom in on these pictures,
which I found scattered about the internet.
Like, did they just have artists copy the style
of like image of like Jim Lee, Mark Silvestri type of comics,
or did they commission them to do this?
Because the one thing that's missing
from these kinds of comics, these drawings
is a little artist signature in the corner,
which I'm sure Disney is like.
They made them sign away.
Or the people didn't want to do it.
Maybe they did it anonymously.
Yeah, they could have.
But I mean, it looks like.
You showed them to me yesterday.
They look like Mark Silvestri drawings,
if you know who that is.
He's a comic guy, you know?
Yeah.
And and and I would say like the style of the time,
but that style never really went away in comics.
Like Jim Lee still sells a ton of comics when he draws a comic.
So, sure.
Yeah, very generic.
Like, but again, I probably would have been very.
I was a sucker for anything branded comics.
Let me say this.
I we were so confused by the layout of this place, too.
I don't think I knew this existed in there.
And I think we missed it somehow.
Yeah, I didn't go anywhere near this.
Like I yeah, if this was hidden, maybe.
And I was obviously like comic comics with an X.
That's all you had to say to me at that age.
And I would have been like, yes, please.
Well, they was located on the inside all of the spaceships
that were jutting out over the the the atrium.
So, you know, the comic characters live in the spaceships.
Oh, that makes a lot of sense.
Now that you say it in the score zone, Mike, get with the program.
The score zone.
And you're like writing like you're what you say.
I was going to say it is funny that they use the X
because like X got used as a lot of like extreme shit in the 90s.
But in terms of comic book, like the spelling with comics
usually refers to like the alt comics like your Art Spiegelman,
Dan Clowes, Robert Crumb sort of world of comics.
That is not at all this world of comics.
Was a Robert Crumb
V.R. right now would be now I'm interested.
Jesus.
It's like a Fritz the cat style VR experience.
What about is there like a leisure suit, Larry V.R. these days?
Oh, someone's got to be working on that.
Right. Right.
Do you leisure shoot leisure suit Larry where it was like a dirty game,
but like nothing ever happened.
Did you ever play that? No.
You know, I'm talking about.
No, I was like a pervy cartoon man and you would play a computer game
and he would like go talk to girls and like bathing suits.
It was on like the adults only shelf at CompUSA or something.
Yeah. And it was a dirty game.
They're an adult game.
It was like three dirty games.
Yeah. And one of the improv team we used to play on was called Leisure Suit Jason.
Oh, yeah.
So I think that was just me, you and past guest, Marissa Strickland.
Right. Yeah.
And she used a childhood photo of you to promote it.
And it's my favorite picture I've ever seen.
Let's post that. We will post it.
Ride the comics.
I'm looking at the video of this.
It's just like a guy on a jet ski and you're just like wiggling a thing.
You're like wiggling a laser sword.
And one of those watching a bunch of dads do this and pretend to enjoy it
and pretend they know how to do it.
You put my dad in this thing.
It's a disaster. Yeah.
And now like dads these days, if we were dads, we'd kind of know how to do it
because we grew up on video games and stuff.
But yeah, I can't imagine the learning curve on the headset
because my parents checked out at Mario one.
They tried to play Mario one and they did for a little bit.
And then I think it was like that was it.
They never played a game again.
They never tried any of the other systems.
Like Wii, they tried a little of the Wii.
They did Gwi bowling.
There was a little bit.
They almost got the parents back.
And I think that was a big reason that Wii sold so well.
But yeah, they were out.
So, yeah, imagining now that that being said, would I like a video of my dad
waving a laser sword at a guy on a jet ski?
Of course, the B-roll footage of people swinging the swords.
I mean, like, oh, yeah, you don't get on him.
You don't look cool doing VR.
Any VR, you don't know.
And those helmets are so gigantic.
I wish it was the like unedited B-roll where the people are obviously being coached.
Like, hey, you really wave your arm more or like really here.
Like, because obviously, commands all of those things that people are saying
and exclaiming are so unnatural.
Yeah. So I would love the full.
If anyone has a copy of that fighting the toy maker, go for it.
Get after it. He's the toy maker.
So number two, and this is a pretty notable thing.
Here's here's one thing overall.
I would like to say about Disney Quest and something I think is admirable about it
and sort of presaging the future is that this was a weird instance
of trying to take properties from the parks and do other things with them.
As we'll get into, there was a Pirates of the Caribbean thing.
There was a Jungle Cruise thing.
There was a Space Mountain thing.
And we have here up in the score zone, the other iteration of beloved attraction,
extraterrestrial alien encounter.
But it's specifically called Invasion, an extraterrestrial alien encounter.
Yes. Yes.
Colonists on a planet are being attacked by aliens.
Earth needs to enlist the help of Chairman Clench and access tech.
It's so ideal.
You have here.
Sexual predator Jeffrey Jones is back.
He's back. Our favorite creep.
Yeah, this is the other piece of media containing
original alien encounter character Chairman Clench.
And he holds a joint press conference
with the president of the United States, Joseph Reed.
I love generic presidents and things,
especially as we as a society step very far away
from just like a dull man in a suit.
And that's the president.
The president's name is Mark Morris.
Like that never happens.
And he but I love that's I love President Whitmore and Independence Day so much.
And you get President Joseph Reed and he's in Chairman Clench
makeup for approximately 10 seconds of footage.
I wonder if they film this concurrently with Alien Encounter.
Do they like possibly have the knowledge to know they were going to do
something else? But that was there's a long distance between those things.
I don't know. Anyway, I love President Joe.
That's another podcast, right?
Patreon promise a full episode about President Joseph Reed,
a character of all of 15 seconds in fiction.
Uh huh. This one looked the game itself, I'll say, like looks maybe fun.
Kind of. Yeah. Right.
Fun kind of.
I think this is among the more well received elements
because it was like kind of just a video game.
Yeah. I don't we keep we were running out of time already, probably.
But like Gameworks was open, which is a place like Dave and Buster's.
And just everything in Gameworks to me at the time was like, this is awesome.
I want to do all of these things.
And all of these things are so boring and not inspiring for a child.
And didn't and by Gameworks was a Sega property.
Is that correct?
Dave and Buster's.
What I'm saying is these places all had the big, good video games
at these other indoor video game entertainment centers.
They had like the legitimate best video games being made
by professional video game makers, not original weird.
Disney has to conjure up all of these things from scratch.
Well, that came first and Disney was like, oh, we can't let them have.
We got to get into this entertainment sort of thing.
Right. Theory in the defunct land video is that it was all all of this was Eisner
trying to strike back against Katzenberg.
Oh, right. Right. Out of vested interest in Gameworks.
Maybe I don't know.
That seems I mean, this seems like a thing Disney wanted would have wanted to do
anyway. And as I said, it was their way to like, let's get into other cities
without having to build a full magic kingdom in Toronto or whatever it is.
But I don't know. Yeah, this seems fine.
This isn't the worst thing.
Yeah, it seems like you could enjoy playing it.
Some level you steer the ship or you're the gunner.
Yeah, that's pretty much it.
Looks like a stand-alone video game rescue colonists.
It doesn't OK.
Inspiring about the like the graphics or the characters in it.
But you know who's really excited about it is the dad in the Mandy Moore
B roll, who is walking up to this attraction and yells, this is it, baby.
Amazing.
So that's that's that's covers the score zone, doesn't it?
I think we're out of the score zone already.
Let's get out of the score zone into the fire into the replay zone.
Let's go down to wait.
Some of the zones, this zone straddles several floors.
I don't know where to go next.
Four and five.
It was like a half score zone and half replays.
Let's go replay midway on the moon.
I don't have this one.
Just made way on the moon.
Looks like it's on five.
Five. It's on both.
Oh, it's on. I think it's a two floor arcade.
What the hell?
Some of the attractions straddle the floor.
I see what you're saying.
Can be more than one floor.
Now it does. I have I'm seeing midway on the moon as well.
For a replay zone and they're both on the OK.
It's a multi floor midway that's on the moon and in the score zone.
And on the fifth floor, it's connected by Food Quest and the Wonderland Cafe.
And on the fourth floor, it's connected by Wonderland Web Adventures.
A thing I'm realizing I didn't really find much out on, but I'm assuming was
Internet Cafe.
Yes.
Now, what you could do there was send an E postcard
telling people what a good time you're having at Disney Quest on a compact computer.
Disney Quest is full of stuff that you would just do at the end of Spaceship Earth.
Yes. You would just go through.
Everything like in Epcot and stuff where you just go at the end
and that whatever they have in at the end of Journey into Imagination
or whatever it's called.
Oh, because they have that kind of thing where you let bullshit.
You make your eyes big and you put it seems like you could put on a little monitor.
You put scars snout over your face.
Yeah. And they print out a photo of that.
It's probably miserable quality.
Yeah. A big waste of time.
It's just some idea that they could like suck people into the ride
for an extra 10 minutes, like some number cruncher was like,
if we keep everyone there 15 more minutes, then we'll have there.
Like the pathways will be much more clear for the rest of the day.
And spend this whole thing feels like a strategy to get people out of the parks.
Like, how can we hide people in a corner for a couple hours
so we reduce the line of big thunder?
Three hours specifically, which was the estimated amount of time.
Yeah, they said the ideal Disney Quest experience is two to three hours,
which is not a lot, not a lot for thirty dollars.
My memory is that we were so confused how to navigate it.
We were so confused at like the wait times that there were things
that seemed inaccessible that we just were so lost.
And we kind of wandered to a couple things.
And we were like, I guess we did it all.
We were so unsure and uncertain of what was happening.
You missed entire things and things like I don't think I went on Cyberspace
Mountain because you walk up to it and like, where's the line?
And then you have to wait, get in line, I recall your own ride.
And then, right.
Is this jumping around if we talk about cyberspace mountain?
Who cares? Doesn't matter.
From the Create Zone?
We might as well go to the Create Zone.
What zone we're in if we jump around, I think.
OK, so now we're we'll get back to the replay zone.
But I will let's talk about the Create Zone zone.
Because we had already talked about living easels in which you give yourself
a scar snout. Yes.
And there's also a thing where you can make
the kind of Frankenstein toy that Sid from Toy Story makes,
where it's a bunch of toys fused together in a freakish way.
Create a toy, which I saw one one or two websites say
you would create the toy and then you could buy the toy at the end.
I saw no proof that you could buy the toy.
I read that something like was broken.
Somebody was like the toy, create a toy was broken the day I went.
Yeah, every day. Like every day.
It's like the lie at McDonald's when they say the milkshake machine is broken.
Oh, well, that's such a that's a that happened a lot.
I've had happen, you know, 10 times probably in my life.
And it's always at 1am or it's always at 12.
I don't want to. Oh, yeah, it's not working.
It's not working. And it's always like you can tell he's like the kid is lying.
This disc just getting lazy.
So there's that.
But then the big thing that you can create is your own rollercoaster.
I'm sick of Space Mountain telling me what to do.
It's a new era. It's the digital era.
I want a cyber space mountain.
So this is we just I feel like there must be listeners who don't know this,
that there's a thing called Cyber Space Mountain.
And you get in a line to stand at a computer and you pick out
the pieces of your track.
People were seemingly fond of this attraction a little bit.
This is the roller coaster tycoon fondness.
Right. It's like making a roller coaster tycoon ride that you you can actually ride.
And your host for this experience is Bill Nye, the science.
Why wouldn't it be the coaster guy?
Is this he does say, Bill Nye, the coaster guy.
Oh, man.
I got to say, I was impressed by how much you could customize a coaster.
Sure. Because they would have had to program all those.
That you can immediately go on a thing that you built and in a good idea.
Yeah. That's pretty advanced.
This was a like it's like a little mini simulator, just two people
that flips around, it goes upside down and then it seems like I saw
actual ride video, non posed, non Mandy Moore ride video
where people were having a good time and you see people's hair go upside down.
And but we should say this is different than the roller
designed and ride your own roller coaster in a in inventions
that lasted for a while called the sum of all thrills.
Really? What was that?
That was there when I was there in 2014.
There was the same idea.
You would get an idea.
Looked like the same technology.
Oh, I don't remember that might have been a kooka arm.
Somewhat. Maybe it was a kooka arm.
It was well, but it was the same thing as this simulator.
Yeah, I don't even remember that.
It was a roller coaster.
We did go on Cyberspace Mountain and I remember being like, OK, pretty fun.
I think we went upside down maybe once and it was fine.
I think the graphics are still like like, again, they're like
not as good as what you have in home and your video game.
Well, in 1998, potentially it is up to snuff with what you have at home.
Maybe maybe by a year later, it is not right.
This PlayStation 2 is better than anything here.
GameCube is in every iteration.
So it only gets exponentially worse every year that this thing was open up through 2017.
Ninety eight has like GoldenEye.
Mm hmm. So so better looking than GoldenEye,
but no one likes any of this more than GoldenEye.
No, GoldenEye. Yeah.
But you do again.
Space map, boring space mountain.
They just take me to space.
Where even am I?
It's not named where you are.
I want mythology.
And that's why Bill Nye tells you your space
mountain experience can take you either to Moltonia, which is hot,
Broopa, Broopa, which is cold and Grumba 12, which is moderate.
I don't know. One for Grumba 12, please.
Jason wants a one way ticket to Grumba 12.
Leave me there tonight.
You have a summer home.
I summer in Grumba 12.
Me and Sherman Clinch are going to go hang in Grumba.
No, don't. Jason, no.
Standing on the edge of my dock in Grumba 12,
looking at the green light across the way at the house.
Slowly, we move on boats in a current.
You write novels in Grumba 12.
The Hemingway of Grumba 12.
You watch the four moons of Grumba 12 set each night, each dusk.
And there's a magic mirror where you mess up your own eyes.
It's like photo booth filters.
And that's the great zone.
Yeah, hold on.
We got to talk about the magic mirror thing.
They eventually it's the magic mirror surrounded a giant Pinocchio head.
Yeah. But eventually they took out the magic mirrors
and put in a seating so you could just sit next to a giant,
like six foot by six foot Pinocchio head.
Unwrapped, lingering behind your wrench.
You're bad at it.
It looks so unnerving.
Feel what Geppetto feels after Pinocchio leaves the house
and only can think about is his lost boy over his shoulder in his brain.
A new dimension of horror.
My boy.
Um, so that's that.
Here, let's backtrack over to the replay zone.
Why replay? What do you mean?
The other ones are replays.
So the yeah, I know this will replay is on.
OK, so replay is five, four and three levels, five, four and three.
And it's like a lot of.
Yeah. So on my map of Disney Quest, you guys have.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
And three all have replay zones and it's all like the right side of the building.
And three also all have score zones.
Yes. So score zone is also on five, four and three as well.
The other hand, those are blue.
OK, so that left side of my map, those are blue.
So the score zones are blue and the red are the replay zones.
So this zone straddle the levels and one floor can be more than one zone.
Right. What are you getting?
I take the cyber later to get there.
You take the cell.
You're seemingly if you go up, if you eventually go all the way up,
like there's a lot of stuff on one and two you want to do there.
OK, so let's I guess let's talk about Buzz Lightyear, Astro Blaster,
singular, singular, Astro Blaster.
And it's not the ride.
It's not the right now from the parks.
It's something else. But this I like.
Yes, this is cool. I didn't do it.
I don't remember why.
Probably a long line.
There's a bunch of no good Knicks who were wanted, you know,
who would have bumped you and throw cannonballs at you extra.
Yeah, these were like soup.
Something that fire in here.
Somebody smell like fire.
I smell food.
OK, it's probably next door then. Sorry.
Thanks. So we'll keep it.
Just keep your nose up.
I think it's probably just probably food coming through. But I think so.
Like at first I'd be like, is that steak?
And then I was like, wait, no, that's OK.
Anyway, that's pretty Bernie.
But Bernie. Well, OK.
So Buzz Lightyear's Astro Blaster glorified bumper cars with cannons on them
that would shoot like foam balls at other cars.
Yeah, this is fun.
This looks like some game show, some fun.
Never made Nickelodeon show or some high concept.
Like there's there's a lot like to like about this.
Just really aesthetically something. Yeah.
And you fire the cannonballs cannonball.
What is it? Asteroid mini?
That's space rocks.
I don't know.
You fire them at a little splat on the side of your opponent's cars.
And if you hit the target, their car spins around.
But that's cool.
A very small room.
Yeah, it looks so small.
I'm sure that's why we didn't go on it, because it was so small.
And like the right capacity had to be terrible.
And cars look like they could barely move.
I mean, bumper cars, you need space to like move.
Yeah. And they're not going particularly fast.
They're going very slow.
Everyone's clumped up and spinning.
Yeah. So in theory, it's a cool idea.
Idea. But yeah, it looks like a like an electric football game.
Like where they all like kind of goes around and fall over.
It's this pathetic little display.
They aren't evenly spread out amongst the field.
They all like all stay in a corner and spin. Right.
Yeah, it's weird.
It's pretty it's pretty dopey.
But I bet of all the things we can hear, maybe we can establish it.
Let's let's at the end say what we think.
I did very few of the experiences, but we could say what we think.
If you had to pick one, what was like the best?
Sure. Maybe in the running.
And then there's also a
video game, like an arcade area called the underground.
And it looks like where Chris O'Donnell in whichever Batman this is
meets Coolio.
It's like it's that level forever.
Right. Yeah, forever.
But that's how that's the kind of underground it seems like to me.
Like it's edgy for a 13 year old.
Yeah. Now you're now I'm stuck on which where's Coolio, which movie?
I think he might be in Batman and Robin, right?
There's similar sequences in there.
That's what I'm misremembering.
With the weird the the Gotham, like underground street racing scene.
Hold on. I just found a rumor I've never heard before
from Hollywood Reporter 2017.
Coolio was courted to play Scarecrow in scrapped Batman and Robin sequel.
So you ever heard that has been courted to play Scarecrow?
And then we've heard Jeff Goldblum.
I have never heard Coolio courted to play Scarecrow courted.
They were trying.
This is Hollywood Reporter was courted.
This is not like a comic book fan site from 1999.
His hair is exactly like a scarecrow's hair.
How could any other actor do it?
Someone get me Coolio's bleeping people on the phone now, Roger.
It was Batman and Robin Coolio's in.
All right.
So after that and that the way he landed, the force he was in that film,
you want to yeah, you want to give him the lead in the next one.
For sure.
I think actually speaking, I think Mr.
Mr. Free is Schwarzenegger's Mr.
Free's, I think drives around a little weird ice buggy.
Yes, kind of like the Buzz Lightyear, Astro Blaster cars.
Yeah, that's true.
I think that's right.
That's right.
Just a couple of spikes on the outside.
That's fun.
So where do we leave off?
Are we the underground?
The underground?
I don't know.
We're almost done with this.
Where's we're done with the replay zone, as far as I know.
We're OK, but we can go to the score zone on level three.
That's in the explore zone.
I know.
It's in the score zone.
It's in blue.
It is. It's in my score zone.
Yeah, I think it's in the score zone.
Oh, you're right.
Oh, so we I skipped way past Mighty Ducks.
Yeah, right.
No, that's OK.
We're getting all the arcade stuff.
Visitor of the Disney Quest.
Like all the arcade stuff,
they didn't seem like there was any fighting games or shooting games.
So I would have been disappointed by that.
But I like this.
You were shooting really funny.
Yeah, the shooting game is the alien encounter kind of.
Well, no. Oh, sorry.
The VR, the experiences.
But in terms of like the midway, kind of like the the arcade arcade.
Oh, I see that they had seemed very like driving.
And mostly driving games.
I've missed something, which is one of these dull men who ran
Disney regional entertainment was interviewed.
Yes, I love it.
Yeah, I believe this that was this guy and he is being interviewed
and he's asked, what is score zone?
And he says it's literally competition city.
Literally, literally.
It's literally a city.
Is it? What do you mean?
And then and then goes on to say, you know, such as the Mighty Ducks.
Well, I don't remember the name of it, but he might do
this thing where you actually become a living pinball.
The dream, which is like the city of Mardi Croft.
Yes, that is exactly what it is.
Indoor multi level.
Oh, my God. That's so strange.
That's crazy claustrophobic pinball rides, except this one
in the city, Mardi Croft, right?
You really are inside a pinball.
Yeah. And here you're just like
you're on.
I think you're sort of on a big joystick.
It's like it like pivots like a segue would, where you put your weight
forward or back or left or right.
And then you're controlling where a ball goes on a screen
and you're against 14 other people.
But you are being
the goalie of the Mighty Ducks is fending off the balls.
The goalie, whose name is Wild Wing Flash Blade.
Well, Wild Wing's leader, the Mighty Ducks.
This is, we should say, themed to the late 90s Mighty Ducks cartoon,
a team of adventurers who are all ducks and have hockey based powers.
Were you into it? Yeah, you were.
Yeah, because I was not.
It feels like I should have been, but I actually don't know any of them.
I can't say any of the names like that to be funny or anything
like I do with other stuff.
I don't know anything about that Mighty Ducks cartoon.
I didn't know anything about it until today.
And I discovered one fact that I really enjoy,
which is that the theme song of the show was called Ducks Rock.
And the singer of the theme song was Mickey Thomas, singer of Starship.
Yeah. Singer of Elvin Bishops, Fooled Around and Fell in Love.
I saw him this year.
You saw Epcot. Epcot Center, a frequent participant
in theme park concert events, because now you go see Starship
and it's called Starship featuring Mickey Thomas.
So this is the guy who's saying, you know, Jane and well, half of
we built this city.
And I don't do you know them?
I don't want to I don't want to destroy the melody of the song
because you might have it in your head more because you watch the show.
But if I could just kind of sing my favorite passage of the song,
here come the money burning up the ice,
try and stop the Mighty Ducks.
You are going to pay the price.
And then he keeps saying like Ducks Rock.
Yeah, Ducks Rock.
Crazy song. That's great.
I will say that the 90s have the best cartoon theme songs for like late 80s,
early 90s, mid 90s. Fantastic theme songs these days.
Don't touch them.
It's even the bad cartoon.
They don't really do it anymore.
The cartoons, though, went for it.
Even the terrible stuff have like very fun, interesting
something something to them songs.
It really, I think, influenced my music taste in general,
because I like a lot of stuff that sounds like the Ducktales theme,
because like the horn players on it,
I got a lot of stuff I like the West and Al Jarreau and Toto and all this.
The ducktales. I'm trying to find more sauce so I can just be listening to
basically the Ducktales song all day.
The Ducktales theme is like one of the best songs ever written.
Really? Oh, yeah.
Sure. Top 50 songs ever written.
But it's also kind of a rip of, you know,
Don't Forget.
Don't you make my dreams come true.
It even has woos just like so you got to talk to the couple of points for that.
Can I say something?
I think it's add them as writers to it and we're on the clear.
Oh, yeah. They should have added credit and then it's fine.
It's also karmic.
Oh, wait, no, this was also Michael Jackson at the We Are The World Recording said,
hey, sorry, I kind of bit.
I can't go for that for Billy Jean. Right. Right.
Yeah. So they're getting they're getting ripped off left and right.
All in notes, better lawyers.
It is crazy to me that there was a I guess you'd call it an attraction
about the short lived Mighty Ducks cartoon,
which also done in conjunction with Disney briefly owning the hockey team.
Well, they started the hockey team.
Wait, they started it. Yeah.
And they built the pond, which is now on the floor.
And for yeah, it was Eisner's idea.
And I found just the beginning it was it was behind the Atlantic paywall.
So I didn't go.
Hey, thanks for being behind our paywall.
Please, if you're subscribing to the Atlantic, cancel it and stick with us.
Yeah, there's so much.
I'm a little bit of a wall.
God, yeah, the Atlantic's full of crap.
Oh, yeah. Garbage.
And plus I can read you the free paragraph before the paywall
behind this paywall.
Eisner apparently just like in that he said out of like,
I wanted to start a hockey team to be a good neighbor.
I was thinking about the city of Anon.
What can we do?
Can we help the spirit of Anaheim?
And they built this and it was all synergy because they had the movie
and a cartoon film, the Mighty Deck.
Well, the cartoon came after the.
Oh, it did. It did.
And this is a show that has like space stuff.
It has like warlords and magic amulets.
It's got a. However, also,
the base of it still is the pond of Anaheim.
There are. I did not know.
That's crazy building that is literally in Anaheim.
And while refer to Anaheim in the show, I looked up really.
Yeah. Anaheim exists in my space cartoon, which also partially is set
in a place called Puck World.
Yes, actually set in Anaheim and a character named Mindbender
says the line My Ingenious New Thermal Bomb
will turn Anaheim into Hollandaise sauce.
Wow, that's awesome. Jason's.
That's. I mean.
I like it. I think I should mention their gunshot hockey pucks.
Or actually buck.
Wild Wings, like he had wrist blasters that shot hockey pucks.
Do you know and can you name
Wild Wings brother also of the Flashblade family?
I think he was the thief who had like a grappling hook and a sword.
And I cannot, but I can picture him was Nose Dive.
And I would know maybe that was someone else.
And then there was a character whose his actual name.
And I don't know his name, but he the character was voiced by Dennis Frans.
And he was the police chief of Anaheim.
That's so good.
I did not know any of this.
So weird. I didn't realize even to that that the team starts in 93.
That's why I was getting all screwed up with my first film.
Right. Because I didn't realize it was that fast.
And by the time they did the second film, they were able to use
the first thing that ever happened in the pond slash today, the Honda Center
was the filming of the finale of Mighty Ducks.
Wow. I didn't know.
Those kid actors, including Keenan Thompson, skated on the ice.
They were the first people ever to be in that venue.
The first event ever to happen was not a hockey game,
but rather a Barry Manilow concert.
Barry Manilow opened the pond.
I'm looking here and Jim Belushi played Phil Palmfeather
and Tim Curry played Lord Jorganis.
What was the what was the bad guy?
It's incredible.
I know the list is crazy.
What was the bad guy you were saying before?
I was saying Mindbender, but I couldn't find any more info.
I can't find anything about mind.
I can find Hookerman.
I can find Dr. Wally Pretorius,
voiced by Matt Fruer, who was
the character on that generation X X-Men movie.
Oh, yeah. He was also one of these on other stuff.
I think he's one of Zeus's henchmen in
Hercules, which is which in these characters,
their names are like chaos or what are they called?
They're in this they're in.
We we in panic.
We got to cut this out right now, because obviously this is an episode.
Full Mighty Ducks episode.
Look how much you're getting.
The Atlantic would never do this.
Fuck the Atlantic. Fuck Jeffrey Goldberg.
The Jewel Thief
character that I liked.
His name was Duke Larrange.
All right. That's not we got.
Let's watch the entire series and we'll come back to an episode.
So that's Mighty Ducks.
And I think what we have missed the most now is the Explorer Zone.
Yes. And that's the important part of my teased story.
OK, the Explorer Zone,
because that has said we're virtual jungle cruise.
Yeah, of course.
It's Aladdin's magic carpet.
And we did.
I remember doing Jungle Cruise and fine.
Oh, it's moving a little bit, but there you're such you're watching a TV.
It's not like you're that immersed.
You're on a raft that is on like a big water bed and you're fake.
You're paddling. Yeah, paddling would be the word.
They had to know when they were developing this and they were like,
all right, we're putting this like they had to know this sucks, right?
It doesn't look it doesn't look good.
It's not even with the with the goggles.
You can say, well, now you look to the right and left.
You see, you know, the jungle, you see difference.
This is not that kid like you look to.
There's like flats. There's nothing there.
But unlike the regular jungle cruise, it is dinosaurs.
Yes, you go back in time, right?
That's the big thing at the start.
You go back in time or there's a guy who's like to go back.
I mean, you start the start screen is a weird magic kingdom world
with the has the Cinderella castle, the big castle, but also a Matterhorn,
which is not right. Disney Park has that.
So that's wrong.
Why is Disney not branding properly? Very strange.
The biggest error up until the point when Ryan Reynolds
tweeted that photo of Deadpool getting arrested.
And you remember this and you you tweeted at him
that he had used the wrong picture.
I think he said, you know, for dead, I think it was.
Tweeted, he got arrested at Disney World
and the Matterhorn was in the background and you were like,
this is not the right park.
Get with it, Deadpool. Yeah. Anyway.
Yeah. So that's inaccurate.
Yeah. But I will say this plus up for the main jungle cruise,
adding dinosaurs, not the worst.
Oh, no, not at all.
Time travel component way into that. Cool.
Hopefully that happens in that rock movie.
So yeah. But then you have Aladdin's carpet.
We have Aladdin's magic carpet ride.
And this was the ride, funny enough, that I was the most excited about.
Sure. Whenever whatever media stuff I looked at or whatever
article I was reading, this was touted as your ride in the carpet.
Three, your virtual world looked to your left or right.
You're in Agrabah. So excited.
So we knew we had to do this.
So I don't remember how long the wait was, but I was this was
this was the main event for me.
I got on it within 30 to 45 seconds.
I felt so ill.
I felt so dizzy and ill
that I didn't even enjoy a sec.
Like I didn't.
30 seconds, probably now they think about it too long.
15 seconds. Yeah.
I felt so ill that I just wanted this thing off my head.
And I was fucked up like the rest of the day.
I never threw up, but I was woozy.
I felt weird. We had to leave Disney Quest. Oh.
It because I'm never like that on rides, right?
Even rides sometimes, even if like you eat and I go on a roller coaster,
I feel like, oh, I shouldn't have done that.
But it's not like a dire situation.
I was not good.
We left because I was just like when we had to get on a plane that day,
I just I think before that is when I bought Blood Sugar Sex Magic
from the Virgin Megastore.
So like, I don't think we went anywhere else.
Something to listen to.
Like that's a late buy.
Very late buy. Yes, I was just getting into the red hot chili peppers
at the time.
Uh huh. Yikes.
Hey, I don't know.
But that seems like that is a Aladdin problem, not a you problem.
No, I that's right.
So so going through all this Disney Quest stuff, I just
first of all, have that feeling of like this thing letting me down so bad
and then just fucking me up real bad on the way out.
And then I remember we got on the plane and I still felt weird on the plane.
And then there's a problem with the plane and they made us
de-bored, which is terrifying.
And then we had a voucher.
We got a voucher for like a sandwich and I ate a sandwich.
And I fucking nice, man.
I remember I ate the sandwich and then I felt a little better
and the plane was OK.
The plane ride was OK.
But man, I have never been screwed up from a ride
more than I have at Disney Quest on this Aladdin ride.
Wow. So that is damning.
Colors my whole Disney Quest feeling.
Yeah, you did.
And how long were you there before that?
I'm not sure. Probably a couple hours.
OK. Well, so you did get your your your ideal.
We got the two hours and we went through all the different zones
and did in childhood nausea.
But yeah, childhood nausea never threw up, which was maybe even the problem.
Like I just never it was just like I think my head was screwed up.
Like I was woozy. Jason's laughing.
I don't know why.
I was going to say so.
So you did eat the sandwich.
You didn't give it away. Give it away. Give it away.
Now.
I was going to say that all the dizziness made you feel like you lost some blood.
That's good. Yeah, we both had one.
I did a good check just to make sure like that that give it away was on
the album and I was like, it's like I felt like I won the lottery
when I was like it was got real.
Yes. Also, I guess also we could say that maybe my blood sugar sex magic was low.
Low. Yeah.
Got a ride called the treasure of the Incas.
Well, yes, that so that one didn't last very long
because it stopped working because of cell phone interference.
Yeah, the thing where you navigated little toy cars through ruins,
but they were controlled with radio waves and once they were in a cell
phones around and then one of them exploded.
I heard once one lights on fire, which is the phone plan points out
a fire within a windowless
five story building, not an ideal situation.
I want to show this real quick back to the Aladdin.
Doesn't this look like something that you would when you go to a shoe store,
they would try shoes on.
Well, you sit on you're straddling kind of a bench
that gives you like the motorcycle vibe, right?
Like you're in a saddle.
But yes, it's tan and it just looks like a like a shoe trying mechanism.
And there's a really funny part also of this Mandy Moore video where she
you follow her in and she goes and puts on the helmet,
but she's already wearing like a partial helmet that then somebody then
one of the helpers who are called navigators, by the way,
all of the really in Disney Quest are called navigators.
And they have a little stripe on their sleeve that says that.
And I found a Disney Quest Mickey Toy where he's in a Disney
Quest uniform with his name says Mickey and then on the sleeve navigator.
What kind of toy are we talking about?
Plush. Nice. Pretty good.
I found like a nice figure of it, but that's pretty good.
Now, this pin, a pin trading pin of Mickey in like kind of a
nondescript amorphous like tech suit.
I call this was another thing of kids cartoons, like characters
wearing armor where you're not quite sure what it does or what it's protecting them from.
So then so the navigators, though, would be like either
navigating you on your quest.
Is that the idea? Disney Quest.
You control your own quest, but the navigators help in case
you don't know where to go.
OK, I don't know if I go is Aladdin's
magic carpet ride on the third level of the explore zone
or is it on the fifth level of score zone?
The navigators know.
Oh, this is a mess.
So as all right. So Jungle Cruise with dinosaurs.
Mike gets nausea.
Yeah, the Incas explodes.
Then you've got a Hercules in the underworld.
Hercules in the underworld
starring the Hades played by everyone's favorite star.
It's still for this day.
James Woods.
Yeah, if only if Disney
Quest had the technology to keep him from being locked out of his own Twitter.
That's something that happened.
I don't know.
Twitter problems sucks.
Pain and panic are there.
I think one of one of whom is the person you mentioned, Bobcat Goldthwait, one of them.
I don't know if they did voices for this.
Oh, should mention, by the way, the Aladdin thing does have this appearance
by John Ennis for Mr.
Show, which we talked about.
Yeah, say any lines, apparently.
He's in kind of like a Hawaiian shirt.
He's a vacationer.
He is like Ken Marino in Rock and Rollercoaster.
And I found an article pointing out the this blight of
talented skits, comedians given no lines in 90s Disney attractions.
1998 Disney attractions, in fact.
Oh, strange.
That's weird.
What do you anything to say about Hercules in the underworld?
I think you collect lightning bolts.
Oh, yes. And I heard the the Manny Moore dad says, give me the lightning bolts.
And then I think Hades also yells, give me back the lightning bolts.
So maybe that was what I read.
That might have been his line. Yes.
Oh, no, I'm sorry. The dad says, oh, yeah, they're walking
under the sign that has Hercules on it.
And then the dad says, oh, there he is.
My favorite guy.
Like he just saw his college roommate.
Like he just saw his buddy.
Hey, there you are, Hercules.
You old son of a bitch.
This one might have like the best graphics
of like the ones that use any character.
And I don't know.
I mean, the bar is low.
You might be right, but that might be right.
Yeah, that's why I'm trying to be like, this one also was fulfilled
its destiny and was eventually replaced. Right.
The only thing ever added to the Disney quests
was an attraction called Pirates of the Caribbean Battle for Buccaneer
Gold, notable for being before the films and the first other thing
besides the ride about Pirates of the Caribbean.
And people kind of liked this one and attribute
the technology that today powers Midway Mania is having a precedent in this ride.
This ride made me laugh because the the the skeleton,
there's a pirate skeleton who talks to you.
He trains you and he turns out to be the boss at the end.
And he also looks like the admin,
the skeleton in charge of at the share zone.
The funny Twitter account with skeleton.
It's like the like memes that look like very intense, like, you know,
the the Carpe the fuck out of the DM,
like kind of like 3D skeleton.
But is this like a youth thing?
Is this one of your?
No, no, I think this is an older.
This is more like a drill.
So it's weird for later.
I think it's been around that long, but it's but all the so all of them.
But instead of saying like, you know, guns and beer, all the memes say like,
I'm sorry, I fucked up again or like depression, anxiety.
But it's like a real intense skeleton riding a motorcycle.
This is very complicated.
And you have to look into this.
So it looks like all right.
So it's graphics. It looked like a meme.
It's a skeleton man.
People did kind of like this, but still not very good.
And this all of the attractions.
I have we made it through the zones.
I think so.
Do we get the snow? Do we get all the zone stone in the zone stone?
I think a thing that stuck out to me about the Pirates of the Caribbean ride
was that it was hard to do, and sometimes you could lose it.
Like you could not accomplish your task.
Good. I like that.
But that has to make people upset.
That's the problem.
Supposedly, they're running into with the Millennium Falcon ride
that will be coming next year.
Oh, yeah. Now, that's one thing.
This is all the beginnings of this is the first
that I think I consider maybe Disney Quest was all experimenting
in a way of to get kinds of rides that are more interactive into the parks.
I think Disney was starting to freak out in the 90s.
People have experiences at home that they can control.
And we need to start doing things like that, which they did far more successfully
with Buzz Lightyear's Astro Blaster's plural.
And obviously Midway Mania.
And now the Falcon is coming.
But all of these things or I don't know.
I don't mind a not interactive experience.
I know. Sometimes it's better. Yeah.
But I it's funny to me that this closes in 97.
Excuse me. 2017.
Jesus. 2017.
Right as legit satisfying VR experiences are showing up everywhere.
Yeah, it's like that whole time.
The void is coming out months or is already out probably when this closes,
whatever the first version of it was.
Money and Falcon Ride is going to be awesome, probably very satisfying.
So they close it right when the technology has finally gotten to the point
where people like this stuff.
That's true.
And if they had just gone in and replaced all of it.
Right. It feels like they could have taken even maybe some of the same ideas
and done the same thing.
Like I don't it's just weird because when Lindsay and I were in Japan,
we went to a VR zone and it was certainly not themed at all.
It was very kind of utilitarian.
You go up to nothing that was that themed.
But they had like 12 different experiences and you'd go over to the
especially the Mario Kart one.
But you go to the Mario Kart one and there's a little like cart,
a design like cart you would sit in and it's not like nothing fancy around it.
But the VR itself is awesome.
So like there exists now to have all this really cool VR stuff
and they close it right like literally within the year,
probably when this stuff starts coming into its own, like with home VR use
is all like 2016, 2017 with Oculus Rift and PlayStation VR.
In the same way that they close Stitch's Great Escape right before they announce
a Stitch live action film, they close Country Bears right before
the Country Bears movie is released.
Some of this timing is very, some of their timing is very bad.
And let's not forget that we're going.
Oh, no, I was going to say talking about crazy timing.
The Chicago one closed September 4th, 2001.
The very month that the first Strokes record.
No, never forget.
No wonder September 2001 looms so large.
And I knew it was something.
This is it. Never forget.
So all right. Here's.
So this enterprise is in theory thriving.
The Disney World one opens and probably does fine for a little bit.
Enough to not change the plans of opening Chicago.
They opened Chicago in a lavish ceremony.
And oh, yeah, the stars, including Melissa Joan Hart,
Joan Cusack and no other stars.
I'm sorry, John. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And Amir and Chicago's favorite mayor, Richard Daly was there.
Oh, is that right?
That's interesting.
The only way it happened.
Daily gave it the OK.
Richard Daly, somehow a better mayor than Rahm Emanuel.
Incredible. So much better somehow.
Anyway, so crazed by the opening ceremony.
I love it, by the way, you get to see everybody in Chicago.
Got to see Buzz Lightyear flying around on a jetpack to the fan.
Yes, yes, that's fantastic.
I wrote that down. Yeah, that's that's very cool.
So we're we're hopping now.
We got two Disney quests.
We're building the third.
And then it just all falls apart.
And and it's you know, I think they could have started to change them out.
And like all of the all of the locations, one that was doing less well
could have sustained others that were I'm sorry,
one Disney quest are doing better, could have sustained ones
that weren't doing as much business, but they only got to the two.
And the Chicago one was tanking.
And I think all of the rest of Disney regional entertainment club, Disney,
this like kids, this little kids experience did really badly.
ESPN never did great.
It just all kind of collapsed.
This whole thing.
Yeah. Philadelphia never opened.
There was going to be a Toronto.
They even picked a location, which today is kind of a little fake
Times Square in Toronto.
It's just that's like movie theaters and stuff.
Now there was going to be one in Anaheim, potentially.
I couldn't find where they intended to put that,
but probably somewhere in downtown Disney.
They were going to, you know, demolish the pirates and put it there.
So it all just started to collapse.
Chicago closes in 2001, canceled Philadelphia.
And then so presumably the closure of Disney World would be to follow.
But it doesn't. It stays open, but never updates.
They just lose elements piece by piece.
The price gets kind of cheaper and cheaper.
There's more like weird deals to get in there,
but there's less and less to do there.
It just becomes like, I don't know, here's a bunch of arcade games or it.
It all like it just was they put like their decay.
Yeah, strangely for so long.
I don't think I realized when we went in 20.
What do we go for 2014?
I think I don't think I realized it was there like you still.
I didn't think I was like, oh, my God, why?
It felt like it was gone for 10 years before that.
There there is an article.
There's a Chicago Tribune article that is so it's so crazy.
To me, because it's before or right around when it was opening.
And I've never seen a news article be like an like an omen.
Like it's right. Yeah, it's not going to work like all.
Here's the quote from Art Levitt himself.
By the nature of it, location based entertainment is difficult to succeed in.
We've got to learn the hard way and see what we do.
Like they already knew like this is going to be hard to accomplish.
And there's stuff in the dimension, the defunct land.
But it's in a bunch of articles to that, like for it to have been profitable,
that would have had to run full capacity 17 hours a day or so.
And yeah, that's never going to.
And if they're your ideal amount of time is two hours.
The numbers never made sense on this.
And also just the base.
How did they not realize people don't want to go to downtown Chicago,
go to a windowless building and play already out of the arc?
Things that suck. Yeah. Yeah.
Like, I don't understand how.
Yeah, even I understand that you invested a bunch of money.
And the certain points are like, well, just open in Orlando.
And let's see if we can get them make the money back that we spend.
But it does seem like you're going to lose more money
opening a full another one in Chicago, which is a weird market to do it.
You have like most of these people had to know this stuff sucked.
The novelty of like they had to be like, we have Disney World.
We know what an experience is that satisfying feels like.
But what almost none of this feels like that.
What if I were to tell you about one very special night
where all the stars in the 1990 sky got to experience Disney Quest?
Not in Chicago. No, in Orlando.
You say to what you refer, Jason.
Oh, why? There's an Orlando Sentinel article
about how one night Ian's earring
I am hearing I am hearing the voice of the.
He's in the Mighty Ducks.
The main one wild wing.
Uh, Lacey Shebert, Shebert, Shebert, Party by Me girls.
Jody Lynn O'Caffey.
I forget what show she was.
Star is coming.
Keep the stars coming in sync.
Uh huh.
Well, they're a manager.
Nicky Lipnicki.
What about Nsync's manager?
I don't know if he was there.
He shouldn't be allowed in Disney Quest without a child.
To see it.
And they also all enjoyed it.
If you can believe that I can.
The first place I saw the celebrities taking part
in the Disney Quest activity was at the Mighty Ducks pinball slam game.
I got a good glimpse of Justin, Joey, Lance, J.C.
and Chris of Nsync, Jonathan,
like Mickey from Jerry Maguire and Ziering as they played a life size pinball game.
Lipnicki what?
That's for the reporter.
You mean Justin?
Yeah, they all they're all professional dancers.
They should know how to pivot better than anybody.
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, I guess that proves that Nsync sucks.
They're idiots.
Lipnicki rules.
But I guess it also shows that for one magical night in 1998 or so,
everything at Disney Quest was perfect.
And that's really what you were able to do until 2017 is go experience
the vibe of a perfect 1998 night.
I found a review of this place from 11 years ago on WDW Magic.
And it sounds like it was written by a person in the company for PR purposes.
But it supposedly was from a fan.
And there must be people that did have a good time is what I'm
is where I'm getting at with this.
This headline of this review is OMG.
I loved this written by a person named Mouse Worshipper.
Although I guess that's suspicious.
Me and my bro were teens, adored this.
The flashing lights, noisy games, being a teen and virtual technology rock hard.
But when I took my mom and 20 something aunt at their own request,
despite all my warnings, they freaked out with overstimulation.
Both of them were totally exhausted by the end.
But for teens, trustworthy enough to be released from parental supervision,
even if the adults are just somewhere else in downtown Disney, it's not to be missed.
Contrary to popular belief, almost everything comes with cost of
admission aside from food, go Cheesecake Factory Express.
That does sound fake, but like, what would be the point of a fake
like a bot, a Russian bot posting on WDW Magic 11 years ago under the name Mouse Worshipper?
I had so much fun.
It really distracted me from the pressure of my balls dropping.
Anyway, signed off me a real teen.
Me and my sister, ages 12 to 15.
I found a video on YouTube from like 2012 where a kid is very sarcastically reading
the synopsis of the Ride the Comics, like outside of the building, like by the box office.
And then he turns the camera around and goes, sounds great for 1994.
And that's great.
Slam. It's very caustic to watch.
It's very unpleasant to watch.
Me after this, I have yet to debut that footage that exists of me
goofing on University of Energy after I went on it when I was like 10.
Oh, yeah. Is that a Patreon exclusive?
That's a Patreon exclusive, I think.
Mike own University of Energy.
While Death Comedy Jam music plays in the background.
Oh, shit.
So that's the tale of Disney Quest.
Yeah, I know.
Look, we've been talking for a while and I don't I don't think I
I don't feel like we should do a full like plus it up, but I do have a very quick plus it up idea,
which is Windows.
I truly think the entire business changes with two windows in Chicago.
You can look out a window on the fifth floor and probably see a cool view of something in Chicago.
What are we do? Why would this?
I think that's all it would take a little bit of natural light.
There's nothing central to the premise.
The windows would have disrupted my plus it up is keep it open for another year.
Redo it to make it look nicer and then put all the stuff you're making for other things into it.
Put the Millennium Falcon right into it.
Put the Wreck-It Ralph ride that's coming to Florida into it.
Put two levels of different void experiences into it.
Great. People will be like, oh, wow, that all the stuff is very cool.
We really like that.
Do you think that somebody like hit a demolition button
like and boom, it imploded and then like checked their phone
and saw a headline that says VR all the rage.
No, god damn it.
It's too late. Yes, that's what I think happened.
Jason, bring it back just as is.
But put an Atlantis game in it where you get to play as Milo.
He said that looking to the ceiling longingly.
I'm surprised you didn't say bring it back, but get rid of everything
except for the Cheesecake Factory Express.
I mean, it's crazy.
There has not been a cheesecake factory at any of the downtown Disney.
That is an odd oversight, I believe, as a cheese.
Oh, really? Smart. Oh, smart.
Yes. That's why the Chinese will eventually rule us.
Yeah. And for and and for the donors who give us
three thousand dollars a month, we will have dinner with you
at the Shanghai Disneyland Cheesecake Factory.
Pay for us to fly out, though. Yeah.
We're asking a lot here, but you're getting a lot.
You're getting a meal encounter that will take less time
than the podcast you just listened to.
So anyways, that you've with that,
you survived podcast, the ride, the second gate.
Should there be some way to sequelify it?
Like it's too you too vived.
I'll figure out how to make it.
Well, for this specific one, I do want to survive.
I could throw that through the vocoder like it's if it was a cyber
sign off or something, but that would be specific to this.
Yeah. All right.
Let's get the whiteboard out, put a pot of coffee on.
We got to figure this out.
We got to figure out how to change the catchphrase.
But for now, we will take the cyber later back down to the bottom floor
and let you out.
But seriously, thank you for listening to the first episode of this thing.
I want to say the people who have
presumably followed us here, unless no one did.
It's possible you're talking to no one.
Yes, could be.
But that's the risk you run with any podcast.
But the people who have like been into this support of this,
you've wanted this kind of thing.
I've just been especially through the city walk saga.
People were so nice.
Yes. All of that.
And this podcast in general.
And thanks for wanting more and encouraging us to do more.
Y'all are great.
We're going to give you some fun stuff here.
Yeah. And we're we're sometimes we're a little cynical, you know,
but we would like to say thank you.
That's like the best I can do because people think I'm always joking
when I'm saying something sincerely, but I am saying thank you for doing this.
Yeah. You said something right before recording.
And I meant it sincerely.
It's not like I was trying to own.
We'll do that. So weird.
Yeah. It was like a problem.
And you would just usually toss it off.
But it came out so weird.
Even I was like, what the fuck was that?
Kind of a stare of daggers.
It was weird, too, because I remember going like I remember
coming out and going, man, what was that?
Like it was we were all shocked is what I'm saying.
We were all surprised at what I said.
Yeah. Or how I said it.
Boy, the pre-show jitters, I think, just made
unnecessary sarcasm explode out of you.
It happened. I'm sorry.
Because we felt a lot of pressure because this was the first.
Right. Second gate.
And we wanted to deliver and we hope you enjoyed it.
Forcing Mike to relive his childhood tummy troubles, you know, and brain trouble
and brain.
All that's so true.
It's just our every podcast is a brain trouble.
Yeah. Revealing their brain troubles.
There's a lot of weird psychosis in all of these experiences,
and we'll delve into all that.
So as always, follow us to podcast the right on Twitter
and email us to podcast the right at Gmail.
But with the with the specific thing, seriously, if there's things that you
want to hear us do
with the second gate, send us mailbag questions, send us lost and found ideas.
And put that stuff in the subject line.
That always helps. Lost and found.
Or organized. Yeah.
It's we want you to put the the topics into different zones
so that we can very cleanly organize them in our mind.
Right. So remember, the zones are different than the levels.
Right. So right what level it is and right what zone it is and what color it is as well,
because there's also color that corresponds to the zones, but not the levels.
The levels don't have a specific color.
Yes. And our tag colors, we're tagging email.
That's actually different than the colors.
But you don't have to worry about that.
That's our burden to bear. Yeah, we'll take care of that.
But we can't we have a lot on our plates and we can't be the navigators to navigate
for us, would you? Yeah. All right. Well, we'll see you.
See you in the next zone. Bye.