Forever...
Dog.
Please, hauntcast the fright.
Welcome to hauntcast the fright, a show hosted by two scaredy boys that are afraid of theme park Halloween mazes
and one big brave boy who overcame his haunted maze fear at not scary farm last night.
I am said big brave boy, Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, two scaredy boys, Jason Sheridan.
I had some excuses.
Alright, that's fine, we'll get into all of this, but I'm boasting hard up top here because I'm feeling very triumphant after my night at not scary farm.
And also Scott Gardner is here.
Dan scaredy, I got no excuses, but whatever. I'm my own man, I can do what I want to do.
I feel alive for one of the first times in my life, going through six mazes last night at not scary farm.
Can you believe that?
It's a lot.
And I'm not, this wasn't a fake thing that I was afraid of these mazes, I was just as scared as you guys were.
I don't like this, I don't like college students jumping out and putting their hands in my face.
You know, here's the thing.
You might be correct to phrase it as scared, I could see that take, but there's another take that is I don't want to do this.
Even if I wasn't scared, it doesn't sound like pleasant.
I did a single maze, we will get into that.
I did it. I wouldn't describe my feeling during it as being scared, I'd describe it more as annoyed and irritated.
I'd rather be at home.
Well, I think that the thing is you've got to get used to the people throwing their arms at you and yelling.
And then once you get used to the mazes, then you start to enjoy all the things we like about theme parks, the theming, the design, all that interesting stuff, the effects.
I can get used to my couch and a bottle of wine.
That's a good excuse to not go anywhere then, isn't it?
That's better than anything, really.
It truly is.
Scott Gardner at 33.
Yeah, I mean that's fair. Why should we do anything?
Let's all just become drunks.
Let's not go nowhere.
Sounds like Scott's going down the Jackson Maine route.
I know he wants me to stop talking about A Star Is Born.
The jump to drunk from enjoying a glass of wine.
You were drunker than me. You were the drunk one at the event.
But last night?
Weren't you? You drank more than I did last night.
I had a mango beer and then I had a Stella Artois.
You're still drunk right now.
So listeners, what this episode, we're talking Halloween Horror Nights and Knott's Berry Farm.
This is not a comprehensive one.
There's a little peek behind the scenes.
We got some to look at how some of this stuff got made.
We've been saying for a long time that we were doing this podcast and we wanted invites to things.
We wanted people to invite us theme park journalists to different events, to different happenings.
And we wanted to get free things and we wanted to look backstage and peek behind the curtain.
And we've been very lucky now and we've gotten a couple cool things that we have gotten to do.
Number one we're going to talk about here is that Universal invited one of us to go check out their new maze,
which is based on the TV show Stranger Things.
And we sent our cub reporter, Jason Sheridan.
My mother will be thrilled that I finally put the two years of an unfinished journalism degree to work.
Yes.
What was your college?
Press badge.
Well, I switched to TV production halfway through.
But you actually did like you would call from college, you would call like Hollywood people, like agents to get confirmation on stories for your local papers.
Like I did a like a long like 30 page feature for like an assignment where I like talk to the editors in chief at the time of only press and top shelf productions.
A couple journalists who cover what is top shelf.
They're like, yeah, you're comics publishers.
There was a thing you had to call an agent about.
Yes, there was.
So this yeah, I was an intern at the Philadelphia Weekly, weekly news kind of Philadelphia is equivalent to like the village voice.
I was an intern there one summer and I had already changed my major, but I had already been offered the internship and they were just like, yeah, you know, any any work is as good as the neck.
I mean, like any internship at this point, I think it was coming out of my sophomore year and I was just kind of interested in doing something in the media that summer.
So I worked at Philadelphia Weekly and they I thought it was a very smart move.
The interns were mostly there.
There was like six to ten of us and we were the fact checkers.
We would fact check articles and call sources and double check stuff that was in the articles.
One thing that I had double check was there was they kind of in a way that didn't mesh with the rest of the paper.
There were horror scopes that tried to weave in like gossip like us weekly kind of gossip to like, well, Taurus, you're you're in for a romantic week, much like who would have the star of like 2005 been like romantic couples.
So Vari, I drew Barrymore married to Drew Barrymore, Justin Long, just Drew Barrymore and Justin Long are an example of this, like that sort of thing.
And one of my one of the ones was that, you know, about Sandra Bullock and Jesse James.
Oh, right. So that's you called her agent.
So but what I found was like I was trying I asked the writer, like, where did you source this from?
And I found the article and the article was from that week, but the previous year.
So they fucked up and I told the editors and they're like, well, call Sandra Bullock's agent for comment.
And how old were you this time?
I was 19 years old and at the time E, I don't think was on IMDb and we didn't have IMDb Pro, but E like E.com indexed the television network indexed like two rep what people.
So I called the main line for like either William Morris or CIA.
I got through to an assistant and I said, hey, I'm calling from the Philadelphia Weekly and they're like, oh, OK, well, let me put you on with the other available.
Let me ask. And I did the same. Hi, I'm calling from the Philadelphia Weekly.
We're a weekly paper in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
The person went, I know where Philadelphia is.
And I said, is there any truth to this?
And they're like, what? No.
Where are you? Where do you call?
And I was like, look, I'm just an inter.
I'm just fact check in a little pop culture part of the better.
There's no truth to that rumor.
So then whatever Libra or Taurus for that week did not have a pop culture.
They just stripped out that sentence that unregularly part.
Yes. So when we were deciding which the three of us should go, this is why I decided Jason should be the guy to do it.
He deals with Hollywood bigwigs all the time.
You're essentially you were a little like kid Ronan Farrow.
Yeah, I used to drive the American Gladiators.
So they drove one of them to their physical.
Like they flew in an American Gladiator to a reporter's job would be.
I don't know. I just talked about the interactions with stars.
It is a scoop, though, that one of the American Gladiators had some health issues.
It was illegal. It was just a basic physical before they could get in the arena.
They made it. OK. So you waited in like the waiting room for one of the Beverly Hills doctor and then drove them back to the airport.
American Gladiator was it? I don't know. They were a prick.
I don't want to talk about it.
Another glacier.
This was like this was this was not one of the main ones and they were really weird.
And they leaned out of the car when like the police there was a lot of police at the airport and they're like, hey, this guy's up to no good about me driving.
And I'm like, I am not being paid dog shit.
Wow. I don't think I've actually heard the story of you driving an American Gladiator to a doctor's office.
Yeah, that's great. All right. Anyway, we got to go back to the universal.
Anyway, so, yeah, I went up there to tour the Stranger Things maze.
I got to go in at Walters Gate and get a little, you know, a badge.
You know, Walters Gate. It was like me and like 10 other outlets.
And, you know, they put us to talk to them. Who are they?
I know. It's one. It's a bumper car boys.
And it's like it's he looks exactly like you, but with a mustache.
I know I didn't. I don't know.
It was kind of like we all got there and they put us in a van and they got us in the toy was pretty quick.
Or you got to go in a van to go from the like city walk down to the soundstage.
So because the so the Stranger Things maze this year is in soundstage stage 29, which is a huge soundstage.
They said it was used in like the Grinch and Jurassic Park when I was an intern at Universal on the back lot.
I just remember the tour guides going like and that soundstage was used in a movie we shot recently called Land of the Lost.
So this was it was huge. Probably used in Evan Almighty.
I feel like they were talking about Evan Almighty when I worked there.
There were a lot of like arc pieces.
That's my first summer.
Yeah, that was like two or three sound stages for that.
That was a real, real production endeavor.
And then also giant sets in North Carolina.
The most expensive comedy of all time.
Yeah. At the time.
Yeah, that worked out.
The but so that this is interesting that they're universals really spreading onto the back lot.
If you don't know the layout of Universal Studios, there's this upper part up on the level that a city walk is.
And then you take escalators down to the bottom and that's a much smaller area of the theme park.
And it's really literally right next door to the soundstage is where your favorite movies and TV shows are made.
And they're like really spreading out a lot more recently onto the back lot, including is it the Poltergeist maze?
One of them is like very deep into the New York back lot sets.
Yeah, really long walk.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, they've kind of built the mazes are built up around the sort of wherever they can get the space because as they pointed out on the tour and I got the tour from Universal Creative Director John Murty,
who's like a longtime Universal employee, really kind of oversaw and kickstarted Horror Nights coming back to Hollywood.
Was it open in the 90s a little and then closed?
I think that's yeah, I think they did a little Halloween stuff.
But I think 2006 is about when they really started going all out with Horror Nights out here.
Once it really started to like cook in Florida.
Gotcha.
Well, because by the time I in 2007, my second year with the tour guide program, I got to I worked on the terror tram.
Yes, which was my favorite thing ever because you didn't have to do the tour.
It was all about time killing and all about bullshitting.
And it was like for sure could be tedious and you might go like, oh, I'm like stuck in one place for 40 minutes with like no material.
But man, I did like I did so much dumb stuff.
There used to be a video of me on YouTube and I don't know what of doing it.
I don't remember what happened. But I was very proud.
You talk about John Murty. I was I believe John Murty himself emailed me and said, I saw your video of you doing the tour.
And I was very scared of what was coming because people had been fired very quickly from that event for using too foul of language.
And I was worried I'd done something fireable.
But instead, he said, you know, most of your thing I don't think would work for wouldn't translate to other guides.
But there's one thing you said I liked so much. I'm going to put it in the script next year.
Wow. Do you remember what it was?
I do. It was that I kind of did the whole thing and sort of even like all the functional stuff I did in like a devil voice that would sort of fade awkwardly as a mumble through boring parts of it.
I don't smoke. And at the beginning, I said something about like like Halloween is a frightful time when chaos reigns and there are no rules.
That being said, there are a few rules.
And and I intended to go over well and they put it in the script and I was really honored.
But then I went back the next year and just got to hear people just plow through that and do that with no timing.
And like Halloween is a time of chaos where there are no rules. That being said, there are a few rules.
It was pretty funny watching the line get like just steamrolled by it.
But I was still that's a really solid like theme park joke.
Hey, thanks. Yeah, that was not I wasn't always like doing things totally counter to the spirit of the place.
I like trying to think of like a good reel like doesn't.
Oh, sure. Yeah, we are good boys.
No, I didn't I may have like, you know, I they said you could be like PG 13.
What do you think the sauce thing you said was?
Oh, I think I made might have made an abortion joke.
Oh, wow. I don't remember what it was, but I remember getting kind of a ooh, which then like this guy, the John Murty, like watched whatever this abortion joke was.
Put me in the Bill and Ted.
Oh my gosh. Spooktacular for these. Yeah, that's that's pretty dicey.
If I can remember what the abortion was joke.
Well, we'll post that video of it.
Yeah, if I can check down the 12 year old abortion joke, go back in your files.
I'm sure it'll hold up just fine.
But the story I remember that I liked a lot was that, you know, they told us you could be a little more.
Sure. You could swear and stuff.
And so here's a profanity warning for anyone listening who doesn't like when we use profanities, but I feel like I have to for this.
But the I remember a female tour guide pulling out of the area and saying like, well, now we're no longer in earshot of my bosses.
And they said we kind of do what we want on this thing.
So fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
And she was wrong. They were we were she was still completely within earshot of the bosses.
And when the tour came back around, people were waiting for her and she was escorted out.
Again, that but that to me seems like copacetic for horror nights.
Yeah, but I don't I think it's not if you watch any of those like the Bill and Ted show, which we'll get into later.
But the there's maybe you get shit.
I know. I think. OK, maybe that's the line.
It's in the weird. It's like the weird American like censorship, like what gets censored and what doesn't.
And it's like certain words.
I don't know. I'm not turning on the George Carlin routine here.
But like those two words are off limits.
But you can make a lot of offensive jokes about gay people or something.
That's right. Yeah.
That's a shit. Baby boomers do not like profanity, even though the sky is on fire, like even though the country, the world is eating itself and heating up.
Yeah. And they're more mad when they're not mad at Trump for using awful language and saying awful things.
They're mad at the channel for talking about it.
But like but they he said it. It's weird to why are you mad at the why are you mad at the person who said the bad word?
Yeah. Yes. Yeah. There's a lot of a lot of twisted values in this country here in this Halloween season.
But let's talk about something more fun. Sure.
Jason Sheridan on the scene. My other horror nights experience was that I when I interned in a production company in one of the bungalows on the back lot, I had to park like I had a little bit of a walk to where my parking assignment was.
And it was I got to go through I would go through the New York streets to take a shortcut.
And I was there like late one Friday, like when horror nights, I knew horror nights was starting in like an hour.
And I was like, I want to get the hell to my car because it is dark now.
And I know the ghoulies and goblins are coming out.
So and that would have been one of the first years they were really going all out.
Yes. So this person is a big oh sorry.
And I'm jumping around. Yeah.
John Murray, a big deal in the universal world, like probably really helped popularize this events and oversaw it and like and kind of like primarily overseas.
This this is like the main thing he does and he only he comes to L.A. for this only he mentioned in the tour that he lives in Ireland now and telecommutes for this.
But like for the right leading up to our nights he is here working on it.
Excuse me. And runs the runs himself.
I'm sure other people use it, too, but runs the horror nights Twitter account.
So you can tweet directly at John Murdy on the official horror nights Twitter account.
And he is very open.
And he was very clear about like, you know, we like that the fans tweet at us and that's where we pull ideas from every now and then, including the Stranger Things Mace.
He said like as soon as that was up on Netflix, people were like, you have to do a maze of this.
And I have to say it was very cool to go through that.
He said very rarely are they given access to a full size soundstage to build the mazes in that's a whole other stuff.
Sometimes these mazes are jammed into like where the line is for another attraction and to have an entire year, an entire soundstage.
And what is happening is they're demolishing a lot of the sound stages that are right up against the theme park for future expansion.
And you can really see how much they've cleared, although we were told, please do not take pictures of construction.
And I have some pictures that I'll post on the show accounts of the construction.
No, of the maze construction.
We were we were told there are parts of the maze we could take pictures of.
But those other pictures later, though, I take any I can show you on a map.
So this was a funny detail about that soundstage two months before we were there.
And before they started to build out, it was the Family Feud set.
Like they were filming Family Feud and then emptied it out and started building the Stranger Things maze in there.
Cool fact, playa. Yeah.
Steve Harvey might say.
It is a full soundstage with like the rat with a catwalks and rafters.
They had talked about using they were able to use part of stage seven forty seven one year.
Which uses airplane like your interiors.
I think they got it.
Oh, really? OK. Yeah.
But they were able to get access to some of that.
But Horror Nights is fascinating because I mean, a lot of haunts have to share space with operating theme parks.
But this is sharing space with operating theme parks and a full working movie studio.
And then they essentially build a theme park within the theme park and movie studio that runs for 31 nights of the year.
Yeah. And so much.
And this was kind of recurring when we got to talk to the nots people, which we'll get into later.
But you it all the amount of effort that goes into this single month begs the question, how do you do the park for the rest of the year?
Because they were saying the nots people were saying we're already thinking about what's going on in 2019.
We're not even close to through 2018.
It's such an immense layer of production on top of the typical theme park stuff.
The nots people were saying that they are secretly starting to put up Christmas stuff and you can't see what it like in the background.
Christmas stuff is going up like it nots already.
So like it's such a like everything they have to be on top of everything so far in advance to get all this stuff done and to get stuff built, as you're saying, in either just a working theme park or a theme park and a movie studio and TV production.
Like it is crazy to kind of have to manage all of that.
Some of the mazes, he said, like a lot of them, they start to build sometime between like late May and Fourth of July, and then they kind of stagger.
So they're not starting them all at once.
But yeah, the Stranger Things maze, like two, three months out from opening.
And this is kind of the marquee maze.
This is on all the promotional material, a lot of the merchandise.
There's Stranger Things based food at Horror Nights.
Wow.
And yeah, so the gist of the maze, I mean, I don't want to.
Horror Nights has been running for a little while by the time this is up.
I don't think I really have any spoilers, spoilers, but it's basically like the set pieces from season one.
So you go through the buyer house, the house that Winona Ryder and the two boys live in.
The letters are on the walls and the Christmas lights are strung up that he uses to communicate with from the upside down.
They were talking about having to get to wire these lights because Christmas lights are like on a strand.
And if one goes out, they all go out and they're like, oh, we need we need to be able to control these lights.
So they had to figure out how to wire these lights so they could control them more individually.
So what should be like the easiest effect potentially just go by Christmas lights has to be manipulated in this crazy way.
And then the attention to detail in the house is is really impressive because, you know, you're thinking like the show takes place in the 1980s.
But the buyer family doesn't have a lot of money.
So a lot of their stuff is secondhand from the 70s.
So there's like this kind of bicentennial sort of wall wallpaper of like colonial people in the boys room or something.
And like there's a very shat like orangey couch in the one thing.
Yeah. So that's where they were like the production designers of the show involved.
Do we know? I know a lot of I mean, Horror Nights has their own like production staff and they're able to pull from some stuff from like the Universal Prop Department.
But then they're just like also scouting like yard sales and estate sales all around Southern California to find like period appropriate stuff for this maze and all the other bases.
So cool. And then like the I'm not so up on Stranger Things.
Was it like a like just was it accurate?
It's all is like walking onto the set.
And there's some stuff where I think in the like so you go through the house and then you go into like you go by like the little castle buyer, the little fort the kid builds in the backyard.
You go through the upside down. And that is an interest.
That room is like a black room with like some props and like hanging fiber optics.
And there's also they were putting in projection effects later to make it look like this weird trippy experience.
And he's like there's stuff in here from the set. There's stuff in here from the Stranger Things set.
And like Murty had to, you know, write a treatment, send it to the Duffer Brothers to get their OK.
And they have like approval like J.K. Rowling.
Yeah, they have approval and like first pass got approved by one Duffer but not Duffer two.
Yeah. Duff one and Duff two.
He made it sound like this one. I know some like they've had to.
I'm sure the Shining Maze working with like the Kubrick people and whatever studio owns that was insanely complicated.
But this one, it seemed like the Duffer Brothers like, no, we know horror.
We come to Horror Nights every year. We're into it. So we're very excited.
Yeah. But like the attention to be like Murty talked about just going through and like he said it took him eight hours to go through each episode to like pull to like pick sound cues.
It's like, oh, I need that. I need that.
And then we're able to get access to the actors to record like some audio and use audio because in the past they have not been able to get people.
So John has been like, I have done the voice of Freddy Krueger before.
He has done Freddy Krueger or like they got people in house to do stuff.
I'm assuming this is a similar but when I was about the and we'll get to Nats, but when I got about to my third or fourth maze and I calmed down a little bit more, I started to notice that they have these cues.
Like the scares are on like music cues, which I didn't quite notice until I was in like four or five and I my brain was less worried.
And then I was like, I noticed in a room like a sting happens and then somebody jumped out like right on the sting.
So like they're doing stuff like that.
And these may you got ahead of it a little recognizing that pattern.
Yeah, I mean, yeah, it was in this, but maybe it was more so in this specific maze I was in.
But I noticed I did just that was the first time I had noticed that that they're like a whole there must be like every 45 seconds that sting happens.
And then this one scare happens.
So like their timing stuff, like what you're saying, like with with people saying things in dialogue and music to match up with 25 year olds jumping out at you and scaring you.
And here's another thing that you all may have noticed.
They're scaring you from from an angle from the left or the right.
They are not getting directly in your path.
This is a thing that came because someone else in the tour asked, has anyone ever gotten punched in the like jumps out against punches them in the face?
And he's like, the way we work around that is we scare from the angle, pop out, pop back or like from the angle below.
This is all stuff that after Mays three or four, your brain starts getting a little more used to of like, OK, they're not going to come at me dead on.
They're really not going to block me.
I'm going to get maybe jumped a little like I'm going to be a jumpy.
But yeah, it's very interesting to sort of figure out then the mechanics of the whole thing after.
Because because really for the first couple of days, I was just like, oh, just like that noise in my brain for, you know, five minutes of the major other big thing.
They cannot touch you. Right.
They cannot touch you the way when they audition actors, once a scare actors.
One thing John said they do.
They put a chair in the center of the room and they say, scare the chair.
And they just kind of have you just kind of have to like act like it's a person and scare around it.
And he's like, if anyone touches the chair, they're cut.
They're out of there. Wow. You have to get as close as you can and get as committed as you can.
Like this is like a real actor like theater exercise.
That's like in the first Ninja Turtles with the bell where the ninjas have to go and get the bell without it making it ring.
They attach like a bell to a dummy and you have to prove that like you're worthy ninja by removing the bell.
And then I think it's yeah, this is the first one because Raphael helps that ninja kid and then they remove all the bells without making a sound.
So it's like this weird precision where you have to get as close as possible, but not disturb the actual chair.
Yeah. So the guy who tried to gnaw on the chair and tear it in half with his mouth did not pass.
We should all audition to be scare actors, not maybe do it, but all the audition to see if we can pass.
Maybe do it. Fine. We'll do it. I don't care.
I mean, they were very clear actually at both Knotts and Universal that it's like scare.
The people who do the scare acting are from all walks. Some of the people are professional actors.
Some of the people have nine to five jobs.
John was talking about a guy who's like, I work all day at my job and then I sleep for a couple of hours under my desk and then I come to Universal and do it.
And he's like, how do you keep this up? And some people do it for five, 10, 20 years.
They just love doing it. And there is a real camaraderie among everyone doing it.
The way he described it sounds very familiar. It sounds like a theater company, sort of like we're all in this together.
We're all putting on the show. And like the last night of the haunts, like there's like, you know, people are very emotional because it's like they well, we all did this.
We all put the show on. We all went through this.
Sometimes there's a all screamed wedding proposal.
What are you doing? I have been my wife and only.
Angle. They don't touch each other. They jump back and forth at angles.
The ring is not actually touched.
What else? Yeah. So you go through, like I said, a lot of this piece that you end up in the lab.
The. And there's all that we just clarify. It's with the lights on.
So there's no scary actors in there. This is lights on when I went through it.
Yeah. Yeah. So this was yeah, it was a press. Oh, this was yes.
Well, we should say because we also and not not scary farm.
We got a preview of some mazes which when which we slowly walked through them without actors and with all of the lights on.
And I'll tell you, I had a wonderful time. Very impressive.
Very impressive. I'm just there to see the molding and, you know, I didn't go on the mazes in the dark with scare actors.
Yeah, both of them. You sure did.
For you. I'm going to brag about it as much as I can.
You see the lab, you see the upside down and they're working like up until the night before.
It was still a construction site. Basically, when you were there.
It was a construction site, as you will hear in a few minutes because I got to talk to John, do a short interview with John and you may hear some construction sounds in the background.
But there's like dust in the air. We could hear hammers and drills and everything.
Did you have to wear a hard hat?
No, they just closed toed shoes was the only request.
Closed toed shoes. Yeah. Okay.
I think that was in the email request.
But that's any shoe.
No, like no flip flops or sandals.
Oh, no, not those. It's sneakers. You didn't have to wear boots.
That's what I'm saying.
What else? Okay. This I thought was interesting.
So the monster and stranger things, the Demogorgon, which they very quickly showed us the pictures of like the mask that the actors would be wearing.
It's insanely detailed.
There's like because they have to rotate through actors like, you know, you're not an actor is a scare actor is not.
It's not there's not one debt.
There's like 15 to 16 Demogorgons every night because they show up at different parts in the maze.
Depending on what they're doing, they maybe they're running like a 30 minutes on set, 30 minutes offset to recover from that.
Although some are just impartial makes of they're just the hand or just the upper half.
They may be able to go a little longer.
Yeah. Should we play the interview?
Yeah. I'm just trying to think if there's anything, any other context.
Yeah. So we went through the maze, asked some questions.
Everyone kind of chined in. Tell us more about the van ride.
Yeah. What kind of van was it? Just squeeze in within a row.
I guess there is a van service that's like four universal employees that goes from the upper lot to the lower lot,
especially with horror nights running and they're working all over the was the driver entertaining?
Like, is he do any jokes like the tram tour guide would?
Very nice. I mean, there was also like PAs and office workers and stuff.
The thing that was interesting to me, the talent building, there was dozens and dozens of people like filling out their start work,
like scare actors and temporary season liars. So crazy time over there.
Yeah. And you weren't but you weren't inspired to jump into the fray and say, you know, I like it.
This is my home. Sign me up. Well, it felt like a conflict of interest.
So but maybe we'll conflict that interest if we all become scare actors.
If you can find us in the park next year. Yeah.
So, yeah, like I said, so at the end of the tour, I got to talk to John for a few minutes and we'll play that right now.
John, thanks so much for talking to me today.
I guess just to get started, what do you think sets Halloween Horror Nights apart from other haunts?
I think first and foremost, it's the attention to detail that we put into everything we do,
whether it's a horror movie or a horror television show.
Our ultimate goal is always the same.
It's to make our guests feel as if they're living that particular horror movie or horror TV show.
The thing I always say is it should feel as if you got up off your couch and step through the TV screen or you got out of your movie seat and step through the movie screen.
And now you're in the world of the horror movie and you're living it and it's coming for you.
And that's what we try to do with everything that we do for the horror nights.
So we put an awful lot of attention into the scenic, the props, the set dressing, the lighting, the audio, everything to serve the story of what we're telling.
Great. This question is very specific to our show.
Myself and my co-hosts are what's known as Little Scaredy Cats, who are easily startled and frightened.
What advice would you have for us for overcoming our fears and attending an event like this?
Good luck.
No, but there's, you know, I always think Halloween is and things like this are very similar to like riding a roller coaster for the first time.
It's facing your fears much in the same way as when you're a kid and you're looking at that big roller coaster that you've never ridden before.
And the other thing I've noticed over time is that people who go through our mazes at horror nights, it's very much the same experience as riding a roller coaster.
When people come off a roller coaster, what do they usually do?
They usually laugh, you know, because it's that release of nervous energy.
And a lot of times when you see people come out of a maze, even though they've been terrified, they start laughing because it's the same release of energy.
So, you know, I would in your mind think you're going to ride the craziest roller coaster that goes upside down and has 400 foot drops.
And you'll be in the right mentality for horror nights and just do that like eight times.
Yeah, pretty much all night long.
Some other haunts in the Southern California area have kind of upped the ante with things like putting a burlap sack over your head or simulating kidnapping.
Any desire to get into that area?
No.
No?
No, I mean, the great thing about the haunt industry is that particularly if you're in Los Angeles, there's so many different places you can go and experience.
And there's so many different flavors to the art of scaring people.
What we do is a very specific thing where we're trying to bring to life movies and television shows.
But no, I don't have any desire to put a bag over your head.
Yeah, I don't have any desire to do it myself.
One last thing I noticed looking at the horror nights websites for Orlando and Hollywood.
Why are they called haunted houses in Orlando?
Why are they called mazes out here?
Yeah, Orlando calls them houses and we call them mazes.
And recently we were both, Mike Aiello, who is my creative counterpart in Orlando, and myself and my art director Chris were speaking at a convention called Midsummer Scream.
And I solicited on Twitter, you know, I asked the fans, hey, send me questions you'd like to ask, you know, Mike or myself or Chris.
And one of the first questions I got was that same question.
Why are they called houses in Orlando and why are they called mazes in Halloween?
And the answer is we don't really know.
They've always been called that.
And as long as you know, as I've been around, I've been doing horror nights since 2006.
And, you know, it had a history prior to me going back to even as early as the mid 1980s.
They did it.
And back then they were they were called mazes out here and they were called houses in Orlando.
And we have no idea why.
So I know that's an unsatisfactory answer.
No, that's the truth.
That's great.
Frankly, I think mazes sound scary because you could get trapped in a maze.
Well, we call mazes a lot of times because the physical construction of them is like a maze.
And when you're walking around in these things, you can easily get lost if you don't know your way around.
So that's always been like a way we refer to it.
Orlando since the beginning of horror nights in Orlando has called them houses.
So it's just a weird East Coast, West Coast thing.
Sure. Well, thanks so much, John.
Sure. My pleasure.
OK, so John's advice, you know, you just kind of overcome it again and again.
Scott and I overcame it once and one time you technically call that overcoming.
I wouldn't call it that.
Why? We went through it.
What do you want from us?
I mean, I want I want full I want us to be fans of the haunt.
Now I'm now a big haunt fan.
Yeah, you're a haunt guy.
I'm a haunt guy now.
So you're there like you're like, are you well, you're going to go to Halloween Horror Nights?
I will go to Horror Nights.
You're going to go to Horror Nights.
My friend Luke, he a couple of weeks ago, he was like, you know, we went last year and he's kind of a scared guy, too.
He goes, you know, we went last year was kind of fun.
You go have a couple of margaritas before and I go, I like the sound of that.
He goes, you know, it's not so bad.
It's not actually as scary as you think.
But when I drink, it's not OK in the I'm a drunk for drinking.
All right. Before we go down this path.
That's true. You were describing.
Thanks to Universal.
That's a relaxing drink.
Wine is an alcoholic string.
Thank you.
Record.
All right. Just shut up for a second.
Just trying to be nice to the thank you to the universal people for having me.
Thank you to John Murty for talking to us.
Yeah.
Tweeted him on Twitter.
Not on Twitter.
Yeah.
And so we took that advice of.
So we were again when we were calling for people to invite us to things,
which this is all about us getting stuff, this podcast,
we were invited by another podcast, a long stand.
Eleven years, I believe, is what they said they had long they had been doing.
The podcast is called the Season Pass podcast.
We've mentioned it many times before.
They do great series of interviews with Tony Baxter and other imagineers.
And this is like the nerd stuff.
Our podcast is like mostly about us and our lives.
Smart times.
Making wise.
We like those.
But this is season pass.
Like if you're a nerd for this stuff, this is it.
You know, the real info and they really delve in and they, you know,
we've now because of them,
we've had a couple of actual theme park people on the legacy now with John
Murty and the folks we talked to and now we've talked to actual industry
insiders as well as Tony Baxter and I'll have show.
They've this is who they have all the time and some UCB knucklehead
describing his vague memory of a ride.
Right. Nick Money doesn't know the ride systems at Astroworld.
He doesn't know what company built those rides.
He's just going to tell us stories from his life.
Story about stealing candy from an actual baby.
Astroworld.
That's what he did.
It's one of his trademark moves at Astroworld.
So we were so Doug Barnes and Robert Coker from the season pass were
nice enough to invite us to a thing they do every year.
They get to go and hang out, get tours of mazes, get to interview people backstage.
They get the full, they get the red carpet rolled out for them.
And they've done this every year so you can go back and hear episodes that
they've done in the past about old mazes and stuff.
But they invited podcasts to ride to join them.
And this is really, I guess, our first theme park podcast crossover because if
all things go well,
we're both going to be releasing episodes where each other appears on the
other's podcast on the same day. When this comes out, you roll over to season pass.
Hear us on the season pass podcast.
Hear us interrupting the theme park industry people with garbage.
To make wisecracks.
They're saying like.
About pink pen in a dirty barn.
That might be, I forgot all about that.
Oh yeah, we addressed pig.
Well, we got to like bring up some of our little like, you know,
particular knots, fascinations, like, yeah, like the freedom center and like
Studio K, their, their, their nightclub.
And I got to talk, I got to ask about the Raven a lot from the mystery lodge.
This is a great tease for there because we, we are on this episode a lot.
So like, yeah, in the episode, I've, if I had to ballpark it based on the,
the time it took to record it, I think their episode will be like about four and
a half hours.
I don't think that's any sort of joke suggestion of how long it'll be.
I do think it's going to be that long.
That's right on the money.
Yeah.
We hung out and talked to a bunch of knots folks.
So if you finished this and you want to hear more head over to season pass
podcast.
And I like the trade that's happening where now we are starting to have theme
park professionals on the show and they are starting to have jackass pseudo
comedians.
If we can.
We're trading back and forth.
Robert and Doug kept talking about, they had heard the Astroworld episode and
they thought that Nick Monday was funny.
So if we get Monday on season pass, I think that's a win for us.
If we can really cross over the universes, but we're not going to like ask if he
wants to, we're just going to send them over to where they live.
We're going to send him a forwarded email with like an address and then I'm
going to say, okay, you're doing this podcast.
And then the same way that he may had us do this pop, make this podcast.
Hey, you're doing the thing.
You're doing the thing.
We're going to just be like, Hey, you're on the season pass podcast.
Here's going to be a guest.
So like, well, that'll, that'll be when we finally start getting all of the
universe, all the characters and Monday around.
Yeah, finally.
So, uh, so we got to, yeah, we, we hung out at, uh, the backstage at not scary
farm.
This was exciting for me because I probably my highlight of the night was
passing through a weird little backstage area and seeing some spare dry,
rapid ride vehicles, just sitting around, uh, you lit up.
Getting rusted out of a tired day.
Cause we have been in the conference room for so long, but there were these
old, just like mildewy ride vehicles and you were like, Hey, it's the most
excited you got all morning zoo.
Yeah.
Uh, I was very excited.
Uh, um, I was, I was excited to sit at a Knott's Berry, a not very far
conference room as well and walk around their offices and see what the
iterations that not people have in their cubicles.
And, uh, we got to go to the company store and peruse exclusive cheaper jams
than a typical just tourist riff raff could look at.
Right.
They were not, uh, I was asking if they were, um, exclusive to employee jam.
Like there are no preserves that are specific.
There's no employee Berry.
Which they should do.
Cast member Berry.
Yeah.
But, uh, yeah, we got to go in that.
We were very excited to go in the gift shop.
That's only it's like Mickey's of Glendale, like an Imagineering, but it's
for only employees at Knott's in a similar way where like you can't normally
get into this place.
And this is, this was very unique for me.
Cause I really have not been to not before we went to the chicken dinner
restaurant for Scott's birthday, but I had not been in the park proper.
So to have the first experience be in their creative departments, offices,
and then backstage at Mazes and then dumped into a back door into scary farm.
Uh, maize that was built into the, uh, what is typically mystery lodge where
that prankster, the Raven lives.
So the Raven, if you want to hear more about the Raven, there's a lot of Raven
talk on season pass hammer and Raven for sure.
Because who did, okay.
So who did we talk to that we'll hear on the other podcast and not this one,
we talked to a merchandise, a gentleman about the pins that they've,
they've started to make it much in their t-shirts.
His last name was Bush.
Carl Bush.
Carl Bush seems right.
Yep.
He was a nice, very nice man.
I asked him to do, I wanted Berry Tales merch and I wanted Raven merch.
He was right on that.
He was right on Berry Tales.
And it sounds like I think he confirmed Berry Tales merch.
And if you don't know Berry Tales, Google Berry Tales, Knott's Berry Farm,
but Google it with B-E-A-R because there's a different kind of bear and
different kind of Berry.
Uh, and we'll, we're going to, I think we'll, we'll,
we'll start breaking Knott's off into smaller bits.
I think we'll talk Berry Tales for a full up sometime.
Uh, cause one thing that he brought up a lot is we are two years away.
This is crazy.
Knott's turns 100 in two years.
Yeah.
That's wild.
I mean, that's from the very original.
He buys the property, sets up a chicken stand.
And it evolved into a theme park very slowly over the course of that 100 years.
But for sure that is the roots of that's the earliest roots of a theme park.
Uh, uh,
I mean he didn't confirm it, but I asked about cloud nine and studio K,
the video opulous of knots, the cool dance club merch.
And he said that there's a lot of people asking about it.
So he didn't confirm it, but I feel like it's pot is very possible.
This is exciting in the drive for retro stuff, which Disney should offer more.
Yeah.
And I didn't realize that cloud nine had come back for last year's boys and Berry festival.
They like arcade thing, which obviously not the full cloud nine.
There was some like cool teens there.
They were regular teens, but they weren't specifically cool.
Um, so they're doing, they're doing a little more of it.
I'm happy to see that they're embracing their, uh, their history.
Cause they're retro.
I mean, we, we got some of it.
They gave us some shirts and buttons and stuff.
And like there it's like, oh yeah.
The sixties and seventies stuff was cool here too.
Like a very scratchy kind of hand-drawn illustration style.
So before we get, so before we get into the maze, let's, you want to throw it to us backstage at knots?
Oh yeah. So we, yes, we got to, uh, and you'll hear more of this if you check out the season pass podcast, but for our podcast, for podcast, right?
Exclusive, we got to talk to a gentleman named Jeff Tucker who works in entertainment at knots has been there for a long time.
Uh, is a show writer there has worked in a ton of capacities.
I don't think we mentioned this on our pockets. We mentioned it on the other, but, uh, I was excited to learn if you go on the ride ghost rider, uh, the, the wooden, uh, the Western themed roller coaster at knots, uh, that if you watch the pre ride video that there's a, like a confused cowboy on it.
And it's this guy, Jeff Tucker, who we talked to and as an obsessive of, uh, pre ride videos, I became starstruck though.
I haven't seen this particular video, but a cool context for this man.
He seems to have a dozen jobs. Yeah.
He performs in the park still. Uh, he's doing like a old medicine show. He was telling us.
That's right. Yeah.
He's also in your favorite attraction at knots. He had performed in that.
He had performed at the mystery lodge.
He trains mystery lodge performers. Oh, he was doing that at current, right? He was like, I gotta, yeah, I've been working hard. I'm training a storyteller. Right.
Which is what I think that was the first thing you were excited to show me at knots. Oh yeah.
I recall you being like, we gotta see the mystery lodge.
That's maybe a little under the radar thing that you don't know about. Um, so yeah, uh, Jeff does a ton at, uh, at, at knots and knows a lot about scary farm is very passionate about it.
So we're going to talk to him over at knots, Barry farm to take it away us.
Okay. Thank you. Us. And now we are, but this has been enough itself was pretty historical.
This is the first time we've recorded podcast, the ride from on an actual site of a theme park.
We are in a conference room in the bowels of knots, Barry farm.
And we're here as we said, with the season pass guys. What's going on fellas? Hey guys.
Thank you. Wow. That was Robert. That was like the worst.
I thought it was fun. You just missed our show. Nobody's going to listen to the season pass.
And after they just heard you do that, that implies they're still listening at all. Doug.
It's like, whatever. He does a podcast.
Hey guys. Thanks for having us.
Well, yes, this is a theme park podcast crossover event. And we are also joined by Jeff Tucker from entertainment here at knots.
Barry farm. Welcome Jeff. Thank you. It's great to be here. Thanks for coming to not scary farm.
Oh, so excited. Yes. Thanks for having us. Well, we're here in the, we're in the middle.
We're learning about the history of this event of not scary farm and what you guys are up to this year.
So let us know what, what, what can you tell us about the question for you?
You guys are all terrified of this event. Is that what I'm getting? Why are you here?
You're terrified. Doug was nice and wanted to hang. It's all the blame on Doug.
Hey Jeff, do you want to come do a show about avocados? I go, no, I'm good. I don't care for avocados.
You wouldn't like the avocado festival. Oh God, no, I wouldn't go anywhere near it.
I would totally go to the avocado festival. My wife goes every year.
I don't like any fruit or vegetable enough to want to go to a festival of any kind.
Although you get to see dioramas of avocados in little costumes.
You're not selling it to me. You know, you know what you work for an organization that does a thing called a boysenberry festival.
I'll get paid to go to that one though. Oh, all right. Fair enough.
John McCluck. Well, we're trying, I feel like it's a good opportunity.
Not only do we want to come and hang out, we just want, I want a me purse. I only speak for me.
I feel like today maybe is the day where I can conquer my fear.
Maybe there is a situation today where I get over something that's been stressing me out.
We will put you in infected special ops. OK, that sounds bad.
There is a zombie apocalypse aiming for you.
The difference is you have a gun and you get to fire at them.
And when you hit them, they fall away. Really?
So you could conquer your fear by actually mowing them down with a gun.
We will get you in that attraction. We'll mic you up for that.
All right, let's mic me up. Yeah. Maybe this and hopefully the gun won't jam or something.
You're going to be like Animal Mother in Full Metal Jacket. Good some.
That's what the character I've always wanted to be. Right, man.
Your hero. The great Adam Baldwin. My hero.
OK, so yeah, I'm thinking maybe this is a growth moment in my life is what I'm saying.
In your life, perhaps. I don't know anyone, anything.
I was more interested in sitting in a Knott's Perry conference room.
This is what I came for. Jason, where do you stand?
50-50. The appeal of behind the scenes and free food brought me down here.
So, yeah, I don't know. We could try it.
Well, that was a good sell. That sounds really exciting.
And we got to walk around some of the mazes with you guys from season pass.
And that was that was a blast.
But but yeah, we're we're told that you know much about the about the history of this event and
or if you if you want to talk about that or how you how what role you play this.
No, we can talk about the history. The events.
An amazing event because you're talking about an event that has almost a worldwide reach in that.
I always I always preface it the same way.
When I was a kid, I loved Halloween. I loved Halloween.
The problem is that Halloween is one night.
Right. I used to I used to agonize for weeks over which version of Luke Skywalker I was going to be for Halloween.
Right. Is it black robed Jedi Luke or white robed farm boy Luke or X-wing Luke?
Right. So you put all this work into it and Halloween is one night.
And not only is it just one night, but it's about five thirty p.m.
to nine thirty p.m. Right.
Yeah, it winds down. That's all you get as a kid.
You got to get out there and get your candy and get home before your mom starts.
I still trigger. There was no cell phones when I was trick or treating.
So we just had to gauge time to go. Right.
So then if you if you extrapolate that and say that what's the first Halloween you remember?
Like how old were you? Eight, nine, ten?
Yes, because I remember there was a front yard.
There was like where the candy bowl was at this house.
And there was like a man sized creature sitting next to the candy bowl not moving.
And I thought, oh, it's one of those straw stuffed scarecrows that are so popular.
Like we've gone to three different houses that had these man sized scarecrows.
But this one lunged at me because it was not a man sized thing.
It was a man. Yes.
How old were you? Probably like eight or nine.
We'll say nine. I have a better memory.
I'm four. Better memory. OK.
Because I was the ghost of ET. You know how ET was in the ghost.
I did that. You were ET and the ghost.
I was acting as ET in the ghost. I was actually just a ghost.
But in your head.
I think that my parents were really cheap that year and were like, you know, you're ET inside the ghost.
Should we buy him the ET mask? No, just get the sheet.
Just the sheet. That's so I remember that because I was like, yeah, I was like, no, no, no, no, no.
How old were you? I think we were like four years old when that happened.
So yeah, because ET was brand new then. It was like ET was the thing at that.
So I remember that. But I also have a really ridiculous memory as a child.
So the average is like nine. And then when do you stop trick or treating? Five. Oh, I'm sorry.
13, right? Oh, yeah.
But age 13, you're like, I'm a little too old to be doing that.
So if we go nine to 13, we get four years. Right.
And if Halloween's four hours a night, we get 16 hours of Halloween.
And your whole life, your whole life that matters. Right.
So the Knott family had this idea. What if we extended a little?
And when they say extended, the first scary farm in 1973 was only a few nights,
three or four nights at the most. And it was the park closed.
They went up. They put some cobwebs around. They had people dressed.
I'm not kidding as the Planet of the Apes characters walking around.
What? Yeah. Because they just surely they have the rights.
Absolutely not. They went to a few makeup guys and said like, what do you got?
And this is all they had. There was no Halloween industry in 73.
Halloween was one night you went and you went to save ons and you picked out
whatever costume came in a box. Right.
Except for Doug, whose parents were cheap. And you went out trick or treating.
But in the Knott family was like, we can extend this a little.
So the park was done up. They played some sound effects records.
And it was a huge, massive hit.
So the idea was, is it coming back was a no brainer.
And they just kept adding to it, adding more value to it, adding the first walk
through mazes a couple of years later.
Originally, the Pekins had monsters in them where if you looked in, they tried to
get you. Well, then they said, let's let the monsters roam around.
So that became the first roaming street monsters.
Then they added more mazes and then they added Wolfman Jack, who did a show here.
The first show here was Seymour, who was a late night horror host.
Now another horror movie. And he actually hosted a movie in the theater.
Right. He came out, he introduced it, and then there was a movie.
Then they had Wolfman Jack. And I've actually seen footage of that show.
It was 1977, I believe.
And it's Wolfman Jack in our theater.
And he's dancing with Darth Vader, Chewbacca.
Wow. Some Jawas.
And the clip I'm seeing, she's like, everybody take a look in the audience.
Carrie Fisher, Princess Leia herself.
And it's Princess Leia, it's Carrie Fisher.
I would have died.
Wow. Wow.
I'm sure they got a big cease and desist.
So the event kept rolling and they kept adding more nights.
And then they added the ingredient that really solidified.
They originally added Elvira. That was the big event.
When they added Elvira, she was a local Channel 9 horror host.
Movie macabre, she introduced movies, she did a lot of breast jokes.
And it was a perfect fit, putting her in a big Vegas style show
where she could sing and dance. She's gorgeous.
And that rolled through the 80s, man. Rolled through the 80s.
There were a couple years we had Weird Al Yankovic here.
Elvira brought along John Paragon who played the breather on her show.
He was also John B.
Peewee. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the Terry.
Yeah, Mekka Lekka Hai, Mekka Hainiho.
Yeah, wow.
Great guy. Really great guy.
Oh, really? Oh, that's cool.
Oh, yeah. And then the family owned it up until 97.
And Haunt was the moneymaker.
I mean, it's like printing money.
And they created the theme park Halloween event
and they created extending Halloween.
We were talking earlier, Halloween began in Florida, Disney World, in August.
The Mickey's Halloween treat was in August, right?
That's how much they stretch out Halloween.
Halloween is beyond, I mean, it's crazy because it used to be growing up.
Christmas was the big event.
Christmas was two weeks off.
Man, I ain't going to think about school and I can't wait to get more Star Wars toys for Christmas.
Right? Christmas was the event.
And now Halloween has become just as big and it's huge.
And people plan parties and they have lawn decorations that are amazing.
And it all traces back to Knott's Scary Farm in 1973.
It's unbelievable.
This is crazy, the level of how much opened up because of this.
And you're making me realize how it proceeded, like everything Universal does.
It proceeded everything as far as the idea of a hard ticket event
where you go and they're going to scare you.
Like that must have been a hard sell back in the day.
We're like, wait, wait, wait, people are going to what?
Well, we're going to bring them in and then terrorize them.
And they're going to pay for it. Oh, yeah.
They're going to pay a premium for it. I don't understand.
It still doesn't make sense to us.
So you mean to tell me I'm giving you money for fear?
Yes. Like that's crazy, right?
Yeah, it does.
And it all goes to if you don't psychologically, we're all going to die.
It's inevitable.
We are the news to us.
I know, right?
And so if we can face a little slice of it on our terms where we know we're going to face it
and we're going to come out OK, have a big laugh with all of our friends,
that's how you bond with people.
That's how I mean, that really is.
Not scary farm has become because we've been here so long.
It's a rite of passage.
You know, your older brother got to go.
You counted the minutes till you months till you got to go.
Then you have kids and then you wait for your kids to grow up so they can go and so on and so on and so on.
And it used to be a predominantly adult event.
Kids were why would you bring a kid?
And then then, you know, things like Nightmare on Elm Street happened.
And if you during the 80s, Freddy Krueger was on everything but breakfast cereal.
I mean, he's a serial killer.
He kills children.
Right.
Here's a wacky toy of him.
Here's a doll.
Oh, so now Horace mainstream.
Chucky is a literal doll that comes to life.
So then we started seeing, you know, preteens, teens and preteens come to the park.
Right.
This year, it's 2018.
I've seen more strollers this year.
Wow.
Than I ever have.
And people are ridiculous.
I don't know.
I've seen strollers and what are those things?
The baby or something.
I've seen those in the park.
But you know, I got to say every year since we started coming into it, we always see at least one stroller.
Yeah.
Which blows my mind.
And I always say the same thing.
I go nothing says I love you like a lifetime of therapy.
I'm telling you right now.
Yeah, these kids are fucked up for life.
They're stronger and hardened by the.
You don't end up with three wimps like us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think it might steal them up and you don't end up with Mike Scott's and Jason's.
Yeah, to a lesser extent.
If we hadn't been scared shitless when we were babies, we would be fine now.
We would have no problems psychologically.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So.
Scare your baby is what we're saying.
Get some chainsaws in your baby's face.
Well, that's the other thing, too.
I mean, for all those strollers we've seen, I've never seen one baby crying in that stroller.
Like for some reason, they're going to run.
There's no concept going on.
Yeah, they don't know what's going on.
So, you know, maybe it is a good way to like slowly ease them into the hole.
It might be an easier way to ease them into the state of the world, too.
Really?
Like, can't miss your future.
Get used to it.
We're all living in a scary farm.
Yeah.
Increasingly.
Jeff, when did you come aboard the organization?
I started in 1994.
Wow, wow.
The family still owned the park.
It was a much different place to work for.
The first scary farm I worked at, Scary Farm 94, I think it started the second or third week of October.
It only ran for about 10 nights or 11 nights.
OK.
Because they just they didn't have any idea that people would venture out into a scary event earlier than that.
The first haunt I worked, I worked at the Silver Dollar Saloon, which is on in Ghost Town.
It's not a saloon anymore.
Now it's a shooting gallery.
But we were the only safe place you could run to when the monsters got you.
We would be serving drinks and people would run in.
Oh my God, oh my God, save me.
You're welcome to stay in here, but they're just going to come in here and get you anyways.
So what would happen is we'd have girls at the door peeking and monsters just going, waiting for you.
I got all night.
Is he supposed to do that?
That's what we pay him for.
Yeah.
Well, he's being ridiculous.
No, he's being a monster.
And you came here to get scared.
You know, you know, it was a weird moment, you know.
And the first few scary farms that I worked were in the Silver Dollar Saloon.
It was a weird, weird time.
But I used to go watch there's a big show we do called The Hanging.
And I used to watch The Hanging.
I'm excited to learn.
I don't know a ton about The Hanging.
It's a big pop culture.
It started out in the early days as an actual witch hanging where they would parade a witch through the town and she would be screaming.
You can't do this to me.
They'd get her up to the gallows, read the charges, put her in the noose.
And then there'd be a big puff of smoke and she would turn into doves and fly away.
Oh, OK.
We got nasty letters from all of the local witches covens saying that was terrible to do.
So then it got changed to we hung a gypsy.
Oh, OK.
But then?
Got the same letters without the return address.
Ah, but a bunch.
So the show eventually morphed into a pop culture celebration of all the people that entertained and irritated us over the years.
And I used to watch it and say, I could do that.
I could write that.
That's my dream.
I'll write that.
And a few years later, I got an opportunity after showing some writing samples and writing some peanuts shows for the park with Charlie Brown and Snoopy.
They said, you want to take a crack at The Hanging with the writing team?
And I was like, that's all I've been waiting for.
So I got to exercise all of those weird demons of characters I wanted to see in the show and writing that kind of dialogue.
The first year we did it, the Cripkeeper was in the show, the actual Cripkeeper from the TV show.
And this was like this is this was a licensed situation.
Yeah, yeah, we had the Cripkeeper.
So I got to write dialogue that was sent to New York for John Casir to read in the Cripkeeper voice.
I was like, that's the coolest thing ever.
You know, and you know, we made it was a very elaborate puppet that would talk and we got to do all these jokes like, what the hell is that?
It looks like Jim Henson took a crap.
But then he fights back.
But it was great because I had grown up watching Tales from the Crypt and like, I'm writing dialogue for the Cripkeeper.
That's cool, right?
And then I've done a lot of a lot of writing over the years at the park, all kinds of hundreds of shows.
I did shows in the Birdcage where it was like a melodrama of a mad scientist show.
I did one that was a fake children's show called Professor Freak's Funhouse for Kids and then an asterisk that said not for kids.
Then I took over Mystery Lodge and we did two shows in there using that technology where you can really make the audience believe there's a ghost coming to get them.
Oh, sure. Yes. Because if you don't know that show, that is the that that show is built on like the with the peppers.
They use holovision. It's called.
OK, OK. It's a very advanced version of that.
And we did a show where I cast my daughter as a ghost and she interacts with the actors on stage.
Things move and she ends up killing everybody on stage.
And then she turns to the audience.
Now, you've seen Mystery Lodge. You're 15 feet from the stage.
And then there's a layer of glass separating you from the stage.
And then beyond that are the the ghost images in that.
So it's what I mean is there's a big disconnect.
Right. And then she turns to the audience at the end and says, now I'm going to play with all of you.
And we had grown men erupt and scream, you're not playing with me.
We actually have it on tape.
Season pass. You have the audio of the guy screaming, you ain't playing with me.
I sat with Doug and I said, I said, that guy right there is going to lose his mind.
And at the end he goes, you ain't playing with me.
I like that phrase. Oh, it was great.
If we were in there, would you have pegged any of the three of us as losing our minds?
It depends on how you're acting, how you were sitting.
OK, it's the people that are sitting really overly calm, trying to will themselves into being at peace.
And then the finale of that show was the exit. Excuse me.
The pre-show doors opened.
If you go through Mystery Lodge the traditional way, you go into a little room where you hear somebody talk and the doors open.
Then you come into the theater.
We went in backwards. So you never went through the pre-show doors.
So at the end of the show, the pre-show doors opened and we had an oversized cutout of my daughter looking demonic.
And the audience got to see that for about three or four seconds.
And you hear people on all the videotapes going, oh my God.
And then we had 10 live monsters run through the audience and we had people lose their minds.
It was a lot of fun. So I've done a lot of really cool things.
Not to interrupt, but didn't you say on a couple of occasions instead of the cutout, you actually had Josie there?
Yeah, there were a couple of nights that she wanted to because, you know, the images is not her.
We filmed it on a green screen. So she was never there.
OK, she didn't have to do five shows.
She was seven.
Not a precision performer.
That was a special effect.
Yeah, if you go on YouTube and type, not scary farm possessed, it comes right up.
Parks and cons put it up.
But there were a couple of nights where the doors opened and instead of the cutout, it's actually her.
And those that had seen the show are like, oh, cool.
And then she moves and steps off the platform.
And that's where we had grown men running, running for the door.
Out of here. Yeah.
But no, scary farm is, in my opinion, the greatest event on earth.
It is so much fun.
I have had more memories created working this event than any other thing that I've done professionally.
Like we were talking, you get to terrorize people.
Look at me. I'm five, six, maybe.
I'm chubby. I look like Sean Astin in Stranger Things season two.
Which has been pointed out like he got one on.
I'm like, seriously? He's an actor.
It was pretend.
There are only so many eligible single people of age in the town of Hawkins.
That's right.
And just to let you guys know, Jeff is like a diehard Winona.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
Important context.
So I've gotten to do things here that are amazing.
And then I'm probably most well known.
I came up with this concept for a maze called Trapped, which the idea was you would go if you go, you're going to go in a maze tonight and you're going to see that you're going in as a communal event.
You are going in with 20 other people and there's 20 people ahead of them and 20 people behind them.
So you have to find your spots to get scared.
Right. Trapped was you go in and the doors close behind you and you never see anybody else.
From the public.
And you awful man.
This is before the explosion of escape rooms.
There were other singular type attractions like that before us.
Trapped. What Trapped did was it proved you could do it on a large scale where you're funneling thousands of people through a night through these carefully orchestrated locked doors and and and tasks that you have to do.
And it culminated in Trapped year three was the last we did it for three years.
The third year was my baby, me and Gus, the guy that you met earlier.
We sat down and said, let's make the ultimate Halloween attraction.
Unlike anything we've ever done before, there were no ghosts, no goblins.
It was all designed to really mess with you.
We had people lose their money and you had to pay extra for it.
It was $60 extra above the ticket price for a group of six to go in.
And if you didn't like if you didn't like what was happening, you had a safe word.
Oh, if you said boysenberry, the attraction ended and you were escorted out.
And I'm you and all your party.
Everybody's out. Yeah.
So you are not a friend at the end of it.
Oh, wow. No.
Oh, 60 bucks.
Yeah.
Yeah. See, I'm naive.
I thought no one would ever use it.
I'm very cheap. Right.
I'm very if I spend $60 and it means getting hit on the head, I'm getting hit on the head.
OK, because I paid for it.
So the idea that somebody would come in and use the safe word, totally alien to me.
And when they started, people would use it.
Really? You you you get you.
I don't mean to personally. You guys went out.
Oh, we have to get out of here now.
There's no refunds. We know we just went out.
OK, cool. Hey, we're really works.
This thing really works. You know, we learned a lot of lessons.
Any other lesson we learned is that people want to have these interactive attractions up to a certain point.
Like in Trapped Year Three, you had to figure out how to get yourself out of handcuffs.
You had to assemble a corpse to get a key from a clown.
You had to face absolutely nothing.
Yeah, right. You had to face a guy in a dress who eventually would put you under a bed,
a real bed that would then would open up behind and slide you into the next room.
Like we did stuff that was crazy.
It culminated in you had to drink urine.
Hang on. Oh, boy.
We had a room that smelled of urine, was filled with jars of fake urine, and we would serve you apple juice with vinegar and salt served warm.
No, I mean, it's not really urine, but that in and of itself is it's psychological.
My wife almost puked. Yeah. Yeah.
She's like, oh, wow.
Yeah. But you drank the urine, Doug.
Hell, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You're like that urine burns on the.
Everybody would do these tasks up until the last task.
And the last task was there was a girl that you kept meeting in the maze who was lost.
She had a Knox Berry Farm guest sticker on her.
And she's like, I can't find my boyfriend.
And she'd go another way. And as soon as she went through a door, it locked behind her.
Now, she's in on it. But people bought it hook, line and sinker that she was real.
So at the end of the maze, she's in a noose and you get to pull the lever to hang her.
And I thought, this is great. People are going to love this because it's not passive anymore.
You're the bad guy. You're the villain. You're Will Smith.
And I am legend. Right. You're not the hero anymore.
I'm the scaric. Yeah.
And was very ballsy of you guys, though, to set that all in Independence Hall.
Very. I'm surprised you didn't get more flack from that.
Yeah. Well, it was a period piece.
That means all the girls are bitchy.
All right.
Oh, did I find the line?
I found the line. OK.
So we had a lot of people that either boysenberry or simply refused to do it.
Right. So it didn't matter what the outcome was.
Somebody would pull the one of our people or would pull the lever.
And I mean, it was very graphic. You went through it, Doug. It was very graphic.
And it felt like this is the end. Right.
And then the curtain would open and then we have enough nooses for your whole party.
So you get up there on a platform.
There's a black cloth over your head.
There's a weighted noose on your head.
The music builds and then the floor drops.
And we actually had people wet, pissed themselves, wet themselves.
Yeah. Sure. Yeah. Wait, then what?
The end of the story isn't then they're dead.
So what mazes are we walking through? Yeah.
To cross one off the list.
The biggest compliment I got, and Doug knows where I'm going with this,
is we sent Doug and team through with an audio recorder to record it
because we didn't allow any cameras in the maze.
We didn't want to spoil it for anybody that was going to pay the money for it.
And Doug goes through the recorder and he had gone through the first two incarnations of the maze.
The first incarnation was about 17 minutes.
The second one, not so good at about seven minutes. Really short.
So I said we're going above and beyond.
We're going to give the guests at least 20 minutes, maybe 25,
which if you're under that kind of, because the maze wasn't about terror.
It was about stress. We were putting you under duress.
You were very stressed out trying to figure out what they wanted from you to get to the next room.
And there were people yelling at you and you would have a success.
And the very next room, there would be like a success is they hand you the keys.
You've done it. Here's your keys.
The next room is you're not getting out to you. Give me your keys.
And the next room is we need the keys. Where's the key?
And it was very designed.
A literal nightmare.
It was a nightmare of anybody who like, we stressed people out until they said, Boyzenberry, right?
So Doug goes through and I get out. I'm waiting for him at the end.
Like Mr. Rourke. How was it? How did you enjoy?
And Doug goes, Jeff, we got a problem here, man.
I'm like, Doug, what's the problem?
You said it was going to be like 20 minutes and it wasn't.
It was like 10 minutes. And we're what do we do?
I go, Doug, what are you talking about?
He goes, we were in there like 10 minutes.
I said, Doug, you were in there like 35 minutes.
No, we weren't. I said, you were.
I said, check the tape like in contact.
Check the tape. And it was and it confirmed you were in there for 32 minutes.
So it was so stressful. You were thinking like it was just so time.
It was just so tense. It was so engaging.
And it just seemed like it like everything was so impactful that whole moment that it just it just flew by.
It just flew by. And then when we got out, yeah, I thought it was like a 10 minutes.
I'm like, this is I can't lie to my audience, man.
And then he was really concerned.
And I just didn't understand my because I'm watching Jurassic Park.
We have all the monitors of the maze.
They're entering the pedophile paddock.
So like I watched the whole time. I'm timing it.
So it was really it was the ultimate compliment, the ultimate compliment.
So, you know, long story endless.
I've had amazing adventures at Scary Farm.
And the weird part now is with we have new creative teams in place that I'm a part of.
It seems like the best is yet to be.
And then all the successes that we've had in the past are just the tip of the iceberg because we have people now that are telling us think outside the box,
find new ways to scare people, find new ways, like he said, to engage people.
And that's where the future is going to be.
And I'm so excited to be a part of it.
And the team that I'm part of is just amazing because we have these think tank meetings where it's like nothing's off the table.
No, no idea is too crazy.
You know, and I'm like, I've been thinking about Scary Farm my whole life.
You know, I first went in 88 when I was 16.
So I'm ready, man.
There were ideas in the first year that I said, you're going to let us do that?
Oh, awesome. Really?
Yeah.
Because at the finale of first year, we actually got morgue drawers and we pulled them out and put people in them and closed you up in a morgue drawer.
This is beyond the pale.
And a casket.
This claustrophobic man got pegged to get into the casket.
And you went to like, wouldn't that have been, that didn't trigger you?
Oh, no, I felt the boysenberry in the back of my head.
It was starting to move a bit forward.
But Jeff was with us and we were actually recording.
I'm like, I can't.
You can't boysenberry out?
I can't purse out when I'm recording.
But like I was saying earlier.
You've got to have that content.
How long did I lay in that coffin?
Oh, three or four long minutes in the dark.
There's a side that you find out on the side that you can actually get out of that coffin.
I just laid there for like four minutes straight.
Jeff opened it up twice.
Dude, get out of here.
I'm just like, I couldn't move.
And then finally Jeff opens up and goes, Doug, let's go to the left.
And he closes it.
And I'm like, oh, yeah.
And then what was really cool is.
I did it.
You guys would be a puddle at the end.
Oh yeah.
In the beginning probably.
You were led out to the arcade where there's a big sign that says I survived trapped.
Yes.
And there's a guy taking a souvenir photo.
Everybody there's people playing video games.
The maze is over.
Except you're still in the maze.
So when he takes the picture, all the lights go out.
And the people playing video games turn around and they're in on it too.
Oh, it was fantastic.
There were so many times I was like, I can't believe they get to do this.
This is great.
Geez.
Well, this is all crazy.
But if I could pitch you an idea that is like the ultimate like, you know, just fear, psychological stress test.
If you could create an experience where somebody had to complete a four course meal at a colonial themed restaurant.
In 15 minutes.
I'm waiting at the airport.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
People are yelling at you.
You have to be getting alerts about your plane.
Red pudding is coming.
Isn't that one of the sequences in seven?
I mean, isn't that?
It would have to be an upcharge.
Oh, definitely.
$40.
Yeah.
Now, were you on a raised like dais or just at a table?
Because in my head you're like on display.
No, no.
It was a tiny table.
Yeah, no.
That's how it felt like I was watching me.
But no, it was a tiny table in a crammed old timey hole.
Have you ever seen this?
I forget when we talked about this.
This was if you missed this, this is a previous of Mike's Disney World Nightmare.
Yeah, I had I ate an all you can eat meal for four.
And also, like, because I was waiting 45 minutes, I forgot to say to get the table also.
So that cuts out my time.
That was another vehicle to it.
At the door, the Rabinowitz family from Michigan is like, is that guy by himself?
Yeah.
We're waiting for a table.
Where is that older man's children?
Where are they?
But you were totally right when you said if somebody did that here in California, we wouldn't bat an eyelash.
No.
Yeah, no.
We'd assume he was a blogger of some sort.
Yeah, yeah.
Or a podcaster.
We automatically assume it's content for something that nobody would really do that by themselves.
No one enjoys themselves in this state.
We're all just making content.
Welcome to California.
What's up, guys?
Well, Jeff, thanks so much for being here and for sharing all this info about all the nightmares.
Yeah.
Check out Knox.com.
There's a scary farm link there.
Go on any social media and put in hashtag scary farm and you can see thousands of pictures of people being terrorized.
What a dream.
It brings a tear to my eye.
It's all I've ever wanted.
Well, yeah.
Thanks so much for having us and Doug and Robert.
Thanks for being here.
You all survived podcast The Ride, but not the audience yet because they aren't done.
We have more to say.
So we're going to take it back to us in the studio with the magic transporting safe word, boysenberry.
Boysenberry.
Thank you, past us and past Doug, Robert, and Jeff.
Yeah, yeah, that was also that was a little under so they were you heard them chiming in a little bit.
Our friends now from the season pass podcast.
So that's I mean, that's a pretty good history.
There's a lot of history there of like knots.
And I honestly I didn't realize that all of like all of the influence knots has had just on Halloween in general and like expanding and how long Halloween lasts at these places.
And yeah, not not an innovator in a lot of ways that I don't think people always realize.
I don't think so.
And we've we've talked about not very far before and we've talked about the the the mine ride and the and the log flume.
Yes. Over there.
And but Jason had not been on these rides and it was a pleasure last night to go on these to watch you go on these rides for the first time.
And there is so much undeniable influence on other rides on Disney rides in all of those super crucial.
Absolutely delighted by Calico mine train and the Timber Mountain log ride Halloween Hootenanny edition.
Yes. Yeah.
Oh wait. Did you guys write down the details of who the like what was added to the the Timber Mountain?
Well, I mean, I have this stuff burned in my mind.
There was a Frankenstein there because this is a there was a sign on the outside that says like that there's a band because it's a Halloween Hootenanny that there is a band playing.
And I don't remember offhand the name of the band.
I looked it was we come around that corner so fast on the thing because I that's what I was looking at.
I was looking at the drum head.
OK. And I was like, what's the name of that? We're gone.
Yeah. I wish I knew offhand.
I know. There was an alien.
Yeah. Little gray alien.
And then my favorite thing at some point, there's an animatronic bear who looks right at your log and goes trick or treat.
Yes.
That was so good.
And I didn't know it was coming.
He kind of talks right at you.
Yeah. So exciting.
It was so delightful.
And also that log ride goes so fast.
Like we go.
Well, we that was a log of five.
There was a three podcast.
Right.
And season pass size adults and one Jason sized adult in that log sitting in my lap sitting in Scott's lap.
Imagine that listeners.
The delight of that.
My lap.
Doug was in Robert's lap.
We were all this.
That was the ultimate crossover of groin groin.
Yeah. And then the final drop like you are you like don't see it until you're doing it.
It's a little bit of a bump there that almost launched me out of the law.
He said, oh, geez.
Yeah.
So you I was in the back of the log and I heard you heard you exclaim because I don't think you realized it was such a big drop.
No, I got like it was at the bump.
You were reacting to I see like maybe it was because I was the first one.
Like I really felt it.
But like it felt perfectly safe.
It was just startling out of nowhere.
They're also like blasting a strobe light at you.
That was an interesting thing.
But I'd done the ride during the day.
I didn't know how they modified it for Halloween.
And it's it's great.
It's it's it's a lot of fun.
I was expecting characters the whole time.
I was too.
They haven't passed.
Have had them apparently.
Maybe not now.
After the first minute, I was like, seems like it's just going to be a delightful band friends.
So I like this.
I think what happens because I've watched video with the characters, the actual human beings.
And the thing is, these these rides were not built for that.
So the only place I can put humans is in all are in all the exit like hallways.
So it's like you can see where all the actors are coming.
There's no way to get like a really genuine scare out of people because they have to be too close to the water.
They're going to fall in the water.
They're like there's no it's really kind of pointless.
They tried it, I think.
And I think it seems like what's really the point of this.
So like maybe they were tired.
They have best characters, best used in other places like everywhere in the park, everywhere in the darkness.
Yelling at you through the fog, scraping the ground, scraping the ground.
We learned that they have metal on their knee pads and on their boots to like make these horrifying scraping sounds.
I got the name of the band for you here.
The Calico Coffin Creepers.
Delightful.
Yay.
So delightful.
That's like the name of what would play a Monster Mash type song, a novelty song in the 60s.
The mind train too also like I think Robert pointed this out like this ride is grandfathered because you are so close to the walls and ceiling.
He was just touching the wall.
Because it's so and I was just the lighting in there and the number of the animatronics and just the scope of like this giant like is truly incredible.
That primary like so there's a kind of a room that you pass through on several in several different ways in several different layers.
This main big mine scene with so many animatronics, a jaw dropping amount of animatronics.
And I was saying to Jason, it reminded me a lot of the main room in the Indiana Jones adventure.
Yes, you get you pass through it this way and then weave into another place.
But then you're back in the main room.
But you're lower now and you can and obviously an influence on Big Thunder and obviously the log flume of the influence on Splash Mountain.
There's just so much Disney DNA there, which I'm sure Tony Baxter would tell you.
So I don't know if I feel like there are a lot of the important fans who have never taken the time to go to knots and you you can get a lot out of it.
But you get a lot to appreciate there.
Those two rides are really great.
And so, yeah, it was we were saying before, though, earlier, we toured two mazes with the lights on.
Yes, much like you do with Stranger Things.
And those are the two new mazes.
One's called Dark Entities and the other is called the Depths.
Yeah, talk about those.
So let's talk about those real quick.
The Depths is a it's aquatic themed.
You end up facing a sea monster kind of a Kraken thing.
Yeah, a bunch of miners unearth an ancient evil fish based ancient evil.
Even though it's a mine.
Yeah, it's fish based.
It's a seaside town.
That's right.
You enter the lighting effects where we're up and going for us.
But you enter like you enter a shaft like an elevator shaft and you're supposed to recreate the effect that you're leaving and going into a different room.
We didn't do that.
They don't have that working.
OK, so we just walked.
We just walked through all fine.
Obviously, all fine with me.
Lights on.
No scare actors because I remember we're so we're walking through this in my brain and I'm sure it's similar to your guys.
You're like, oh, I'm imagining I'm walking through this with people jumping out and I'm trying to remember things.
I'm trying to remember.
This looks like a little cubby hole for a human to jump out at me.
And they're also showing us fun stuff.
First of all, it is very cool.
It's cool to see the effects.
They have these big practical monsters.
They also spoiler alert.
I guess if you're going to nuts, they have.
Yeah, as we're saying, a giant octopus, they have this like I'm trying to remember.
Maybe that's actually the other maze.
They had that.
No, that's the other maze.
There was an alien head that pops through like a window at you.
This had like fish.
This had like fish monsters.
And yeah, you could go.
It could show up at any one of three windows so people wouldn't know where it was coming.
Yeah.
So and there's a shark.
There's a crazy shark at the end.
Yeah.
Really bloody and like is giant.
Like it's very cool.
There were dozens and dozens of people.
And then there's so we're going through the depths and they're I'm trying to really keep a mental note of the scares for later.
Like because I'm like, I'm going to have to do this later.
You want to outsmart it.
And I'm going to outsmart it.
And the one thing that was disconcerting or the one thing that I thought I was not going to be able to do was that they explained there was this one room and that later there's going to be laser and fog, which is going to make it feel like or at least look like you're walking through water.
And they were like, there's going to be actors under the fog and lasers.
Right.
And I was like, oh, shit.
And it is legit.
I was like, that sounds awesome.
Oh my God.
I don't want to deal with this because that's terrifying.
And I don't like people I can deal with.
I think the people coming from the left or right ago, but I don't want a top or bottom scares.
That sucks.
But I was like, OK, so you got to remember they're going to be like walking on the ground when you're here later.
So we did that.
And then we did.
Wait, well, so what then did you do it?
Does that factor into the later story?
Well, yes, I did it.
And well, I'll get to that in a second.
There's a little more of an arc, you know, I'm trying to build a hero's journey really of me getting to go to the depths.
So then we did Dark Enities and it's like a very aliens type maze and then we're still going through the previews.
And that's very cool because there's robots.
They build a robot or two robots really.
And they're like old school 50s robots.
And there's a giant alien at the end of it.
And again, I'm like, OK, remember, the alien is here at the end.
He's going to be moving.
Giant puppet like giant.
Yeah, crazy.
I was kind of blown away that that even existed at not because I was like, this seems I don't know.
I don't know why I just didn't expect giant puppets.
Yeah, those everything we saw in that avenue was so impressive.
And again, this is made for like less than two months.
The attraction like and not I thought this was really clever.
The big billboard outside of not they listed this year.
They listed all the dates it was running.
And when a date like a day ended like you would write on a physical calendar, they put a slash through it.
So if you were driving by, you know, like only 15 days, there's only 10 days left.
So, yeah, so we so we did those two and it legit we got to walk through with one of the lead designers.
I think the guy from Dark Ennity's and you can hear again all this unseasoned pass where there's a live walkthrough of us doing this.
So go over there if you want more details about us walking through a thing.
And my concern about what the National Labor Relations Board would have to say about all Jason is a good runner.
Yeah, there's a theme of you like throwing people off all day at not yesterday.
They weren't prepped for the Witten wisdom.
Like don't make it sound like I'm just trying to derail.
So we like funny, funny, good jokes.
Let's let the listener decide.
All right.
Hey, you know what?
Fair enough.
The season pass people like the listeners of the season pass might be more serious theme park fans.
So they're like, who is this guy and what does he think he's doing?
Well, we're we will be the bug main of their podcast.
We're the same ratio.
Shocking.
I tried to go back and forth between jokes and then like a question I thought might be legitimate.
So we'll see how that goes into that too.
Look, I'm just being silly.
I guess I'll say here now that we went out for drinks for my birthday the night before.
Oh, yes.
This is a good context.
Yes.
Yeah.
So if you'll recall the I believe it's the Small World episode from last year, a similar thing happened where I was in a bad way.
Oh, yeah.
That was after your birthday, too.
Yes.
That's right.
So I you know, I had some french fries at Portillo's and I drank a lot of water and I sort of perked up once I was on microphone and but and then just did a marathon for hours and hours.
You were very concerned before this.
You're like, oh, it's going to be a probably a long day at nots like my birthday the night before.
I better take it easy.
There was a whole like discussion about it.
And then when we were talking at your birthday, it was your birthday was very nice, very low key, nothing.
Why?
The thing the closed place closed at midnight.
And then like we hadn't talked for maybe 45 minutes and I was talking to other people that are and then it closed down and you walked over and I went, oh shit, he's really drunk.
And like you like you were like this.
Mike is always the arbiter of very.
No, you weren't as drunk as God is any given night.
I lost track of time.
It was I lost track time.
I at some point in the evening, I was like, oh, I close at midnight.
We got lots of time.
And then the more drinks I had, I was like, I time is moving weird.
And also like that night, there was like lightning strikes going on and like rain going.
So like great.
I was just I wouldn't have been concerned other than I knew that tomorrow was a long day.
I bet you know, I'm a professional showed it up ready to work.
No, I know I did it.
I texted you in the morning.
I was a little worried I was going to have to wake you up.
And you're like, I am showered.
Oh, can I read the texts you sent me at night?
Oh, yeah, I guess I said, Mike, some very aggressive.
I love you guys so much and I'm afraid to say it to Scott sometimes, but like I just think he's the best.
And haven't I complimented you enough?
Like,
for evidently not.
I guess I got an alcoholic and I had like I was that is that used up all my energy of like, I'm going to text Michael and I'm going to text my friend Lorraine who gave me a ride home.
I should also say I while walking up the driveway to get home, I ate it very hard.
I really attacked the ground and have a large scabbing gash on my arm and my right thigh is still occasionally in pain.
So I'm going in.
Happy birthday to you.
So I was ill Saturday morning.
I texted you.
In and out in and out of sleep on the drive down to not.
Yes, you've nodded off.
We were driving.
You were closing your eyes.
I was like, you asleep?
And you're like, I'll be fine.
As we're listening to the new Elvis Costello album, which to me sound I just chalk up to being dream music now.
Like you made it up.
There is no help.
Yeah.
All right.
So this is the text I texted you at like 1am and I said, did you make it inside?
And you said, yes, I'm good.
Period.
Thank you for your concerning, which reminded me of like the tiny, tiny, tiny for your concerning.
Yeah.
And then you said, this is just a demand or a command.
You're driving to not.
I'm still collecting myself, but I'll be good.
But I'll be good to go once I have a live mic.
And that was Jack was right.
Boats me on and I shine.
I was a little difficult getting out of the house and into a lift to your house.
Taking a lift.
I still had the disease when I woke up.
So anyway, I do this like twice a year.
This is not I'm not like a problem.
Like, yeah, no, I'm not my full bottle of wine each night.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So that's where you're coming from.
So I come in and hot.
So, yeah. So we do these two mazes and then we go and do what felt like six hours of interviews.
So then they're like they're basically saying then you're going to get to go out in the park and they're going to give you like this is great.
Like we're getting wristbands that are front of the line wristbands.
They're like so nice to do this for these guys and then for them to invite us.
So we go out in into the park and immediately we go to one of the mazes.
We were first the plan was kind of like maybe we have a drink, maybe we have a beer and then that eases us into it.
But it was like, you know, acceptable amount of an acceptable amount, one or two.
That's the way to drink.
Logistically, that did not really work.
Oh, you drink before we went into the park.
What do you mean?
Yeah, we were backstage and we had to go to our cars and that sort of thing.
So yeah, yeah.
So we saw they I think Jeff was like, well, the zombie one is right here.
You may as well go right here to the zombie one.
The only reason I got on, I was going to try to slip off.
I was the one I was like, he's going to peel off.
He's been telegraphing it all day.
Jason told me I will do one or two earlier.
So I was like, OK, Scott is going to leave quickly.
Jason is going to stay with for one or two maybe.
But then I don't know how he's going to get back because I drove him.
So he has to go with Scott if he's going to leave.
I felt more kind of when they're like, oh, we'll go to the zombie maze first.
In that one, you are given a gun.
You have to run the lunge at you.
You shoot a target and it'll fall back.
And I'm like that I am into that.
Although some of those zombies did not have targets, so they just kept coming regardless.
So it was like it was more of a maze.
I actually thought it was more of a game, but it seemed like just a maze with a gun.
Pretty much. And I didn't even check my score at the end.
I forgot that was a thing to be done.
Somebody said I had nine kills, but I got like a shot.
A lot of the people on our side.
So I should have had more. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I guess I was just every which way.
And here's what I so I it's probably been a very long time since I've done anything similar to it.
Or amazing what I I was I was pleased that I never went like, ah, I didn't like Shree.
But what I what I decided to do kind of inspired by that now I've I've been doing Splash Mountain and I did that log flume last night.
And I did the Incredi coaster.
And I think I was I described previously that launch coasters like I get those like this weird shortness of breath or something that happens.
And I realized, oh, the way to overcome that is to like kind of project and yell.
And maybe that's how I get over it.
I combat that by just letting a big sound out.
And I decided to employ that in this maze.
So at every possible turn of a scare, I was just going, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And that I that did it for me.
It made me feel like I felt like a dog who is a little scared, but trying to going overboard to prove that, no, I own this.
This is my territory.
I was doing I I don't I was sort of doing a similar thing and I sort of settled into a rhythm of it later where it did feel like that you can kind of like take ownership of the of the situation a little bit.
You're like you're not you're not a victim.
You're going to come.
So I was like kind of commenting.
I was like sort of trying to be a little funny.
And then like when Robert would get scared legitimately, I'd be like, yeah, take that Robert.
Like I would I would say stuff like that and like trying to make Douglas.
So I'm trying to distract myself to some degree shaming our new friends.
It was such good nature.
It was good natured like the alcoholic joke.
You know, I wasn't being serious.
I didn't really want to see my new friend Robert get scared.
You know, I'm just razz and you're breaking balls.
That's what we do on podcast the ride.
You guys break each other's balls like the cellar.
Right.
Exactly like the dirty table.
Exactly like the great place.
The cellar.
We all did a set last night.
So we so we did this thing.
But to contextualize like Scott was saying how he reacts to this stuff when we were backstage scare actor.
We were all going to the bathroom.
And I was waiting outside and a scare actor went into the bathroom without his mask on.
And when we were coming out, he had the mask on and I looked away and I looked up and was startled by this monster coming out of a bathroom.
It was fully lit like backstage.
Fully lit office office building.
Monster casually walking out of a stall scared you.
So you know that the actual jumping and banging on a wall.
Yeah. And we were.
Look, there were people.
We saw monsters on their lunch break.
We saw the people behind the scenes.
I wasn't afraid of a monster eating a sandwich.
That was great.
I love that. I love seeing monsters eating under a tent.
And I said this on the show before.
One of my favorite Comic Con memories is seeing the Flash villain Captain Cold going to the bathroom like in a big parka going to the bathroom at Comic Con.
I love that.
So yeah.
So we went so we went to the zombie.
It was called Special Ops Infected.
And there's a cool part where you go through like kind of a subway car, which stressed me out because it's closer quarters than the rest of it.
But it wasn't so bad.
So we get out of there.
And my first feeling about it wasn't because I was hoping I was going to go through it and go not so bad.
You like this now.
I was hoping that was what was going to happen.
And it wasn't really it was more what you're describing where I was like, do I need this?
Do I mean it's like I like the subway car part.
But like the game wasn't that fun.
It wasn't that satisfying to blow away zombies because it's like they're humans and they're trying to pretend but they're not going to fling themselves against walls over and over again.
So like we got out there and I was like, OK, I don't know.
I want to do more.
But I had the same feeling of like, why do I need this necessarily?
But then then we said, let's go get a drink.
I don't know what restaurant it was, but it had a giant two giant pictures of Mr.
and Mrs.
Not on the wall.
Walter and Cordelia.
Regular pictures.
Their eyes did not follow you anywhere.
Right.
So we did that.
And then we went on those two dark rides that we mentioned.
Yeah.
And at that point, we got the he tapped out.
Jason and Mike tapped out because as we were in line for we all had one beer.
Some people got back in line for that too.
And I leaned over to Mike and went, I think I'm crashing.
I have the shivers like when I start to get real tired, I start to like you have the disease earlier.
I had the disease.
I have the shivers.
Sometimes this happens after a comedy where it's just like, oh, the adrenaline is wearing off and I am crashing.
And like certainly after hours of podcasting when I was not 100 percent and then being scared.
I mean, we went through scare zones.
I didn't know they were so dark, but that it's also very crowded.
But the scare actors get in between the crowds.
But there's also a lot of teens there doing teen bits.
And I'm like, is that a teen goofing or is that a ghoulie or a goblin?
So I was you clutched my arm at one point.
That was adorable.
That is any time I've had to go through a haunted house.
Like I think I did that.
There was like a haunted house at like a school dance once.
And I was like clutching the arm of like a teacher or a friend.
Like it was embarrassing.
I went in the house of horrors a couple of years ago.
I told it on the show with my friend at Universal before they got rid of it, obviously.
And I was just embarrassing.
I was dodging and making weird noises.
And especially when I was a kid and we went, I went through like a very mild version of it.
And it was just I couldn't I couldn't deal with it.
Like what we were saying, and they have these they were telling us that they have like metal on their shin,
like or their knee pads and their shoes to make like a louder noise.
So they're encouraged to slide and make these.
Yeah. And it's it's very effective.
But it's kind of hard to tell where it's coming from, but it's very unnerving.
And they'll just pop up at you.
That didn't bother me so much as that actually didn't bother me as much as I thought it would.
Because there's so many people around.
And even though there's like a giant scary masked person, like it's not close quarters.
The close quarters, I think, is the thing that especially freaks me out about it.
So like that, I didn't mind as much.
So we get on those those two rides.
And I will say that I was I was feeling what your I was tired and the first maze didn't do much for me.
But when we went on those two dark rides and the lighting, that's a really nice, beautiful, cool looking piece of real estate.
All of the other that whole area is so great.
And after we got off the log ride, I was feeling very good again.
And I felt really like we got it. I got to do it.
So you guys. So we talked about it, especially once once they reminded us like, oh, yeah, don't forget this park has multiple entrances and excellent.
You can go out the back right, right around the corner.
And we're like, great, because that part of the park has a lot of attractions.
So there's not a lot of scares back there because they need to get people on and off those.
We didn't see anybody on the way out. See anyone.
So we some. Yeah, some zones don't have much.
And then we went through his own later and it was like clowns everywhere.
And like there was not many there were not many people around.
We almost went on hang time, the roller coaster.
We almost did it. But we were sort of running out of time and I had to come back at a certain point.
I couldn't be a hero all night. I want to go back to I want to do a full day there and get the full experience.
I mean, hang time seems cool. I would I'm so psyched to do those rides again.
Not to Mary Farm is coming up, which again, that just sounds delightful.
We should tease it at the end, but we will be back for the Boys and Berry Festival.
I think we can confirm this now. A tease that is going to be very exciting listeners,
but we will be back for Nats Berry Farms.
Everybody's got the shivers at home now and the disease and the disease.
So the next thing so Doug is like, you got to go on Dark Ride.
You got to go in Dark Ride maze. And I was like, OK, because at first it sounded like we were going to just do the other two mazes and then go home,
because that's sort of what we were discussing. Doug's like, you know, you got to do Dark Ride.
It's like an old carnival that shut down. And I was like, OK, so we go in Dark Ride and there's a lot of clowns on Dark Ride.
And we go through Dark Ride and I'm still feeling the same way I was feeling about the zombie one where it's like, I don't know, people are jumping.
And you get to the last room and there's a big kind of clown, almost like Joker style, like, you know, an old carnival.
It's been converted into the lair. And I remember going, OK, this is kind of cool.
I kind of like this. And it's again open air, which is I think a big deal, like not feeling like you're claustrophobic.
So we left that. We then it's clear like Doug is trying to very Doug is a very nice man, but he's trying to get me to go on all of them.
And then I'm like, OK, you know, you can do this. You can. It's fine. You made it through to.
We go into Shadowlands and Shadowlands here. I'll show you the art of it. Cool.
It's kind of cool. Like, oh, yeah, it's a whole different.
It's like a samurai motif. And it's like there's like zombie geishas and like guys with big swords.
And we're getting better. I'm get I can feel I'm getting better on it.
So I'm walking through and I'm like, oh, this is cool. The art direction is kind of cool.
And there's some like interesting things.
And I actually kind of look at a person that's trying to scare me for the first time as opposed to like darting my like, I don't want to even look at what you're doing.
And then you start to be like, OK, maybe I'll just look at the actor and go, oh, yeah, you're like 28.
Like I can like maybe then it'll start. So I'm starting the wheels of motion.
Now, I don't fully love Shadowlands. I'm not fully like enjoying it, but I'm like I can feel it getting better.
So we go over to I forget the order.
We go and do the depths. Yes, we went to earlier in the day and we went through it.
And I knew where all the scares were, which was good.
Very good. And we get to that room with with what I was saying with the water and the lasers to make it look like you're walking through water.
And I see there's just hands coming up through the fog.
No, no, no. And the thing is, though, once I got through the room, I was like, OK, yeah, no one's going to grab you because they can't.
They can't. Yeah. So once I got through the room, I was like, like, by the way, that's the first maybe the first time where I was clear headed enough to be like, this is awesome.
Like it is a truly very cool visual thing. There's like weird hands like fishy hands coming up through the through the water.
And I'm like, all right, that's cool. So then we go into dark entities and dark entities.
We saw with the lights on dark entities with the lights off is awesome.
Like the lights because they were saying it's 12000 like it's like quadruple the amount of lights they have in a normal maze.
So it looks like an alien ship and the robot is working.
The robot is talking. I walk in there and I feel the first time in these mazes, I feel some joy coming from like my brain for the first not that I didn't like appreciate the lab, the depths, because I was like, the depths is cool.
I like the effects of ship rocks. I get on dark entities and I go, this is cool.
So the robot, there's this 50s style robot and you see another version of it later.
And we walk through there and I was like, this is awesome. This legit. And it's there was still scares. I still was like, oh, like a lot of times.
But then I'm like, okay, I got this. Yeah, you're doing it. And then it's like this feeling of like riding a bike or something like I'm like, I think maybe I'm good.
Maybe this is good now. So then the last one we did was see it's called paranormal ink.
And again, this is spoilers for if you want to go. And it's very much like paranormal activity, like like hospital with people that are tortured by ghosts or whatever.
So they have a whole pre show now. So this is the final thing I did. This is the final thing we did.
They have a whole pre show of like a fake show. That's a paranormal investigation show. So now it's even more like a theme park ride. They have a pre show video.
Oh, I should mention too. There were like video displays in that alien ship too, with clearly like people that were there.
And all that stuff is very cool and makes you feel very it makes it so much more immersive. So let me go to paranormal ink.
And there's a whole pre show with like a girl who's showing like I'm on this show and I'm talking to this and that's very fun. And then something goes wrong. I'm like ghost.
So so Robert, I think goes, hey, look up there. So I look up there and there's a really cool video effect of like a girl appearing in this glass.
And all of a sudden, the girl breaks through the glass and on a wire, she shoots across the ceiling. And I was like, whoa.
And I wasn't it wasn't it was far enough away where I wasn't like scared. I was like, this is awesome.
So then we went through this paranormal, which is like you're going through an asylum and I'm leaving out so many details.
You can look at all these on YouTube. But the coolest thing I think that was that the last.
So you go to the hospital, people scaring you, you're going through like people in hospital beds and stuff.
The last section is a long corridor in a hospital and it flashes back and forth.
Somehow I do not know how it how they do it. You'll be walking down a regular hallway and then a flash of light and a noise.
And it's like you see through the walls and it's hell. And there's monsters.
There's a giant monster. And then the flash happens again and you're back in a normal hallway.
And I was like, holy shit. Like I and like that was legit is cool of an effect on any ride that I ever see.
Like any like seeing like Shanghai pirates where he kept and Jack turns into a skeleton or something, stuff like that.
Legit. I was like, I don't know how this is happening. I'm in the middle of this. This is awesome.
So like we left on a high note and I truly felt so it's so embarrassing how triumphant I felt.
Sure. Doing six mazes. And then I do think they were stacked almost in the perfect way to like the stuff that I would really be like interested.
Like I love alien shit and like and then ending with probably maybe the most most spectacular of all the illusions and all these mazes.
And then by then you could just appreciate that aspect of it and not be freaked out.
Yes. So like I kind of that's why I'm saying like I would like I probably will try to go to Horror Nights before the season's over.
I kind of wouldn't mind going back to Knott's and doing because we did a lot of podcasting,
but it would be kind of fun now to go back and just do the night and have a good have a good time with it.
So I yeah, it was great. Honestly, by the end I was like these are great.
I don't know if I love those first few as much. But yeah, so go to Knott's if you're around.
It's fun. There's a lot of teens, you know, there's some of that.
But I I I'm in I am a haunt guy. Yeah.
The biggest fear still is the presence of course. But besides that.
And I just mean they we get into this a little on the season past podcast, but it is not.
He's like essentially a neat they refer to it as a neighborhood park because there's like houses so close.
Right. And it is very intimate, very small.
And, you know, they have talked about like we have to get creative because we don't have like the insane budgets that like Disney and Universal do.
But they've got very cool people working there and they do have some money and there is some like very cool stuff going on down there.
There are normals, especially that one.
And that one's the most popular for that reason, I would assume. But like the money went into that.
And like there is yeah, they are still pulling stuff off there that like you would think a place with a bigger budget would have would only be able to do so.
Yeah. Also at Halloween, they put the Charlie Brown characters into costumes such as one of them in a Frankenstein head and Snoopy and like a sheet.
And I think that's great, too. I just want to give some vocal some air time to that.
Yeah. Look, you said it on the show yesterday. I think you said on the season pass.
We can't remember what was going where. No idea. But yeah, that is look, I love the peanuts.
I love them with the costumes on, too. So, yeah, I get what you're saying.
That's what you get. All the flavors and that's for everybody.
I also want to say and I this is just a thing that like I love and I talk about all the time.
If you trend, if your taste trends more towards the whimsical part of Halloween and you are in Los Angeles, the local haunt Boney Island, which is a bunch of delightful skeletons doing fun tricks.
And there's a little water show used to be in someone's yard in Sherman Oaks.
And then that got to it got too big and too popular.
And they took last year off as they kind of like had to reset and figure out what they were going to do this year.
It is in a section of Griffith Park and it is bigger and there is like a nominal admission fee.
But I'm so happy it's back. I'm so happy to go.
I believe it's also right next to the ghost train, which is another fun, like whimsical thing that I know our past guests, Justin Michael and Mr. Strickland are big fans of.
These are very different and family friendly that like, say, the haunted hayride.
I was that scary. Maybe I'll conquer the haunted hayride.
That is, I think, yes, supposed to be scary. There's a limit for me here as far as being able to do scary stuff.
So, yeah, you're no longer what is it? You're a no, you were a no fright queen.
No fright queen, but I'm now a fright. You're a fright queen.
Yeah. Yeah. So yeah, Boney Island and Ghost Train.
I'm excited to to check those out this year. We're not being paid to say that.
No, yeah, we're not being paid to say any of this. We're not.
But all these places gave us things and keep giving us things.
Sure. Please. And I hope you're all happy for us listening that we got the thing.
Yes. Are you happy for us? Let us know in the comments if you could both say that Michael Carlson, you survived podcast ride while you look at my eyes.
That would be really good. Michael Carlson. Both at the same time.
How do you look at both of us, though? All right. Well, just shift back and forth.
Michael Carlson, you survived podcast ride.
Yeah, that's actually the better way. Yes. Thank you. Thank you.
We're proud of you. Very proud. That's what I wanted.
The Seven Dwarfs. Now you look at me and say, Scott, you don't have a fucking problem.
Scott, you have no problem. I was just riffing earlier.
You having having one glass of wine a night is fine.
That's what like Patrick Stewart does. And he lives. He's 77 years old. He looks great. He's in great shape.
Everyone loves him. OK, great.
I'm clearly every bit the physical specimen of Patrick Stewart.
I'll take that. And thanks for looking at me in the eye.
Thanks for listening to us in your ears.
Keep checking out. We got more spooky delights and scary frights coming up all month of October.
Yeah, the big one next week and a big announcement coming next week, too.
True. Yes. Yes. Let's let's let's tease that.
Yeah, next week is going to be a great one. And but all the stuff stayed the same.
We didn't switch the name on all the socials like podcast, the right on Twitter or Instagram or podcast, the right at Gmail dot com.
And we got the shirts around as a haunt cast, the fright shirts available as well as all our regular ones.
I survived, which you should now wear with pride.
I really did. Impressive. You know, we we got to support each other here.
You were you all were supportive about Splash Mountain for me. I will be supportive about this for you.
I don't know what you need support on, Jason, but it's just all of my life choices.
All the things. Yeah.
It's a support on your arm that you've cut up.
Yeah, sure. It's mending. You're doing my jeans and my sweater.
I like to wear fine, though. That was that was my concern.
Oh, yeah. I feel naturally. No, they don't.
Now, if you have more of your day to kill, go to season, go to the season pass podcast and hear the more of this
incredible multi podcast crossover events and more content done from a Nats Berry Farm conference room.
Yes. And thanks again to those guys.
Thanks to everyone at Nats. Thanks to everyone at Universal.
Very fun to go behind the scenes while this stuff. Yeah.
Yeah. No kidding. I'll check us out next week. More fun.
Goodbye. Bye.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.