Forever...
Dog!
When your town has let you down
When your porch has fallen short
When you're too worn out to run
And need some ribs or a Cinnabon
You need a place, a place for rock
A place for roll, a place where Oakland Raiders merch is sold
A sublime hot topic and billabong
A place where you can purchase a candy thong
So let's go take a walk
Let's all go to City Walk
Tonight, tonight
The Saga Finale
We're there!
We're gonna get through all 19 sectors
Now available on our T-Public store
A t-shirt, I survived the City Walk Saga
Go to our T-Public
The award you have is to buy a shirt from us
Is to buy a shirt on sale, like all T-Public shirts
New design launched, on sale for a few days
Also, I believe, classic I survived podcast array too
Oh yes, that also, a new shirt
On the show in general, hey we have a T-Public store
That's the big overall news
And some of you have already bought shirts
And we've seen them and we're so happy you're getting them
But a new line, the survived line
But I want to institute a strict moral code here
An honor system, you may only buy the shirt
You may only get the reward of giving us money
If you actually did listen to all 19
Imagine the shame somebody would have to feel if they wore that shirt as a lie
Yeah, this is like if you were to go to Disney and the gift shop
You were not allowed in it unless you truly went on the ride
Which I honestly kind of think it should be enforced that way
Well there is merchandise that only annual pass holders can buy
So think about it like that
A little bit, I'm just saying you gotta go with the experience though
You can't get any, you know
We would like if people would tweet at us
Screenshots that show listened to and the dates
That would be good
Show the timecode and that you made it all the way through
And then you may purchase merchandise from us
And also tweet at us pictures of you enjoying anything you've gotten from us
Again you can click the link in the description of this episode to go to the T-Public store
Okay good, that question
Yes, it's in the metadata
The description, depending on your podcatcher
There's a link in there, you can click that
And we appreciate it
And then we have a little tantalizing tease without saying too much
I think here's the big way that the City Walk Saga has affected us, the podcast, the Ride Boys
Is that we now have a taste for doing far more content than should be legal in this country
We are, we're just thirsting to ramble about more topics deeper than Theme Park World
And that is why we are proud to announce here today in the grand finale that at the end of this month
We will be cutting the ribbon on Podcast the Ride, the Second Gate
Ground is being broken as we speak
This right now is the groundbreaking ceremony
Yes
It's a whole new world of bullshit to explore
So we're talking about Patreon exclusive content
That's correct
Just in case people don't know what Second Gate means
Because there's probably people that may not know
They're not insiders like we are with the Theme Park terminology
It's an industry term, that's what happens when a park opens
A second park next year
Yeah, so they call it a second gate
And the gate is where you...
This is, it's like California Adventure to Disneyland, but we got to it way quicker
And it is going to be way better out of the gate
This isn't like cheapo original California Adventure
This is a top tier e-ticket experience
And all you need to do is purchase a Patreon park hopper pass
And then you may enter a fantastic world
With hundreds of new digital acres of discussion
Of rides and hotels and treats and all of the things
A lot of the things we've been talking about, specific characters
There are robots that literally have no backstory that we would like to talk about for an hour and a half
We have a lot of fun stuff to talk about
There are alien robots that we're obsessed with and we'd like to talk about
That's all we'll say
There's a lot of fun coming, we won't explain everything yet
But this is the groundbreaking ceremony
We're all inserting pantomime shovels into your floor, Mike
And will be a fun way to kick off our one year anniversary too
Yeah, we're heading to the one year anniversary
There's a lot of stuff going on
But let's get to the thing that is happening right now
Our guest is here
You know him as the guy who all podcasters rip off their business model from
Ladies and gentlemen from Doughboys
Returning to the show, Nick Weiger is here
Hey man
Guys, thrilled to be back
I'm so excited about Podcast The Ride getting its own Surfers Cove
Which as we know is the water park that's next to Legoland
Of course, all the surfers
Yeah, so I mean, I think we're all waiting for it to happen
It finally is here
I was actually honestly I'm like a little deflated
Because I was going to come on here and I was going to castigate you guys
For releasing 19 bonus episodes for free
And not figuring out that this was something that you could monetize
Especially with the enthusiast fan base that you have
But I'm glad that you're doing this because this is like
In addition to because you guys put a lot of work into the show
It's a very good show, it's a very entertaining podcast
One of my favorite podcasts
Thank you
And you know, but you haven't really
Have you made any money off of this?
You've been losing money on this, right?
Yeah, absolutely
You've been losing money
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, we made a little from the t-shirts
The first round of t-shirts
Don't tell them that
We made nothing
We need your help
The economics of podcasting are tricky
Because even the ads that you run are like
You know, you're sharing that with a network
And there isn't necessarily great money for those
So like, you know, some sort of paywalled content is the
Is really the only way some people can make money off of it
And I'm glad you guys are doing it because you should do it
Because it's a good show
And I'm sure you have listeners who will be excited to support you
So I'm very excited for this, this is great
Thanks so much
I really appreciate that
I'm having on day one
Oh, boy
Oh, geez
Well, we had also talked about and thought about
Do we put some of this behind a paywall?
And do we put this episode behind the paywall?
Just one episode
It would have been really cruel
Right
But yeah, we I don't know
We wanted to be nice and generous
Before we get real rigid
And put up big old barbed wire fences
Like the ones you don't even see on the outside of Disneyland
But you're there
If they're there, if you try to jump a wall
There's hardcore security
We're going from like humble artists
Just happy to do something for free
To like we're about to merchandise the hell out of this
I want, if we could
And somebody tell me if this is possible
If we could have a Jason Plush doll
Oh, my God
Within a year
So if somebody knows of a way to do this
Where we're not going to lose a million dollars
And the scale on this would be one to one
All right
It's going to be one of those episodes
Wow, this is just going to be like the other 18 sectors
I think now that you say one to one
It's just it's called a real doll, I believe
So that's possible
That's a high that's a high priced item
You can feed hot dog dinners
With an opening in the mouth
Nick, you have a relationship with the real doll manufacturers
Wait a minute
You have a full dining room tables worth
You dine with every evening
Yeah, I dress them up
We have dinner parties
It's a blast
We'll have Jason to your collection soon
In a Dunce's cap in the corner
Hey
What?
That edition is hurtful
The Dunce cap
The Dunce cap is where it went too far
We've all got to have a code
We've all got to have a line
Back off, Carlson
I said there was going to be an expensive doll
People would have sex with
That was you
Four speed hot dogs too
But the Dunce cap
Well, that's because Jason is
I think his spirit is from a time when Dunce caps actually were applied
He remembered how hurtful those were in the 40s
No greater shame
Yeah, we've lost track of
Sure
You know what?
I'm so sorry for the Dunce cap remark
Okay, thank you very much
That said, podcasts are right
Dunce caps will be available on T public
Oh, yeah, yeah
We'll get sell them all day long
That's fine
Okay, so Nick, thanks for being here
I feel like for
I imagine over the many years of Doughboys now
You have like
There's a high concentration of chain restaurants up at CityWogs
You must have been up there many a time for the show
We've probably overlapped and covered a lot of stuff that you've covered
For the show
Specific CityWalk visits we've made for I think four chains
Margaritaville
Johnny Rockets
Tony Romas
It's the only Tony Romas I think left in SoCal
And the other one we did up there is
Bubba Gum Shrimp Company, yes, yeah
And you know, it is
Yeah, not just for chains
But specifically those chains that tend to be concentrated in touristy areas
Places like Bubba Gump and Margaritaville
Like that CityWalk is the place to find them in LA
Either there or Hollywood Boulevard
The Hollywood Boulevard area is so horrible
I mean, like the city
Like if you guys are doing like 19 Hollywood Boulevard episodes
We'd want to kill yourselves
It's such a dingy unfun area
Versus CityWalk is at least something approximating a fun spot
Yeah, and it's possible to have fun there
We had fun there because
We should say before we
Explain every step of this thing that we all
The four of us
Literally did walk through every parking garage
We didn't like go stand in every space or anything
We might have skipped levels
But we did want to get a general gist of what all these places are
And that was fun
I thought we were all pretty exhausted by the end of it
Yeah, I had my full backpack which I have with me today
Because I was carrying around with all my work stuff
That was an added layer of challenge for me
But I did find it
I did have a blast
It was a real hoot
And that wasn't the only thing we did we should say
That we did other things on the
That we did other things on this trip that made it more conventionally fun
But even walking through the parking garages was fun
I like that
Yeah, and you get some odd
Some genuinely cool views of stuff
Right
There's a lot of weird talking points
But I might say that walking through the parking garages is more enjoyable than having to park in the parking garages
100%
Which not all of us did
Which all of us actively avoid to do
Yes
In all of our visits up there
Oh, wait a minute
But wait, are we talking about the parking garages today?
I don't think we know
We haven't gotten the official actual assignment
But how are we going to be sure?
Boys, boys
He's here
He's in the room
Yes, yes, I'm here and I have more strength than ever, boys
The Sector Keeper
You look great
It's like one of those milk commercials where you start small and have grown and grown
Exactly
And you're a big strapping lad now
Oh, thank you, thank you, yes
I'm so excited for Sector 19, boys
You've alluded to it
Sector 19 is parking garages
Yeah
We have it officially
Thank you
Charles Atlas, hero of the beach
Yes
Around everyone
He started small and he became the hero of the beach
I couldn't have put it better
Charles Atlas
We're all making Charles Atlas
We're all making the 60s comic book hero Charles Atlas
That guy that you worshiped when you were a young man
Yeah, I would nail away
So bullies would stop kicking sand at me
Sheridan, put down that periodical with a picture of Charles Atlas on the cover
Go sit on the corner with a dunce cap on your head
No
We did put him in a penalty box
Yeah, he did get a dunce cap
He's asking for it
Sector Giver, we're in Sector 19
Were you ever worried that we weren't going to make it?
Were you fearful during this journey?
There were times where I wasn't sure
It seems like you were getting distracted by treats at times
Oh, no, that was all pertinent and tight conversation
Yes, of course
And at other times I thought maybe I enjoyed purgatory
I wasn't sure what heaven would be like
There was a time where I met a little boy named Colton Burpo
Wow
He went to heaven once
Yeah
And he made a movie about it
Heaven is real
Heaven is real, boy
And I wasn't sure and it scared me
But now I'm getting excited
I'm getting excited because Sector 19 is the final sector
It'll be the final Sector Stone and my soul will be complete
And ideally, well, I don't know what's on the other side
But hopefully it's good
Yeah, hopefully
We're minutes away
We're only, I can assume, two and a half hours away
Based on how we do these things
But with every minute that we get through this thing
Maybe you probably don't even want to rush things along with your coughs
You're probably a little scared of what's coming at the end of the episode
I've never really mentioned this
But for every Earth minute you spend in the show
It is a hundred years for me
Wow
Oh no
You're trapped in a weird time paradox
Yeah, it's difficult
But I do understand that this sector is very tenuous and very detailed
There's lots to talk about
And it's a sequel to one, I don't know if you've talked to any other
Like anyone who keeps sectors over at Downtown Disney
If you've heard about when we did this before
But we did an episode about the Mickey and Friends parking garage
That was excruciatingly detailed
And I can't imagine being any vaguer than that time
Right
No, yes, just keep in mind a hundred years for every minute, that's all
So every minute that I'm just going on and on and on
And not getting to the point
Those minutes, you're in hell for hundreds of years
Like this one right now, this is an eternity for you
Yeah
You wouldn't believe what I've seen in the past 30 seconds
Oh my gosh
Sectorkeeper, during this time, are you like
Does it like, you feel like a hundred years worth of
I haven't eaten a meal, I haven't had a drink of water
I haven't had an hour of sleep, I haven't used the restroom
All of those, all of those
God, that sounds miserable
Everything heals slower too
Right
So if I were to pull my hamstring, it would take a hundred years to heal
And you're working your job, checking people into purgatory during this time too?
I'm still working on missions at purgatory
Oh God, well I want to say that as soon as you're free
I have a gift and I will tell you what it is
It's a DVD of the movie Gladiator
And it's just because he hasn't been
He's not supposed to pop culture before his time
After his time, excuse me
Gladiator?
Gladiator, yes, so there's a DVD of that I have for you
And that's just something to look forward to at the end, is what I'm saying
So this might feel like forever, but
Considered one of the best films of the period that you've missed from 95
Starring Nitro?
No, not starring an American Gladiator
A man named Russell Crowe, he was mostly working in Australia when you would have been alive
And then he became a big star in America
Some people think this is a bit of an art house movie, but I think it's a real crowd pleaser
Thank you, thank you
You know, I actually, Sector Keeper, and I didn't tell you guys this
But I actually have a gift for you as well
It's a CD of the debut album of Russell Crowe's band 30 Odd Foot of Grunt
So if you just want to catch up on the best music of the era
That you're not familiar with, you have that as well
Boys, you bring me strength, you really bring me strength
Thank you, thank you
You're welcome, yeah
Well, we gotta get you listening to this album and watching this film and watching all the Crowe fest
So let's get down to it, we're talking about the parking garages today
I feel like a subtext of our Mickey and Friends parking garage episode
Is that the Disney garage is so efficient and relatively pleasant for being as sprawling and teeming as it is
And it's just stressful to park there, especially with a family, no matter what
But they keep it pretty pleasant as opposed to Universal
Yes
Which is a big fucking mess
100%
It's just chaos when you go to Universal, you don't know where you're going to be parking
It feels frantic from the moment you get off the freeway
And you're approaching those parking structures, there's cones just arbitrarily blocking your way in different directions
You don't know where you're supposed to go
I feel like until the moment I'm turning into the garage, I don't know
I feel like I'm turning down the wrong way down a one-way street
It's so stressful
And then you're assigned to one of five different structures
Although in my experience I've only ever been pushed into one of three structures
The other ones are kind of enigmas to me
But the structures are...wait, no, it's six, right?
It's actually six, as we discovered
There are four structures
And then two surface lots
Oh, okay, alright, but they are still separate parking...what's the word to use?
Zones
Parking sectors, thank you
We have six mini-sectors within sector 19
So we'll label these 19A, 19B, 19C
Thank you
And then the spaces are...it's like they're smaller spaces
They're not easy to park in
It always feels like when I'm parking at Universal, it feels like I'm parking at a mall during Christmas
It's so busy and everyone's so crazy
And you just are turning and you feel like you're going to plow right into a stroller that just appeared out of nowhere
And it's gotten to the point that when I go to Universal now, I take the train or I take a lift
I try to avoid driving to it because it's such a pain in the ass
And hey, that also lets me get a little more crunk, you know what I'm saying?
Oh yeah, you know what I'm saying
Yeah, in fact, this time, we've parked up there a lot recently because we've been up there so much
This time, I think the only one of us that actually parked up there was you, Mike
You're correct
Because you were running a little late
I was running a little late and I wanted to try something out
Okay
Yeah, I don't know if it's the time to reveal or...
Should we maybe talk about more regular parking experience?
Yes, I agree, I agree
Before we... which I guess we'll just talk in order
Well, how about this? The broader parking situation
I am looking at a chart that explains how the parking works
Okay
And it is divided into several categories
It shows you the general parking, preferred parking, front gate parking, valet parking
And $5 movie parking
And then it shows you what those cost before 6pm and after 6pm
And there's various little notes within all that of how those prices differ from Sunday to Thursday
And if you're in the City Loft Club valet parking zone
Or if you have validation from a full service restaurant
Or if you've valeted for under two hours or over two hours
And here's what I have to say
This is way too much
And Universal Studios, I think particularly, caters to tourists from out of town
Yes
Who do not speak the language of English
And imagine if you just know the most basic English words
And then you are confronted with a super complicated parking diagram
Right
With vastly different quantities and prices
Like, truly, like day-changingly, you're already spending a lot of money at a theme park
And then if you go one minute over one thing, that can be $30 more, it's true madness
How could this chart be this complicated?
Yeah, it's too much
And also too, and I don't know if you were touching on that in the validation
Did you mention the movie theater?
No, we haven't
Well, that's a whole thing
A little bit in the episode
Or did we? I don't know
But that is, they do, the movie theater will validate
But the way the movie theater validates is you give them your parking receipt
And they give you cash
Well, that is how they have been doing it up till the last month
Wow, they've changed that policy?
Yes, and that might play into what I'm talking about with the hack
Oh my goodness
Oh, you used their own flaws against them
I feel like, now I've teased it too much, I guess I gotta say
Yeah, you gotta do it
With all of this, let me say a couple prices
Sure, go for it
If you're just going to, if you're going to a regular day at Universal Studios, you're paying $25
Which is more than Disneyland
Yes
$5 more than Disneyland, crazy
Disneyland is 20 all day if you go to that Mickey and Friends garage, but at least it's consistent
And I'd say Disneyland is better than Universal
Of course
Well, yeah, I'm kidding
Oh, the theme park you mean?
Oh, I was just meant the parking garage
I thought you meant the garage, too
$35 is preferred parking, which takes a couple of minutes out of your wad
It's a little less of a wad to get there
Front gate, I'm not sure where that drops you off
$50, valet if you're over there for over two hours is $45
These are heavy, priced at $45 for a two-hour, minute-long meal
This is all the stuff that you're seeking to avoid
It's why I've spent a lot of time, because I'm from here
I've spent a lot of time finding the places to park down the hill, walking up the hill
Yes
Just figuring out what's the shortest lift route to where I can get off more financially, Scott Free
There's so much to avoid, and that's why, Mike, I'm curious what you figured out to avoid
Well, I'll start by saying I think this works, because you're not supposed to park in the metro lot
No
And they're monitoring that now more than they used to
How, though?
In 2003, you were set
Well, I don't know, maybe they aren't
There's more cameras, signs are scarier
You just gotta pay
Where is the metro lot?
It's right down on Lancashire
First of all, this is not the hack
I'm just giving you another idea for a hack
But I used to do that, and now I don't feel as comfortable, because they put up a lot more signage
They have more signage, but you pay $3
Oh, it's just three
So it's $3 for the day
This is a good first hack, it's not your main hack
I have not tested this out, so don't maybe do this if you're worried
But go pay, pretend you're walking over to the escalator, and then just keep going
There's no way they can start arbitrarily towing cars that they think
As long as you paid
So that is a good way to do it
Someone would have to be watching you carefully
I would say maybe if you're going with a family, and you're clearly going to the theme park
You're wearing minion gear or whatever
Then you're going to be someone that they'll target
Like, okay, I know this person is pulling a scam
But if you're just a couple of adults
Just going to like, you might be riding the metro
Leave your thing one and thing two shirts at home though
Don't telegraph that
Or change into them up at City Wall
That's fine, put them in a bag
Keep them underneath a hoodie and not underneath a Harry Potter cloak
Or if you can, take the red line
Because it leaves you at the bottom of the hill
I've done this a couple times, walked from Ventura up the hill
The sector keeper and I walked up, just parked on Ventura
I guided you
Yes, he had two sets of footprints
We talked before in a previous Sector, Sector Keeper
About how when Mike has waking nightmares
Caused by blackout curtains
That's you calling to him
You've been summoning him for years
As he has these horrifying dreams
That's right, yes, yes
Yeah, we just figured it out
We just figured it out
Why are you doing that?
That's very mean, I think
Oh, I thought you liked it, my bad
You thought he liked it?
No, I was like, my sleep would be disturbed
Oh, well, you know, it's like a sleepover
First person that falls asleep
It's like a sleepover inside me?
Yeah, it gets razzed
Sleep in it?
But it sounds like you've been giving him a taste of your hell when you do it
Yeah, well in hell no one sleeps, only sleep paralysis
Oh, my gosh
Well, that adds up
I have another question
We've started to feel your presence looking back throughout our lives
And wondered if we had encountered you in some way
Let me just ask
If you remember the day, and I bet that you do
When you perished in the Dancing Fountains
Yes
Was it because you got in an especially long Jodie Moroney's line
And the last person in the line was a short brown haired child
Wearing a Future Lakers Club t-shirt
And that was that the thing that made you go
Oh, how about I do the Dancing Fountains instead?
Oh, yes, it's all coming back to me, yes
I think I might be responsible for your death
Oh, my God
What?
It was me, and I didn't mean it, I just wanted a hot dog
You, you, you caused my death?
I mean, it could have been anyone, I didn't, it just occurred to me
Lakers Club Boy, in your friends with Sparkies?
I don't know Sparky, I really don't, I swear
He took my place
I am not in alliance with that awful man
I know I'm in alliance with Nick Mundy now
But there's other people, otherwise I'm not to blame for anything
Bad man, bad man
Bad man, Mundy, bad man
I don't think I'm a bad man
This episode has not been released yet, I don't know what went down with Mundy
I'm very excited to learn
He tried to rearrange the order of the sectors
We all learned a lesson about friendship from it anyway
I just, if I was in any way responsible
But you would have, look, visiting the Dancing Fountain should have been a fun thing for you
No, it was fun, and I can't hold you responsible, I hold Sparky responsible
He took my place in heaven
He's the one, he's the bad man, he's the bad boy
You're not bad boys, you're good boys
Thank you
We are good boys
I think you're really backtracking here, it sounded like he was directly responsible for your death
And now you're just like, I think you're saying this to make a film out of it
Mike, tell us about that part
We gotta get to the hack, we gotta get to the hack, Liger
Who cares about the person responsible for it
I took in mind one minute, a hundred years
Yeah, that's true
You can get over a lot in a hundred years
Don't dig deeper in your memory and realize that this hypothetical boy cut in front of you and pushed you out of the way
No, no
Because that didn't happen
But I do remember that my parents went to put their names in a Bubba Gump
I was lured towards the fountains
Alright, so you were also waiting for the... your parents... it's your parents' fault
They killed you, dude
Yeah, yeah, it's their fault
Also, I had a staph infection, give me some fucking antibiotics
Whoa!
Wow
Whoa, he's learning out of Kurt
He's learning, he's truly becoming a real boy
You've given me strength, also I gotta hold a new medal
In gaining my consciousness
Oh, you know about like Limp Bizkit and stuff?
Yeah, it's awesome
Oh yeah, isn't that dope?
It is cool, yeah
Do you like West Borland and stuff, his makeup?
Oh, West is cool, his eyes, his eyes are cool
Yeah, that's hell yeah they are
He's like a devil
Homework sucks
Hey, oh boy, you're in a lot of attitude as the years come back to you
So, the hack
Alright, this is very important
So first of all
I think I know what you're gonna say
Probably, because it's sort of similar to a different hack that I've mentioned on the show before
And I honestly am a little worried about saying this because we'll lose this hack, I think
If someone listens to this, somebody will figure out a workaround
Jason is literally spinning a Mickey fidget spinner
Is that what that is?
Yeah, it's been a long day
I've been doing this occasionally
And you're so stressed out about the hack disappearing
I'm so excited, it is very calming
So anyway, I'm excited to hear about the hack
That's such a modern thing, I expect you to be playing with like a cup and ball or something
Yeah, it lights up and everything
Some jacks
It lights up, not like toys from the 1930s
I'm surprised you even know how to use that technology
If you are listening and you hear a slight whirring sound
And you'd like to complain to us about it, write us on Twitter or on iTunes
Or keep it to yourself
The hack, Mike, the hack
Boys, boys, the hack
While you're talking, Jason's just gonna push a little hoop around with a stick
Like every episode
Got a maple in here?
He's one of the little rascals, let's be honest
Okay, hack time
Here we go
Again, I'm scared, I don't want to lose this hack
But I think we have to say it
So here's what you do
Now they've taken the movie theater discount
Which is knocking it down to $5
But you should just be handed out in a dirty piece of cash
Now it is...
Which is insane, by the way
You walk up and they give you cash
They just hand you $15 in cash
Because you paid $20, $25
If you paid $25, they'll give you a $20
You just have a 22-year-old handing you a $20 bill at the end of your movie
It's like you're doing a drug deal
A lobby of the Universal Cinema
Which is crazy to think about how many 20s they have to have on hand
Because if you see, what, 500 people see a movie at a weekend
So you gotta have...
Somebody do the math
Oh, way more, way more than that
$10,000 in 20s?
There's a fucking heist to be done
Oh, wait a minute
Maybe that's why they changed the system
Yeah, because now that I think about it
They still have this cash system in place
Because it doesn't work if you book it through a fandango
It doesn't work if you book it through several other movie sites
Oh, got it
You have to book it through the AMC website
I wonder if there was some way to find out where the vault was
If there was some sort of omniscient being that knew all of the secret places of the city
Boys
I guess we'll have to talk to you off air about this one
Or behind the paywall
Patreon episode one is how to rob CityWalk of $10,000
You pay us five, but you'll get a guaranteed $10,000 down the line
Pretty good deal
Yeah, that's really good
All right, hack time
Now it feels like we shouldn't even get to the hack, right?
No, just...
Come on
All right, here's what you do
We're going in the parking garage
I thought of this last second
So this made me feel really great
Because I was doing this on the fly
I was like, you know what I can do?
I bought a movie ticket for an hour from now or whatever
For the house, that Jack Black movie that Eli Roth directed
The house with the clock in the walls
The house with the clock in the walls or whatever
And I was like, I know that they now have a digital way to get the rebate or whatever
So I bought the ticket
Got an email that said, here's your parking code
Have them scan it at the thing or whatever at the booth
And right before...
Let's add this to the Mission Impossible score, by the way
Or the Ocean's Eleven movie
And right before I got to the booth
I canceled the movie ticket and got a refund
Wow
So I showed it and I was like, I wonder if this is going to work
Because if it doesn't, then I can actually just do the same thing again in a second
Or be like, oh, I just got whatever
I'll have to do the manual thing and go get cash or something
Right
I showed it to him
It was a tense 25 seconds
And now again, I'm a good boy, so I was sweating pretty hard here
Right
He scanned it, he goes, alright, here you go
And $5 was the price
Now the only extra thing I had to pay was there's a service fee that's now refundable
So it's like $1.50
Okay
So $6.75 or $0.50 parking hack with my movie theater canceling trick
Wow
So you waited to cancel until like right before you were exit
Right before I exit
That being said, I think you can cancel after you've done it too probably
Yeah, that's the next try
So again, this is, don't tell, guys, if you're listening, don't tell anyone
Because I would like to use this in the future
Did you buy, sorry, for the movie
It was a movie that was going to be starting after you knew you were going to leave
Like you timed it out that way
No, I just, it was in an hour
An hour from when you parked or an hour from when you left?
It was like, like I said, we parked at 6.30, it was 7.30 movie
So this was a movie that you didn't, like you didn't, but wouldn't it have started?
How did you know, like when the, I guess I'm confused about when the transaction took place
I bought a ticket at 6.30 on my phone for a 7.30 movie
We went into the parking garage at 6.35
You're paying as you enter the parking garage, not as you're exiting
That's the trick now that they've changed and now their system is susceptible to my trickery
Yes
What if they start now like geo-tagging it somehow
They might
They prevent you from buying one within 100
This is the danger of me saying this on this show
First of all, what they should do is like how they, when the government finds hackers
And they're like threatened to lock them up, instead of locking me up, they should hire me
Yeah
That's what they should do
To help them make the parking more expensive?
Yes, I will find ways to clamp down on the holes in their system and add more tiers of parking
If there's an extra 30 minutes, it's another $25 in valet
Let's figure out ways to get more money out of people
I'm willing to join the team
I am willing to hire me is what I'm saying
You deserve the Frank Abagnale Jr. treatment at the end of Catch Me If You Can
Yes
You get rewarded after your life of crime with a plumb job at the FBI
That is exactly what I'm asking for
So there's the hack
That's a great hack
That's amazing
Amazing hot off the presses news
I had a hack, past tense
But I think I spoiled the hack for everyone
And it's not a hack that anybody else would have had
But here's what happened
I largely stayed on the schedule as a universal tour guide
In order to get free parking
In order to still be able to use the employee parking
Which you park in the Frankenstein lot, by the way
And the...
So I would do a shift there
Even though I had a full-time other job
I would do a shift there once a month
Partially to keep the parking situation
And to get a slight amount of money in return
But then they took me off the schedule
There were enough people they didn't need me
I was fired from that job via a letter
A form letter that went to six other people
So then I didn't have it anymore
But I still had my ID
So here's what I did
I scanned it in
I believe whenever the year needed to change
In Photoshop, I changed the expiration date
Now, I probably could have taken this a step further
And laminated my false badge
But it was always inside a plastic lanyard thing
So I just put the paper one
With another little punch card for a sandwich shop
Behind it in order to increase the thickness
And so I would go through
You can name the sandwich shop
What's that?
I don't think I know the specific one
It could have been a Jersey Mike's
I don't recall
But any sandwich shop will do
I thought you were being coy with it
I apologize
No, no, no
Any sandwich shop card can help with this scam
To get free parking at Universal Studios
So I would just
Those people are not paying a lot of attention in the booth
I'd flash that thing real fast
Oh yeah, I go through
One day after successfully doing this
Six or seven times
The guy started
He half-wayed me through
And then said, wait a minute
Oh no, a nightmare
Yeah
Stop me
Heart-beating
Good boy
Trying to keep it calm
It's like I was pulled over drunk driving
Though that certainly has never happened
This is the worst driving thing that's happened to me
This was like a hundred years for you
Wait, this waiting period
Busted by security
It was a purgatory
And so the guy eyes it
Opens the zipper
Takes out the false ID with nothing on the back
And then just looks at me and goes
I'm gonna keep this
You turn around
And he watched me turn around
And go out the main gate of Universal Studios
Wow
You fucking cad
Yes, this was something
I think I'm a more good boy today than I was then
I was really pushing it
I was young
I was dumb
I wasn't afraid of risks
So, but here's what ended up happening
Was that
The
I was worried I was gonna be put on some list
And I wouldn't be able to go back up the city walk again
But instead
The badge was handed to somebody in the front office
It was thrown down on somebody's desk
And it was, and they said
Hey, put this thing on file
We gotta watch out
This guy, Scott Gardner, who used to work here
He's now, he's using a false badge to try to get free parking
So I don't know
Just like keep an eye on him
Put him on some list
Whatever you gotta do
The person whose desk that landed on was a friend of mine
Wow
Who immediately texted me and explained
What happened?
I just got a paper ID on my desk
That's so crazy
So she was able to just crumple it up
Make sure it was like nothing ever happened
Oh my gosh
So you and I both, you're screwed
Like this is very revealing in terms of
Maybe we have to
We better cover all the other Universal rides soon
Because we might end up on some
And Jack was here
He revealed a lot of the secrets
Oh yeah, Jack was real bad
Sneaking into Universal
Right
Without paying
Wait a minute
Can I reveal mine?
Yeah
Yeah, oh my god
So this one I feel like is kind of known though
And I haven't tried it in a few years
But when I interned on the back lot
You know, I had a generic Universal kind of badge
And I would want to go up there
They told us like, oh, go to the Frankenstein lot
Go park in the Frankenstein garage
And usually just flash the badge
And they wave you through
Right
I was also like later told by someone
After I had to give that badge back
Like, oh, just go park in Frankenstein
Tell them you're there for a shoot
Or like you're going to the town office
Just tell them that
They don't give shit
That's it
That was it
And you haven't tried it in a while
I haven't tried it in a while
But you did it
I think I tried it like once or twice
Seemed to work
It worked
I've heard other people say it works
But I don't know
They may have changed that now
Because Extra wasn't shooting their extra shoots up there
And now there's a lot more production going up there now
Say you're there for Street Smarts
That's the new one
Street Smarts
Yeah, I'm just going to Street Smarts
They'll let you guys do it
That's great
You just keep abreast of what the production is
That's going on in that Universal lot
That's a great idea
Look up the name of the host of Street Smarts
I don't know it offhand
But look it up
Say you're his assistant
You got to get up to the
You're late for the Street Smarts shoot
I'm here for a Snapchat thing
They're shooting it on Snapchat
Street Smarts bonus content
Verticals
I'm a slam ball player
I thought Jason's dark universal confession was going to be
That he stole a bunch of butterscotch from Popcornopolis
Like unprocessed butterscotch
Cook it at home
Put it in the microwave
Before they mix it in the corns
Just the industrial blocks of butterscotch
It makes sense because you have a fresh glass of butterscotch every morning
Buttermilk
No, buttermilk
That's not true
I took a sip of buttermilk once
And it's disgusting
It's mostly used for baking
It's very strange
I had a joke about your eating years ago
That you regularly ate curds in way
Oh, my toughness
Yeah
God bless
The next heist that we do
Once we figure out the movie theater heist
Then we figure out the butterscotch heist
That's really the key to this
Doing all 19 sectors is we know the ground so well
That's true, yeah
Maybe this is the birth of us becoming bad boys
Maybe that's the little punch list
Bad boys
Sometimes it feels good to be bad
Whoa, wait a minute
Sector keeper himself
The influence of corn
Yeah, so have you been bad in purgatory?
Because you're always a good boy
I'm a good boy, no
But maybe you guys are rubbing off on me
Oh, okay
Our coolness is making you cool and bad
Yeah, I feel like I'm running with the cool crowd
The way you describe adulthood rules
Did you know that chocolate-covered starfish is buttholes?
Hey, whoa, Jason
Whoa, hey
I'm still a kid
Okay
But you were listening to that?
Never mind
Have you gotten to that Al Olimpiscate album?
Yeah
Oh, you have?
Yeah, I started
Have you broken any stuff since then?
Yeah, all the time
Oh, damn
Oh, boy
Wow, there's going to be no purgatory by the time you're left
Yeah, well, I just feel like I'm so close
You guys are doing so well and you're giving me strength
Oh, yeah, but I guess we'll really give you all the strength
if we start talking about each individual parking garage
Yeah
Here we go
Get ready, listeners
That's what's happening
Unless there's more hacks to go through
Not right now, at least
Nope
All right, let's go in the order that we walked through them with
Yes
So we started in Curious George
Right
You know what?
I'll hold off my thought on the theming
I will say generally, because there's one thing I want to zero in on
a few garages from now
But in general, the theming is chaos
It's completely incoherent
There's nothing running through it
It's kind of like, you know, you've got the Toy Story lots over at Disneyland
and it's kind of, you know, you get that, okay, these are all Toy Story characters
They've zeroed in on something specific
Mickey and Friends, they're all Mickey characters
They're like the canonical main Mickey characters
Here it's just sort of like it's all over the place
There's stuff for kids, there's stuff for adults
There's like classic movie monsters
There's modern franchises
It's just like Universal's library of franchises
It's just all over the place
And some are characters
Some are characters
Like you see in Curious George, but some are a whole film
Some are a whole film
It's very confusing
But Curious George, you know, I will say that I like the signage
The signs look nice
And it's a five level parking structure
At least that's what my notes say
The view, so actually parking at Curious George is not pleasant
This is one of the three structures that I parked at before
You know, none of them I think are
None of them are appreciably better or worse than the others
At least that's my take
That's my layman's take
You guys are experts, you may have a better, a more nuanced view of the lots
as we can comparison to each other
But they're all like kind of like unpleasant to park in
But the, you know, I guess we're going to
What we did is we went to the top levels of each of these structures
And the top level of Curious George has pretty good views of downtown Burbank
Good views and good views of universal backstates
Yes, that is actually nice
We were looking over the big like holding area where I discovered Botanicus
Back in the day
The rotting Botanicus
And we saw some stuff back there that is maybe a spoiler
Or it was just something temporary that they are storing
It's half a dinosaur next to a bunch of port-a-bodies
Right
And we wondered out loud if that's a dinosaur being added to the Jurassic World's re-theme of the Jurassic Park ride
However, I think if that was a complex animatronic, they wouldn't just leave that sitting around
But Botanicus was just sitting around
Botanicus is out and obviously he was not being installed into the ride, but still, you know
So yeah, or it could just be like less mobile robots, you know, maybe they're adding a couple other things
Who knows? It was big though
And probably just for a photo op, but who knows
It looked like it might have, what is it?
It's the I-Rex, is that what it is?
Oh, the Indominus Rex
The newer Indominus Rex
It looked a little different than Indominus Rex though
Was it the one in the new one?
Is there another new one?
They engineer a hyper killer one
That's worse than the I-Rex?
That's worse than the I-Rex
Because the I-Rex was bad
They can aim like a sonar gun at a target and shoot it and the dinosaur can track the sonar at that target
Oh, okay. I don't know if that was this one
But so if you go to the top of Curious George, you maybe get some universal spoilers along with getting an actually amazing view of Burbank and Toluca Lake and a lot of the San Fernando Valley
I will say this, I took a lot of photos while we were up there
Some of the prettiest, nicest photos I've ever taken on my phone camera
It was kind of around sunset, I was getting some cool lens flares
And somebody gave us the tip, and I don't know if we take this because we're good boys, but in this episode maybe we're turning a little
Maybe we're becoming bad boys
But somebody on Twitter or somewhere told us that's a good spot to maybe roll up your car, roll down your window, get a little high
Wow
Would you guys ever?
No
Do we dare?
I think it was a listener said like get a little stone and watch the sunset from Frankenstein, I think Frankenstein gives a different angle
But the top of Frankenstein is the theme park
So you wouldn't be able to go to the top of it
But yeah, beautiful views of the sunset up here and the San Fernando Valley and the mountains
This is a good tip I would say, if you're coming to LA for the first time, taking out a towners, go to the top of this garage or the one next to it that we'll talk about
Great views, great photo spots
And similarly, if you want a good picture by the Hollywood sign, look up the Hollywood Reservoir and the Hollywood Dog Park
That's really where you want to go to find parking, get photos
Just a nice little tip because you don't want to go up the streets that a lot of people live on
Bother neighbors and stuff
It's also too, and I think people can perhaps infer this from our tour of these garages
But you can, unlike some theme parks, you can very easily just walk into each of these garages if you so desire
You can just go ahead and go on a walking tour through them if you want to get to the roof and check out those views
Which we did
Send us those pics if you do it, walk in our footsteps, do the legendary walk
Like Christ's walk up the hill with the cross
This is now the second best walk to do a tour of
Speaking about the parking, so the actual process of parking, I feel like the
Actually pulling up to the gates is fine
It's not like once you're in the structure, I don't feel like I'm
It's too chaotic in terms of figuring out which gate to go to to pay
But I think once I'm actually inside the lot, there's less direction than I would like
I like at a theme park when they're just waving you into a specific space and you're being guided down a different
You almost don't have to think about where you're going to park
Here I think there's a little bit too much discretion left to the driver
Which creates bottlenecks and also creates additional stress
And also I feel like too, the ceilings for these levels I think are a little low
It feels a little cramped
I also feel like I'm pulling in and there's an employee there who suddenly starts gesturing in a way of like
No, no, no, that way, that way, suddenly it's really hurried and you're doing something wrong
But why? I don't know what the problem is here
One person calls in sick, the whole thing could fall apart
Because they seem to have half the amount of people flagging and waving people in than Disney does
Because Disney literally, as you're saying, walks you through it, it makes it dummy proof
Here we went in, this is one of the many parking stories we have
A couple months ago, Lindsay and I, she has an electric vehicle
And they put a little thing on the front of your car that says EV and then they point you to where you go
At a certain point, there was no employee anywhere to tell us where to go
There were three choices, we chose one, it took us out of the parking garage and into the Curious George parking garage
Which does not have electric vehicle parking
So we were like, what the hell?
Like we were trying to figure out where we were going
We went out of the ET parking garage into Curious George
Then had to exit Curious George, exit all the way
And then go back into the ET and go like, hey we just paid, where are we going?
And they're like, oh, go and then they pointed us and we finally figured out what to do
But that shouldn't happen
You should be flagging, you should be really hardcore on every car
Because it's a big confusing place
Conversely, when we were up there walking through
The most universal employees I've ever seen because it was the second weekend of Horror Nights
So they had cones everywhere, there's people everywhere, there's tons of people
What was that for?
Horror Nights
Oh yeah, it's scary to us too
When you're a full grown bad boy, you're going to be into that
Yeah, you're going to think that's cool
Okay, I just always think, what if one guy takes it too far and really gets in your face
It feels like there's not a lot of oversight, I don't know
What if all the seasonal hires who are not usually around
Were just there for that month and they would essentially hire anyone
What if one of them brought a knife into their job for the day
Or they put the chainsaw they have that doesn't have the blade on it
What if he snuck the blade in somehow?
He swallowed the blade in a little bag
Oh, because he knows he's a sicko
Not that, because he gets to go through a metal detector
So maybe he put a lined bag with the blade inside his stomach
And then he shit it out and put the blade on to
That's true, could be a ceramic blade doesn't set off a metal detector
Could be a ceramic, you could probably 3D print a blade now
And you could take a plate from any universal restaurant, shatter it, use the piece
Shove it into the throat of some Halloween Horror Nights ghost
You're making me not want to go as I've continued to not go for many years
I said we should go this year, Jason of course said no
And I said it would be funny, but we'll talk about it
We'll talk about it, and we've got some stuff coming up for this
The most spookiest month of the year
Maybe Sector Keeper you can go when you're free and you're real
Do they let fourth graders go or is that too young?
I think you can go, right?
I think you can go, I think they advise against it
If you're with your cool uncles
Then you could go with
Yeah I should mention, you're my guardians
Oh, wait, that's the deal?
Like once you're free we take care of you?
At the moment, yeah, I mean I'll do my best, but
Oh, because he doesn't know where his dad is, or where his family is
The host of podcasts, the writer, your legal guardians?
Yes, and then when they can't do it, you can, right?
I mean yeah, I guess so
The most read, the last guest out the door in the Sallena Saga series
Would have to take care of
If that's okay
I'm okay with the wider part, certainly as for us
I mean is this some binding document that if from the afterlife
Like it's kind of above our heads so we have to do it
Or is this just like you're where you just want us to be your uncles?
Is there a difference in your hearts between the two?
Great question, legal responsibility helps make the case
Why don't we just see what happens when we get all 19 stones together?
Who knows, maybe you transform and you're the age you're supposed to be
Oh, that's interesting
You won't need a guardian
We're not, I don't know
But he'll be like big and he won't know how to live on his own
Right, right
You saw big, that was in your time
Yeah, yeah, I loved it
Well you might end up living a big life, we'll see
It also sounds like Weger will watch me, right?
I mean, if we've established like a line of succession
I think the odds are pretty low that all three of these guys are going to be
A separate malady
Yeah, they're all gonna be incapacitated and I'm gonna have to take control
So I guess I'm okay with that
Okay, cool, alright, let's keep going
Boy, be careful, yeah, I get caught on a technicality
Well, let's go to a more pleasant, less scary character than these Halloween Horror Nights murderers that we've been discussing
Let's talk about our old pal ET
Yes, so we took a land bridge from Curious George over to ET
Which was, we were very, we were actually like a little, you know, speaking to you guys being good boys
We were like a little worried because there was a universal employee at the end of this ramp that connects the two structures
And we were a little worried that this guy was going to give us some guff walking over there instead of driving on this, through this roadway
But we just went for it
Can the listeners guess who was the most worried about this?
Who was the most hesitant?
I'm trying to even remember who was it
Who do you think?
Jason?
It was me
It was you, sir
Yeah, I felt like you were very hesitant to step foot even onto the-
I was hesitant because it was a pathway but it was kind of like a blocked off path
Let's say this though, we shouldn't have been walking there
Right
Probably not
Because if a-
If it's open to pedestrians and there was a little-
There was a little walkway but the walkways had things jutting out in front of them
So there was no clear sidewalk to walk
Yes
So I think in the official universal rule book that was against the rules
And I think that that's for sure
What is the line for if not for pedestrians to walk in?
I thought it was just a shoulder
I thought it was just like a little bit of-
Fair
Semperi shoulder
A freeway doesn't have a sidewalk
Yeah
They don't want- there's no practical reason to have people walking from parking garage to parking garage I don't think
I mean that's-
To get to their vehicle in the dense web of many confusing parking garages
If your car breaks down on the tiny bridge between ET and Curious George
Then you need a place to go out there and wait for the tow truck to come
So you go over and-
That's very true
That's just shit on the little sidewalk there
I was initially nervous and then I gambled like this guy probably doesn't give a shit
Or like-
Your gamble was correct
Yeah or this guy was distracted by the incoming-
He had a job to do
There was a lot of cars coming in
Right
And that's what he had to do because yeah Horror Nights was like an hour from starting
We survived the pedestrian- not the pedestrian we survived the auto bridge, the first obstacle of our journey
We made it
Yeah
We made it into the ET structure and went up to the top and went to the furthest space that you could possibly park from the theme park
Yes
Which the number was 7W
Yeah so this is a 7 level structure
If you're in ET 7W you are the furthest from the- which if you think about that the furthest corner of Universal Studios is probably the Transformers ride all the way
It's like miles away, it's a literal miles long walk
I- when we were up there because there was that level was huge and completely vacant
The exposed roof level and I was just thinking like man how fun would it be to ride some bikes up here?
Sure
Just like this giant open space to just ride around, that'd be a hoot
They might let you, there's bike racks in these lots now
I bet if you brought a bike there and you went to the top level and you were just riding around while it was unoccupied you could do it for a while without anyone bothering you
Yeah I would be a little stressed out doing it
Yeah definitely
I mean I'd be stressed out doing it too because I mean I would- it might be fun to try
Sure
A little stressed out doing our little- we did a little photo shoot up there, we took some pictures
That's true
You were stressed out about that?
You know what I was more stressed out, Nick and I talked about this when we were up there
This stressed me out more, they had blue light phones like every few spots
Yeah
If you have been on a college campus you might know the blue light phones of like pick this up if there's an emergency
Right
And they built those into the new garage
That stressed you out?
Yeah
So it indicated that there was not extreme security and that maybe like a Segway car, a Paul Blart might take a long time to get up to that level to help you
Well I think Jurassic Parking is so close to CityWalk, I don't think there's a lot of that there
All of it is close to CityWalk
Yeah but this is like the farthest away from like if you needed security or something
Yes
So I think it was a call box essentially
Yeah and you know maybe it's for auto trouble but I don't know and maybe it's something that was put- installed in the years before you know widespread cell phone ownership
But it did make me think like oh this is a high crime zone
Please
Well and I don't want to dwell on this but there was a murder in a CityWalk parking garage
Wow
And it's really bad, it's not a funny murder
Oh my god
It's an awful murder and it does indicate that there's enough uncovered ground up there that something bad could happen
Sure
And now one of you make a joke
Yeah
What in your mind would constitute a funny murder?
Clown dying?
Well I guess it would
Yeah sure, I don't know somebody, I guess somebody falling off the structure wouldn't be funny
No yeah
But if he you know if he landed flat and a marching band walked over him like they could gun then yeah
Oh if one person falls in an open manhole, oh no that's tragedy
Yes
As he takes a flick of his fidget spinner and looks wistfully into the distance to think about years gone by
A million people die, no yes comedy one person falls in it
I was more reacting to what you did after the thought
You know what I realized on the back of the little petals of this fidget spinner there are drawings of fidget spinners
That's cool
Yeah
That's awesome
Post pics of that for the audience
I think this is the quote, I think it's a version of this, it's comedy is one person falling into an open manhole and dying
Tragedy is when I stub my toe
It's like the idea that something that happens to me is tragic no matter how small and something is comedic if it happens to someone else even if it's like horrific
Right that's it
You know since we're talking manholes to get us to a lighter point
I'm probably jumping around I think this was in the Frankenstein lot but I'm not totally sure where but in one of the universal parking garages in the 90s
There was an event that was only open for two weekends where you could go down a manhole and who would you meet but your pals the teenage mutant
Oh my god
Yeah you love them
I would have lost my mind
They're still around they're still kicking ass there's a promo for this I'll put it on the Twitter but yeah seeing kids like sneak down they turned the top level of a parking garage
That's so cool
Into a sewer
Oh my god
Legitimately cool there were TV ads for it that were fully produced even though it was only open for two weekends apparently but a friend of mine David Love went and in addition to that you could get like crazy turtle kinds of pizza
You could get pizza with gummy worms on it and stuff like that
That's so awesome
Oh heck yeah
Yeah that's your kind of food
And I just somebody was just telling me about this because I got to do it when they were a kid and you would get a free figure
Yeah
You would get a free and it looked like it was original
This is insane
It was original line figures it was all the original like you know just the turtle splinter shredder April you would get a free one and he said like you would just go back in line and get like you could go every day
This sounds like something that your liar friend would say at school
Yes
You know except that it's true
Yeah
You know like your liar friend would always be like oh they're working on Super Mario 4 and it will be out like next month and you'll be like what are you talking about
I have a Ninja Turtle version of Liar Kid he goes I saw that I don't know what he called trailer the preview for the Ninja Turtle movie he goes there's a in the movie Leonardo takes his sword and slices Crane in half
And I was like what?
Whoa
Oh my god
It's much more grizzly than anything in a turtle movie
But I thought that that was going to be in the movie when I saw the movie
It's not true
You didn't see it? It was out
Yeah I know I think about it I saw it
That seems like you're lying now
That seems like you didn't see it
It's okay you didn't see it
It's okay to say it
Yeah I just I don't know I just wanted to fit in
Hey Sector Keeper good news there's like three or four more Ninja Turtle movies you can see and like a dozen different cartoons with different animations
There's so much content
Cool
Yeah
They should make cause like now in this era of you know they've got we're building Harry Potter land we're building Star Wars land in this era they should build a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle sewer that you could go into and hang out in and you could just sort of like
They've got a pizza joint down there they've got turtles walk around characters they've got kind of like their sort of lab laid out I mean that would be fucking amazing
Yeah dads and sons and daughters and moms would all enjoy it
Yes all the types
All the types would enjoy it
All the quadrants right cause Ninja Turtles has reached a point where people who grew up watching it now have kids yeah well they should 100% do this that actually described it sounded amazing
This is one of the great properties that is untapped in theme park world and only was for two weekends apparently and there was a live show in Disney World but that wasn't much
Yeah but they would have to settle on one style of turtle unless it's a historical thing and they try to do all the styles of turtle
Well I mean you know they've got a color scheme they've at least decided upon that
Make them the theme park exclusive turtles a different design there's already 10 different designs let's make the 11th be the theme park exclusive turtles
And give them a little dick like you're Leonardo
Yeah post a picture of that little dick
We will post a photo of Leonardo's little dick with a set of cupids right over your shoulder
Yeah I love it's cool
Yeah somebody said a turtle's sex organ is in his tail so that is Leonardo's dick
Oh the toy
We're all staring at a turtle dick
Whoa Weiger Weiger easy you're gonna okay alright you're gonna break the toy
Make us put you in the penalty box again
So yeah turtles
He climbed over me to get it
I just want a closer look
So the ET garage this is new though you mentioned like oh did they put the emergency phones out there
This was built in conjunction with like oh we need more parking for the Harry Potter
This is two or three years old
Wow this is that recent
Yeah
Okay
That's why they have the electric vehicle charging in the bay in the lowest level
And then cool tunnel the ET tunnel
The ET tunnel is fucking awesome
Yeah it's this blue lit up hallway looks like something from a music video
Right
And ET's there and the moon is there and the bikes are there
It looks great and honestly it's like one of the best photo ops I think in CityWalk
Like it's just such a cool like that's worth the trip over to that ET parking garage if you like just cool shit to look at
I am surprised though hearing that this is a recent build
Why call it ET which is not the most irrelevant of properties in this day and age
Especially if it's built for Harry Potter demand
Like why not a Harry Potter
You know I wonder because there are no Harry Potter lots
I wonder if because there's no levels either right that ever have Harry Potter
I wonder if that's in the JK Rowling agreement that like Harry isn't a fucking parking garage character
Right
He lives in Hogsmeade or whatever in Hogwarts castle
I wonder because it seems like that they have such a specific like hold on that to not use it in certain ways
Like Harry can't just be hanging
Like for instance if Harry was around when that Trump photo was taken with The Apprentice
Harry would have been barred from appearing with Trump
There's this crazy photo where Trump is like clearly in the middle of you're fired
And he's with Curious George and Frankenstein
And Shrek is there
Bizarre tableau
They're all dressed like Trump except for the mummy who doesn't have Trump pants
He has his regular mummy legs
Right
Otherwise and since they're all suited characters they're all looking in different directions
So Shrek doesn't know where the camera is nor does Frankenstein
It's great
And if that had been the furthest Trump had ascended in power
I would love Trump
He's friends with Shrek
Of course
A friend of Shrek is a friend of mine
Do we have more about ET or do we keep marching?
ET is the best parking garage
Yes that is
High ceilings even though we got lost in it
They just really the problem with it is the cleanest they need more employees directing
But like when you go down to electric vehicle charging it's very spacious
I mean the ceiling is high it's fairly nice
You go right to the escalator there's a little bridge and then you're over there
If all the parking garages were like that I think you've got it's a whole different ballgame
Absolutely
Half the size of Mickey and Friends for those keeping track of fans
Interesting
Wow
That's a pretty mighty parking garage and still only half the size pretty crazy
Let's keep marching to Jurassic Parking
Which we tried to walk into and we got up to the end of some stairs that led nowhere
Even though there was a big sign that said Jurassic Parking
I think everyone likes that it is Jurassic Parking
That's fun and you see people Instagram that or tweet that
I just wanted to mention real quick because you were talking about walking up those stairs
One of the things we walked by climbing those stairs were some bad kids sitting on the stairs vaping
And that's just like an element that you have to compete with at CityWalk
Because there's some roughnecks about it
And I kind of like
It is the kind of thing where I'm so much more of a Disney guy that that element of CityWalk
When I'm around like oh I might just stumble upon some deviant youth
I'm just like I'd rather not deal with that
I'd rather be around some wholesome families having a good time
Yeah say that for the walk over like I did
When you're down at the metro stop
But yeah Jurassic, the pun
Okay I like the pun in isolation
But in the context of the other lots it doesn't work
Because one is called Jurassic Parking
And then the other just named like the name of the property or the name of the character
Frankenstein Parking
Exactly you have to make some sort of effort at puns for the rest of them
Or you don't do the Jurassic Park one
Because that's also too that's the one that's not a character
Like a lot of them yes, Curious George and E.T. are the names of the franchises
But they're also the name of the characters
Jurassic Park is not a character
It is a I mean in a sense Jurassic Park the setting is a character in the film of course
In the same way that New York is a character in Woody Allen's Any Hall
Oh fuck I never thought of it like that
But it's like it's so
But it should be like the Ian Malcolm lot or something like that right
It should be like a character from Jurassic Park
If it was the Velociraptor lot
If it was that sexy Ian Malcolm that everybody likes online
And that with that artwork
That would be great
I mean that's a little too body for me
It's also bleeding
Everyone forgets sexy Ian Malcolm is bleeding
Make it as you're saying E.T. is a little old
Like make it the new character you know the main character of Jurassic World
That character that we all can name right now
Oh you Chris Pratt's character
No but his name we know his name
One two three four Owen Grady
Of course right
Owen Grady everyone said it
I definitely didn't say Jonathan Borg I said Owen Grady
I think is Grady's last name?
Yes
Yes it is
There will be no further discussion at this point because it is
I agree
Jurassic Parking is really where it gets chaotic
That's where chaos theory unfolds
That lot sucks
Yes I think that's I think I would call that the worst
It's the most claustrophobic and it's the one where
If you park in there you don't know where you're going to come out
You don't know if it will be in the food court
You don't know if it will be above the Bubba Gump
I think there's still another one like under the Skechers
It has many exits and you don't know which one it's going to be
If you're trying to meet friends you don't know how to meet them and where
A lot of times you have to immediately like walk to the edge of it
And then go down to get to what feels like Gramp
But like it can trick you into thinking like wait no I thought I was on Gramp
But it's like no you might have to go down one or two escalators
It has a light tunnel too similar to ET
I think it's just not as good
No it's not
It also has an area that has caused us a lot of turmoil
And that is the valet lot
And we have several instances of parking in the valet lot to talk about
I think Peter complained about this a little bit when he was on
But we've had some incidents as well
Would you like to talk about I believe you have one but there's also another story
I have a valet
I tried valeting in both of the Frankenstein and Jurassic Park
Mr. $90 huh?
Well there were seven they were $7 because I had meals
Set a timer and sprint to your destination
Yeah man that's stressful
I did the Jurassic Park honestly the Jurassic Parking valet even though it's not as nice aesthetically because it's older
That went or no excuse me I reversed that
That one actually is nicer than Frankenstein
Frankenstein valet
Well do we save it for Frankenstein?
Yeah that's what maybe
Because the other story we have is about Jurassic
So should I is that what you're getting at?
Alright so here's what's happening earlier in the series in a previous sector
We pre-recorded some thoughts about a valet incident with our guest Jason Walliner
And now we turn to a pre-tape
Hey future us it's we're back here in sector three having just recorded with Jason Walliner
Yeah what are your lives like now I want to know
How is it going up there in three weeks from now?
Yeah you got to be having a blast especially wandering around the parking garage
Anyway so we're here to talk about our experience with Jason while you're here
Because you utilize the valet parking at City Walk and had a particularly odd experience
Yeah I found out because I was going there to meet a friend a couple months ago at Margaritaville
And they said if you valet you can get it validated at Margaritaville or Bubba Gump
Or any of the sit down restaurants not the fast food places
But any of the sit down restaurants validate and instead of 25 bucks it's like 7 dollars
So I valeted and then we went and checked out sector three
And then you guys kind of walked me around and talked about the other sectors
And then you guys had wisely parked outside of the camp property
I was dropped off by my wife you guys walked from very far away in the neighborhood
So I was going to give you guys a ride back to your car
So I got it validated at Bubba Gump having not eaten there
Which is kind of a hack that I came up with
I walked into the gift shop and I was like hey could you validate this
And she did
So I didn't say that I had eaten there
Do I come off bad in this anecdote?
No I mean we're good boys as you know on this podcast
So we're a little uncomfortable by it but we've straight here and there
We've done some things similar to this
Jack Allison ripped off City Walk more than any other guest
So you're not as high on the spectrum as Jack on the ripoff spectrum
How did he do it?
Well the audience has heard this now back in whatever sector he was in
But he snuck into Universal he put highlighter on the back of his hand and said it was a stamp
Oh that's much more than just elevation here
But you were punished then
That actually, slightly less future us knows that
Past us maybe shouldn't know that
Oh boy we're hitting some paradoxes
So then we went to the valet and to pay the $7 I was planning to pay
And then the guy was like $45
I was like what? No I got the, do you not see the Bubba Gump stamp on my ticket?
And he points to the sign which says, I can send this to you guys if you want to put it on the Facebook group
Should we blur the guy's face?
So the unvalidated it's $25 for 2 hours, 45 after 2 hours
Validated it's $7 for 2.5 hours, 15 for up to 3.5 hours and then 45 after that
And we were like just over 3.5 hours or I was because I got there a little earlier
So the tiers of this to say those prices again
Yeah it's $7, 15, 45
It comes from 15 to 45
It makes sense that once you get to 3.5 hours if you have the balls to present them a validated ticket
Thinking you'll get a discount but you spent 3.5 hours there
They want to say to you no you're not getting any discount
Like you obviously, you didn't come here just to eat
You came here to enjoy this place and you're going to pay like anyone else
But Mike was saying, well there's the trick
The upside is he knew a trick that when you valet they give you a golden token
Official golden City Walk coin I'm holding in my hand for a coffee machine
A sort of instantly or hot chocolate
You know you pick your drink
One side of the coin says City Walk, one side says Cup of Joe
So these are specially made
Oh yeah and he told us that while we were walking over he was like you gotta get that token
You have to ask for it because I've seen people not ask and not get it
And so I was like $45 I validated it and he's like look at the sign
It doesn't matter after 3.5 hours and I was like well can I at least have my token please
And he went yeah sure and handed it to you and then we went around the corner
And the machine has a giant Aldebaran sign on it
And there's no way he didn't know that the machine is broken right
He would already have gotten into it a little with him
$45 what do you mean yeah that's what it is it's on the sign
Okay can I have the token?
Just give me the damn token
Yeah go get your coffee white don't you
It's like the last little bit of
He got a dig in at you at the end
Yeah
The reveal as we rounded the corner that the coffee machine that you spoke of so highly
You as if clear dialogue in a film you have to get the token to get that coffee
Oh that sounds good I love getting free coffee at places
Yeah there was
Alright let's go get the coffee turn the corner out of order
Also he should have given us four tokens for our troubles
Good point every time
That was never going to happen
He's only been one so yeah that seems that seems like a pie in the sky kind of a thinking there
That's too much money they don't want to piss away
So this was a disastrous encounter
As well as my valet parking experience
Presumably I'm not sure how this is going to plug into the episode but we're probably about an hour and 45 minutes deep into
Complaining about other parking issues so this settles right in and helps us
And we'll pass the baton to Nick Weiger now and see where he takes this discussion
But I'd like to just point out though that this makes Jason Wollner a four time guest
I don't know if that really matters
Four time is cool
Oh wow
Yeah well congratulations
Anything you'd like to say to Nick Weiger
Wish him luck on the episode
Yeah good luck and yeah just go for it just you know yeah here's the baton
And just like me in the past I now hold that golden coffee cup point in my hand
There it is
From the story from 15 sectors ago
From the very story
Wow
I've held it on to my person this whole time
Is that ebayable
Maybe
It is now with photos with certification
Well as we learned from Jason in the prior episode if we get a photo of Leah Thompson
Signing it or something next to it then that validates everything
But anyway that story just meant to show the madness and the depths that the valet situation
Can lead people to $45 cards and coins there's so much confusion
Yeah I was just gonna say I set it off there but I should have set it on my story is worse
Wow
Yeah exactly but when we get to Frank I mean maybe we'll write here but whatever you're gonna say
Well the other lots I don't have much to say about
The last thing I'll say about Jurassic Parking is there shouldn't be a situation at a theme park
Where people are stalking people leaving
Which is one of my I hate when people in a parking garage wait and sit and wait for somebody to pull out
I agree
There's gonna be another space just move you're stopping the whole thing from like
Oh that's the worst
Following people but this parking garage is constantly it's happening and it's so narrow
That it's hard to go around sometimes it blocks the whole thing up
Yeah
Like it's the worst parking garage there
The most bottlenecks
And that especially like because there's you know there's no employees there and at that point
It's been filled up because I think they must fill this one up early
Well this one I think is kind of where you it's not a guarantee but if you're coming from Lancashen
This is probably where they'll direct you again no guarantees
I'll say this about Jurassic Parking it's got a nice little the valet part has a nice little lighting
Yes that's nice
Popcorn lights
That is nice
And when I went up for my solo buka meal
I got the coffee machine was working and I had a nice
Oh hell yeah
Oh there you go
There are happy endings
So that was good
The first time too when I went up and I did the Jurassic Parking valet that's the cough
That's when I learned about it I went I got Johnny Rockets validated and I had like a hot
Cocoa in my car on a 90 degree day
With no lid filled right to the top
With no lid yeah
But it sounds like we've had two positive experiences and two negative which is not a great ratio
So yeah as far as Jurassic Parking that's those are my thoughts
Jurassic Parking should be chained
They need to do some work
They gotta do something
Demolish it
Blow it up like Jurassic Park itself
Yes
It's time for a site two
Yeah
Bomb it like they did at the end of the first book
In the book and not
Isla Nublar was bombed I believe yeah that's right
Because they weren't thinking about it the sequel
Right like the Jurassic Park franchise the
There's just so much peril and danger and honestly like inconsistent quality in Jurassic Parking
And you know I mean that's just an issue
I would say that for hearing your guys' valet stories I've never attempted to valet universal
But it seems like the valet hacks are high risk high reward
Like the reward is like getting $7 parking that's great
But the risk of getting $45 parking is just so punishing
Like that is just it's such a
It's crazy and I'll say bigger picture I think the general parking rates
It really seems like early generation CityWalk
It seems like they wanted the locals to come
Now it seems like they're trying to keep people out
It's pretty hostile in terms of how expensive it is
Yeah I mean even like I guess like oh after six o'clock $10
I guess that's okay but you can go to other malls in L.A. and park for free
It's just a mall you can go yeah it's like you know what's another comparison
The Grove the Grove parking is no is you have to pay at the Grove
But it's nowhere near as expensive as it is at CityWalk
And there's much better stuff to do there
There's more stuff there
It is better
Yes
So why how does CityWalk hang on and especially how do they hang on when this is how they treat their parkers
It's just such a it's a small amount of real estate
Yeah
That's the problem because there's a if there wasn't a theme park attached to it that's the issue here
Right
Because the theme park lives on sucking parking money out of people
Yes
And there happens to be one that's just plugged in next to it
So it's impossible to take that element out of the because everyone would be parking up there for free then
It's serving dual purposes and that's its downfall
But if you went to Shoe Palace and bought like a 50 or 60 dollar pair of sneakers
And they won't validate like that's crazy
Yeah
And then you spent $25 for parking
But they probably worried about like a trick where you would like get it valid
Like there would be so many ways to validate general parking it would be like crazy
Yeah I mean the only way to live in LA for sustainable amount of time is to figure out all the tricks
Sure I hear what you're saying
These tricks that we're giving you if you're thinking about moving to LA
These will be crucial
This might be
Or you could not go to CityWalk at all
But don't do that
That's not a way to live
You want to go to the Americana
You want to go to the Americana park at the Galleria by the Target
It's free
Let me do my story then
Yes please
Let me ask what we got for Frankenstein
We'll start here
Okay
So this was at the Bucco di Beppo episode
Or Pepo as Jason called it on the episode
Remember everything
What is it supposed to be called?
Bucco di Beppo
B
B not a P
Where did you get Pepo?
I think I was saying Beppo
You said Pepo and Scott says like oh he doesn't even say it right
Beppo
You said Pepo
And in that one episode you did say that's a good note to go down on
Hey 24 7 365 something stays on my mind right folks?
No
Oh whoa
Do you know what that even don't even
Do you know about Runaway?
The Kanye West song
You know you don't even know who he is
No
Jason's being naughty
Yeah naughty
Okay so
So we're back to
I think if I remember when I was amongst you during that time
You blamed it on having Philly mouth
Well I did that is true
You mush mouth it a little bit
Philly mouth
We get so angry sometimes we can't even finish the words correctly
Bucco di Pepo but it's Beppo
Beppo?
Yeah
Yeah you're saying it right now
The sector keeper told you a long time ago
So you did think that was Pepo
That was not just a Philly mouth
No I know it's a B
Oh you do
Beppo
You're saying P though
You're definitely out loud saying P
Pepo
And I guess you're thinking about P too
Tell us your fucking story
Okay my fucking story
Frankenstein valet it was the Monday episode
And Monday and I were running a little late
We had just come from an important digital content
That we were involved in some digital content
Very cool
On Wilshire
Really?
And yeah so we were running a little late
And we were coming
I was like you know what
We're gonna valet
It's gonna be right there
It's gonna be no problem
I thought we were going to the Jurassic valet
It's impossible to figure out how to get to
One specific parking structure
Like if you're coming up Lancashire
I'm like I know where we're supposed to go
And I thought we were going in the right spot
But we ended up in Frankenstein
Which is on the other side of City Walk
From the Bucco di Beppo
And so we went in
I go no problem valet
We just walk across City Walk
It's still you know six seven minutes
But not a big deal
We go to valet
Everything's fine
We have the keys
We have a nice time
I get a free hat
It's lovely
We go back
And it's about 9.30
It was not a late night
We got there at 7.05 or something
And I know
Because I checked texts of like telling Scott
We're here
So I go up
I put the ticket down
And the guy goes $25
And I go no no no
I go it's I was here
For under two hours
And he goes no you were here at six
Like 15
And I go no
There's no way I was here for six
At six fifteen
He goes the card says six fifteen
I was like but
And I'm just like I don't know how many
I go I can show you text messages
That say I'm here
I go there's no way
I got here at seven oh five
That's not
I'm not crazy
And the guy's like it says six fifteen
$25
And I was like but you don't understand
I'm not trying to scam you or anything
I go it's truly I ate dinner
And then we went to the hat store
And we're here
I'm not he goes
And then I see the valet
So now I'm to a person that's just watching this go down
I'm a madman
I see a valet
I go hey oh hey hey
You remember like I came in
Like a little while
He looks at me like he's never seen me in his whole life
And he's like oh I don't hey I don't know
I'm not sure
I go but I came in earlier
And I go you know it was like around seven o'clock
And the guys are going I don't know man
I'm so I don't know I don't know what you're talking like
He just was like I don't need to deal with this maniac
And I go back up there I'm like I don't
And Monday was just sitting over
Like far away just looking at his phone
He was not involved in this at all
I kind of wish he was
Because I think he would have like put his fist through the glass
He's always saying he'll stick up for us
Right
And beat somebody up for us
This was his chance
He loves
He didn't say it
He loves talking about how like
The acquaintances of his
He would like bring a gun and meet them
Somewhere downtown if they asked him to
He said that about Evan Susser
He said I don't know Susser that well
But if he needed me to kill somebody for him
In the middle of the night I would do it
Quote Nick Mundy
He did say that yeah
We were talking on the phone
And he's sitting there ignoring
This crisis you're in
Yes he could have come in and like
He I'm not a tough guy
He's a tough guy
He could have really intimidated this guy
And this guy and I are just having a standoff
And I'm like
I'm feeling crazy because there's no
Chance
That we pulled in at 6.15
There's no chance
Hold on so was the card time stamped
Yes
So what must have happened is somebody
Timestamped a card before
I was even in there and they didn't even realize it
Yeah that's shady fucking business
That's so crazy
You're supposed to use
You're paying a premium to use the valet
You're supposed to get a different level
Of service
And it wasn't even like
The guy who couldn't
And again these people are
Who knows how they're paid or treated
But like the guy could have given a fuck about
Like he was just like
Either I don't believe you
I don't care
I paid $25 to get my card
Like I felt so crazy
That sucks
Like I was trying to prove every which way
And no there was no
So I was like fuck
This is the worst
What a nightmare
Denied at every turn
Using logic
And you don't feel like you're being heard
It's like the American people right now
You were a make up for
You weren't represented
Thank you
It is exactly like that
Someone had to say
So is it
So you had the card in your possession the entire time
Yes and then they validated that at Bucatibepo
So the fraud took place before you were handed the card
Right so what must have happened was
Either somebody came in
And they thought they were going to have to go valet
And they pulled out
And they stamped a card
And then ended up just putting it on the thing
Or there's some funny business going on
Or they transposed that card with a different card
Like they should have handed you a different thing
Maybe
I mean they
The problem is then too
Is that the guy had already taken the card
So I never got a chance to take a picture of the card
To sort of like figure it out
I should have
You know I really should have emailed and complained about it
I was waiting to say it on the show
I can still email and complain
You're waiting for a fan to write all this fan
And them to email it
They owe me 18 motherfucking dollars
They absolutely do
Yeah let's get your 18 dollars
But we need to get Jason's Lowry's points back
Landry's points
That's my mistake
We need to get our 15 dollars each
We paid Jason Woolitor
Boys, boys, boys
Yes
Rob the vault
Wow
Why aren't we talking 18 dollars
When we could have 10 thousand dollars
Good point
He's really been listening to that new metal
The situation you've described
You would have had to
Enter from Lancashire
You would have had to avoid it
The little turnstiles to go into Jurassic Parking
Taking the road down
Past the hotel that kind of wraps around the Hilton
To get to Frankenstein?
No, no to get to Jurassic Valley
If I wanted to do that you're saying
If you wanted to do that
You would have had to take this little road
Right, right
That goes by the old box office for the
The late Gibson amphitheater
And then gone up the entrance from Cuenca
Yes, that's correct
Which is craite
Such a pain in the ass
Right
Why isn't there just signage directing you towards these lots
Why isn't there just a clear way to get there
Kind of is, but it's rough
The problem is
The problem is it's too much information
As far as which valley you're going to go to
To convey to a person driving
Right
Like they're on opposite sides of City Walk
But it's going to be impossible to be like
Where are you going in City Walk on a sign
And say here and then direct people
Like it's that's
I get it that it's just like
Valley parking this way
And if you came up here you're going here
And if you came up off of Ventura you're going here
We know City Walk better at this point
Than any other human being on the planet
And it's still
Other than the people who built it maybe
Yeah
To figure it out
There shouldn't be complicated verbal maps
That have to be described
There shouldn't be tickets with false timestamps
No
And coins
That don't lead to free coffee
This is all madness
It's madness
And you know we could keep talking about
The other parking garage
Throw in anything else you have
But this is all
It's led me to a higher point
That
Okay
In the first episode we talked about
Some general stuff about City Walk
And the founding of City Walk
And what it was trying to do
And what neighbors wanted out of it
But there were
I didn't get into this in episode one
There were a lot of people
Who were angry about City Walk
Authors and social critics
And that kind of thing
Wow
And I have some quotes from a couple different sources
But it starts with
A book called City of Quartz
Excavating the Future
The author Mike Davis
Who sighs at the mention of City Walk
And let me
The bigger
The entry point for all this
Is that people were upset
When it started
That you know
Like town centers should be
A vibrant part of the town
It should be up on a hill
And only for the super wealthy
It is like City Walk is trying to get people
Without money to stay down
To not climb up the hill
Right
If you are a poor person in a wheelchair
Who can't roll your chair
Up the freeway overpass
And to get up to
The Golden City on the hill
What do you do
So authors that people were tearing apart
City Walk in 1993
And here is a couple of choice quotes
I consider
Mike Davis
I consider it the moral equivalent of the neutron bomb
MCA executives have always stressed
The most popular parts of LA are now too dangerous
The city scene is a criminalized third world
So now they go off the real world
To simulators
Buzz buzz
There is a struggle going on today
To save the democracy of public space
I think City Walk ought to be burnt down
Wow
That is harsh
From social critics
Here is one I don't know the source of this
You can Google this quote
Or I will figure out where it is from
This guy gets even heavier
City Walk sneeringly mocks us
As it erases any trace of our real joy
Pain or labor
City Walk is the moment when
Baudrillard, not sure that is
Draws a huge satisfied breath
And draws deeply on his cigar
It is the simulacrum of the simulacrum
And then there is further quotes about how LA's
You know, the MCA executives did say
Downtown is too dangerous
We built a city for you
So you don't have to get into gunfire
They said real brazen stuff like that
And that leads this author to this quote
This author predicts
That as economic problems worsen
The territorial carve up of LA
Will lead to a Brazilian or Filipino style
Final solution
Private death squads protecting the enclaves
Of the super rich from everyone else
Wow
Yeah, kill me with a gun
Universal death squads
Whoa
So this is
By episode one
I thought this is silly
So that is pretty insane to derive all that
From just putting a fake city up on a hill
But after all of this parking madness
I kind of think Mike Davis, author of City of Quartz
Is onto something
And now I'm getting real worried about those death squads
Yeah
Well, Uhteriard is a French philosopher and sociologist
Often quoted in like college
You know, meta-textual papers and stuff
And in comedy stuff written by Harvard dudes
Right
I see, okay, very good
So anyway
Yeah, the kind of people who read Howard Zinn
There's George Will quotes in year two
There's a lot going on
Wow
Oh, God
I wish there was baseball up there
You know that bitch loves baseball
George Will, you a bitch who loves baseball
Now that's one for the Harvard guys
So, I don't know
Don't these quotes ring a little more true to you
Having been in these, you know
These awful confined quarters
In these parking garages
Here's the thing
There's places in Los Angeles
Up in hills
Like little places to shop
And you really get the sense that
These are for rich people
All the shops are for rich people
And it's like it's literally up a hill
So if you're homeless
There's no way you're walking up that hill to go get up here
I think there's truth to it because of geography
If City Walk wasn't just full of trash
Right
And I mean food
I mean
They're protecting the flip flops from the poor
If it was a much more attempted high brow experience
I would more agree with what all of these people are saying
But
And I say trash
Mostly lovingly
It's full of trash
We had a good time
I've ended up being more positive in this series than I thought I would be
But this parking garage
The more you lay it all out
You hear Jason's tale of woe
They're frustrated
Here's the issue
And this is what Mickey and Friends gets right
Is that the start and end of a day of a delightful day
Is as stress free as a stressful thing can be
Right
And here I feel like it's the most stressful parking situation you'll ever encounter
Both parking and exiting
In particular hearing your guys' stories about valets and hacks gone wrong
It's just you potentially could be left with a very large bill upon exiting the lot
Exiting CityWalk slash Universal Studios where you've already spent a lot of money
Where it was already an indulgence
It's like an extra fuck you out the door
Sure
And that is not what a parking structure should accomplish
To the quotes you were talking
CityWalk is not an exclusive enclave for the super wealthy
It is not the Brentwood Country Mart
It's very different than what those people were anticipating it was going to become
Because to Carlson's point it is just a trash place
It's just a junkyard
The super enclave for the super wealthy don't usually have an upside down pink Cadillac with a cow in the driver's seat
Not all the way, they might
Yeah
There isn't a giant candy store
It's a tacky place
It's very tacky
It's a super tacky place
It's a touristy place
The parking structures I think suck
Frankenstein lot I've never parked in
The thing I liked about it is that it's underneath the Minion Mayham ride which is great
That's kind of cool that you're just underneath it
And I think the signage there is actually kind of fun
There was a Frankenstein restroom sign that you took a picture of
That I thought was just in a nice
Where the bathroom silhouettes, one was the hair of the bride of Frankenstein
And one was like a Frankenstein monster
Which is great, that's a lot of fun
I would like that
Thanks for getting back to a positive note
I think the theming at the Frankenstein lot is okay
The other lot there that we didn't touch on
There's the fabled King Kong lot which I've never even seen in person
We found that at the very end of the night
So that is sort of like a little surface lot during horror nights
Where a lot of pick up and drop offs are
It's adjacent to the, again, the old Gibson amphitheater standalone little hut box office
And now it's used where like crew trucks will park too if they're shooting
Got it
Nice and simple
Paints an easy mental image
The Woody Woodpecker lot is a surface lot adjacent to Jurassic Park
And that's the one where if you pay $35
Which, alright dude, why would you do that?
Like that gets you, I guess a little closer but not real
The main thing it does is you end up skipping City Walk
Which is maybe something you pay $10 to do
But also why would you? Especially after all this
Wait, you skip City Walk because it dumps you out right into Universal Studios
Closer
But you can backtrack still into, you're not banned from going into City Walk
Okay, right
What confuses me early on like as you're talking about this
Like the newer restaurant Vivo, it's an Italian place, just opened
That is like a higher quality than a lot of the places we ate up there
And a lower price point than say like a Bubba Gump or a Margaritaville
So like I kind of, I don't understand, so the parking is going up
But food prices are going down, same with Ludo
Like Ludo is cheaper, like you get a little bit of a premium charge on that
Because it's a little better ingredients than like the Panda Express
Because they made the chicken extra cold for you
Yeah, because they pay for the cold
They're not perfect
But the Panda Express is the same Panda Express that is a few blocks down on Ventura
For like two or three dollars more
The economics of it makes no sense
It's kind of confusing and I think that's the spot where City Walk is weak
Where it's like, oh even Jason's parking that did go over
There's at least a minute logic, there's at least a logic to that
It's the stuff that there seems to be no internal logic
Or it's grown bigger than it can control
It's a weed, it's out of control
It's a weed that's out of control, yeah
I think it doesn't have to be this way, I think there's hope
Look at that, that Vivo situation, there's more reasonably priced restaurants
Where you actually get the value that you're after
I think that, here's what I, and I think they have to do this
With places like The Grove and The Americana
Which are total successes, everyone, snarksters love The Americana
This mall in Glendale with a little trolley and everything
Super cynical people, go have a great time
I think it's, some parts of it have like Disney level theming and production value
They did a great job
And City Walk I think has to step up their game
I think you'll see a lot more local traffic if they ease off on all this
Why do they have to be such greed mongers in this parking area?
Right, yeah, it really doesn't make any sense
But you know what's gonna happen in response to this is that they're going to add like
The Fiona lot from Shrek
That's like, they'll pick that character for some reason
And then parking there will be like $55
Unless you get there before 5.30
At which point it's $8 if you stay for 4 hours or fewer
It's like they're gonna have a more complex solution that's gonna make this even more
Complicated and convoluted for customers
I just think like, I don't love getting there and getting out of there
But I kind of do have fun when I'm there
City Walk, yeah, like Jason was touching on the economics of the different establishments
Don't make any sense, they're wildly inconsistent
Some places are overpriced, other places are resembling a value
The movie theater I kind of like
I don't know why I'm getting into my general thoughts
We're supposed to be in Sector 19
We're wrapping up the saga, say whatever you want
Okay, because I was worried the Sector Keeper was glaring at me
Go for it
But yeah, a lot of the businesses there suck
And a lot of them are really bad
There's a few diamonds in the rough
And it's also just kind of like a fun thing to walk through
If you're going to Universal Studios
It's like a fun little bonus
Like the same purpose that Downtown Disney serves
So I like it for that reason
But yeah, I just wish they'd figure out the overall experience
By the way, we think of all the lots
King Kong, Woody Wedpecker, E.T., Frankenstein, Curious George, and Jurassic Park
Just like the most incoherent Avengers movie ever
Like what is happening here?
And the E.T. attraction long gone
The Curious George play area gone
I guess he walks around still
Frankenstein definitely walks around
Maybe they should just re-theme them all to characters from one of the movies
Right, just make them all minions
Just make them different minions
And then kids get to see minions on their way in
You get to see Bob, you get to see Stuart
You can tell which...
I mean, that could be confusing because the minions do look pretty similar
So maybe that's not a good idea
No, it's the three-eyed one
It's the one without goggles
But you could be in the minions garage
Or the Gru garage
Or the girls garage
The Pharrell garage
Yeah, the Pharrell
I was going to say just make them all E.T. characters
E.T.'s depressed mom
Depressed Elliot
Depressed Elliot's sister
Maybe they're all just versions of Elliot
Isn't every character depressed in that movie?
Sick Elliot, healthy Elliot
Obviously the garage that you want
Hashtag Botanicus
Yeah, he would cheer everybody
And he'd be a nice kind of like guide on the way
To start your day
And put the robot, what's left of the robot in there
Yeah, he's still bumming around
I hope putting the photo out there can help us track down where Botanicus is at
God, it's so sad
Yeah, have him welcome you
This way he can explain all the rules
$45 if you're here past two and a half hours
You know, I think this is it
I think this is what the solution is
I think you keep Jurassic Parking
And use that as a baseline
And you go around and you make the other lots named after dinos
And then so you've got
Because dinos are different sizes and they look differently
And that's also fun theming
And then it's all like Jurassic Parking
It's all like part of that
And you've got the main hub
And then you've got the peripheral raptor lot
And the T-Rex lot
And the Triceratops lot
Was there Triceratops in Jurassic Park?
I don't remember
Oh, that's right, that's right
And you know, and
Big pile of poop lot
Right, there you go, yeah
I agree
Here's my idea of a solution
Private death squads protecting the enclaves of the super rich from everyone else
Well that sounds like Universal's The Purge series
Oh yeah, oh name them after all the different purges
There you go
Anarchy first year
From Fitzr
I have a radical idea
That's my idea for what City Walk would be in ten years
Oh, I'd like to hear it
I think they should just get rid of all the parking garages
And there should be parking garages
Like kind of far away
But then there will be like a high speed
Something, a high speed gondola
Something to shoot you up into City Walk
Because we need so much real estate now
For more City Walk
For more theme park
And that, those parking garages
Take up a lot of space
And the way we're going, if they keep expanding
There's only going to be more people
So we're running out of space as it is
Let's get rid of all parking up there
Except maybe for an employee
Let's let the employees park up there
Yeah, move it a little bit
Get a little bit further off site
Have some sort of, what was Elon Musk's
Cocaine dream for Dodger Stadium
Magic roller skates you're getting on
Yeah
Fucking George Will-ass bitch
Hahahaha
Let's get Elon Musk to build a high speed gondola
That will shoot you from
Like some Burbank parking garage
To Universal in 25 seconds
I think if you tweet that at him
There's like a 30% chance he'll just
Say yes
We're working on it already
Yeah, we're already underway, we asked this one guy to build it
But he's a pedo
Yes, once again the diver is a pedo
And I will get on top of that
But yeah
Abolish all parking at CityWalk
Yeah, I think that's great because also too
That solves a lot of the confusion
You got one central lot and that's how a lot of theme parks work
You're directed to a lot
And then there's a shuttle that takes you to the facility
Why shouldn't CityWalk be modeled on that
Helicopters, like Jurassic Park
Yes, fine, great
They're running helicopters all day
And you park up in the Burbank Hills
And then you see
CityWalk and Universal Studios
Approaching as you fly over it
I don't want to just walk right into my
Segment, but maybe I will
Then you can make a big
Sort of lake out by Margaritaville
A little man made lake
And then you can fly Jimmy Buffett's Hemisphere
Dancer plane, the plane
Famously shot up by the Jamaican government
That he wrote the song Jamaican Mistake
Oh, okay, thanks for reminding me
Would there be a
Walkaround Bono character on this plane
As he allegedly was
Oh, that was scary
Close call
I've got a radical solution
For this radical problem
Yank that Were the World set
Wow
Get it out of there
That's a huge plot of land
That's been there for so long
What do you think about this
It's such a hit though
It's so amazing
Such an amazing set
Radical problems require
A radical solution
I don't know, it's time for the new
Would you keep Whoville
Always keep Whoville
Of course
Whoville is the only thing keeping the Grinch at bay
I don't know
The War of the Worlds
I like War of the Worlds better than I like
The Fast and Furious ride
Part of the tram
Practical
I like seeing what a horrific plane accident
Would look like in real life
Versus the kind of screeny
But better than Diagon Alley
Wait, we're not talking about Diagon Alley
We're talking about parking specifically
If you're telling me
I have a choice between Diagon Alley
Or a plane that's been
Crashed
Yes, I agree with you, put Diagon Alley over there
What if the crashed plane was
The Hemisphere Dancer
In an alternate reality where the plane
Was brought down by the Jamaican government
That's a fantastic idea
And there's a slain Bono on the ground
His sunglasses
Cracked in half
And Horror Nights gets even more graphic
Body riddled with anti-aircraft fire
The Edge controlling
The gun
The Edge killed him?
That's the sort of scary twist
That you expect from Horror Nights
Yeah, I'm okay with that
I'm fine with that
Can I just, one more thing on the parking garages
It does kind of make City Walk as part of the city
Kind of an eyesore
Those parking garages are
Super aesthetically pleasing from the outside
But I will say
That in the last couple years
They made the trip down the hill
At night
A beautiful experience
You align them with palm trees
The lighting looks really nice
So when you finally find your way out of this crazy labyrinth
And you're going down
I feel like it's a very nice and pleasant
And better aesthetically than when you're leaving
Making friends
Some of the universal heroes
Saying hi to you, King Kong, the dinosaur, the Simpsons
All your pals waving goodbye
This is true, there are signs saying have a good night
Good night humans
And this gives me hope for the future
Of City Walk and parking
The infrastructure that they've done
In and around the area
Yeah, that hill is nice, those signs are nice
All the metro improvements
Recently
That stuff is good, some of that stuff is more
Aesthetically pleasing
There was a lot of concern from residents about
That they removed a freeway
Overpass and that it was going to cause a lot of congestion
But it's actually been fine, they did a good job
So there's been some good universal things
And I say all that just to say
Please let us come do live shows there
And don't kick us out just because we set all the hacks
And because I tried to sneak in with my paper ID
Yeah, we opened the John Lovett's comedy club
So these guys can go into a live show
Yeah, let us perform in the abandoned space
I don't want to rain on your parade a little
But so having crossed over from the metro a lot this time
More often than not
The escalator up to the bridge has been broken
So it's just kind of that weird sensation of walking up an escalator
That's just stairs
I hate that
So I took the elevator the other day
The elevator fucking beat up
Oh no
Flywood and duct tape
Someone like punctured the glass elevator door
Wait a minute
I think I know who did it
It's this newly brazen
Limp biscuit listening brake stuff
Sector keeper
Sector keeper?
Yeah, that's right
Oh my god
Violence rules
Oh shit
We're better to rebel
Than in your own home in city walk
Where you're trapped
Yeah, I'm sick of this place, it's dumb, I want out
I think that's how I feel
Sector keeper
I don't know, you kind of imagine
I can't take it anymore
I'm lashing out
These are like my teen years, man
He's got a cool
He has a cool leather jacket on
He's dressed like Shia LaBeouf's Matt Williams character
Matt Jones 4
He's got a lighter with a body
Forties babe on it
I don't care for that, could you please not show that to me
I like babes and I like motorcycles
Vroom vroom bitch
Watch out, he's got a switchblade
He's flipping it around his hip
Just to come
Oh my god
You got us
SK, you got us again
I messed up the elevator good
Yeah, well I mean
Wait a minute, but also if you're able to
Manipulate the space around you
And if you're in your teen years
And you're wearing these greaser clothes and everything
I feel like that means that your strength is getting all the way back up to its final state
Yes, you've given me strength
I think I have a reason for that
It's because the Sector 19 stone this whole time
Why it's been the City Walk gold cup of joe token
That's right
We got it early on
We didn't know the meaning of it
It's just been sitting in your pocket
You could have lost it, you could have used it as a laundry coin or something
No, no, I kept this close to my heart
It was yours the whole time
You had the key
And it only cost you $45
For which you didn't get coffee
Yes
So we've got all 19 is what we're saying
We've got all 19 stones
Boys, boys, you've given me great strength
You sound so much older now
That's right, I'm feeling great
Whoa
Wow, you sound like a guy who just did all 30 days of like Whole30 or something
Yeah, yeah, I'm feeling really good
Oh my god
Wow, you've been so many years all of a sudden
Yes, it's all coming back to me, all of it
All the years that I've missed
And boys, I have to say that not only do you give me strength
You give me great knowledge
I've learned that through this journey
There are other places I want to visit
You do?
Boys
I have to say that
There's one more mission
You're kidding me
As a boy
I heard of a place
A place like CityWalk
But it wasn't just a city
It was truly downtown
Boys
In order to complete my soul fully
Oh my god
The journey continues
I need you to take me to downtown Disney
Oh, right
You son of a bitch
Damn it
Watch your head, this old ass motherfucker
Look what he led us into
Oh no
Now that you're older I'm gonna kick your ass, you prick
Please, please, I need to experience it
Take me around, the entertainment, the food
I don't want to see it all
Wait, you seem pretty like, corporeal now
You seem like
You just drive yourself
You're just like a guy now
Alright, well, is that an employee badge?
Do you have a job now?
Do you work at the ESPN zone
At downtown Disney?
It's been closed though
You got a job at a closed ESPN zone?
It might be reopening it
The hotel's not getting built
I'm looking for a place, if anyone
knows, has any leads
Right now I'm crashing in Alta Nina
That's a rough commute
It's a hell of a commute
All our places are pretty tight
And it's all pretty close
to Universal Studio
We all live close to Universal
And you know that, you want to get into a different
part of town
I know a guy who lives in Santa Monica
who probably has some space
Mr. Weiger?
Can I stay with you?
Look, Sector Keeper
I'd love to help you out, but as we've already
established, I'm fourth in line
for succession, so I mean if some tragedy
were to befall each of these three gentlemen
then that would be the only way I could possibly let
you into the home in Santa Monica
that I share with my lovely wife
Well, thankfully we're all
in great health, nothing will happen
to us, we all eat right, we definitely
we get all of our hot dog
nitrates, and I'm not afraid
of anybody having any sort of
heart incident
Jason has plenty of apple strudel all alone
For dinner
That's right, Nick joined us on our hotel outing
where the waiter owned my ass
Well, I like the
waiter said to you, I guess
we're going on our own round too
Oh boy guys
Here we go again
Oh boy
Well, I guess with that being said
Nick Weiger, you survived
Podcast The Ride once again
You survived the City Walk Saga
and all of you at home survived
the City Walk Saga
Incredible
To commemorate the closing out
I'd like to do something
I was inspired by Scott
starting the City Walk Saga
in a triumphant manner
and I'd like to close it out on a similar note
Sector Keeper, if you wouldn't mind putting
your microphone toward
the computer and I have not
rehearsed this, so let's see if it happens
Can you put down your Jules Sector Keeper
Alright, here we go
I always knew City Walk was a great
place, now baby I'm sure
I love sugar for the candy
even though
it's steaming's mature
I love Hard Rock's new doll mascot
her name's
Harper Ray
Jason's washing himself
with a donut
What more can I say
Alright everybody
No, you now
City walking on
City walking on sunshine
And it doesn't feel good
Wow, I know you don't need it anymore
but does that give you strength?
Oh man, I don't know what that gives me
it gives me something
Well, I can't
think of a more beautiful note to end on
other than my beautiful
note to end on because I also
did the same thing
that you did
Same song? No, no, no
I was getting a little worried
I thought of a different one
and what I thought
of kind of stems from, you know, in the first
episode we were comparing all of the
architectural works of
John Jertie to different
U2 albums and we were just talking
about U2 now, about Bono's
body shot down in the War of the Worlds
area and yeah, yeah
and you know
I just feel so bitter sweet at this moment
and I, it's just
I feel like what I've learned
through all this is that City Walk is more
than just a theme park adjacent
retail center
what it really is, is the
mall that you can't leave behind
Here, Mike
hit it
It's a double encore
And if the popcorn
upless
no longer
pops
And if the LA
sock market
runs out of
socks
The Raiders still aren't
in LA
So indoor
skydive away
You can fly
Sector Keepers
fly, you're free
now, goodbye boys
Walk on
City Walk on
If you park
you can rebate it
with your movie theater
ticket, park on
City Walk on
It's five o'clock
somewhere
There you have it
Wow, there you have it
Boys, boys, you give me so much strength
Thank you, thank you
Now why don't you do yours
Yeah, I mean
I was gonna do mine, but first
I wanted to let Jason do his rendition
of Walk on By
by the Stardust Jazz Singers
Were you Googling an old song with Walk in
I was looking for something like
Count Basie Big Band or something, that was the best thing to do
There's that song Walk Right In
Step Right Down
So I was going, yeah, I was like, boots are made for
walking, I thought about
Walk On
It would have been funny if we both, we had two different
I had been trying to figure out how to
make the chorus of the
Videopolis thing song
We're going to the walk to the city walk
and that's about as far as I got
That's pretty good, wait, do that one more time
though and just super commit, maybe we can lay in music
We're going to the walk to the city
walk on a shopping
time till we drop at the city walk
Great, great, wow
We all did songs
and Sector Keeper
boy, I thought we were going to
I was worried I was going to have to say goodbye to you
and we'd never see you again, but I guess
see you in Anaheim
See you in Anaheim
Just be careful, you're spilling your dip cup
Oh yeah, your char cup
I chew skull now
Wow, that's cool
I spit it into Mountain Dew Code Red
bottles and I throw it
Well, here's the roast
So you've gone from like a 50's greaser
to like a Mid-Aughts
dirt bag
I'm still finding my way
Please forgive me if, you know, when you see
me next it's nothing like this
You know, I'm figuring it out
You're going to have some tribal tattoos and a
tap out shirt
Is it possible that you're going to sound like you're being
portrayed by a different actor
entirely? Potentially, yeah
depending on schedules and what not
So that people with audience would have to forgive
that if that was the case
You know, I think no matter what the case or cadence
or sound of my voice, you know
you'll see me one place and that's behind
a paywall
Oh, very good
I like the way you think
SK
I like the way you think, like the way you look
which is kind of like a Phil K. Dick
like morph suit from Skinner Darkly
where your identity is constantly
changing so as to disguise
your real nature
but I guess that's between the worlds
you're walking between the dimensions still
Right, that's right
Well, you're one of those and
us three, good but
increasingly bad boys are going to be
heading down to Anaheim
with a lot of trips with a teenage
dirt bag
Eventually, with no
timeline attached to it
With absolutely no month commitment
whatsoever or an amount
God damn it
I know the sector keeper doesn't know
the amount of sectors
It would have to be more than City Walk, right?
I don't know if it would have to be
I think there's an argument to be made
that it would be less
The problem is that we'd have to review all the businesses on Harbor
Oh no
Yes, most definitely
Captain Kidd's Buffet
Let's cut this thing off before anyone gets
The Mimis on Harbor
Harbor is a many miles boulevard
Yeah, yeah, just a couple miles of it
Oh no, alright
Well, see you for the 67 part
Downtown Disney
Saga
Someday
Alright y'all, you did it, we did it
Goodbye
Subscribe to our YouTube channel
Follow us on Twitter and Instagram
At ForeverDogTeam
Thanks for watching