Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast includes a high octane discussion of ASCAP song registration rules,
a guest rattling lack of knowledge about DreamWorks animation,
and Jason's spellbinding encounter with a plate of assorted meats and cheeses.
You've heard us talk about the land, now you're just the restaurant.
Zach Reno pulls up a chair at the Three Brewsticks on Podcast The Ride.
We'll be right back.
podcast the ride the theme park podcast hosted by three men whose favorite songs are as follows jason sherryden grim-gritting ghosts mike carlson
blood on the saddle by big al and scott tomorrowland area music loop
Listen to that tomorrowland music loop when I when I write sometimes because it's just me
Exactly just like nice instrumental kind of like, you know, like mall music but slightly
Respecified you know, I mean really I like to call it the colloquial name though the the bubble shuffle loop
Oh, right, of course the first song on it is the song bubble shuffle by jazz guitarist Larry Carlton
You really lit me up you set me off right at the top of this episode Mike
Yeah
it is like I said something like I was I was getting Jason very excited on the Tokyo episode because I was talking about
Different food stuffs and certain different experiences the rides and the excitement I saw in Jason's face you matched
I believe when I said tomorrowland area music loop. Yep 80s smooth instrumental jazz
But but also but it's I like that answer better, but it's in tight competition with another part of me
Oh sure. Yeah, I like we're here to change the world too
But the the song on bad that is at the end of Captain EO also one of my favorite part
So I would like to keep talking about this. Let's bring the guest in. He's a music man
Do it you know him from the great podcast off book, this is Zach Reno
I do get the phantasmic theme stuck in my head all the time
It's really good. I think at one point when like lime wire was still a thing. I downloaded just the audio for it to listen to it
particularly there's a part where like heffa lumps and woozles kicks in with like a
hardcore electric guitars like
It's like it's legitimately badass
They add lyrics to
There's a guy and I hate him and that's like just like
Like he's I don't know what he says, but it's bad. It's like not cool, but the guitar itself is cool
Yeah, I think phantasmic is really great. Although side note when we went out with the crafts
The Richard Nicholas craft who did the that's from Disneyland Gallery
They're pretty versed in like music and score and stuff and we brought up
Phantasmic and they said well, you know and they said to look up the 1988 winter games song done by David Foster
Musicians it's pretty close. Look it up yourselves
Extremely fantastic. Here's the thing guys
Western music we don't we don't use quarter tones. So we only have so many notes
Put them in so many orders before I works
Saying is thank you so much for having me
We've completed the off-book collection we had Jess we've had you on mm-hmm that was that was easy
Two for two are not Zack's first appearance on the show
Yeah
On the show in fact, I believe it is
17 appearances specific. Yes, cuz Zach of course saying the city walk
Be careful people are gonna cry all over their phones people were oddly emotional about that song as I was why it's first of all
Michael it's a great. Thank you. Thank you very much. It's very very good
It was stuck after recording it was stuck in my head a lot after seeing it
I was walking through city walk you guys the Zen zone was popping off
830 at night
Sunday Wow
Like like full and I've and I've never seen anyone in the Zen zone before so I feel like one y'all really turned it around
to a walk by the fountain that the
sector keeper the sector keeper passed away
Well, it's happy ending but yeah
Not to spoil anything if you haven't heard the saga, but yeah, he's in a better place
He's fully dead has been for a while. Yes, but
Well, that's boy. That's that's nice to hear at night
It is odd going to use the water coffins and in the dark. It's weird. It's real weird
Yeah, did you find yourself kind of just hanging around stores kind of singing it like half under your breath?
But hoping that maybe you get discovered
Stars born me
Recognized from your you're very popular podcast
Recognized from our from singing the song on our pod
I'm trying to think of like what the phrase would have to be that I could like casually just say
Hoping that someone to not be too obvious. I think I'll be like, oh a place where Oakland Raiders merches sold
Outside the store
I don't think I real I don't think I re clocked that there was such an
Enormous hot topic there. It is a lyric in the song and I don't think I've ever realized that there was one there before
And I didn't until my wife Nicole was like, what is this? Oh, it's a massive hot topic. Hmm
Yeah, there's look there's a lot of stuff there that a lot of people don't realize and we just were doing our civic duty by
I can't believe you guys
It's truly I when I describe it out loud now, it's wonderful
I'm so happy you did but I also cannot believe that you did one
Thank you for contributing to it in such a wonderful way
Do you feel like you were like channeling any particular influence or vibe in your vocal performance?
Yeah, well I had direction from from the composer and it was supposed to be
Mike what did you say? You said you said do it I can look at you said do it
Intense but also sincere it was not it was meant to sound like someone trying very like to say very stupid things
But to do it as if it was like a very
Beautiful pose doing it more. You don't want to be don't like power ballad D
Like like poor man's Jack Black like you're trying to do it band or something. Yeah
Would have been okay
I said poor man's Jack Black doing intense vocals a lot of fun. There's
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I'm looking through my directions and I'm not sure what did I say here?
That was that was the vibe that I got it was think you may have just been like I know what to do
You sure did it was beautiful and now I feel like I'm I was trying to think of a good
Analog like not the right it's it's like you're this you're the Celine Dion
and Mike is the
The Diane Warren agenda flipped both of you
But I'm like, you know to be around the songwriter and the singer for the first time right?
Electric I'm happy to give you that experience. You know what? I think it was I think if I was channeling anyone
It's probably it was like a matchbox 20 years
Yeah, what feels right?
Can you help me?
One thing about this is this is not necessarily theme park related one of my favorite things about
Zack ever is that he said that and this is gonna make Scott very upset and I just realized it now
He thinks that counting crows are a much better band than the Beach Boys. Oh
Why are you putting those together because Mike asked me
Well, you know, I love counting crows this unironically my favorite band
Oh, Mike was basically just being like better than this and I was like, yeah
For me. Yeah hundred percent. Well for me is a fine qualifier
I get that that that that helps me out and you're also making my wife happy cuz she hates the Beach Boys
It's a big our big our literal biggest difference is I'm a real Beach Boys worshiper and she hates them
It's important to also know that I don't know anything about music. It's a very it's a very
Very music music. Thank you
Yeah, I don't know like I don't know anything about
Bands like I had to say Matchbox 20 because I didn't remember that
Thomas was his name until I was saying it and even then I wasn't super confident until this moment when you all affirmed it
That was the name of the singer of that band. That is also a 20 year old band. Sure
All the reference points at the moment on the table are pretty including Celine Dion and Diane Warren
I'm no hipper than anybody and the Beach Boys and Larry Carlton
I'm sounding like a very old man right now. Yeah, the most recent artists are Mike Carlson and Zach Reno
What recent music am I into? Yeah crossing Reno?
This is a song from this podcast all about city walk that's my podcast that I'm on so I'm into that
People I saw somebody today. We're like they want it on iTunes. They want us to sell it on iTunes
I don't even know how to start. I don't know
It's very easy. Okay
Point of time it was not it's well it is now. I mean it depends on I mean, how do I register with ASCAP?
I need to like join and then like you need to get
ASCAP is ASCAP is music ASCAP is the one that is
Like $25 to join for forever or something. Oh, is that right?
It's a union that we're talking about by the way for anyone who doesn't know ASCAP is a composers union. It's basically
It's a one-time fee. It's very very easy to join it
All of the composer unions are except for one and I forget the name of it
And yeah, so you join that then you go to like tunecore.com and you're like, here's my track
I'm putting it up. They say where do you want it? You say iTunes and Spotify
They say do you also want it on zoom and you say no, I don't
They say here like five other streaming services you have never heard of some in Latin America
Do you want it on those and then you think like well Latin America is a huge listening audience
I want it to be on Latin American Spotify and then you still say no and you just put it on iTunes
Wow you've done this journey and then the cash comes rolling in and then the cash comes rolling in you live off those residuals from
That one track because you know Spotify famously pays artists right very very well. Of course
Yes, our podcast is available on Spotify and we're not quite sure how that happens
so ours is too and I know many people listen to it on Spotify and
As far as I know we've never been paid through it. Maybe earwolf has and they're just like keeping that money, but also I
Truly don't know. It's all very confused. How did these things pop up and why it's there's nothing
Feeling we probably all have all the time like what something I did is here that's something I would get paid for
Absolutely not never all right. I'll never mind
But whatever it's a hey, it's if these things are out there
Anyway, I mean enough talk about the biz
Now the listeners at home know how to sign up for
Sign up for s cap but how to
Once signed up get their music out there. So any aspiring musicians you weren't expecting to get a tip today, but you did
One for you lander
Landr.com will master all of your tracks with robots for very cheap and is it good? Yeah
Really than I can do I'm not a man. I don't know mastering should I remaster the song Citywalk song through lander calm?
I don't think you need to pull vocals too much out of that mix do you it's pretty I jacked the vocals up
I had a lot of compression on them. Oh if you want to maybe it's very cheap. Wow we could talk about yeah
Well, we'll talk Michael project is Mike a better
Producer than Brian Wilson from the Beach Boys. I don't know
Question for the ages put it up to the audience. Yes
So look Zach your music guy you love phantasmic
Today we're talking about three broomsticks the restaurant from the Hogsmeade part of
Harry Potter land. Yeah, we kind of did the overview with Jess, but it felt like yes
She did with you coming on it's like well Zach's gonna want to talk about Harry Potter
Right only do you want to talk about Harry Potter? I mean I could have and it's also like I grew up going to
I'm from Santa Barbara, California
So I'm at it was you know an hour and a half away sure and there were I want to say
Like eight to ten years of my life where we went once a year as a family
So I went to do that a lot. So were you okay?
I mean you like fun and we I know you're like when I think of you
I think of like a person who likes whimsy a person who likes fantasy and fun
Were you obsessed with it as a kid or was it just a thing you did once in a while?
I was never Disney obsessed, but I loved Disneyland right and ironically unabashedly
Oh, I think I still really really really like Disneyland. I haven't been in a couple years
but
You are correct in terms of things that
Spark my soul as it were being in a place that like has a castle and is
Beautifully manicured and themed and we'll get to talking about this
But I am more about theme park elements that I am about rides themselves
Well, I mean you're in the right zone
I think cuz we're not we like the rides too, but we like rides with a lot of robots
We like fake rocks. Yeah, and we like yeah, that's the type of stuff
We like to obsess about and I think that's what cuz I I've all I've only been to Magic Mountain once and I had a
Good time and I did you know X2 which was terrifying and once was enough, but it was I'm glad I did it
I had a good time. I like roller coasters, but I would take I will take a not as good roller
Take thunder Mountain over X to any day of short, right?
I mean we just did Thunder Mountain and we all declared it a perfect ride. There was nothing that could be done
It's got with a dynamite in its mouth. It's truly wonderful an icon an icon of the park
Mark or any tattoo if I'm not mistaken. Oh is that right?
Yes, I think we need to have it. Oh, yeah, that's crazy. Wow. So yeah you so yeah, we're just while we're talking Disneyland
So top right like top rides at Disney real quick top places top zone areas
As a kid
It was definitely
Peter Pan's flight was number one which you mentioned as a possible topic
I did bring it up and you could I feel like you could you have the bill to play Peter Pan in a movie
Of course never on the stage only women play it on the stage
We've talked about Mary Martin a few times I think on this podcast
That doesn't surprise me it was an early one where you and I were talking about how our moms made sure we knew who Mary
Martin was and saying I did it come up because
It was that the Sandy Duncan episode we know all the pans who's the other pans tell me that my freak
There's another one. I don't know all the pan Robin Williams. No, I'm talking about the musical
There's Mary Martin and then the other big Oh Alison Williams
No, the biggest the one who looms biggest of all from the NBC live production
Featuring Christopher Walken as Captain Hook. Well, this is like a repressed memory coming back to me
It feels like a lifetime ago, I think it was only like two mm-hmm. What's everybody's favorite live musical?
I can't believe the last five years. Yeah, there's been a lot of them now
I haven't watched all of them so I was because I love Greece. Okay, I've said a lot
That's a weird thing with me I
Do not like Greece regular but I so that's how good the live one was it
Overshot that I specifically really dislike Greece. I was just so impressed by production value
I'm gonna be crazy as a person that does a lot of musical theater
I have not seen most of the the new live I've seen like parts of hairspray
Mm-hmm cool parts of errors. I filmed at the Universal lot in fact, they utilized the lot in a fun way
Yeah, that what I did like what I saw that one I liked I only saw the second act of Jesus Christ Superstar
But I thought that one was good. Yeah, that seemed pretty solid
I think it did very well. Were you in play? Were you in musicals?
Mm-hmm, and what would be what have you been in? What would I know you're from?
You would know me from nothing unless you were watching community theater
No, I did I did I started the first well my
Elementary school made every sixth grader be in a musical every year
We did like a kid's version of Into the Woods
Which basically means you stop at the halfway point before it gets dark
Oh friends friends at a neighboring school did that when I was growing up and it didn't occur
I didn't really know that musical it wasn't until I was in college and learned about that musical
I'm like wait, so it's just the first half where it ends happily before all the fucked up song time
For children, yeah for sure. Yeah, we didn't even do the straight-up kids version
They I think because it was probably only I don't know 45 minutes long or whatever
They were also like princes were singing country songs like one of the princess thing. She's right on the money
For some reason and we all did a square dance because like it was it was part of the program was we I think as like
Bizzette we're learning a dance to do together as well. It was wild
So then in junior high I did a hello dolly and kiss me Kate and then high school I did
pirates of penzance lame is fiddler on the roof and
Anything goes in outer space because we had to take the set to Edinburgh Scotland and we needed a reason to have the scat be inflatable
Guys I could talk for hours about just that by itself and then in college I did you're in town
Westside story
Anything goes again
Normal style
Time me boat and maybe something else, but that's all I'm remembering right now. Wow amazing buddy work. You have a favorite from there
Doing it. Mmm. I don't know. Oh, I did
Okay, so there is a lesser-known
Because it's bad
Sequel to you're a good man Charlie Brown, but it was just called Snoopy, which is a bunch of dumb
Bullshit that should not have been turned. It was like a couple of good songs in it, but largely
It's like you're a good man Charlie Brown is pretty much wall-to-wall
Good songs and Snoopy has like a couple
Okay, but I did I did you're a good man Charlie Brown also before doing Snoopy and that was real fun
Oh sure enjoyed that one
I'm a noted fan of at knots when they're the little shows in Camp Snoopy
Where like Charlie Brown is a Frankenstein head and they like they do thriller and they but they simplify the dance to just be
Like they spin around my mother and this is the reason she like my family never went to Knott's Berry Farm because
Apparently, this is a story we were always told and I assume it's true
They used to have a sign outside that said no dogs. No Jews. I don't know when they're talking about
Way way way back unless this is apocryphal and this is just something that my mother heard
But she definitely said no, this is the reason we will never go to Knott's Berry Farm
I mean not sis coming up not sis in its original form is a hundred years old
Okay, their court they they are coming up on their hundred year anniversary in in a couple years
The fact that y'all hadn't heard of this makes me wonder if it's real. I wonder the other hand there was a lot of weird
Not says a very
Interesting background Walter not as a very famous
Conservative man and that he had like a weird center in the park where you would go and learn conservative values
Okay, but like John Birch Society like so crazy
if anyone can confirm the or or
Disapprove this sign existed that would be very interesting to me because that was what I was always told
Was that not had this sign and I feel like there is this weird lore?
I mean like you guys would know this better than me about Walt Disney and anti-semitism, too
Well the Disney stuff. Yeah, there is I mean everyone is also very anti-semitic
To some sort of there was so much anti communist stuff and right back in the day and and a lot of that was
legitimate fears of communism and then a lot of it was coded anti-semitism someone let me know if there really was a no dogs
No, geez sign it not sparrif I mean like we would
There's some truth to some I bet there's truth to something in there
But there's some thread that you go like always very conservative man
And he wanted because they have a chapel on the grounds as well
So maybe there is some there is some obviously religious only element there, but I want I wonder maybe I'm so curious
Maybe I don't know we would have seen I think we would have seen it
They are not selling that in their throwback merchandise
Replicant no dogs no juice
No, no a no Jews sign that doesn't sound too Nazi
That was sitting there because I found myself over the years
Describing something with a nots vibe as being Nazi and I've done this in public places
Out loud and Aaron has had to say
Do you realize what you're saying?
You have to get that word out of your vocabulary
I believe we're talking about plays and musicals and stuff
I believe Jason played a Nazi when he was like 10 years old. I played a Nazi spy in a
Children's musical was music or something else. No, it was okay
There is I think the company is called and I think I've talked about this on the show before there's a company
I think it's called pioneer drama services. They churn out all of these
dust pioneer drama services
No, it is not but they churn out all of these musicals specifically for like middle school age kids because there's like
30 to 40 characters. Yeah
one character always tap dances because inevitably they'll be a
Kid who has taken tap
and
a
Handful of people get solos and but then there's also a lot of extra part
You know a lot of one-line roles and stuff
And so the first play I ever did was play called Kilroy was here and it was about a USO in New York City and
I played a roving hypnotist that was an entertainer at the club, but he was also feeding
He was a Nazi spy. He was like
But and they like they made me
I got it because they're like and everyone when you're auditioning
try to do a German accent for some of the lines and I
Got the German accent down, but it wasn't until like a month before the play
They're like wait
It doesn't really make sense that he would be doing the German accent
I'm doing the hypnotism accent
So then they're like can you try and do a British accent and I like tried my best and God knows what it sounded like
But then in the scenes when I'm meeting with the other Nazis then I'm talking like, you know talking like this and the the
TH's sound like V's and you're very good. That's it. Yeah, that's pretty much it
I kept having to watch they're like, oh go watch this movie
I think it's called IQ and it's about it's from the 90s and it's about
And he tries to help like some young couple fall in love yes, and they're like, well he speaks in German
He's got a German accent. That's a new wrinkle. I had not heard that part of the story before
By the way ten years old years old and I have no memory of this movie
Even though I probably watched it like five times to try and get the accent down and I like learned my line
I like had my lines down Pat you're emulating Walter Mathau like the original Homer Simpson. Oh, yes
The original yeah Dan Caslon is original Homer voice is very math
I'll ask each kind of bark talks like this more than he does how he would eventually sound this is madness
Let's keep on our patreon content I want to hear a reading of
Your scenes from I think I bet I will look at Christmas and see if I have the script
I know I have a copy of the full script. I've begged you
Where is a video because I have a full script of a play that you did when you were ten years old
Haven't done 30 plays in musicals. Okay, we hold on to these precious memories
Well, we were supposed to give the scripts back but that year
But and I did but that year because it was my first one my family got so invested
My mom photocopied the whole script so she could run lines with me
And so I always had this copy and like a keepsake box
But Mike really wants me to bring back the video tape because they would be
I have a three camera shoot
Edited but I have this V it's the only copy I have so I have to figure out how to
Because I'm so afraid of traveling with it if it gets damaged or I guess I could get it
Duplicated at Walmart, but yes, they hand it off to a teenager at Walmart film off the TV for now
It'll be it won't be perfect, but I'll get the idea across
That's actually not a bad idea that literally didn't occur to me that I could put a little iPod
Hey, and there's ways to hook to VCRs up. I don't want to get back into ASCAP
Just list a process territory, but you can hook up two VCRs and do a little dub
Oh, I didn't even think about what I used to because I made
Copies of three driven three camera shot local plays from my high school
So I was the media crew so you the actor and me the media crew need to put our hands together
We can okay piece of art back to life
And traveling with a copy I would feel a lot better and Mike you do have a VCR here
So yeah, what is the this is a good question for you guys?
What is the Disney property that has not been turned into a stage musical that should be?
Oh interesting. That's a great question captainio flushed out by other Michael Jackson songs and the Tomorrowland music loop
Yeah, new lyrics Michael Jackson captainio jukebox music. That was another I was in leader of the pack the Ellie Greenwich musical
Which is all Brill building songs and like Phil Spector is a character in it
There's like hardly any story because it's mostly like 30 like to do Ron Ron and
Going to the chapel and sure my captainio is the best answer except for my answer
Which is of course country bear jamboree live on Broadway
Oh, man country jamboree live on Broadway human beings in bear
Was and this is a movie not a ride, but was the Robin Hood the Fox. Oh, yeah
Oh
Full music
It's just most on stage it would be like the whistling for two hours
You have to you have to be whistling mostly Allen and Dale whistling. Yeah. Yeah, you would have to flush it out
But that's good. You want to have right things if you had a country bird jamboree
Definitely have to write some more songs
The great American songbook and just have them sing a lot or like Delta bluesy kind of stuff brother
We're now a lot of the songs are abbreviated versions though in the country bear
So I think if you maybe just did the full versions of all of them
I think you guys should do a live the three of you should do a live country bear jamboree
I'll start right now. We will stop doing this
A live country bear jamboree show and then seven years later we open off Broadway
It takes and it's literally all of our time up until that point
That's pretty good suit and it's over. Does it? Yeah
They wait for us to start the performance then send in lawyers and you can get around it you just call it like
Good old good old bears sing a long time jamber good jamberoo. Jamberoo. That's all you have to
Jason what was your answer? Did you answer? Oh, well doesn't have to be parks. I realized your question was Disney
Well, it shouldn't be in parks because I was trying to theme it for this podcast
There is Disney's open the issue of Robin Hood the Fox, right? Although I believe there is
The walk around characters, yeah, yeah
Chip and Dale feel like an also an obvious
They're like their performers Chip and Dale like be a Hope and Crosby style buddy comedy
Yeah
But that was the rumor that was gonna be Mickey and Roger Rabbit hopes in open cross. Oh, yes, that's true
When a dark horse back this was like I think it might have been one of the first movies I saw in theaters
Oliver and company with the cat
Yeah, with the cat very many dogs in the one cat. Yeah and little cat and the Billy Joel dog
a lot of songs in there the best
Billy Joel song it's a great song. It's yes. That's also a great just like that animation sequence of that
that song is so great because they're like walking through construction zones and
He he gets the like sausages around his neck and I love that as a kid
I don't know why that was so memorable to me
But he stole sausages and I thought that man this dog is the coolest dog. Yeah, cool as hell
I'm still I get a little like weirdly emotional from the Huey Lewis song that opens the film
I think is I think maybe the first movie I ever saw in the theater as a child was that movie
So I think I have some just like weird baby brain
I'd block it from my memory, but I just remember I saw Tarzan live on Broadway. Oh
Yeah, so long people swinging around sure. There's a man turn off the dark mostly swinging
I want to say directly up and back down
Mostly holding on to vines that would go up and down
Jumping from the third balcony. I didn't see it that does exist, right? Yeah, it did
Yeah, that was one of Disney's like they had the big hit with Beauty and the Beast and then again with Lion King
And I think was Tarzan like the third Broadway almost pause when they were doing
No, I'm we're dining if I saw right. I must have doesn't matter. Sorry. What's this podcast?
I love this musical area that we're in though, and I want to make all of these things happen sure
Yeah, I mean, maybe we need to revisit this at some point and like just say kind of our thoughts
We need to like flesh out how these would work right exactly
Yeah, well, I let me I'll bring it back around Zach. What do you think about?
Although there's quite a lot of music and the Harry Potter stuff in the parks. How do you feel about that?
I mean you get the movie soundtrack in a lot of the stores and the three broomsticks and yeah the Frog
Choir and we ever seen recordings of the Frog choir. I've never actually caught it live and I've tried multiple times
Yeah, I just never seen it. Mm-hmm. So that's my boring answer to question
I think that the way that music functions
Inside Wizarding World at least LA is the one I've ever been to is very good
Yeah, it for the most part
there's only one place where I've heard sound bleed from a different section of the park and it's the very very back of
Did it did it do three broomsticks, it's the outdoor section of three broomsticks, it's right on the edge of
Springfield yeah, yeah, but weirdly the sound that I was not Springfield it was I was hearing the like Jurassic Park theme
It was just there was some some section walkway that park is just playing like the generic universal
Tracks maybe the tram entrances right there. So you're getting like hooray for Hollywood
But I think that I think that and I was I said this to Nicole if we were leaving for your booms
Just because we were there the other night
That the level at which the music is playing in that restaurant is fantastic because it's pervasive
You can hear it really clearly all the time, but it's not so loud that you ever feel like you need to scream over it
It's it's almost a little haunting like I have found myself at the three broomsticks in a weird mood
And then catch the right part of the music and a wash in melancholy
No, it's it's
That's a really often. Are you melancholy?
0% of the time I'm only ever living I'm only ever in a
100% joyous
I see I'll see what you're saying Jason in that like not it's definitely not all
Celebratory super up happy music. No, it's not it is more melancholy parts of the score certainly
Mm-hmm, but it's still it you know, it's fun. It adds to the magic
And you know, I'll say as we start getting into it
I went up there with my wife also on on Friday and we had a wonderful time a long conversation
Like we we you know had a wonderful beer there that the the custom beer they have up there is wonderful
We like whatever the Scottish ale one is which is
Hogshead yes, I had the red one. I think that was the first one brewed exclusively for
What we're doing are we supposed to do that we said yeah
Yeah, we did say that we do we started we do it in a tease at the top and part of the design
There is so that if we get way off course, then we don't write we did pre record us saying
What it was so that if it isn't an hour until we get to the main topic
That's sort of the design but hey, but I still like announcing it three broomsticks
Yeah, I know this is a great topic idea like this this within
Wizarding world because I think you know sometimes we pick these topics and you end up feeling
Sort of rushed honestly and within within with Jess. You're a comedic partner
You know she it's like she clearly could talk about
Wizarding world for 10 hours each individual part of it. I mean you there's
two right I mean there's not much to talk about with like flight of the hippogriff, but but
Forbidden journey you could talk about easily for an entire episode and we will and you will I'm sure then you have the wand
Ceremony then you have all of the many many carts and
Stores in there and then you have the three broomsticks, which is I think I think
Mmm, my either favorite or second favorite part even even compared to the the ride. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you're not wrong
I don't that's not an insane opinion and not because I don't like the ride but because just for me
the appeal of a theme park is to is the immersive element of it and
the idea of eating in the three broomsticks is
Better immersion than the actual being on the ride with the possible exception of the line rate
up to the ride because
Walk because once you're on the ride you're like on a bench that's flying around and you're somehow part of the Harry Potter
Cannon at some point. I guess this happened. Well, you're taking an enchanted bench. Yeah, the famous Harry Potter
It was bench where they put muggles on a bench and they fly it
I don't like being called out that I'm a muggle. I think that's I think
I think that's not but I know you're saying cuz it makes you feel less special because what you want really is the full
Experience that I've never read the books. I've seen all the movies. I like
The episode I meant to talk to you about having I read the books. Yeah, so a bad reader
I'm a slow reader audiobooks from an asshole who can't read who does the audio book who reads someone really good
I don't know just listens to them all in loop every year
Right, I should do the audiobooks of Harry Potter because I like all the mythology. I like it's all right up my alley
But it does seem like what you would want is you want to go in there and you want to feel special you want to
Feel like you're getting off the Hogwarts Express. You're going to live in this school
That's you're getting away from your bad parents or your bad caretakers
That's what you should feel. You shouldn't feel like oh shit. They're mad at me for being a tourist here
We're all dressed like shit
The wizards here look cool. I look like shit and shorts and a t-shirt
I happen to be there when they were doing some I think like
9 and 3 for dress to the 9 and 3 4th ball or something
It's one of those things where just fans who are very very fancy dress up in like I think I want to say
1930s
40s garb, I don't know and just kind of hung out in Harry Potter
Period appropriate to that era in the park
So it was it wasn't like the school uniform
It would be like you were a fancy wizard around the time of the movies that are coming out now, right?
With a level of nerd that you like what is your level of nerd?
I guess what I'm asking like do you have a rope? Do you own a robe?
Do you own whatever your house is which I believe I know is Slytherin is Slytherin
I am also a fellow Slytherin. Yeah, let's just review two Hufflepuffs over here on the couch
We got two Hufflepuffs. Yeah, I didn't remember
Thanks for knowing. I also I double-checked
My Patronus is a st. Bernard dog
My Patronus was my wand is an elmwood with unicorn hair core
11 inch and quite bendy flexibility not terribly interesting that one
But I love that my Patronus was a big floppy dog. That's very good. Yeah, do you what is your Patronus?
I've taken
So because I'm very interested in exploring the Pottermore website to a lot of depth. I have multiple accounts on there
What because the questions are so like you can take the test two times
Answer truthfully every time and get a completely different set of questions both time you've done it
So I've gotten both nightjar, which is a bird. Okay, and then rat which is a rat
As to what kind it is and then I went up and looked like that at the matrix breakdown about how to
Get it to do all of the like all of the animals that it can give you and all the ones that you
Based on what choices you make?
And I was like one question away from Fox which was a bummer for me because that's your favorite
That's what I would have thought it would have been
But you know, we're all just like asked a butterflies wing between a fox and a rat
So you're a nerd who goes on Pottermore and tries to get every possible combination and tries to almost beat the site
You're trying to figure out how to get what you want
so the first time I like a real Slytherin is from what I
First time I got sorted I got sorted into Slytherin and I was very
Shocked because I had always thought that I was a Ravenclaw
So I went back on to Pottermore again to cheat my way into Ravenclaw and realized like no
What a Slytherin should be it would be doing it the sites the sites got you pegged
Which is crafty Ravenclaw is crafty or their hard work no Hufflepuff is hard workers, but also very lazy
Slytherin is shrewd
Okay, I'm rude which is weirdly like I feel like look is it loaded term?
Yeah shrewd feels like a little bit. Well, there's a tape is the most famous right Slytherin professor Snape
Merlin is the most famous
Wow
Talk about people that got like
Retroactively added to Harry Potter Canada, but yes
Snape also in in hmm. How did Merlin get added? He would have been sort of the same either. He was what piece of
Perfect answer. Oh, you mean
added
Like someone
Witter and she's like
When you get and I'm sorry I just just like what piece of media is this available Pottermore? Oh, it's just this is Pottermore
Laura which is all canon because it's all written by her but it's it's
When you get sorted into your house you get a welcome letter from your house
Which is another reason why I took it multiple times because I was interested in like what happens when you get into Hufflepuff like
What happens to get into Ravenclaw?
What are the things that they write for you?
Because they also all shit talk the other houses
Which is very funny to me like Ravenclaw doesn't shit clock shit talk Ravenclaw Ravenclaw's
Prefect's letter but the other houses all do and one of the things in the Slytherin letter is that like Mervin was
Merlin was a Ravenclaw Wow
So Merlin as a famous he's a public domain wizard at this point
I guess so you can add him so she could add like everyone who's in the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen
Into the Potter universe now like Frankenstein could be in yeah, he could be a wizard
He could not be he could just be a different bad guy. So that's interesting. I didn't know Merlin was so Merlin
Is a Grindelwald collaborator?
Merlin was kind of in this series already
Okay, because there is an award that Dumbledore has which is order of Merlin first class
I believe it's like an organization within the wizarding world
So Merlin I guess had already been lightly put into
Harry Potter canon at that point, but they had never gone into any detail about what it was or or who or what or what?
Do you think the wizard who walked around the City Walk nightclub wizards?
Is he in this is he the same as Merlin or is he like a trickster?
Since he's ripping off Merlin to some extent so he's and I don't we don't know much about
Three seconds in a sizzle reel, but I like to just add him officially to the Potter more cannon
Yeah, we're putting him in you know, I did see that was a little bit someone was dressed
I think as Grindelwald and I think as Harry Potter Grindelwald, which is Johnny Depp
Which is a weird costuming choice to be making
Like Disney is
Looking into rebooting the Pirates franchise like that's the rumor that Disney like the Pirates movies are super successful internationally
But they want to divest from Johnny Depp where it's more brothers. It's just stuck with them down for years
Isn't is the poster right now is the poster?
This the guy with his back turned is that Johnny Depp? Yes, so they are keeping him in the shadows
Yeah, kind of but then it was also really is the word crimes are so big
I mean the crimes of Grindelwald are sneaking dogs into Australia and also domestic abuse
Buried the lead there
And then all the I mean cuz Grindelwald like the Hitler of the Wizarding World straight right the straight-up Hitler analogy in a weird
world in which Dumbledore and
Hitler have a weird
Gay relationship do you huh?
Does that happen somewhere as a relationship with Dumbledore and and
Grindelwald because Dumbledore again, this is post-canon
But did JK Rowling does this she releases like a lot of stuff that like the whole Nagini thing
Which I guess I can't get too much into with y'all because none of us have seen the movie and whatever but Nagini is
Voldemort's
big snake big movies pet question mark, but in
The new movie that's coming out Nagini is a character that is a woman that becomes a snake which is
Problematic for a lot of reasons, but I guess it depends on how they deal with it. We'll see
I think it was also that that they they added the the story
The story is sourced from an Asian culture and they just kind of cherry picked a lot of it
And the snake story is the Nagini
Some of the Nagini
The lore of a person cursed to be a snake and that's most of the Harry Potter magic is pulled from some culture or another like
JK Rowling also got in a lot of hot water when they released the American Hogwarts
Oh, yeah, right. I remember this.
Ilvermorny is like these in I believe Salem, Massachusetts
Makes sense. I believe is where the school is. I don't remember but
All of the houses in that school are based off of Native American iconography and it wasn't treated with
necessarily the most like
respect or reverence or even like
I guess they're hmm. It's been a while since I've gone looked at it
That one is stranger to me because like yeah, you said it in Salem
You have the Salem witch trials that seems like a slam dunk like it's right there for you
You take this circuitous route and you just like trip over your own shoes
I get the impulse because you're trying to make the world ancient and if you're looking back to like, okay
So what would the roots of magic have been in?
North America, it would have been Native American culture, right?
It just wasn't like researched enough or done with any respect carefully enough
Which is a bummer because it's a really cool idea
Yeah
So so you're something of a nerd for all this stuff
I could yeah Harry Potter is very much you or you like theme parks to us Harry Potter is
Yeah, maybe you enter this. Do you have how much how much clothes? How many of the clothes do you have?
Do you have wands multiple wands? Do you have how much give it the merch? What's your merch?
So this is my this is my similar answer to what Jessica said
I would not wear like a full Hogwarts uniform and walk through the park. That's just that's not me. That's not my bag
I fully
Respect people that can I just can't it's like too much for me personally
And on the one till you were in the Wizarding World part, you'd feel real embarrassed
I will say though when you're going to it right now half of the people you see walking around universal are just straight-up wearing robes
Yeah, that's the people in city walk
So you're very much not alone if you're doing it
I will say though when I went I wore it so they're in socks and my shirt that has snakes all over it
Like okay, those were like just for me. I was wearing a sweatshirt over it. No one else knew
You're Potter bounding really because there's a new phenomenon called Disney bounding where you sort of like dress a little bit
It's like a sad nod, but you're so you're like Potter bounding. Yes a little snake here and there, but you're not doing the full outfit
Yeah, I love it
also because the idea like if I'm wearing a Hogwarts outfit that means I am between the ages of
12 and
19 and going to school at like I'm cosplaying as a child at that point
Like a beanie hat and a big lolly. Yeah
cuz I'm not I'm like
when you see people wearing a sweatshirt that says like
Slytherin seeker like that's you're wearing a high school football jersey at that point
So it would seem like a sad guy may be wearing his old Jersey going back to visit his high school. I love I love
I'm into the merch stuff. I don't have a ton of it
Merch merches, I don't have any ones, but I think they're really cool
I look at them every time I see them because as you know
They have the little I don't know tech the tech in them that when you go around to various windows in the park and move
Stuff it makes things happen. There's more of those than I thought there were before
There's one that makes like fire shoot out of really the top of one of the roofs and makes a door like rattle like there's a dragon
Behind it. It's right by the train. Yeah, they add every now and then they add a few more
I think I think they're very cool and yeah that like as a kid
I would have lost my mind for that sure, but I don't own any of the ones when did you?
Do you remember what age you got into the Harry Potter? Yeah, I
Grew with the series. I think only only the book only book one had come out when I started reading it
It was on one of those things where you remember in school you would get a magazine
Yeah, I like books to buy and my mom was I think might have actually checked it for me
She's like you might like this and then so I would have been you're like 11 or 12. Is that 99 or?
And you followed book rule every book really like yeah from book one
So you would wait the day would you get him day of mm-hmm? Amazon actually if you bought them like later on
When Amazon was the thing if you bought them they would show up
The same day that you would like the next morning
as if you had waited till like midnight to get it at the store, but
Later on I found that there was a hack of like weird
Grocery stores would have the books and there would be no line
So I didn't hang out at lunch parties so much that again wasn't that wasn't like the important part for me
The important part was to get the book the night that it came out
Wow, so your hardcore is what we're saying and you know, I'm a full ten in terms of Harry Potter
I don't I don't express it through wearing this stuff all the time, but I it's it's you default to like
Thinking about it and like bored online
Probably you're digging into something if like a Harry Potter thing like pops up online
I will click it like there was recently leaked footage of a Harry Potter video game
That's coming out and though there isn't too much more information than that and I looked at I watched it
There should be a an M. M. What is it?
RPG Jason you're preaching to the goddamn there should be where you are a student at
Hogwarts and you go through the school and you help Harry and his friend
It would be amazing now Jason
You'll be happy to know that that that fact did not go unnoticed by the video game industry and there is a fact a game
Called Wizard 101 that is for all intents and purposes a weird little Harry Potter clone game
But it's like card based combat. You're basically building it. I mean, it's a cool
Spent money on it. I played it. I'm gonna get as close as I can, but you're right there
I think they're I think they're just leaving an insane amount of money on the table by not making
subscription based
Harry Potter MMORPG guys hit me when the longer month if you're paying monthly
You're incentivized to do it faster because if you're like it the longer you take the more of those fees
Accrue those games work
monthly content every month
Most of those games are moving towards micro transactions right now
Yeah, they're basically where you it's a free but you pay for the skin you pay for different outfits
I'm gonna tell you young guys talking about
I got Larry Carlton jazz in my head
Fortnite Zach so when you're looking at when stuff's popping up about Harry Potter like you have Google Alerts
Does this stuff pop up?
Do you see like for instance that there may be a giant new amazing Harry Potter coaster coming to Florida next year
No, I'm not have you heard about this?
forest roller coaster what no full forest building and for around a giant roller coaster with full
animatronic scenes and that sounds incredible the only stuff that I know about it and even the
Like you guys were my clue into the fact that there are owls that
Harry Potter Japan or no, that's the one in the lake
Lake they all think they also had the owls. Yeah
Hang it out. You got you guys are my lifeline for that stuff
So you guys gotta I mean that you Jess has been to Orlando though, right? Has she been to Diagon Alley?
I don't think she had when she was here. I think it hadn't opened yet. She not okay
We've talked about if we ever had doing an off book. Yeah, you got a book just
Excuse we will definitely do a show in Florida. Yeah. Yeah, so
Yeah, so you and your part your partner Jessica McKinnon go to the three broomsticks to work
Am I correct? We have had multiple right here just meetings there correct? Okay good because that's what I heard
and that's why yeah when we heard you want to do this it makes a lot of sense because
This is a thing that we do in various states at CityWalk
It is I kind of did it a little bit alone at Disneyland by myself on Sunday
We were there to do some work which is just we want to we love these places so much
We're just going to sit here and like not necessarily go on a ride
But just enjoy the ambiance and maybe get some work done
Maybe get a beer and just kind of like pretend you're working in a castle that you love from a world that you've spent
You know days of your life thinking about better way to open up your brain
I was trying to say my wife and I yeah, we had like these like great meal
Wonderful beers and we're having this like heady conversation about childhood and religion and all this stuff with that
Score playing and the light coming in through the windows and week after like being we were just kind of in a trance for like
Over an hour, and then we kind of snapped out of and like wow well that was something
I think that's really transported. It was great. Yeah, I think that those spaces work best when they are
When they do kind of seal you off from everything which three room sticks does very well
There's a bunch of windows in it, but they're all semi frosted so you can see like light comes into it
But you can't see what's going on. This was the one I was the other day
What's the first time I had been ever there when it was black like night outside?
Like full full black and it made me really think about the lighting design of the place
Which is really cool every light in there is meant to simulate a weird gas flame
There's no like straight up lights in the ceiling type down stuff
There's also projections of house elves working that pop up every once while that I had never noticed before and they come in
There's definitely two places
But in both of the places on the walls where it's just like you'll see a house elf like carrying some trays around or something
There's multiple different ones that show up on that same
Screen for lack of a better and there's like I have there's owl projections also
Yeah, I kept seeing something at like once every 15 minutes or so
I was really looking at it this time because I knew we were gonna come talk about it
But there's there's only one actual mounted head and it's the the hogs head for the for the bar
Yeah, excuse me
There's a ton of antlers everywhere and some of them are weird fantasy antlers of animals that are like far too big to be actual
Like deer or elk or stags or whatever and I thought that was very cool, too
Oh like there if you stop and stare at you're like well, this is a mythological
Huge
There's there are some that are I want to say like 15 feet wide and it's like well this couldn't and and and there's weird details
And then there's like oh, this is not an actual animal only a fantastic beast could have this
Cryptid of some sort and there's also all of the art on the walls is like weirdly like there's weird magical creatures like
hidden in them not all of them, but a lot of them also
I'm sure this came up on the on Jess episode no coca-cola products like everything
Hogshead has gotten a little more leeway. I don't I I guess they had this when they like hogshead does have
Your British beers and German be like you can get Stella in Guinness
But on the website they say they list the custom ones and then they say or you could have you know
One of your muggle beers. Yeah, yeah, and you make sure go well the hell no
Have a muggle beer and you put it that way that's correct. You shouldn't you shouldn't be getting like yeah
Yeah, yeah, especially because as I said beers awesome similar to the Duff and I we went for we walked from
three brimsticks over to get a we went to Moe's and got a
Holiday season Dufftoberfest Wow. It was great. It was really Universal Studios. It's good beer
it's good for them and also the
Fire whiskey that is liquor made for them. It's like fireball
I've never had it
It's I found on a beer review site or a liquor review site like the fire whiskey is like fireball
But it is smoother and people like to get it with a little strong, but you dump it into strong both cider
It's a little cinnamon a drink
I also found I didn't realize this because
We should say we are including the hogshead pub
Which is connected to the three brimsticks is we're including that in this episode
Yeah, sorry to disappoint
Do Zach do you know and listeners maybe you don't know do you know about the drink?
They're called the triple. I do not sometimes called the deathly hollows
It's three it's a layer of strong both cider and then a layer of hogshead and then it's topped with a layer of Guinness
So it's like three different things. Yeah, it's a lot that sounds bad. I don't know if it's good
That was very funny. It's a light beer and a dark beer in a cider. It's a it's a beer suicide
It's a snake bite that has something else going on too. I mean I gotta try that I'll try that
Yeah, I would try it just to try it when we were there
I bought I was buying multiple desserts just to try them because I've recently been like
Kind of a pescatarian so I there isn't a whole lot to eat there limited options limited options
Oh sure, and my wife's a vegetarian and so she did not eat a main meal there
Yeah, you although I did discover you can do the bangers and mash where they will substitute the sausages for asparagus
Which is basically like a spare a bunch of potatoes and peas and cabbage
It feels very British in a way that everything in that place kind of does in a really good way
Yeah, but we got multiple desserts which were
So did we what'd you do I was very
Surprisingly I have not sampled a lot of desserts no neither neither had I now they were out of one
I wanted to get the chocolate trifle and I couldn't okay they were out of it
Um, so we got the potted butter beer
What I have had yeah sweetest thing I have ever eaten. It's very very very sweet. It's good
Yeah, a bit much it's like too probably too rich for me and we thought about doing another
was the other with there's another thing that sounds like
Super super rich and we I was glad we didn't do them both. Yeah, I've been an overload but I
It's it's great though. It's just over well
It is yeah, but I love that they presented in the little in the little pot with a little latch. Yeah, that's pretty good
It feels magical you have to eat it with a plastic spoon which sucks, but I get it
See we got the sticky toffee pudding which that's why I was worried about that being too rich
I have had before and I will tell you that the sticky toffee pudding is great
It does it is playing with I want to say the same flavors as the potted butter beer
It's just in like different consistencies and it's very like
Caramel II very sweet
It's just one is like a baked good with ice cream on top on top of like melted caramel chips and the other is like
a straight-up
Not a yogurt pudding. It's a pudding. It's a pudding. It's like
Chocolate mousse, but caramel. Yeah
Butterscotch it's like a layer of butterscotch pudding with like a layer of caramel on it
And then what tastes like cool whip a little top. Yes, I flower just on top of it
I don't mean to throw shade. It's very good
It's very sweet and then we also got the apple pie because they didn't know the chopped
Yes, we do the apple pie to the great solid apple pie. Absolutely. I was worried
I was like is that like a dull option?
Is that just gonna be a the piece like you get in the market that and like no is great
It comes in this little tin you got a raisin component that kind of elevates it
Oh, whoa. Whoa, really good and I that I like the sound of that
It's kind of the whole thing has kind of it is like apple pie with kind of a run raisin overlay
It's a little like smokier or something. I love the idea of that. It's pretty you give it a try
I gotta try it. I actually did not notice that
Yeah, it took Aaron a sec
They're not is it wasn't immediately evident but I would I had also eaten a bunch of the other two as previously stated
Extremely sweet things right before that. That's your over. Have you had the I haven't had that
I've had the soft serve version in Florida the butter beer ice cream. They have hard pack butter beer ice cream
Oh, yeah, we saw that there and I asked like what it was and they were like, it's it's kind of how it tastes
I was like no no, like how is it actually served is in the cup. They're like, no, it's just like a scoop of ice cream
I was like, yeah
They didn't really there's a full ice cream parlor in Diagon Alley. That's just a life
Yeah, Jason loves ice cream I do like dream about that ice cream parlor
So good. It's so much you've been yeah
Yeah, a friend of ours was just there last week and I kept saying go to the ice cream parlor good
He's like I'm standing right outside it. I would die. I would love to go speaking of this same friend
His name is Andrew Grissom and I was at the funniest order
I'll say I've ever seen at the three broomsticks is one time he ordered a cup of water and corn on the cob
As long as he proves of it
Pretty funny you can just get a la carte anything. I think there
We what do I like to say he was texting us a lot about his trip because he was he was working there
So he was at universe studios for like for a week solid and essentially living in the world of Harry Potter. Yes
everyone's dreams magical but like the
he was I think a little overwhelmed right away by the
like he was starting to feel like
Am I not going to have like a fruit or a vegetable the entire time that I'm here?
Is that not an option here at Universal Florida?
And he was where he was we were commiserating about that fact and I threw out a joke that it was apparently too accurate for
Him I said what have you been to the all pez place you got to try the pez potatoes
Fairly accurate what CityWalk would have and then the next day he was like hey, where's that pez place?
Also in terms of like theme park food I feel like three broomsticks is pretty good cuz I
Had their like lemon chicken that comes with a bunch of vegetables
Which I thought was great by restaurant or theme park standards
I've had their fish and chips, which is good. Certainly good enough for theme park standards. Yeah
Well, yeah, I thought JK Rowling has to approve all the food stuff
Or like all the take it to your house and feed it to her with a spoon
Yeah, I mean you're not far off apparently they tried like 15 different
recipes for butter beer before they got it right and eat
Is there's no high fructose corn syrup in it? It's all sugar
Which I was surprised by very sweet but I love it
Can I give a shout out?
I started getting curious with the with the beers and everything with butter beer and and though the sort of like very
Specific nature of this food. I was like, is there a specific person you can trace it all to and in fact the executive chef
In Florida, okay, Steven Jason is the guy's name went to the Culinary Institute of America
Worked a lot of country clubs and for the Hyatt Corporation and then was hired
Just all like very low on the totem pole for at Universal Studios in in 1990 right before it opened and has graduated all
The way up to the executive chef and he is the guy
responsible for
Figuring out the butter beer flavor
It's it's a specific guy who I think we should try to talk to on
Twitter because he doesn't have a lot of followers and he mainly tweets about like soccer
So I feel like he might talk to us and be nice to us especially because I want to praise his work
He seems like great. Yeah, and and like cuz what I like like to have to manifest
the very specific flavor that children are obsessed with and why I've want like millions of children want to have very badly and
To do it with such success people love all of these butter beer products
So I'm very impressed and just like we're just really quick. I read a big interview with him
He talks about how like he had people in his office go through the books highlight every food and beverage like put tabs in the book
So he and then he's so he's really seeing every mention of any piece of food anywhere in the books watch the films paused
Anytime they're in the Great Hall looked at what's on the table
He went to England Scotland Ireland went to pubs taverns talked to chefs figured out how to make it an authentic
Experience from that area then he flew to Scotland to meet with Rowling presented the menu
Like served her pumpkin juice. She tried the butter beer and she ended up with the white foamy mustache
So like just it seems like this guy like really cared about doing this
So I want to give him his proper credit and then this one he's after your heart here Mike with this
They ask like just favorite culinary experiences at Universal Studios
He says I eat most of my meals at Universal Studios
So that's something first of all and I have to say my favorite breakfast is the fluffy pancakes they serve at the leaky cauldron
Creating this world and taking it from the books to real life will be a member always be a memory that I'll never forget
This and the opening of Jimmy Buffett's margarita
So let's meet this man
He's my patronus
Steven Jason is your patronus from the sky from the slither in and patronus is Steven Jason
Patronus is a human man
What I like I was looking at the breakfast menus at at three rooms six and
Is that when you their breakfast items all come with both bacon and sausage and a fluffy croissant
Even the pancakes come with a croissant and I was just delighted by that Wow
The real quick the butter beer we were talking about butterbeer butterbeer on a recent one of Jim Hill's 15 podcasts
He said that they had like just reached like 20 million in sales of butterbeer
Yeah, and I don't remember exactly the the amount of time it took but he said after like six months
Universal just when they initially opened up the Harry Potter world in Florida
They made back the money that it cost to build it just by butterbeer it's like sales
They like showed somebody like the ledger and they were like look we've made the money back just through the butter beer
Butter beer is their minions. Yeah
And they have the minions too
Concessions are like 30% of right in park revenue if the if Steven Jason had not nailed it
Like he's responsible for recouping the amount of money in a such a
It is also outside of Canon and brave for him to decide to be like also we have three ways of making it
We're starting with frozen and liquid and then later we're gonna add in hot which I have not tried hot and I've not tried fudge
Okay, I've tried fudge, but I've not tried hot. I've tried hot but I've not tried fudge
Hot's great. I will say it's very sweet
But if it's like cold outside and drizzly and rainy which it seldom is in Los Angeles
But I happen to be there one time when it was it's perfect
I mean that sounds you almost don't need the whole thing because it's very sweet. It's very sweet another hack
I've heard and I I think they started selling it
But now I think or maybe they encourage they're like, oh, we don't want to encourage this
So just buy it separately is you you order the fire whiskey and a butter beer and you pour it in so it's like a hard
Butterbeer. Yeah, they don't want to encourage
Do that off-site if you're gonna do it. Yeah
I've had the fudge is good, but it is insane
It's too much you need it needs to be like a little tiny piece
I think cuz they give you the big block and I didn't like shove the block in my mouth or anything
But I cut a normal punt mount off of it and it was still like a little too much at one time
y'all talked about this one when Jess was on but the
My god, what is it called not Zonko's joke stop the shop that is attached honey dukes honey dukes honey dukes
Candy counter is a little bit of a missed opportunity for them still the candy is good
but it's just like if they had put the amount of time into
Three rooms because they had into the selection of like what is available what that potentially could be if you can imagine going into like
a Wonka esque shop of all the insane
candies that are mentioned in the Harry Potter books, it's like truly
It's it's they're leaving a ton of money on the table by having things that look like they could kind of have bought anywhere
We're zipping all around here in our topics, but just since you bring that up. Is there something in the books?
Ride or other or food or something that you're thinking specifically. I wish this food or candy
In the park so here so I wish they did chocolate frogs but did it better because they do have chocolate frogs, right?
They're big they're like 20 bucks a piece and there are I think
Somewhere between five and seven actual cards that you can collect and this is yes
There is them back for people there is no way to do this the way that it should be done
but in Harry Potter canon there are hundreds and hundreds of wizard cards and you buy it kind of akin to buying a
Baseball cards exactly. So it should be
$5 much smaller chocolate and a ton more cards because no one cares about the frog
You've made a chocolate in the shape of the frog. You're done. That's great. Sorry. No one cares about the frog
What did I say? I don't know it's for the cards, right?
And then it's like the gum in baseball cards
Yeah, basically baseball cards would have a stick of gum in it, right?
And then like that's what it was fun to have that but it's like the cards are sort of the thing
It's like when you eat those popsicles for those sweet sweet jokes
I
Hurry get it done. I don't know in the book. Sorry
I have a lot of questions about these cards in the book
Is it the only way you can get these cards through the chocolate frogs?
No, I got frog cards. This is the card. I feel that universal
Disney at least is catching on more that
Universal doesn't sort of embrace like a big crazy
like
Marketing merchandise opportunity like Disney like pins like pins. Yes, exactly
We've talked like there is not really equivalent to so many different like whether it's pins or whether it's when Disney was doing on those
final nation vinyl toys like
And they do have universal vinyl they do
Rudging it's kind of exactly the same level and not at the same amount
And I will say something that both Nicole and I like stopped and spent I want to say five minutes looking at not outside of Harry
Because we went to it was one of those universal stores that kind of sells stuff from all over the park
Yeah
and we were there specifically to see if they had a gretzko stuff in which if you haven't watched on Netflix is the
Hello Kitty company made a cartoon about a red panda who works in an office job and hates it
Oh, yes, and she's furious
This has come up on the ship and she sings heavy metal to release from that and it's very very good watch the
Subtitles we went to Pearl land in Japan. Okay. Yeah, so they have Hello Kitty
Universal crossover merchandise, which is very good
It's like Hello Kitty in the jaws poster and she's above the shark and the shark also has a bow on its head
And it's all kind of and it's smiling. The shark is smiling. The shark still looks scary King Kong is Oh King Kong
Oh, okay, but King Kong's cute
It's like immediately a great
It's great. They're doing a lot of great stuff. I have or the best wrestling company in the world is New Japan professional wrestling
I have a Hello Kitty New Japan professional wrestling shirt. So maybe it's just
Hello Kitty is like Hello Kitty and then the New Japan logo. I bought it at the show in Long Beach last month Wow
That I don't think has that character as that newer Sanrio character is not there at all
Because I had this experience in 2014 when I was trying to find good atama stuff at the Universal Sanrio store and
Just had not hit peak. Yeah good atama yet. Now you can get good atama everywhere. He's the egg. Yeah. Yes
He's the lazy egg
Jason's favorite character in fiction. I mean it's a piece of bacon as a blanket. It's very good
I mean, sorry, you're looking for an egg everybody good atama. Yeah. Yeah, we all have our good at that
Let's get detective good atama out
We're making detective movies, I mean Disney is the undisputable king of like merch
I don't think anyone would argue that they they make so many products that are based off of their properties
They find like but yeah, like I'm just saying like they have a whole like collector
Gotta have it man
I have these two
Tiki mugs that I had to get on eBay because they sold out
Because there were like a thousand people in line to get them because they're exclusive and they're only gonna make a certain amount
Of them if they did this with Harry Potter and there were certain cards and then all of a sudden a hundred of them would be
Retired like people go nuts. If you could go wizard cards, I would be fucking broke
I would have every single I would like they're screwing up here by not doing this and like just taking money from you
They're not possibly removing it from you is a like it is a like take my money scenario now what they are doing
That's the weird thing they're doing it but the price point is too high to be a collector because if you look at the
Wands they have right and they just released a bunch of new ones for Fantastic Beasts crimes of Grindelwald
And there's a bunch they like every time there is a character
They take whatever their wand is in the movie and they make a replica of it that is functional within their park
But they're all over a hundred dollars. So you're never gonna buy more than like right who one for you and one for your you know
Child who you don't want to share
Me and my brother each got a Gameboy one year because they're like what we were gonna get you one Gameboy to share
Yeah, like don't come on
Because once and it occurred to me that like if you were made of money, that would be a cool
Kind of like this is I guess only a slightly cooler version if you ever been to someone's house and see they have like
What's what's what's Aragorn sword called?
Oh, I don't know I yeah, I know yeah all those Lord of the Rings replicas if you have any of the like Lord of the Rings
replica swords
If you see that up on the wall, it's like almost
Normal enough to be a normal adult house decoration swords
Maybe not so much but the ones are like tiny little things, right? They look cool. They look like art pieces
They look like movie replicas. They're very cool. They're they're basically looking they're they're shooting much more still I think for tourists
versus
Hardcore nerds people that go there and have meetings at three broomsticks
Well, I mean as you guys have said Universal is not a go-to it all the time type park
There's just not enough there. You can do the whole thing in like less than half a day
I don't think they were prepared for the amount of people that like specifically would go for
Harry Potter
World to just be there and that's really that's really all they're going. Yeah, you can imagine a scenario where they
Knowing what they know now totally redo Springfield or like add on to Springfield in a way that makes it much more
Hangout able they have they have hangout able places there. Mm-hmm, but yeah
I mean Harry Potter is the first time like they had a built they had a built-in culture
Surround it whereas Disney has always had a culture of people like kind of just hanging around and it's not just marketing exactly
Towards tourists. Yeah, it's marketing towards like idiot Southern Californians who want to go and line up at 7 a.m
For a tiki mug and then certain ones who didn't are mad at themselves
And then they have to get it. Yeah, I did get it
I had to pay more than it's than the cost of it was but I felt there was a period of time when Universal was basically
Giving away their year-long pass. Oh, yeah
They're doing much better now
Financially, but it's they should have been they weren't offering and there wasn't much
But yeah
the addition of potter like just the perfect thing to get them to Disney level and to prove they could do
I'm kind of very upset that it doesn't seem like Diagon Alley is ever gonna come
Yeah, we're not sure what would go I mean those water worlds
Yeah, you could do that. Could you really?
Put that much in there. You probably can't do the Hogwarts Express and it's probably got to be a slightly
You'd have to change the architecture of the ride of the Hogwarts Express to simulate like it was moving and it only really moved
100 feet or something. I don't even know that that's the I mean honestly if you just want to double
Shop footage that would be enough for fans like me who don't like the rides are almost secondary
It's the theme park stuff that you're going for you would rather have just a land without the actual ride
If if it was that or nothing I hundred percent
That's the thing with Diagon is like people like that ride but like it's mainly just being there
I like though I like being there so much more than the ride and I like the ride fine
But it's the fact of like could there be an ice cream parlor? Can you do a leaky cauldron though?
I mean those two things way higher priority for me than then yeah
Which a different menu the leaky cauldron then three broomsticks great like they purposely both in one day
Yeah, I'll tease what the my favorite part is of is nocturne le I loved I'd love to go to nocturne
I watch a bunch of wizard. Yes. What are they selling? It's the greatest. I'm into it
There's heads that talk to you in the alley there. Whoa
And skeleton dancing skeletons and a friend of ours
Anthony Geo just took Jason and I around the Universal a lot and we were doing some snooping
And there is a big plot of land down down on the you know level of Jurassic Park
But it's probably Nintendo. It's probably not gonna be dying on alley
Next to Transformers. Yeah, right. Yes, right next to Transformers. That's what people are saying
Very active construction site, there's a ton. It's a ton of land
It still doesn't look enough land for a bit still doesn't look enough for anything too substantial
Yeah, supposedly secret life of pets is going up on the top lot in the New York area
I agree with you. No, but like even for did that
Did that make them that much money? Is that a land they can make?
Now okay, there's no problem anymore
Okay, is the dog he saved us yes, he's the dog the dog has been recast who was the dog we don't want to
Know it doesn't matter cuz it's Patton now
They've made it the correct rotund alternative comedian
It is no problem
Now I think you have to don't you have to do
On on the back lot somewhere and you take the
Can I throw out something real outside the box though, you know, I might get screamed I might get shouted down
Doesn't it seem like you think about what's right next to the Wizarding World of Harry Potter?
What if some of Harry Potter invaded the place we call CityWalk? Oh
What if oh, what if you what part of it?
Some of CityWalk I got a look at the map here. I'm not sure
Underground tunnel into parts of CityWalk do it like it's under ground that would be
Here I'll write it for you. You take it's not the other green guard green gods bank ride
It's a new one and it's just for taking you underground from Wizarding World to the parts of CityWalk that you've knocked down
And you come out of the Goblin Bank and you go past the dragon and it's very scary and you come out and you're in
Diagon Alley, which is attached to green gods banks. What's canon? It's fine. Everyone loves it
I mean a rumor that we talked we've talked about before there's also a rumor of an expansion to Diagon Alley potentially a ministry of magic
battle ride
Ministry of magic ride and
Battle breaks out like a magic land is a rumor as well land
Is third park or fourth park in Orlando rumor ministry of magic land or as your third do it?
But as your second here, no, give me the things that I already like yes
I mean, I agree
I pitched a few episodes ago like yank that were the world set out there build a Diagon Alley
Maybe the primus it's very prime real estate
But it is like it is a big people do like it on the studio tour because it is a huge set
I just had a thought and this is a little bit of last term
But we were talking about how Patton is the dog now and it made me thought about another beloved like DreamWorks character
Poe the panda who is voiced by a very good friend Jack Black
I guess he's can we talk about how wild it is that Jack I guess just is because he's a star of a certain
brightness is allowed to
Simultaneously do Poe the panda and
Tenacious D and no one has been able to stop him from doing that. Well, so what do you mean?
What do you mean? You mean because he's because tenacious D is of an R rated or but there's many exactly
I mean Sarah Silverman is in wreck at Ralph and she has some material that's not PG 13 like Don Rickles
Himself used to make fun of all the races and gender
I just think and I don't dislike it
I just think that it is incredibly savvy of Jack Black to have simultaneously had a career where he
Can be Poe the panda and the house with the clocks in the house and the walls of the house
Is like a keys more of a kid movie star than an adult movie
But he is like simultaneously releasing like fucker. Gently is like sure. Yeah, just D type stuff
I think that's a thing. I really I've always really liked about Jack Black's he like keeps the cred alive
He'll still make a cameo in some weird thing or being a channel 101 thing. Let me be 100% clear
I love Jack Black. I love tenacious D their new album apocalypto is out now. They're on tour that it's very very silly
It's very fun. I haven't heard of tenacious D. Sure
Out of the kindness of your Jack Black can get it, but I'm
so you feel
So you're are you trying to like you're admiring basically
I'm admiring the fact that I feel like a lot of people get so worried when they go into quote-unquote children's entertainment
I think Dreamworks has done a good job with Kung Fu Panda all the Kung Fu Panda movies are great
I as an adult like all three of them a lot. Do you like the new show?
The new 3d Kung Fu Panda show Universal
I didn't watch it was closed when I came and weirdly Pinocchio still work in the turnstile at that
So so they could swap stuff in and out
He's got a gig, you know, all right, yeah have some income
I think I'm just I feel like I don't know would Disney have hired him to be a main voice knowing that that was still
What I think that it's yeah
I think unless some weird conservative guy on Twitter makes a big case out of something like what happened to James Gunn
I think that no one's paying any attention. No one cares
But you can like fool Bob Iger and Alan Horn into firing somebody very easily it seems
So like maybe we're maybe what you have just done on this podcast is open people's eyes to the fact that there's a very filthy
Album and that Jack Black is about to lose his job is poe the panda
I think Jack just found out about some very upsetting material that Jack Black
Released over a decade ago
This man is encouraging people to fuck gently. I don't understand this at all and hard and hard
Part of the song he's sending mixed messages, too
Well, no, he'll keep his job. I think it'll be fine. I don't think Bob Iger Alan Horn listen to the show
Hmm, and I can grab the congratulations to everybody at Disney by the way on the smash success of Bohemian Rhapsody
Fox's biggest hit of Disney who only works with the most upstanding
Great to see Bryan Singer coming back from international waters to have a number one movie again truly
He's still got really incredible
moral compass no
Great cinematic. Ah, yes, I was trying to figure out the moral compass in international waters joke
Sailed through international waters without the use of any sort of moral compass
The official director of pizza gate Brian
The pizza gate the movie Jason that movie you can it should cannot buy or you or you can buy just on the dark web
That is that joke is gonna cost you a number of different voiceover gigs. I think
Unfortunately all your blue material over the years. Oh all of my blue all of my
dragging Brian Singer for
Eight years
All right
Newer entrees at three broomsticks like the Christmas ones
No, I haven't seen the Christmas ones, but this you know, they do rotate stuff in and out and they added a
Sunday roast sandwich. Mm-hmm the cheese toasty with chicken Nicole got the cheese toasty
Was a good title it looked
I mean like well, yeah toasty is a much more common
European thing to call it or I guess maybe specifically British or crazy stuffed grilled cheese with a fried egg
It's a stuffed good cheese. It did not have fried grilled on top when she bought it
It had chicken and bacon inside of it. She said it was very good. Very greasy the bread itself
She actually described this kind of garlic bread ish. Mm-hmm. I had it. Yeah, but it looked good
I've had it. It's a little too much. It's a lot believe it or not
And then the last one is the plowman's lunch
No, is that meat in it that I can't eat? Oh, yeah. Yeah, it's a lot of meat
In fact, it's a scotch egg a bunch of a sort of deli beats like three or four kinds of cheeses a cut-up apple
sliced bread
pickles olives and then like a
Cranberry shot. I don't think all of these are available at Universal Studios, Los Angeles
I know because Jason ordered it so I ordered it
Okay, so I had seen this in Florida and in Florida it says serves two and in Florida
It's mostly salad and a scotch egg and some cheeses
That's what you're showing me right now is a lot more reasonable than what Mike was showing me
Yes, and again, it says on the menu for two or more
Hollywood did not say that and they replaced the salad with assorted deli beats
Well, this will be a lighter fare and
It was not at all
And look like you had just taken a tray out of a like a deli counter at a supermarket
When Mike before we started recording had said he was gonna show us something that you had ordered
I was almost I was 90% sure you had ordered the great feast
For I think like six
It's just is it just chicken and ribs and all this side
Yeah, I believe if I'm correct
I think Mike did the great feast for four and it was weird because you had booked a flight out of LAX 15 minutes
Later and then you thought like well, this is too much
I have to go and then you went back up and just out of your business for no reason out of your mouth
You said another great feast, please
Classic Carlson I had to review I wanted I knew we were gonna review and I want to try it twice
Anyway, everything on this plate was very good, but it felt like an ordeal once I was halfway through
It was so much and then once you said like well you can get a lot of the stuff a la carte and now it's just
I probably just wanted the Scotch egg. Why didn't I just say ask could I get
You could get this stuff all a cart. Is there what's the meat in a Scotch egg? It's sausage. It's pork sausage. Okay, cool
The catchphrase of this podcast is gonna become my tummy is too full
Fully too fall after eating most of three desserts that they had to come with yeah
Asparagus and mashed potatoes and I think with a lot of theme park menus
This goes for Disney too. You can get things a la carte, but they don't advertise it because they want you to buy it together
So if there's a hamburger with fries, I'm sure 99% of the time you can get it with no fries
It's just they want to sell it to you
So all you have to do is go can I just have the hamburger? Can I have it without this?
There's I read a whole like article like years ago
About like how to save money and it's like don't get cheese on the hamburger
Okay
That's when I think I first learned that the wall of though like just asking for a cup of water because they don't advertise that
Obviously either they just want you to buy a bottle of water
You buy a pumpkin fist which is very good
But very sweet and if it is the only thing that you have to kind of like drink down the potted butterbeer
It does become problematic even though it by itself. It's a very good drink
Yeah, it mixed with yeah a giant meat feast topped off with pumpkin
Juice mixed mixed thankfully with seltzer because I think the pumpkin juice by itself would be a little too much
But the pumpkin fizz is good
And I think Jessica had suggested that that is what you throw the fire whiskey into
The pumpkin the bottled pumpkin juice is good too, but very very sweet is a juice you're drinking a juice
Yeah, you're drinking a juice like a child
Drinking a juice flavored with like pumpkin pie spices like whatever the cardamom nutmeg
Whatever the classic pumpkin pie that sounds right. Mm-hmm
I want to throw out a broader point here that gets us outside of Potter a little bit what I was mainly
I'm sitting in that that main ballroom ballroom. What do you get the main out of the main room?
Three brimsticks they're just thinking this is this is so grand it enhances the experience so much that this is like that
There's an experience that is so immersive and cool in this park
That is not a ride and I started thinking there are a lot of these now
I clearly
Star Wars is gonna be great in the food department with the Cantina. I haven't been to the avatar
Restaurant, but it seems like that really adds to the dull experience and expands it
if this isn't quite on that level, but I think that cars diner is really fun and
Keeps the story going and yeah decent food there and I just first of all, I just want to say I
Disney and Universal how great a job the chefs are doing the the people building these places
It's like it just expands these worlds in such a wonderful way
But I also I also thinking I just wanted to pose in general if you now that
movie-based
Restaurants are on the table a little more is there a place in like or or specifically a menu item
From a film or media that you would most want to have done to perfection
you know in a
Immediately, I think that I would like to get I would like to go up to a replicator on a starship
I order just and put cars. I was just thinking
Tea hot
And I wanted to replicate hot
Yeah, tea Earl Grey hot is what he would say and it would replicate and then I would want to enjoy it in my quarters
Well, you know, you know what? I was just thinking is that I think that one potential for
Future growth that I haven't seen before in Harry Potter
Famously in the the Great Hall where they all eat food just sort of appears on the table
It's not taken anywhere and it doesn't it's just like the plates appear and then they vanish
So picture a restaurant that you have to walk up to the second floor to get into and you're seated around a table and
The method for meal delivery is such that the kitchen is below it and dishes dumbwaiter style
Just go up and appear like under what it like, you know
You could magic it up or whatever
But that would be a sort of that is really sort of like blending the line between what is a ride and what is a restaurant
In a way that is very cool to me
The other two things that I also just thought of were if you were to theme a sort of like outdoor place as a
Lady and the tramp eating spaghetti and meatballs in an alleyway style restaurant
Could be fun and a ratatouille restaurant where a rat makes your food
They have Tony's in Florida, but they don't have an alley
Special that being their version of the chef's table is the alley is a special romantic
Also that restaurant famously
Fine like it's fine. No one cares about what they now I just saw over the weekend that they have a care a guy playing Tony
That I would like to eat at
And I've been it's probably a year
I've been stringing this out because there's I'm getting close to the end
But I've been watching the Sopranos and I would like a pop-up
Whatever. No
No, I want to go to Vesuvius
I want to go to Artie Bucco's restaurant and I want to walk around Artie Bucco to bother your table
Too much to constantly be asking how the food is and trying to encourage you to order dessert and try to tell you bad
stories
I want that like the mom's diner at Hollywood Studios
We're like mom yells at you if you don't clean your plate just already going like I got the sea bass. Oh
Maroon, this is it's crazy
HBO is owned by who Warner Brothers. Yeah, so we're working maybe maybe a Sopranos land in that Dubai Park
And Warner Brothers movie worlds. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah some wise guys sitting at another table. They don't even need to make a scene
They're just there they eat and they leave without paying they just nod at Artie and they have a tab and you actually had another good idea
For a theme bar on the our episode we do with Jeff Garland was a rock
I believe a Rockford files theme bar
Yeah, well, I wanted a Rockford files a themed bar kind of and like the bartender would be
Rockford would be an old cranky
Like sunburned man who would serve you what I want is for the the Sheraton
Universal to make things right and to reconvert it to being telly's been in fact amended perhaps to be sloppy
And maybe a walk around telly's of all this checking in on
Yeah, yeah, they have a lot of very generic photos hanging in that lobby like old Hollywood photos. Those should all be telly's of all this
Project if you're living in like the sort of like rainforest cafe vibe also where you can make a restaurant and just kind of generally
theme it rain forest
I'm down for that game. I like I'm
Like if you want to do just like a general
fantasy
Tavern, right? I'm not even talking Harry Potter. I'm talking like Lord of the like every
Every King Arthur Lord of the Rings or X elves, whatever
Yeah, yeah, like that there is now the problem is this place is famously the food is like gross because it's a media medieval food
No, yeah, it's all pretty like it's like a trough. There's gotta be I mean like you don't consider
the that in real life to be round table pizza
That doesn't go far enough for you man, I wish I could have a place where there was around table pizza
In like other cities around me there's one in Burbank, you know, is it came on
It's like a Panera had like someone like dashed a little camel on on top like a sprinkle
I don't know that it's nice like Panera. I think the theme
According to what are two old co-workers. The theme was a food poisoning
Dined at that King's table. I
Have one more just like the ideal meal that I would like to have and Jason
I know you'll you'll be into this and back me up. I want to go into the little cafe in
Phantom Thread where Reynolds Woodcock meets Alma for the first time so that you can do his massive order of
bacon some scones
Butter butter and cream butter and cream
And the only thing on the menu is that big list and then you and then you order it you have but you have
To say the whole thing in whatever that accent is and then she and then the walk around Alma actress will write
to my hungry boy
I love it since it got on HBO go
I keep I keep getting just a little stoned and watching theater Phantom Thread and making it about
20 minutes 20 minutes at a time before I fall asleep, but it feels like
It's so heightened every line is so loaded and it's also just it's such an intense experience
I think you only get something about that very funny. Yes. It's very funny on repeat viewings
You start to see like all the little the cuts all the slights
They're giving each other on the barbs and stuff
Seen Paul F. Tompkins recording of what he thought the Phantom Thread opening credit song should have been
He did one for halt and catch fire which my friend created is a really good hall and catch fire
Like the crossfire song a little bit great
I
Who owns Phantom Thread and where can we put that experience what park I'm thinking practical sure sure sure
Megan Ellison land what's the who's that woman who finances?
Yeah, right so Anna perna Kingdom, okay
This isn't one specifically. I don't know. I know where they would go cuz Disney owns it
but I don't know what it would be there needs to be a
Muppet
Restaurant mm-hmm. What is it? Well?
There is a bad Muppet restaurant in Hollywood Studios called Rizzo's which is a pizzeria
But there's barely any reference to the Muppets inside
It's just like Rizzo is on the outside of it only recently became full like Fraggle Rock
Restaurant well sure
What are the crystals I forget they eat something
I
Know you're the big ogres or whatever and you eat Fraggles all the every meal is
Imagine like
Sausages or other meat products, but they have to like carve them into the shape of a Fraggle
Yeah, and then you get a plate of just fried up. That's that's you eat Fraggle worse
Idea
I'm wondering if the new the newer the Toy Story land and Hollywood Studios in Magic Kingdom now that we live in a
PF world, and I'm not talking about PFT Paul F. Tonkin talking about chains. No I'm talking about
No, this is you can divide a line in modern society the
Post forky and pre forky
Screams I don't belong
the the craft project that seems to be having an identity crisis that a lot of
Toy Story 4 hinges upon will all the forks now in Toy Story land
Oh good will they look like forky will you use forky to then you throw forky or there's a mass grave of forks in the
Garbage can someone's someone famously treated forky is no rambi and there
Thing a little tiny puppets not
If you like if you had to eat with a with pipe cleaners
Like and they're permanently attached you can't like dismount them. That's it. That's a deeply unpleasant experience
Yeah, and it's also if people have pointed out isn't forky a spork. Yes
Rounded head sure is you know well, I'm sorry. I keep this thing about more restaurants
I feel like Kung Fu Panda has become a de facto Thanksgiving Day movie always plays on your favorite movie
And your favorite band the con and crows no
Panda saying long December would that be your greatest musical performance if Jack Black's saying
long December as
Poe from Kung Fu Panda, but with sincerity. I don't feel like he would sing that song Michael
This is the sort of thing Mike would do is because that Mike Zach and I were on an improv team together for a number of
Four five
Four five and and we would we would all do this to each other where like you keep bringing up this
Is this one of your pocket like favorite things?
Yeah, I mean I do I do like Kung Fu Panda a lot. It scratches a lot of issues for me
It's Jack ever seen all Kung Fu Panda against it
Jason
I think I've only seen bits and pieces
Movies I'm a man you know Jesus no
Okay, come Kung Fu Panda. It's on almost every Thanksgiving on TV. So like if like what channel every channel
It's not on every channel. It's on Fox News. It's on CBS
Drug special for for real Kung Fu Panda is is a very good movie. We should have done Kung Fu Panda the 3d movie
I haven't seen it though. I can't
Do that yeah, I for sure will my point was sorry Kung Fu Panda's
Adopted father is a duck that works at a noodles restaurant
I know the duck cuz they have a character of him that has shown up in the parks and he talks to the people
There's a lot of parts. We know it if it's not we don't know all the all the cartoon food and Kung Fu Panda looks very good
there's no reason that there shouldn't be a
Chinese restaurant in Dreamworks that is a kung fu
That's great
There is our food and accounting crows song you would want to eat I'm gonna think here
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Hard candy shop an album that really grew on me if I'm gonna be a hard candy
I always liked and tightest back in the Dreamworks. Yeah counting crows do a
Song what's the problem, baby? What's the problem? I don't know well, maybe
The opening song from Jack to good song Wow well we demand a counting crows presence in Universal Studios
This must have among many other things there's a lot of stuff
We have the counting crows replace the Blues Brothers as the Universal
Resident musical in Adam Durant's wings
So you've seen all the cars movies I assume
You see the first two okay, you've seen you've seen multiple minions movies Jason
Yes, Despicable Me
One that's not a new movie and the minions. Okay, that's a minions movie
You don't think the people me one and two are minions movie. No, they're Despicable Me
It's come from there. I think I see what you're saying if you're gonna call one minions then that
Is
There are those are crew movies I've seen some of the minion shorts as well sure
Your man, so you go down the movies that are worse that we've seen
I'm trying to establish that I know that you guys are not like snobs about watching animation
You like you like Wally up, right? Sure. Yes. Yeah, you saw brave of a very seem brave sure
Okay, so I
Panda is much much better than brave. Have you seen how to train your dragon? I've never seen any
Now those I know are supposed to be very good. Yes. They're anyone go the music is great
I mean you talk about like that's we're minutes away from having that be a theme park
I guarantee you they will make rumors about that going in the third parking universal
It's an incredible world that they've created
Like Wally where you'd have to make like a trash planet and be like come hang out on trash miserable
Yes, yeah, I cannot I cannot believe that you guys have not seen
The third one's coming out there one's coming out two of them so I can catch up on that I guess to
It's two movies like I'm a bad movie watcher in addition
Watch in the first 20 minutes
And then I pick up where I left off
When it first came out and now I'm rewatching and I'm savoring it like he savored that 4,000 calorie breakfast
Ten hours of professional wrestling to watch a week
Videos on YouTube and that's about like boycott some of it until they pull their shit out of Saudi Arabia or whatever
Well, it's not that I'm not saying WWE. Okay. I don't know. That's all WWE. Oh, that's true
You're into a lot of yeah, you're in plenty of other wrestling. Yeah. Yeah, that's all pure and there's nothing problematic
Our stock yes, I sold my sock. Yeah
We socket stock I tried to sell was a bunch of chicken stock
Animation is not theme parks. They feel adjacent enough to me that I don't know why that's so
Surprising to me that you guys haven't seen this a little odd thing that I don't like I'm so theme park
Centric that like I there's a lot of movies. I only know about cuz they're in theme parks
That makes sense. It is different. You're fully correct. I end up
Actually exploring Harry Potter. It'll be because it's the park thing now. That's a Thanksgiving those movies
They marathon a lot around
holidays
Is Harry Potter a Thanksgiving movie
Harry Potter does take place during Thanksgiving. It's kind of the emotional backdrop of it
I think you could argue that it is so it is I guess
Alright, we answered all we solved a lot of debates. We came up a lot of ideas any before we wrap it up
And any any final thoughts about about three broomsticks? Oh, what's everyone's favorite entree to order?
I only had one so the one I had fish and chips. Okay. I think I had a fish and chip a while ago
I think I liked it better than that. What is my sandwich called again that I had
Toasty I think back when I was still eating chicken the the lemon chicken that they had I should try that that's great
It's very good. I I so want them to bring this out here because right now it's only Orlando. They have pasties
Cornish pasties delicious wonderful not a not a common dish to find in America
No, we don't do meat pies super a lot out here, which is shocking because nothing could be more
American than the idea of like taking a bunch of ground-up meat and put it in like a good fried dough thing and
But doing it really really well. There's a place in Scotland. I think it's a chain
I don't know if it's outside of Scotland, but it's called pie maker and
Anytime sorry, I'm talking about Scotland because it's like all of the Harry Potter
Yes, and you've been to Edinburgh, yeah, and Edinburgh is where at JK
Rowling lives when she was writing a decent amount of it
So a lot of that city informs the books in like some ways. I mean that's right up your alley. That's perfect
Yeah, it truly is there. I
Can't get into it. It would take it would take too long. I'm saying meat pies are very good
It's called pie maker that makes them shout out pie maker. Please open a location in the United States
There apparently was briefly a pie shop on sunset by you see be like a few blocks from there that had like meat pies and
Hand pies and so I don't think it lasted like very long wrong location. Where was it close to East to be sunset like heading east on?
The perfect place for my fancy meat pie business right next to the improv theater and the vape shops next to the the former
methadone clinic
Yeah, that that's such a bad location that Jason never went there
When it was so close to a place he goes to do sketch comedy
But and you were like such a pain in the
Fly I mean there's a poke place. That's a block away. That's very good that I go a couple of times
So bring me pies
I was a location and make them full of a
Fraggle meat and kung fu panda meat
I'll say my last thought is I'd like to eat up in the sea like upstairs somewhere
I so I know it's a trick, but I'm like I want to go up to that second
Staircases and yeah, and stuff up there. It's it's it's designed so well the high see that's my that's my final thought of it
Like the physical building of it the attention to detail the ceiling is so high it makes you feel like you're in a big space
It shuts you out from the outside world. The sound balance is great. It feels like you're walking into another world
Which is exactly what they want and they did it good in terms of infrastructure
I I may have mentioned this before but like operating a full capacity inside and the patio
Holds hundreds of people patio is huge. It doesn't look like it
I didn't think it looked like when I first went up there
But when I really walked around the patio, I was like, yeah, I could see how this could hold three five hundred people
It's real big and if you go and it's kind of almost closing which is very early if Universal Studios for reasons
That still boggles my mind. Um
it's like pretty empty and
Sometimes you can pick your table and it's just like it feels it feels like a real wizard restaurant. Yes. Yeah
Yeah, you can actually have like little moments of peace up there. It's pretty nice
Well, it's a very nice note to end on Zachary and I used to five podcasts the bride
Thanks for being here that was a bit just a pleasant for that wasn't like a hater II
Talking shit about things that was just a that was a delight is this place is very nice and go to it if you're in
the area, but the yeah
Hey, we're like to let you exit through the gift shop. Is there anything you'd like to plug? Yeah, I mean
Got a podcast off off book. It's found where podcasts arts and improvised musical
Another friend of the pod Jessica McKenna make up a musical it's about an hour long
It's got fun fun guests and it's it's a good time just featured on a vulture comedies
Very convoluted the 29 comics to watch
Comics to feature. Yeah. Thank you vulture. I love them very much
What do we got to plug follow us on Twitter on Instagram?
Check out our patreon at patreon.com slash podcast the right. Yes
Right now here the recently released Club 33 episode our experience going to the good boys get fancy
Oh
Perhaps our friend the correct the people who did the that's from Disneyland Gallery where we did our live show and we had a yeah
We had a wonderful feast there
Tummies are too full you wash your hands under those golden goose
No goose where's a golden goose I saw pictures from the bathroom and apparently like the sink faucets are gold
Maybe this is just the ladies bathroom. I saw pictures from the ladies bathroom taking my cap
I think she went well, that's the way
That's the one place you're not supposed to take picture in the club
Or any bathroom it is out well
pictures because as always we are very good boys, that's right
Anything else just nah nah nah nah nah
Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah yeah
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boehm Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey
for more original podcasts
Please visit forever dog podcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcast
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and
Liking our page on Facebook