Five, four, three, two, one.
podcast arrived, the second gate, the fancy upper class rich person edition
right behind that sweet paywall. My name is Mike Carlson as always joining me
Jason Sheridan. Hi Scott Gardner. Hey yeah if you if you're listening to this then I
assume that you have paid your $25,000 episode admittance fee and that in order
to continue listening to it you will pay your $10,000 yearly episode renewal fee.
And if you haven't paid those things and there has clearly been a lapse in the
patreon system if you only paid a some $5 monthly then there's a big we're
missing out on a lot of funds. Someone had mentioned because about the patreon that
we should have like a club 33 like there should be some insane like $5,000
membership for some other specific like I don't know what it would be like being
sitting here watching us do this live that doesn't sound pleasant. I thought
the joke was that it was $33. I saw a different one I saw that too I saw a
different one though. Oh I saw another one person mentioned like an actual
tier I think. If we can think of a decent enough tier to yeah 33 is like cap it
because it's supposedly club 33 is like 500 members is that right? That's a
number I kept seeing pop up but there's it's not clear. There's a lot of like
numbers that aren't clear about club 33. I think it gets dicey once you incorporate
corporate membership. Right because some of the memberships. Yeah companies they
could be counting it as one they could be counting yeah. I think I think $33 a
month maybe gets you exclusive China sets each month delivered to your home
with the podcast the ride logo. Super fan so we have to find a China manufacturer
once we do. Okay that's good. We got a great perk. You get a new plate every
month and the longer you subscribe the more you end up with a full 30-piece set.
Yeah that's a good look that's a great idea if we can find a cheap China
manufacturer. Don't tell them it's cheap no it's the finest quality real
gold leaf slated into the plates. Well we'll work on that is what we're saying
but thank you by the way this is the first one recording patreon where we've
seen the people actually are interested in the patreon. Yeah. And they like to thank you
It's super encouraging and it makes us very excited to do more stuff. Yeah we're having fun
patreon ideas all the time and I especially love that right away people
were commenting you got to do this you need to do one and so again this is this
is for y'all tell us what you want us to do and what we're very happy to get the
prompts and you know the more obscure the better over here you know. Yes.
We're unfettered by people who you know we don't have to go back and explain what all the
stuff is we can just dive straight into yeah I don't want to ruin any surprises
I guess but we were talking about a well who is the character the in the in the
factory that you go oh yeah so so yeah we don't want to we will tease a little
bit of an episode that will be coming in the next couple months probably but
there's a character if you know it his name and he's a character I think he's a
real man as well but his name is Papa Steve and even just leave it at that
like will you write us and tell us if you know what Papa Steve is I didn't but
you guys have a long history with Papa Steve yeah I have multiple I'll just say
this I have multiple photos of Jason through the years I think at least two I
got to go back to the archives of Jason and a picture of Papa Steve and well
yeah let's just leave it at that I mean you guys are theme park nerds and
weirdos so you figure out who Papa Steve is fan favorite maybe that's what
deep-cut fan favorite yeah and that's what paid the patreon's all about yeah
I think maybe maybe what if it's that someone has to either email us or
comment on the patreon or tweet it as who Papa Steve is and that will unlock
the episode oh yeah then we'll have to do it like pretty quickly but somebody
has to name it yeah yeah yeah that's good I like that but otherwise maybe we
should just do it get it in the can but maybe it never comes out unless people
solve the mystery of Papa Steve sure I bet it doesn't take much well I don't
know it's a this is a good little theme for the audience to play I do think Papa
Steve is on the higher end of obscure Disney character although that's a too
much of a hint actually okay I said Disney but I think he's I think we'll
see we'll see I will I will will be surprised yeah
a licensed character there is not a park star of Papa Steve there's no vinyl
nation of Papa Steve as far as I know no t-shirts available yet no merch we
popularized Papa Steve with our audience and we and we profit off of his likeness
yeah the Papa Steve merch will roll we'll get a lawsuit from his estate
there's a state if you're dead yes okay sorry I don't know cuz I frankly well
I'll save it I'll save it for the episode but uh yeah when we sell Papa
Steve t-shirts and then the bootleg knockoff puff puff sativa shirts which
is just the Papa Steve shirt and he's got a little joy this map so everything
we talk about we're going to sell pot themed version like Bart Simpson kicking
Saddam's ass not sure if and I would have you Google Papa Steve the first
thing that comes up is Papa Steve's no junk raw protein bars and it's a guy
named Steve Dybald this is not Papa Steve we're talking about that's a good
hint that's a good narrow down right I'm really excited I'm glad we gave the
audience a little mission here and I'm excited to see if it's fruitful and also
Papa Steve 100% sure on Steve right oh yeah it's in the photo okay as long as
it's in the photo there's for some reason I got in my head Papa Mark but I
it's just a pizza place in Pennsylvania my family goes to sometimes no I mean I
I'm gonna look right at the photo here I sent it yesterday there's a picture of
you looking longingly at this photo and it says Papa Steve at the bottom okay
very good so confirmed Papa Steve but please send us when you discover Papa
Steve is and that will unlock the episode yep I'll give it hints Papa Steve is
from an active attraction it is not a dead attraction oh so you can find okay
yeah that's good oh that'd be the best way to unlock it send us a photo of you
and Papa Steve yes yeah huh interesting okay this is this is great well I think
you're gonna start I also think somebody's gonna get this immediately
yeah I think that's entirely likely yeah yeah also we have not when we say unlock
we don't mean in the patreon sense we have not recorded that episode yet just
general scheme of it'll force our hand there's a lot of terms yeah on that
website that we're still learning so look at this we're still to work we're
sending in on on the exclusive scavenger hunts this is a per this is a premium
experience already and which which is fitting with today's topic which is the
ultimate Disney Disneyland premium experience that we got to experience for
ourselves will this be a braggy episode potentially and I apologize to the
audience if it verges on that however you've been listening to us presumably
for a little while I hope that you're that you're happy for us that we got to
enter the promised land of of Club 33 so how do we and we'll talk a little bit
about you know Club 33 in general in the history of it and everything but let's
I guess explain our experience I think we alluded to it in an episode but we got
to go thanks to our our new friends as of the who made who made our live show
possible Richard and Nicholas Kraft who ran the that's from Disneyland gallery
where we did our live show which hopefully you checked out and also we
were at we were it was very fun to be joined by Paul Scheer who also did a
and to say thanks Richard brought us into Club 33 and specifically into the
into the lounge where which is a newer area of the club called Le Salon Nouveau
Le Salon Nouveau so we had a we had a super fun lunch that went on and on and
on that dragged out we were there for so long it was such a delight and don't
I was gonna say dragged on seems like it might be like a bummer but no yeah wrong
drag good in a dragging in a good way yeah like leisurely a leisurely drag
drag from what I understand about Europe absolutely yeah yeah yeah so hey this was
this was a blast how do we handle this do we talk about the the place in
general and we talk about our experience or yeah I guess I mean it was very cool
in general we went to that we Jason I went down with Paul a little early we
rode the Ferris wheel which is the first time I ever rode the Ferris wheel
around yes and that'll be an episode pal around definitely a patreon episode and
yeah and then so say is pal around separate from yes wheel for sure
separate from fun wheel yeah that's two different episodes no way we could
possibly contain fun wheel and pal around yeah the mythology is all different
from pal around to fun wheel yeah I well on the other rounds I don't well I don't
want to give away to my but I had a perfectly lovely ride on it and once we
got off you were like I was I had a comfortable I had a little mild panic
attack as the first who was going up and it probably didn't help we were loaded
in with a another party I didn't realize I thought like oh Ferris wheel we were
we will get our own car oh yeah well they got to pack them in because the
thing is such a bad loading that helped because they took a nice picture of us
yeah that was nice I where is that photo send that to me I haven't seen it Scott
hasn't seen anyway but so we went on a couple rides and then we met up with
Scott and it was a very crowded it was Columbus when it was Columbus yeah and
that was nightmarish around there like getting me getting into the park and
to like inside New Orleans Square which is where Club 33 is and I made a joke
loudly that we have ten minutes hopefully I don't think we're gonna make
it which is crazy if you know how close that is to each other but the crowd was
so bad and the crowds like the lines were being rerouted through pirates that
like we almost didn't make it it was just an insanely crowded day away yeah it
was so awful yeah which just really let us I think savor in writing in this
private calm location on an incredibly stressful day yeah that's I was gonna say this is why I
bring that up is because the park was so crowded and I remember I think I said it
to you or something my understanding always was that this place was sort of
packed every day that there was full of people dining and eating and the
Club 33 is you know the waiting list goes on for decades right and you know
you know maybe if you're lucky your child will get to go in after you're
dead or like it's so like the terms are so stacked but then but and yet we're in
there and had place to ourselves yeah basically it was wild so yes we made it
there just right on time and Club 33 used to be closer to where the Blue Bayou
was which is the Pirates restaurant.
Yeah the restaurant that's in the launch point essentially of Pirates.
Scott you've been there before you had been to that version of the entrance.
I had yes so that's yeah Mike and Jason had not not been to Club 33 I got to go
thanks to my friend David we had a blast there good like you know five years ago
and yes we had been we'd been into that entrance which had a like private little
elevator yes French lift yes okay and it was like a which we in looking up the
history of this was something that Walt found somewhere and tried to buy it
from the building and they said that's impossible to remove it nor are we
interested in removing our elevator no matter the cost.
We also need the elevator.
Yeah yeah it's extremely functional so so he just so he like took photos and had
imagineers just build one to his specifications and it's yeah that's like
that's that was that was an incredible little experience to have going up that
thing and really takes you into the past but that is no longer there that is one
of the changes and this is a whole you know I think Club 33 was a certain
certain way in a certain amount of space until like 2014 2015 and then it's been
pretty drastically not drastically but expanded an amount of yeah mostly
expansion mostly a good thing mostly allows more space and more more room
more empty space where no one is yeah.
But also controversial because they they took over the
which is this is like very peaceful manicured courtyard like New Orleans kind
of courtyard that for many years anyone could just go back there and take
pictures there's tons of photos online of people's engagement photos or
proposal like in the Court of Angels and I used to love going back there and
getting pictures and showing it to people because it is an interesting like
this doesn't exist anywhere else like this is only in Disneyland it it's not
an attraction it's not a show it's not a restaurant it's just a cute little you
know bit of place making and now it's gone and only for the rich yeah it's
over and X sing yeah people are shocked that Disney has made moves for money
making purposes right it does like it does it does make sense though to have
a better more out of the way area to load this place though I mean
unfortunately I it is a bummer that it's gone you can't just walk into it
because it was nice it was one of those spots where it was like a little
peaceful it was very yeah it was like a couple and it's still peaceful like that
well sure and there's little there's a locked or infused water for you to wait
before you are back in oh my god the infused water was so good yeah it was a
wasn't iced tea but it was like infused with like
the time I lavender I believe yeah yeah did I say when we were drinking the
water that like the employees were looking at us like we were two hobos
that had wandered into like a rich person's restaurant I mean it did feel
that way and the sheer number of napkins that I got out of that place oh yeah my
got crumpled over there they're sitting on the sound bar we all do this
I think so yeah not cloth napkins by the way paper like nice paper like the
bathroom paper towels essentially well do you worth taking home do you wipe
like your hands on a special occasion with them they've all been free there
there in 12 frames napkins and 12 identical frames if you got liquid gold
on your hands and needed to clean that off maybe that's that's when you break
open the frames and start using the fancy yes yeah so you're staying with if
you have caviar all over your fingers right I'll say this then they were very
this makes it sound lawless but there were very few rules at Club 33 the only
thing they told us you can take photos anywhere you can walk into but not the
bathroom yeah doc take photos in the bathroom so that normal rule of society
right club 33 but I would have taken a photo in the bathroom very a very nice
ornate bathroom with Chuck Berry wouldn't like it there no photos that's
his favorite pastime it's a good point what in the bathroom we're talking
bathroom already I was shocked that they have little vials of mouthwash yeah I
got oh you took some I did not take Richard and I both mouthwash together at
the sink and then that was I was like I thought about it but I was like I'm not
gonna take a handful of there were glass too or were they plastic they were
plastic they were plastic okay if Richard had taught you how to shave that
would have been the experience he's dabbing your cheeks he wanted to see if
I was good at flossing he wanted to see yeah that would have been better it was
in there the Florida ceiling doors on the stalls as well right yes and pull
chain toilets like oh I cuz I didn't go into one of them I have the pull chain
had the where the the water tank is like closer to the ceiling and stuff oh
wow like I should go in the stall how did you not go in the toilet well I go I
went to the urinal and I didn't think you didn't need to use right I didn't
need but of course I should have explored all the every inch of it I went
a few times because not to be gross but hard liquor just goes right through me as
I've gotten older what do you really yeah quickly that's weird it's weird it
is weird you just hard liquor but not water yes really is there have you
googled this is this a real phenomenon like you okay no no yeah I mean as long
as that songs there's a bathroom close by which again the laws of society I
want you to leave places that serve hard liquor have a bathroom close by new
episode title Jason shits at club oh no other other other side okay oh yeah no
that would be more oh yeah that's what yeah I thought hard liquor makes you
makes you shit oh no I just have to you're an oh okay okay yeah oh yeah no
that would be very bad that would probably mean I had some sort of
allergic yeah all right some sort of that's what I was picturing the way that
coffee like could so yeah coffee yeah yeah yeah okay I thought just like a you
know yeah like some sips of rum yeah I really don't drink that much except on
your birthday it's all right and then you let it then you let her risk yeah
let's all wag our fingers the wound is healed thankfully okay so entrance area
that one yeah I guess we're trading out a cool thing for a less cool or for
another cool thing the elevator is not there but you get to walk in this this
Court of Angels area that's now annexed and that that is cool like boy yeah
wonderful entrance beautiful staircase and the elevator they turned into a
booth so you can sit in the elevator and eat your meal that that's in the lounge
I don't think it registered with me that that's oh I didn't realize that they
moved the little like the tiny little pull chain door the elevator into you
can like sit in there and it's right next to a little table really yeah but
like one person can barely squeeze in it'd be a very odd place to sit and eat
that's for sure there was also a table in the back of the lounge with one table
one tiny table almost like an old-time school desk yeah and one chair looking
out on the bay windows looking directly at the train station hmm and if I was
popping by myself that is where I would request to sit yeah it's this little
private nook it's yeah it's pretty neat but then there's a lot of like cool
stuff all around like every table is neat I think there's said there's some
table that was a prop from the happiest millionaire this 60s Disney movie
period piece the host station oh is that it I think and then there was an old
there used to be a phone booth in the original okay I think not there anymore
I or in another room I didn't think to look for it but that came up reading
about the original Club 33 huh huh and beautiful beautiful paintings and all of
the yell so where is also what they call Richard craft absolutely that I mean you
like in his element I'll say that what are like you know what a blast hanging
out with them and like I don't you know I'm not gonna go telling stories that
he told us but this is like you may have heard in the episode he's like he
represents here's his Danny Elfman he represents Jerry Goldsmith he represents
Marc Shaman the writer of Hairspray and all that I didn't also and John Bryan
who but Mike I love him we just saw last night and in concert not been a friendly
way we paid to see him right and and also I don't know if it's him or if it's
the company but but air apparently really the craft management Wow yeah
like air yeah there's one of them their film scores are wonderful it's also he
represents like all the coolest like like Pat like past and present a wide
wide range of cool composers and he had like amazing stories from all that and
yeah super super cool to hang out and hear all of it and what else well we
went so like let's like let's step by step a little more so we go to go into
the back of like New Orleans Square toward like if you're headed if you were
headed to the Blue Bayou and we're Club 33 used to be you just keep going back
to the Court of Angels so then there's all it sort of indicates I forget how it
indicates outside that it's 33 it's not as big like it used to be that we
couldn't figure out how to do it like Hill people we were just knocking on this
right so we know this is the real door yeah so we eventually figured out that
that was the real door yeah and then I think Nicholas like a like scan a card
or something yeah I think that there is supposedly there's so much rumor about
exactly what it is but I think yeah you're right there's a card scanning and
then you go and you're in a tiny little room with like two or three employees or
something yeah and they have like two or three employees with a desk and a
beautiful crystal display case of all the Club 33 exclusive merch yeah merch
and collectibles and stuff which really caught me off guard I totally didn't
realize there was Club 33 exclusive merch which is embarrassing I didn't
remember no yeah which of course I went wild for and I'll say what I got later
so yeah it's just like a normal restaurant thing where they're like
looking up your name and then they basically send you into the Court of
that amazing water what was the flavor of the water do you remember it was it or
was just fruit and I said lavender oh you said it okay it was like yeah cuz I
had never had water that good I don't think I think it was the best water I
ever had it was really nice and I Jason I can only zoom lavender water treats
your body just fine yes do you think though you you weren't peeing because you
ate straight had so much lavender water earlier and then you had like a cocktail
I mean yes cumulative it probably out I had I saw you with your mouth on the
spigot just pouring the lavender water in yeah and you could see the water
going through like bumps in my body right yeah yeah yeah walking water bed
yeah and then we had I rolled you up the stairs yeah I mean I think I was
drinking a lot of water to begin with that's healthy yeah yeah so then we you
kind of down there and then did they call I'm trying to remember my memories
already he's kind of overwhelmed and there was a lot yeah it's it was like a
dream a little bit of a dream yeah and then you would just walk upstairs and
the bathroom is up sort of on the like Terrace type thing or in like the walkway
up there and then you go through big doors and you're in Club 33 and there's
tile display yes we have a photo of that yeah yeah and then they kind of like
make you wait a second and then they take you to the table yeah there's a
hostess I mean every door open for everyone greeting you very nice asking
if you need anything yes well that's what I've read is that there it's I mean
like the does this Disney standard of service that you find everywhere and
certainly in the restaurants and the hotels especially the hospitality is
always great but I think the Club 33 people are like hyper trained yes yeah
like many months of super hospitality training and yes and it showed and like
boy did they were they helpful with food and drink recommendations right and
they put like their most knowledgeable people I think on it too I mean the
person we there are waitress had been working there for many many years so
knew a lot of stuff but I think like they probably have to pass like extra
tests in like Disneyland history and I bet like I bet like they have to know
more they have to be like there yeah I mean she's just telling us about the
lounge she's like oh of course this lounge is new in the last few years this
whole physical space you are in used to just be storage for like the stores
right below or like other New Orleans Square area merchandise and stuff and
then they had to reconfigure all of that because the pictures is pre
refurbishment the bar was so tiny like the lounge bar area was so tiny and
like just had a few maybe a couch and a few chairs it was almost just like a
hallway mm-hmm yeah whereas now this is this giant ornate bar it's just
wonderful well should we hear should we talk about it's okay so we're we're
entering you go through this hallway that's very very dim that is on either
side of you is case after case of fancy wine bottles you know so my eyes were
bouncing out sure like the mask and my pupils turned into wine bottle shape we
all turned into cartoons at certain points it depends our star particular
things active and then when I went up to the merch I saw the merch thing the
cabinet with the glass I my tongue like shot out and my tongue was giant and
like licking the glass in front of the exclusive club 33 merge and when they
accidentally put the check in front of Jason Richard he turned into a devil
like the incredible five feet up in the air and my legs looking like legs and
we're just spinning tires like yeah the check came and then we just turn there
a puff of dust Jason's perfect shape yes he sped out of there to steal more
paper towels so you yeah you go through this it's this amazing hallway like mood
and they're just like perfect I couldn't pretend to know the type of wood but
right is very like old-school mahogany crazy wine cellar and then further down
this hallway on either side of you are a couple of booths yeah very small and
exclusive yes that are all in each one is themed to a different ride I believe
there's a Pirates one a Haunted Mansion one a Tom's Island one that's like is
if it's like Tom and Huck on on the island like watching the Mark Twain go
by and then is it a bit was it a big Thunder I don't remember the fourth I am
looking through my photos I have a picture of the pirate ship and I have a
yeah I don't know I truly like felt so weird and overwhelmed in there I don't
know why I didn't photos yeah I felt uncomfortable doing that I think I was
trying to play it cool as well yeah yeah I think I don't want them to be like oh
look at those rubes look at those like they were more than encouraging oh yeah
they didn't photos ask question that's we get it mm-hmm right that's my that's
my problem not theirs because yeah I think I didn't take these pictures till
later like we were walking in I was like oh cool cool yeah cool oh great oh
whatever well you don't want to do it right away but once we felt like at home
once we sure there for three and a half hours whatever it was but anyway yeah
there's like there's there's little bits of Disney magic throughout this
restaurant is really what makes it so cool and these paintings have little
effects you know the Mark Twain puffs smoke or that I don't know what they'll
do but it's very it's like the ship's a little boo oh okay okay it's it's very
similar to the effect that the effects they have it like Trader Sam's yeah yeah
we're like a volcano shoot like shoots up once in a while when you order the
right drink which to eat at one of those booths would have been great but we had
a bigger with a bigger party and we were somewhere kind of just like dead
standing up dead center of the of the lab Le Salon Nouveau we sure we were
there so long though we could have each for an hour just gone in our own booth
alone yeah yeah because there was enough seat out like yeah pretty quickly the
most we had the place to ourselves and we're able to the bar had effects going
to similar to Club 30 oh yeah our effects were very cool yeah so yeah in
the the bar has kind I mean it's just like it's it's you know it's it's very
like Maleficent essentially it's like sort of like apothecary weird like yeah
study with vials and stuff and then with a big like crystal ball orb thing in the
center and every once in a while the crystal ball lights up with a swirl of
magic and the swirl spreads down the bar to like a little trumpet on either side
and then a ghost appears and starts playing the trumpet back and forth
trumpet goes yeah oh cool that's my highlight a mate like a bar with little
and to be you know that it's it's that it's well done Disney magic it's not
some like half-assed theme bar thing it like yeah it was so like detailed and
subtle and it's yeah it's I have a picture of it when the effect is not
going and it just looks like I don't know if that's a trumpet or like I
guess a tie yeah it's just a tiny trumpet or like a flugelhorn maybe is
what it's called but it's just like sitting there are you laughing at
it is a funny name it's just it does like it's one of those effects where
it's not clear that an effect is coming or is going to happen it's just looks
like a trumpet or whatever is sitting hanging there yeah and then when the
effect happens a ghost is playing it and it's crazy and you're really not sure how
it's done it's wild yeah like there's a couple effects like a Tokyo Disney like
they're like that where you're like staring at it and going what I'm not
sure like so cool yeah very very cool thing like that but only the members
get to see or the roofs that they let join them right only Goldman Sachs
employees get to see that ghost playing a flugelhorn yeah and it should it
should be noted that the lounge they were saying it's like oh it's harder to
get a reservation at the lounge because for one thing you have to be with a
member right like a member can make you reservations for the dining room
although I saw one thing online did you guys come across this that like say
someone made reservations for you or I think even for members this holds if you
are going to eat in the dining room there was a food minimum oh yeah possibly
equivalent to a one-day admission ticket sure per person it's pricey yeah per
person or the full full meal I think per person mm-hmm yeah because they're and I
think this is the appeal of the lounge is that if you've gone there for dinner
you know for for the many decades this has been open it's been like a you know
fancy four course meal that you have to do and and probably liquor on top of
that and to make the minimum and which is great and it was it was wonderful
when I got to do it but you end up spending a lot and the but in the lounge
it's more casual you could do piecemeal stuff you can get you can get a burger
although even the burgers are like we're crazy fancy burgers and it's still like
elevated and great food but you can it's it's certainly more casual than I think
that the dining experience have been although would they we were offered
four course menu they're like here is the four course menu right a la carte
menu if you see something on the four course menu you can order it a la carte
it was lunchtime yeah we were there it's unclear yeah so so the thing I kept
finding is it's unclear exactly what the system is for like because there are
tiers now to club 33 membership as well okay for different lounges and it's or
it's unclear now exactly what level because I think there's only the top
tier gets you into the lounge in general I could I can be completely wrong about
this somebody easily can correct me I'm sure but it seems like access to which
we did go to later do we even talk about Club 1901 we probably have to right yeah
yeah sure but there's a club in California Adventure that is a lot
smaller and I think that is like supposedly you have to be top tier access
in Club 33 to do that and I think also lounge access as something like I think
there might be like a base level Club 33 that you can just go to the dinner and
lunch in the regular dining room it's unclear though is what I'm saying there's
a lot of missfully there's a lot of misinformation online there's like old
I think stuff a lot of stuff has changed the membership fees they list are all
over the map we should have called oh and I tried to figure out that number is
not public oh right we would have had to acquire it some oh there's an official
website for Club 33 but it says nothing you can't you write sign in as a member
right there's no FAQ where it tells you how much it costs like some Hollywood
agencies or production companies that essentially just they have a website
because they have to but it is just essentially a business card yeah yeah
pro website right yesterday Scott we were talking about this and we'll we'll
probably do this at wrap-up but now that I'm thinking about it remind like we
were saying like what our dream version of Club 33 would be like what we would
pay for and I've just I'm just now realizing I know the perfect thing so
let's remember to do this
we'll hold on to that at the end
where are we saying that?
misinformation about
you know what I keep finding is that when I tell people we got to do this I say oh we went to the
California Adventure one too they don't know 1901 I think people know yes and so
if you're so next time you're if you're at Disneyland you're waiting in line for
the Carthay Circle restaurant off to the right there is a sign says 1901 it's
sort of hidden and you have to put your card up and then the 1901 lights up oh it
lights up yeah fast pass but oh that's so it's like you know what is hiding in
plain sight too because if you stand under the marquee of Carthay Circle
straight ahead is the lobby for the restaurant slightly to the right is
direct entry into the bar I think and then next to that is the 1901 door yeah
and I didn't I I've heard of somebody told a couple years ago it was like
there's one in Carthay and I was like what are you talking about and then it
was confirmed that it exists I still did not know where the door was and we've
waited in line for Carthay a million times it's right next to the door yeah
we've we've been in there before I just was like all these two doors that don't
go anywhere but they go to 1901 it's like the it's like the Buzz Lightyear
astro blaster target in the hallway it seems to be the same technology where
it's like dark and then you shoot it and it kind of lights up in a little like
D way that's what it looked like to me when you like they put his card to the
1901 sign and it lit up as 1901 anyway to that and there should be a secret
target that you can hit in Buzz Lightyear that gets you lifetime oh yeah sure
Club 33 I feel would be a lot more incentivized to I don't know why they
need people to be incentivized but right I knew about the 1901 lounge but I
thought it was upstairs like cuz there's that patio that's what I thought too yes
I'm like wait how can I sit on that patio so I guess it's just outdoor seating
you know you can set up there for regular and Karthik yeah I've sat on
that patio before a car thing but I I thought it was upstairs somewhere they're
just like a magical upstairs place that I didn't think like I didn't know or it
was like I didn't think it was in like the tower and the tower whatever you
would call it's not a cloud that's a little private bar all the way up in the
That would be great. Yeah yeah yeah. That would be fantastic. Well here let's go back.
Let's stick with Club 33. Okay well you want to talk food and such? Yeah because I also when you
talk about remodels and stuff that have happened there apparently was a room
called the trophy room that is not there anymore which I guess I recall now when
I was there five years ago I do have a picture there and it's a very like it's
product of its time so it's definitely what fancy people thought was like a
novel back in the 60s yeah yeah it is filled with I think Walt's original idea
was to have it filled with animatronic animals oh that didn't really happen but
we'll talk about the fanciest Chuck E. Cheese in the world yeah there are a lot
of mounted and stuff like game wild game animals yeah were there and then a lot
of photos and memorabilia including signed a signed fest part rifle signed by
fest Parker Davy Crockett and then a bottle of fest Parker wine signed by fest
Parker oh sweet I love the fest Parker wine that's cool yeah but so so my my
my cocktail it was a was called the trophy room cocktail as a tribute to the
what used to be there and apparently I was looking for something that like I
bartender at Le Salon Nouveau it was in the section Le Salon Nouveau originals
bourbon cognac maraschino, Cynar, whatever that is and bitters one of the best
drinks I've ever had insane so one of and like and high high content like
really good like the the thinnest drink there's like very little liquid in
there but man potent I was sailing it was great one of the best cocktails I've ever had
high marks for that I took picture because the drink menus were were
dressed up like you know old books yeah and then I was like oh that's a fun
container and then inside I'm like this is almost a novella length like there
were so many pages of drinks of like yeah the classic cocktails that are are
hard to find like you can they had a Vesper which is the drink James Bond
woulders in Casino Royale named after Vesper and it oh I I wanted to order it
and then I'm like no I will be under the tape because it's only vodka gin and
lilette which is I looked up or I asked someone and they're like oh it's a
fortified wine you would have been in the bathroom constantly for sure yeah as
it stands I forget the name I took pictures of the drink menus I did not
take a picture of the page the drink I ordered there's a picture I was like I
found a picture online it was called like a ship of the sea or something it
was called something was nautical both yeah you both laughed when I ordered it
oh really it's mostly it was rye and cherry bitters and something else
served up I think I just now I might I just have a base of enjoying listening
to you order in the wake of when we went to this City Walk Hotel or the
Universal Hotel and hearing you proudly say an apple strudel please it was done
with such gusto I feel like any probably just some boring drink item I would
enjoy hearing you order at this point yeah well look I know if I'm ordering
something a little sale with like a silly Dave or something I think you
are barely alcohol content you're gonna get at Club 33 can you make a
transformer I ordered their version of the transformer I think right well I
honestly I don't have like great photos of it I ordered the hurricane though I
think yeah you order the classic hurricane the paddle the original the
hurricane invented at Pat O'Brien's in New Orleans the drink and this was like
I didn't know the history version the original made with fresh fruit juices
and stuff nowadays I think people think oh a hurricane that's like syrup and
tea serve yeah I'm gonna get fucked up that looked very good although they
brought you a different drink yes I got double drinks you got double drinks and
they're like oh sorry we must have some wires got crossed just keep that one
we'll get your hurts you would do was the other one I'm trying to remember it
was kind of like a why it almost tastes like kind of a wine spritzer or something
it was very good it was like kind of like a subtly wine type of taste but I
don't remember the name of it did anyone just to refresh my memory did anybody
get the Louie the 13th rare cask cognac for $1,500 per one ounce serving I
stared at the cognac like locked cabinet uh-huh because those prices were truly
fascinating to like I didn't if I were sheer got eight of those right yeah and
had to be we had to call him a cab to get him home sure sure in a torius mess
yeah yeah yeah yeah and loves to spend money like loves him like loves a
$10,000 drink yeah he's like yeah this is this is nothing to me and then he
shoved all of us in the face I he's a monster usually has like a coke bottle
that he dumps the soda out of and pours crown into and he's like this is my fast
pass he kept saying this is my fast pass of course this is silly but we I get we
could probably say because he was Steve's you know joking around to everyone
with it that like he we stayed pretty late at the park and he's like I have to
she was working yeah she was shooting great of course well the fact that I had
forgotten that that she is in the cast of grace and Frankie as Jane Fonda's
daughter yeah which is a very fun so yeah impressive body of work June was oh
my god June was with Jane Fonda and sure was with Jason and Mike and Scott the
so all right so we're all we're all wasted on cognac we also ordered when
they asked if we wanted second like you and I both ordered beers like club 33
exclusive beer like I had a porter mm-hmm that they they explained they're
like oh this was made just for us it was aged in bourbon barrels that at one
point were used to make bourbon just for us oh cool and yeah sir they're like
it's a very small portion because it is potent and it was good it was like a very
I don't order dark beers a lot but I was very interesting like to have yeah this
beer there was another beer there was like a blonde ale made just for them
they're like we're out of that and oh I would have really enjoyed that I got
something that was well first but first I got a like giant goblet of wine that
was a Kurt Russell wine yeah so I'm drinking a Goldie that was that was a
blast and then I threw a beer on top of it and like walking up and we'd already
the meal had closed out and walking up to the bar and like paying for paying
for a big nice beer at the club 33 bar felt super cool and then we that post
our meal like we went outside to the veranda and said and like stood out
there I forget if you guys had drinks or not but I didn't we didn't you know but
then I like sipping a beer on a porch Disneyland incredible I do not take this
for granted that was super cool I felt just so like relaxed and posted the
picture yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah there's a little hint of where we were pretty
quickly caught on yeah yeah yeah it was there was so crowded too it truly felt
like you were we were king like kings ha ha ha we are here and quite like nice
air-conditioned we have a room to ourselves and I'll look at all of you
it's 85 degrees out and you can't move anywhere I am drinking a beverage that
you couldn't have in this park right tried until I until you've journeyed to
2019 until the evil Lucasfilm Empire yes sullies the park forever with the
novelty blue cocktail until Dexter Jekster serves you an alcoholic milkshake
at his diner well well we finally like as a return to form in tribute to the
old tobaccoist will will you be able to get deaths or death sticks were you
about to call him cancer sticks I was gonna call the cancer stuff fucked it up
I knew it was death yeah death sticks is the name for cigarettes and the prequels
oh that's really I have cigarettes and they call them death sticks Kenobi like
you know takes a trip to flavor country and one shot at Dexter Jeksters huh I
would just I would love that if they had a there's no way they're selling that
sticks at Galaxy's Edge vapes back in Galaxy's Edge there's no way I think
it's a good idea love Jules is the thing I've learned that's another cool
youngster thing you got me I don't know about jewel yeah by the federal
government or the New York State oh my god very cool movie past jewel all the
great companies currently under all the best all the best companies were founded
after 2012 all the coolest least corrupt most progressive CEOs hey I'm still
holding on to my Theranos that stock what's there I know there knows was the
blood testing startup that turned out to be a massive scam oh my god yeah and
this is very odd woman Elizabeth is Elizabeth Holmes I think like trying to
jobs and like it took a few years but there is a book out about it called bad
blood that they has been exited cheese cool and it's it's like a page turning
read like I've only read parts of the but it's like wow what a con like music
music man level con there's pictures of like Joe Biden touring this place of
like this is gonna revolutionize blood testing and they're gonna partner with
and it all just turned out wow I've never heard about any of this oh I can't
I can't wait for wait what's the name of the company Theranos there in us there
so this do we think Theranos has a corporate membership to club 33 or
juice oh yeah for sure crazy juice one where you could you could just squeeze
the packages yourself if not use the $400 $500 pressing machine it's a
you're paying for like a little prick the bag yeah you're paying for a
glorified sewing needle insane so it's really what you know in this situation
we are we are living like like CEOs essentially because like I don't think I
and looking into the history a little I didn't realize that a lot of the
memberships and the initial impetus for starting this place was it was to
entertain clients and sponsors right of Disneyland and that's a lot of the
memberships are like interchangeable like that company can send somebody to
I don't know what the companies are necessarily it's not public oh yeah I
guess I guess it wouldn't be but that's part but part of the the rumor about the
name is that 30 33 potentially was the number of sponsors at the time oh right
also but also 33 well people have said it's somewhere it's like mouse ears
turned on its side I think it's the address of the club is 33 Royal Street
yes but in terms of New Orleans Square storyline and might also be the address
on the liquor license yo and that's part of it's probably the literal need for a
an address was speed needed a separate address from Disneyland yeah but there's
also do you guys catch the crazy rumor but what club 33 refers to I don't know
like though that's how the Satanists greet each other it's you're not you're
not far off people think that Disney himself was a a 33rd degree Freemason oh
that's a level of Freemasonry that you can climb to and it's a it's a nod to
that and people have tried to pick apart like designs on the floor like this
spiral or whatever clearly is a reference to the to the Freemasons
that's like so I know like Denver Airport shit that's Denver Airport thing
oh the Denver Airport people like it is it's apparently a very odd architectural
creation and there's a lot of weird art and and people if I talked about this on
the show I feel like I've talked about this before but there's like art that
people are like no this is this is to summon the demon mullock and this is
like there's illuminati messages or Satanist messages which I think the
airport is now being refurbished and the Denver Airport is like having fun with
the urban legends and stuff like you know they should have find out what
secrets will be revealed yeah they're playing with it because it's now it's
just so old and such a thing it's a the mode it's a haunted Auntie Anne's yeah
it may also be a people mover that might be one of the few existing I believe
Houston had a Houston Airport has a people like a Disney a wed way people
yes I don't know about other words there's other other places have like
similar implements right I think theirs is an official Disney made anyway
I don't know that is bizarre that that's a 33 does have Freemason right
significance should I join the Freemasons sure how easy is it Evans I
don't know how much does that cost we talked about joining the Elks Lodge
yeah we should join the Elks Lodge like a like rotor rotary yeah and just hear
old men tell stories well I think that's what you go do this and oh shrimp boils
shrimp oils and like this I didn't realize that was part of it yeah there's
all kinds of cool clubs we could join in fact I was gonna propose to you guys
should should we like maybe the prep the perfect use of the patreon funds is to
just start a corporate membership for the three of the podcast the ride
corporate membership club 33 just all it all goes right to that I don't know you
know I know it's a great write-off we can entertain podcasts the important
podcast the right clients and guests you know like our girlfriends and wives I
think it's a good could be crucial to keeping up the relationships I don't
look I like what you're saying I think that it makes a lot of sense I think
maybe we start with Florida because it's cheaper I think initiation fee wise
all right okay I think there's one in each park and there's one in each park
new pretty new and the last very new yeah I think maybe they all are not even
open yet but I think it's they announced pricing for them so that's official and
I think they're like 25,000 to get in and then like 10,000 upkeep because I
think Disneyland if we want to do the good stuff it's a hundred grand now to
get in so maybe we start with Florida just because it's cheaper mm-hmm and then we
can entertain clients and it makes a lot of sense to have a membership to an
insanely expensive private club in your state across the country I think that's
right if we can get like some real Chappo Trap house fuck you patriot money
I think that's fair that if we start making that level of money sure yeah we
can do something dumb that it actually that it actually might behoove us that
it might be all right off if we make if you want to look up Chappo I forget how
much money they're making if we can make that amount of money we will send Jason
to Florida permanently and he will be a permanent on-the-ground cub reporter for
Florida so we can be bi-coastally represented he's looking to the sky and
he doesn't he's not upset about it well cuz I feel like last I saw they were
like a hundred thousand yes so now so now what we're asking people to do it's
not like okay help us out a little and then we can give you some fun bonus
episode we're relocating one of the hosts and I like to you know what I think
the issue would be if we were always Skyping with Jason they'd be it'd feel a
little impersonal and you wouldn't feel the dynamic presence of Jason in the room
T1 line it's a paper like t3 or or yeah well that could be a help in what I'm
proposing which is what maybe one better which is that way and an animatronic
Jason that he is operating like an avatar remotely yeah up to all of the
wires and the sensors like the guy programming the carousel of progress guy
so you what we need now we room and board for you in Florida and like phone
robot mechanism so that there can be a robot Jason here at all yeah here's what
we need we need three months of the El Chapo trap house patreon first month
hundred grand we can get you a house in Orlando for a hundred grand I was kind
of hoping for like whatever the highest suite at the boardwalk hotel you want
to live like telly at the boardwalk telly is probably healthier sloppy telly
tissue boxes on my feet as shoes that's gonna be a lot more expensive
unfortunately so maybe you're probably right so we're gonna have to up well
clearly all right latitude Margaritaville latitude Margaret that's
what I think we can do that I think that's two months worth of El Chapo
trap house we were looking at no no I screwed up yeah I can't screw it up
what's the highest level of patron and I think okay it's 33 grand a month which
gives you the satisfaction of knowing that your favorite host Jason has put up
in the nicest room and board possible we can get your family down there too like
telly yeah sure what would it be if we didn't move your parents also yeah I
think that's a great idea and then yeah paintings you need better but you need
to redecorate the suite also yeah oh 100% yeah this is a single visit to Club 33
has I'll put it on my so it's gone to my head I'm dreaming lavish tree yeah
I can't go back to coach because I've been in first class we're looted we're
mad mad now yeah I know we lost our minds yeah these new microphone stands
have really changed at Club 33 in these new microphone stands they've freed us
yes yeah expense number one microphone stands so you don't hear our wires
rustling around to relocation of a host in a robot in his place reasonable just
know that the page the patreon donations are going to real things that
we really yeah well so the food the food yeah so we order I had a cheeseburger I
had the cheeseburger so good it might be one of the best if you really cheeseburger I
it was yeah at least top two or three I don't even have the other examples of
what though are in the top three but I was like whoa this is legit awesome hmm
yeah and the fries were good very good but not like at the level of the
okay the cheeseburger had like bacon jam and it was a fancy cheeseburger
cheese they told us like just so you know the patty is made with the
trimmings of our sir Lloyd's and fillet so it is essentially a real right yes
exactly oh my god and that's like a rugel on it yeah and yeah like some what
was the cheese did you say that I had never it was it was similar to a brie
or like a goat cheese or something Andrews or post it I have a picture of
this yeah picture it was cheese squeezed out of the Big Thunder Mountain go they
had actually it produces cheese only for club 33 members and they were very
using robot I asked like oh do you because I was like oh the steak frites
are the burger and they're like the steak frites are steak frites but the
burger is very special yeah she pushed the burger and I choose right to do it
Andre cheese sauce Bernays tomato it's kind of like a tomato relish or
something and it cost $33 which I thought was very cute very cute yes very
charming I had a fancy fish thing that was great I don't remember a lot of
details about it but I love you know Carthay Circle makes really good fish
any whatever their catch of the day is always great oh yeah you had the catch
of the day and I remember it was served in lobster bisque cheese yes and they
caught it I would have like I think was lobster sausage yes or people like did
we are we do we sound horrible yeah it is a disgusting episode yeah and then we
then it was the most perfect sauce I'd ever have usually when I go to the park
like I stop at a grocery store to buy a bottle of water at a cliff bar ahead of
time so I don't have to yeah and I've like money there and I figured out all
the locations of the free water so that I don't have to buy a sunny
constantly yeah this is how it usually works this was a treat and we really
appreciate it and it was great we're not becoming monsters here's the test of
how when you will here's when we will become monsters is when you catch wind
that we go a lot and we don't talk about it that is when we truly will become
monsters because you will not hear about it we will keep our monster
monsters in his private right now we're just humble nice guys that are very
excited to go to a fancy place that we've dreamed about going yeah when
people on the social media are like hey I was in the park and I walked up to
what I thought was one of them and I said hey are you from podcast a ride and
and they wrote they replied no wouldn't make eye contact and walk away they
wish I used to be now I'm better they somebody walked under us while we were
on the balcony of Club 33 and they said podcast the ride guys save us and the
podcast the ride guys turned and said no hard rain hard rain hard rain fell on
New Orleans our rain of four dollar to Saudi water a school fall we know that
Club 33 is equipped with ropes you could pull us up to the balcony no drown
we're up here there's a reason we're up here I cheeseburger was great yeah so
so good I had so much catch of the day here's another weird Jason moment
because they said like oh it either comes like on a bed of a lobster bisque
or a bed of oyster stew and you heard it out you got excited to go to sleep I did
well I know what but I kind of cut in and I was like can I ask is it a
traditional oyster stew because traditional oyster stew is is you can
it in some set places in South Jersey it's mostly cream and some light spices
and fresh oysters it's pretty simple it's not the most robust flavor that's
a very acquired taste mm-hmm and it's very creamy and I they're like yes it's
prepared the traditional way and I was like yeah maybe get the bisque you did
help me out you gave me good tips and and the bend the wages was super helpful
and like recommended pretty like talked me through so much stuff it was it was
oh it was wonderful it was a wonderful like perfectly catered experience while
we listened to wonderful stories from our from our friends and guests and yeah
it was great time so also what another thing that happened is that Jason
celebrates his birthday like kind of for a month straight so like he had a
four days after my birthday but you are a birthday guy who loves to stretch it out
sign up for all these email programs that restaurants and stores have right
they've gotten pretty good they've gotten good this year I was very happy
because a lot of them were like this is good for the entirety of your birthday
but so I've not bought a lot of groceries no I know cuz you you are I
mean look I'm a guy who likes checking I'm a guy who likes deals I like to
promotions like just locked down I've never seen someone do it so much you'd
be like I have 12 free birthday lunches coming from various restaurants like you
have got it down I had a free pastry for breakfast for Panera on the drive down
yeah right I remember that and then you oh yeah because you were like hey do
you want this thing and you first you acted like you had just bought it for me
but then you know I asked if you wanted something and you say just get me what you get and I got a
you revealed it to me later as if like well I just in full disclosure I got it
for free you did say like you did I thought that was funny because like the
doughnuts they're just like no I just take it right which is another time when
you came over with doughnuts and you and the employee told you just take it we're
closing soon and I said it's like six o'clock they're not closing soon and
you're like I don't know right what do you mean all right that's that's I'm not
insulting you that's just what happened
yeah I know anyway sitting back and watching this is something the first no
no no scolds okay so this is so dessert related context for this all I was just
doing was goofing on you for celebrating your birthday for weeks I
wasn't goofing on you for getting those three donuts okay so you asked for the
button up for these look I got a free butter cake to go from California Pizza
Kitchen one day I was coming home from something I'm like oh I got a free
dessert and the fine print says you could do it for takeout so I sure walked
in and walked out with a piece of cake to eat it I believe I think that you have
some I think you have different drivers licenses every state in the country and
you do it do you do a birthday tour you it's a different birthday every three
weeks that is a great scam because you've worked out a string of CPKs and
Jersey mics yeah he's thinking about it also you should have bought went before
the upstar crow stopped selling those life fake licenses you should have just
bought those oh yeah it was right it's yeah it's apartments this I believe
there's you were born on John Lennon's death day it's a free egg roll you're
John Lennon you're oh you are John here you you want your free birthday scoop
but it says under restrictions diabetes I don't know if the good conscience I
there is a novelty drivers license the word that said Halle Berry's as it
mentioned that she has diabetes which is a fact that I didn't know and really
yeah I didn't know back to the city walk so basically so it does it can they
brought us dessert menu yeah well hold on going back a little bit one of my
favorite things is to go with you in the week surrounding your birthday because
you insist on the birthday button which is something I've never gotten it's like
too much attention for me for whatever reason but you get it and it's great
because everyone wishes you happy birthday yeah and sometimes you get
little and sometimes you get little treats which I guess honestly makes you
smarter than me because I should have to just do that every year one of my
favorite times we were walking down by the Grizzly challenge trail and a man
was playing like nice soft acoustic guitar and he's like happy birthday Jason
like I was like fantastic this is wonderful so we walked in and you got
asked for the birthday button and they say happy birthday so because you were
wearing that in club 33 they brought you a special dessert and you because no one
ordered dessert we got dessert menus and I'm like oh Valhura chocolate
absolutely chocolate mousse tart 100% but everyone else was like nah I don't
think they have a dessert and like your heart saint we heard it yeah and I
guess I could have pushed but I was also a little groggy from that burger was
really a lot yeah it was a lot the drinks for a lot so well the thing you
take me better for my body if I hadn't had full-size dessert I think the thing
is you take your cues from people who have taken you somewhere that's probably
if everyone had had a dirt road yeah so that's the only reason I would have
indulged with you that's all I'm just making an excuse yeah but they brought
me a very charming little dish of strawberry ice cream and a little Mickey
house butter cookie and it was delight it was actually worked out great was the
perfect amount of like sweet to have great yeah I know seeing you with a
little Mickey cookie on a plate on a oh yeah plate that was that was I have a
video of singing happy birthday to you oh that's nice so we can post that yeah
and they went you know this is the cookie you can get in the park it's just
a little bigger yeah that's what they hell yeah sure yeah right to your head
so that was fun again yeah usually I'm there like I'm walking in at the park
going like okay yeah this is my birthday child get the birthday button and then
maybe that'll get I can save some money on that this is that's the normal the
normal hustle to like you save money the day it actually is something we haven't
talked about off air or anything what is your I don't get let's all just try to
eliminate because we're talking a lot but like what is the birthday path you
take like what is the what are the places you have to hit when you have that
birthday button to try it yeah Disney I don't know I we're joking about but I
feel like I forget about it pretty quickly uh-huh there's not a specific
place you go oh you're like they're gonna give me a little this I didn't
have this on but when my family was last visiting we were eating at Napa Rose and
both it was like the week of it was right around both my dad's birthday and
and the person I was dating at the time's birthday and so I like snuck away
to the to our waiters to grab our waiter and like hey we have two birthdays and
and he's like oh okay I'll take care of it and so like after the meal they came
oh he's like I hear there's some we're celebrating some instances so what would
like for your your birthday desserts so he it wasn't like oh here's the little
birthday cupcake we have he brought the full dessert menu and whatever you two
oh wow he did once and then he looked at my brother and I were also there he's
like yeah you guys can order birthday dessert you can get this so like you
know that's like a few $40 $50 free thing at Napa Rose I will say this if
you haven't been to Napa Rose the level of service there is is very is pretty
close to Club 30 like they really take care of you there too I had a guy who
you know once I read an article that was of somebody who was I think
disappointed by the Club 33 experience or not maybe no it just like didn't
think it was like the greatest thing they'd ever they'd ever done even at a
Disney park particularly in terms of food quality and they argued that
Carthay and Napa Rose are both superior just pure food wise which is interesting
because Andrew Sutton the executive chef of Napa Rose was poached or shifted
over to be the newer executive chef of Club 33 oh interesting I didn't know
that huh this was an older article too so maybe that maybe the quality has
improved because of him so that makes sense but that's that's something I
don't feel like they will be lucky enough to get to go to Club 33 I had a
great time it was wonderful I don't this was not like some like earth
shatteringly incredible experience and you know that nor was the the food
exactly that's just the one thing I would say is like you know if you're
looking for top-tier nice Disney experiences Carthay and Napa Rose are
great and like super comparable mm-hmm to this I say just to like if you're
feeling like oh whoa is me I will never get to enter the Xanadu of Club 33
there's great those those places are like you know yeah right it right in
line yeah I mean your steakhouse 55 at the Disneyland Hotel supposed to be
pretty nice to I've never done I would like to do yeah I had a cheeseburger at
the bar once and it was very good I can't remember it was yeah I like that
bar it's a great chill option if Trader Sam's is just oh yeah going back to the
bottom of Trader Sam's is just out of oh yeah I mean like always yeah all the
time yeah well I don't know where what haven't we done we do well we mean we
Intermeal enjoyed enjoyed a truly relaxing beer on the verandah Club 33
where I forget if I said this on the podcast but I told it to you guys and
then the crafts how that in the previous time that I was a Club 33 that I had my
we got there before our before David Melissa who let us in and and we like
watched phantasmac finish out on that porch and I was like I had the ring I've
been like looking for the opportunity to pop the question to Aaron almost did it
there I was gripping it like is that this is pretty cool we're in this like
exclusive zone maybe maybe I do it and then I was like yeah but then we're like
the dinner will be so distracted by that like it'll be hey thanks for letting
us into this nice place anyway we just got engaged and that's more important
than I didn't want to end up in that scenario yeah
Disney Parks blog is here they wanted to write a nice little post about the
engagement yeah yeah Kayla cameras are on us now I don't but I don't but I was
very sad I that's another I've now I've between having a beer up there with y'all
and gripping my my wedding ring and thinking about popping the question five
years prior nice memories on that up on that porch and there's many memories that
come in Florida when we're constantly at Club 33 in all four parks when we shift
our operations on the coast yeah we could do a little Club 1901 well I mean I
think to to wrap up officially Club 33 oh it's a Disney attraction without the
gift shop yeah so so we walk out into the lobby and there's a big glass case
and I think I said I was like oh my god I didn't realize there'd be merch yeah
yeah there was some exclusive shag prints I think there was a print there
was a paint a shag piece in the lounge yeah made for the lounge mm-hmm and
there's a lot of like what they're like wine glasses with 33 the logo on it and
like polo shirts and a lot of golf stuff. That was the one thing. It's really saying like you know we know you're a rich guy you buy some of this golf crap.
That was what I found like I like a baseball cap that's like a little
distressed or a little you know a little beat up and it was very like the one
baseball cap they had was like had a lot of those like ventilation hole like it
was very like glossy and it's like yeah this is for golf people yes right for
the rich yeah so I immediately my eyes fixed I was like where the character I'm
looking for like anytime I'm there's merch I'm looking for the character and
he's sitting up here now on the mantle and I'm still not sure if we're gonna
take take him out of the box we could probably will take him out of the box
because he needs to have like a stand like he was in the box yeah that's a
nice box it's a nice box but also like if you go up it kind of looks cheap to
me if you really look at the box well it's got a vintage aesthetic too I think
that yeah I'm torn about it so so anyway they have like a very old looking
distressed Donald Duck not that distressed but he's like his color
palette looks like it's a classic Donald stuffed plush and I was like oh I'm gonna
guy was like probably making a noise on his little foot and on his little foot
is a 33 the logo is on his little foot and this poking it's I'll post a picture
of it online 33 owns him like Andy owns would exactly yes so this is the Donald
for the rich this is rich persons Donald from the 50s I was like having I was
like I don't need glass with stuff and and I turned around and I was like oh
there's a second display case and I'm like there's a keychain and I I love
like good quality part keychain like that is usually my little you know I buy
t-shirts I have a Disney World hat but I don't buy a ton of stuff at the park
I'm pretty picky about what I buy at the park but I like to have a little fun
theme park keychain especially just if you're like doing errands or stuff for
your like like going through the day it's like oh there's a little bit of
parks to cheer you up if you're in a bad mood or something mm-hmm so I've had a
Ministry of Magic keychain which I like Harry Potter I like Harry Potter fine
but mostly I bought it because I'm like I like the park specific like that this
was like hmm a lot of the Universal Harry Potter stuff is very good quality
very detailed and that's kind of why I bought it and now right walk it out for
a little while for this Club 33 keychain nice little blue in the logo I'll take a
picture of it me I haven't swapped it out yet it's still in the nice little bag
Oh really you haven't done it?
No, they gave me this cute this very charming Club 33 bag
hmm right that's Scott you almost weren't you like looking at the wine
glasses you were thinking about it yeah then maybe I didn't have done it
there did there needed to be more characters I think in the merch it's a
lot of like clothes and like let's wear the action figures right like oh you're
Club 33 specific action figures I want to see formerly poor characters hmm like
the Cinderella mice oh yeah that'd be great fancy and snooty yeah like holding
Club 33 scepters yeah there should be like a toy where like Belle goes through
the doors of Club 33 and comes out with the dress on the big yellow dress
the characters in Disney who become rich there should be some sort of diorama
that that happens I know a lot of the design inspiration you know they talk
when they were redoing it they talked about taking cues from Princess and the
Frog a lot oh cuz that's in New Orleans and you could also because there's a lot
there was a jazz festival coming off in the club oh so you could have a toys of
the aristocats in tuxedos oh but they're fancier yeah they're not street riff
riff yeah they got a great gig that's fine they're like set for the year from
this corporate gig there and they're playing way it's not like fun 40s scat
jazz it's like very syrupy corporate you know acoustic guitar right yeah it's
yeah they're playing bony James type jazz adult contemporary you talk about
the design of the place I want to hit the before before we move on I want to
hit the the the two people primarily responsible for how it looks around
there and I think other areas of New Orleans Square because if you walk around
the rest of New Orleans Square it's the same level of ornate and detailed and
feels very authentically New Orleans and the it was based on the club is based on
sketches commissioned from by Walt from Dorothea Redmond Dorothea Redmond was
is considered the first female production designer in Hollywood history
worked on Gone with the Wind worked worked extensively with Hitchcock was
the production designer of rear window and Rebecca Wow I didn't know that yeah
so she did sketches that like set the tone for like what you know Hitchcock
showed to his DP and whatever on those on those films I think she did six seven
films with the Hitchcock all told she designed the private room above Pirates
of the Caribbean that Walt was going to move into which all right that never
happened but they did turn it into the Disney Gallery did you guys ever get to
the Disney I love that Disney Gallery yeah yeah that was really really nice a
Tony Baxter installation in the late 80s at Disneyland and now it is now it's
enclosed again and it is the Disneyland Dream Suite the private now it's not
the dream it's a private dining room now private above Pirates yeah yeah that you
can get for like 15 grand something crazy yeah like if you pooled 15 people
together and they each had a few hundred dollars for a meal like it is it is the
next it is it might be one level up from Club 33 because it's such an ordeal
that's insanity yes I'm incredibly please you can stay anymore I don't
believe so oh interesting okay very right yeah she's amazing her body of
work she also apparently helped design the space needle in Seattle well they
lived till 98 what a badass amazing body and then the actual the actual
interior was designed by the set designer Emile Curie who did production
design for 20,000 Leagues Mary Poppins it's a wonderful life and Hitchcock's
rope man so the level of I think that that really adds to the the authenticity
it's not like some fake fancy experience right like the you're like the the best
Hitchcock people were creating this environment so so cool and I you know I
honestly didn't realize till we were there and I asked the waitress about
this that that Walt's I didn't realize he did not set foot in the place it was
a year or 67 yeah year after he died so this thing designed his specifications
like a perfect place for him and he never got to go but we did so yeah that is
she mentioned and we think we looked at on the way out he used to be in the
trophy room there was a turkey vulture oh and the there was a room set aside
for an actor to be in with a microphone and there were microphones scattered
through out the trophy room with the idea being the vulture would converse
with the guests now that never came to pass and the additional animatronics
never came to pass but when they redid it they mounted this turkey vulture in
the lobby of Club 33 and now he does like wake up and talk every now and yeah
we did get to see him talk and what did he say do you remember it was really
brief yeah he say hello or like good afternoon right and then we like rant
we were like oh hey and then like we stayed for like a minute and we're like
oh that's it huh nothing more happened but that like I'm three drinks in of
like three of the finest drinks I've ever had like great beer great line great
cocktail and then I'm talking to a vulture it this was a perfect little
zone of time just wonderful but I will say I will duck Alfred the vulture points
in that I do he is not well here my personal animatronic of the month this
was not my animatronic highlight it but that instead would have to be as we
talked about before we went on the knots log ride and the bear turned to us and
said trick-or-treat sure that was cooler I have to say then then the vulture sure
so you know this premium robot experiences a lot of other places but
to use the new mobile ordering system yeah I ran over to his side of the table
and I was showing him how to order a dole whip that's true yeah I was
watching Mike in heaven like showing teaching yeah one how to check I was
trying yeah I was trying to teach Scott that when we were there later and he was
like I said I don't care I'm getting in the regular line and I was like I don't
know and then to prove a point I mobile ordered I mean it wasn't really to prove
a point I was just trying to use this system because I like using it and then
we got like our food at the same time but I got to sit down the whole time
instead of standing in line you got to turn to me and give a little look like
hmm see self-satisfied yep no blurring so I don't know self figure it out but
at the mo we're like on the way over like we're almost there like next to the
thing but it's fun as we'll and it's fun to mobile order but we get over to
California venture head and scan the secret thing to get into 1901 I had
also got into that thanks to my friend David and the like I was I was so
excited we get to go in there again because if you've been in the car they
circle bar imagine getting a zone like that but to yourself and I by that point
I do stop dry like I must begin to sober up for him in trouble but I was so glad
that you Mike ordered a drink that came with an orb ice cube well it's yes like
so they have the same drink menu as the car they launch which we've been to
oh what not hungry like exclusive yeah right they had a couple of things but
like I don't know if any of us ordered because we were also just like well yeah
so what so I was asking because my favorite drink at the car they lounge is
a car they Manhattan which has a beautiful circular orb of ice and I
don't know what did Richard say like they have the ice they'll show you how
to like they'll make the ice for you uh-huh which we had not experienced at
the lounge so I was asking away I was like do you make the ice at the bar or
could you make he goes we can do it over here if you want I go well we got to do
it so he brought the ice or making machine over to us and we got to see a
circular perfect sphere of ice be made in front of us that they take a big cube
right and using this gravity press machine it becomes a perfect sphere like
like technology that's probably hasn't changed since the 30s yeah and it just
slowly crushes it into an orb crazy bartending like the or I love this so
much I would watch that I wish I would I'd pay an extra ten dollars at that
lounge oh yeah the orb show that was that's how they made the orb that Trump
at the Saudi Arabia leaders that was that insane anti-terrorism center they
all realize the orb that was an ice orb too it was it was a cube first and then
they said but only he who is pure of hearts can turn it into an orb and Trump
of course the purest of heart and it became the most beautiful orb you've
ever seen he's been doing great lately really killing it 1901 I mean 1901
probably again we'll have to do a full episode on it but you know do we not
everything has to be a full episode hey we got a patreon we got a fill of a
patreon here is a cool what do you what sports cool lounge this cool photos like
the effects that drinks great snacks I'm done well the effects that weren't
working which there was that thing that looks there's tooth I think two of them
oh we saw the one we saw the one they said look at this it's the worst
animation you've ever seen oh it's it was a picture I think of Walt who were
one of the other artists yeah sort of then the arm started to move and draw a
character but it moved it like that wasn't jab.com yeah that wasn't great but
there were two effects not working which they have wallpaper that look just looks
like wallpaper but then once in a while there's like in a silhouette of Walt's
that appears in like the wallpaper because 1901 lounge is named after the
year he was born right so it's very it's a very cool effect supposedly that's
what everyone says but it was not working the whole thing is very like
there's a bar in there there's a lot of comfortable couches it feels very much
like someone's was the word rumpus room is that the term like oh it hasn't been
for many decades right but sure sure but you that is maybe what I would be
referring to is that what a rumpus room was or no I thought it had a lot a lot of
the study or a day bar but then a little bit of the sort of craftsman accents
what room in the house would this be do you know he like a den or something
room dad's room that's all my dad's dead yeah the dead or a rumpus room is you
know I was gonna say rumpus room is appropriate because it's John that
character that was created 70 years ago yeah and he makes a joke about it
yeah John aka Jason so it's great I mean that was yeah that was wonderful it was
a hell of a time great great stories from these folks this was this was just
blast yeah yeah really really cool to have experienced it but we were we were
talking about this last night that while it is a while it is a wonderful
experience we had a wonderful time and wonderful meal it is I would not say
that it is some mind-bending Lee incredible level of Disneyland access
it's not as if like it's all very cool but there's no like thing that you get
to do or thing that you get to I mean having a drink out on the porch is
great but like I'm just I think I think what we were talking about is is there
if you're gonna pay that amount of money thousands of dollars every year to be
part of this club what is the the exclusive only for you experience that
that the club 33 membership could provide yeah that would really
deeply be worth all that money right and I think last night my first thought was
if club 33 was in like the top of Space Mountain or something like if you if
there was a bar the top of space money you look out over Disneyland there was
like like something like that yeah like and everything was very very hyper
stylized Space Mountain motif inside and like yeah if you could just generally
like in the dark they don't really change anything but there's just like
there's hallways and stuff there's like it's like a secluded little like bar
zone that leads you I like I like what you're saying about at the top if there
was some vista within Space Mountain right and then probably where you like
really have your meal and hang is where the ships take off like where currently
the employees are checking on the the Rockets but get them out of there move
them somewhere I want to have a like a purple drink in there yeah that I mean
like a blue bayou Space Mountain but exclusive club 33 yeah I almost think
three people at a time I know that sure small so yeah let's not we're not filling
that up yeah I want my exclusive rocket vista I almost feel like blue bayou if
it was exclusive would be cooler mm-hmm than like if you could drink and blue
bayou mm-hmm that was your exclusive club that kind of is a more highly
themed experience but I like that it is open to everyone well of course I'm not
saying shut blue bayou none I'm just saying it's a more themed experience
that is true that is more yeah no I'm not saying the rich should only be able
to access blue bayou we're starting to siphon off we're separating the cars
every if there was a if there was a much fancier radiator Springs I want it like
a butt like a book like a private I want a Maserati that's alive who like you know
at the other cars and who all who wins every single time sure he'd like I don't
know what kind of crowd on if Maserati's electric or whatever but it should be
like super gas spewing right the people you should win against the other car
guaranteed and a bunch of such should blow in their faces sure salt entry
that's great yeah we got a I've got a add-on I've got a club 33 at oh go ahead
yes you are you are given a key card and you to for the two for use at the
Grand Californian and you check in at the front desk and they're like all right
your nap suite is available and you're gonna because I mean that was a heavy
heavy so it's like all right we will come and get you at the end of four
hours so you have an hour to settle down get comfortable and then a ideal I
suppose just under three hour nap because then you need to collect
yourself so maybe you you use that hour 30 minutes before 30 minutes after to
compose yourself you get a nice so now you're saying that then you come back to
life and maybe they bring you that nice water at the end and then you're like we
hope you enjoyed your stay so for 50 grand entrance and then like 10 to 25
thousand a year you would if you could take a three hour nap at this a three
hour nap in a really not and I feel like hourly hotels are you presented
usually for seedy affairs frowns upon okay that's not a bad idea to add my so
what the mind the thought I had during the show which I realized is is
basically that the all the touches of of imagineering and theming are awesome in
club 33 but it doesn't feel overwhelming which is sort of the feeling you want
like a blue bayou it's like you're in it you're in the bayou whereas like oh
those are awesome effects here and there but even like being in Trader Sam's to
me feels like a little bit more of an immersive themed experience maybe not a
little bit maybe a lot more so if it was like adventurers club 33 mmm and it was
like as themed as that mm-hmm I think you'd obviously I'd have to be doing a
cool with actors and like the effect which they never did but like you could
talk to a ghost while you eat at the bar like if it was like that hardcore level
theming I think at that point you're like me and I mean that's hundred
thousand dollars but yeah I mean if you could hundred thousand dollars if I was
a multi-millionaire I guess we're talking yeah there's no way if I like
make a hundred grand that's something you order and the puppet general presents
it to you the adventures club that drink that he would have which was just
a bottle of Beefeaters but with like seven straws taped together so we could
reach up to him that's fun so like something like that again if I was a
multi multi-millionaire I would say I do want to go to that club a lot like
cuz that would seem like it would be really worth it to keep going back I
mean I get also that it would be this whole thing would have been more
enticing back when you couldn't get liquor anywhere mm-hmm but now you can
drink every so I've said many times you can walk 500 feet and get a drink so
it's not a big deal and in highly themed great places yeah so yes you know like
the point of like even if I had some money I still think like you probably
would it doesn't make sense to pay for this unless it would they've turned it
into something insane like crazy well that's mine mine would be I mean it's
Kick em out oh yeah right I'm hanging in there now and that is a perfect
vantage point for the big monitors and I want to be able to put whatever I want
on that TV there's a game on I'm watching the game oh you love watching
the game you know me yeah get the game on the big game I want for using the
copyright free would term that we're allowed to use we can't even say the
initials of the football organization you all know the big game yeah so I
that's how Doritos frames it yeah but I want to be able to like imagine this you
can like that maybe I don't want to cut it off from the the regular or you know
a space crew it starts or closes at five o'clock every day it's a that's a
private dining room I sit up there see 3PO and R2D2 talk to me they ask how was
your meal sir well they should be the waitstaff R2 brings the stuff on his
tray like he does a job as Palace yeah see 3PO is though it does you take your
order and Rex is just like sloppy telly he's just it's his little comes out in a
bathrobe and he chats with you and he you know he's got thoughts on the game
cuz he's got money right he's got credits riding on it oh yeah yeah yeah
and I want to hear how everything's going with him and Roxanne I think
they're married and they're doing great and he is one of the top DJs in all of
space he's he's in I want to hear all the wonderful details of Rex's wonderful
life oh yeah he's making Steve Aoki like Vegas money now that's fuck you money
yeah he's smashing his head into synthetic cakes so all right that's my if
I could be I would pave to turn the Star Wars TV onto anything I want and to be
best friends with Rex and now I'm paying 100 grand now all right well
hundred grand for you to live in Star Tours hundred grand for me to have an
adventures club or a space mountain hundred grand for Jason to nap in a
theme park done everyone's on sort of game here I do have I only have one I
should get a new one the figured out years ago where Disney supplies sources
the pillows for the hotels for the night so it tells everybody for really like
50 bucks bucks on Amazon save that for the Disney pillow patreon episode you're
gonna lead the way on that one down is a pain in the ass to care care for though
you can machine wash it but then you really have to dry it because it's a
little wet hey save it for the episode save it for the pillow and we don't want
to give that away here also I think the top tier are another perk of the 33,000
the the the super patreon tier is to is to be able to watch Jason nap oh yeah a
live cam of you nap all right you can access dot com slash you can make more
like twitch you could like how you could sleep in pajamas that are branded so
you're like you're sponsored getting money from Hewlett Packard you're
like what is which is policy on like people sleeping Street or like ASMR
stuff good question like ooh no we know there's some weirdness attached to it or
they're like as long you don't do anything openly dirty you can do it hmm
now I gotta look into well look into it you're the hip young one who knows what
the hip apps and programs do and I yeah I know about jewels and corrupt Silicon
Valley disgraced Silicon Valley blood testing companies and we're not we're
not advertising blue chew yet on the main show oh you don't know about that
Jesus anyway penis thing oh like yeah you know we're doing ads for a penis
thing not yet no but a lot of podcasts these days are doing those oh really
yeah why are we getting that penis money the blue chew penis money let's happily
we'll ask forever dog although maybe we can negotiate that for just the patreon
episodes Jason can cut a deal with the blue chew people on the side for just
the patreon line of discussion at one of our business meet one of our
organizational meeting I want to find out what like the ball enlarging pills
we can get to sponsor the fun alright we got a show sponsored you by WWE's
crown jewel oh boy that will have happened by the time people yeah that's
true or not I know it'll happen but it will yeah all right we gotta go Jason to
Saudi Arabia yep if we get enough money in the patreon you know what I'll put
you in a box of mail you to Abu Dhabi that's the second time that's all right
well we're here we're looping so we should wrap it up you survived podcast
the ride the second gate hey thank you so much hope you're enjoying everything
so far a lot more fun coming our way coming you're coming your way email us
a podcast the right a gmail for more more stuff you want to hear or if you
feel free to do that just the subject line fancy Dave's gold and they all the
regular stuff thank you so much for your support it's been yeah it's very so
encouraging and knowing that the audience is back debated and into it and
in supportive we feel wonderful that so yeah thanks so much thank you all right
we'll see you next time