Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following episode is a street fight of polite but intense theme park conversation.
It's park versus park, Orlando, Florida versus all other cities and one company's vinyl collectibles
versus another company's vinyl collectibles.
Zach Ryder joins us to talk theme park toys on today's Podcast the Ride.
The theme park podcast hosted by three men who all, last night, spent 15 minutes texting
each other Google Map overheads of Disneyland.
That is true.
I think actually now that I think about it, I wrote that, but I think I was the one primarily
sending the overheads.
But we were all discussing sort of the breakdown of Disneyland.
By the way, my name is Mike Carlson.
I'm joined by Jason Sheridan and Scott Caradon.
And you were right, but what, yeah, you sent a map because this was based on the idea of
can the Tron coaster fit somewhere into Disneyland?
And I believe I told you I had previously done map comparisons to like, and sort of
like eyeballed.
All right, so at this scale, the coaster is an inch.
And so if you move this inch from Shanghai on top of, you know, on top of the Autopia,
if you were to get rid of something that is unnecessary in Disneyland, such as the Autopia
or the submarines, there I set it.
Yeah, sure.
You know, would it fit?
I think, but what we agreed on essentially is that, you know, I think, I think gut almost
anything in Tomorrowland to get that Tron ride in.
Just save Space Mountain and everything else can go.
Everything else can go.
Because I looked at it and we were talking about because the space Autopia and the subs
take up, it's massive.
Like you could fit what looks like seven space mountains in that.
I could be well, that's not exact.
But when you really see it overhead, you go, look at all the land that is just wasted here
on two rides that I never go on.
Yeah. And as we discussed last week, the monorail track in Disneyland, especially has been
changed and reconfigured so much.
It's not an alien idea to that.
They can they can rejigger that however they want.
We started talking about we're going to get to an interview, by the way, with WWE
superstar and podcaster Zack Ryder, aka Matt Cordona, just a little bit.
Oh, my God. A superstar from another avenue from Orlando, from paradise.
He will be taking away some of his precious paradise time to join us.
Right. He's won an Intercontinental title.
He's won a US title. But we don't care.
We're more impressed that he's living in Orlando.
That's the thing that we care so much.
We want to ask him about that.
We're going to ask him about theme park toys.
We could, I guess, just talk to any Orlando resident.
I'm glad if we're going to talk to anyone that it is a WWE superstar.
But some of some of his questions were we're going to ask him almost anybody.
And I'm excited because oftentimes we reach consensus or at least like, well, I
I don't agree with you, but I understand where you're coming from.
But Matt has some real hot takes.
And, yeah, it's good we have.
It's good to have opposite opinions on the show.
Will we be flustered? Will we be alarmed? Will we agree?
We are always flustered.
I mean, I think that's clear in our lives.
Sure. So, yeah, just to go circle back to what we were talking about.
I think that we started talking about Disneyland and the layout and where stuff
could go is because we saw this video that is sweeping theme park Twitter
and everything, every social media.
This beauty and the beast ride coming to Tokyo Disney.
Disney Sea? No, it's Disney, right?
This is Disneyland. OK. Yes.
That is am I wrong?
I'm not even sure where is I think it is.
I think you're right. I think it's Disneyland because they're doing
the Disney Sea expansion with that's in twenty twenty two.
And it's going to have Peter Pan and there's a frozen thing.
And that's all there, I believe. OK.
So, yeah, Tokyo Disneyland.
And it's three minutes long and it shows off robots like they show so much in this.
Yeah. And the primary thing, I mean, you see robots.
Look, they're they're all great.
But you essentially you see robots of the beast of Bell's horse,
Philippe, as all the Philippe fans get ready.
You're finally going to see a fully rendered Philippe, but also
the Bell, several animatronics of Bell.
And I don't want to speak for you guys, but to me, the Bell
animatronics, the most mind blowing.
Absolutely. It is like so alive and has the texture of a cartoon character.
All of the oddity that you feel with I think I think that Ariel
animatronic ended up pretty good, but I think there were probably like errors
on the way and your hair was weird at a certain point.
The the Bell animatronic is so crazy out of the gate.
It is just it is a living toy or something.
Her moving is, I think, what everybody's responding to.
And I think initially I thought because I saw a thumbnail of that,
like when she's got I think she has like the lantern, like I don't know
what scene that's from.
Maybe it's I think it's in the winter when she's like looking for something
or the beast. I can't remember exactly.
I could be wrong now. Now that I'm thinking about it, she's not wearing a winter coat.
So don't crucify me on Twitter for this.
And maybe they'll give her they'll give her the coat later.
They bought the coat.
Maybe the coat is not there yet, but she's walking.
And it basically is the important part.
And I saw a thumbnail of it and I thought it was a cartoon.
And I showed the whole thing to my girlfriend, Lindsey.
And she I had to tell her that is a robot because she goes,
Oh, I thought that was just a CGI Bell.
It looks if you haven't watched this and please look it up.
Although I think the name of the video is is in Japanese.
So learn Japanese and then look up the video.
But yeah, it looks absolutely like very well rendered 3D animation.
But it is a physical thing in some warehouse somewhere
that will soon be in the parks in Japan.
But it moves not just like smooth movement or life like.
But Scott, you said movement like the animation movement.
And they said they worked with the animation studio,
but they always say we worked hand in hand with this.
But in this case, it's this case and like the lantern dangle.
Like you can see the lantern moving like if you were holding a lantern.
Like it's it's so crazy, not just they could make it look so natural,
but look natural in a style of animate.
Like it's wild. Yeah, it's it's it reminded me of the frozen right
because the frozen right is really great animatronics and they move,
you know, a good amount.
And everybody always talks about the Olaf animatronic
because he kind of follows you around.
He walks and he like looks at you.
But, you know, he just don't he's like a snowman.
He doesn't have to, you know, move like a human or whatever.
I don't have to move anyway.
You don't want me to.
My limbs don't work like human limbs.
I'm a little cartoon guy.
I'm a cartoon snowman.
Nothing says Christmas morning like Pillsbury Crescent Rolls.
It does sound like my Pillsbury doughboy voice, which I've done for many years.
But it is the similar voice.
I'm a little I'm a little snowy doughy boy.
Yeah, that's what he says.
Like we were just kind of loosely quoting him on the right.
He says basically all that stuff. Yeah.
We're born. So, yeah.
But like he moves and that's the most impressive, impressive animatronic on that right.
But it looks like they took the moving part of it and they put it on the humans characters.
And that's the really thing that's going to blow people's minds.
I think it's this weird, this odd step between there are the very humany characters,
like the all of presidents and like Benjamin Franklin Climbing the Stairs.
And then there's pure cartoon characters, which seem like in some
you know, it's all very difficult to do, but maybe easier to render a cartoon character.
And this is this in between a cartoon of a human that moves
so fluidly and so realistically, it is it does feel like a just new type of animatronic entirely.
Yeah, it's it's like between this and then those like stunt tronics.
Is that what they were called? The Marvel? Oh, yeah.
The flipping ones. Yeah, they were like they may be called stunt tronics.
And it was like they're going to be able to do a stunt show and robots will be able to do stunts
and the robots will probably be dressed like Iron Man or something.
But you'll have be able to have Iron Man fly through the air during a stunt show.
So between these two, like all the robots are going to get way more realistic,
from hopefully from now on.
And it's going to be awesome.
Hopefully not scary. Hopefully not some sort of Skynet thing.
We're inching closer and closer to the itching scratchy land episode.
But those are clunky robots.
I guess so.
Those are a good time to prepare for an attack by those clunky, itching, scratchy robots.
We're heading closer and closer to Westworld.
And it's finally by the end of our lifetimes, we will be able to engage
in sexual relations with the Avengers.
With the Avengers.
You know, I don't know who's in that Iron Man suit.
Maybe it's a hot lady or it's just doesn't matter to me.
That is the comic book equivalent of an eyes wide shut mask.
Oh, yeah.
Where the Iron Man and anonymity?
Maybe I'm in there.
Maybe you're not in the suit.
Oh, man. You know, this makes me really happy about thinking about kissing Olaf.
Yes. Dressed as Iron Man.
Dressed as Iron Man.
Uh, this I'm melting in this suit.
This this makes me think of Independence Day resurgence,
which is a phrase no one has ever said before.
But, you know, we had 20 plus years to prepare and we're not ready.
20 plus years to protect, prepare for a robot sex at Disneyland.
Yeah. I never thought it would happen to me.
Big Al.
He's a big he's a thick boy, you know,
takes a real man to take a big Al down.
Yeah. Well, we finally outed ourselves.
What this podcast has really always been all about.
Kiss Eyes Queens, Iron Man, Kissing Iron Man.
And I'm sure our our guest will be very happy to have this discussion
as his introduction.
Yeah. So what a beautiful red carpet we just laid for him.
Yeah. So we'll take a break and collect ourselves,
because now we're all heated up.
We're all flustered.
And we'll be right back with our guest, W.W.
Zach Ryder, aka Matt Cardona.
All right, folks, welcome.
We'd like to welcome our very special guest.
You know him from the WWE and his podcast, the Major Wrestling Figure podcast.
He's the Michael Jordan of wrestling figure collecting.
Matt Cardona, aka Zach Ryder.
Welcome to the show, Matt or Zach or however we're going to whatever we'll say.
Like, do you prefer whatever?
It doesn't really matter to me.
I think at this point in my life, most people call me Zach, even my dad,
even though my real name is Matt.
That's funny. So so.
Very. So, yeah.
So you for personal, like close friends, they call you Matt.
Yeah. My real name is Matt Cardona on the wrestling figure podcast.
I'm Matt Cardona, aka Zach Ryder.
But most people, they know me as Zach Ryder.
Nobody knows who Matt Cardona is.
You know, right, right. Well, we can do that.
We can try to get the word out that you are Matt.
Either or, you know, either or.
I try to do both on the podcast, you know, so I can create my real identity.
You know what I'm saying? Sure.
But what would you get stitched into Mickey Ears?
Ooh, I mean, I would definitely.
I think I would definitely get the whole give of all the Zach Ryder stuff, everything.
All right. That makes sense. That's the way to go. Sure.
Do you think they could fit Woo Woo Woo onto the back of Mickey Ears?
Is there enough room?
I'm sure they could do it, but I would not do that.
OK, I wouldn't get.
No, that's where that's that's across the line.
That's a little too aggressive of a brand, you know, branding.
Right. A little too much like like I listen.
Right now I'm in my I can't really see what I'm doing, but quote unquote office.
I'm doing like the figure quotes.
I say office, but there's a computer here and a bunch of like toys and stuff.
But there's a Zach Ryder cardboard cut out with a Darth Vader
slash Mickey Mouse helmet on it.
So you guys are missing that right now. Hey, that sounds great.
Yeah. For those of you who do not know, Matt is
can I say an insane toy collector?
Is that OK? Sure. Sure.
If you want to say insane, I just say I'm a toy collector.
Like you said, the Michael Jordan of wrestling collecting.
But he's an insane basketball player, I would call him, though,
because he's like so good.
He does it so well. Oh, insane is a compliment.
I'm using it as a compliment.
No, no, no, no. For sure. For sure. For sure.
So, yeah, we're going to talk like theme park merch, toys,
general theme park stuff.
But before we start, I do.
I don't know if you remember this.
You've actually talked theme parks with with one of us being me.
The one person being me.
We were at a mutual friend's wedding over the summer.
I don't know if this jogs your memory.
I do remember that at John Morrison's wedding.
So you know what I'm talking about?
We had a little we had a little argument, right?
Yes, we did. So so this is this is before I heard the podcast.
Now I listen all the time. Sure. I apologize.
No, it's OK. I wasn't calling you on it.
I thought it was great.
But did you know once you started listening to the podcast that that was me?
I kind of put two and two together and I never was 100 percent certain until just now.
Sure. Can either side of this give your side of the events?
Yeah, yeah. My recollection of it was that John
John Hennigan, John Morrison, Johnny Mundo, he has many names.
He was just on Survivor.
He's everywhere. His wedding.
And he said, hey, bro, this is my buddy, Mike.
He has a theme park podcast.
And my recollection is that you immediately started quizzing me
like pretty hardcore about theme parks.
I think your first question was, what's the best ride in Magic Kingdom?
And it was like, I was like, whoa, whoa, wait, what?
And I was like, well, did you and I think I said, well, when you say Magic Kingdom,
you mean obviously Florida because Magic Kingdom and you were like, well,
there's that's the only Magic Kingdom.
And I said, well, they call the you know, they call Disneyland
sometimes Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom in videos.
And I think you said then it's Space Mountain.
The answer is Space Mountain.
So that's my that's
that's my recollection of the start of it, at least.
And I think people were like standing around and I think it turned into like
kind of like a rap battle of some where people would be like, oh, like
once like somebody said a good thing or I was like, well,
have you ever been in Walt's apartment?
And then I think someone's like, whoa.
Yeah, I mean, to be honest, I had a couple couple of drinks that day.
I don't really remember every little detail.
Sure. But what's funny is that I was quizzing you and now listening to your podcast.
I realized I don't know anything in compared to you guys.
I guess that's what I was talking about on Twitter about.
Like, I can't do like a whole topic.
Like, you guys know, like the voices and rise.
I thought I was a diehard.
You guys put me to shame.
Well, you've pursued other interests in a successful career.
We have nothing better to do than know who Thorol Ravenscroft is.
OK, see, there you go.
But I mean, I like all my friends.
They think I'm like this diehard Disney freak.
They think I'm obsessed.
They think I'm nuts because I I have an annual pass in Orlando.
I live in Orlando.
So I go a couple of times a month.
And, you know, some people, they just don't get it, you know, at all.
And you guys like the opposite.
You guys totally get it.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, we get like, yeah, for a normal person, like you are unusual.
But like when you look at us for knowing
like some 60 year old character, character actor doing voices of robots.
Yeah, like then that makes you look normal versus like
so there's a whole spectrum.
That was what I'm trying to say.
But like we're all absolutely all four of us are strange
compared to the normal person in the world.
That's what we're all.
For sure. Yeah, absolutely.
Matt, I do want to commend you for immediately going to get the upper hand
on Mike, because he will just you can just tell by his voice.
He will run rough shot over you if you don't establish dominance.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
All right. Now I know Jason is Jason is happy that that's
what everything went down.
No, I honestly out of that interaction, I was like, that was the greatest thing.
That could have the best thing that could have happened was that
like I got to talk theme parks in a very funny way.
So do you stand you stand by that space mountain?
Would that be your assessment today?
For me? Oh, yeah, for sure.
Space is my favorite.
I know, like, OK.
Pirates of the Caribbean, Haunted Mansion, like I get their classics,
but oh, man, there's no way I could ride those every day.
So, yeah, so so I was listening to your interview with Kevin Perger,
who does defunct land, and you were.
Yeah, for those of you who don't know, we're talking about
we've mentioned many times he does these great videos about the history
of different rides, stuff that's not there, stuff that's not in the parks anymore.
And he also has a podcast and interviewed you.
And you kept giving him heart attacks because he would bring up
like classic rides and you would be like, yeah, boring.
Got to go. I would like to burn that down to like you didn't.
You said, I think Carousel Progress.
Correct me if I'm wrong. Carousel Progress.
No, gone boring ride.
I think you said it about I think you even kind of soft said it about pirates.
Like, no, no, no, listen, I was pirates.
I get it. I respect it. I respect its history.
You know, like every once in a while, I'll do it just to say I did it.
But I think even as a kid, I thought it was boring.
OK, so that was just boring.
That was not Carousel Progress needs to go 100 percent.
Shots fired shots fired because the classic fans, you know, they like
that's the history of Disney.
And so would you would you even want to plus that up or was it just like gone?
Let's have a fun new ride.
Now, if you want to plus it up and update it, go ahead.
But when's the last time it was updated?
Oh, I don't know. 20 years ago.
Oh, even more because they still have 90s virtual reality.
Like grandma's playing like a fighter game.
It's like one step above F zero.
Just barely. That's zero point five.
A few years ago, they swapped out like a furniture
sized big screen TV
with the, you know, big two part behind it for a modern flat screen TV.
And that was the last update I noticed.
So the answer is they haven't really touched it in a while.
Yeah, we're proving the nerd dim here that Jason knew that the TV had been changed
in the final scene of Carousel of Progress.
That doesn't count. That's not enough for you.
Yeah. So my mom, my mom came to our parents came to Orlando about a year ago
and she really wanted to do Carousel of Progress and I did not.
But I went on because she's my mom and, you know, give her a good time.
And I was asleep. I can't wait through it.
Do you do you even like the song?
Like, is there any element of it you would like?
Like, do you like the song? Is it charming at all to you?
Do you like the songs in general on the rides?
The famous songs like Yo Ho Pirates Life?
No, no, listen, I shouldn't.
Let me take it back. I don't hate pirates.
I understand its place in history.
It's OK. And it's cool.
But like, if I was going to take someone who's never been to Disney
World to Disney World or Disneyland, I would take him to Pirates
because it's history. It's classic. Right.
But for me, I'm an annual passholder.
If I'm going to go tomorrow, I'm not going to go on Pirates.
Gotcha. All right.
But when I would come, when I would come every couple of years, of course,
you have to hit Pirates. Right now.
Not in every time.
Are there any of the are there any rides that, you know, are
are kind of boring or dry, but that you do you are fond enough of it to
to put up with it?
I mean, Haunted Mansion, like, I love it, but it's the more you ride it.
You're like, oh, for me, it's like, OK, I did it.
I did it the other night.
I was like, oh, man, there we go again.
I'll imagine you just feel like it feels like a profession.
It's like a job.
Yeah, I think I almost spoil myself, you know,
because I have this annual pass and I don't go all the time.
I go enough.
And like every time someone comes to visit me in Orlando,
they want to go to the theme parks.
I want to go to Disney Universal. So.
I kind of ruin it for myself.
Yeah, I get that.
I mean, there are rides that we don't go on at every time.
Like, for instance, like great moments with Mr.
Lincoln, which I imagine you would be OK with if it burned to the ground.
I'm just guessing.
Do you? I've never I've never done that or Hall of Presidents.
Really? Never done it at all.
I mean, they're both dry history lessons.
My parents might have took me to the Hall of Presidents
when I was like a little kid that I don't remember.
But like teenage and up, there's no way I was ever in there.
OK, well, yeah, like like a ride like that is like a once a year ride for me.
Like, right.
Lincoln is like a once a year ride, but it is nice that there is a robot
Abraham Lincoln that I can go and hear about the Civil War.
But once a year. Yeah.
I keep telling myself that one of these days I'm going to go to Magic Kingdom
and do all the things that I haven't done or hate.
And just like get it over with. I never do it again.
But the problem is, like, I can't do that with somebody.
They'll they'll never do it.
And then I can't go to the parks by myself, because it's kind of weird.
Unless you guys do that, then it's not weird. Sorry, guys.
But we're for me. We've been alone.
I've come to terms with it.
Much more common in Anaheim, much more common in Disneyland, I feel like.
Yes. And when you're often unemployed actors or writers or whatever we all are
and you've got a day to fill, let's let's head down.
And I'm perfect way to fill it up.
Yeah, nothing weird about it.
No, not not remotely.
Mike, you've told this one.
Sure, Mike, you've told this one on the show before,
but I kind of want Zach to hear it, which is that you went down
to see Dick Van Dyke in a parade.
Yeah, this is you're going to make fun of me for this
because I didn't go down even to go on a ride.
I went down because the real man, Dick Van Dyke, was going to be in a parade
at Disneyland because he had his 90th birthday.
No one would go with me.
And I was frustrated.
So I said, well, you know what? I'm going alone.
I went down for literally an hour and watched a 90 year old man
driving a little car down Main Street.
And then I went back up to Los Angeles.
So, you know, we all do.
It's like a good it's not a good hour and a half drive, right?
Or a little hour, hour and a half.
Yeah, hour, hour and a half.
Sure. Spent more time in the car than watching the old man in the little car.
So did you get to wave at him, at least?
Did I get what? Did you get to wave? Did he wave at you?
Oh, yeah, I got a picture of him waving in my general direction.
OK, that counts. All right. OK.
But like if we say you were an unemployed actor
and you maybe didn't have too much going on that day, but I said,
would you go with me to Anaheim to watch an old man in a parade for an hour?
Would you have said no or yes?
I mean, it depends who it is for Dick Van Dyke, probably not.
So like Michael J. Fox, maybe if he was like at Universal or DeLorean.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, maybe I do that.
He has been he opened back to the future of the ride down in Florida,
I think, along with Thomas Wilson and maybe maybe his Zemeckis appearance.
So he's he's been down.
He knows what it's like down there.
Oh, that DeLorean and Universal Orlando.
It's it's it's embarrassing.
It's it don't get me started on that.
Oh, yeah. I listened to you on on Jericho's podcast with Cody Rhodes and
got a big laugh at describing sad DeLorean next to a bush.
Yeah, it's like it's next to the bushes and a taco stand.
It has no it's like there should be like a spotlight on it.
It should be right in the middle.
Yeah, it is just that it's hidden by some bushes.
Tossed off after after the Simpsons.
Another thing that came up on that show that I definitely agree with
is that Universal has pretty much no sense of nostalgia
in the way Disney Universal will just build new rides left and right.
Right. There's no way the castle progress would be standing at Universal Studios.
No, no. Good point. Yes.
No way. Which ends up being a real pain for us, because like researching
universal researching Disney stuff is pretty but like finding weird
deep cut universal stuff, you're really like scraping the Internet archive
to find remnants of it.
Was your favorite?
I'd listen to that interview, too.
But I forget if it was back to the future, like your favorite ride of all time
when you were younger or now still.
When I was younger, I loved it.
And even now, I still consider one of my favorites of all time.
And that and as a kid, I wasn't even that really
I wasn't really that big of a back to the future fan.
Like now I'm like a diehard as I've grown older.
Come to appreciate more and watch it way more times.
So I would love to ride it now, like as an adult,
because like my last memory of it, I think I'm like in sixth grade.
So I don't really have vivid memories of it.
Well, you got to get there's a DVD re-release.
I got the DVD.
The ride is on the DVD. It's preserved.
And if you just kind of shake around in a chair, it approximates
what it's like to go on the ride.
I don't mind the Simpsons.
Simpsons is OK.
But, you know, I wish it didn't take the place of Back to the Future.
Yeah, that is the one that is the one that should still be there.
But I was like I was so worried around that time that they were going to
I knew about the future was going to be torn out.
But with NBC's awful synergy,
I was ready to be replaced by like a ride of The Voice or something.
I think so.
Bottom of the barrel.
I don't think that's out of the world.
One thing that, yeah, one thing that Universal still has
standard is that Fear Factor Live, nothing needs to go.
It's perplexing.
It's wild that it's still going.
Do they even run it, really?
Like occasionally during high traffic times, I think, right?
I haven't been in there in years.
I have never seen that show.
That's a theme park area.
I didn't see it in Hollywood.
I never saw it in Orlando. Skipped.
That's my burn it to the ground.
Yeah, I've never seen it either.
Did you? Bizarre.
And I said this before on the show, it's like the most valuable theme park reel.
It's just a huge it's like a block long.
So big. It's so big.
Yeah. I mean, Jaws has to go.
Jaws is torn out.
And yet Fear Factor is not forever tenant.
Yeah. I heard on that on that interview you had done with Jericho,
you were talking about like you're down on the animal actor show as well.
Yeah, that is true. Yeah.
I think I think the way Cody phrased it is that you guys were like backstage
because you got to do some cool tour or something and that you got to meet
the dog from the show.
And Cody said that you right.
Cody said that you buried the dog five minutes away, like five minutes
or five, excuse me, five feet away.
This is what this is what happened.
We had done one of those those VIP tours. Right.
So the last thing we like, you know, I don't know, half hour,
four minutes left and like I want to get some more rise in.
Cody's wife really wanted to do this animal actor show.
Like this is what we're going to waste our time with.
It's an actor show.
We can be cutting like lines right now.
So I was already pissed.
You know, so we watched the show.
And of course, like nothing goes according to plan.
The dogs, they all mess up.
The birds fly the wrong way, all that stuff.
And then they say, hey, you could stay after and meet some of the animals.
Something like, OK, maybe we'll meet like the pug for Men in Black
or something like that, you know.
But we'd be like, just like a dog, a golden retriever.
Like, what is it?
Just the regular dog.
We can't be like big, big or something like that.
Oh, yeah, that is a little bit like that's not a famous dog.
You wouldn't want to have met one of the famous animals from the properties.
Yeah, that makes sense.
It's a bird that could hypothetically be in a film if a camera was pointed at it.
Yeah. Right.
So you live in Orlando.
You when did you move there a couple of years ago?
I moved just over two years ago.
OK, did was a big part of it that you would be close to the theme parks?
Yes, actually, it was.
Hey, that's OK. We dream about it every day.
Every day we think about, hey, maybe we just quit this whole thing
and go down to Orlando.
We do. And I don't know.
You're going to have a different perspective because you have things going on.
But how do you like how do you feel about the Orlando situation?
And would you recommend it to others?
I love Orlando.
Oh, I love it.
Every so I fly out, you know, I've wrestling shows every week,
but every week when I fly home and I step foot on that,
that ugly carpet in the Orlando airport, I tell myself, I'm on vacation.
It's it's great.
You know, you go to the parks whenever you want.
There's always something going on because it's like this this tourist trap.
But I don't live like in the center.
I don't live like at the Magic Kingdom.
You know what I'm saying? I live like 45 minutes away from Disney.
So I live 10 minutes from the airport.
It's great. The airport's super easy.
I mean, I like the TSA pre if you didn't have that,
you'd be waiting on these crazy long lines.
But I love it. And the weather right now, it's December.
I'm in shorts at a tank top. New York, where I'm from.
It's it's always snowy. It's cold. It's expensive.
I don't know. I don't know. Everly will. I love it.
I didn't even think about that because you are on the road a lot of the year.
But every time you get back to Orlando, you get to ride that airport monorail.
Yes, every week, every week.
It's a ride. Yeah, you get to go on that ride every time.
And the TSA pre is sort of the fast pass of commuter travel.
So I even have something called clear.
So I passed the TSA pre.
So it's like people are saying like Orlando airport's nuts.
So we go, yeah, I don't wait on the lines.
Wow, that's great.
But I fly I fly every week.
So it's worth it for me.
I think it's like one hundred fifty dollars a year or something like that.
But it's saved so much time.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Would you be willing to help with the sales pitch to our respective wives
slash girlfriends to make the move to Orlando?
I mean, absolutely.
I mean, my my my mortgage is one hundred dollars more than my rent
was from an apartment in New York.
It's cheap down here.
That's really attractive.
That's all you had to say.
That's the only fact that matters.
Brand new house. No one ever sat on the toilet before. Brand new.
OK, that's another strike in the good.
I'm telling you, they're building all these communities all over.
Like where I live is like a new community every every like,
you know, a couple of months to build a new community.
Got to move down.
She's all right. Maybe we just have a cul-de-sac to yourself.
I mean, the houses are a little close together.
They're like 10 feet apart, but that's OK.
That's all right. Everything's we're in apartments.
Yeah. So my whole life or like my whole adult life,
I always live in apartment apartment apartment in New York.
All my stuff in stores, paying all this money, shoveling snow, all this BS.
Now I live in Orlando, go to Disney World.
Oh, it's the best.
Palm trees.
The Denny's by the airport has palm trees. Oh, it's beautiful.
Well, if you could see us, we're all like wistfully looking off
into the distance, imagining this life here.
You're painting for us.
We love it.
We're in the middle of the one of the few stretches of when it rains in L.A.
and everything just falls apart when that happens.
Like it rains every day.
You almost did Orlando and everyone's fine out here.
It's like the end of the world.
Yeah. So when you're in Orlando, what are your theme park habits like?
How many times do you go in a month?
Do you have a universal pass?
Like what do you have a strategy or is it sort of spur of the moment?
So I had a universal pass the first year I moved down, but I didn't use it.
I mean, I paid for it with the amount of times I went, but I didn't use it that much.
So now, like when I go, I only go with like people come and visit
or if it's like Halloween or nice, because I feel like it sounds weird.
But Disney is a whole world, you know, and Universal
those two parks and I love Universal, but I can get old quick, I think.
And Disney, you can really spread out like with Disney.
Disney has all the hotels and the resorts.
You go eat somewhere in one of those hotels and go to the Disney Springs area.
It's phenomenal. They've really redone that.
It's my favorite thing to do in Orlando is go to Disney Springs.
Oh, wow. Yeah.
So have you gone to like every restaurant there is to go on the Disney World property?
No, not even close.
And that's what I love about it.
I wouldn't even say like less than half, probably a third, if that.
OK, so we're talking restaurants in a Disney World area.
What are your top couple, top three?
Top three California Grill at the contemporary.
Yeah. Right.
I was just there two nights ago in Disney Springs, some called the Boathouse.
I love the Boathouse.
I love this Boathouse.
I went once two years ago. It's the greatest.
So good. The food's good.
The view is good. The atmosphere is good.
Really, really love it.
And then what else?
And there's so many good ones.
Let's say Gico and Animal Kingdom, the Animal Kingdom.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
That was called. I got to do that once.
Yeah, that's that's fancy as hell.
And like, yeah, like odd food you wouldn't get elsewhere.
Yeah, really cool.
And so like deep.
And don't get me wrong, I'm not going to these places every night.
You know what I'm saying? Sure. Sure.
And that's OK. If you were.
We wouldn't have a problem if you were.
Every lunch at Gico.
So, yeah. So so how often are you going to one of the four Disney parks a month?
I would say once or twice a month.
It's not it's not crazy excessive, you know, for instance, the other night
I went to the Mickey's very, very Christmas party
and I might go to I might try to go to Hollywood Studios next week.
So that'd be two times this month. Sure.
So you hit events and stuff, it seems like special things.
Yeah, I've got my favorite.
So I go to Epcot a lot. Yeah. Yeah.
What's the world showcase like?
I saw some Instagram pictures of you.
I think John was with you guys a while, a while ago, but like
going up and down, I assume drinking around the world.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
As a kid, I hated Epcot.
If my parents would take me there, I was so mad.
I didn't want to waste the day at Epcot.
But now, oh, it's my favorite.
I would go I would go to Epcot every week, for sure.
Is there do you have a favorite Epcot country?
Oh, Mexico, for sure.
Oh, yeah, that's a kilobar inside.
Oh, my God, the best.
And that ride, you are guaranteed no wait.
You will never wait for the Mexico boat ride.
Interest in it has never gone up.
It's just you could always jump right on that thing.
I think there's a reason for that.
All right. So you want to burn that one to the ground as well.
No, it's cute. It's in there.
It's like in the restaurant.
I don't really count that as a ride. Keep it.
Oh, OK.
But what if I what if our idea was to like drain that
and then just make it overflow for that to kilobar?
Oh, OK. I like that.
OK, maybe that's the way. Maybe that's what we should do.
And if those if those animatronics, if the three capoeiras serve you drinks,
they're poor. Yeah, if they're operating the taps, that's the way.
Yeah. When so when you were a kid, like how did you go a lot as a kid
to these places was?
No, I probably went like every like five years or so.
So maybe like four times in my life until I became like an adult.
There's a little, little kid I went and when I don't even remember,
it's like third grade, sixth grade, like 11th grade.
So like four times. Yeah, you.
You loved it.
You tweeted us a photo of you at like a 20th anniversary event
at Star Wars in 1997.
And I think we're all.
I was. Yeah.
And it made me realize like, wait, was I at that too?
Like, because I ended up down there.
One one of the times when I was down there with my family,
it would have been like one of the first Star Wars, like weekends
or Star Wars anniversary things,
which was like very fun and different at the time.
And now it's it's always Star Wars time.
Yeah, luckily, I love Star Wars, so I'm OK with it. Yeah.
You psyched for for later in the year for the the grand unveiling of Galaxy?
I'm a little nervous, but yeah, I definitely psyched.
Yeah, yeah.
Do we I don't think we've recorded an episode since we saw the
there was a news story going around about how people are expecting
200,000 visitors on the day the thing opens,
which is a tad imposing.
Maybe that you guys are.
OK, you guys are getting away before us, right?
Yeah, that's what they're saying.
Like months before, possibly six months to longer.
So that means I got to come to Disneyland.
Yeah, I was going to say, like, you will.
You have to make that stop then.
Oh, 100 percent.
I I mean, maybe because I've been to Disney World so many times
and because it's in my own backyard, but I prefer Disneyland over Disney World.
Yeah, we've had that debate on the on the on the podcast before.
But I think when you just the amount of rides
and amount of things you can just do in Disneyland versus Magic Kingdom,
I still think you got to give it to Disneyland.
I mean, I guess for one or two day experience, I would say Disneyland.
But for a whole week, it's it really depends on what you're
what you're talking about. Right.
But there's no boathouse in Anaheim, though, which is one of the.
That is true. The downtown Disney.
I'm not a big fan of that.
Well, it's getting better.
We've got the cool bowling alley now and we've got some ice cream.
So let's go. Yeah.
Splits. Oh, we have that.
I'm next. Next time you're out, I vote yes on Splitsville.
I haven't bowled there, but I've eaten there.
There is a splice fill in Orlando. Oh, that's right.
Oh, how's the splice fill in Orlando?
It's OK. Overpriced bowling. Yeah.
Yeah. Overpriced food, too.
But, you know, decent food is in short supply in the Disneyland resort.
So I'll take what I can get and I'll pay 30 percent too much for it.
I actually think the food's like the better at Disneyland in Disney World.
It is better. Yeah.
Well, you got like quick service food.
Yeah, yeah. There's a little more variety.
Yeah. Florida quick service food is still a lot of burgers
and and pizza and stuff for the tourists.
We when you search your name and theme parks, I forgot all about this.
If I ever if I maybe didn't even know it at all, is that like last year
you did all six parks in like 48 hours. Is that right?
Yeah, yeah. Less than 48 hours. Yeah. So pretty wild.
How many hours I would recommend?
I would recommend doing it.
No, maybe it was maybe it was like so I started off at
California Adventure Disneyland and then I took a red eye back to Orlando
and I slept on the plane, went to my house, took a shower
and then did the four parks.
So it was like just under two days. Right. Right. Wow.
Then did you got it done?
Then how many rides per park?
I would say a decent amount.
I didn't write everything down.
I was obviously I didn't everything, but enough where it was like
I didn't just walk in and leave, you know, and I made sure I did
like the heavy hitters in each park.
A substantial. How did you get from even just the single day
at Disney World is imposing doing four parks in a single day.
How did you make it from park to park?
For a couple of months, they had this thing that it's not there anymore.
And I think it's not there because one of my theories is
because they didn't really advertise it.
It was this this bus that you just I think was like thirty dollars
for the day.
And you went to these secret locations around the park
and you would take this bus just right to the back entrance of park
to park to park.
And it was like twenty five, thirty bucks a day.
I forgot what it was called.
Yeah, it was only around for like six months.
They were trying that for a while where like the load
and unload areas were technically backstage.
But like anyone could sign up for it.
But it seemed like, yeah, it seemed like they wanted people to do it.
But like you said, they did not advertise it.
And then I think they shift.
Like it wasn't even at the ticket window.
You had to ask for it.
Yeah. And now I think they're trying to push people into that mini vans
service they're doing with the lift.
Right. That what a what a what a scam.
Oh, it's incredible.
Oh, what a scam.
Have you done it yet? Have you been in one of the mini vans?
I refuse. What's the point?
I could just use an Uber or a lift.
Why why pay double or triple the price because it has many
mouse like dots on it.
Yeah, no, I think we talked about on the show.
I think we said like if if like many was driving, that would be worth it.
Sure. But if it's just a regular person, then who cares?
Now, with that being said, I also refuse to take Disney buses
and I Uber everywhere. Oh, wow.
From park to park.
I refuse. The buses suck. I refuse to do it.
Huh? I didn't know.
They're never on time. They're crowded.
They stop too many places.
Yeah. Not for me.
And haven't been updated in a long time.
I don't think I realized you could Uber from park to park.
I haven't been down there in the age of Uber,
but that's pretty comfortable and easy.
Uber, it's so easy.
You can Uber from everywhere from hotel to hotel,
hotel, park to Disney Springs.
I didn't know if they cut down on that, like in the way an airport does,
but I guess not. That's that's cool.
Wow. Huh. You got it figured out.
I would say I've it all figured out.
But what works for me, you know? Sure.
Was there was there a particular highlight of the of the two day marathon?
Just that I survived, really.
Yeah, sure.
It was a lot of fun.
And like I said, like I don't go to Disneyland that often.
So even when I go now,
it's I still use like the map, you know, I don't really know where everything is.
And I like that.
Yeah, it reminds me of like going on vacation as a kid.
Like you're discovering you can discover some around the corner.
But you've been on like you go like once a year, maybe Disneyland.
Yeah, the past few years I've gone at least once a year.
Yeah, for sure. Right.
So you've done like Guardians of the Galaxy and.
Yeah, done.
Guardian is Cars Land, all that stuff. Right.
Do you have a favorite robot in all six parks?
Favorite robot?
Oh, yeah.
Animatronic on a ride or even even like Sunny.
Oh, OK.
So I like Sunny Eclipse, but.
Huh, I never really thought about that.
Nice.
We think about it too much.
Uh.
Huh, I like that Sunny Eclipse answer, actually.
It's pretty good.
Sure. I'm glad that's not on your list of stuff to tear out of there.
I'm glad you're the Sunnyside Preservation Society.
When I was a kid, like with my family, like
I didn't know there was like
like four star like dining on Disney property.
I know there's real restaurants, you know, we would go to,
you know, to go eat at like whatever that.
I don't even know what it's called, where Sunny Eclipse is playing.
Cosmic Ray Starlight Cafe.
Right, right.
So like that was like that is like what I remember.
Like my parents are going to treat us.
We're going to Cosmic Ray's.
So like I used to love going there as a kid.
Which is the most like hamburger hot dog chicken finger.
Exactly.
I remember just squirting copious piles of ketchup and mustard
onto the most basic burger.
No vegetables, nothing like additive to it.
Just just just pure crap hot dog and watching a robot for a while.
Paradise.
My family always liked Cosmic Ray's.
Like my parents were would always acquiesce to eating there
because there was at least a toppings bar with like
fried mushroom fried on it like and cheese sauce.
So you could at least dress up like the standard Disney burger,
like a Fuddruckers almost.
But not as good as Fuddruckers.
No, not as good.
We're really selling this restaurant.
Not as good as Fuddruckers and less robots than Chuck E. Cheese.
What's the Disneyland equivalent called?
It's like without the outside seating in Tomorrowland.
This is like the burgers and stuff.
What's that called? Oh, the Tomorrowland Terrace.
Yeah, I actually like I like those burgers a lot.
I was just there, I think, in February and I got some some burger.
It was delicious.
Yeah, it's certainly like
I haven't had a burger in a while there, but last time I had it,
I was like, oh, pretty good.
And then the last time I think I ate at Cosmic Ray's, I was like,
this is terrible.
So, yeah, I think that that's a terrace is better for sure than Ray's,
but doesn't have a robot. So it's, you know, that's true.
If you ever do Paris, do not do the Tomorrowland restaurant
or the Discoveryland restaurant.
I had just a basic burger there and that was garbage.
That was the worst meal of a two week Europe vacation.
I've only done the domestic parks.
I can't wait to do the other the other Disney parks.
Yeah, like bucket list for me.
Sure. Yeah. I just did Tokyo and it is as good as people say.
That's awesome. Yeah.
So let's see.
I was listening to the interview with Jericho and you were
or Cody was talking about how you have rules for like theme parks.
And I was wondering, he
mentioned specifically, like if you're at Universal
and you see somebody wearing a Disney shirt, you will be like, hey,
wrong park or something.
That is true. Yes, that is true.
Are there other like sort of feelings you have about like just, you know,
what the outfit you should wear at theme parks is or what like
like we had a guest on Jessica McKenna who said like, some people wear
like the gaudiest like theme park stuff and then and she's not kind of cool with it.
Or if somebody's dressed as Captain Jack Sparrow, that's lame.
Like when somebody's got the full like wig on that makes them look like
the Johnny Depp character.
But like, do you have any feelings about that, how you should dress,
how you should act?
Well, see, when I did that interview with Cody and Jericho,
I was at a different time in my life.
I wasn't living in Orlando.
So Cody and I, we would go to the parks every couple of months together.
And I just hated his style because he was a big like sit on bench guy.
Like get a beer, just sit on the bench.
And like I was like, no, no, no, we got to hit every single ride.
I had like I had a, you know, like a map in my head.
We got to do this, this, this and this, you know, a whole like checklist
of all these things we need to do.
But now that I live here and I can take my time, like now I'm like
I'm like Cody, like, oh, if we don't do Space Mountain this time,
we'll do it next time.
You know what I'm saying?
Right. Before I needed to hit everything.
Like I needed to be there at rope drop and stay till the very end.
But now I'll go whenever I want.
Going for a couple of rides, get something to eat, I'll leave.
But that's because I'm spoiled and I live here.
Sure. So you've so you've loosened up even on the dress situation.
Like somebody dressed like.
I used to be very like I used to be very bad.
We're like you could only wear a Disney shirt
if it's like a Disney parks official shirt.
You couldn't wear a Target Disney shirt.
Oh, interesting.
But I've since I've relaxed on that.
I myself have like, you know, there's cool Disney shirts all over the Internet.
Target has great stuff. Very soft shirts.
Sure. Oh, I love. Yeah.
I love Target stuff.
I agree with you. I have a couple of them.
But one of my Mickey shirts is like so like it's like it feels like it's wilting.
Like it's it's so thin.
It's about to like I had to make it a sleep shirt.
And now I think I just have to throw it away.
But I love how soft it was.
So I agree. Totally. Right.
That a unit in Disney Springs just has tons of like cool oddball stuff
for like a third of the price of the actual park shirts.
Yes, yes.
This is the best I've done.
Yeah, I would.
I was there for a little bit and I loved it.
Do you have a lot of clothing like you have a lot of toys and stuff like that?
But you have do you collect shirts and stuff?
Because I'm I'm I'm a decent toy collector.
I have a like for again, for a regular civilian,
I have too many toys in time, but I collect a lot of shirts, too.
So I feel like I have maybe like something crazy,
like 60 shirts that have things on it.
Oh, wow. I don't collect Disney shirts.
I do have a lot, but I'm someone where like after where like for
I don't know if I have for a year or two, I'll give it to like Goodwill or something.
I'm not keeping it forever. Right. Sure. Sure.
And I love to rotate it out of my collection.
I just got it's a collection or anything.
Right. I just got an Oliver and Company shirt from Hot Topic on Black Friday.
Well, wait a minute. What? Yeah.
The movie Oliver and Company.
No, I know. It's my favorite favorite Disney movie that gets no respect.
No love. Yeah. No respect and good songs in it.
We were just talking about this the other day, too.
Oliver. I'm busy.
So there's like there's like two or three new Hot Topic Oliver
and Company shirts, and then I found I need to go.
I need to go to Hot Topic tomorrow.
I got joking. Yeah, no, there's a bunch of like there's like rescuer shirts now.
I saw they're doing a whole line of these for like we're all around the same age.
I think so. We all had the same references when we were a kid.
So they're doing they're like catering right to us now.
So I did not get all of them.
I was very, you know, I was conservative and only got one of the Oliver and Company shirts.
But yeah, they're they're doing it right over there at Hot Topic.
Like what a world we live in now.
If I was a little kid and my dad was like in his mid 30s
wearing a Disney like shirt and brag about it, he was like a weird dude.
Yeah, no, he'd be locked up, be sent away.
But now, I mean, I'm going to go to Hot Topic tomorrow and get that shirt.
Yeah, I hope they have it because I had ordered online and the woman when she
when the online order came, she was like shocked to see it.
So I would I would maybe call ahead to make sure they have it in store.
And if not, obviously, you have to order it online.
So, yeah, no, the world has changed a lot.
And what being in your mid 30s means is a lot different than it was 30 years ago.
Right. Which in your case, toys.
Oh, yeah. Let's let's talk about this.
What what do you like?
What's going on in the collection in terms of Disney, in terms of
park affiliated toy business?
Yeah, so I have a a whole room.
It's just my toy room.
It's all these toys on display.
And the room isn't super duper big, but it's a decent sized room.
And I do have two cases full of Disney stuff.
You know, I I really was into as a kid, remember those ceramic
like glass figurines they would sell at the parks? Yeah.
They make like every character like imaginable.
They will sell like the Disney store and stuff like that.
They don't they don't make them anymore.
But I had them as a kid and I went back and I got the ones I was missing.
And my mom's been going crazy.
And she's been like, I told her I wanted a couple of them like every couple of weeks.
I'll be like, oh, here's a box of the, you know, the beauty of the beast ceramic figures.
Like, oh, well, thanks, mom. I don't really have room for all this.
But thank you. You know.
So, yeah, I have a lot of Disney stuff.
And now this this company, I'm sure you know, Funko.
Oh, yeah, sure. Yeah.
Funko pops. So they have tons of Disney.
Funko pops.
And they have a lot of park exclusives, which are real pain in the ass to get.
Oh, we know. Oh, yeah.
That's a story I had a few months ago.
I was down at the park and I happened to open Twitter and a theme park news
site had said a store in downtown Disney has the Splash Mountain ones in stock.
And I texted Mike and I've never gotten a reply so fast as him going,
get me two of them.
And I walked in and I did get to they had about
like 15 and 12 in stock.
I bought two.
And when I walked by at the end of the day, they were all gone.
Yeah, I mean, I love those things.
So did you did you get the Splash Mountain one?
I had the Splash Mountain one.
I didn't get it. I had to get it off someone on the Internet.
Do a little trade. Sure.
Do you are. Yeah.
Is there a criteria like when you're looking for Disney stuff, is the criteria
it has to be sort of theme park specific because I think that's my general
criteria with collecting like I like characters from the park specifically.
Well, for me, you know, Disney World and Disney in general,
the merchandise isn't going to run out.
It's never ending.
So I need to be very, very, very specific. Right. So
we were just talking about Oliver Company.
I have the McDonald's Oliver and Company, like Happy Meal Toys.
Yeah, I have those in my collection.
I think I got those. That's great.
I remember the ads. Yeah.
Heartwarming McDonald's ads from the 80s.
Yes. I also got the McDonald's.
They made like Epcot, like all the different countries toys.
Oh, so it's like Mickey Mouse, Mickey Mouse, like red, white, blue Mickey Mouse.
You know. Oh, OK.
So like he's got like a sweater with the French flag on it or something.
No, you got to throw it in your Google machine and pick these up.
They're incredible.
Are any of them, you know, racially questionable?
Oh, I don't think so.
Nobody's in like a hat that they shouldn't be in.
Nothing. No funny business.
No, I don't think so.
No, I think it'd be offensive to the Norwegian people.
No, I think I mean.
I think it's OK.
All right. Well, then I must be fine.
Yes. So are those plush or are those like plastic?
It's just little plastic like Happy Bill toys.
OK, I'm looking through.
I see plush. I see plush.
When I Google.
We'll find it later.
I'm sure there's plastics.
I know this is this is tangential, but I'm just I'm very proud of my
full set of Mac tonight, riding different little vehicles
like this kind of like a 50s Cadillac and a little little biplane
and a scooter, like every type of car somebody can operate.
And my beloved McDonald's Moon Man Mac tonight is piloting them all.
That's that's a fun set.
I recommend that one if you have any Mac tonight interest.
Matt, were you a fan of Mac tonight, the Moon Man from McDonald's?
I remember it. I had some of those toys, too,
but I don't have them currently in my collection.
No. Oh, you ever been to the the world's largest McDonald's down there in Orlando?
I don't think so. Where's that?
Oh, look it up.
Now, I can't attest to what it's like now, but
this is a this is a case.
It was a case where I just I was talking to somebody who I'd never met.
A stranger has stuck up.
I had a conversation with on a set and he's like, you know, like in Orlando,
there's this big old it's a two story McDonald's and there's pizza
and ice cream and a record your own karaoke booth
and a Mac tonight robot in the restaurant.
And that's all I needed to hear.
And I booked a trip to Orlando several days later.
How about to be there?
I could not let I could not let a lot of weeks pass.
And I don't know if the Mac is still there,
but it still is a gigantic, gaudy, like awful to look at McDonald's.
And it is in your area.
I think it's in the I drive zone.
OK, that's like probably a half hour or so for me.
That's that's where all the tourist stuff is.
So that makes sense. Sure, sure.
It's over by where the American Gladiators
theater used to be that now is a mega church.
The American Gladiators theater was this.
I don't remember that.
There was kind of a medieval times dinner theater situation in Orlando.
But that what that was for American Gladiators.
And they got gladiators from the show.
But also, like tourists would compete.
But like, how did they possibly have people every week to like
you could tape a TV show every week.
But how do you have enough tourists who are like physically capable of going
against the gladiators? I don't know.
I think it was only open for like two years and it closed.
And it's a church now like a big Baptist church.
I was a big American Gladiators fan.
Oh, geez. Yeah, yeah, I bet.
Anyone that you admired in particular?
I think like Nitro, is that one of them?
I assume it sounds like one. Yeah.
When I was a kid, I had an American Gladiators birthday party in my backyard.
And it was my dad used to own these bodybuilding gyms and some jacked up guy.
He was the American Gladiator and he was all dressed up and everything like that.
So it was fun.
Wow. If you had to choose between if you if you were like
actively seeking employment in the Orlando area as like a medieval nights
jouster or times.
Oh, yeah. Medieval times rather medieval times like Jouster guy
or a pirate's dinner adventure, a swashbuckler swinging around on a rope.
Or let's say gladiators is there still or I might be missing one.
But if you were going to be in you were going to hit the Orlando
dinner theater scene, what would you choose?
I think I'd rather be like Tigger, like a character breakfast.
That's a lot easier.
It's less physically taxing.
Oh, I'm a big fan.
I'm a sucker for a character breakfast.
Really? So do you still do the character breakfast now once in a while?
Every once in a while, I'll do it.
100 percent. Yeah, I love a lot.
A lot of people, even if they're big theme
partners, sometimes they are they look at me strangely because I do want to take
photos with the characters like I think I've taken.
You got you got to do it.
I agree. Yeah, I understand.
You know, I'm not going to be the same character every single time I go,
but you got to go and, you know, I just met Mickey the other night,
which I'm very upset because now
Mickey doesn't talk anymore, but he used to talk in Magic Kingdom.
They took that away.
Yeah, that's sad.
They when I was there last, like a year ago, we went in
and we knew he was talking, but we went into a room and he wasn't talking.
And then I went up to like town hall to complain.
And they were like, well, you know, he's not always guaranteed
to be doing something like that.
And they go, you can go back and you can ask somebody
if Mickey is feeling talkative today.
And they like winked at me.
And then we did it again.
And he talked and it was all it was like amazing.
But it's so good, right? It's so good.
You've seen the video where he speaks Japanese to some tourists.
I have not seen that.
So Mickey was speaking Japanese to tourists like he was doing the impossible.
And now it's gone.
And I don't know why.
I think the head was malfunctioning or something.
I heard and who knows that this is true, that, you know,
people were complaining that he wasn't talking everywhere.
Oh, interesting.
So until the technology gets cheaper, they won't have one Mickey that talks.
I mean, who knows?
I thought I thought it was great.
I thought it was special that in the front, he would talk.
I agree.
Can I just back up and say, Mike, you went to City Hall to complain
about a Mickey related issue.
Yes, I we had a fast pass, one of our precious fast passes
for that Mickey meet and greet.
And I was telling my girlfriend, Lindsay, over and over,
I go, Mickey's going to talk to us.
Mickey's going to say something.
And I'm like, I was very excited about it.
And then you get in the room and Mickey Mickey keeps his mouth shut.
And I was upset about it.
So we went across the street and I was like, hey, I've seen online
that Mickey talks and they were like they were weird
because they wouldn't confirm that he talks either, which I found very
like weird and suspicious, but obviously they don't want to promise things.
That's why there was never anything like come see Mickey, have him talk to you,
hear him speak Japanese.
They wouldn't say that.
So they gave me another fast pass.
But I mean, it was like such a big part of my excitement to go to Magic Kingdom
is to hear Mickey say hello.
Hmm. Was it equally exciting, though, to lodge a complaint
at the formal establishment City Hall?
Well, look, I don't like I feel like Jason is better at like lodging complaints
than I am in general.
So I look I wasn't happy to do it, but it was necessary is what I'm saying.
I needed to do this.
I needed to complain for you. Yes.
Matt, do you complain once in a while at these parks?
I was about to say I don't think I've ever complained at the parks.
I don't I honestly I'm trying to think of another time I did.
I cannot think of another instance where I complained.
But this one, I was very I was adamant that we needed to get to talking Mickey.
Yeah, there are there are people I know that are like like complaining and like
getting free stuff, but I'm much more of like I would send an email later.
I'm not a confrontation.
Yeah, OK. I would do like a public tweet and bash them.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, that's the fastest way for you. Yeah.
You have a lot of followers, so that would certainly get their attention.
The most damage once.
Yes. Just kidding. I'm just kidding.
You wouldn't do that to Disney.
You would do it to some other park.
You would publicly bash SeaWorld on Twitter.
If it came to that, if it came to that, if it came to the Hilton company can take it.
Yeah.
Oh, yes, Mike, a couple.
Yes. On your podcast, which is very good, I recommend everybody if they like figures,
if they like if they like another podcast about people in their 30s
with a very specific interest, I highly recommend your podcast.
You were talking about looking for these specific parks toys,
which I never I didn't know they existed, but they look like the characters
in costume specifically.
So it's Mickey, Minnie, Donald, Goofy and Daisy.
But they look specifically like human beings might be inside them.
Like you would see them in the parks.
Oh, I see what you're saying. Yes.
These look exactly they don't look like cartoon characters.
They look like human proportions.
Daisy and Donald and whatever.
And I just like it.
Maybe I missed it on the show. But is there an update?
Did you finally track these down?
You were looking for a very specific type of them, too.
So I'm looking for the Minnie Mouse.
I do have the rest of them.
The Minnie I don't have.
And I thought I got lucky.
I found the the Tokyo Disneyland version of Minnie, but she's not the same.
It looked exactly the same, but she's on a Tokyo Disneyland stand.
She she's like glued to it.
She won't come off it.
So I can't use that.
I need the the US one.
OK, so you have everyone but Minnie and it's a US specific stand for her.
She's in that same pose where she's got like one leg in the right.
And she's holding her figure.
The figurine is exactly the same.
But on the US ones, they're able to come off their stands.
But on the Tokyo ones, they're they're glued in.
But not only they glued in there, there's like an extra piece
that's like gets them stuck into the stand.
So you couldn't even just like rip it off.
I see because there's like an extra little square peg or something.
So it's really it's really pissed me off because I can't find it.
Matt, I was going to ask, do you have you gone looking for toys
at the Disney character warehouse?
Do you know what those are?
I have not been to that. What is that?
Those are there's two of them in Orlando,
and they are essentially Disney Parks merch outlet malls.
So stuff merch you would find in the parks,
but like heavily discounted and stuff, oddly enough,
not just from the Orlando parks, but like from all over the world.
And when I was reading about it today,
the website Touring Plans does like regular runs
and takes pictures of what is there.
And I'll post this on our Twitter account.
But they were selling some of I like when these come out,
these Disney does like mashup stuff sometimes.
So these are this is goofy as Davey Jones from Pirates of the Caribbean.
And oh, wow. OK.
Donald as Will Turner from Pirates of the Caribbean,
which is Orlando Bloom's character.
And they found them.
They they found at this outlet, they found goofy from the American parks
and then the one they would have sold in either.
I think it they sold in Shanghai.
So you can find some weird stuff at those outlet malls.
It sounds like that's going to be a scary place for your bank account.
If you go there, Matt.
Yeah. See, luckily, I'm very specific when it comes to like,
I can't just get random things.
So if I'm not really looking for something, I might have to just pass on it.
Did you ever did you do you have any of the they haven't made them
in a couple of years, but they're called Park Stars.
I'm not sure. No, I don't have any. What are those exactly?
They're like vinyl mation. I could send you a photo of them.
Oh, I don't do that. I don't do that.
All right. But hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
I know you're thinking you're saying vinyl mation.
I don't like that makeup design with the ears and it painted on because I totally agree.
These are vinyl mation, but they are not the Mickey design.
They are their own unique design, but they're all park specific characters.
And I have six different lines of them.
I'll send you a picture of them to see if there's something
like that you would be interested in.
But I was like kind of down on the vinyl mation in general
because I felt like it was sort of a, you know, it just kind of like
it looked cheap to me here.
I'm sending you on Twitter right now.
I don't know if you can see this is my collection of Park Stars.
But we're talking you got Sunny Eclipse, you got Hitchhiking Ghost.
Oh, wow. You got a Bonable Snowman.
Yeah, this is like this is all the hits.
This is all killer. No filler. Yeah, exactly.
So like orange version.
Cool. Like these I was obsessed with these and it looks like they're not making them anymore,
which is shocking because we haven't gotten some of the classic characters.
I was hoping we'd get John from the Carousel of Progress by the time this whole line was done.
But it looks like they're going to they're going to break my heart and keep it here.
But they obviously from looking at the photo, like you can see,
they got they hit a ton of very ride specific characters.
Carnival, Barker, Potato Head.
You like which one, sorry?
Figment. Oh, yeah. Figment, the Dreamfinder back there.
Yeah, no, it's so I was obsessed with these.
But I yeah, I should stop sending you photos of other toys that you could possibly collect.
I don't I don't. I don't need to do this to you.
I have my girlfriend wants to kill me. I get way too much stuff.
I have pictures. My favorite theme park toy I own, Zachy or Matt.
Whatever we're calling you.
Right. I did.
Do you remember the ride Alien Encounter that used to be at the entrance of Tomorrowland?
Yeah, I loved it.
Yeah, they they sold for a little while.
And my mom surprised me one Christmas with them.
They had action figures of Skippy,
Sir, the robot voice by Tim Curry,
and then Skippy after he was all crisped up.
And and then they had one of the alien of the monster.
And they they came in like tubes like in the ride.
Wow, that is pretty cool.
And I mean, they pop up on eBay every now and then.
But they're like for the time for like late night, they're really detailed.
But they're like to packaging.
I mean, I've taken them out before, but I don't.
They're still at my parents house.
And I never like I'm like, I want to bring them back,
but I don't want to damage getting them back across the country.
Oh, yeah. Do you have any advice for transporting?
Yeah, because you're doing that a lot when you're going to these places
because you go to a lot of different toy stores across the country.
And obviously, you have to ship them back to Orlando.
Right. Well, you might think I'm crazy, but I don't collect things in the box
in the packaging, so I take things out of the box.
So if the package gets damaged, it doesn't bother me.
That's that's the big thing on our podcast.
We say, let them breathe.
We just open them up. Let them.
You get real pissed.
I heard that.
And that as a I have always opened up my toy.
I don't like when I get toys, I don't leave them in the packaging.
But like this one, I'm like, at least this one's kind of cool.
It's kind of like, you know, it is like a base or something. So
is there are there any things you are park specific that you are looking for
other than that many that maybe our listeners might know?
Like why? Because you always talk about certain things
like wrestling wise that you're looking for.
But are there any other sort of like white whales
in the theme park area that you're looking for?
I think right now it's just that that many.
And then, like I said, some of those ceramic figurines,
like I'm always like I found like the the rare rabbit from Splash Mountain.
So I don't know if they made all the other characters or what,
because like eBay is very hit or miss.
Like it's really just what someone wants to put up that week, you know.
So there's no official checklist of every ceramic character.
All the Disney parks made. Right.
So that's I know of at least.
So I'm always interested to find like some obscure
like ceramic characters, because now like I just wanted to have like the Fab Five.
And my mom's she's got me so many that now I'm all in, you know. Sure.
How many do you know about? How many you have?
Probably like 50. Oh, wow. Really?
And luckily, like they're not that expensive on eBay.
They're probably like, you know, the same price they were at the time,
you know, like less than 10 bucks each.
Unless there's like one super duper hard one.
But everything that I found, I found a good price on eBay.
The problem is, is that they're so delicate and that you got that for that.
You have to make sure that they pack it carefully when they're sending it to you.
Right. I had a Jafar come in.
The whole back was cracked off and broke my heart.
Oh, wow. That's sad.
Because like, yeah, those are who knows how many.
A lot of this stuff is not documented on the Internet of what exists.
Like, and I think we didn't talk about this earlier, but
well, the only thing that that I was upset about from your defunct land
interview was that you said you would be OK if the country bears closed forever.
Everything else. OK.
Well, honestly, if pirates closed, I would be upset, but I wouldn't be that upset.
If country bears closed, I would like pick it, I think outside.
Country bears, I'm with because like what's going to take its place?
Just, you know, it's so right, right.
You're throwing me.
Why can't they fix like the clicking noises?
Mm hmm. Good question.
Or is that part of the charge?
Mike, would you be upset if there was no more clicking?
No. Well, you know, this will be interesting because when you finally go to Tokyo,
they have the country bears in Tokyo, but the animatronics are much newer
and cleaner looking.
So there's not the clicking.
There's not there's not a rundown feeling.
Also, the audience is happy to be there as opposed to an Orlando
where they seem like they're like, OK, this will get us out of the hot sun for a while.
But I did one of those after hours events a couple of months ago.
Yeah. And there's not one person in the country, which Embry,
the poor guy outside the podcast members like waving people in.
But nobody wanted to come in to see the show.
He was like a sign spinner, desperately trying to.
Yeah, I felt really bad.
Geez. Yeah.
So so like for the country bears, like, would you still collect country bear toys?
Like, you still like the characters, even though you find the right little rundown?
Yeah, like for instance, if Funko made country bear pops, I'd get him in a heartbeat.
OK, well, that's good.
So you like just you want a newer, hipper country bears.
Just updated a little bit.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, I hear you.
I'm not saying you have to make a whole new show, but like,
get rid of that clicking, like make sure everything's working properly.
No, I don't disagree with that.
Certainly. There's no not taking it out.
You just want to add oil.
Yeah, it's fixed up a little bit.
Yeah, no, I agree with that.
Wait, I have a question, which I'm confused by the difference between
you're into Funko, but you're not into vinylmation.
How what's how do you how do you explain that difference?
Why is why does Funko work and not found a mission for you?
Well, like like the vinylmation, they're all like the Mickey
Head, which I don't like, first of all.
And I like the Funko pop.
No, no, no. The Funko pops with what really
well, that when I first realized what they were, I'm a big Ghostbuster collector.
So I found these Ghostbuster toys, which happen to be Funko.
Oh, these are pretty cool.
I mean, look up, you know, who makes these blah blah blah.
And I'm like, oh, this company makes Star Wars and they make Ninja Turtles.
And it turns out they make everything.
This was like five years ago.
Now they really make everything and everything that you like, you can collect.
And it's all as one, you know, it's all as one line.
It's not like you have like the Ninja Turtle action figure
and your Ghostbuster was a little bit taller, a little skinnier.
You know, it's everything is uniform.
And I love that. Oh, sure. Got you. Got you.
Were you a fan of that?
Did you get to do that Ghostbusters show in Orlando when you were a kid?
Oh, I loved it.
Ghostbusters is my absolute favorite movie of all time.
And I love that show.
And I still think if you watch it, the YouTube video of the show,
I still think it holds up.
Potentially better than what that's been a weird spot with Twister
and Jimmy Fallon, like they might.
Oh, it might not be crazy to to say maybe they should have left
Ghostbusters as is or kept plus in it up.
Jimmy Fallon sucks.
Yeah. Well, as you know, our Jimmy Fallon policy.
Not the person. Not the person.
No, no, no. That's exactly our Jimmy Fallon policy is because
politically, as we work in the comedy world, we feel as though we should not say
that ride is odd and dumb and bad and relies on the same universal tricks
that they use on every ride.
We don't say that. Right.
I hate it.
I refuse to do it.
I have to say this.
Yeah, you have less to lose.
So yes, please, please say please say it.
All right. So, Matt, usually to wrap up sometimes when we're doing
like a specific ride, we'll ask the guest what they think on a scale of
should we keep a ride at same as is.
Should we plus it up or should we burn it to the ground?
But since we didn't do a specific one, I was thinking we could do a lightning round
with Magic Kingdom rides with you.
Yeah. And we're going to rip through them.
So there's three choices for all the us.
I'll just list the Magic Kingdom rides and you will basically just say,
keep as is, plus it up or burn it to the ground for insurance money.
And you can shorten all of those.
So there's three choices.
OK, so we got the game.
I got it. So I'm just going to rip through all the attractions
at Walt Disney World's Magic Kingdom.
Astral Orbiter.
So are you going to burn it to the ground?
All right. Burn it to the ground. Got it.
The Barnstormer. Burn it to the ground.
Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
Uh, keep it as you know what? Spice up a little bit.
OK, plus it up. Plus it up, plus it up, plus it up.
But I still like it. I still like it a lot.
I hear you. Buzz Lightyear Space Rangers spin.
Ah, maybe I plus it up a little bit.
It's still cool, but I think it needs some updating.
OK, I agree.
Casey Junior Splash and Soak Station.
I don't even know what that is. I don't either.
Keep moving. Pass, pass.
Country Bear Jamboree.
Plus it up. OK, Dumbo, the Flying Elephant.
Keep it as is. OK.
The Hall of Presidents.
Burn to the ground.
Those are fighting where people are going to come
after you on Twitter now. Haunted Mansion.
Plus it up just a little bit. OK, it's a small world.
Let me just let me backtrack for a second.
OK, sure. For Haunted Mansion.
So like when they added all like the
like the animated faces on like a lot of the characters
and stuff like that, the tombstone, you know, I'm talking about. Yeah, yeah.
It's it's like so like 2000 ish bad CGI.
Right, you know, they need to fix it up a little bit.
It looks dated. A dicey time for theme parks.
No theme park should have done anything in the early 2000s
because it's all it's all bad now.
Anything that was done in that era.
You know exactly what I'm talking about.
I'm not crazy, right? No, no, we get it.
It doesn't age 90s CGI is better than 2000 CGI.
Right, right. Yeah. OK, good.
OK, Jungle Cruise.
Oh, boy. Plus it up.
OK, Mad Tea Party.
This tea cups.
Let's keep it. Sure. Hey, wait, Jungle Cruise, are you into
there's rumors of like the rock is on the ride.
Is that a good idea or bad idea to you?
I mean, I just did Jingle Cruise the other night
and I trust me, I love like the skippers and I love like the jokes.
And I love like some of the stuff is just so like the animatronics
are so old and oh, man, but I get it. It's a classic.
It's a classic.
So they're going to plus it up a little bit.
I'd be I'd be interested in seeing what they did.
So maybe some scary animatronics like they actually seem like they're
lunging at you or there's there's threats in the jungle.
Well, I mean, I did it the other it was at night.
But like you could barely see anything in the dark.
I think they just need to like and better lighting.
Or they can fix it.
Yeah, I don't I don't disagree with that.
Yeah, no, I'm on board with this.
All these opinions thus far.
All right. Back to the game.
Many adventures of Winnie the Pooh.
Keep it. All right.
We're at the end.
I'm going to go put on a cup of coffee.
No, no, there's only a few left.
I hope there's not a lot of Z's.
Mickey's PhilharMagic.
I haven't seen it in a while, but I can only assume that it is outdated.
So plus it up or burn to the ground.
I'll say I'll touch you and judge on that.
I'm going to say plus it up.
But the screen is so dim, like, come on, like brighten the screen up for that 3D.
It hurts the eyes if it's not that bright.
That's me, though.
Monsters, Inc. Laugh floor.
I just did it the other night.
Amazing. Really?
What? I've never.
I don't know anything.
I've never heard like a strong opinion either way.
They say that this that one's bad.
I don't think I've done it in a long time.
I feel like I've done it twice in my life.
And like I did it once and I I really, really liked it.
I did it again like two nights ago.
It's amazing.
So keep as is.
Listeners told us to like you got to reconsider Monsters Inc.
life. All right. We got to reconsider that.
Peter Pan.
They're like real, like real jokes and like they interact with the audience.
And it's great.
You didn't get like roasted by a monster, did you?
No, I did not.
But now I know where to sit to get right.
I realize they're only picking people like in the middle, like.
So I got to I got to make a better seat.
Gotcha. Good tip.
All right, Peter Pan.
I keep it as a classic. Sure.
Pirates.
Oh, yeah.
I see. Oh, I'm not.
I would never say burn it down.
Maybe maybe plus it up a little bit.
OK, sure. Seven.
Maybe you guys can help me with this.
I don't know. There's a lot of people.
There was all the story of pirates is this story of pirates is that.
I've been on that ride probably 50 times my throughout my life.
I don't know what's going on.
What's the story here? OK.
So here's they've done a thing at Disneyland recently.
They took out the mist and that bad like projection on the mist
to tie in with the pirates.
And they've done a really interesting thing.
I feel like they've put a little it's stationary,
but it's like a skeleton slash human like man.
So when you're going through the skeleton part with all the pirates
have their riches, you go by this like figure and it first looks like
it's a skeleton.
But as you go, like it kind of turns into a man.
And then you're out in the place with the ships
and shooting cannonballs at each other.
So I feel like it's trying to transition and say, hey, look at all these pirates.
Look what they look what they did and look what they stole.
And they all died just like, you know, scared or like worried
that their treasure was going to get taken.
Now we'll see what they were like in the hit and like back in time.
This is what started all of this.
So it's not like a very strong story, but they're trying to like
paint a picture of like we're going back in time.
And it's much clearer now, I feel like, at Disneyland than it is at Disney World.
OK, then I'll have to check it out next time.
You want to? That covers it.
I mean, also, though, there's like pirates and they're hammered
and they're chasing women and burning a city down the city.
This story isn't like so strong.
But I don't know.
And then they just put Johnny Depp in there whenever they could, right?
Well, yeah, and then I think they fucked up the story
probably by adding Captain Jack Sparrow,
because now it doesn't really make any sense.
Well, because that's what Disneyland, they got rid of the mist,
because I think they were trying to get rid of some of the movie stuff.
I don't know. I never saw the movie, so.
No. Yeah.
Jack Sparrow's in a bucket and then he's leaning out from behind a post.
And then he has all the world's treasure.
Very clear story.
It is funny that there are like all of these animatronics
concerned with plundering and pillaging.
And then there's like two next to Johnny Depp who are like,
I'm concerned about Captain Jack Sparrow.
Only some of the characters know who he is.
Yeah, he hasn't gotten he hasn't met everybody in town. Right.
He's working his way around.
Yeah. All right.
Back to the game. Seven Dwarfs, Mind Train.
Oh, keep it as is. I love it.
Yeah, that's good. Space Mountain.
Man, I wish it was
the Disneyland one is way better.
I wish it would spice up a little bit.
OK, plus it up. Splash Mountain.
Is it?
Maybe just clean up the animatronics a little bit.
So plus it up.
OK. Swiss Family Treehouse.
God, get rid of it. Burn it to the ground.
Tomorrowland Speedway.
Burn it to the ground. Oh, yeah.
And what a space waster.
Exactly. Yes. Love this.
I'm very curious about this one.
Tomorrowland Transit Authority People Mover.
I love it. Keep it. Oh, nice.
Good answer.
A little journey of the Little Mermaid.
Love it. Keep it.
Carousel Progress.
Burn it. Get out of here.
Oh, finally, you lost me. Tiki Room.
You know what?
I don't think I've done it in either park, so I don't know.
Oh, OK.
I just know it's a lot of clicking birds.
And then the last thing I'll ask, Liberty Square River Boat.
You ever got a boat?
I've never I've never done it.
So, OK, it seems silly to burn the boat.
That's the way it looks. Nice.
It looks nice. Yeah.
Yeah. You keep it.
It's not it's not hurting anybody.
Hey, how about in advance the Tron coaster?
Oh, man, I don't know.
Oh, really? Skeptical.
I'm not super excited about a ride that's already somewhere else.
So it's already outdated about a movie I've never seen.
It's not popular in the United States.
I don't know.
That's a film with like the the the plot is even thinner than the ride.
Pirates of the Caribbean.
I don't think you need to know the story of Tron.
It's pretty lights. It's neon.
It looks cool to me. Yeah, it looks cool.
I think it'll be great. I think you'll dig it.
I think it but that train shut down for a while because of the coaster.
So no, no train rides for you in the near future.
Well, I mean, listen, the train ride is boring, first of all.
So what it is, you have to look at.
Yeah. Yeah, that's true.
But like this Tron, this this goes is coming in.
Like I said, it's going to be outdated already while Universal's
building this like state of the art, you know, Harry Potter coaster.
It's going to blow it away.
Hmm. I don't know.
We'll see. I think there's going to be more robots on the Harry Potter one.
So I will have an edge maybe in that area. That's better.
So I guess you probably are onto something there.
But I think you're underestimating Tron.
Have you watched the ride through video of it, though?
It looks great.
I'm not saying it's not good.
I'm just saying by the time it gets here, like I think it'll be a little outdated.
Well, we'll see. Yeah, we will.
I mean, even if it was in the park today, it's an old ride.
It's already a couple of years old.
Well, but maybe it's a newer version. We don't know.
We don't know if they've updated it for we don't know what they've.
Supposedly that Ratatouille ride going in Epcot is going to be like a slightly
newer version of the one that's in Paris. So who knows?
I hope so. All right.
We want Tron in California and we want Autopia gone.
We want maybe submarines go whatever it takes.
We're like submarines got to go.
Yeah, we are on the same page.
Totally agree.
Maybe easier for, you know, people in their 30s to say.
But I don't know what kids are that into the submarine or the Autopia.
I mean, I love Nemo, but that's it sucks.
That submarine thing is the worst.
It just takes so much time.
You're so crammed in there.
Oh, forget it. Yeah, forget it.
Burn it to the ground. All right.
Well, with that, Matt Cordona, Zach Ryder, you've survived podcast the ride.
Yeah, I made it.
Hey, what plug away your podcast.
Anything else you want to talk about?
You guys are doing a toy drive, I believe, for the holidays.
Oh, yeah. So we're doing a first major
wrestling podcast jobs every Friday, wherever you get your podcast.
We're doing this major recipe or toy drive.
It actually ends this Tuesday, December 11th.
But you can still order it whenever you want.
Any wrestling toy from ringside collectibles.com and just use the
I don't have the address that I need to put in here, but it's like Google it.
Do it on Google, the creative pro wrestling address, and they will void the shipping.
And that's Kurt Hawkins.
My partner is wrestling school.
And we'll just pick up the toys. We'll donate them.
So you don't have to go to the post office or mail.
Yeah. So, yeah, just just listen to the major recipe podcast on Twitter.
At Zach Ryder, Instagram, Z Ryder, 85.
You'll find me, I guess.
You know what?
You'll find me.
Yeah.
If you like toys and you're constantly I feel like I was looking at your live
Instagram story and you were at the parade, I believe, what a couple of days ago.
Yes, yes.
So, yeah, if you like theme park content, follow this man.
Follow all of his accounts.
Yeah.
And I just like to say, having talked to you for a bit, I'm so
the fact that I don't know what you will end up doing tomorrow.
But if, in fact, you go to a hot topic to get an Oliver and Company toy and that you
could potentially go to the world's largest McDonald's or that toy warehouse
that Jason talked about and then you could go to Disney Springs, you could go to the
boathouse, you could hit all the parks in a day just Ubering all the way.
You've made me very jealous of your life,
of the possible day you could wake up and have tomorrow.
And I just want to say Godspeed and enjoy that Orlando life.
Thank you very much.
I know you guys are the kind of guys I would love to do a park day with,
because when I go, I'm always like the tour guide.
I'm always the guy dropping knowledge on people.
I would love to follow someone around,
follow their schedule and have someone point things out to me.
You know, sure.
Maybe one day we'll do that.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Yeah, we'll go out here.
Yeah, we'll go to Carthay Circle Lounge.
We'll do the best.
You got to get one of those like the rainbow shot at the Carthay Circle.
I have not done the shot.
I've done the Mickey's Funwheel drink at the Cove Bar, but that's not a shot.
But it is like a big rainbow drink.
But I think you're talking about something different.
It's like it's like a row of shots and it's like all different colors of the rainbow.
Oh, wow. I will do that.
This is my dream.
I'm the rainbow drink guy of the three of us.
Yeah, I don't know exactly what it's called,
but I've gotten it at the Carthay Circle a couple of times.
Yeah, OK, I got to do that.
Yeah, I have the transformer at the Sheridan Bar at Universal, which is multicolored.
So any time it's multicolored, I'm in.
So we will you'll come out here and we will all do multicolored shots at Carthay.
I love it.
Incredible. Great.
So, yeah, thank you again for doing this.
And I appreciate it.
Yeah, we'll see.
We'll we'll see you later.
We'll see you out here, I guess, in Anaheim.
All right. Take around the rainbow.
Let's do it.
Thanks so much.
Thanks. All right.
Thank you.
Right.
OK, and there you have it.
Zach Ryder, that was blessed.
Not as controversial really as we were like he really falls in line more.
He's just honestly he really all it comes down to is that it's like
he wants the robots to be new and fresh and he wants the park to be up
like a lot more upkeep in the name.
How can disagree with that?
Yeah, I mean, they do let Orlando, you know,
it takes a while to for stuff to change there because the majority of people
are going maybe every year, every other year, every 10 years.
So like you can let it go a little longer.
Just oil big, I'll snout a little more is what basically we're getting to,
which Jason wouldn't want big, I'll snout when I bring that up.
Oh, sure. No, he's big boy.
Do it as much as you want.
Oil that snout up.
That's weird.
So for oil that snout up,
T-shirts go to our T-public for more info on us and the podcast.
Go to our Twitter at podcast, the right our Instagram.
Check out our Facebook group.
Visit podcast, the ride, the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast.
The ride.
What else?
And yeah, check out check out Zach's stuff.
Oil that snout.
Well, oil that snout.
Hashtag oil that snout.
Bye. Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.