5, 4, 3, 2, 1...
Cast the ride, the second gate.
And we're here today and I'm not gonna lie,
we're a bunch of freaks today.
Yeah, he call us the terrifying triad.
Yeah.
Mike's Mike, Scott and Jason, my kind of guys.
Oh yeah.
Couple of freaks ready to get the freak on
behind a paywall.
That's devilishly greedy.
That voice is Scott Gardner, I'm Jason Sheridan.
Mike Carlson also here.
Hey, also doing the voice.
His trademark hey.
Maniac Mike.
Who's also like a DJ for a local radio station,
but he's also in the, what was it?
Terrible triad or whatever that is.
He's in the terrible triad.
Oh yeah, let's go terrible triad, sure.
What did you say?
I think I might say terrifying, but I think terrible
has a nicer clip to it.
Because sinister and terrible.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think those kind of match.
So in case you don't know what we're doing,
you didn't read the headline.
We are talking today about just the David Letterman
performance of the Spider-Man Turn Off the Dark song,
A Freak Like Me Needs Company,
written by Bono and the Edge.
Yay.
I haven't been so excited about a topic maybe ever.
Yeah.
I've been so excited to talk about this,
and I think we're probably all in the same area
where this thing happened in 2011.
But I think, I know I watch it perhaps quarterly,
perhaps every quarter since then.
Oh, for sure, yeah.
And I can say without a doubt
that Mike would have sent this to me pretty quickly.
Like day after airing quickly,
he would have sent it to me and some other people,
saying you gotta watch this.
Yeah.
I felt very lucky because I watched this air live.
I didn't tune in specifically to see it,
but I happened to put it on right before it all went down.
But it also made me crazy
because I had no one to talk to about it.
Like I just, I felt like I hallucinated it.
I'm alone at night just staring at my TV on the couch
and like, what the hell?
And then it didn't really blow up immediately.
But I remember I was working in the Funny or Die basement
with a lot of fun weirdos you heard on the show.
A lot of them, all your favorite freaks
from the world of podcast.
Imagine a kooky basement where both Nick Weiger
and Bugmane shared cubicle space.
But it was such a big hit in that basement,
like a week or so later.
It took a little delay.
We talked about it nonstop.
And I think it spread a lot through this little scene
in comedy world.
If I'm correct, I wanna say our friend Eva Anderson
wrote or was like largely responsible for the tribute
to it on Comedy Bang Bang.
Oh yeah.
They did it with Tom Lennon.
They did kind of a quick little, like he was the phantom,
but he transmogrified essentially
into the Green Goblin for one song.
So it's like- The hammy Green Goblin.
The hammiest Green Goblin, far hammier than Willem Dafoe
or who would it have been in the-
Chris Cooper, I believe was gonna be the Green Goblin,
but he died.
They killed him off in the second round of Spider-Man movies.
Oh, okay.
And then Dan Don was the Green Goblin
cause it was his son.
Right.
That's, you know.
So, but the point is, all right, before we go-
We're watching this by the way on loop in the background
and the lizard just came in and I totally forgot
what is like the Kurt Connors, like part of him looks like.
The lizard looks like that inflatable T-Rex costumes
that are like popular at Halloween
or like I saw a marching band have a bunch of them
like recently in a YouTube clip,
but this is years before those inflatable Halloween costumes.
When it was like- Yes, now they're everywhere,
but they, when you see those costumes,
know that they were pioneered by Broadway legend,
Julie Taymor.
Yeah.
That's the thing about this that's so crazy,
like the level that knowing the budget,
is stated in the performance.
It's a $65 million circus tragedy.
Actually more like 75, he says, because that is true.
It ended up alluding to the cost of 75.
And for those of you who aren't Broadway heads,
the average cost of a musical on Broadway
is five to 15 million.
Really?
Yeah.
That's the differential?
I'm sure things like King Kong that is currently running
or about to start running with the giant King Kong,
I'm sure that cost a little more,
but this is a notorious catastrophe
in the history of Broadway.
Yeah, yeah.
And so if, all right, if you haven't seen this performance,
first of all, we should have it in the show notes
or you can just go to YouTube and I think the full,
just type in Spider-Man, A Freak Like Me
Needs Company, David Letterman, and you will find it.
Yeah.
Because we're as, once again,
we're not talking about the full show,
Spider-Man Turn Up the Dark,
we're talking about this wonderful performance
where the Green Goblin, due to some very lax security
on the David Letterman show,
the Green Goblin bursts into the Ed Sullivan Theater
and takes it over and engulfs it in his freakiness.
And also, they should note,
this is an exclusive version of this song.
The original cast recording of this song
is just the start of the song and the end of the song.
He doesn't stop in the middle of the song
in the Broadway play and introduce these characters, right?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, he does.
Oh, yes, he does, yes.
Okay, so you've tuned it for the soundtrack.
Yeah, I saw the, I've seen it.
I saw it on Broadway.
Oh, I forgot that you saw it.
I saw it.
You saw it like a month after this.
Is it that soon?
This aired in July, 2011.
Oh, I guess I did.
And we were in New York together in August, 2011.
Yeah, you're right.
And I saw it alone.
No one would go with me.
No one would go.
Richie went with me, my friend,
and he all of a sudden bailed on me
because I was like, I'm gonna try at the last second
to get Spider-Man tickets.
And I did, I walked up to the box.
I was going in there like,
well, are $29 tickets that are a little view obstructed?
Is that okay?
And I was like, of course,
that's the perfect way to see this.
And I just went in alone.
It was raining, I was soaking wet.
And I loved, I enjoyed the whole thing so much.
I was in the top part of the theater,
right by where Spider-Man would come down and swing.
He doesn't get really up close to you.
I've been watching footage.
They're way up in the third balcony
and he would jump and swing down.
That's pretty crazy.
I mean, there was, see, it does seem like they pulled off
a legitimately amazing show at times
and the sets were amazing and some costumes were amazing.
Yeah.
It's just something about the way it all added up
on the Slenderman performance.
So here, I think, I mean, watch the performance certainly,
but let me just, let's just play the tiniest taste of it
before we talk for much longer.
Get your free.
I'm fine.
That's about all we need.
As long as you know, General Tenor,
he broke into The Letterman Show,
and he is the scariest freak of all time.
Do you know why he says that at the start?
No.
Because there was a break-in at the Ed Sullivan Theater
not long before that.
What?
Some crazy guy broke into the Ed Sullivan Theater,
so he comes in and like, I'll tie it into theme parks,
makes a topical joke.
That's why I go, this place is surprisingly,
easy to break into.
It was a reference to a real person
that broke into the Ed Sullivan Theater.
No idea, wow.
I've learned something before he's even gotten in the door.
This is great.
Yeah, the budget is a topical reference thing too.
I think the one thing that's missing
is that he didn't say, everyone be careful on this stairs,
we don't need another injury.
The scariest villain of all is the worker's comp man.
Yeah, in total six people were injured
while working on Spider-Man,
and at least one of them was injured twice.
People get injured, come back,
get injured again, and then leave.
So this show fraught with peril,
extremely expensive as the Goblin himself mentions,
and giant story problems.
It was horribly reviewed by the New York Times
and all the major Broadway press,
and they shut the whole thing down,
and in fact, this song, Freak Like Me Needs Company,
was part of the revamped version
of Spider-Man Turn Off the Dark 2.0.
This is one of the big additions.
So this is late in the game,
and an attempt at an enhancement of a troubled show.
Also, to contextualize it,
this was the second Spider-Man Turn Off the Dark performance
on David Letterman within six months.
The first one was the song Rise Above,
which, did that get cut from the original?
No, no, it was in there.
It was like the centerpiece, I think, of the show.
Well, Boy Falls from the Sky also, you could say.
I think Boy Falls from the Sky is probably the best song.
I would say this is the best song by a mile.
At some level, yes.
Okay, yeah.
I think Boy Falls from the Sky is like,
sort of like, by the numbers, you too,
and this is at least something.
This is something.
Well, some of the other songs,
like Boy Falls from the Sky,
you can feel the Bono and Edge influence in it very strongly.
This, there is such a disconnect between the Bono.
I disagree completely with that.
I think that Bono and the Edge,
if you are into the U2, Pop Mart, and Zuroba,
and Octong Baby eras, this is right in that wheelhouse.
You're right that it's like the normal U2, Bono,
that's not what this is.
But as a non-encyclopedic U2 non-fan, I guess,
I just, I don't listen to them or not listen to them.
I don't, whatever, either way.
But yeah, I was not aware of that evil characters
doing hijinks is part of the U2 mythology in general.
We're talking, of course, about Bono's alter ego,
Mr. McFisto,
who is a man with a white painted face and devil ears.
And a gold sparkly suit.
Gold sparkly suit.
And fancy shoes that he shows off.
And he's not gruff like the Green Goblin,
he's kind of this lascivious,
he has so many feels that he just has to whine.
But I think that is who,
I think you could see Mr. McFisto
leading the Sinister Six in this is what I'm saying.
Absolutely.
He is very much in that,
this is what he, first of all,
this is what he thinks super villains and heroes are.
And I think it's evidenced if you,
I was doing karaoke two nights ago,
and this is unrelated to,
I wasn't thinking of this when I was doing it,
but I put on the song,
Hold Me, Thrill Me, Kiss Me, Kill Me,
which is from Batman Forever, which is U2.
And it's such a,
it's the first part of this song in my head.
It's a little bit more U2 sounding,
but it's very much in line with his attitude
about characters.
And really, when we get down to it,
he's just treating these characters like,
they're weirdo art people from New York.
That's who we're all just trying to.
I'm not a bad guy.
I'm just a little cuck,
I'm a cuck and I have cucky ideas.
The collection of people they assembled to make this,
Julie Taymor, Bono,
and the way they talked about it,
all of them talked about it.
It's like, well, it's like rock and Broadway
and a circus and wrestling.
It is very much the way regular people think,
fancy rich people talk about art.
But it's about Spider-Man.
It's about the most everyday working man superhero.
Well, and primarily to me,
with all the buildup and all the expense
and all the pretension and the level of,
Bono, Edge, Julie Taymor,
all of them beyond just revered professionals.
They are like gods to be in these fields.
And then you see it,
especially if you don't know nothing else about the show
and then you watch just this Letterman performance,
you're like, how did all of them add up
to Spider-Man rocks at Universal Studio?
It just is, it is so similar to the dumb show
which we reviewed many, many episodes ago.
But like, there's no, this is,
it's broad theme parky, bright colors,
no texture, no nuance.
And not a good, like Pop by U2 is an album people don't like.
I like half of Pop and it's,
the songs feel so much more sophisticated than this.
It's so, like, especially go on Spotify
and listen to the recorded version of it.
It is so tinny.
It sounds like the fakest, flattest garage band hip hop.
And Jason, you're talking about personnel of this thing.
Let me add a couple more on to this list.
The, it was produced,
this track was produced by Steve Lillywhite.
Produced all of the main, he's U2's primary producer.
He produced all the Dave Matthews bands,
like the big Dave Matthews band albums and songs.
He produced for Peter Gabriel, Psychedelic Furs,
Rolling Stones, The Pogues, XTC's song,
Making Plans for Nigel and a Freak Like Me Needs Company.
He, but because he was not like a rap guy
and they wanted to bring kind of a street influence
to the thing.
They did, there was additional drum programming
by a guy named Shay Taylor.
Shay Taylor produced Frank Ocean's Think About,
Thinking About You, Think About You,
Beyonce's Love on Top, Great Song,
and a lot of Neo records.
So they had a legitimate- So all of these hit makers,
all of these hit makers are here and-
It sounds like I could make a quality recording
in an afternoon on Garage Band
that sounded exactly the quality of the record,
the official cast recording of that song.
Yeah, it's so thin, so tinny.
It's inexplicable to me.
And then let me also build up the scene,
how I feel lucky the way I got to experience this thing
that before several commercial breaks,
before the Green Goblin did his immortal burst
into that Sullivan Theater doors,
it was an entire Bono and Edge episode of David Letterman.
They were on the couch and they told stories
about all of the amazing humanitarian work that Bono does.
And they talked about the tradition,
about Andrew Lloyd Webber and Tin Pan Alley
and to partake in this tradition and then-
Not for a ball ball.
God damn it, I'm getting mad just hearing-
I know, I know.
And then they talk about their songwriting process
and they talk about building up the song
that I do like, the song Stuck in a Moment,
You Can't Get Out of It.
And the Edge pulls out an acoustic guitar
and they perform the stirring acoustic,
the lights come down, it's this wonderful acoustic,
you two such a gigantic band
and seeing this intimate performance,
which they explain in a lengthy setup
that the song was written about the death of Michael Hutchins,
the singer of NXS, a tragic, awful death.
So all of this humanitarian work,
the death of Michael Hutchins, Tin Pan Alley,
Andrew Lloyd Webber and then, all right,
we'll be right back with the cast of Spider-Man
Turn Off the Dark and then, well,
New York City, Angel Briega.
The other thing, I mean, this,
there's a lot of conflicting emotions
because I do like this, I think on the level,
I'm sure you guys probably, there's a level,
you like it dubbed like, look at this spectacle,
what is this, this expensive monstrosity?
As a comics fan, I'm horrified.
Oh, I see, that's it.
Oh, no, that's, no, I couldn't disagree with that more.
What do you mean?
No, this is nonsense.
This is great, like 60s, it's not the quality of 60s Batman.
No, do not, it invokes 60s Batman.
Nonsense. How dare you?
But this is, comics have so much trash associated with them.
I'm just saying, like, this shouldn't make you that upset.
There's so much great comics trash that you and I like.
I mean, I get, my thing, I think is like,
why does the Green Goblin,
I like the Green Goblin outfit best of all.
Everything else looks like weird walk around characters
from a theme park or like inflatable mini Macy's table.
Like, they have the money
and they have the costuming know how to make.
Here's my point.
Okay. Here's my point.
There's a version of like a much more serious
Spider-Man musical where the Green Goblin comes out
and he's wearing like, I don't know,
maybe a little bit less of a goofy outfit.
And he sings like a serious Green Goblin song.
And I just, there's no way to pull that off.
There's no way that's gonna be good.
No, no, that would be bad in the other direction.
That's like, I think saying like,
Batman and Robin is a movie is bad,
which it is bad, but it's great.
It's fantastic.
But it's bad.
This is bad, but it's fantastic.
Batman Forever is like closer to,
if you're like flipping a coin,
like a two-faced coin,
the Batman Forever lands, I think,
more on the side of good bad
and Batman and Robin's like, all right.
Yeah, for sure.
I agree with that.
But also it's fantastic in the way that this is fantastic
because it's just so bad.
I just realized a swarm,
a man made of mutant bees just came out
and I just realized a bee fell off his suit
as he jumped out.
Yes, one of the best things.
And that you're hearing about the Julie Taymor level
of detail and artistry.
And then immediately a bee falls off of the bee man.
The first villain who comes out.
These are clearly inspired by like the heightened puppetry
and costuming of The Lion King.
Sure.
But it just looks so bizarre.
Like, K's are, not K's are, Craven the Hunter looks so odd.
They look different.
They look like they're in different universes too.
All I'm saying is this is glorious trash.
Yes.
And I would much rather have glorious trash
than like those amazing Spider-Man movies,
those second round of Spider-Man movies
that were very boring and flat.
Well, I think they got it wrong too.
A lot of the Steve Ditko designed original Sinister Six,
there's a reason in the comics
the costumes have changed very little since the 60s.
And the stuff that's kind of a let that,
like the Spider-Man movies,
it's always like, well, we got to put them in a trench coat
and then Spider-Man outfit has to have a lot of,
superhero outfits now always have a lot of bubble.
Like, why do they all look like?
Scales.
Scales, yeah.
It drives me nuts in superhero.
Like, why didn't just give them latex or leather?
I don't know, but it-
So they don't slip by a pool.
I guess that's true.
They need a track show.
It's, let me say what I think is,
I think absolutely the song itself is defendable.
I think the costumes are defendable.
I think the Green Goblin costume
and performance are dependable.
But here I think is really where it tilts is that you win.
We should also maybe kind of go through this chronologically
a little bit, but when the Green Goblin bursts in the door
and there's a, it's green lit,
there's a bunch of green smoke.
It's going to bloop back around here in a minute
in the video we're watching, the backup dancers.
Oh yeah, yeah.
These people who lean really close to camera
with their broad Broadway makeup and costumes.
These guys, they're the original B boys from hell.
All right, stay away from this crew.
All right, there's like dyed green hair.
It was like, you know, silver makeup smeared,
like not carefully applied.
They don't care about careful makeup applications.
We just splash it in our face.
They're like the dancers from the horny number
in all that jazz ran head first into the cast of hackers.
And then this came out.
Beautiful, wow, yeah.
That is a good way to put it.
I was just going to say, he's got it in flannel.
They were like wearing flannel shirts
and like cheap tank tops.
The women doing the scary faces, like making jazz hands
and going, ha, that's, that, that.
Some of the costumes are just a green hat tilted to the side.
They don't care about traditional hat directions.
I'll put my brim where I want.
And then some of them are literally,
some of these people are just a girl with a green scrunchie
and kind of like a green and black workout outfit.
And that makes her evil.
Yeah, it's weird.
She's bad now.
It is weird, yeah.
It makes everything feel cheap.
That is the thing that makes it feel cheap.
If they were all dressed like,
oh, they're like green goblin henchmen,
which I don't believe henchmen,
I don't believe he ever had those in the comics, right?
It's kind of like heavy.
It just kind of like goons.
It's like heavy goons.
But if there were like thugs, in a way, yeah,
that would be better.
But yes, they look like they ran out of money
and they were like, just go to the Rite Aid
and see if there's some tank tops
and hats on the shelf there.
Somehow.
I think a lot of, again, I love this as spectacle,
but some of my resistance,
it's coming from the fact that it's such a hodgepodge,
it's not quite comics, it's not quite rock and roll,
it's not quite even Broadway.
It's theme parks.
That's why we're talking about it.
That's all that is.
I guess that is, looking at it from that lens,
it makes 100% sense.
Maybe it's like, okay, we think that that Aladdin show
that was at California Adventure for a long time
where the genie tells silly topical jokes,
that is what it is.
You know what you're getting when you go in there.
I'll have fun, I'll laugh at it.
It's silly, but let's have a good time.
But if you found out that the score was written
by Loudon Wainwright or Leonard Cohen or somebody,
and that it took them eight years to land on
the genie making a slap chop joke.
I think it's the balance of, if this just was,
if they let it just be purely this is dumb and silly,
but the fact that there's that Bono pretension
makes you have to judge it more carefully.
The Taymor pretension, even more so.
It seems like Taymor's pretension outweighs Bono's pretension
by like 20, I don't know, 20%.
And she also, she bailed too.
No, she got fired.
Yeah, yeah.
She got out of there somehow.
She bailed when they made her bail.
Yeah, and there's an interview where Bono says,
I think she was there the whole time,
and I think we were in and out because we were on tour
and we'd come back and we'd see obvious problems,
and I think they were less obvious to her.
And that's what this whole thing feels like.
When you go to a super wide shot of all of the freaks
crying around and punch in the air,
you're like, how did no anyone with an outside perspective
could have said, you just made Spider-Man rocks?
You all of this work and seven years of effort
and playwriting got you to this.
Some of the other people involved in this,
a listener sent us that Glenn Berger,
who co-wrote the book, which the book,
in a Broadway musical is what the script is called.
He wrote a book about the musical called Song of Spider-Man,
the inside story of the most controversial musical
in Broadway history.
Which I believe I have Scott's copy of upstairs.
No, no, no, you gave it back to me.
Oh, I did, okay good.
But I brought it back here.
Oh, good, all right, leave it here then.
I will, yes.
I brought bookmarks of relevant passages.
Have you read all of it?
I did read all of it.
Is it good?
I think Glenn Berger has a pretty slanted view
of how it played out and I think the book
is entirely an effort to show that at every step,
he's like, see I knew, I knew this was gonna happen
and I was right, I was right.
I tried to make this better but they wouldn't let me.
First like big gig, right?
Like he's written kids cartoon, was this like his first?
I'm not sure, let's read his author bio.
Well, he wrote the play underneath the lintel
and oh lovely glow worm and yes, he wrote for Arthur on PBS
and then the most damning thing in the author bio,
Glenn spent six years co-writing the script of Spider-Man.
Wow.
Turn off the dark, six years of your life goes to that.
Guy brought in the last few months to help fix it
is Roberto, I'm gonna massacre this last name,
Aguirre Sacasa who now makes,
is the person who makes the most sense
working on this piece, he had written a bunch
of Marvel comics, he was also a playwright
and he's written, he wrote on Big Love and Looking
and he wrote the script for the recent Carrie remake.
He is the current chief creative officer for RT Comics
and executive producer of Riverdale
and Chilling Adventures of Sabrina.
Whoa.
Like he oversees those things.
This lineup is so stacked.
The credits of this group for bonkers
and not to mention the man who plays the Green Goblin,
Patrick Page is a Broadway luminary,
I don't have the list offhand but I believe
he essentially ended up in this because I think
he was the Grinch on Broadway and it's a similar role.
He's green.
Yeah, he's a green villain.
Was he Scar or am I mixing my thing up?
Oh, I think he was maybe Scar.
I think he was Scar.
But a very well respected actor, I have no complaints.
I think he's fun as well.
He's great.
And he's having fun.
I think I saw him, I'm sure I probably did.
He did topical jokes also during the show.
Man, what did he do?
He did a Shakeweight joke.
Yes.
He was like, had picked up some device and he was like,
it's like a Shakeweight or something and big laugh.
And then the show had to stop too because a Spider-Man got
tangled up in a wire.
The one you went to?
Oh my god.
Nobody fell and broke their leg.
It's just like a guy flew from the balcony, swung onto the
stage and then got caught on the side.
And then there was a pause.
And then it was like, Spider-Man will resume in five minutes.
Like a theme park.
Yes.
And then when Green Goblin has a thing where he's at a piano
for some reason.
So he's playing like, we'll have to stop the show if something
goes wrong.
He was ad libbing.
Whoa.
So it was full theme park.
He would cover if shit happened?
Yeah.
So he was great.
I think at that point, after that many concussions and leg
injury, like they were probably had a million alternative plans
in place.
I mean, I got to say the interesting thing to me, like all
the bad reviews and stuff were because as soon as preview
started, all the critics rushed to see it, which is an unusual
thing.
And usually previews are a way to smooth out issues with like
and it's not going to be the same show as when it officially
opens.
This was such a catastrophe.
The critics were like, we got to see this immediately.
Desperate, I'm sure.
Yeah.
Just a side note, I was thinking about how much I would love
to play the Green Goblin.
Yeah.
I mean, this guy's given 110%.
That's the funniest thing to me is how he comes in like a
stadium is screaming his name.
He is coming in hot.
He's coming in ready to go.
I think, though, he's giving it.
He's so confident he's not giving it 100%.
He's given it 75, but he's so confident there's a couple of
dance steps, a couple of dance steps he does that are like
very late.
He's an older.
I think he's like in his 50s or something.
So maybe he's not a great, but he does a couple of dance steps
later on.
Maybe I should zoom it where he does kind of like he's in step,
but you can tell he's like not a dancer and maybe not trying
very hard.
Like I kind of a slow little stomp.
Yeah.
Like I can't.
I'm not even trying to put him down.
I think it was the right choice to not like go.
Let me see where it is here.
The other everybody else is hoofing it more.
Yes, everyone's going.
Sure.
And he is holding.
He is just holding the attention of the audience.
The little point he just did what we just saw where he like
points three times.
I saw footage of Julie Tamar here.
Sorry.
Here we go.
Oh, yes.
That stomp backwards.
Kick, kick, kick.
I'm sure he doesn't have as much mobility as the people
in workout wear around him.
I'm just saying he's in time, but he's not
like he's not given the Springsteen effort
in the fourth encore is what I'm saying.
Well, that's my favorite.
I think in that part, they're singing the light light
and all the freaks.
And they all kind of go up like that.
And they all like swoop with their hands like zombies.
It's just the most that's really these backup dancers being
scary.
That is truly where it gets silly and me.
But I was saying that point, I saw Julie Tamar coaching him
and how to point.
She has a glove on and she's like, make sure you're like
that's footage you can watch in a 60 minutes piece.
So now we've looped back around.
All right.
Let's see what's happening.
The Green Goblin breaks in from the back topical Joe walks in
struts into the Ed Sullivan theater, owns it.
And he's already planted a gang of freaky freaks
in French coats.
And then he joins the most and lab coats.
The scientists, people too.
And then over here on the right, you've got like a guy in front
of a laptop who looks like a modern Geddy Lee crossed with
the crow who's like leading the band.
And that's another funny thing about this, that this is being
played live by the David Letterman band with Paul Schaeffer.
Let's add another luminary to this.
Yeah.
And the part where the Green Goblin walks up to Paul Schaeffer
and sings next to him, that's one of the highlights.
Also, what we're looking at right now where he sticks his
tongue out and it's like the tongue is green.
Do you think that he had to like eat a green sucker?
Right.
100% green apple sucker.
Did he do it every night is the question on Broadway.
Did they need it to be green even though for the people in the
front row.
Michael, I have a question.
Is Norman Osborn in this musical?
Yes, he is.
Is it the same actor playing Norman Osborn?
I believe so.
Really?
They got that costume on.
I think they did a costume.
Wow.
That's my memory of it because every other villain has just
just basically name checked in this and they're just like
dispatched easily.
But he's in it.
They're not really.
I had a feeling he was the only one really fleshed out.
So let's just.
All right.
Lyrics.
I mean, I know this thing by heart, but sure.
We already covered it, but I just love it.
Similar to like, I don't know, like the way how hard I laughed
at the first line of the room.
The first time I saw it, you're just like so high, babe.
You're so in.
And that like if there's any question of like, is this thing
silly or good or bad or that when he the way he phrase it,
if you're looking for his got his learn, he's going to have
committed.
That's it just tunes you perfectly.
And then the reference to how expensive it is.
And then he explains that he's the new Coney Island and all
the rides are open and free.
And he also I also like what he's what he says of me.
Like he's such a freak.
All he needs to say is me.
And you know, that's the craziest thing you could be.
So if you were reading into this and you didn't know what
the context was, he's like looking to have sex tonight.
Right.
Like if you didn't know, I don't know.
I think I think your body meter is going off again.
Maybe I miss.
But he's like he needs company.
A freak like me needs company.
Well, here's a little story from the making of the show
that when this title was first presented as a OK, apparently
a bond is working on a new song.
It's called a freak like me needs company.
And the director said, no, no, no, no, no.
It needs to be a freak like me needs family because his view
of the song is that he's a guy, he's a loner,
and now he's going to form his own family by giving people
poisons and chemicals.
And now he's got this family of freaks.
So there I think this is a little bit of contention.
Maybe in some people's mind it is about sex,
but in other people's mind it's about family.
Well, and this is interesting because in the original
The Sinister Six, who first appeared in 1964's Amazing
Spider-Man Annual Number One, which I looked up,
the way they come together is Doc Ock breaks out of prison
and contacts everyone who has been beaten by Spider-Man.
And the ones who show up and get back to him decide
they want to fight Spider-Man because they've all been humiliated by him.
They've all been defeated by him.
But they can't get their act together to work together.
So they fight Spider-Man one at a time in a gauntlet.
And sure enough, he dispatches all of them.
And they're humiliated once again.
And because it's Steve Ditko still drawing it,
they're all very gross and ugly.
OK, wow.
So Sinister Six is like a hallmark of Spider-Man for many years.
And there's been a lot of different members.
There's been a lot of different members over the years,
including in this one, Swiss Miss, a character created for the musical.
She's a woman made of knives.
And they brag about it.
I remember the media coverage at the time was like,
then there's a villain created just for the musical.
And she's called Swiss Miss.
And it's like, oh, and what she does is strut up,
wave her knife arms twice and then go return to the back.
Yeah. Yep. And that's it.
Yep. The end.
So the lyrics, though, like in I've been told that what you're supposed
to do when you're writing a musical is that the character is supposed to be
somewhere different by the end of the song.
Character starts in a certain place.
You're supposed to you're supposed to make like an actual like
something happen in the narrative in the song.
That's what the song is for.
So the first verse is like he's looking for company.
Then he explains in the chorus that weirdos are weirdos are there.
And then he has a crew in the second verse.
So I guess he's looking for the people.
Maybe he wants maybe he means sexist company.
Maybe just means literal company.
Well, maybe this is a good time to play the extra verse.
That's not in the letter.
Oh, yeah. Right. Performance.
I don't have to play the whole thing, but just a little.
It's really all about the first line of of verse two.
And I think I'm looking at it.
I'm also looking at it.
Uh-huh, that's what I was looking at.
I got a crew of body and I'm a mutant.
And the rest of the verse just really lays on it
and truly becomes like, a group of freaks,
cause I'm a freak.
Demon hairdo evil dressers who just won't be denied.
Is the next line of that.
Yeah.
And I have another thing to say about what I think
contributes to kicking this to the lamer side.
Okay, imagine Bono's guide vocals,
where potentially he sings the backup vocals like,
like me needs company.
And that's one way to sing it,
but the way the singers do it is,
a freak like me needs company.
It's that super Broadway.
Make sure you really hit each and it's three,
so ba ba ba, you got that ba ba ba.
It's very much like Bob Balaban,
the music director in Waiting for Guffman explaining like,
and half of you will say, blay and the other half
you'll say blane.
Like these bizarre pronunciation rituals.
You just feel that lame Broadway.
And no matter who wrote the song,
as long as it's a big Broadway chorus doing it,
it's just gonna come off silly.
Yeah.
There would be, first of all,
I would think that the holy grail is to find
the Bono and Edge demo of this.
Oh man.
Oh, if anyone for some reason.
For some reason.
Has some in. Yeah, takes, yeah.
Because he did like, temp this.
Yeah.
And he was like messing around in the studio
with a loop and improvising lyrics.
And this is a passage in the book,
if you don't mind me,
maybe I'll turn to one of my first Post-It sections.
This is like, because I bought the book,
Song of Spider-Man,
with the hopes that it was 100%
about the Letterman performance of Freak Like Me.
But in fact, the Freak Like Me content is pretty small,
which is disappointing.
But this one part did not let me down.
And let me find it.
So the song, you know, they gotta rush this song out,
cause the play is up and running,
and they gotta introduce it and rehearse it
and get it in there sooner than later.
So it's the middle of the night.
Bono is lying on a ratty couch
in the middle of the recording room,
improvising goblin lines over an endless groove.
He was in character, a dissipated lounge lizard,
shaking off last night's bender
and warming up for some new kicks.
He was scatting, hacking up tar,
yawning, cackling into the mic.
And then in the book, you get extra lyrics
that are nowhere to be found in the song.
And Hugh didn't have to cover your ears, Mike,
because he gets a tad bawdy.
You know, he's not worried about,
he's just letting it flow.
They'll edit it down later.
But here's what comes out of Bono's mouth.
Bring out the dancing girls.
The crossroads of the world needs a little resurrection.
It used to be really rotten around here.
Now can't even buy me an erection.
So it's the middle of the night.
Bono's on the floor saying that shit.
Hacking up tar.
Apparently hacking up tar,
which is troubling.
Preparing for his kicks.
No, no, no, he's just playing the care.
Yeah, he's not really hacking up tar.
Oh, I see, okay.
Like he was three sheets to the wind with,
can you tell this was written by a Broadway book writer?
It's with stained silk bathrobe bravado he's saying.
He thinks it's awesome.
Yeah, yeah, he loves, and he's like,
he's watching an artistic process in action.
Right.
He watched him improvise the line
about $65 million circus tragedy.
How did he come up with that?
I don't know.
Bono's the cheat key.
That is good.
Oh, he's got a spreadsheet with all the numbers on it
and how much it's affecting his bottom line.
He's gotta sell an island.
I should say though,
this musical did set the record
for one week Broadway sales once
during one of its weeks of its run.
It turned around.
2.9 million.
Jeez, okay.
But its operating costs were estimated
to be $1 million a week.
So I think it did end up being profitable
because it did, and it also ran for two and a half years.
I think they broke even or something.
Yeah, so at least broke even.
So also, and the guy compares
what Bono was doing to like Tom Waits.
So there's a little bit of Tom Waits influence in-
Greta Goblin.
There's a lot of Tom Waits influence
on Heath Ledger's Joker.
And that's, I'm being serious.
Oh yes, that's how I recently learned that too, yeah.
There's a clip of like him talking,
Tom Waits being like, hey, there is Dean.
And then you click, they show the clip of Heath Ledger
and you're like, oh yeah, though it's the voice.
It's the same voice.
And the way he kinda like smacks his lips
and shakes his head around.
And yeah, so all the great supervillains
have some Tom Waits.
But also in the demo,
when they say a freak like me needs,
it was the edge.
It was the edge stacked on itself, multi-tracked.
So this demo does exist
and we have to get our hands on it.
We gotta get it, yeah.
But here's where it gets truly insane.
It's March 17th as they're doing this.
It's the middle of the night
and all of New York's most famous freaks
are flooding the streets.
So who should walk in into the recording session
of this song but Elvis Costello?
Let one more luminary, Costello is in the building
while they're doing this.
He's wearing a pair of devil horns like Mr. McPhisto.
Like Mr. McPhisto.
So Bono invites Elvis to Steve Lillywhite is there.
They play him the track.
Elvis listened intently,
hardly moving until the songs were over.
And after he said some very complimentary things
and headed out into the night, Bono said,
"'Yeah, I heard the songs through his ears
"'and there's some things we need to fix.'"
Then writer Glenn Berger goes on to say,
"'And that's what you get with a community of artists
"'is an exchange of ears and it's all about how he's isolated
"'but he doesn't have company.
"'Of freaks like Bono and Costello have with each other.'"
I love Costello coming in and going like,
"'This is good.'"
Like they're all just like kissing each other's ass
and stuff about it.
This is good.
It requires a willingness to be self-critical.
These guys in the devil horns had it.
Yeah, I'm sure these guys are real self-critics.
I'm sure.
Bono in the Edge, super self-aware still.
Very hard, very hard on themselves.
Do you think Costello was like,
you should have like a knife woman.
You know what would be fun is if you have like a knife woman.
What's scary about a knife woman?
Anyway, back to drinking, bye.
He sticks his head back in.
Maybe a gun woman.
Guns are scarier.
It's up to you, it's your show.
I don't want to be prescriptive.
See you at Sardis.
If Costello had written a line in this,
that would be a great lore.
I don't think the fake story of Prince writing
the frozen,
Yeah, yeah.
It didn't bother me anyway.
This is, you know, Mike,
listening to the song a million times before recording this
really gives me a new appreciation
of the City Walk Saga theme song.
What do you mean?
You're saying Mike's a better songwriter than Bono?
I'm saying that, yeah.
Although apparently some people were haunted
by a sublime hot topic in Cinnabon trying to figure out.
There was a lot of mystery in the,
my intention was behind writing the lyric.
Was I talking about sublime the store
or was I saying that hot topic was sublime?
And here I'll say this now, I'm not going to tell.
Yeah.
Well, an artist has to be ambiguous.
Who were you?
I mean, you did a demo of the vocal, like Bono,
you did a demo of the song before it was,
you were replaced by the Broadway caliber, Zachary.
Did you, were you channeling anyone while singing that song?
I assume Tom Waits, but besides that.
Tom Waits, I was sort of more of like a,
I was kind of getting in the place of like
the Gregorian chants.
That's what I was sort of thinking like a kind of,
like primitive music.
I was sort of trying to think.
The kilter hills, yes.
They can feel the spirits and, you know,
it's really the pre, before City Walk,
there were the hills of Ireland.
But of course, all popular rock and roll goes back to
Muddy Waters and Mississippi Delta.
Blind Willie Jefferson.
Brian Eno via Mike Post, I'll say.
Hey, great.
Yeah.
Why didn't Eno, why didn't they get Eno down
to consult on this?
Yeah, Eno was a big, Eno was Octong Baby, right?
He kind of played, well, I guess he didn't play characters.
In this video, you know,
he could be a malevolent figure in certain songs.
I'm sorry, I just had to point out.
So Letterman is on stage standing in front of Swiss Miss
and her knife knee pad is still spinning.
It has not stopped spinning.
That's great.
Oh wait, we just popped up.
And once you see it, you can't unsee it.
Okay.
So we have established in the song that all the freaks
in New York City are out tonight.
All the weirdos are all around,
but we need further proof of this.
And so there is a roll call of each member
of the Sinister Six, perhaps we should go through them.
You've got a really, I don't know.
It's hard to pick a favorite line or anything,
but for sure we got a man made entirely out of mutant bees.
He's kind of tossing it off.
He's getting a little half-assed.
And then of course the bee falls off.
Yeah, that would be Swarm.
First appearance, champions number 14, July, 1977.
This character, I think the actual comics design of Swarm,
it is just a mass of bees.
The character has been from Wikipedia,
the character has been depicted as a former Nazi sympathizer
and has been mainly featured as an enemy of Spider-Man.
His entire body is composed of bees
surrounding his skeleton.
And on top of that, he has a big purple cloak.
So that's one of those things like, oh, only in comics,
until Broadway came along.
Until somebody put a bunch of sticks
on a yellow and black unitard.
Yeah.
Wait, who's next?
What's the order?
Oh, the lizard.
Next is the lizard.
Yeah.
Isn't it?
No, I think it's the lizard.
I think it's the lizard.
He comes up the aisles.
Right, right.
And that's legitimately impressive
that an inflatable dinosaur bursts out of a scientist,
out of his stomach.
Electro is the guy with a torch in his hand, correct?
He's sparking a lot.
Yeah, he has cool spark effects, which I think they kind of
use similar spark effects.
You know how lettermen always have those spokes models
with the metal that they would be sparking
when they would hit metal on metal?
Does anyone know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
He would have just, I don't remember,
they would be showcasing something.
Will it float?
Many different times.
They would bring in these women that had metal
and they would just do these sparking things
that would, but it looks like a similar effect
that Electro has going on.
I see.
That's also one of the top lines of the thing is,
hey ladies, how about a human lightning bolt?
You want it?
You got it.
Why ladies?
Electro, not to be confused with Shocker,
Spider-Man's other electricity-themed nemesis.
I love Shocker, I'm a big Shocker fan as a kid.
The costume kind of looks like,
more like Shocker's than Electro's.
Is Kraven next?
I think it's Kraven the Hunter.
And that's the joke.
He makes a joke which seems like he's implying that,
because Kraven the Hunter, Jason,
do you have facts on Kraven you want to read?
Sure, Kraven, real name Sergei Kravinov,
a maniacal big game hunter who seeks to defeat Spider-Man
to prove that he is the greatest hunter in the world.
And he favors his bare hands.
He does not like using guns or bow and arrows.
In Kraven's last hunt, he famously commits suicide,
which is one of the most famous stories, right?
Yes, because he thinks he's killed Spider-Man.
Right, but he hasn't.
And won, but then he tries to replace him,
and then it turns out he hasn't, so he commits suicide.
And in the show, in the Spider-Man show,
he says like, Kraven the Hunter,
like what he, I forgot, I should have written down the line.
It's like, he likes the animals,
but maybe a little too much.
So that is about sex.
That is for sure implying that he's had sex with
whatever lion or tiger he's hanging around with.
He's almost like a lion king on Broadway style puppet,
because he's like a big cartoonish looking man
and in his main, his costume.
Yeah, here it is.
He's got a whip and leather pants.
It's a lion, literally roars,
like the lion on his chest.
He's very good, yeah.
It's really good.
And he factors into this other,
we're gonna direct you to another YouTube video
I recently discovered, in which Spider-Man
and the Green Goblin put their differences aside
to hold a press conference about Halloween costume safety.
There is, please look this up
or we'll put it in the show notes or something,
that the Green Goblin, Spider-Man's not really talking.
He stands off to the side and the Green Goblin handles it.
Different actor playing the Green Goblin,
but he says, now Spider-Man and I,
we've had our differences,
many of which have played out on the public stage,
but there's one thing that we can agree on
and that's Halloween safety.
And then he pans around the other villains,
like now my friends here are dressed very outlandishly,
but they make sure to have the maximum visibility at night.
And these sad reporters have to be there outside the theater
covering this non-event.
It's so funny.
Anyway, I'm a fantastic super villain,
but I do wanna say blue lives matter.
These guys, they're out on the stairwell
every day putting their lives on the line.
And you know, stop and frisk works.
It's a word we wouldn't have used it for so long.
If it had a word.
Come on Mayor de Blasio, it's 2011 so.
Yes, they all turn their back.
They'll replace you next election.
And then it goes to like a very bland police officer,
just reading facts about like,
do not wear all black costumes,
make sure you have reflective materials on your,
and during that Craven the Hunter leans in behind him
and kind of like cranes his head and smiles
as these dull facts about safety are listed.
It's the funny, these villains are truly left with like,
well, the only thing I can do is ride around and look evil.
And so what do they do when we're talking about like,
kids don't make sure that candy's wrapped,
make sure they got no needles in there.
They're at a loss.
If you're going as cops and robbers or cowboys,
make sure there's an orange cap
on the end of your toy costume pistol.
Oh, you have to be too careful these days.
You are smote, son.
So that's a great video, check that out.
Craven the Hunter, the all star of that one.
Carnage. Now we got,
I don't remember his name.
Carnage. Carnage.
Cletus Cassidy, Jason, you wanna give us some,
the symbiote?
Carnage is interesting to me
because the original idea was that the writer, David,
is it Michelin? David Michelin?
Oh yeah, I don't know.
He wrote a lot of Spider-Man comics.
He was going to kill off Venom.
He wanted to kill off Venom.
And- Big mistake.
Big mistake because he was too popular,
too successful and management was like,
well, we can't kill him off.
And eventually the storyline became, we'll kill off Craven.
But similarly, they, he could not make Venom.
They needed someone even more extreme than Venom.
So they made Carnage,
a similar symbiote based Spider-Man enemy,
but Cletus Cassidy is a fucking psychopath.
Venom has a moral comp, even though it's twisted,
he's got a moral compass,
but Carnage is just fucking crazy.
Yeah, he's a very 90s character.
I mean, Venom is a 90s character,
but Carnage is 90s, baby, like extreme and violent.
Venom created at the end of the 80s, I believe.
Oh yeah, that makes sense.
And ahead of them, just like Cable,
and then just became, when the 90s just ran
with these extreme characters, you end up with-
Carnage. Carnage.
And the way this extreme, the extreme nature of Carnage
is presented in the Letterman performance is,
he killed his grandmother and tortured his mother's dog.
My kind of guy, Carnage. Shout out Carnage.
That's the first time also he's talked about actually killing,
I think too.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
That's pretty thrown away, yeah.
These are literal murderers, don't forget.
It's pretty innocent up until that.
Up until he says, we got a guy in the team
who killed someone and he's-
Where does Carnage, Carnage has a grandmother?
I honestly don't, the history of Carnage
is a little cloudy to me.
I assume he killed some person in his family.
He was just like, he was like a really crazy
hillbilly character. I think he was kind of,
I think the timing works out where when he would have been
created and starred in the comics,
lines up with Silence of the Lambs being a big hit movie.
So it's kind of like, oh, it's like Venom
meets Hannibal Lecter.
Cause like all the early Carnage storylines were like,
this guy's so crazy.
He'll just straight up murder people in cold blood.
Like any nuance or any like, well, he's tortured
because of this reason.
Like Dr. Octopus in the second Spider-Man movie.
He's tortured because he's trying to find this,
prove this scientific formula.
But then he's haunted by his wife dying in the process.
That's called, Carnage is just a straight up psychopath.
Which, but there's something about it being his grandmother
that just makes it feel like, you know,
he told his teacher to suck eggs.
That would seem like it would be more appropriate
for what had come before in the song.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That it's all, it's no, there's no reference made.
It's just, we're going to have a freaky party.
Yeah. Anyway, he killed his grandmother.
He was, you know, they stacked the jury.
So he got off.
It wasn't totally clean.
You know, look, I think they, I think they bought
that election and they had some sway with the DA.
But anyway, he's out on the street.
I've got some thoughts on partisan judges.
I, and then you, and then you got Swiss Miss,
the most tossed off of all.
And oh, one more.
There you go. Okay.
There you go.
There is a female also.
Okay, bye.
That, that's kind of,
I forget what, I forget the character's name
in the Spider-Man ride in Florida.
Scream. Are you referencing?
Yes. One of, one of the carnages.
There's a yellow venom symbiote with lady.
Yeah, one of the symbiote spin-offs
and it made it sound like, well,
we got to have a girl bad guy.
Like in both of these, it's, it does feel so tossed off.
Yeah. I don't know why they didn't go black cat or like,
I mean, she's like a tweener if you're, if something,
but she could be a bad guy, you know?
She doesn't, she could be in this, in this universe.
An anti-hero, bit of an anti-hero.
Black cat. She's good sometimes.
Sometimes she's bad.
We don't know. Black cat.
There you go.
Very young, has a streak, has a lot of white hair.
Think she's like Catwoman? She is.
Her biggest, the biggest crime is being a ripoff artist.
Intellectual property theft.
Oh, man.
So that all is so delightful.
He's just the most theme parky villain.
He's so much like the Janey. He's so much like,
he's like Bugsy. He's like exactly like Bugsy.
Yes, that's true. He is a lot like Bugsy.
He's the devil.
But he's, he's mean, but he's also cheeky.
He's kind of cute.
I think this, I am so upset this isn't still running
on Broadway.
There was a rumor it was going to be running
and they were going to move it to Vegas,
which is the perfect place for it.
This is 100% Vegas.
And they never like get the funding to move everything,
but they should have done it.
I'm gonna throw a pitch your way.
Here's a plus set up.
I have a pitch too, but yeah, go for it.
Okay. I'm worried I'm saying your pitch already.
No, there's not, I don't think there is.
I think it's a different.
I think that here's, this is the merger
I want to make happen between a couple,
like not 100% successful musicals,
but I think you do this pair up and it's perfect.
The Jimmy Buffett musical, Escape from Margaritaville
proceeds as it did, whatever the hell happened in that show,
but halfway through, well, well, well,
what's this little beach party?
It looks like y'all are getting laid.
Look, I make jokes.
Maybe I need to rain on your little sunny parade.
The Green Goblin as a threat within Escape from Margaritaville
would form the greatest musical ever achieved.
There's no doubt about it.
I mean, there's no, yeah, there's no reason not to do that.
Just to have a main character
of the Margaritaville musical, Tully Mars.
Need some help, Tully Mars?
Spider-Man, thank God you're here.
The actor playing Tully Mars has broken both legs.
But the multiple Tully Marses swinging in
from the balconies, Tully and Spider-Man swing, yeah.
Now that's a problem because those swings
have to be precisely timed and choreographed,
and Tully Mars ain't never won a watch.
He's on his own time.
He's on island time. Island time, obviously.
And in the end of the show,
the Green Goblin's getting threatened,
and he's gonna, he talked to the mayor
and he's gonna cancel summer.
But then he sees them all drinking margaritas,
and he's like, wait a minute, drinks can be green?
Toss one of those my way, brother.
And then they all cheers and party together.
And then they sing like a mashup of Margaritaville
and Boy Falls from the Sky.
I'm into that.
I'm wasted away again in Margaritaville.
The Bono mobile guide.
Yeah, no, that's not what I was gonna pick.
The Julie Taymor lost shaker of salt
that's a living creature with like,
Oh yeah, that's great.
Children crying at the appearance of the salt shaker.
Certainly the cheeseburger is also
an anthropomorphic cheeseburger in paradise.
He's got a big floppy cheese tongue lapping around.
A volcano would be real,
or it would be like that volcano from the Pixar short,
who's sad.
Oh yeah, sure.
Lava.
Why did they use actual lava?
Julie Taymor insisted on real lava.
The cast all, their feet got singed,
they'll never walk again.
Oh God, the safety strap wasn't fully on their harness,
and then they stepped in lava.
That's a real insult to insult.
No injury to injury, no insults at all.
Do you have another pitch?
My pitch was honestly not as good.
My pitch was just that I wanna see Bono on the edge.
It's about time I think for them
to tackle another superhero property.
Cause we had Batman forever, then we had Spider-Man.
I think it's time for them to do another
big famous superhero.
And I'm open to pitches on this,
but I mean like, there needs to be like an Iron Man musical
written by Bono on the edge or something.
A big superhero and get their take.
Like what is, when Bono on the edge wanna write a song
where the Mandarin is the villain,
what kind of song are we gonna get?
Oh, I'm the freaky little Mandarin.
I know nothing else about the Mandarin,
but that's the song.
For sure like harpsichord, like Asian inspired influences.
And like Bono certainly getting into a problematic
character head space before he's doing the lyrics
for the Mandarin.
Yeah, I just think.
With the freaky fantastic voice.
Or at the very least, an original IP
of all you two characters from the tours
as its own musical superhero kind of a mashup thing.
Yes, wait, who will take us through some other characters?
Well, Bono is like the pop tour.
Bono is like a box.
Bono is the boxer and he's got like a big like robot
and like it's Bono is usually the interesting character
on the show.
So can I pitch where it would take place?
Oh, please go for it.
Joshua Tree National Park.
No, that's the different, that's a different era.
I just mean a setting.
Yeah, you could combine it.
All right, fine, fine.
It's a jukebox musical.
Wait, your YouTube musical is just like three albums.
It's not even a dressing all of it.
The covered YouTube stuff is all the nonsense
with the characters and stuff.
Stuff people don't like.
The stuff that people, people like Octon Baby,
but people get a little bit weird
about the Mr. McFisto stuff for some reason.
You've also of course got in,
if it's multiple Bono villains and characters meeting,
you gotta get Dr. Robert, the character he played
in Julie Taymor's film across the universe.
From the Beatles song.
That's why this all happened.
It actually started with Bono and the Edge,
not Julie Taymor.
And they had one condition, the condition is Julie.
That's so they caused, they created this monster.
Was this after Across the Universe?
Yeah.
Wow.
It's been a long time.
So you just saw how she just did not understand the Beatles
and they're like, what if she could
misunderstand Spider-Man too?
And rap music in general and Tom Waits.
The other characters, I forget,
the other characters on the Pop Mart tour
other than Mr. McFisto were Bono's the fly character
when he had big, his giant glasses and then Mirror Ball Man.
Barf.
I was looking at some articles about Mr. McFisto.
I didn't really have time to do the full research
I would have liked to.
And I don't know how much I believe this,
but according to U2Songs.com,
Joel Schumacher, the director of Batman Forever
had met with Bono to discuss an on-screen role.
Initially it was thought that Bono would play a villain,
but there were already two evil characters
in the film already.
So instead Schumacher considered having Bono perform a song
in costume as McFisto.
McFisto is almost in the movie.
I believe that.
Yeah, I don't know why I wouldn't.
It's a crazy movie.
Coolio was in the second, it was in Batman and Robin,
I believe, there are little weird cameos.
And then there's like decent, I don't know,
Drew Barrymore is in like a tiny role.
There are people that are put in the movie as is.
And he did a song on the soundtrack.
So it makes sense that he met with him.
And it makes sense Joel Schumacher would have been like,
I like Mr. McFisto.
This feels like a good time to bring this up.
So I don't know if you guys had anything like this
in your middle school music classes,
but I sure did.
And it's still confusing to me to this day.
So we would get this,
the music teachers would get these magazines,
like glossy magazines that every student got a copy.
And for like a couple of weeks at least,
we would analyze a popular song
using things we had learned in music classes.
And the one year it was Kiss From A Rose,
Kiss By A Rose?
Kiss From A Rose.
And the next year it was, I Believe I Can Fly.
Whoa.
So.
Both of the big Warner Brothers, R&B crossover.
Yeah, so maybe that magazine,
I mean, I'm sure that magazine was funded by a record label,
probably Warner Brothers Records.
And I, but it only went, we only did that,
maybe it's just the same teacher,
but like I never did that again.
Was it sanctioned, like a curriculum passed out
on a professional level?
Yes, like that looked in like a magazine
that looks like a thin floppy Rolling Stone kind of thing.
Which really, maybe that gave you a thirst
for music and song and lyric analysis
that led to this very podcast today.
Like I'd like to get that booklet now and say,
okay, so let's move on to line three.
I'm a rolling baby rolling in the green,
but I'm unique, a freak.
Now, what do you make of that?
I love it.
I love Batman Forever.
I hope we keep doing a lot of Batman Forever talk
in general.
But you know, we're missing a big component
to what makes this video great,
which is that at the end,
we get to see the real time reaction
of wonderfully cantankerous David Letterman.
Watching him, so he comes out
and is kind of that bemused mode,
like, oh, oh, oh boy.
And he makes this very odd lame joke.
It's like a party at my mom's house
and is kind of, and then gets surrounded by all the freaks.
And that it's just priceless.
It's wonderful.
And then at the very, very end,
the YouTube video cuts off in a wonderful way
where with half a second to go,
Electro lights up a flame
and he's taking his mask off by that point.
So he's just this enthusiastic dude, like, hey.
And it's so wonderful.
He barely gets it in there.
A big open flame next to David Letterman.
And what I think is that any other host,
this is not as funny.
Like that this is about performance being done
in the, like in the home of the meanest man.
Doesn't like anything.
Does he, yeah, cause I feel like
I don't remember what the verdict was on this.
Usually does Letterman usually like the musical performances
that were on their show or not?
No, he was usually checked out.
No way.
He likes the Foo Fighters and he likes maybe like.
Springsteen probably.
Springsteen, like the Black Keys probably.
I think he likes.
Super chunk or New Pornographers would play,
be like, hey, that's great.
I think he might like some of that.
But I think.
Beastie Boys, I think.
They seem to have fun with Letterman.
He famously, I think is an old crank
and doesn't like most things.
Yeah.
So yeah.
That's the thing that today,
this performance is done for Jimmy Fallon or James Corden.
And they come out after and like, oh my God,
that was fantastic.
They're there, they love it.
They eat it up.
They like suck up.
Like it's, it's the best thing I've ever seen.
That's how it's done, baby.
That kind of, and I, it's just, I miss so much.
Smokers.
Hooray.
Yeah.
Like if you're saying, give it at a hundred percent,
they will give the reaction to it a hundred percent.
The cast of Spider-Man, turn off the talk everybody.
If you know, that's my Jimmy Fallon impression.
I always do everything.
He always says, everybody.
Yeah, he does that weird.
It's apparently bothers no one but me.
In fact, no, I know what you're saying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
The only, the only funnier version of this
would be if they were doing this exact,
the performance on Ed Sullivan.
Now, ladies and gentlemen.
And like, he had to kind of like walk around
and just like not know what to make of it.
And like, he wouldn't be able to sell that.
He was never an excitable man.
So like that would be an equivalent, but yeah,
no newer host would like show you what he felt.
Yeah.
Would immediately sell out the piece.
And I've got one more little thing,
which is that as you said, Jason, this,
there was previously a Spider-Man turn off
the dark performance and that was the star Reeve Carney
performing the big ballad Rise Above.
And that's my absolute favorite part of the book,
Song of Spider-Man.
That I think is the most,
listening to a handful of songs from the musical,
that seems the most Broadway-y of the songs, I think.
Sure, yeah, it's the big soaring moving.
Actually, I was wrong.
The singer is T.V. Carpio who plays Arachne.
And this gives you a,
if you're interested in reading Song of Spider-Man,
this is a real like window into the tone of the book.
But this is like, he's at,
the writer is absolutely at wit's end.
He owes incredible changes,
like massive overhauls of this play that's falling apart
and hurting people.
And right at that very moment, he's alone.
He's removed from his family.
They literally live somewhere else.
He hasn't seen his child in months
because he's putting together a freak like me needs company.
And he's, so he's like, he's alone
in his New York apartment.
It's cold, he's shivering, and he turns on the T.V.
And his very work,
Spider-Man, Turn Off the Dark, comes on.
And the lyrics,
your strength will be a vision beyond visibility.
And the, sorry, the lyrics,
And the gift I've woven for you will give you new eyes
to see that you can rise above yourself then.
And I let out a scream, loud, ragged, and long,
until the walls echoed and my throat hurt.
I felt like throwing up.
I felt like slamming my hand against a wall
until I had shattered some bones.
But I didn't.
I made myself some coffee.
The most, and I, what I love about that is that for all,
this is a man having a melt, he's abandoned his family.
He's having an absolute meltdown alone.
Just all like curled up in the ball of the floor.
And a woman on T.V. dressed as a spider lady is singing,
you've got to rise above.
And he goes, ah!
He's like screaming.
He's having a meltdown like from a movie to himself,
from a fucking Spider-Man performance of a theme,
it's a theme park show.
This is so rich.
These are adults acting like this and doing this.
And then he made himself a cup of coffee.
And then he tossed in like Vanity Fair celebrity profile,
first paragraph details of like,
Anna Kendrick walked into LaMille and ordered her latte.
And it's like, we don't, these profile,
like stop telling us what everyone's ordered.
Actually, I kind of know what, I like to know.
How else do you get to know a character?
You learn how they drink their coffee,
what they order for breakfast, how they shave.
They exchange money for goods and services just like me.
It's a regular, it's an average temperature day
in Los Angeles and Mia Cabrera is sipping on a cup of water.
To soothe her voice apparently from a big performance
the night before.
Yeah, you're absolutely right.
What are these?
Why do articles need to pad out with this crap?
Steve Bannon ordered another cup of slop
as he walked into the garbage dump that he called a home.
Directly with his mouth.
Yeah.
Every item made of corrugated iron that had rusted.
He had a 10 gallon drum of bleach to pour into a hot tub.
But nothing would clean him of his sins.
Oh, there he is, the green goblin.
We've got a perfect final frame.
His wonderful smile.
I don't, I mean, it shows you how much,
I think we've all been waiting probably for years
to talk about this at length and there's so much there.
And there's more.
We'll get to more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sure we'll do a sequel to it.
We haven't.
We'll do the whole Mr. Mephisto episode.
Mike saw the whole show so we can do,
we can go through, we can do an episode
on both versions of the show
because they were different after the rewrites.
Oh yeah, we'll find.
And after the previews closed.
Yeah, yeah.
So you've got YouTube homework to do
if you have watched them talking about Halloween costumes.
Watch everything you can get your hands on
because this thing, what I, I mean,
I guess it all sounds like shit talk or something,
but truly this thing makes me so happy.
It's cheered me up.
If I'm in a bad mood, I could put this on and I smile.
I thank everyone involved for doing
this wonderful piece of television.
I agree.
It's made me so happy for so many years.
And I thank both of you for making me relook at this
with a theme park lens where yes, it's perfect.
With a Broadway lens or a comic book lens,
it is a puzzle you will never be able to solve.
But if you think, yeah, it's theme park entertainment.
I'm in the world of a villain broke into the Letterman show.
I do, I love it.
I wish things like that happened all the time.
Just, hey, thanks everybody.
It's so great.
Well, you survived podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
One of the most enthusiastic episodes
you're ever gonna hear.
Tell us more bullshit that you wanna hear us talk about
at length by emailing us at podcasttherideatgmail.com
and subscribe to our regular stuff on Twitter,
Instagram and Facebook.
And stay weird.
Most of all, keep it freaky.