Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may include human skull slice down the middle, cruel destruction
of alarm clocks, a pretty good pitch for Michael Eisner merchandise, and grappling with the
ultimate moral quandary in what scenario is robot theft justified.
Buzzy, if you're listening, don't give up hope.
You will be found as a result of this episode about Cranium Command on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show hosted by three men who are piloted by three much smaller men,
but have the same voices as the regular sized men. I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Scott
Garandir. As opposed to the Buzzy scenario? No, the Buzzy scenario is the same. Is Buzzy his voice?
The child's voice and Buzzy's voice is the same actor. Okay, that is a question I had. And yes,
it is the same and the little Scott sounds like this. Hello. This is Mike Carlson. I'm confused
though because isn't Buzzy like almost a temporary, he's just on the job for the first time in the
Ride Cranium Command, which is what we're talking about today? In theory, yeah. I never put that
together or had forgotten that the child's voice and Buzzy's voice are one and the same. We're
right. I figure we get into this deep into the thing, but yeah, I'll go straight to it.
Okay, if he's a new recruit and presumably this 12 year old boy existed before he was being piloted
by a little guy in his head, what did he sound like before? Right. Is it that like, if you're
changing out little guys in your head, that voices would constantly be changing. You would
constantly have a new voice if like your little guy was fired or the- Maybe this is the issue in
puberty. Maybe that's what we're like. Oh yes. When your voice is changing and cracking, it's because
your guy is sliding in and out. He's been fired. But that would only really work like, isn't it
possible that a seven year old boy would have a really gruff voice and then suddenly get higher?
Yeah, of course it is. I mean, this system, this doesn't, this ride makes no sense.
It's almost like they had less than six months to turn it around.
Save it for massive plot holes. In case we're diving too deep into the deep end today, we're
talking about Cranium Command, which was a show at Epcot Center where you go inside the head of a
12 year old and meet all of the people who, the tiny people who pilot the 12 year old.
Why this ride? Well, you, the listener, very well might know. By popular demand.
Yeah. I don't think anything has been sent to us more than this. Absolutely. Yeah, so many people
tweeted this at us and it was a genuine Twitter thing, I feel like, at least as far as I can tell.
I'm pretty theme park centric in my Twitter feed, but there was a lot of hashtag find Buzzy
because the little guy, the pilot, the single audio animatronic in the ride, Buzzy, apparently
was never removed from the ride, though you haven't been able to go on it in a decade.
And now it is missing. It is missing now. And apparently his clothes were taken back in August
and the animatronic was taken in December. That's how it played out?
That's the update I saw and I think they did, they arrested someone and questioned them.
I saw a name. I don't have it handy, but the person has been named.
But not charged. Wait, so go back. So you're saying that Buzzy's clothes were removed by
Walt Disney Company or somebody snuck in and just stole the little boy's clothes?
The little boy's clothes because the breaking news at the end of December was that the Buzzy
animatronic is gone. And then a lot of the websites I saw posted updates where it's like
he's gone, but his clothes were taken back in August and there's a police report on file you
couldn't find because so and someone has, yeah, like I said, someone was questioned and arrested.
I think they were arrested for non-violently resisting arrest because they were refusing to
turn their phone over. So, you know, speculate on that.
You know it's full of stuff. A fake naked boy.
There had to have been like a cop show investigation where there's a room and there's a good cop and a
bad cop. It's like, what do you know about that little robot boy's clothes? And then like, don't
make me bring in my buddy here because I'm the nice one or whatever. And then like he's like,
you guys spits at the cop or something. I don't know nothing about that little naked robot boy.
And they're actually doing that. The room is just the Wonders of Life pavilion and but they're under
like a caricature of a wine glass smiling or whatever garbage. And it's Disney Security.
Right. I mean, it's ex-Blackwater guys, but they work for Disney.
Right. They're pinning the guy under a big making of me sign that fell off.
Wonders of Life pavilion. And you know what also, like there was just a big article in the New York
Times about podcasts getting turned into TV series. Dirty John just happened and was a Bravo,
a little mini series among others. I think this is our shot. So we got to make it count today
because like Three Guys Gabin is not going to ever be a TV show or at least not a fictionalized one.
But the true crime, that's your shot. So I think we need to make what you're that scene you just
described. Yes. That's in the show. But until but we can't until there's an ending, I don't think we
can actually go pitch this. But I think absolutely free Buzzy is our shot at a television show.
It's a great idea. There's a lot of ways to do it too, because we could also just do the Tom Arnold
Trump version of it, where we just try to make a documentary. We tried to find Buzzy. A very lazy,
thing. We like lie a lot on TV, but maybe they we don't think they're lies because we've done a
lot of cocaine in our lives. That to me feels like the next that was the next generation of
where in the world is Osama bin Laden. Sure. Oh, the Morgan Spurlock. Spurlock tried to find
America's most wanted, you know, and it's a lot of us just stopping freezing the footage and going,
so what happened? We got to crack. We got to get our voices like to up to that register.
This is good. We're going to get eight episodes out of this. And then if God willing, another
animatronic is stolen, we get a season two. Sure. And then maybe we are the ones who orchestrated
that. Maybe we made Jason go steal. Who knows? I mean, there's a lot to talk about just with the
theft. We could do all of a sudden on the theft because what other robots are just hanging around
is also my question that we could get like, why would that not be the first thing that you
protect take out? It's oddly. I mean, our previous experience of this was botanicals just sitting
outside of the parking garage, but they at least didn't. Well, I guess they replaced it with another
ride and that's why it moved. Right. But in this case, if you don't know the whole story, this is
we're talking about the wonders of life pavilion, which is at Epcot center, but you cannot go into
it. And they only open it up for the food and wine festival. So apparently it's just been sitting
there. But if you, and there's a lot of like abandoned type videos and urban exploring where
your fair thing, Mike backpack man. Oh my God, I can't believe I'm in here. I can't believe that.
What's my favorite modern male fashion style, the tactical dipshit, a lot of traps, awful sunglasses,
is very, very weird backpacks with way too many pockets.
But certainly not a, not a weapon or anything. They aren't actually prepared for a fight.
Yeah. Right. Yeah. So this thing's just been sitting there. And if you watch,
like you can learn about what happened to body wars, which is the other main attraction and
wonders of life, which was kind of a star tours, I'll say ripoff attraction that was like the same
layout had a flight simulators. The flight simulators have been gone for a very long time.
So they took the time to take out these massive, you know, hydraulic structures,
but the robot was just sitting there and losing his clothes. Yeah. And they have like
going to D 23, they have exhibits of old robots. Exactly. They have archives. They have plenty of
room somewhere. It's crazy that they wouldn't take the hero of a pretty prominent ride and
put him somewhere else. Somewhere. It's crazy. It's kind of like hanging off of a big arm,
which is where he sits and that's where he pilots from in the show. So he's just dangling off this
thing. Yeah. He could have fallen easily. He could have fallen. Maybe that's how they got him. Well,
and they just left it as it was for years. It very quickly became, you know, not possible to restart
it with, without major maintenance work. Cause you can't just leave hydraulics without servicing
them. Yeah. So a lot of theme park Twitter was upset about that. I'm not that I'm not upset about
it, but they were very much like, you know, we would never like, everyone was very much like you
shouldn't steal from a ride. It's not as per person's property. I'm assuming it's a man. I
don't know why is that it's gotta be a man, right? Who stole the, I believe so. I would guess. It
seems like, yeah. Uh, so my first thought was like, well serves Disney, right? For not locking it down
like you should have, I think I said on the episode, you should have stolen botanicals.
He was rotting. They weren't doing anything. It was garbage. He's a part of theme park history.
If Disney's going to let Buzzy rot, let some backpack weirdo go in there and steal them.
Let us teach them a lesson. I gotta say, this is just me speaking, but as a kid, I loved the
wonders of life pavilion. And I was so sad to see them just let it go to seed. Like even the last,
a few times my family went and like, and when I was finishing high school or in college in the
summers, I feel like it was so sporadically like open or like, I feel like they just treated it
like shit, but I let, I loved both attractions in there, especially today's attraction. I loved
cranium command and I love the building. Like I thought the building was really cool and it's
that they are like cognizant of like, we need to update this a little.
Well, and right next to that weird, that restaurant that just rots the Odyssey,
yes. Like how could there be so much of a major theme park that is just unattended and apparently
sneak in a bowl because there's also, there's a ton of videos of people somehow wandering it.
And they just, I don't think it's even like some stealth Ethan Hunt thing. I think they opened the
door and are in, so they didn't bother to lock the door to one of the, one of seven pavilions
or whatever. I might be wrong about the number. Don't yell at us, but the, like, it's not that
many. How could you lose track of like, how do you not lock the door of one of the only things
in your decaying theme park? It's correct. And also speaks to like the lack of security in general,
which also scares me a little bit. We were like, in my mind and people have said this, they have,
70 plain clothes officers walking around the theme parks and they're ready to spring at a
moment's notice when something goes wrong and you're like, oh, that's good. That's reassuring.
Meanwhile, a robot was told a prominent robot. This isn't just a little star of the show. The
star robot was stolen and no one knew, no one noticed it. There were no cameras on. They don't
made millions of dollars selling like every little, you know, the lid of a trash can from
Disneyland that goes for $30,000. How does a robot, how do they not know the value? Why does
Disney not want to make the potential hundreds of thousands of dollars by selling Buzzy, even if
they aren't going to use it? Yeah, I regret not stealing the robot myself. I regret when I was
there for maybe like not the last trip, but the trip before September when Lindsay was, I wish we
should have gone in and stolen it. But were you cognizant that he was there? No. Did you know he
was there? I didn't know that. That's really the news of all of this. That is the big news. Yeah.
He was left there and you're like, you're a good boy also. You follow the rules, especially at a
Disney park. Of course. I would never, but to teach a lesson, sometimes you must break the rules. That
is what I believe. It's only just. And also I don't, as I said, I don't think it would have been that
hard for you to do. I think it would have taken you 30 seconds and you would have been back in line
for test. It would have been easier doing that than like sneaking into a comic-con party at the
Hard Rock Hotel, which I've tried to do before as well. That's impossible. The most secure place in California
one time of year. Yes. We've, Jason and I have been there. We've snuck into plenty of parties,
a Hard Rock one, impossible. I think this Buzzy theft would have been the easiest thing in the world.
No false identity required. I think you could have held it in your hands and walked out with it. I
think you could just walked it, like held it up like Simba and walked out the exit of Epcot.
As long as you were taking selfies and they're like, oh, it's a person who brought a doll to
take pictures with. Yeah, sure. Whatever. You were changing his diaper. I thought it was a baby.
Just put, yeah. Okay. So there's a naked Buzzy. You have a diaper, put the diaper on Buzzy,
put it in a baby carriage and wheel it out. You put your tactical dipshit sunglasses on it.
I thought this was a changing station, a giant domed changing station. Should I replace
like Buzzy, like Indiana Jones style with a different doll? Like a my buddy doll or
like that's a, what's it? Bring an actual child. A child fine. He'll make his way out of there
someday. Yeah. But that being said, they will never notice the child's there. So the child will die
probably because no one ever goes in there or has any cameras. Anything good. There could be like a
weird race of people live like some scavenger race living in the wonders of life. Wow. What else is
still there? Like let's think about this. What else is still? Some of those bikes that you pilot around
like that. I just remember a lot of like what's the actual, the recumbent bikes. Yeah. That you
could go through the parks or go through cities. You could ride through a video of Disneyland and
I'm in Disney world watching a fake video. I'm pretending I'm back at home in Disneyland. Yeah.
I loved all that shit. Yeah. Yeah. But are there any other things still standing that have robots?
Like are there any, like, cause like river country famously, but they don't have an
animatronics, but river country is still kind of standing. Although they're going to be abandoned
area with a robot. That's what I'm trying to think of. Wait a minute. If Buzzy was there,
is hypothalamus still there? The robot, the other robot character. I think it's very
good chance. Hypothalamus is still there. Nobody wants him. He's just on a pole.
No one likes hypothalamus. I think you could take a Louisville slugger to that pole. I think you
could beat that. You could break that pole in half and get out of there with the top half of
the hypothalamus. I mean, right now I think they probably have the security locked down. Well,
now I'm just saying before this, I think hypothalamus, I, yeah, I think for sure
hypothalamus is still there. I think you could get on that land boat ride and just pick up like a
guy on a rocking chair and walk out with it and no one would care. You can get back on the boat.
Oh yeah. The rocking chair guy. Everyone on the boat is asleep. So that nobody notices.
Could you get one of the alligator alligators? Can you stop the ride for a sec? I'm going to grab
this. Yeah, sure. No problem. Horizons was demolished. So none of that is still there.
I can't, this is a good question. I'm having trouble thinking of anywhere. I don't think so.
It would have a robot. It's a unique situation. Right. And Disneyland and California Adventure,
I don't think have anything. The real estate is so limited. Knott's Berry Farm. Oh. Let Kingdom of
the Dinosaurs sit for a long time. So it's possible that you could have broken in there and stolen a
dinosaur. But you know what? Buzzy is perfect for it because he's small. There's no way I'm getting
out with Botanicus. There's no way you're getting out with a full dinosaur. With a full dinosaur.
Could you have gotten out with just Botanicus as like leaf clothes? Oh maybe. I could have,
if I could have taken the staff. Well the staff is yeah. Just replace it with like a tiki torch.
Alt-right. Oh new merch. Alt-right Botanicus. Alt-righticus.
Whoever buys that one we are giving to. You're banned. Yeah you're banned and we're giving your
name to the government. To the watch list. Yeah. He's using his crystal ball to imagine a world
that's cleansed. Yeah at the very least having the Southern Poverty Law Center put you on blast.
It's a shame that tiki torch, you can't have a tiki torch now because they still lead the good
use of tiki torches. Well I think you can have one in a backyard but I don't think you can hold one.
All right no more holding them. Yeah because the tropical hideaway at Disneyland. Right.
Presumably, I haven't been there, presumably it has tiki torches but if we all went and picked up
the torches and all went like ho! No good. When you see that photo of all of the alt-right guys I
can imagine they're all they're all screaming like Howard Dean screams ho! 70 of them at once.
So hands off the torches and it's fine. Okay that's fine. Well I guess at this point we go
backwards and figure out how we got to this point. How we got to this ride in general. Yeah how did we get to
this? I mean like I said I loved this ride as a kid. I loved creating a command. I loved
the Wonders of Life pavilion. I feel like it's another thing where it's like you are
leaving money on the table by not having more throwback merch for that. Like letting this go
to seed. It reminds me of I know I've talked about this on the show like Marvel just letting the X-men
kind of languish for many years in the comp because they were so they're like well we have to publish
the comics because they they do make money. Well they wanted to kill it because Fox owned the movie
rights. But there were so many kids like when we were people our age there were so many kids who
grew up loving the X-men so much it's like you were just leaving money on the table same thing.
They did do Buzzy and General Knowledge, Vinylmations about four or five years ago. But very little.
There's no merchandise for all of the parts of the body. There's no Halloween costumes for right
in the brain. You gotta make your own. Well they probably have to pay rights for Hans and Franz.
Yeah but they're generic Hans and Franz. Yeah that's the thing. You know they use the catch phrases of Hans and Franz.
Hans and Franz wear gray sweats. These got left and right ventricle have big muscly arms so they are
different. This is getting ahead of ourselves but did Lorne have to sign off on the use of them or
did he know even? I can only imagine because I think he has to sign off on anybody doing anything.
Probably Lovitz doing it. Right there's that famous David Spade story of him trying to like wanting to
do like a million dollar commercial for the Super Bowl while he was on the show and Lorne said no.
Oh no. That's the old days too because now I think Lorne would love it. Yeah but Spade has a story.
Every SNL cast member is in constant commercials. Yeah that's the dream now. Right but back in the
day he didn't like that. Yeah. He prevented him from doing it. But then I love the idea of somebody
coming on. Look at Lorne. There's a Disney World ride and they want to use Dana and Kevin and Hans.
We're lip-cocks in a place where they can appeal to the kids. It's kind of got a world's fair vibe.
I know all about the edutainment industry. I know. I know. I'm doing that Bradberry thing.
I gotta find out if he ever knew about this. Yeah yeah yeah. I hope he doesn't find out about
those impressions or we're screwed. But yeah I think like I think the fondness for this thing
does come from it was kind of the first Disney World or the first Epcot thing rather pretty
specifically for kids. Like everything was pretty unfriendly and grown up and super educational.
This thing's educational as well but with these actors with with Carvey and you know with Charles
Grodin. Now we're getting into what the kids like. I mean my guy. What year does this open again? 89.
89 yeah so it's like so pre-Beethoven Grodin. Yeah yeah. Where would a kid have known him from at that point?
Pre-Clifford Grodin. Right. Maybe mid-Clifford. I think Clifford took like oh yeah Clifford was
a shoot and just sat on the shelf for a long time. Yeah they shot Clifford and like with
540. Yeah how many years later? It was crazy. Yeah and then with another Epcot man Martin Short.
Oh that's right. Yeah just down the way and making the Clifford cast was owning the part.
No Mary Steenburgen. Well Mary Steenburgen I think attended the opening of the Back to the Future
ride but is not featured therein. Right. And that's how the cast of Clifford fits into the theme park universe.
You wanted to know. It's something else that that is like cabin boy level oddball movie. Yeah yeah.
I don't know how often today also that you're seeing somebody play wildly not their type. Oh
with a 40 year old man playing a child. Yeah yeah which sort of would things like that would happen
more often back then I feel. I guess I guess the is in Little Man the Wayans Brothers movie is
Marlon Wayans a short person playing a baby. What is the plot of Little Man? Oh what is the plot of Little Man?
All I've ever seen is the clip of him like we're like a woman he puts his like little baby head
to a woman's bosom and he likes it and that's all I know and I was like I think he's like an older
person. The movie should have been a Vine it should have been that scene the end. Right. It might be
you got to the theater and there's just a title card that says that was it you saw it don't tell
anybody there's no movie here. All right. Here with this booze for you in the back. Your secret save with me.
Your secret save with me Little Man. Let's see the plot is Calvin babyface Sims who is a very short
convict. Okay so he's a very short man who pretends to be a baby. So he's literally a little man. He's
close to Clifford syndrome as you're getting today. Let's bring back this genre. Let's get more man babies
in our films. So yeah we were saying so this attraction opened in 89 the pavilion opened in 89
little after the the actual opening of Epcot. It was in the original plans there was a doesn't
this sound thrilling a health and life pavilion. Doesn't that sound exciting? Yeah I'm glad they
Yeah and the things in it sounded fairly dry. Oh like a show called Head Trip that would share
space with a dentistry themed show called Tooth Follies. Oh the Tooth Follies. I wish Tooth Follies existed.
So bad because Tooth Follies it seems fake it seems like there's no way they would ever make a
thing called Tooth Follies. But how would they all be different from each other? The teeth you mean?
Yeah assuming that it is teeth coming to life. It would have to be teeth coming to life. Yeah let's
think on that. We got molars, we got baby teeth, got canine, got uh maybe like a fang comes in.
Did you call them front boys? Those two front boys? You call your two front teeth front boys?
My front boys? Well and for sure it would have the food rocks situation of the the rotten uh the bad
guys who were like and like who like sucked up sugar and like didn't want to be rejected the
brush say no to brushes and they like they try to poison the whole thing. Dave Thomas is the bad
tooth or something. I'm trying to think of other like sc tv level stars of the time. Oh sure. We
were just watching clips uh over the break of Follow That Bird and it's Dave Thomas is the bad
guy and Joe Flaherty. I'll put hey I'll put this on the Scott is scared uh follow that bird. Uh Miss
Finch. Oh. The I am scared still today from childhood of Miss Finch. There's a part where
she laid just any part where she like pulls up and like leans out of the van and just kind of goes
hmm I am scared of that. When she's chasing Big Bird through the parade, like that to me was like
the space that Chucky occupies for probably a lot of kids. My wife for sure. Uh I have like Miss
Finch is the worst whore. That's my it. I hear you. I guess I have seen that. Is it this is Big Bird
gets lost? Well Big Bird kind of a road trip and gets adopted by a bird family but they're weird.
I should not have. This is going to be another this should have been episode full episode but I
should have not have mentioned Follow That Bird but uh Miss Finch yeah this is where Big Bird ends
up in like a circus essentially yeah and like is a blue which is another saddest thing ever
fucking thing all my feelings are contained in this movie but I know I saw it multiple times
as a kid I thought it was some like sctv spin-off movie or something for a second where you're
talking about Dave Thomas and Joe Flaherty. They're in it they're these kind of like bad like carnival
barker guys they're like they're the Pinocchio like well round you up put you in a cage they're
very good they're very funny in it yeah John Candy's in it at some point uh Chevy Chase is
the news guy I liked that a lot as a kid I think Lorraine Newman does a voice. I'm gonna admit uh
that is a big hole in my comedic education I really have not seen much sctv. I haven't a ton
except for this one this thing where uh Rick Moranis is in a pink suit and he sings
this bizarre lounge easy listening version of Downtown the Patula Clark song with background
vocals from like a ghostly Michael McDonald who's not there this is my favorite I mean there's the
more famous Michael McDonald right Moranis sketch where he's like rushing in to do the
background parts on Red Like the Wind both of those sketches are phenomenal they make me laugh
so this Downtown one is not that known oh my god it is so and he's like just in this horrible suit
just strolling around weird shady parts of Toronto uh I can't I'm not gonna do justice describing it
it's so funny sctv I don't know now we're talking sctv we're getting back to Cranium Creme but sctv
is a much like tighter show than early SNL oh yeah I mean it's not live. I think by design it was post SNL and I think it was there like they were like we're not
gonna let the talent go to SNL anymore we're gonna do this our way and we're gonna do it tighter and
with um and cinematically and you know nail these styles in a way that SNL can't because they're live
and closer to an actual like second city company yes review yes for sure um follow up the big thing
up to me about sctv is like when those when all those guys were off the show like they just
dominated yeah right oh yeah 90s like just killer everything you could name from all of those guys
there's obviously everything Rick Moranis is in John Candy Katherine O'Hara all when you add up all
the parlor John Hughes movies and Home Alone and everything Rick Moranis and Ghostbusters and
like god what a like assassin squad of comic actors Eugene Levy holy shit yeah it is wild
to see everybody from there because it feels that feels like the most successful sketch comedy cast
of all time yeah got about it and it's so many of them made it to blockbusters like even the ones
that aren't the star the top build star of the movie and they came out of the gate quick too
like splash Eugene Levy John Candy amazing in that gigantic hit movie bringing us back to Disney
sure a little bit but like yeah hey this is just a good earnest yeah discussion of uh
anyway they'll play the teeth they'll play the teeth in teeth follies though if this were back
in time that might have been the era you're all sct people sctv people in uh uh Disney attractions
are there much and well Moranis is in Honey I Shrunk Fear and Martin Short is in three things right
a bunch yeah yeah yeah quite a few um and then i'm trying to think yeah is John Candy ever in a ride
or anything i don't know it seems like Eugene Levy should be in a theme park attraction oh yeah
isn't that waiting to happen yeah well we'll look into this someone's like screaming at their phone
right now because there's like a voice someone did a voice in the cartoon and then they reprised it
and ride and yeah yeah yeah yeah probably actually relatedly uh i do have a little here i'll take
voices out of it just for good to make to crunch this a little okay can you guys name on camera
appearances from SNL cast members in theme park attractions i have a count of six
and not including cranium command including cranium command which is so that's three of them
well Martin Short is an SNL cast member too so many of those things a ton of them oh canada
monster sound show cinema g and making with me right uh race through new york my man of course
you got it yes that's one one more though there's one more uh i'm trying to think
hint i just named it it was in a list that i said oh oh shit disney or universal disney okay man
this isn't good podcasting again it's a lot of silence building tension just say it again we'll
need to build tension when we do the true crime buzzy thing yeah we're like the hydraulic fluid
left alone for that long develops a deep crimson shade so it looks like this crime scene of blood
where buzzy once sat controlling the child well and we'll need to like we'll fill every we'll
we'll need more air in the podcast and we'll have to have that music that all the podcasts have like
it's always american beauty podcast music is locked in american beauty from 1999 and you know
like in a very sinister voice reading cadet benny is 24 years old benny is twice as old as cadet
an was when benny was as old as and is now how old is cadet an that's one of the that's one of the
trivia question from the line yeah that's one of the trivia questions from the line oh okay
well to answer this trivia question uh chevy chase is the answer do you know the ride it's
a phone show oh sounds dangerous with jerry i guess people are not i don't remember that
yeah well we'll hit that one when we're uh really in the dregs and that's it there's no those are
all the on camera with his voices right that's uh that'll be too long to to say but that's i mean
okay the the to get back on track i think the bigger point here is that i think it was maybe
little unusual to have current uh comedians and pop cult like recognizable pop culture figures in
theme park attractions right a little more common now still not a ton but i think they were like
in this era at mgm studios and with cranium command they were starting to break into that a little
bit um and i heard an interview with the director of cranium commands jerry reese jerry reese who
another sounds dangerous connection oh he sounds dangerous he sounds dangerous jerry reese's website
lists all he has been involved with like 16 disney attractions there's so many so many uh
uh i mean michael and mickey is one i don't know if people remember this super well but if you never
got to see it there's this great it like played at on the disney mgm tour where like mickey gets
michael eisner to round up all of the characters to go to a screening on the lot and it's very
charming and mickey michael has a mickey watch and mickey has a michael eisner watch i think
that's still one of my favorite things they're leaving money on the table by not selling a
michael eisner watch oh yeah if we can figure out how to miscell watches yeah well let me let me ask
you a question uh i keep sidetracking but i am a big toy guy statue guy if they sold like a
reasonably price and i'm saying reasonable 50 to 100 yeah it was like a nice michael eisner doll
with mickey there and it had maybe the watch gag in it would you want it yeah yeah yeah like
i'm not a really a toy guy and i would get it i was like i think scott would want this you have
a small collection of things but i think that's in my wheelhouse they're missing out not licensing
eisner i think yeah he should license out his like classic like young whatever age he was in the 80s
yes because that is he's almost more iconic to walt than me because that's what i grew up with
right and walt now is everywhere and they have these big paintings they sell in the different
art stores on main street and like there's no eisner and eisner was such a big part of all of
these things yeah it would be funny yeah time has passed and so now we're raising him up too soon
for our eiger dolls we don't need no i don't know he needs more time on camera watching him
introduce the star wars thing on the christmas parade this year was weird he also i feel like
changed topic too fast there was no he was like happy holidays to everyone i hope you're having
a wonderful holiday season star wars is coming up and like there was no it was a real rough
he's got to learn seg with the art of segways right which eisner obviously brilliant perfect on camera
perfect on camera yes all those eisner watches i'm buying all the eisner merch
eisner merch i'm so curious again leave the money on the table they're leaving money on the table
with like with karate chop action great uh getting stars to fall in line uh i'm thinking like a
hundred hey jeff daniels you think you're you really think you're getting an extra
500 grand for arachnophobia like a hundred like i have this batman 60s toy up here that's very
detailed and has a lot of like posability that level michael eisner detailed doll
with a little mickey i think is the way to go yeah and then sell that on the in the statue and
art store like batman he's holding a big bomb but it's the in his case it's the film canister
for the movie powder is there a better disney bomb from his era well the plans for california
adventure sure oh yeah yeah poke fun in it anyway when we have eyes around the show which people
i've been noticing over tweeting at him and his son to do our show oh yeah that makes me please
don't bother too much breck is a very busy and successful yeah but i have a part of me let him
do it on his own terms whenever breck whenever you want to come around we have it yeah part of me
thinks we could get michael easier than breck yeah maybe but i think he likes to talk he had like a
yeah he had a show on cnbc for a little while yes kind of in conversation he talked to lauren
for a while maybe they established their friendship when he asked to can we get lovitz and carvey and
neil and so that's i that's i think how we got to the this was an early instance of of stars of the
time and especially this to me stars of their time like playing their game doing their shtick i mean
bobcats there he's doing oh yeah yeah absolutely well well no oh sorry okay oh uh you know hans
and franz unofficial hans unlicensed hans and franz uh grodin just one of the best straight
men of all time one of the best voices reasonable time yeah yeah yeah yeah and george went is very
much in his zone right when yeah i think um well so i heard an interview i think this was on uh
season pass our friends of the season pass podcast they interviewed jerry reese who
dragged ended up directing cranium command he also directed back to neverland which was another
this was a thing on the disney m disney m james studios tour as well uh where walter cronkite is
reporting uh from the theme park or something and then robin williams as not named as robin
williams but he's a tourist who's you know doing shtick like robin williams he comes up and like
takes a tour and gets animated and learns about animation in the process and ends up in neverland
and making hijinks in a robin williams way there was apparently according to jerry reese some
general consternation about this like well aren't the theme parks kind of this escapist world and
why would you have just robin williams doing his robin williams thing and he said well if you think
about it panocchio the voice of uh jiminy cricket in the 40s was recognizable as that comedian doing
his oh yeah edwin edwin absolutely yes a guy you might know from tv or movies and and we'll do a
cartoon character who's like him right phil harris the voice of blue was like a boisterous
kind of drunky radio guy uh so like uh so it was actually playing into a tradition more than
anybody thought and kind of updating it back to neverland went over so well that they apparently
started just throwing stuff jerry reese like can you fix this can you be part of this there was
some little thing on the tour where he directed george lucas setting up a clip or something or
thus the night of the opening of disney mgm studios george lucas and eisner take him aside
and like hey jerry can you fix this indiana jones stunt show for us we just feel like it's not
there's no like i don't know it doesn't have any heart there's no build there's no story
so now so this guy all of a sudden is just everywhere like like lucas needs him to do
these things where he's a fix it guy is cranium command um which is about was having a lot of
problems and was a like hated project within the company at the time yeah well they had outsourced
the animation to a different company and it was coming out apparently was all coming out they were
they were giving them and imagineering like they were following the directives but it seemed like
coming out very dry and like i think they said like oh you know like those 1940s informational
films they show in schools and it seems like they were making that and it was dry and kind of
condescending and not super funny yeah and i maybe you saw the same thing as me i found a list of
like what so they had uh they had jerry reese watch a cut of it and so a lot of the pieces of
this were there there was a uh there was there was like you know guys in your head controlling
your body uh general knowledge i think the character was still in there but it wasn't
buzzy wasn't buzzy yeah it was a guy named captain cortex which sucks like that i disagree with that
you think that's okay i don't say it's great but i don't think it's i don't know if you tell me
yeah i mean it's pleasing to the ear but i think that comes from it was a lot harder
a harder star trek bridge parody like i don't need to get so hardcore yet buzzy's kind of a rex rip
off in my mind i was thinking he's rex he's not as good as rex and i think i'm i look down a little
bit on him because of that i like his design but i feel like i know that you're getting sad
but buzzy is a poor man's rex is all i'll say oh i'm sorry jason's got i hear what you're saying
the harshness of it i'm being a little harsh maybe i'm i have five hours of sleep but maybe
that's just me today harsh for the the sake of humor uh you'll put your differences we'll put our
differences aside i may be taking this personally because we were texting over the holidays and i
said i'm gonna get ahead of this now i know i resemble buzzy and like set a side-by-side picture
where i had drawn the hats and the headphones on myself jason sharon which i will post yes please
jason shared and for buzzy on disney plus the new cranium command tv show let's start that going
now okay so in addition to the true crime podcast about the finding of buzzy right there is also we
will also have a narrative show in which jason is buzzy yeah cross platform four quadrants all
the words all the buzz phrases there'll be a tier you pay for on disney plus it's just cranium
command based programming it's an extra five dollars on top of the regular fee well you know
what's there's a lot there because you there's all of the workplace drama within the head right it's
it's yeah jason is buzzy uh you know trying to keep the gang together it's kind of a uh it's kind
of a 30 rock sort of like everybody's a kook in my office but we got to unite for the common goal
and then you can also do wonder years style coming of age stuff with the boy whose body
you're piloting oh yeah and then you can do like some prestige stuff like he discovered like
has to cope with a death in the family or like if you really want to like cranium command of like
kid from gummo like oh god really dark art movie sort of cranium command yeah i mean every genre
and the potential for cranium command all the actors that appeared in the ride aren't on a tv
show right now and could easily do the show we could have going through it and yeah you're right
they're all available wow so that's we'll line that up once we get everything else they're all
still around they're all still around and i think all of those people are very funny they're great
everyone's great what a good cast so we've already got a perfect cast now led up by jason sherdin and
anybody ever needed to leave here's what happens like if you know if george went wants out then
the kid gets sick needs a stomach transplant a transplant yeah you know a stomach transplant
yeah that thing that happens all the time and and you and you so he and that's a very dramatic
episode as well and then you end up with a new uh i don't know who josh gad sure i mean he's busy
but i'm hungry i'm hungry um we can do i'll put mitch on the list oh yeah sure i'll submit it to
disney it's up to them if if that's gonna work for him i think mitch would knock it out of the park
i agree 100 we believe in mitch uh so this is oh my god great ideas left and right we can barely
focus on i know the actual on the ride we're just trying we're trying to stay it's just the joy of
ride is pulling us away from the disaster of uh how it started i know it's a bummer to think about
uh that there was ever a time when this wasn't working so apparently all right so the so they
show a cut of it to jerry reeves and a cut of this is very confusing because if you have not been on
this attraction you are inside a head and there are there is a animatronic doing a lot of the
lifting who's going back and forth on an arm there's two screens that are the eyes there's
other screens that are the where the various parts of the body pop up and uh do their status reports
so imagine trying to piece this together how do you possibly edit this thing it's so many components
all sinking up so they show jerry reeves some version of this uh he said as you said jason this
it's very obvious and patronizing uh it's it's like talking down to you it's too educational
uh the i screens were only used occasionally and then shut off so there's these are like the the
biggest screens in the theater and they are black for a ton of the show and he's like no no this
needs to be madcap we need that needs to always be on and little sequences the kids running to get
the bus and he's in a food fight and all these pov things that'll be tough to pull off but look
really cool uh and he also i think all of the body parts that they fleshed too were animated and not
live action so that was one of his pitches was well if we don't have a lot of time here
let's only animate the pre-show uh and the general the rest of it let's do live action and let's have
these recognizable actors so instead of building all this mythology it's like oh george wendt i
know him uh uh uh charles groden i know him and you can plug right into their appeal yeah and it
seems like they they were able to accomplish that pretty easily because when you break down what the
actual production is you shoot all the pov stuff in the school and the house and stuff and then
they went to sound stages and shot each comedian and like it was very interesting reading about
like okay so they had to like match shots and use blur so like the eyes looked right and stuff and
then when he was shooting the comedians they had a monitor playing the the other the live action
footage they had shot from the kids pov really just incredible thinking about this and i i saw
an anecdote about it the the ad on it then after this went and worked on t2 judgment day and he
this was the best training for that because that was so insanely complex of a production wow it's
so deceptively complicated yeah because like the thing is very fast and i think most as we usually
the barometer is like most dads wander into the riot and they're like okay yeah got it okay and
then they leave but like if you really think about breaking it down and how you have to coordinate
all of it it's pretty crazy there's a ton go and all the mediums it is cell animation apparently
the last disney product fully done in the traditional yeah like in can paint style
you know other things still used a lot of that but not entirely front to back i believe at the
newly opened disney mgm studios animation wing oh they oh that's right that was also on the
jerry reese interview that you if you went it right when the park opened if you took a tour of
the animation facilities the they take the first place they take you is the storyboard room and
they were storyboarding cranium command a future attraction for just up the road so yeah like yeah
live action and pov and robots all of this working together and apparently when jerry reese had to
show rough cuts of this thing it was like unwatchable and katzberg is sitting in this
going like i guess i just got to trust you here because i don't know what i'm looking at i don't
like uh and it i think it didn't really come together until the last minute which they gave
once jerry reese gave notes on it then they gave it's like all right you fix it you have like free
rain but this we've used half the budget and you have to do it in this time frame like it is
it's crazy how complex it is and how it's still like watching the video of it i was like this
still holds up this holds up better than journey into your imagination a ride still into in the
everything holds up better than that yeah i know but it's it's weird i mean it's yeah it plays it
plays well yeah yeah and it's all very dynamic and i think the the style or like the rushed timeline
created some fun stylistic stuff oh yeah they that's i think why they had to do uh cut out
sort of monty python terry gilliam style in the pre-show if you if you watch the pre-show like the
commandos get inside their heads and the and the heads are live action and they like climb up into
them uh which i associated at the time as you can't do that i was gonna say that yeah what i think
i'm gonna go no no that's monty python they stole that from yeah i had to learn that that that was
not a like an open style anybody could do that was terry gilliam that scared me too as a kid uh
just in general oh the idea of your being head cracking open too like i who i hated it yeah yeah
that pre-show of course the first directing job for kirk wise and gary truesdale yes that's another
thing that's crazy too is that situation that um that was their first directing job and catzenberg
liked that short so much he may have liked it more more than the actual that's what he said he goes
this is better than the ride it's better than the ride and so he gave them it's like hey can you
take it over and that feature was beauty and the beast yeah god which also had a yeah they were
there was a director who had to get fired from that right so yeah oh my god yeah you handled that
little pre-show so well please make this oscar caliber but similar problems like it wasn't
funny it was like it was too serious so is that right they they they had done this funny pre-show
and and they got to do this uh should also say jerry reese directed a movie i really liked as a
kid the brave little toaster yeah sure um which is i mean already i think that's a great uh work
uh it is the best i think of what i call the upsetting era of animation we're talking create
mouse detective land before time uh american tale the first one less the second one all dog go all
it's good to have and probably the most upsetting one rockadoodle rockadoodle upset me because it
was always lightning storms and tornadoes and he couldn't see lost his voice and he finally gets
it back but just wait rockadoodle was most upsetting to you as a child stressed me out
rockadoodle obviously the scariest movie ever made is follow that bird are you crazy jason that's a
yeah he isn't elvis chicken but he's like washed up elvis chicken for a lot of the movie
the idea of struggling in an industry stressed you out as well that you were preparing for later
oh yeah um yeah all dogs go to heaven is about dogs dying i mean i hear that yeah you you may
also in that list missed secretive nym which i don't know very well but isn't that fairly upsetting
and very so i think so black collard is very dark as well what about fern golly i don't know
there's darkness yeah the smog is very upsetting i think too though that is like 90s like i think
in the 90s you saw a brighter color palette like and i found that more rescuers down under
fern go is it yeah yeah yeah yeah that's like 93 isn't it wow i'm also uh also very upset by
rover danger field i mean seeing seeing it and seeing a poor defenseless animal get no respect
more setting than these sort of dark uh rockadoodles 91 sorry oh okay so so tail end but
little mermaid rescuers down under fern gult you saw a brighter looking animated films and i think
i found that more at ease well oliver and company brighter looking forget the dark poster of rock
a doodle see but that's that's so bright not accurate to the movie because he's just constantly
i gotta watch rockadoodle i've never seen rockadoodle yeah me neither we gotta watch
what you're talking about i watched it a lot too because we had it on vhs i mean look at the
trailer for rock a great mouse detective i think i was comforted by like well he's clearly a
sherlock holmes type like i knew the concept of sure he is a hero he'll figure this out
i will tell you i will say this in to to defend you now rockadoodle is darker than that poster
it is like a little bit of trailer you're watching yeah just a little like darker color palette
um and it doesn't look like the fun romp i always imagined all right we gotta we gotta do it
just gripping this uh you know uh erinovsky-esque um dramatic film it's like the cool world right
i mean if i had to write like a term paper i would probably and it's people have already
probably talked about this where it's like all of those movies and like the pre of those movies
black cauldron all that crap all the scratchy dark looking disney and other animated movies
it's probably like oh is this the first or second generation that really grew up with feature life
cartoons and now they have their own ideas but they want to push the limits they want to make
it dark like oh maybe yeah well and it also seems like that 80s when disney was not before the
kind of darker in general was a disney at some point correct i believe he was i think so
forgetting another name in the in the darkness i mean like uh it wasn't laster originally involved
with brave little toaster yes and they didn't want to do it and then he just made a different
version of it called toy story oh were they so were they sort of affiliated well just like in
the sense that it's like not human like little characters going on adventure like there's a lot
of humanized inanimate objects yeah anthropomorphize and toy story originally
notoriously the the like animatic storyboard cut of it was very horrible yeah depressing and
woody was an asshole and uh so a lot of these things i think start i yeah i don't know i think
there's something about animation i guess that's so like you know nebulous that you can end up with
something that just i don't know this should work that we got funny voices we got good artists and
why doesn't it work yeah it's kind of magical when it like does all come together there is a
figure by the way in this i have i have a lot of like i'll hey dry facts ahead i wrote down there's
some pretty interesting like personnel on this on cranium command in general especially the pre-show
and there's a figure i found who i hadn't heard of before who's uh you know maybe part of navigating
animation out of what you're talking about into the brighter zone uh this guy named david pruixma
who was the main character animator of buzzy in the pre-show uh he's he's he had a nickname at
cowlarts where a lot of these guys came from he was the king of cute and uh and he applied that
buzzy certainly one of buzzy's pretty adorable if there was i bet captain cortex was not as
sort of rambunctious relatable as buzzy right so he made the character cuter made the whole thing
work he went on to animate the seahorse messenger and little mermaid oh he did mrs pots and
in uh beating the beast like the supervising animator of these parts the sultan in aladdin
another short retunned lovable roly poly guy i like that
you have yourself career in much better shape than the sultan i try to work out uh and uh and
he apparently uh well oh i think i missed uh pumba i think he works in pumba and then uh
personally animated almost every frame of uh flit the hummingbird in uh pocahontas oh so you're
not even looking at him like giving notes like this guy personally drew a lot which is crazy
to think about i'll be honest i did not remember flit no none of those characters really landed
but i bet if you watched a big if you watched a bunch of flit you would probably appreciate
i mean i know the art of it i'm sure i would i mean i know grandmother willow i know um meek
what's the raccoons name meeko meeko uh and then that's about it huh huh now that's a whole other
the the angular 90s mid to late 90s disney animated pocahontas uh hunchback i guess a little
certainly hercules atlantis yeah everything got more they all got like like like corners in their
noses right yeah got a lot more like uh yeah what what is and the dreamworks character oh you're
like road to el dorado's are all kind of like craggy and angular and weird which one of these
fellows uh went on to do atlantic her quies did directed atlantis oh that's right oh and they both
did uh they did hunchback they did hunchback together and then uh the other one went i think
they split off and did did their own uh work one of them directed p body and sherman a few oh okay
um other personnel on this thing the music by david newman who is randy newman's cousin who is
also a film score composer uh he has like all the newmans are film score composers everyone in that
family his his uh his not his dad but his like uncles were composers too god everybody and like
going way back to the dawn of cinema yeah yeah uh this he he reunited with jerry reese uh having
also done the score of brave little toaster and the original frank and weenie short for uh tim
burton uh went on to do all of danny davido's movies from thrill mama to the train to death to
smoochie wow uh ice age bill and ted the flintstones the mighty ducks the nutty professor uh and and the
recent night school so he's still doing a ton of stuff this is one of his first uh scores uh and
this was the weirdest one to me the dp of this thing who did an amazing job with all of the pov
all of those crazy sets in different worlds for all of the body parts there's a guy named david
m walsh who was also the dp of the woody allen film everything you always wanted to know about
sex but we're afraid to ask which culminates in a section that is essentially cranium command
oh yeah have you guys seen this movie yeah the final it's like an anthology movie kind of in a
piece of it is the like a body preparing for sex woody allen is one of the sperms and in the control
center tony randall and burt reynolds it really that movie may be the real impetus of the idea of
lots of little guys in your body controlling it yeah that's interesting the same guy shot both of
them very strange wow that is weird he's never talked about i assume there's no big interview
with this man about cranium command or anything to say like oh that's why they hired me because
they saw that and they knew i could handle uh military sets inside of bodies huh uh and let's
not forget an animator on this one of their first jobs pete doctor director of inside out
right he said you know heavily influenced by this working on this attraction so crazy this was one
of his first jobs ever he was a development intern yes the disney company was like there was there
was such little staff and they had to rush this thing together and people liked his shorts uh and
they so they said i you know you could probably handle some shots of this movie so there's a
couple of shots fully animated by pete doctor one of his first things went on to be involved in every
pixar movie directed monsters inc up inside out uh and is now the creative head of pixar so yeah
crazy uh incredible staff of this thing who all went on to do like to really it's like an all-star
group it truly is yeah all sorry directing co-director of ins- ronnie del car- oh ronnie
del carmen is the co-director and i think pete doc oh really okay as director they started doing
more of that in recent years at pixar oh maybe even in the next people sort of an apprentice
yeah sure sure but yeah inside out also yeah cranium command predates inside out in terms of
watching the mechanics inside a body although as pete doctor points out it's a lot more emotional
than the the physical and the functionality of the body right but i'd also like to shout out
another thing uh between bridging the gap of tiny people and bodies from uh cranium command inside
out we can't forget about meet dave the eddie murphy film in which eddie murphy there is a
spaceship that looks like eddie murphy being piloted by lots of tiny people including our
have you guys heard this story he's told this on several podcasts i think i would repeat it but
where he was hired to be lieutenant butt because they saw a headshot and thought he was fat from
the neck down they like some of the vile from his face thought he was fat so they hired him to be
the butt and then it was a really tense filming it and they fired him on set and he walked away
was upset and then they came back and said oh yeah we well we thought you were fat so we got the sound
guy to do it because the sound guy's fat anyway you want to be the kneecap and he filmed a scene
felt very just like hey let's toss him a bone the scene is not in the movie his shoulder maybe is
in the movie uh a very odd thing but yeah paul shears done time in the in the body minds the body
might uh the other one of course is herman's head oh my god there's a lot of these it's a robust
genre yeah the 1991 show on fox where he had like four different people i think in his head
playing these like different emotions right including yardley smith yes yes simpsons
that's the only thing i know about it and there was some like simpsons joke at some point where
lisa defends herman's head like right yeah yeah that's why that's in there um now i solely know
herman's head as a comedy point of reference like i think on the simpsons and another 90s show made
a joke about like herman's head it was on for three seasons oh my god what yeah what that's wild
that's like one of those like fox shows oh man the dog's comfortable uh uh where uh like i didn't
realize how long like models inc like shows i didn't watch but you would see ads for it during
the simpsons sure rock i was thinking about whatever rock was roc yes yes they started doing
rock live when how was it i always wanted to see rock live why haven't i achieved that dream now
yeah well we'll do that in this when we watch uh rockadoodle we'll also watch rock
oh yeah all right yeah rock fest podcast the ride rock fest yeah so followed by action check out j
wars action we're gonna yeah we'll do a mini podcast every episode of action uh was on herman's
head too whoa several simpsons cast um the do you what did you see inside control rooms in herman's
head do you know that's a good question they represent the who what was in the head um well
the poster has like four people and his head is split open but i don't think that's how they
showed it are you freaked out by that still on some like baby level yeah yeah split open
there's uh i didn't like when mr burns cut open homer's head in the treehouse of horror and you'd
see his brain that's upsetting yeah as a kid i was like it really creeped me out i thought that was
cool wow you were well you were because we've established you were the coolest of the three of
a child oh i don't i didn't know i i'm looking at the opening to herman's head right now i think
they were just like sitting around like this and like talking through stuff love the opening by the
way great strobe effects yeah really it looked better on old there's hank hank is hank in the
head i guess these are all in his head ken hudson campbell rick lawless the original lardy ling
peter mckenzie yeah so that's i think that's how they were in the head they were all like crammed
in there huh i think that's like bloody or did it look like a library was i think it looked like
a yeah like a library like a little crammed hold on i'll pause it here because the audience is
riveted again yep yeah it almost looks like the back like beekman's world in the back or something
it's very fish eye yeah in your face um the the inside the brain the uh brain brain dramas i
don't know what to call these um if uh it's i i like a lot of stuff in this genre yeah scratchers
sure great i guess that's more they're called head scratchers
oh
fox now disney owns fox so disney owns herman's head oh officially i think so they can get well
all right on the disney plus show disney plus show and in and obviously they'll be fine giving
us the inside out characters yeah easy the the oh my god it's waiting to happen the cranium command
boy dates the girl from inside out and herman is around as like an uncle figure
and then who owns meet dave i hope it's fox and he owns it now it might be fox oh please oh please
i think that i think it might be is it fox oh my god here we go is it fox anticipation
podcast music distributed by 20th century fox yeah dave all right let's go all the head
name of this series and extended universe is pretty wow what a triumph yeah i don't mean to
make jason not the main character it'll still center on you but all these other you know the
long the more we can expand this universe the better it will be for me so do you guys want to
get woody allen in on it too i don't know burt reynolds i guess is in wild about that amazon
show we'll discuss off off pop um so uh oh my god a robust genre and this is a fantastic entry
in it should we talk about the uh should we go through the story of the of the ride yes you see
you enter through you enter into a hallway with four posters in it which have uh a trivia post
well there's a propaganda recruiting posters which is a go-to theme park cue thing that's off
yeah that's why there's so many people flooding through any space as you're being brought into
some mission yeah uh it's a very chintzy hallway i think all the money went to fixing the movie and
not yes the hallway it's an unimpressive hallway i'm sorry i'm offending you with this no no no it's
pretty it's pretty uh lackluster i mean yeah so yeah the propaganda posters like you said scott
yeah the the brain teasers uh what is does someone know the answer to that cadet betty one because i
could not figure it out i felt so dumb don't know it offhand i don't either um we could put it to the
listeners solve this for us solve this is brain teaser is a better word for the genre of the show
brain benders brain benders brain benders as the name of the of the genre is not bad that's good
yeah yeah we'll keep at it also we'll get closer we'll keep chappelly by the end of the episode uh
so uh several posters then you sit and you watch this video in which general knowledge
is talking to the recruits people were going to go inside the brain they've presumably finished
the commando academy they're all taking on their missions and most of the commandos are more
militaristic uh starship troopers type uh handsome uh bright young boys and girls service equals they
very under do you want to see more uh so then but there's but one guy is late and it's our little
buddy buzzy buzzy now now is he younger than all of them is he a doogie howzer it's a lot of questions
that are not answered yeah i think he's just a little guy trying his best and i think that's why
like him uh um i i certainly related to that as a child a little guy trying his best i you know
what did not sink in when it is said at some point you'd think how much i watched this and how much i
liked it this would have sunk in more when they say like um uh oh god what was it it's something
like um uh worrying yourself sick real stress or imagined stress like those lines were very that was
my childhood like i was very nervous child and not from any i was all just doing it to myself
but uh for whatever reason even though cranium command is like no matter how you generate stress
it will feel the same way it's okay calm down just take a minute and breathe that never sunk in the
lesson never sunk in you heard it you can you can recite it but you'd feel like today you're still
in the same shoes as now i'm figuring it out now i'm working on it yeah just recently in the last
three years well and through therapy yeah which equals this podcast yeah do you think do you think
maybe as a child you had like kind of a buzzy guy in your head and he wasn't so good at managing
everything probably yeah that's probably the guy blame the guy and that wasn't your fault oh okay
cool it's it is a real this brings it all brings up a lot of free will issues oh yeah we all just
piloted by a little guy i would argue that if we want to get i do think like free will is an illusion
i kind of i do think that's true damn oh wow i kind of feel like man you're talking like the
john lovett's right yeah i'm right bird love it's i'm like a real hippie man uh yeah no i think
that's true i think we sort of everything's we're gonna do what we're gonna do and we're if you're
if you're able to change you will change but if you're not it's not gonna it's all it's all pre
to tell it's all a man it's all an equation is what i'm saying i believe it's sort of all an
equation and you can sort of guess what everybody's gonna do if you had the most like crazy precise
math equation whoa that's what i feel uh but here the other the only the other thing that i know
about your uh philosophy and role models is your love of jimmy buffett that's true who is who is
relaxed and easygoing do you think he's relaxed and easygoing because he knows everything is
predetermined so let's just chill out and let it happen or is he relaxed because he does like i
you seem like stressed out in your free will assessment yeah i i'm i guess i mean i think i'm
Jason i'm sort of a stressed out person in general um i think jimmy buffett uh there's a persona jimmy
buffett and then the craven businessman jimmy buffett so i think craven craven businessman
knows everything's predetermined he's torn between left and right he's torn between the two
some of your stress might also be coming from the fact that you you look to jimmy buffett for
inspiration but you're also constantly talking about how sick and twisted that clown prince of
the joker is and how he might actually be the most sane one oh yeah that that thing i'm always
talking about he talks about i mean 10 years for 10 halloweens now you've been wearing that joker
makeup and why so serious i say i say it all the time it's all part of the plan um you know i think
really honestly maybe my stress comes from me trying to um fight against my own programming
i feel like i'm trying to break out of a simulation i don't want to get too weird here
i'm trying to yes but um i think my flaw i think i was formed by the end of back to the future 3
where the fax is erased uh because of the future is what you make of it sure i think that movie
taught me but i think that uh i i think at that uh at the age of 10 seeing that film i think it
me think i think i do believe in free will because doc brown showed that the future is not
determined interesting and uh which you and some parts of back to the future might make you think
that it is because things just line up uh i'm losing i'm not smart enough to even hyperanalyze
back to the future three but uh no yeah i uh doc brown i think uh saved me from uh thinking that
i'm just cogs in a machine thanks doc that is a better way to think about life and if i really
analyze it at free will i guess i do feel like you can fight against the worst instincts in your brain
and change so i guess maybe i'm not as cynical if i truly analyze it because you know i do think
like like i i've broken out you know i've broken out of some bad habits in my life so maybe you
maybe we can change you know i don't want to get too you started wearing a hat this year yeah yeah
that is a good example like i was a hat not a hat man for many years and uh but then maybe i'm also
just like predisposed to trying to change things up so really i don't really know you did open up
and tell us the story of how you got those scars figuring out this this runner this runner is the
joker this bit is one of jason's like ham-fisted like i'm gonna keep cramming this in here i mean
i'm happy to to jump on i'm just figuring i just want to call out the game if we can the game yeah
mike is the joker the game the game is like i guess the if we analyze what this joke is the joke is
that like i'm kind of like a lame like hot topic philosophy guy who like really like is like the
joker who has sort of a 15 year old like an unformed yeah like a like a bat like a shooter
inspired by the joker yeah i think that's the thing right and everything off of okay yeah so
i yeah so you get all your inspiration from hot topic t-shirts exactly and like i call my girlfriend
harley and stuff and we wear makeup and make out all right you've crossed the line tmi you should
if you're gonna take inspiration from anybody at hot topic it should be that free will in deadpool
he does what he wants to do that's true he doesn't take crap from nobody and his will is freer than
anybody's it's true all right he deadpool proves that free will exists it'd be less joker and more
deadpool well that'll be my 2019 resolution uh okay anyway out of the free will stuff uh yeah
well i also i have another question stemming from this and i don't want to also open up a can of
worms but you know i know this is like this is well a hot topic to repeat that for this kind of
a hot topic but um is a baby a human being at conception or are they a baby or are they a baby
when the little boys put in their brain oh yeah when did well when they're not converting why do
try to do this off mic when do they get their little boys the question
um do you get what age do you get your little boy you get your little pilot uh yeah when when
in the pre-show when we're looking at the room of all of the broken heads if anyone's listening to
this episode who hasn't there's more than any you need to have watch this thing so you know what the
fuck we're talking about yeah there's actually there's full good quality ride throughs on youtube
i was happy to see yeah like hd in hd yeah 2006 i watched the video from oh still going huh still
going i was shocked that's what's so confusing is that buzzy gets in the head of a 12 year old
boy but as i said who was in it before what metaphysical space is the opened up head in
and we also see just we see like elderly people in that room of heads where are you when do you do
do some people not get their little head controllers until it would make sense it is odd that they just
didn't go with and i'm trying to think of a narrative reason it's just odd they didn't go with
like babies it's like a stork kind of situation it's odd that you would just like there's not in
the cartoon he's yelling it all the same stuff can happen and they're like little cartoon people
and they jump into babies but then how do you get to the 12 year old how do you get to like navigating
a day i think that's that's i guess you're right that's the narrative problem is that you needed
to have like hijinks and stuff go wrong and you explain why buzzy is so bad at controlling this
person and that is like the right age where like everything feels important everything feels high
stakes like adolescents kicking in you know 12 i think because buzzy first like welcomes everyone
into the auditorium he's like all right let's start this up he's waking up in the morning i
was assuming that the heads that is all taking place in the dream space or like the subconscious
like that's almost like a little bit yeah they show you a little bit of everyone getting in the
heads and stuff so i'm assuming that's almost like if your car is at the mechanic the car is
off it's stationary it's not running so this is it's like the humans are at rest so that's when
get resets now whether do you also get new uh people running your organs do you get new left
right ventricles are they swapped out at some point or are they with you for life well that's
what i was saying about a stomach transplant right uh i think for sure that for sure if you get a new
heart then there's a new person in there however i like why did why was there a buzzy change are
you able to change people out just when they're asleep or does you have do you have to like have
an act do you have to be in a coma for cranium commands to do the switch i think what they
should have done is that they shouldn't have buzzy's voice should not have been the kid's voice
that was a big problem but i think you could explain that like this buzzy type character
whoever was controlling the kid before did such a good job he's going to move up into a like a
human so he's like he's now he's going to control like a ceo or a president
and then a new one has to be hired to fill the role of this 12 year old let's also possibly
died in action well that is too dark okay he is in a bomber jacket yeah is he a is he like the sector
keeper a ghost from the path a ghost boy oh yeah past uh locked in time again i i believe reading
about this thing storyboard this in a week so um that's that's the answer we're looking for
it's the free view so wouldn't we be the like like we're always everyone complains like network
notes but the three of us like i don't know here the that's a good point i don't like this attitude
in a way of like picking apart the logic because yeah if we were like giving them this attitude
while they were making the thing there wouldn't they there wouldn't have been a cranium yeah it
does i mean again yeah it still plays as mike said like it's so there's enough grounding there
for like a 20 25 minute experience uh-huh no one is thinking of these issues while they are watching
george wint as the funny stomach man that overrides any of these bizarre metaphysical issues
yes but there are story problems i think the voice not being that that's a big i think that's the big
fix that hole and i i shut up about a lot of other stuff you know we have to think about these
things because if we're looking towards a sub platform within another streaming platform of
exclusively brain bender based shows you got to figure this stuff out so you have solid footing
you know i my fear though is that this project ultimately is not us doing it it's the little
guys in our heads and i'm worried that they're gonna fuck up the brain bender like we're
ultimately at the whims of these little guys so i just hope they've got a good tv show in them
well yeah you know command our little finger guys to type type type the scripts well
one way to exercise power is by releasing you know releasing control it's harder than taking
control to exercise power but release stepping away and releasing control can uh is that a
therapy thing you learned that is a therapy like you have to let your of the three of us go the
only one in therapy i believe so yeah yeah yeah a couple years now right it's great it's very
helpful very smart yeah i think we'll both be paying the price for not not not letting a lot
of stuff go for a long time yeah then like it really building up when we're like 45 oh yeah
oh it's just like the weeds are so overgrown at that point that the therapists were just trying
to get out of there and try to figure out oh we should have taken care of this earlier
yeah because it takes a while for the lessons to set in and become you know
yeah sure uh we've all got like horror we've got horrible dense armies in our brains we wish
it were as simple as adjusted charles groden and a and a john luvitz right they have plenty of
space to move we have like yeah just weird some faceless foot army yeah my like there's like
10 people doing the job of one charles groden in my head i was bumping into each other trying to
know different opinions about what to do fuck you yeah i gotta say groden and luvitz playing off of
each other i think is is very fun i mean i did used to i know we clowned on luvitz a bunch in
the past but like as a kid i loved john luvitz on snl of course he something happened i feel
when you add up not just him on s obviously great on snl but then yeah everything on the simpsons
league of their own big um if there's something else pretty good i'm missing uh i mean this he's
like and he it's like he's playing a character that is not his exact wheelhouse you haven't seen
luvitz do this shade exactly uh and i think it's very good i don't know he was like he was he was
real sharp i'm definitely an appreciator of uh yeah of course the the yeah the early john luvitz
body work uh also in uh brave little toaster oh yeah yeah brave little toaster is john luvitz uh
and and phil hartman pre snl and mindy sterling uh for our best and from austin powers which makes
me think jerry reese was up probably on what the groundlings were doing he's like i'm making a
little movie i'm gonna hire a bunch of groundlings and you could see that he kept his whole his body
work uh which also includes kevin pollock and alien encounter and kathy and jimmy and stuff like
he has like he casts fun comedians and all this disney stuff and brings that influence into
everything uh which now all things have comedians voices everywhere but i think i like the sensibility
of this guy i mean like a lot of the pixar stuff it's comedian types and inside out but disney
the little mermaid was like a kind of put like putting a foot out for them like if i or maybe
they do one because like bob newhart and rescuers are like they would allow for one voice you know
but then the rest are kind of like in right well once there's so much singing like they're pulling
from broadway quite a bit oh that's true yeah yeah yeah you got i guess you got robin williams genie
probably when we saw that we didn't know who roan atkinson was sure yeah so that's it's a new
level to appreciate it on now i knew who james earl jones was and i'm sure you know david augden
stires your favorite actor as a 90 as a in 1992 he was uh cogsworth oh cogs okay i could see young
jason being a big mash fan oh yeah oddly no but i have a match think for like it's funny you bring
for later later oh okay oh it's a treat for later okay um okay i don't have we done any have we
been explaining this coherently at all so you're in this training room you watch this pre video
with all these great animators involved that's really fun uh you get the basic information about
how to be a brain commander and if you're a bad brain commander you end up having a pilot of
chicken around who has not very many options and can ascend to great levels like a like a human can
you also get those the jokes that are killers every time you're in there uh at least at least
when we were kids in the 90s the joke the joke about there were uh you know we've had some
successes and it's albert einstein and some failures and it's earnest i remember thunderous
applause and laughter whenever that played drag him drag earnest get him a fictional character
a fictional character that disney is making movies about right now how did he end up there
yeah they aren't like uh they aren't making a mental health judgment about a real person
right uh you know a lot of this would not be okay uh today but then uh you've got the uh that what's
the other killer joke oh that like then then it's time to get into the brain get into the theater
come on move move move what do you think where do you think you are disney world which also a
little bit of a growner in a way but like i think maybe self-reflexive comedy in dis in a disney
attraction in 1989 not super common right comes back in a different ride comes back at a different
ride later on i'm not going to tell you which one until you're right is this another tease oh i see
gotcha uh oh it's you know it's uh top of the you know it's a top of the what oh i know that's in
there you mean in guardians so i know that yeah yeah yeah where were you i know that it's the same
yeah yeah you're right well done many years prior by cranium command so then you enter the you enter
the head now you're in a head here's a question who are we in this experience we're not cranium
commandos or are we like taking notes behind buzzy to me as well yeah that's one that's another hole
a little bit are we auditing we're 200 secret shoppers yeah yeah i don't know i think because the
we're learning so i think maybe just in the catch-all of like hey you can come and watch what
happens it's like if you're sitting in a surgery with an open right window i think that's what it
is you're loading into like it would be very cool if instead of just a hallway it was like you were
loading into someone's ear or something oh there should have been one more step like the maybe no
budget by that point i think yeah no budget so they didn't do it just putting a big ear around
the doors yeah it would have been it wouldn't make sense for four years though because you want to
but i feel like hmm i don't know we all have theater doors in our heads that's the other thing
this right teaches you maybe it's like one giant ear with four doors in the year
i don't know how that would look yeah they all fit within the yeah we all have little doors in our
ear yeah okay so we're learning a lot from this it's like no it's like tower of terror where
you wait in lines of four and they just take each line separately easy okay so they go row one row
two row or whatever they do at six row one in order to make the one ear okay big ear that's my
plus one big ear mike carlson's big ear yeah easy done so now you're in the head and buzzy is up on
a platform although when you walk in strangely he's like just in the dark sitting there as he
has been for many decades yeah apparently but then he comes to life uh general knowledge comes back
yells at general if we didn't explain that you know he's he has this kind of drill sergeant
attitude and they said in the revamp he became a lot more like r. lee ermy uh um so you know that
whenever things are going worse the worst for buzzy the general can jump in and stress him out even
more right um so he starts powering on the machine he's not exactly sure how to pilot it like poor
man's rex um he conjures the second audio animatronic figure by the way i should say
this thing was supposed to be teeming with audio animatronics in its original conception probably
all the body parts left brain right brain all of it are audio animatronics but that's a big budget
cut we can only have one thus it became the protagonist buzzy not a big problem but obviously
more robots always better always better is hypothalamus considered an audio animatronic
is just a robot yeah yeah i think so to some it's not as complicated and what is he how do we
explain him he's like a he's a head on a neck oh the non-mo yeah it's just like a pole with like
a pair of goggles on it a lot of binoculars he looks kind of like those skinned geese in the
star tours line a little bit just sort of like kind of genericky robot type thing uh voiced by
director kirk wise okay co-directed the short and i think does a great job of this very dry like
monotone like thing because it doesn't pop up that often because what is the hypothalamus
control like non-motor or like non-conscious didn't stick with me and the word didn't i guess
whatever they were trying to teach me there i just didn't uh i think it it's it regulates like all
the stuff that your body does in the background like not consciously you don't have to think
yeah that you don't have to think about huh we all have the hmm strange this is um i would be
look we're a theme park podcast so when i get a breaking story on my phone sometimes i have to
break in and say it absolutely on walt disney world news today it just says concept art for
country bear jamboree dark ride released what i guess this was a never made country bear dark
oh no i guess that makes me sad almost so huh i got very excited thinking it was like a new one
but i guess it's not anyway we'll post we'll link that later okay yeah yeah um you you live your life
yeah you're stressed out because you're so jumpy at any second you get an alert about like uh a new
mug that got released notifications for every app and everybody follows on twitter not everyone i
yeah yelling at you too much information for one person um so uh your your day begins uh the the
eyes open up uh you're waking up in your 12 year old boy uh bedroom you start meeting all of the
body parts the left brain charles groden who is very logical and lives in this awesome cubist
world i love the set of right i think that's my favorite i think there's a lot of fun set design
this thing love left brain uh and right brains in a more like freewheeling psychedelic world
this is one of those learning things that did stick i do feel like i always it really helped me
seeing kind of like a gray black and white left brain and a colorful right brain i think that
concept is always clear to me and and in being create being a creative person and sometimes
having to wear like a producer hat and sometimes having to just be freewheeling and be a writer
like you have to balance those sides and i do literally picture like i'm a little too charles
groden right now it really honestly stuck with me it really did like i gotta i gotta be more love
it's we're gonna throw that at you we're gonna throw that at each other now it's like you'd be a
little charles groden right now quit being such a groden jason constantly thinks of himself just as
a charles groden type in a good way i mean uh confident charming handsome but sure i think you
said he was like your ultimate actor i think so well i think we were also like oh who would be we
be if if we were gay who would we be attracted to and i think you yours was charles groden and
mine was young elliot gould yeah yes oh sure who's mine i don't know maybe it's it's somewhere
between probably uh some era of mccartney uh uh i don't think i look i'm more of an admirer of the
the physique of the facial physique of michael mcdonald's 70s mcdonald's okay i'm not sure it's
an attraction i'm just like i think he's what i want to look like right yeah but so those are
those are the bones all and obviously uh hans and franz in this thing well sure you get my hands on
those big arm muscles yeah um yeah what is their name in this though they just call them they're
vons and johns oh they're not but they play left ventricle grocery stores oh they're also a rip
off of the grocery stores uh we'll see meet them too uh problematic today that they call people
girly men and yeah that's problematic yeah is it wrong to shame somebody for potentially triggering
a flabalanche was that one of their lines too probably not in this but that's what i associate
that with hans and franz oh wow i want to say how much i love dana carvey i mean kevin nealon as
well but dana carvey if you watch any hans and franz sketch is having so much fun and just keeps
like pointing for no reason he's having so it's like he's a kid with a toy he can't let go of
and then like keeps doing that like lascivious and kind of staring down the camera he's clearly just
having a blast every time he does whichever one that it haunts i maybe uh and you get that in this
a little i don't think you get like the fully there right franz feeling but fun to see him
right yeah i mean they're all on screen for such a little amount of time i feel like
does grodin have the most screen time um by like what seconds maybe he chips in a lot because he's
almost like a villain he like needs to yeah obviously very useful the kid wouldn't get
without uh charles grodin yes that is a couple things i want to talk so we are led to believe
this 12 year old sleeps naked hmm some people do i guess so i just i don't think some 12 year olds
do i suppose i guess i guess the logic is there for the joke jason how do you sleep oh sleep well
i don't like a lot of layers um usually like some sleep shorts and a t-shirt sometimes no t-shirts
sometimes sleep short i'll say this i would be way into sleeping nude except that the temperature
my temperature changes during the night so often that i will wake up like sweaty or weird like i'll
wake up weird if i even try to sleep like shirtless so i have to do i prefer sure well if i wear too
many layers i wake up covered in sweat and then i'm cold yeah i'm i'm change shirts i'll wear a
but i think i have to wear that shirt because it will at least keep some heat in if i throw the
covers off because i'm a little bit of a restless sleeper as well interesting what is your answer
scott i'm just shirt and boxers but it occurred to me like the most on brand you know what shirt
i've worn like so much that i can't wear anymore because it's just like gotten too thin and
full of holes but for the last decade probably almost every night i've worn a captain eo shirt
almost every night not like not as like pajamas not like i'm going to be kept eo in my dreams
just like it's a really comfy shirt like what they had at tomorrowland you can you know it may it
makes sense i should have taken advantage of that i should have pretended to be kept in my dreams
i was gonna say but maybe subconsciously somewhere yeah that might be well it's so it's the stripe
it's the rainbow straight right right i have that but i lost it i realized the other day oh i had it
i don't know where i wore it out i can't like that alternated between that and a live-age shirt
which i also so also pretty on brand you know what i've been wearing to sleep though lately
and i this is going to seem like a hamfisted ad but lately in the sleep shirt regiment
patanakush oh yeah shirts available at tpublic.com i don't remember the rest of the
day separate they're different they're most people i think do but i would advocate if you
get a patanakush shirt do both sleep in it wear it out more so it looks more shitty when you're
out in public with it that's the issue with the patanakush shirt our favorite my favorite shirt
that we offer is that it won't really have its full effect until you've worn it a lot after five
i would also you gotta get wrecked and that'll really work i would also and this is jason's
gonna be probably mad at us or mad at me for saying this bootlegging the shirt yourself somehow
i might encourage it oh i'll like yeah i would encourage that if you want to just like
draw facsimile of it and then airbrush it at like a local airbrushing place that wouldn't be bad i
would be very happy to see knock off bootleg patanakush by the way because even then we're
getting advertising we're getting well i'm just saying for fun i'm just saying for fun not
thinking of i'm not a craven business man like you are as much you know also in case you don't
know what we're talking about on a patreon exclusive episode just dedicated to botanikus
we created an alternate version that loves weed named patanakush and we're selling a shirt of him
like bart style and if you don't know what botanikus is we're too far deep you know there's
that thing where podcasts are supposed to like every episode could be the first episode sometimes
we're just too it's hard it's really hard it's hard yeah the level the the depths of knowledge
just you gotta go backwards it's a syria that we're this is the wire okay i think we do a reasonable
job i think we do a reasonable job of that but we cannot touch every running storyline no nor
we can't go back and explain what every single thing is and you know botanikus but botanikus
hopefully we've helped make such a such a major part of pop culture the main goal of the podcast
yes um then we don't have to explain them anymore uh so you see you're in the day you're doing the
day oh the ride yeah doing the day and for our younger listeners uh just a heads up when when
alarm clocks would wake us up in the 80s and 90s you could only shut them off by knocking them off
your nightstand violently if you watch any movies from the tv and uh movies or tv shows of the time
you'll notice every character constantly knocking over their alarm clock and the alarm clock
industry was thriving because everyone was destroying theirs all the time yeah and you
you're worried that you can't make it on time uh but hopefully it'll be all right and you'll be
by the bell yeah that's the optimal scenario kind of kind of plays out that way for cranium
command kid he doesn't make it to school but he's he doesn't seem to eat uh uh he doesn't eat he
never urinates no his bodily functions are not addressed probably for the best because this is a
uh 12 year old boy also he takes the bus but he can run through hedges and be at school that quickly
i don't know we're gonna have to solve that well it's all it's the artistic license i mean i think
in star tours the this version of star tours now there's a couple jumps time wise where you're
like yeah we got out of orbit of hawth pretty quickly so they have to take some license i feel
i suppose condensed experience right day yes uh um well also how quickly is he in the cafeteria
so quickly yeah like if he gets to if this is real time lunch is happening at this school at
8 04 yes yes that's a good point so there's a lot of issues here but again we're just trying to make
a good thing perfect it's not we're not trying to tear it apart uh but now here's something i would
not do again if we were to go back into the cranium command world um i think it's awesome he
meets a pretty girl he's talking to a girl in class gets flustered he she asks him a question
he says beautiful and uh a slip of the tongue uh um you know good 12 year old boy stuff he's he's
flustered a girl he has a crush on throws him off but then a couple of odd things happen uh the the
brain john lovitz starts kind of like is like celebrating he's like he's like a flutter about
the girl but he is john lovitz and she is 12 yes this is strange to me and then we end up in this
section where he's there's a little fantasy occurring and the fantasy is mainly zooming
into black and white photos of the girl which unmistakably are the the head shots of the actress
yes right like yeah they just found three of her glamour shots uh poses yes and they're like
cycling through them i i think it's a it seems a little lazy to me why would they be black and
white you know when you meet a girl you like and then you imagine her black and white like
putting her hands against her chin her at a sears portrait studio you think about her like that yeah
of course uh shout out to the uh that actress natalie gregory was also the voice of the little
girl in oliver and company hey hey how about that oh very good well she's great in that and she's
good in this and uh um you know not these aren't big problems i just find that little head shot
uh uh uh fancy a little unsettling it would be yeah in the first part it would be better if they
were all kids in the kids head like if there were kid actors yeah sure it would be a little less
problematic of like there weren't enough famous kids at the time this is pre mccally colkin there's
no colkins to flesh out these parts oh yeah you're right okay so that's but there's some kids from
sitcoms right there's a small wonder what was small wonder doing it's the only small wonder
and charles in charge disney does what about ammanuel lewis uh oh you're right yeah yeah yeah
get ammanuel who was in a lot of disney parades yeah i yeah this little kid controlled kid bodies
uh that would be fun but i don't know but also getting like having a having a adult suited
charles groden in your brain of course just sorry then let's just cut the scene
can i say i there's another thing tv and movies uh made me think as a child that whenever there
was a new kid at school they were either gonna end up being my best friend or my crush
because that was all that's such a storytelling device in kid's stuff to like shake up a character
where it's like oh there's a new character and now you're best friends with them or now you're
dating them it i i think i think i had the same thing as you and i think it like i was like not
really dating in middle school in high school i think that was my hope was that the like the like
perfect out of a movie transfer girl would come because like otherwise the social structure
do you guys you guys have that feeling in high school that like when did the social structure
get decided without me being there and why am i completely outside of it they all seem to know
each other and have inside jokes and where where was i when this happened yeah it does like your
insecurity also forms part of that equation because you immediately feel like an outsider
maybe that was in my head the whole time and then it becomes the reality of it
so it is it's sort of a self-fulfilling prophecy yeah and it was sort of it was destined to hand it
was sort of there was no controlling it it just sort of free will for the left thinking there isn't
isn't a there isn't free will i think is maybe depressing i mean that's giving into depressing
thoughts yeah the idea that you can control things is optimistic optimistic and right um
so yeah i think that's we don't need therapy jason we're doing it here that's what the show
is for we've said it early on don't tell us to get it we don't need it we don't want it we're
busy can't lead a horse to water another thing that tv and movies convinced me i was a kid is
like well one day i need to be ready for a food fight i was never in a food fight has anyone seen
naturally occurring food fight no i've never been close to a food fight it's never happened
i think i saw one shot like a one thing thrown something thrown in response and that was maybe
the extent of it so you never saw somebody get nailed in the eye from across the room
this to get the attention of everyone in a crowded cafeteria everyone turns and goes ooh
and then the person perfectly wipes the mashed potatoes out of their eye and then and then a
fight is set up for the end of the day well they uh but i would think in that scenario then all
of a sudden every kid just starts whipping food oh yeah yeah that's probably the better this was
a thing according to one of these behind the scenes uh pieces of info that disney wanted to
cut they were not on set like non not on set budget people called jerry reeves the director
and said you're doing a pov food fight that's impossible we have to get this thing done
and he said is it okay to turn in a half complete show no well then i'm gonna go shoot the scene bye
wow cool badass nice nice uh and it's a fun it's a fun little sequence um yeah and seeing that in a
pov way is is cool yeah um but you know the kid's day gets worse and worse and now he ends up in the
principal's office uh where he the body like melts down entirely this is kind of a clever
sequence like the idea like that your body your body parts are not like all like and so one can
trigger the other right to go and the other one and you're physically flustered and all just
and you don't know what to say and uh it's a neat little yeah that's fun he is like staring down at
his lap for like a full two minutes or so yeah i did think i thought it would be funny if only there
was a way to see the principal's point of view and go like what the hell is going on with this kid
did this kid just turn off like what the fuck i guess he's dead throw him in the garbage
turn off means throw him in the pile this keeps happening what's going on at this school
off so he ends up uh buzzy through his his will and uh sort of viewing things from a new perspective
realizes that he needs to be honest and that's his only way out of uh talking about um you know
that's the only way uh he can progress with the principal and not get in too much trouble is to
just tell the truth and then it works out it works out great he gets some punishment he just has to
clean the cafeteria but that is all and he's rewarded for it being uh valorous the principal
believes this right away i mean it is accurate but uh what's to stop the bully from saying yeah i was
trying to protect the girl too sure yeah the principal's kind of a soft touch or a real easy
mark i don't know what you'd call him uh but yeah he sort of just buys it i guess maybe the kid's
been in trouble before that's what i got yeah i'm sure those bullies have been in that principal so
he knows i think he is an mo yeah so that's fair yeah yeah and who is he to stop young love from
blossoming no don't he wants annie to fall for what's the kid's name even is he assigned one i
don't think he is hmm yeah what principal doesn't want just romance the blue between 12 year olds
might be another thing that needs to go
well he doesn't really if you watch the scene he's not he's not like he didn't take pictures of him
and draw little hearts around him and push them together but there's that one shot where he's
rubbing his hands to get where he's shipping students yeah new principal ship students i'm
sure they do i would think it's problematic as well not ones you want to be around um so then
a lesson is learned that is what is the the morals at the end of this movie are really
laid on that well first of all he gets out of the principal's office with a mild punishment
annie the girl knows that she uh that he stuck up for her and he gets his first kiss and all those
body parts uh go crazy uh um that's it's kind of a sweet little thing it's nice and then and then
you get and then buzzy just like tells you stuff for a while so remember keep your head on straight
if you're uh stressed out then uh count to three and i don't remember the full list but he really
just like like bullet points what you're supposed to learn uh pretty like i don't know like there's
no there's not a it's you you uh the moral shoved down your throat is what i'm saying
it's a little heavy-handed yeah but i don't remember what they are it is with that well he
turns at one point he looks right he like right at you and he goes like hey i know some of you in
the audience are weird little kids they're gonna grow up to be weird adults so just calm down take
some deep breaths and drink more water that's what i would prefer he that's what you projected
into into buzzy's mouth i do think also jason thanks buzzy you're i'm you i mean that's what
we all we want all the media we could sue it to be like i'm you i i think i know in the way that
left brain right brain stuck with me i think i was maybe hesitant to talk to girls at 12 because i
was like if you even try you're gonna mutter the word beautiful and you're gonna get laughed out of
this school uh so just don't talk to them i think maybe cranium commands uh screwed me up i'll be
i'll be honest i don't remember if i went on this as a kid i probably did because it's right by body
wars which i for sure went on and have a very clear memory of i don't know feeling in this
i don't really have such a great memory of it so i was so confident talking to girls at 12 that's
obviously what happened i was so good at it never worried this movie needs to be off limits for kids
is a really kind soul because by all all rights she was it was within the realm of possibility
that she could have ruined that get like and she would have been entitled to like this fucking kid
is a stranger to me and he called me beautiful like she she should have been like you think me
beautiful that's what the line is right that's right that's right oh yeah me
you're in the new kid at school you're feeling stuff out like it would have been very reasonable
for her to talk to other people like hey what's this what's my lab partner's deal like he just
came out with beautiful out of nowhere it kind of caught me off guard like what's going on you
know what's weird is that yesterday he talked to me with a completely different voice than he's
using today there's something up with this kid well you know jason as you said on on the
topic of where we're all finding our various connections to this movie and the way it spoke
did not speak to us at the time i had an idea for a segment and the segment is called cast a
commando now we've already we've we're already talking about multiple iterations of this this
universe being turned back on us but if we were to just redo the live show or redo the the epikott
show and it was about us and our body and you had to cast a famous actor or pop culture figure to
play one of your body parts who would you cast and i can start yeah please like yeah
okay i'm gonna choose a body part that's not represented in the original production and that
is the liver and my liver is going to be played by donald fagan from steely dan
he's a he's a freewheeling guy and he's like keep keep him flowing daddy yo keep that hey i've had
a little more grapefruit wine uh he loves it uh he's like george wench the white wine is piling
up to his uh great right up to his chin by the end of it great um yeah how about a little cuervo
gold make tonight a wonderful thing the kids want to see more the kids want to see fagan
in attraction yeah yeah yeah fagan merch and stuff uh gentleman any who would you cast as a
well i have an unrepresented section of the brain uh the checking part of the brain uh and
just because i like him so much wallace sean would of course be the checker
he would be like there's there's a max pass availability open up for the guardians of the
galaxy tower you must get it now your friend is at disneyland he doesn't even know that there's an
home they have not asked for assistance but you can help yeah so that's i think that's perfect
by the way wallace sean needs to be on every ride he's an amazing man he needs like good and
goofy movies good and good and everything all of the movies he's in and in and he will be in the
new in our in the new brain bender uh the franchise yeah jason do you have any yeah i i'm also going
for an unrepresented body part i i was going to go with the lungs and uh one of my favorite duos
i alluded to this earlier i'm paying off the mash thing it's uh donald southerland and elliot
gould from the 1970 movie version of mash i saw that in high school and i thought they were the
coolest dudes i thought they were so funny and charming and laid back and that's how i'd like
my lungs to be operating at a normal operate even when times or even when there's shelling going on
in the korean peninsula uh i'd like to just be a couple cool wisecracking dudes and southerland
and gould i mean i i so great i i was thinking about maybe gould and george seagull i feel like
they were fun together but southerland and gould uh yeah just just great 70s sure the fun laid back
as opposed to like the deadly serious deniro uh deniro pacino uh cassal actors of the godfather
movies and you want like you know you want fresh skinned uh lookers as your lungs you don't want
like some haggard old guy uh yeah yeah you want to know those things are are operating smooth
sure yeah um this is great uh i think this is a good you know this would be all perfect to put
the ride as a refresh of it yes uh to get the kids excited with these great actors the combined
age of which is 340 years old we got donald fagan yeah mine are a temporal impossibility
oh okay you have to be they have to be mocapped younger yeah uh yeah in the past versions of these
on is current walla shun fine for what you what you need perfect yeah current current fagin's fine
too we don't have to i feel like he was uh you know he was like a odd frog man in 1970 he never
aged but he started at 75 so you think he'd be more reliable as a liver than say like dean martin
oh yeah well he can uh he can keep him coming yeah that's true he can uh yeah he'd be dean
martin would be like it'd be above his head and he'd still be like gurgling wisecracks
what's going on up there that'd be great
would mike love be any part of your brain
what part controls your business center oh that's good or how about how about dancing
it's just a hat it's just suddenly this auditorium is like the you could see the
brim of the hat somehow mike love is the hat and you might say the hat is not a body part
but in my body with the way i was raised in a mike love centric fashion that yeah the hat's
got free will and it's it's mike love man um uh love it well uh i want to see our cranium commands
in action and i guess i mean maybe that's the plus up is to bring it back and cycle through
some different brains it can always be buzzy but those other guys i i have a quick plus up
i we've been pitching so much on this episode but you know there's a ride coming out called
millennium falcon smugglers run we all know the name is there any punctuation in there there's a
i'm sure there's at least a couple different colons or semi-colons you gotta have a colon if
you're making a ride uh and i would think that there's a cranium command where you actually
because my big problem with this is sort of it's it's a fun show but like i feel like once you see
it once you don't need that jason's getting mad at me i think once you see it once um i don't know
it's not like you want to ride it again there's not a ride ability it's like oh it's a fun show
whatever let's put you in the head is what i'm saying millennium falcon puts you behind the
controls of the millennium falcon sure put you in the head you're each representing the different
parts of the human brain and you gotta hit buttons and you gotta do stuff and you gotta see if you
can get this kid to get his first kiss from a girl you know that's a fun plus up i think that's a
much more active way to put the uh the audience well and it's a nice like as all of the wonders
of life attractions should be ripoffs of star wars attractions body wars it's a star tours but
you're in the body uh new cranium command is smugglers run but you're in a brain right and so
five years they'll do that i think that was my thing as a kid i was it didn't concern me if buzzy
was a lesser rex but because body wars was was good but a lesser star tours yeah undone deniably
yeah and like more unpleasant like as you're going in and out of like you're watching like
valves in your body clothes it like gives me like yeah like phantom pains to think about it
uh body wars will be an upsetting episode for all of us yeah um i have a legitimate plus up kind of
uh based on what a thing i read about one of the concepts for the ride uh and i forget you know
what generation or who exactly said this but i think the um at some point they were considering
oh well if it's just screens we can swap the footage in and out and i feel like that's such a
it's come up so many times as like a blue sky thing for different attractions with like and then
part will be module and then eventually you can change that in and out and guardians of the galaxy
is the exception like that is a notorious exception maybe the first time they've actually
utilized it actually used it but anytime they've been like and then you can swap
and change this part it never fucking happens the only yeah toy story midway mania right when three
came out they did it they added some stuff so they added like garland's buttercup and stuff to the
overlays and things yeah they have never been that yeah so screens need to be brighter i mean i think
like that that kind of drives me nuts eventually when you read about these rides and like oh and
then they potentially were gonna swap this in and out i think if they had committed to that for a
lot of the epcot stuff that park would be in better shape than it was especially since it's supposed
to be about the future and like keeping up with the future or bleeding ed stuff so quickly
fell to the wayside because that costs so much money to do what it's it's here's here's some
therapy realizing that i the things that i loved the most as a kid in the disney parks were all
forward-thinking futuristic stuff that things that i saw from the ages of you know three to nine
that made me think boy there's a great big beautiful tomorrow area the future is going
to be so cool and then every single one of those things has decayed or been replaced or just ignore
there's no area in disney parks more that were just it was replaced by nothing it was replaced
by a lock uh then like the future things what a bummer uh uh the future is dead yeah i so
upset theory that thought should come back because they're designing so much of this stuff
towards the end of the 70s or in the early 80s not exactly boom times for you know coming off
the vietnam worm water gate and sure and then gas shortage and the hostage crisis and thing after
thing after thing but then people are feeling optimistic about the field like we have to be
optimistic about the future and now in a very bleak time i guess we end up in an optimistic
because right now it's just like well guess what new streaming service you're signing up for next
year motherfucker like that is the future well when president warren is assuredly elected without
any issue when she sails into office after we see every single democratic candidate's kitchen
and maybe some even some republican primary challengers
probably not that probably not shouldn't be a problem she shouldn't be undone by
one single trump insult that he will repeat no 700 times no no no her bizarre dna test solution
will not constantly dogger who boy oh man well uh you know here's i have one more uh hey speaking
of optimism you know we got what you're talking about with the screens uh and being able to
slide new characters in and out as much as i love hans and franz those aren't that's not who kids
today like we need to get new today's best comedians into the ride and i think i know
just the guy uh we're gonna you know who i'm gonna draft into new cranium command
to play the friggin balls louis ck oh no no the man who's willing to tell it like it is
and when the body's confused he's down there going hey kid hey fuck you hey shut the fuck up
he doesn't say jokes as much as the current cranium command people he just kind of says
fuck you and that that is in place of the joke but i think that's what we need is a guy who's not
afraid to uh you know tell it like it is yeah yeah yeah we'll talk about him after we have the
woody ellen in our universe discussion in the brain bender universe discussion so we'll talk
about it off mic louis and woody in great well i didn't say that i said we'll talk about it
after you keep both these men away from my buzzy
hasn't he been through enough hasn't he been through enough we don't know where he is buzzy
they don't know where he is yeah which brings us to that you know we'll like we'll we'll uh
might not come out for a sec as we record this and we'll you know we'll update we'll add any
updates of anything that's going on but it's so confusing is he gone or just the clothes gone
it's different uh uh hey you know what you talk about plus ups for rides i have a plus up for how
disney should have treated the situation they should have sent out an amber alert real kid or
fake kid we should have all gotten an alert on our phone uh you already had one mike but now all
in the country should be on their feet looking for buzzy as we speak at the very least like the
amber alert in orlando so like zach riders should have gotten it on his phone at least because he's
a resident he would i think he would have been found by now i think he would have snapped into
action what's the the stat in taken that like you know you have 72 yeah he would have got yeah
yeah uh zach would have been on the case right then and there yeah he'd be back and then he would
have bought it he would have anyway had it in his case and it's mine yeah um well let's uh uh
let's let's just let's free buzzy is fine buzzy free him from where he is and when he's found
put him in a museum if we have a he belongs in a museum let me ask you a question before we go
uh if you if say you i don't know where this would be say we were in larland and we were on
vacation and we walked and we saw in a dumpster buzzy say buzzy was just sitting in a dumpster
whatever it was a bunch of waste and you're like oh my god it's buzzy would you take buzzy and
keep him for yourself or would you go to disney and say we found but i think what is the real
buzzy what would you do it's like the it's the scene in boogie nights where don cheetal has the
money on the counter but everyone's been killed so he's a quandary it's not his money but no one's
a one-to-one i think it's exactly one missing that money but it's going to improve his life
there's a lot of blood around though in either case or at least hydraulic fluid
so do you take buzzy if you think i think he belongs to the world i would feel too much guilt
keeping him for myself so you would give him back to disney scott um i think it depends on if he's
clothed or not clothed i think if he's clothed i keep him like if he's not clothed i'm too weirded
having this naked little doll in my home okay in my scenario if he's naked i keep him i take him to
a baby clothes store and i buy him a new like little winter jacket and snow pants and then i
take him and he sits on the shelf here with the ninja turtles and batman but you know he's a little
bigger but what good is it if you can't you can't instagram about it if you have to keep it secret
i'm i love that i love keeping that little secret i would be okay with that because you would know
and anyone who came over right would know um but you might i don't know don't you think the guilt
might eat at you eventually when you hit that maybe when you hit the moment where you need
therapy in a beyond repair manner i'll confess to the therapist i found buzzy i should give him back
to the walt disney corporation what would those three dozen voices in your head say about that
i think they would all have different opinions that would drastically vary it's swing wildly
back and forth and i think the first thing the therapist would say is what who's talking about
and the second thing is we have a lot of work to do this is the first thing you want to sort out
you found a robot in a dumpster yeah you don't understand you don't understand how he got here
i was a robot of a ride that i loved that i never went on i never went up i love it
my my question my initial question to you michael was how are you doing and you started
talking about a robot boy named buzzy i bought him snow pants how are you feeling then you
explained mobile ordering to me for 10 minutes you started talking about barbecue will be better
if you mobile order right now your conflicted feelings on sexual candy stores i don't
we're not gonna escape this episode alive no god it feels like we've been doing this for three and
a half hours i blacked out several times like buzzy's eyes they just uh yeah um well i guess
i guess we survived podcast the ride that we've been left with a lot to think about a lot to think
about um if if you want to hear further psychosis from us you can go to patreon.com
podcast the ride yes or we'll discuss things at length that are even more obscure than
premium command uh and uh check us out on twitter on instagram check out our facebook group
uh email us at podcastride.gmail.com if you know where buzzy is and you want to help us be the
heroes maybe dm us we can set up a signal account and if you want to meet us in a parking lot and
we're maybe willing to pay we do admire your stealthiness and we admire that you taught
disney a lesson yeah i'm happy to reward you sure and if you have botanicus's staff too
if somebody took that yeah we'll pay for that as well god i know we need to find all these out
yep uh well a lot of work to do here in 2019 yep we're getting on it so more to come thanks
for listening bye bye bye forever dog this has been a forever dog production executive produced
by mike carlson jason sharridan scott gardner brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey for more
original podcasts please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts
spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by following
us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook