Five, four, three, two, one.
podcast, right? Second gate. Um, this is going to be a mailbag episode.
We just started talking about something and I feel like we should record it.
Uh, tomorrow we're recording here as Jason Sheridan is here.
We're back from the holidays. My name is Mike Carlson. Uh, we're talking about,
um, tomorrow is like the last day of the holidays at Disneyland.
And it's the first day, all the pet, not all the passes, I think,
but most of the passes are unblocked again,
cause there's that two week period between or around Christmas and new years
when only the elite, which are passes. We don't even,
we don't want to spend that extra $75 to go for those two weeks.
You mean the, the does the signature, there's like a 365 kind of, yeah,
signature plus I think is the one that has those two weeks. Okay. Uh,
and that's everybody. So that's for,
there were two weeks there with where annual pass holders only in that elite
club could go.
But tomorrow is the last day of the holidays and when passes are unblocked
again. So it's going to be insane. Yeah. And I'm,
I'm going right is what, uh, we figured,
I booked a nice little Napa Rose for Aaron and I, uh,
and which maybe we just go down and only do that and don't even get on a ride.
Uh, but Mike, you were just saying you were trying to get down.
I was saying, Lindsay, do you want to go?
Cause I kind of want to go on small world holiday,
which I hadn't been on until we went a couple of weeks ago. And I,
I was like, wow, this is great. I haven't been on this.
I feel like in a couple of years.
We all remarked that it was like, wow, this, this is really good.
Yeah. I almost like it. Fuck.
Everyone else in the boat was mad at us because we're going fuck me.
Oh my God. The song. All these cute little shit heads.
And also, and then we'll do it on a full episode, but I was like,
I was like, oh, this is so great. It goes in and out of small world.
And then what jingle bells would, yeah, jingle bells. And I was like,
that's great. If the ride went in and out,
I think people would be less annoyed by the song,
which I'm not that annoyed by the song.
The in and out of a different song. Yeah. But like a different,
my little or something. Camp town races.
Skip to my little. My Bonnie lies over the ocean. My Bonnie lies over the sea.
It's a long way to Tipperary though, which plays on main streets.
And I love, I love long way to Tipperary.
That's a, as kids say now, that's a bop.
Oh yeah. I guess. Should they say that's a bop?
Your book ends of, you know, cool phrases,
but also are from 1902. Yes. I don't understand how you work.
Man, I fucking love all those tragic ass world war one songs.
I'll be home for Christmas.
When we need a current,
the small world dolls need to be singing a current song about like harmony and
hope, which of course is fight song. It should be in between.
It's a small world and this is my fight song.
His fight song will never go on it again. That's it for me.
I think it's, yeah, it's a little older. I mean,
if we could get that DJ snake song that's only played at city walk in there.
And if we could, if they could reprogram, I don't think it'd be that hard,
but we get some of the small worlds kids doing the floss dance or any of the
fortnight dance.
Can the small world dolls dab? Is that in their programming?
I mean, they can't as it is, I mean,
they could get Rolly Crump to go back in there and design some dolls that could
dab, but.
So that tells me he's not, I don't think he's into dabbing.
A psychedelic expert is not a dab guy. Yeah. Or maybe he is.
Who knows? We'll have him on the show and ask. But I was talking,
I was saying, I tried to get, I was like, Lindsey, we should go last day holiday.
And I was just telling Scott and that's when I hit record on the podcast because
I was like,
it kind of excites me to go on an insane day when I know the park is going to be
a capacity. And I don't know.
Why in the fucking world you're out of your mind? What?
How can you justify that?
I'm trying to think how I can justify it there.
I think there's some something fun to me about with my checking brain.
I think there's something fun to me about navigating the chaos.
I think there's something because I like Comic-Con. I like an insane crowd.
It doesn't bother me at all.
I've been to Comic-Con with you several times now and I'm like as fast as I can
get to something calm off the show floor to your end too. You know,
yeah. You, I know you're a fan of sneaking off to Joe's crab shack.
On the other side of the convention center,
which is oddly not populated for it being the biggest event.
We will do a Joe's crap shack episode on this.
Joe's crack counts as a themed experience, but you, I don't,
I don't get you like I, if I had never went on the floor at Comic-Con again,
I'd be a very happy man. I don't, I don't know how you can deal with Comic-Con.
I don't know why you would a full capacity. That's,
you remember when we went right after labor day and you,
we were in the park for a total of 40 minutes on the way to the angels game
with Monday. Yeah. So it was insane. Yeah. It was insane.
And you still after that,
you still are into going at peak capacity.
Yeah. Well I've been, we've talked about this, that,
that Disney day that was 24 hours was the worst day ever.
And Disneyland was like closed essentially to new people.
And we went to California adventure. And then we just like,
I don't know. I think it's fun.
I'm trying to analyze myself here because I'm not exactly sure, but like, I like,
we like hung,
we found a little spot to hang out in when it was just full like California
adventure was almost filled to capacity. There is something I like. I don't,
oh, it's not that I just like it like this, but there is something fun.
Maybe I think it's like a challenge and then I do enjoy sneaking away from the
crowd for a while. Maybe there's something psychological about that. Like it's,
I'm trying to find my own Joe's crab shack at Disneyland.
Where is it going to be the rest of it?
The answer is it's here. It's where you live.
That's your home or a nice restaurant with no one in it.
I do remember going, I went,
I met you down there for one of those 24 hour days,
but I left LA at like midnight or 1am and like got coffee at
7-eleven and like got down there at two or three. And at that point,
it had calmed down, but you all seemed shell shocked. Like you all,
you were still going, of course.
Yeah, of course.
You did seem a little bit like you were somewhere else when I looked in your
eyes.
I've had a mic line in my head for a while and I think now is the time to say it,
which is that I think that the only way that you would enjoy a relaxing
beach vacation is if there was an app that got you better beach than everyone
else.
Now. Yeah, that is, I like the idea of that. If I could figure out like,
well with this thing, I actually get 3% more shade than,
I do that does. Yeah. Now you're not wrong about that.
Do you think it's the collective experience?
Cause a thing I like and it becomes more and more rare as time goes
on is I do like watching like live broadcasts
as they're like the Superbowl, like knowing that like, Oh, every,
everyone quote unquote is watching this or even though it's a live music,
like this is a thing. This is happening live. People are seeing it live.
I do think that is novel in a time when everything is on demand.
That's a reason to go to Disneyland when it's crowded.
No, I'm just trying, trying to, I'm trying to think of, yeah,
psychologically logically part of a mass experience.
Yeah. I think what the 24 hour Disney day, especially that's what that was.
Cause I think I like saying I was there when they did that thing.
That was like a fun energy and there was,
that feels like an event and it feels like a story you can tell. Yeah.
I think there is something. I mean, we were in the,
I'm trying to think of the last like concert, the last,
Scott and I went to Kanye West a few years ago. Oh yeah.
And it's in the pit down.
It was the one where he has the flying stage over the audience.
And that was super exciting though, though very stressful when like it,
the flying stage moves and then everybody moves backwards or forwards to try
to get in the right position. Yeah. I know I didn't be right under it,
but why not be right under it? It's going to happen at some point.
I didn't understand all that ducking and weaving.
I thought you would just post up in one spot and just let the stage just observe
this. I would think part of that would be like, Oh,
sometimes I can see it. Sometimes I can't. Yeah.
Like I think it was really weird. Everybody's scrambling to get out of the way,
but you're right. Yeah. That was like crowded and sweaty, but super fun.
And sometimes it did. Sometimes it can be right. And like that, yeah,
that's obviously a very specific, there's, you know,
it's two hours long or whatever, but here's my point. Of course,
a crowd at your,
you're in a giant crowd for the once a year Comic-Con or for,
or for Kanye West or for the Rolling Stones or whatever it is,
you're at Disneyland always. No, I know you also want,
so now I'm in a Kanye level crowd to get onto big thunder mountain.
I, that's what I don't get.
It's a good question that I don't know. And again,
Jason's the only one in therapy,
so maybe I won't know the answer until that happens and we really explore it.
But I guess I like, yeah, I don't know.
I really don't have a good answer other than it seems like a fun challenge for
checking. And I like,
I like that. I don't know. I do like being in a big sea of humanity. I think,
I think I kind of like it. And yeah, I guess I'm used to it.
I've been trained on the floors of Comic-Cons my whole life.
I like,
I like the feeling of being anonymous in a large or like a hotel space,
like I like hotel spaces because there's kind of an anonymity sort of there and
an expectation of privacy. Yeah.
So I guess I don't have the greatest answer for why,
but was will Lindsay's response to this pitch? I said, well,
it's going to be like a very crowded. I go, we could also go, you know,
a few days later and it'll be much less crowded. And she's like, well,
let's do that. Makes sense to me. Of course with me, I was like,
let's go both. Let's do both. Why not? Well, look, I'm going down there.
Sure. Yeah. That's why I'm doing it. I don't think we're going to end up going.
I forgot about the, but, and you know what? You, you are correct.
I'm finding my little island of with the, with the,
with the Napa Rose. That's my, wait, what'd you call it?
The, you're talking about the wine specific restaurant?
Yes. Yes. Yes. How dare I enjoy some wine with my wife?
What a weirdo Scott is. I didn't say that.
I didn't say that. You, you really get the, all that came from you.
So it's my, so I'm, uh, I'm going inward on some level.
I think it's weird. Well, I don't know. Jason's interest.
My mother does. I was over the holidays. Like, Oh, I'm just saying,
it's interesting. It's, uh, you know, just interesting.
It's like a Trumpy like people are saying, uh, right.
Shouldn't be calling your mom Trumpian. No, no. Uh, anyway. Yeah.
I'm going to fucking great time. Yeah.
It's a wonderful restaurant. I've been there once. Super jealous.
Hold on one second. Uh,
I'm hoping he's not just going to show up because now he has a, I'm going to cut
this up. Okay. Uh, obviously he just wrote running late. Sorry. Overslept.
And then I just wrote, Oh, you know, we can, we let's reschedule.
We have another one scheduled for in a bit.
So let's just figure out another time, but he hasn't responded.
Oh, like is he just going to show up?
If he does, we can try to delay Doug. Yeah.
So I'm just wanting warning you guys. Okay. That's what's happening.
I'm hoping he just pops in. He's in the shower and they'll go, Oh yes,
let's reschedule. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm hoping that's what happens. Okay.
And he lives next door and I don't know that.
Yeah. So that's what's going on. Anyway,
keep going. Yeah. Right. Um, so we were talking about your,
you just said you're, I think we were kind of done on that topic.
We were just, there was a good segue there. Okay. Sure. Sure. Um, so Jason,
you were saying, uh, your mother does that. Um,
you were also telling me like you think it was yesterday, uh,
about your gifts for the holidays. We were sort of catching up about everything.
I have some things to share about what I got for,
for like theme park related gifts, but let's start with you.
You were wearing Wolverine socks and I said, Oh,
there was X-Men socks and you pull it up and they were like Wolverine claws.
And I was very fascinated because you said something very specific that you told
your mother not to buy you that she buys you every year. Oh yeah. Okay.
So like we haven't really given a holiday update, like what our holidays were
like. So in addition to the mailbag, this is kind of like, yeah,
how I spent my Christmas vacation. Um, I,
my wording was something along the lines of, of telling that I told my mom, mom,
please no, uh,
novelty boxers here because at some point my mom started giving me every year at
Christmas,
like a Simpsons boxers or Marvel comics box or Star Wars,
was there ever Disney turtles? I don't think there was.
And I believe this is,
this went for about five or six years because I have about five or six pairs.
And so she did not.
So this year she instead opted for novelty,
but like shifted to like novelty,
saw like men's, you know, thin, I don't want to say dress socks,
but like, um, you know, patterned socks.
So yeah, I got a Wolverine pair and I got a Mickey Mouse pair insist,
which I had a pair of already, but she insisted they're slippers socks. Now,
I have, I didn't know the art to tell her. I don't think there were slippers.
I believe they are like knee length,
like skate socks like that you would wear if you were wearing shorts and vans
and we're skateboarding.
But slippers socks were a popular in my family. Uh, when we were younger,
they were like thick socks that had like the, the warmth of slippers,
but then like rubber grips on the bottom, but they were just like heavy socks.
Uh, I have not worn slipper socks for many years.
I have never heard the term slippers. I had a feeling this was going to be a thing.
Sounds familiar. I can sort of picture what one is.
I picture like the socks you put on that are temporary socks.
If you're trying a shoe on like just like a very,
like imagine wool socks. Imagine like a foot,
like fleece lined socks kind of, but with like rubber grips,
grip padding on the bed. Oh, yes. Yeah. I see. I know what those,
I didn't know that was the term for it.
I think we had those when we were very young.
Yes. So, but you, you know, with your parents,
sometimes you're stuck at an age. Sure. Yeah. You don't get beyond that.
An age in the age being your late twenties,
early thirties where your mom has been in a long streak of buying you boxers.
Yes. Now my dad, a little more on point. My dad,
who knows about T public now for us, got me an alien encounter.
T-shirt from alien. Very on point. Got my brother a people mover T-shirt,
cause my brother always loved the people we were growing up. Very on point.
God bless those people just doing blatant copyright infringement on T public.
It always makes me laugh.
By the way, there's, isn't there, so people are, there's a shirt of the poo,
the girl from our, from our live show,
the painting that we got for the crafts.
Which is not us. That account is not us. We make no money on a shirt.
We don't make money from it.
Nor does the actual artist who should be making money from it.
That's true. So the actual artists make money from the sale to the,
to the us there and therefore the crafts. Very good question. I mean,
I think I bought it on an eBay, like art reseller,
collectible reseller. So it's possible it was bought from them.
It wasn't from an account that was entirely a double mint babes hugging Disney
characters in a three percent sexualized manner. No, it was not that.
So yeah, I don't know the answer to that. That's too bad. Cause you know,
yeah, you get like, you know, King John being, uh,
some, some tennis radigan from great mouse detective and a nice young lady.
King Louie. Yeah. So kind of a reach around.
I wish I do wish it was a full, a full lineup. Yeah, that would be great.
I mean, I think we've just called for fan art.
You got to be like, that was pretty top tier illustration that babe and poo
so it's, um, yeah, somebody's got to really step up the art game. Uh, that looks,
like that was like a beautiful, it was like a still from a story book.
It was really nice. Yeah, it was great. Yeah. Boy do I wish if we found out there
were like 12 of them, what a day that would be. Yeah. Oh my God.
It was part of a set or a period. The artists. Yeah.
It was a, you know, he had his landscape period and then he had his, uh,
Disney characters with sexy babes period.
Yeah.
Wild cleavage meets, uh, some overachiever characters,
some overachiever and the listeners are, is going to do it all.
That is a calendar. We got a calendar now.
I only ask for separate drawing one-off drawings of Jason.
So we're not asking you to draw 12 different drawings. That's a lot of work,
but boy, would I be happy to have the, the cat to see the calendar.
Would we love it? Yes. Yeah. Disney babes of 1974,
2020 calendar.
So I did have more Christmas treats. Oh, you do. Well, my,
my mom and stepdad got back from Orlando recently.
So I got some Orlando stuff and that,
that was a similar thing to the, the side. Like my mom gave me a hoodie.
I had like an older version of like Mickey on, on the like breast pocket and on
the back. And that was, that was good. But then I also, and I have,
I will bring this over. I didn't, I couldn't fit it in my suitcase.
So they were going to, they were sending, shipping me some stuff back.
And it is a small plastic bowl that says Walt Disney world on it and has a
bunch of characters on the bottom, including Duffy himself.
Wow. I have no idea what I'm expected to do with the small plastic
bowl. I think maybe what I am planning on is it's the perfect size for a couple
scoops of ice cream. Don't you?
Odd question. Like what am I expected to do with this? But whatever you want,
it's a bowl.
I and I had said like go easy on the chachkies too,
cause my mom likes to go at teaking sometimes just every now and then some
Disney, Disney McDonald's toys.
Just a clutter or a weird Christmas stuff you don't really want sitting around.
But is there a bowl you've ever seen where you weren't like, you know,
a couple scoops of ice cream would fit in there?
No. You know what I like?
I too a good trick with ice cream portion control is to use coffee mugs.
Do you standardize coffee mugs? Cause that can only hold like a couple scoops.
How many can you get in there? It's still a five.
How tall can you stack the scoops?
Well, come on. I don't want to be a practical,
I am a balance in 14 all long ways right outside of a,
yeah.
The answer is it depends on if you are using a traditional scooper or if you're
using one of those slab kind of scooper, you know, those flat guys.
Okay.
I imagine the bigger the scoop, the like heartier and sturdier it is.
And you know, they could get smaller as they go. Right. Yeah. Yeah.
There's a number of ways you can do the stack. The Jason stack.
I'm so now it's in my head. How you eat ice cream is a giant tower.
Jughead eats it like that. I assume.
The main way is regularly. Sometimes the answer is daily.
If sluggo could afford ice cream, he would eat it like that. Uh, if,
he would, he's poor kid. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, does Dagwood, Dagwood eats a big sandwich.
Dagwood eats a big sandwich. Who knows if he has room for ice cream.
For seven scoops on top. Yeah. And I, here's the thing though,
and I'll throw it, throw it back to me. I am the one,
I've never seen you do a double scoop cone with sprinkles. That's my thing.
So I, I'm actually the scoop man of the two of us.
I'm the stacker is what I'm saying. You mean out and about? Yeah. I've never,
you probably have gotten a double scoop before.
I think so. I usually just, I,
I usually don't necessarily want that much, like whatever these smallest,
like we have an ample Hills now in Los Angeles and their kid size is like a
good amount on a coat. Like that is enough for me. Uh,
ample Hills. I got accidentally got three scoops in a cup once and I was like,
this is too much. Oh, I got the flight. I demolished a flight myself.
Six scoops of ice cream. Smaller scoops.
Yeah. I lit up like saucers, which they were just put in a saucer.
They should have ample Hills should do the flight, but stack them.
So you have six scoops on top. Like a cartoon. Yeah.
And I got to say my too much.
So my throat kind of hurt by the edge. It's too much sugar.
Jason Sheridan's sugar throat.
The thing that you would get as a child often. So getting sugar throat is a okay,
but having a nice wine based dinner with your wife is insane asylum.
Territory. No, I just said it was interesting, Scott.
There's a lot of implication and interesting sugar throat.
There also could have been like a 2003 new metal band.
Sugar sugar throat. Just on the bill with like disturbed or
like it out. That seems like it makes sense. All right.
I'm going to show you what I got for Christmas. My sister got this for me.
Oh my God. Oh my God. I guess it's, I'm holding it upside down.
I've always wanted one of the, I've literally always wanted one of these.
It is a kitchen. It's a tea towel cabaret tea towel.
And it has like most of the characters on it.
And I think she got it on Etsy. And I'm not, yeah, Jason is jealous.
What about it specifically? Yeah. So it's like a, it's like a, it's a,
like sort of a tick tack toe, but with more squares. Right.
And it's got all your care, very various characters. I'm looking today.
Does it have, where's Mr. Dairy Goods? Is he not on here?
Is he food? Is he food rocks? Yeah. Is he through rock? Yeah.
Maybe you're right. He's food rocks.
But all of the various members of the, of the kitchen cabaret band and,
or bands are all represented in pretty sharp colors.
It's pretty vibrant. You get the couple of them twice, the banana twice.
There's some repeats for sure, but like the broccoli is only on once.
And thank God, not those cereal sisters who scare this shit out of me. Yeah.
No, that's good that they're not there, but it's a, it's a,
this is a very specific present for a very specific man.
My sister knocks it out of the park. Also, I don't have it yet.
Cause she was saying there was a shipping problem. She bought me and she made sure,
she said it's got tags on it. So she doesn't think it was ever worn.
And a vintage Epcot center hats, cause I'm a hat guy.
She knows I'm a hat guy now. So she bought me like a classic.
She should get a scare guy to deliver it to you.
She knows about the haunts too. She knows about the haunts,
but she, so I saw a picture of it and I'll,
I'll debut that on the show too whenever I get it.
So she knocked it out of the park with park specific gifts for me.
That's great. I don't have a lot of, I got that nice Walt Disney's Disneyland,
the, the Tashen. Oh yeah. Yeah.
Which I haven't really been through a ton, but that's very nice.
But I don't think I have,
other than that my parents got converted some money to yen for me and Aaron as
we are going to Japan this year. So that's, I guess,
Disney related. Yeah. That's where I'll be.
A lot of my money to Iraq, Iraqi denar.
I have fallen for the scam that Mr. Trump is going to reinflate
and when Disney Iraq opens,
when Disney illusion open.
So, well that's basically, so our holl, so in summation,
how are our holidays? Jason got a bowl.
Jason got a bowl and there's one quick thing. Yeah. You want it.
That I would like to, you've,
you sent me a couple of photos that we'll get to the mail bag right after this.
You sent me a couple of teaser photos.
It's something I've been asking for from you for years. Yeah.
And it sounds like you will eventually give me my Christmas wish of 2010 or
something.
The play I was in a 10, Kilroy was here. Yes.
I have it in DVD format and MP4 format.
Oh, digital and streaming most of a day.
And I, I,
I was thought I was going to have to drag like Jerry,
you know, rig two VCRs and do it. And then my mom dropped.
She's like, Oh,
I bought a VHS to DVD converter years ago.
Cause you kept asking about this and I forgot about it. So now it is not one,
it was not what I was expecting. It was just a DVD play.
It was a, like a VCR DVD combo thing,
but the DVD, but you can, they're both writable.
So you can write VHS to DVD on it, or you can write DVD to VHS,
which is interesting. So,
so hooking that up to a TV and then running it took a while and then
duplicating the DVDs and create using disc utility to make a disc image,
to burn backup DVDs and then using handbrake to make MPEGs.
My god, a complicated conversion process as if restoring a classic,
uh, as if restoring a Hitchcock film or something. This is, uh,
incredible archival work.
Yes.
And as I finally received my Indiegogo reward of a digital copy of the other
side of the wind, cause I was a backer to that campaign four or five years ago,
it was his last movie, uh, which then of course,
Netflix put up the final finishing funds and it's been on Netflix for months
where they finally got around to sending out Indiegogo rewards.
So I lost on that one.
We have the best digital copy of any media now.
Which I have not watched myself. Like I, I put sick cause you had to let it run.
You had to let it run real time. Uh, and then, uh,
like the burns were quicker, but I was watching like clips and stuff,
but I was also amazed at like, Oh man, the video production company who set this up.
I clearly put one of the microphones by where people are entering and exiting a
plywood part of the stage cause you just hear a thunk thunk with characters walk
on stage. Uh, and also did not,
something is off with the lighting of downstage,
but still it is a three camera setup for children from middle school production.
So we will figure out how we're going to present this. You're a Nazi by the way.
I'm a British hypnotist.
I have a Nazi spy masquerading as a British hypnotist, USO,
entertainer.
Do you have it? Did you see any of yourself? Do you have any sense of,
is it how watchable is it? How, uh,
recognizably you it is. Yeah, it's me.
It's clearly me. And there's also,
I think Mike may have traveled back in time to be there because you can hear
people laughing at a 10 year old walking out and committing hard to this.
You're getting laughs before you open your mouth.
Yeah. Probably also like it was intoxicating,
but also a little scarring of sets of reality.
That time. Yeah. So,
I don't know. We'll see.
And also like seeing some of the full cat, it's like some of the musical numbers.
I'm like, Oh, in my mind, this wasn't so tinny.
It's all wasn't so tinny. I didn't really have to sing solo at all.
So I'm not really singing as much only in like group sequence,
group numbers and stuff. So, but no,
I think we should have people over to watch.
You mean all the patrons? Is that what you're saying? No. Like our friends.
I don't know. I guess we should upload it to the Patriot. I don't,
it's weird that 60 other people are. We'll see.
We'll work on a distribution plan.
Clips of me. We have to get this footage and survey it.
Like when they found the sound to remaster the sound, if it's a little tinny.
Yeah. And is it a cut down or do you present it uncut as it was originally
intended? Yeah. Will pioneer drama services get angry?
I hope, I hope they come after us. Cause it'll only be good press for us.
By a drama turd publishing company. Yeah.
Controversy creates cash. So I have it. And I couldn't,
I don't know that I could have predicted, although you're involved,
since you're involved in Michael, I guess I could have predicted that just show
just slowly became a spalding gray model log about my life.
To Cambodia sort of exercise my whole plan the whole time.
And the audience is here for it. I think you'll see the theme park content,
slowly diminished to where you keep, don't even realize it happened.
And it's just entirely true conversations with Jason Truman show,
Jason Sheridan with Jason. Yeah. Hey, speaking of the audience, uh, let's,
we got questions pouring in. We asked for questions live. Uh,
I'm going to start out with a real quick one. And then I have some,
some emails highlighted, uh,
friend of the show, Nick Weiger tweeted out and asked Ken Jason,
finish one of these himself.
And what he is talking about is apparently a new option at Walt Disney's magic
kingdom. It's called Ralph's family challenge.
Did you change his words? Cause he, cause I have, I have a tweet from Liger.
It's by memory. What did he say? Cause Liger did a much more casual. He goes,
could Sheridan take this down solo? Okay. Yeah. His is funnier.
Nick is funnier than a, uh,
well that's not what I'm saying. Hey, no, uh, uh, could I, you know,
there's not a description of what all's in it,
but it is a trophy filled with ice cream. Uh,
Oh, it's got a wreck at Ralph in the middle of it. Yeah. Okay.
It says Ralph's family challenge.
For a family of three or four or five to take down. Let's, I mean,
it's hard to see the scope on exactly how eyeballing it.
It kind of looks like about the size of an ample Hills ice cream flight.
So I think the answer is yes, but my throat will hurt.
Strong risk of sugar throat, sugar throat. I mean,
here's a different angle. We'll post these angles. They're, they're,
they're clearly it's a, it's got a lot of depth to it. Jason,
here, do you want to take a look here? So I still think you could do it,
but I think you're out for the day. I think I'm a, yeah, I think you're right.
It's smaller than a kitchen sink. I'll say that.
You're only making it to instead of the normal bedtime of 9 PM. It's a,
it's a 7 30 PM for you. Whoa, whoa. Take a look at this.
Look how tall this one is just poking out of the, it's a, by the way,
it's a big trophy cup and then at least like six scoops atop the cup.
I think it's more indication of how many are down within it. And this is,
where is this available? Disney cruise? No, well,
I think it's in the magic kingdom now too. Okay. So the answer is a, for sure.
Yeah. Yes. So if we discover it's in Disneyland,
then we're going to have to go give it a try. Oh yeah. I don't think it is,
but yeah, we should. Yeah. Well, well, there has to be an equivalent to it.
And we'll do, that'll be an episode of can Jason put down 12,
12 scoops of ice cream, 10 candy bars.
Now I have to do talent challenges in addition to being vulnerable and open
about my childhood.
It's all my plan is coming.
You got to do jumping jacks, run around the room, then improvise.
It's all part of the plan. Like the Joker, right? My God.
I am just like the other new bit that new is the Joker. It's landed good.
All right. So I have another email here. This one takes,
I know what he means. It's got a little bit of context.
Wabin Wu writes a big fan of the show and theme parks.
I have a problem. I'm not sure if you guys have ever had,
I go to Disneyland with my girlfriend every year,
Buzz Lightyear Astro blasters used to be one of our favorite rides,
but in recent years I've gotten really good at the game where I score over
150,000 points every time. Now the problem is it's ruining the experience for my
girlfriend because she's not good at the game and she gets irritated.
Every time we walk off the ride and my score is 10 times hers,
she's starting to not want to go on the ride anymore because of that.
And I just feel really bad that I sort of ruined that for her at this point.
If I score lower to get on our level,
she would be bad too because she would just know that I do it on purpose.
Toy Story made it is starting to become an issue too, but not nearly as bad.
Is that a situation ever an issue for anyone looking forward to hearing back?
And I'm going to start. Yes, I have had this problem before.
Yeah, my, my ex and I would always would go on these rides and I would smoke her
ass every time. So,
that's why I was so intrigued by this question.
Have you guys ever run into this?
I don't want to sound like chauvinistic,
but I do beat Lindsay most of the time on these two rides. She's,
she beats me on other things, but on these two specific rides,
I do feel like I win. She's usually like frustrated by it.
I don't know if she can hear me talking. She is upstairs.
I don't know if she's frustrated. I mean, she's frustrated by it,
but I don't know if it's like ruining the rides for her.
So I don't think it's maybe as severe as what this gentleman is describing.
But I have to sit in like 15 minutes of stewing. Yeah.
And it's not like she's like,
I don't want to go on toy story cause you're,
you score 50,000 points higher or something like that doesn't happen.
But I wonder if I had a follow up questions for this person.
Have you taught her all the secrets? Does she know the secrets?
Are you holding the secrets? I don't know. Yeah. Cause like,
there's this on Buzz Lightyear famously, there's the famously,
there's the secret target in the dark hallway that doesn't lit up and that you
get a ton of points for that.
I'm wondering cause I realized there was, there was an addendum to this.
And he said he checked the last time he played and he,
his score was closer to 500,000. Okay.
This says also bragging by the way, how good he is at these games.
This is really kind of a humble brag email that this gentleman is like,
I'm the best at Buzz Lightyear and Toy Story.
But it's couched in the guys of like, this is a promise. What am I going to do?
It's like, by the way, I'm really good at these games.
I think we buy, by, you know, after a while of doing this,
it became more fun to see what the discrepancy is.
And I should say when I ride these rides,
cause I used to ride these a lot with my brother when my family would go down.
My brother is very good at video games or games in games of these type.
And he always owned my ass.
And so I just got so into like just trying to score points.
But then that, that does kind of occasionally make it a joyless experience
where you're just trying to rack up points and win.
Well, first of all, I will say we just played that, like,
I forget what it was called those Jackbox games for and switch over the
holidays with my family and Lindsay and my mother both kept smoking all of us
at the games. So I'm, she's beats me on plenty of things. Anyway,
I would say, especially Midway Mania, Midway Mania,
there's an element and I'm sure we'll get this on the full Midway Mania
episode, but there's like a secret thing in most of the levels.
That's very worked together. Oh, so like, if you,
I think I believe it's a few destroy all the lava stream balloons in the lava
level. Then all of a sudden stuff shoots out of the, of the volcano.
And then there's tons more balloons with tons more points.
And that's how you get a very high score.
Maybe this gentleman is doing that already,
but I feel like Toy Story Mania, you just say, Hey,
we're working together to unlock cause that's every,
every world has a little unlocking thing.
If you really stress that you're unlocking together,
it doesn't matter what individually points you get. You're doing something together.
You're working together to make everything. Now it's possible.
He's already tried this,
but I think that that's a fun element now once you've done that right so many
times is that you go, Hey, I know if you do all and look it up online,
cause I don't remember all of them.
But if you like knock all of the lava away and then another one,
I think it's like if you get all the aliens off of that rocket ship at once,
so they keep popping up,
but if you can get all six or seven to shoot and then have it to be empty,
then the whole thing opens up and a whole bunch of other stuff comes out.
Really? Yeah. It's very fun.
And I didn't know it until years in that that's what was happening.
Like,
so maybe the thing is to reduce the competition between the two and make it more
us against the world. Yes.
Maybe you're trying to be just to know that you're the,
you're like kicking the asses of the other cars. Right. She,
she's on your team as she is in your life relationship.
And it's time to acknowledge that in how you play. Yep. I think that's perfect.
I think there's a perfect way to describe it. It's really nice.
And you,
and he will always have the pride of knowing that he smoked her as many,
many, many times.
And he can enjoy that in his own memory. But for the future. Yeah.
That's fine. Wow. Well,
we got to give some relationship advice as a long with just remember it's
supposed to be fun, you know,
Aaron is better at me than that. Better than me at Midway mania for sure.
What else? I'd like you're not like, um,
she doesn't really like that ride and we don't go on it together as much.
I'm I'm slightly better than her. It's not like, uh,
nothing's crazy. No, no, no. I got you.
Really the big thing that gets you on that ride, the, your, your, the wrist,
pain at the end of it. Do you guys feel like adorable?
People have described that's again for the other full episode, but, uh, yeah,
my wrist is killing. It kills me.
It feels like you have to carpal tunnel all of a sudden.
And then for like 10 minutes after the last round, oh, it destroys you.
Flicking and flicking.
There's a way to do it where you're trying to just do your fingers like this,
which I know looks a little bit weird when I'm doing, I'm showing you like,
you're supposed to just do it with your fingers,
but I find it's hard to keep that up. So I feel like in our private time,
we have to practice using just our fingers like this to save our wrists.
How could one practice the motion for midway mania in their private time?
It's a good application in your life.
Anyway, we'll say that for the full episode.
Yeah, we'll talk about that for the full one.
Do you have a, I have a, I have a call. I have a quick one.
Somebody wrote in Tyler Holtz on Twitter wrote,
how many days is ideal to spend at Shanghai Disneyland? Obviously one park.
You need two days for that. So that's quick.
We don't have to, no one else has to weigh in two days.
Shanghai Disney.
Depends on how much you want to explore the hotels too.
I'm never getting into a day mess again.
Here's one sort of in the same vein as the Buzz Lightyear question.
If you were to propose your significant other in Disney world, where would it be?
Disney world. So it's a whole Disney world property.
Disney world.
Let me say this. This isn't, this isn't Disney world.
I'm going to get off with Molly Lambert.
Do we answer ashes?
Yeah, we're talking about where we'd get engaged to the afterlife.
Oh, okay.
You're getting aged to the ground.
Yeah, you're thinking of death and not marriage.
Well, hey, hey, hey.
How much different?
Hey, save it for the dirty table at the cellar.
Am I right, fellas?
The last bastion of free speech in America.
I wanted to try to figure out how to do it.
And I didn't at Disneyland, not Disney.
So I guess this is all I'll try to think of a Disney world answer as well.
But what I wanted to do was arrange.
When I describe it, you will say, well, this there's no way this could have been arranged.
But Captain EO is very special to me and to Erin as well.
I thought, what if you could arrange like it's the last showing of the day
and you somehow get some favors in with whatever
entity runs the captain of theater, Magic Eye Theater and say, like, I made a little movie.
Oh, we play it in the and then I propose like, is there someone you could ask to do that?
And here's what happened.
I started thinking about how could you do that?
Hmm. Got distracted.
Never actually asked anyone, realized it would be too complicated to do in doing so.
Forgot about, oh, I kind of need to propose to Erin in general.
Ended up being way too late on doing that bad move on my part.
Like the like my pursuit of this, which involves nothing other than thinking,
maybe I should see if I can make a little movie.
And I just got like distracted, forgot about it.
Sure. And didn't pull the trigger. That was stupid.
Our engagement ended up being extremely nice.
But I was trying to like how you made a little like
you get into the theater in a different movie plays.
How magical would that be?
Yeah, that'd be amazing.
How was I ever going to sort that out?
You would have had to go on high up in operations. Right.
I think to ask because you would have need some managerial side because
you know, front of the line cast members could have gotten in real trouble
for playing anything, not just the one thing.
Absolutely. Yeah.
The answer is either like you really are tight with somebody high up or the answer is money.
Yes, I'm sure.
Like, yes, there's the ability for them to create a viral video out of it.
That's the thing, Aaron.
And I want the least is for any thing.
Our engagement to be viral.
Look, you're bringing that up.
I guess I was thinking now, like because I was at first thinking like practical.
That is a little more impractical to me.
Yeah. But still in the realm of practicality, I would have been a lot of the hustle.
Yeah, tons of work and like something they don't ever do, probably.
That's really different than in front of the castle.
Yeah, right. So now my choice is going to be something that's even more impractical
in Disney World.
When swinging Teddy Bear comes down from the ceiling in the country where
she's wearing a wedding gown and she has a ring and then the show like stops.
And I guess there's maybe the new like there's a new like maybe a song
playing that I've written or something.
I take the ring from Teddy Bear and then propose.
I think that's the fantastical way I would do it.
You take the ring.
So you get up on the stage and like.
Yes, I get up on the stage.
I'm trying to think of the geography from stage to Teddy Bear.
How if I could reach and grab something off of her person, I might actually
be better to make the exception for you to do this.
Yeah. And you'll you're already talking to operations to get her fitted for a
wedding dress, also the dress myself.
I'll make the dress for her.
And you have to find as soon as Lindsey leaves her, you got to like quickly.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I'll measure her.
I think I'll go down there early and measure her and then make the dress.
Well, she has Chloe.
You could go talk to you, get the sizes from whoever in 1971 first dressed.
Yeah. And I'm sure like Len Testa in those Disney World guides has Teddy Bear's
measurements and one of the old guides, he probably lists all the country bears
height and weight and everything.
Hey, the post office can go two ways.
People can send us questions and we can send out questions such as what are the
size that what is the dress measurement for?
With Swing and Teddy Bear.
Yeah, she's up there on the tree.
Well, you just gave me an idea for one, which is that if we're having robot
shows involved in our proposals, I would have the Hall of Presidents begin its
roll call and then and when it gets actually, why don't we get we can get all
the way to the end.
We can have George Washington or Trump making a speech and then and then it's
interrupted by so I'm talking about new animation, new voiceover, new robot
programming should be fine.
It's in a it's all interrupted by James Buchanan, our bachelor president, who
sure who interrupts the speech and says, wait, I'm sorry.
I when my name passed, I thought about my life and my regrets and my biggest
regret was never locking down my truest love.
And there's someone in the audience who would have the same regrets, worry to
let this moment pass.
And then the floor is seated to me and then the and then I propose.
She says, yes, obviously.
And after that, you're going to say no, would you say no?
And then God bless America plays the most dramatic song.
Your guys is song.
Yes.
Jason, I spent a number of minutes sitting here trying to figure out the most
beautifully landscapes and just in the last 30 seconds, a bit like, oh no, we're
doing robot bits.
Fuck.
I don't know.
I had always pictured like I would think you.
Apple Hills, Apple Hills next to the bottom of a family side, the family
challenge ice cream.
Now see, they're Jason.
I scream flights are more like, like it's a, it's a dish made for the flights.
Like now, Ample Hills out here in Los Feliz.
Uh, it's just like one of those paper, the little paper trays that fries come in
now, six scoops in that anyway.
So yeah, that could be fun.
Um, I was dry.
I would probably say on the grounds of one of the hotels down there are so nicely
manicured and have a lot of pathways and some things.
So, so maybe like a wilderness lodge or animal kingdom lodge, or I mean, I like
the border, the boardwalk has a lot of cool little rooms and stuff, but I would
want somewhere without an audience somewhere, a little private.
I mean, Mike, you mentioned earlier on crowded days, finding little quiet areas.
And I do think that is a big peel.
Uh, the thing I like a lot of the parks.
So probably something along those lines.
Oh, you know what, maybe a legitimate answer.
If you could get, if you, if you could call and arrange like the nicest table
possible for fireworks at the top of the war, the contemporary California grill.
And then you could maybe share like a champagne toast, but that'd be pretty
fucking weird, don't you think it'd be pretty psycho to have champagne
in a moment like that.
All right.
Um, let's do that.
See that is still a rest or I think restaurants that that is a bit of an
audience, so that's, that's a little, yeah, potentially, but if you, I mean,
maybe you get the clap for the clapping after, but if you, if you do the actual
thing quietly or if there's private like Carthay has those private rooms that
like are not, I think you can just request them if you have enough people to fit in
them.
Yeah, sure.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Let's do a couple of quick ones.
Sure.
Do you guys enjoy, this is from Twitter user Desi chainsaw fingers.
Uh, do you and you guys enjoy Roger Abbott's cartoon spin?
Yes.
Uh, I don't really, I don't really do it ever.
You, but do you enjoy it?
Yeah.
But I don't, I don't do it as much.
I agree.
I don't do as much as a lot of other rides.
Terrible line, but that's, that's even with fast pass at the line is a bummer.
Claustrophobic.
I forget it's back there.
I really do enjoy it when I ride it and I think it's a good level of theming.
And it's crazy to think that that as big as that movie was, we, we almost like
forget that that ride is there.
Yeah.
Uh, grossest thing you've ever seen it at Disney park.
This is from Daniel J Morris.
Uh, just some bad bathroom, a gross bathroom.
Yeah.
Somebody else asked if we had any memorable, disgusting bathroom instances.
I can't, nothing sticks out in particular.
I think just like the high traffic ones.
Um, I, this isn't gross.
I guess this is more haunting, but, uh, Lindsay and I were leaving Disney and we
was very late in the whole parking garage.
There's only a couple of cars left in the middle of an empty parking garage,
just an abandoned stroller.
We were like, Oh, that's what's known as evidence.
Let's see here.
Uh, somebody asks, is it weird to go to Disneyland alone?
This is Nathan Torres.
Uh, does it just need some getting used to, uh, is it weird for the world?
Yes.
But for me, no, I it's fun.
Yeah, no, I don't think I, I for a long time hadn't gone alone just cause it's
such sometimes a burden to get down to Anaheim from Los Angeles proper.
But, um, it is fun.
I mean, you can really follow your own flights of fancy.
You can just do whatever you want because no one else is like, you don't
take anyone else's feelings into account.
And D and decent place to just to go, go think.
And like, if you're going to go, Hey, take a walk and sort some stuff out in your
head, why not do it at Disneyland?
Sure.
Yeah.
Or get some work.
I, the hotel, the public wifi is really good.
And park wifi is a little iffy, but the, um, it's, you know, if you work freelance
or whatever, like I know plenty of people who go down there to write stuff.
Um, uh, van, our former, uh, former guest pot friend of the pod, uh, asks top
three snacks in Disneyland.
I don't know if I have three.
I just let's give her a favorite snack.
Maybe I'll say double scoop Gibson girl ice cream cone with cone that has
sprinkles on it is always my favorite like treat to get at Disneyland.
I'm not too creative here.
I do just like the basic carts.
I like a churro and I like a Mickey bar.
Uh, and my dad was so fond of those Mickey bars and built them up before we went
every time we can't wait to get one of those Mickey bars and I follow in his
footstep is it the greatest ice cream in the world?
Not necessarily, but I have like a lot of fondness for it and for that, whatever
that shape that fake shell chocolate is.
And yeah, I do.
I do love the Mickey bars.
I like that too.
Uh, my, I, my flavors are generally cookie dough and rainbow sherbet.
Interesting.
Hmm.
Jason's got so much to consider.
Uh, I'm just trying to figure out how to do it.
Um, number one, I'm going to say the, uh, I don't know what they're calling it right
now.
It's available at most of the, uh, candy counters and stuff.
You can get it back in poo corner.
I saw some, one of our listeners had posted about it recently and it's the
peanut butter ice cream sandwich, but it's like a graham cracker, a thick layer
of peanut butter and it's all covered in chocolate and it's like a massive Hershey's
peanut butter smore kind of thing.
That's good.
That's really good.
It's, it's, it's easy to share, um, uh, cause it's a lot, but it's very satisfying
and not too expensive.
Uh, I put that at number one, uh, number two, I would say this is kind of general,
but, uh, any Sunday, like each Sunday varies by quality, but I think of a
Sunday as an event, like ice cream, I scoops of ice cream, a little utilitarian.
Clearly I eat that plenty at home, but a Sunday is a real treat.
So like daily event, but like, you know, I had that, so that Christmas Sunday
when we went down that I raced to get the jeer deli Sundays are very good.
Oh, I just did one of those the first day.
Yeah, that was, that's fantastic.
Really good.
Those are good.
Uh, good quality stuff.
And then number three, I would say, um, and I'll have this as a meal
sometimes the hot link corn dog at corn dog castle.
Uh, I really like it's, it takes the elevates the corn dog cause it does
have a nice spice to it.
Um, I wish they had it at the corn dog cart, uh, but I will accept that.
And the different, yeah, different corn.
You can just get the regular corn dogs, but if you don't want the chips or
apple slices, just get the corn dogs, all the carts, a little less money.
Well, that was quick.
Yeah.
The moment you've been waiting for your own life.
This is my shallow.
This is my star is bored.
Owned it.
You got your moment and you owned it.
Um, here's an email to podcast thread at gmail.com.
This is from Francesca's jumpsuits are in and they're 25% off.
Uh, so apparently according to Francesca, she's got 30% off Bogo and 25% off
dresses seems like rompers, a pretty good deal as well.
You had to really search for that one.
Cause I remember archiving that this morning.
Cause I think it was the first thing I saw when I opened my eyes.
This was the notification.
We now get Francesca's emails every day.
And Francesca's is one is just a boring store at city walk where I bought
Carly Rydgipson pun shot glass.
Uh, so we get those emails forever, but we're nobody, nobody's shutting them off.
I notice.
No, I know we could.
I think it's very funny.
I think it's very funny to get them.
Let's all go get some rompers.
Let's just shut up and do it.
There was very brief period where they were trying to make romp him as a thing.
I guess rompers is kind of a bit of a without an H it'd have to be romp.
Um, someone asked where they should, they're going to Disneyland and they want
to take a photo with their podcast, right?
Shirt in the park.
And they're asking where we would like them to take that photo.
Hmm.
Uh, this is user Tim at shut up, Tim.
So what do you guys think?
What's the best place to take a photo with?
Or what's something that we want?
I don't know.
I mean, I, we can go a lot of different angles.
I don't like if it's just scenic, I think it's always the, uh, from the war,
like the wharf, right to the car's land.
That's always like one of my favorite photo ops.
I mean, it's nice that people do this at all.
We love seeing these pictures.
So anywhere in the parks, uh, recently, some people, poor people had, I survived
the city walk saga t-shirts that they took a picture in, but in downtown
Disneyland Orlando, and that just delighted me so much.
Um, maybe it's, uh, what are we all fond of?
Yeah.
I specifically, I was, my first thought was like you and can you take a photo
with Rosita at the new tropical hideaway?
How many people are we talking?
One person that you mean wants to, I think it's just one gentleman with a shirt.
I don't know.
I'm not sure he doesn't specify if the whole party has a, okay.
I'll say this.
If you see any obscure characters walking around, that's always, I mean, it's just
fun to get pictures with like, we have a picture with the full cast of Robin Hood.
Yeah.
Well that was like a limited time thing.
Uh, any of you, you know what?
Do you pick your favorite fake rock?
Oh, take a photo in front of it.
We don't, we don't want to tell you what fake rock to take, but you
choose you think, think hard about it though.
So go through the park all day and go, what is my favorite of all these fake rocks?
And take a photo with that in the background.
And it could be, yeah, it could be touching it if it's touchable or it could just be
pointing at it way in the background, but yeah, yeah, customize it.
Customize it to you.
Yeah.
So it's a little bit of you, a little bit of us.
Thank you for even considering taking the photo with that shirt on.
Um, uh, I got a couple more here.
Uh, someone asks, what is each of your favorite secret piece of magic
in the Disneyland parks?
Hmm.
Uh, that's a good question.
Um, I feel like Carthage still feels like a little bit of a secret to me, even
though it's not everyone knows about it, but it's still like the line at Carthage
is always still fairly short for just the lounge, not for the restaurant itself.
So like, I always still kind of feel like we're in the like couple percentage
of people that go there regularly.
So, and it's small enough, it's very intimate.
So it always kind of feels like our little special place in a way.
Yeah.
Well, everybody get off my ass, but the Napa wine zone, uh, I'm sorry for
being the way that I am, but I, but like even more so than, than Carthage,
like people are not up there.
Yes.
That's second level, uh, where you can have a glass or a flight or
where it is really nice.
Like, yeah.
And you don't, you, you can like have views where you see, uh, the
guardians or cars land in the background a little, but if you want to just
like shut off and it's a little like pastoral and you forget you're in
the park for a little bit.
Yes.
That is, that is.
And I like that nobody, it's not a big old line to get up there.
Like there is for, uh, um, the lamp lighter.
Yeah, right.
That's a huge line.
Generally.
No, that's crazy to me.
And Carthage is pretty manageable that line usually, but it is when like
Chili's has figured out the system for like, okay, we'll text you to come back.
Disney hasn't adopted that yet.
Lamp lighter maybe doing that now.
A little, I don't know.
Yes.
There's, I don't, I forget if there's texts or not, but they might have some
sort of system of coming back, but I think it was last time I was there.
It was a bit confusing.
Um, when I went to that a couple of months ago, when I went to that, that
wine terrace, um, I, I did think it was a little confused.
I think it was because it was an hour before it closed or so.
So they didn't really have anyone stationed outside and it was a little
confusing in that sense, or maybe they were understaffed.
I remember when I've tried to go in the past and maybe this was before.
Like all the newer DCA stuff opened.
It was just so packed up there.
They're like, come back later.
But I think recently it's hasn't been that crowded.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um, what have we got something?
I mean, there's, we, we got a lot of emails that we didn't, we have, we
didn't actually like go through them, uh, before we just put out the, the, the
request and we just are doing it.
Uh, we'll fuck it.
We'll do it live, uh, to quote Bill O'Reilly, but the, um, you know, if
you asked a question, we'll, we'll get around to it.
Some of these are like, are like complicated.
We want to take a little more time with them.
I'll throw this one out though.
Uh, it's been Murphy, uh, dear Jason, Scott and Michael.
I know it's been a few months, but the people must know what are y'all's
thoughts on flows V eight cafe changing their menu.
If you ask me losing the Turkey dip is beyond, beyond all caps egregious.
Yeah.
Ben Murphy.
That's a great point.
Cause this is like the fourth or fifth generation of flows menus.
I mean, I liked it when it was, when it first opened, it was like, pick your
protein and your sides that it was like, you know, home cooking sort of thing.
And then they kind of adapted those into sandwiches, which they used to have the,
the roast beef sand.
They, there used to be this roast beef sandwich that was covered in like a
white cheddar cheat, like a real cheese sauce and like caramelized onions.
And for the longest time it was at the Fiddler, Pfeiffer and practical on
mainstream, and then they just stopped serving hot food there, but they came
back at flows and I was very excited and it was still good.
Sometimes it would have it at, um, Jolly holiday too.
And then it kind of faded away, but, um, flows now is kind of a bummer for lunch
and dinner.
Yeah.
I can't disagree with that.
Uh, I had, we, we had a little breakfast there not long ago, which was pretty
good, but I didn't have any context for if that has changed or I don't know if
that's changed, but what a, like a month prior we had a dinner ish meal there.
And I think I got like a tuna sandwich, which I'm a big tuna fan, but it was
very lackluster, lacked the personality of the meals, the meals used to have a
real personality to them.
Um, and it's gone and it's a bummer cause it's, it was fun to get, uh, like
Thanksgiving meal.
So like, like a bunch of whatever turkey or something.
I don't know.
I did a very, it was just a very specific menu and now it's very generic and the
food I had wasn't even that good.
It wasn't bad, but yeah, it's a bummer.
We should probably wrap up, but it's, I just saw this one and I, it's hard to
resist.
I think you have to, uh, John Rhodes asks what theme park animatronic would you
most like to have as your significant other?
If you currently have a significant other, they will leave you in this scenario.
So don't consider them in your analysis.
Fair enough.
Keep up the good work, Johnny.
Uh, yeah, he's right about that.
So there's no way you present, uh, uh, there's no way you make a, you know, I
was thinking we could bring a third in to our relationship and that third could
be a robot.
There will be some clicking noises, but I'm sure it'll just be white noise at a
certain point.
It was just made in the background.
Get used to it.
Um, so I mean, there could be an answer for third and girlfriend.
You know, you could do both if you want.
I think he's outlining the, he just wants our current.
Okay, fine.
Then we'll just do that.
You know, they leave, they leave, we leave for, I mean, I'm, I'm playing the
field so I can clear.
Yeah.
So I have no negative repercussions from this.
There's really, you know, there's not so many female animatronics, not to say
that it, uh, that it has to be, uh, it's, it's all up to us.
And, and as I said, James Buchanan is on the table.
Um, but, um, that's the reason he stayed a bachelor.
Yeah.
I mean, there's the problem is it's like with country bears, it's swinging Teddy
bear, uh, and you can't go with the, the three, the bear sisters because they're
like children, that would be weird.
I got one.
Go for it.
Technically, what kind of an, uh, Lyoda.
Oh, madam, the older, yeah.
I love, uh, I love a confident woman.
I love a woman who's like good at her craft and her job.
Who's better at summoning the spirits from places beyond than Leo.
Well, sorry.
Also good at her job.
I can only assume.
I don't know what she's, uh, it could all be nonsense on her clipboard, but
Spaceship earth, uh, scientists, uh, scientists, uh, with all yellow outfit
and, uh, Afro, yeah, she's pretty rad.
That's a really good one.
Best style of any animatronic anywhere.
And clearly smart unless she's just taken notes for somebody else.
But I don't know.
I think, I think if you saw the other side of the clipboard, she's like
cracking something major.
She invented the iPhone.
That's her.
She has the early prototype of the iPhone and then it was stolen from her.
Um, you see, there's a lot.
Yeah.
The you're here.
You're picking the few humans that exist.
Like I just mentioned Rosita too, but I shouldn't mirror.
I shouldn't date a bird.
I like her as I want to find this for her, but I was thinking about,
Oh, you're smart one.
There is smart one.
Female.
Well, but did we, you know what?
Jason's communicor robot.
Yeah.
That's smart one.
Much like the raw, the robot in Rocky four, which they change the gender of it.
So the theory is that Paulie uncle Paulie changes the gender of the robot.
This is all true by the way, Rocky buys Paulie a robot in Rocky four.
Uh, I don't know exactly why, but then Paulie changes the gender of the, of
the robot mid movie in order to have sex with it.
That's a fear.
That's a thing.
I mean, he, it for sure changes like the way it talks.
And then it's like, hello Paul.
Like he starts out much more like deeper voice and then it's much more like up
here and then the theories online or at least that Paulie has been having sex
with the robot.
It doesn't say that in the movie.
John Taffer connection to that robot.
Did you see this was going around like in December and November,
going around the internet.
There's a video that robot was apparently the like center attraction at a giant
nightclub in Philadelphia.
Whoa, really?
And it was like a UFO would open up and this robot would come out and kind of
dance with the crowd and John Taffer is narrating this video and even going like,
I was managing this club and this robot was a star.
Like we packed this robot was a star opening night.
People wanted to see this robot.
People lost their mind.
He, you know, he's always selling.
He's always talking about his customers.
He's like, and they use that robot.
We got, we lent them that robot.
They use that robot in Rocky four.
Oh, so it was existed already.
Yeah.
Existing club attraction.
So Stallone was at the club.
To that club.
And we got to get the movie.
Wow.
Really?
I didn't know anything about that.
Huh?
Can we Disney world?
Like there was so many different female stars on the great movie ride.
Yeah, I was going through there.
I'm on now.
They're all thrown in the wood chipper.
Uh, so I mean Poppins or Ripley.
Oh Ripley.
Oh, Janice.
Yes.
The morning we were.
Yeah.
A Quentin Tarantino favorite, I believe.
Oh, interesting.
Early crush of Quentin Tarantino's.
Uh, yeah.
But is there an animatronic Janice?
Yeah, you're right.
That's right.
She's just sticking to that.
We are sticking.
We should stick to the question.
You know what?
Um, I'm just, I'm looking at a list of, uh, animatronic rides and animatronics.
The, the, like the daughter in, um, uh, carousel progress in like 90s mode.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Still might be like 16, 17.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's defined.
She's in a turtleneck.
That's true.
She could be 21.
Yeah.
That indicates that she's in college at least.
I mean, I think the, which makes it fine.
To stop this conversation soon or somebody's going to walk into a hole.
The red head from pirates of the red, the original, well, I was met the
red with the big hat.
Oh, well she didn't talk.
Uh, would you ask her to keep the hat on?
I, it's such a, she looks so great in that hat.
I mean, so you're just picking her.
Well, my concern, I didn't say her first.
Cause I think I had a moment where I went, well, she's out of my league.
You were giving yourself some chicken or something.
Without a more robot love story.
Hey, if we have to go with the non-human, if we could challenge ourselves,
yeah, what about the, uh, nine I real Pearlman's, uh, oh yeah.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
Oh, I forgot about.
Grip onto her and she like ride her through the future.
Uh, sure.
That was panoramic times of France.
Yeah.
Um, easy one.
Uh, Ariel.
Does she, I guess she's more cartoony.
Yeah.
She's a robot.
Although she might be too young to.
Although I think, for sure she's a child bride in the, but also nine
I could be two years old.
That's a good point too.
And I guess when it, even though she sounds like an adult,
ex machina kind of.
Yeah.
I'm going to just to be safe, I'm going to pick, uh, what's the wife
and carousel progress's name.
John's wife.
Does he ever say, how dare you break up that marriage?
I'm going to break up John's marriage because your real relationship is ending
in this scenario.
Yeah.
Doesn't mean John in the toilet.
I'm going to drag John down.
First of all, he doesn't pay attention or you've seen the ride.
He's always, he's, he's confused about things, stuff going on.
He doesn't take care of her.
Like he should.
He's extremely dismissive of his whole family.
That's what I'm saying.
Good luck in there.
The oven blew up.
Who gives a shit?
Like that's John's attitude towards everything.
So he doesn't deserve that wife.
So I, I'm going to choose the wife.
He was in that rat race commuting to the city to make a
asbestos and agent orange.
I'm surprised you didn't pick the wife on carousel of progress
because yet that is yet another character that friends of ours have
texted you and I and said, Oh, Jason is John from the carousel progress.
So I would imagine that you, I would thought you were going to pick her
just because like you kind of self identify as John.
I guess.
Well, then in theory, I already go home to her.
Well, but then is that's my relationship.
I'm breaking up my existing relationship with an animatronic
for a different animatronic.
Or at least the grandma, you could go with the grandma.
And it doesn't say if it's John's mom or not though.
I think I've got the funnest combo between us.
Okay.
Jason and the Navi river shaman.
Oh yeah.
Oh wow.
Navi river shaman celibate though.
Are they pledged?
No way.
Stories.
She'll plunge her hair.
If you were to for to fornicate, she takes the hit, like it's all hair
connection and it's a different thing.
So they're not celibate.
I'm saying my spot destroyed, destroyed my spine with your hair sex organ.
Yeah.
Well, that'll that I wonder if they'll do something like that in one of the
sequels where a human and Navi come together, not just in an avatar.
And hopefully it cripples him and it cripples the human.
Yeah.
Maybe like praying mantises making love.
And it murders the other one.
Yeah.
Spiders.
Geez.
Well, thanks to Johnny for destroying our relationships and leading to a
scenario where Jason is a sexual death.
Yeah, that's what it is.
Yeah.
Boy.
Well, that was a mad cab.
We have got, we got too many.
We were like, Hey, now we have so many.
Yeah.
If you didn't hear your question, don't worry.
We'll get around to it.
And thanks so much for writing the podcast, the right post office.
Uh, this is a blast.
Really fun to get people's questions.
Yeah.
Uh, look how much you learned about all of us.
That's three creeps.
We're weird.
I guess what you signed up for though.
Yep.
You knew what you were getting into, what you're patronizing.
Uh, thanks so much for your continued subscription to podcast.
We're at the second gate, uh, and check us out on Twitter and you know all that.
If you get too much of us as it is, tweet at me.
If I forget to post a picture of that little bowl, if you're dying to see that
little bowl, you are going to win the day that comes out, you were going to blow
that's going to break the internet.
Break Ralph style.
Uh, all right.
Hey, thanks for listening everybody.