Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains rampant baseless speculation, non-specific wildwood
critters, and you asked for it, your official guide to Hershey Park's new gate.
Not a new theme park, just the actual gate you walk through to get to their existing theme
park.
All this and more on our thrilling look at 2019.
Come on in to the 2019 Preview Center on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show hosted by three men whose new year's resolution is to go to Disneyland more.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Scott Gardner.
I'm mildly accurate.
And Mike Carlson.
I would say mine would be to go to Disneyland more, but in like new interesting ways, you know?
Oh, I think that's a great, great point.
That's what we're, kind of what we're talking about today.
New interesting ways to go, but do you mean like go by hitchhiking?
Do you mean getting down there in interesting ways?
Closer to what I'm talking about. Yes, if there's a different way to get down there, maybe there's like a
not ride sharing, that sounds a little bit unpleasant, but
maybe I should take the train down and see what that's like. Go from Glendale to Anaheim, see what that's like.
Or you can do Burbank.
Burbank by the airport? Yeah, I mean, I'd love to take the train down more.
Maybe, you know, like let's go with strangers that I've never met before and I'd show them around.
You know what I mean?
I'm just spitballing. I'm not saying I'm gonna do that.
I'm just saying like see the world through a stranger's eyes. See the Disney world land through stranger's eyes.
I wish, I mean, I feel like this is a case for a lot of Los Angeles and Southern California.
I wish trains ran later and I, because then I'd be more,
like if they had ones that ran for like two, three hours after Disneyland
closed. Right. That's a tricky thing. It limits you on the other end. It really does. Yeah.
There is, I would, how much, I was thinking about this. How much would you pay for a, an annual pass
to a bus, an easily located bus to take you down to Disney and it would run pretty regularly and it could drop you back
off up here
at midnight or 1 a.m. It would need to have no stops. It's got to be a bullet train.
I think if I'm making stops the whole way,
Okay, how about this? There's a Valley stop and then there's a more of an
Hollywood stop. There's two stops and then it's straight to Anaheim. I suppose so. How much do you, how much is that worth?
I'm just trying to figure out the- I feel like you need a downtown stop to make it
viable too. I think there is some sort of bus that comes from a little further inland
to Disneyland and like a commuter bus for employees,
but anyone can do it. But I think it got too popular. Well, if we get a job,
then we can use the bus and that'll fulfill the resolution to go more often because we'll be there every day because we have to.
Well, we have to be, we're going to become scare actors.
I guess we're going to become churro cart attendants now.
And it'll fulfill my thing because now I'll be able to see Disneyland in a different way because I'm working there.
Yeah, so now that's a new way to experience the park. So you'll be able to see it from
behind eyes that are crying because you're depressed to be having a Disney lunch. Possibly depending on what my job is.
But you know in the new year the money changes for what you make at Disneyland, right? That's good.
Yeah, that's good. But we've uncovered some nefarious stuff about that in our political episode.
Wait a minute, we shouldn't get all down. Look, hey, welcome to 2019 everybody. Happy new year listeners.
Happy new year. Hope it was as exciting as every night at Pleasure Island.
Uh, though how could it be really?
But uh, yeah, it's we're we're here's the first new episode of 2019.
We took a little break and we're sorry, but we're back now and we're here to talk about all of the exciting new developments.
What will be happening in theme park world in 2019? 2019 is an exciting year.
Though, uh, you know, there's exciting ones to come as well.
I mean to shoot right past it, but 2020 also has a ton of crazy stuff.
I think that's guardians and in florida and uh,
2021 is disney world's 50th anniversary. We're a couple years away from not berry farms.
100th anniversary, which they because they're counting all the way back to
roadside chicken stand.
Which you insist on counting back to.
Yeah, well I insisted on counting all the way back to the first berry seedlings planted and they said please shut up.
Yeah, they said no. That's fair.
So there's you know, there's there's a lot there's a lot of excitement in theme park world in the future in general.
But yeah, we got we do got a big year coming up.
You know, especially with especially in terms of disney. I think they have like
Muscled their way through to make sure that they have the biggest year, but uh, the other parks are not sitting on their hands. Neither.
That's true. Yeah, um, there's a lot I guess. Yeah, uh, there's a lot the right like just let's talk rides real quick rides opening
Mickey and Minnie's runaway railway Hollywood studios in Florida.
People have been talking about this on the message boards for a long time people saying this ride is awesome.
I don't know, but everyone says like the word on this is that it's like very impressive.
It's uh, if you haven't heard it's like replacing the great movie ride.
It is like you're on a little
I think is it wi-fi controlled?
A little like train, but everything is screens, but it's like you're in the cartoon. It's not just like a yeah
Sort of there's moving practical they've shown demonstrations of it of like this these these
Practical things that switch that are being projected on or like all of a sudden you're in like a black and white cartoon
But then everything flips around and it's full call
The whole room is full color and you're in a giant crazy colorful cartoon. Oh, this is news to me
I don't know a lot of details about this in general. That sounds great
Yeah
They've sold some of the store like Mickey and Minnie are going on a little picnic and then they see a train and goofy is the conductor
And then you go into the like you are watching it and then you go into the screen and you're in the cartoon like
Everything that i've heard about it. It sounds does sound legit. Very cool
And this is what this is the summer opening. Is that I think I believe may
Maybe may it's always hard to tell with these things if you aren't checking the rumors sites like us
Nothing changes more than theme park opening dates. It's not like the movies where they declare
We're july 4th 2021 way in advance
Uh, these things are real muddy and they'll also like start kind of previewing
Quote unquote a couple months out. So it like and then but then there isn't an actual like ceremony
It is officially open even if it's been technically running for a little while. Yeah soft openings
Yeah, mike and I hit the soft openings for the wizarding world of harry potter in hollywood like two years ago
just from following like twitter and blogs going like
Uh, everything's open
Yeah, right. We were I remember we were together but no way
texting back and forth because my my memory of it I was uh,
I was doing when it back when I was running with my friend and our friend andrew grissom
Uh, I was monitoring a twitter account that was like it might open today
And then I was like, I think it's gonna open i'm gonna go up there and he was like
I got like things to do it's the middle of the afternoon and I was like i'm gonna go up there and they put us in a
Holding like pen and like an area for people to wait
And then it was like is it gonna open is it gonna open and then like I waited like an hour and a half
And it did and I was like one of the first 30 people in the first soft opening of of the hollywood harry potter land
Because by the end of the day there was a video posted by somebody else who was in there like a theme park
vlogger person and I
I watched it and there I could see you in the line. Is that true? Yes. Yeah
I feel like I don't didn't know that yeah
Someone else who was there with who was checking it to such an extent that they were there immediately then had the video up
Several hours later and you were in the line in the video. I mean I went the next day
Because I think it was inside universe. I like tweeted at them because they were posting pictures
Is it open there like it is right now and I got over there and just walked right in you're right
No
I'm having indigestion for this weird coffee energy shot. I just
Know
No, it's fine. You know, it's fine equals don't ask me about this anymore
Mission not accomplished. Jason always what? No, it's fine. Yes
No, it was it tasted pretty good. Where did you get it again? It was like a free coupon at ralph's
But and it was like all the reggae was like organic coffee organic milk organic sugar and like it tastes okay
It was just a little sweet. So the coffee was completely free. It was a completely free
Completely free because I don't wouldn't buy these energy shot things normally but and it claims it's too worth like two cups of coffee
Essentially. Yeah, but it's all hitting you right now. No, I think I was just kind of burping
Uh as I was trying to talk you're clutching your side. My hand is cold. Okay, and this
This throwbacky kind of chunky sweatshirt that you could find on everla.com is keeping it warm voluntary plug
You're also like twiddling a pen in your hand like your groucho
Yeah, you know what?
Uh, that might be the coffee kicking in because I don't normally jiggle a pen as I record and I realize i've been doing this
For about 10 minutes. You're gonna shatter that thing open. You're gonna have
So excited for coming attractions. It's 28 2019. Do you have your fidget spinner?
I don't have my disney my official disney branded fidget spinner on me. It's too bad
Anyway, well, yeah, there's a lot to be excited about but you know
I say let's let's cut to the chase
Let's talk about the headline the big thing that has been under construction
For a very long time dragging out and out and of course I am talking about an exotic outpost
From which endless adventures are possible. You know what? I mean margaritaville resort orlando
It is finally opening in january
No bigger theme park development right than this
We have a listen we have many listeners who have sent us pictures that live down in orlando and somebody just did
Somebody just drove by
And and put it on our facebook page and it's just like water slides that you can see from a freeway
Basically, yes, and from the water slide you can see a gas station
Mm-hmm
And so anticipation is what i'm saying is anticipation anticipation is building. Yep, you can feel it
Uh, yeah, it's getting out there the the the trailers are leaking on youtube and by trailers
I mean 45 seconds of drone footage taken illegally
Everybody's talking about it. Um, you know, I actually did I was looking into some stuff about
Margaritaville orlando in advance of the inevitability that we're all there
Together
Uh, we we gotta start getting the lay of the land now because if we if we get lost like the shaker of soul
You know, then we're losing valuable chill out time, uh, um, okay
Do you first of all, do you know the name of the water park? I feel like I don't
Um, you know, you know
You know the the buffett margaritaville
Verse landscape of yes the margaritaville verse multiple. It's a villana verse
So our margaritaville verse, you know extremely well, you know every possible song that they could name anything after the the from the big ones
To the obscure ones. Uh, does anything strike you is what the water park might be named after one of the songs
Well, just if you know if that's what it was
Uh, gosh i'm trying to think is anything falls is there anything falls?
It's not math sucks
Uh water park
It sucks. So come to a water park instead, right?
It's not the name of the park
I don't think they'd go with volcano with that volcano themed water park down the road. Ah true. No, no, no that would conflict
It's not I will play for gumbo
Falls it is it's a gumbo
It's all and the all the water is dyed to look like gumbo
So it looks like you're so you're swimming around in a big gumbo pot
Is it is it an homage to he went to paris called he went to the water park
Finally you got it. It's not grapefruit juicy fruit
It's it's going to be like the second or third biggest ones after margaritaville, right?
The paradise that the cheeseburgers can be found in that is the full name of the no I don't look what i'm getting at is
Uh, you know
It's it's just salty bay or something. You might think it's something like that
Something like uh, you know fawning from a song the name of the water park is island h2o live
Exclamation point water park. Oh
Thank you algorithm. Thank you for naming our water park island h2o live. What do you yeah exactly?
They like just they've put like 50 words in a blender and then three were selected randomly
Yeah, that flow doesn't make island h2o
island h2o
Iowan water it the like big time water place
Uh, this is nothing. What is this name?
It's especially galling because frank bamma's splish splash mama. Jama is right there in wow jason
You just came up with some awesome ip frank bamma. Of course is jimmy buffett's character on hawaii 5-0
And his alter ego in his fiction. Oh, yeah. Well tully mars is his main
Character I suppose. Yeah
There's many different buffett verse characters, did you just spit that name out?
I thought you were referring to a real place that was there. No, no
I spent about 30 seconds trying to figure that out
and i'm as
Amazed as you are that I got it all out without fighting my tongue
That's an excellent name and I think there's still time to change it
So you would have to think island h2o live
What do you mean live like as opposed to other water saturday night?
Live is live unlike other tv shows. Is that what you saw h2o live? No, it's not I saw it somewhere
You have a press release. I have a press release. Yeah falls. Sure. It's right. I mean, yeah, i'm just tossing out gold here
Yeah, um, let's see if there's anything interesting in here. Uh, this was from november 13th central florida's newest and most immersive water park
Will make waves when island h2o live at margaritaville resort orlando opens in spring 2019
Secondly, it's at margaritaville that's is that all part of the title also
I get
Uh, i'll say yes, so what you can buy a ticket for the water park separate from
Margaritaville hold on. Let me let me keep going here. And then there's also a section i'll tease that says behind the technology
island h2o live will unleash the power of pure play and enthusiasm with nine different thrill rides a lazy river a wave pool a
Kids area and a river raft ride for the whole family
Designed to enable guests to customize their experience and share it with the fan or the willer
Excuse me the world the park uses a new rfid wristband system
Which sounds like that volcano bay that will enable guests to personalize the music and lighting they experience on select rides
Well now well now i'm a whore
So you wow, this is crazy so I can listen to jimmy buffett's summer's
Song with a z in the middle of it while i'm on this ride summer's school summer's z
Like you've fallen asleep
Or summer's cool, it's both nice. He's saying you gotta have a time out maestro
You gotta go to summer school double entendres so you can listen to summer's school
Yeah in island h2o live exclamation point you could listen you can listen to a full
The full beach house on the moon album i'm sure
At in a single slide live. It's a long the lazy
That's lazy river. Okay. Okay
Um, you can't make the slide go so slow that it takes a full album's length
No, you can get like the chorus of despacito
On like one of the speed slides
Not if mike has anything to do with it. You're not getting any of that despacito shit
It's it's all buffett all the time. Yeah, no fuck despacito with this is least in the walls of this
They're only gonna play like the restaurants are gonna play jimmy like every third song
Four song they're talking about the rest are like avril lavigne. It's something that's not even in the world of yeah
Another high-tech feature be live invites guests to sing karaoke or star another audio visual experiences with clips from these sessions shared through the app
The gamified app be live. Yeah, it's a water park. What are you talking about the game of gamify gamify
Gamified app also allows guests to earn loyalty points with every ride now jason's on board for this
Oh, I love experiences and activations. I love gamifying my content and all my faith. I love properties
How about that? We all love properties guests can win prizes such as free food and beverage items skip the line passes and more
Well now you have my attention. Mm-hmm
Uh now this part says personalized paradise the experience at island h2o live will be all about creating your own unique
customized experience for those looking to soak in the island vibe listen to music and have some chill with their thrill
Tropically inspired havens will abound with hammocks cabanas and soft sand beaches around every turn
And adult only areas will offer cocktails only steps from your beach chair and nudity
I don't think that's involved to keep the fun going island h2o live is within walking distance or a short trolley ride to margaritaville
Orlando resort hotel and cottages and back to that trolley ride
Did I your emotive transit? Yep
Uh, I don't know if it's a margaritaville branded trolley though
and then they just list all the other they listen you're in walking distance to a
Burger fi capone's ford's garage game time sketchers and more
Um, well that takes us to another area of this that there I don't I didn't realize this about margaritaville resort orlando
That they are also building a new outdoor shopping complex as part of it and it is called sunset walk
So something tells me that the gang here is gonna have to take a walk. Oh, yeah, let's all take a sunset walk
I've got another yes, uh, they should have called it. Uh,
Well, this would get dicey with copyrights, uh flip-flop shop stop
That's good. Oh, okay flip-flop stop and shop
There we go. There's a little bit of a drunk over there because then the flip-flop stop and shop cops will
Give it the drop. Well, and you might step on a pop top
That's the biggest concern because this shopping mall is filled with loose pop tops a a beer, uh,
Delivery method that has not been used in decades
It seems in buffett style. Yes. Yeah, but anyway, there is a mall being built. That's part of margaritaville
At this point we're facing the dilemma of are we gonna have to go do a trip where we don't even step foot in disney or universal
That trip that is entirely about us and the old ux us and the keeper
Uh, who's gonna have a whole new world of sectors to right keep
Well, if he's out of the clink from all that copper wiring he's been stealing from abandoned houses. That's right
He's been up to no, he's not we've been keeping tabs. He's not the sweet boy. You recall
Yeah, um, I have a I have on this press release a media contact. So
Maybe
We see what they can do for us. All right
uh
Yeah, um, well this this is a big adventure coming our way
I also the the things that were not in that list that of stuff that's at sunset walk
Uh, you got a rock and bruise. Yes, of course the kiss owned the half of kiss owned restaurant
What sort of treaty or parlay did they need to come up with to get the margaritaville brands and rock and brew brands to work together?
The parrot heads and kiss army notorious enemies, uh, and it's ended in bloodshed before so to get them to work together. Um,
We'll see black magic had to be employed. There's no cabo a la cantina is there I don't believe so
But you know what you got you got a sketchers that might have been in your that was in there
Yeah, and you've also got an itch sugar
Just like city was like our beloved city
There's a lot in common between city walk and sunset and there's no itch sugar at the orlando city walk
I don't believe I don't believe there is this is potentially
Or unless i'm way off could be orlando's first it's sugar or I look and it's like it's seven 50th
uh, so
Are you just are you just gonna have to move there or be like a bi-coastal?
Like I don't I don't think like four days is gonna give you the hit you need
I think I just I feel like mike we're gonna lose you for like well a couple months vacation will have to be at least a month
I'm looking here. There's an itch sugar orlando international outlet
Oh, but that's at the outlet malls probably right? Well, I think yeah
There's that outlet in the name. There's two of them. So that's all like
spoiled edible underwear. Yeah
It's like a week from going bad. It's like yeah
It's like the food stuffs at a marshals or a tj max you can eat the underwear but do it fast. Yeah
Eat it fast, please clock's ticking
Uh, so there's a lot of stuff
Going on down there. Uh, uh, and and also
like
This is something that's going to happen in 2019 and we will have to we should just like emergency get the recording going as soon
As we know anything wherever we are
Let's just or if somebody has to be on the phone
We should respond to this as quickly alive as we can when we find out what the street names are
At margaritaville because if you didn't hear us discuss this, uh in a previous episode, uh, uh, uh,
Jason mike anthony geo and I submitted a giant list of names several years ago
Recommended streets for margaritaville resort
And it remains to be seen if they're going to use any now I was looking into
Have any of the street names been declared?
It seems like the main drag that gets you into the margaritaville resort is inspiration street
And that one's on the map and that could be a leftover potentially from the like
It was like a chinese gardens or something before I forget unless is that a buffett thing is inspiration?
Buffett somehow i'm trying to think that might be a lyric in a song
I feel like he's more into perspiration from sitting out on that hot beach all day
Well, there could be a perspiration street that is adjunct to inspiration story. We'll find that out soon
But the only one there there has been
uh unemployment fair
Uh to to start hiring up for margaritaville resort orlando, uh, and the address of the hiring fair
I don't know if it's a permanent building or just a tent
I don't know what people found when they got in there, but you were directed to go apply
At 8011 fins up circle
So that's pretty good. We got one we got one there
And I don't know if that was on the list. I don't know if that came from us that might that might be a basic
um, somebody sent us a couple street names they saw from a
Government thing and they were all pretty generic. I'm trying to remember where that map was that was that on facebook?
I'm not sure
Because there's certain ones like fins up or like I feel like we have fins up something
So like is there going to be a situation where we claim we made that up or are they going to say well, this was obvious
It's got to be clear cut. It's it's it's got to be one of our deeper ones
I don't know if you can remember any offhand. I was a fan of short street. Uh, I I was pushing for margarita strida
Um, I don't remember any of yours, but like it's gotta be one that's clearly from us
I'm interested in the employment fair aspect because I feel like I read an article or heard something not too long ago that like
There is a shortage of labor in orlando
Like not a surplus which they've they're building so all these places are building so much
There aren't enough people to work the jobs or just like the jobs are kind of thankless and probably underpaid like housekeeping
or custodial
Which the answer to that shortage is lure people there with money pay them more
how
How like come on is it this this is where it gets dicey for mike because to call the nameless
The faceless disney and universal corporations to call them greedy or say they're not spreading the wealth is one thing
But to put the blame back at your hero. Mr. Buffett
Well, yeah, it's a different situation because like he has a different lifestyle and like the brand is just a totally different brand
So there's obviously like economic concerns that you guys aren't even thinking about when we're talking about the margaritaville like brand and lifestyle
And like jimmy himself as sort of an entrepreneur like he needs to have a lot more capital on hand to make
Bigger more innovative changes with the business. So I think yeah
I think it's totally unfair to sort of put them in the same box
No, I mean that is we we were passing around a times article a while back from from when jimmy was working on the musical
Which has since closed that like right the one thing jimmy doesn't really do nowadays because of all his endeavors is really live the lifestyle
Right. He's too busy. He's too busy
But is it my instagram as my my it didn't it kind of confirms my instagram theory
Of them shoot like doing a photo shoot with him on a beach once a month and then spreading it out during
The month to make it look like he's just constantly on the beach to make it look like he's not in a boardroom
Trying to soak those minimum wage workers for as many benefits as they can
Well, I won't work for lower. What do you mean?
Meanwhile, look at a intern is posting like him in a hammock
With a big coconut drink and like I love life. It says under it if they were
Truly part of this lifestyle. They'd work for gumbo
Um, well so that's all exciting there but there are uh, non
Uh margarita centric events occurring. Yeah
There's more. Um, what else do we got? Uh, um, there's uh, let me see
Uh that what the skyliner is opening we talked a little about the skyliner
When we talked about the monorail, yeah the the gondolas that are going to be a new transit system
Connecting a crop of disneyland hotels and connecting epcot at the international gateway and connecting
mgm student, sorry hollywood studios, uh showing my age
I i'm interested. I mean, I think that'll be cool. I'm always down for new modes of transits. We know
Uh, I think uh anything around mgm studios is mostly going to be uh, get people out of star wars, uh
stuff, uh, mostly distractions from uh, the
Potential crowd nightmare that will be galaxy's edge. Yeah
As we're talking about do we delay it or not? But why don't why not?
The I mean obviously the seismic and we're gonna add we're gonna disney world or and disneyland
We're gonna start by quizzing scott on the three different
Locations that you could refer to star wars land as obviously we said one. I know them
Yeah, now now I know it's so, you know the planet name is it batu? It's batu
But what's the town called black spire outpost?
That's good. Good. Very good. You've hammered it in number three
Well, I was saying galaxy's i'm saying galaxy star wars galaxy's edge
I was making sure there was not a third that I didn't know or the number four star wars land
The thing everyone will call it. Yeah, with the millennium falcon ride in the uh, the big ride and the other the different ride
The different ride, uh, we haven't we tweeted about this. We haven't talked about it on the show
Uh, we know the names of the star wars rides and one of the rides is called
uh star wars rise of the resistance
and uh, which is mainly
It's mainly uh, tributing alec baldwin's work, uh defeating the trump agenda sure. Yeah with a with a quick
fist to the face
Baldwin style to some random guy black irish karate
And then and the other one is called the millennium falcon smugglers run
That's yes poland smugglers. Oh, yeah, we got we need to get every we need to get
Semicolons and winky faces and every possible
And ellipses every piece of punctuation disney can jam into a ride name now
What's what ride starts this trend of like galak mis guardians of the galaxy mission breakout twister ride it out
That's the way I said it a lot in that episode
That's the that's the totally the predecessor of this new bizarre way things are named
I mean in all fairness, we do have a podcast with a colon in the name and we're not a ride
No, we are a ride, but we're not sure uh, but like some of the services we have engaged uh, patreon and
There was a set. I don't know if it's on t public
One of them does not allow you to have a colon in like your username or something like that
So we've been stripped of our precious colon in certain sections of a website that you would never notice unless you went hunting for it
Surprise no one called it out yet. Also. Well patreon.com
Podcast the ride you don't put a colon in the later part
I would send you the wrong break though. You have a you get a virus from break the internet like ralph himself
Is mickey is it mickey and minnie's
Runaway colon railway
I know but it should be semi-common minnie's runaway
Railway rail rail question mark way
Exclamation point that one I guess the mickey minnie that is a pretty good name. I feel like that one's fine
Yeah, but it does feel like it's a lot of there's too many more than two words often in a in a name
Two thoughts is I think the problem
Yeah, two or three like thoughts is what's happening here. Are they both called star wars this?
Maybe technically. Yeah. Yeah
So that's but you feel the like the the legalese
Of it and you know, no human being is going to
Who will ever like a child will not say we have to get to star wars rise of the resistance
Do you guys want to ride ride of the rise? I can't even say it rise of the resistance
It takes you back to the days of michael eisner wanting to call
Uh call the ride star ride
In the early days, but I think it's I don't know. I think you'd be lucky to have as
As tidy of a name as star ride. What do we what we know about this ride?
Is that it's like you're escaping from the jail
So that doesn't really suggest anything about that. I who who knows like that could not be the ride
But like you're talking rise of the resistance. Yeah, excuse me rise of the resistance is about a jail escape. Yes
Yeah, it was it was it at the code name alcatraz for a long time and they called it like battle escape essentially
I think yeah
It's a ride about a rise
Of a movement. Yeah, because the rise of the resistance is like
That's what's happening in the galaxy, but that's not what's happening to you the entire
Some the story of the resistance rising which takes three films to tell
Will just happen in three minutes in one ride. Yeah
I don't know what people are going to call that
Well, because you know, I watched that holiday that two-hour one of the holiday specials and they kept asking
The performers what did they ride and everyone just kept saying I wrote the avatar
I wrote avatar even though there's two like no one's
Oh, they aren't even disney's allowing people to not allowing it
I think because it was like they didn't they they were just like well megan trainer just performed
It's gonna look better if we don't cut and we just talked to her naturally or whatever
But it was no one's saying like wait a minute
I'm already I had some problems with megan trainer on the last special and now you're telling me she didn't use the full title avatar flight
Of passage megan trainer you were on scotch shit list or the boat. What the hell?
What is that boat the navi river journey?
I believe is what it's called
But like I think people just call it like the millennium falcon ride and the other or the big ride or something
I think by not calling these things something specific
You're forcing people to sort of use a generic thing and invent their own name
There will be like a populist name for these rides essentially
I think you should come up with something as good and catchy as space mountain or something for each thing
That would independently find that's fine, too
I think when we will know more once we know what the ride actually is like will people call it the escape ride or the
lightsaber because like there's talk about like you're in a ride vehicle halfway through you get out then the experience changes and then there's there's
That's not on the ride maybe that's early stuff
We don't really know we don't know really know what I think
I know can I tell you what I think I know sure what I think I know is that
The first part of the ride is you wait in line
The whole thing the whole premise of the ride is that you're just going on a regular space flight like star tours
So yeah, by the way, this might be legit
Yes, you're in a magic rising bread line
Yeah, you're in the bread line and you're they're like let's go up to space and eat your bread while you look out onto space
It's gonna taste better up there. You'll get kind of more oxygen into it. It aerates it
Yeah, it makes a lot of sense. So you go in there
And you go in a ship like star tours. It's a simulator
You go up and it's high it's fun
You're in space and then all of a sudden you get caught in a tractor beam from a big imperial star destroyer and they pull you
In and at that point then you deboard in a hanger
And you walk through a giant hanger with a ton of robots
And that's the second part of the line
So you have the first part of the ride when you say get off is just that star tour simulator
That takes you up until the prison. So now they're putting you in prison
You're walking which is secretly another queue
And then at that point you get loaded into those fun vehicles that they showed at d23 and in that teaser
And there's like eight and eight and it's a trackless wi-fi thing and at that point
That thing zips around and by the way look up these teasers that they just released which are actual on-ride footage
From anaheim were filmed on the set. That's right. Yeah actors walking around and I didn't realize that until you said it
And when I went back and watched it, I was like that does look really cool
Like it looks like a full set because what's really what's extra cool about it is it's wi-fi
So there's not even tracks in the ground
Yeah, so you won't know
Where you're going in it
So it's basically like you just built the movie sets
And this car that can drive anywhere is just going to drive around it
Which is going to change from that's what i'm thinking visit to visit
It's i'm assuming there'll be some variations because that's what they do now
And we have not seen that in the trackless systems in domestic disney parks. I know no
Right, they had a pooh's honey hunt. Yeah, which apologies scott. I don't get to see it
Closer when i'm there or this year, excuse me this year. Sorry. It's this year. I'm good. That's hey
That's side note big theme park development for me personally. I'm so excited. Yeah, that's for sure disney
Tokyo disneyland tokyo disney sea and uh san rio puro land. Oh, yeah all in my future
And tokyo maybe the decision to not do
No, oh not that i'll do the dome city. Yeah, I'm uh, no, uh, no universal osaka for me
That's what we decided sizable distance between the two sure
Yeah, and I and we thought about it and like yeah
but if we uh, you know if we went I could go take a picture under the uh,
The king kong in city walk osaka we could post it on the twitter
And I said that and I both like just stared each other in silence and they were like, okay, so maybe not do uh,
So apologies no picture. Yeah
um, so
Yeah, I think that's why we were all we were just talking star wars
So yeah, so that's that's the rumor of what the ride is and then at that point you're shooting through and then I guess
The resistance comes to save you i'm hoping that droid there's a droid on each car
Is that do we know that for 100 you can see in the picture?
Oh, they're a little black droid in the car in the front and he's like bad, but I hope he's not like I hope he turns
I see so each car has a droid on it, which is fantastic
Cool. I also by the way, this is just a side note. I was going through the mice chat message boards
These fuckers
Are like this video doesn't excite me at all about this ride
I couldn't believe it like multiple people being like what is this show?
This isn't as good as this space mountain teaser from the 70s
And it was like yeah this space mountain 70s the space mountain teaser is one of the best things ever. It's fantastic
But it's a different thing
And I can't like the idea that you wouldn't be like, oh they really like recreated a star destroyer
The millennium falcon teaser that was filmed in the cockpit. Yes, I believe that looks cool, too
It looks fantastic
which it's funny that like this this sort of practical thing that was created out of scraps and and
Whatever pieces they could afford in the 70s have become so iconic. It's just like yeah switches and shit
So yeah, that's true. We're essentially
Like yeah, it's like original star wars is a little like junkie and janky and now we're like perfectly recreating shitty
what they like threw which it does speak to like the
Inventive spirit of the original star wars with like leading edge technology
like the way they're gonna have to render the footage in the millennium falcon ride with like
room for um
Individual like if you shoot a wall the wall explodes, but maybe you don't shoot that wall every time
Well, no, you don't shoot for sure. It has to be it's fully so anyway
So there's also this video showing the cockpit of the millennium falcon, which is the other ride
Which is a giant video game essentially. It's a giant simulator, but all the graphics are rendered in real time
Yeah
so it's like that basically means that like you can fully make everything if you want to blow everything up in the
In the senior and you can I don't know that that'll be possible
But it means that there's like a lot of flexibility customization a lot of room is what i'm saying a high end
There there if you imagine like a really high end computer
It takes eight of those to run one of these cockpits or it's some insane amount of processing power
And it's like it's six. This is just totally nerding out
But it's like six people I think in a cockpit which also makes it like such an intimate
Experience because you're in the cockpit with just six people. It's not like
It's not an open air. Most rides are like six people eight people whatever
But like you're in this tiny thing with six people and you're in
Like the you're in the thing like they've recreated it perfectly you're in the cockpit how many cockpits I don't know 20
Hopefully because the thing's gonna have such a shitty capacity
You're gonna have thousands and thousands throughput in an app for an hour
But I was thinking like they in that video
They show like close-ups of all the switches and the dials and shit and it's like yeah that really
Like imagine going in the batmobile like imagine doing a ride in the batmobile or whatever whatever vehicle you like from your thing
Like being recreated perfectly and then just getting to do it because like for a long like anything
I feel like a lot of rides based on tv movie or whatever like they get close to the promise of it
But this really feels like it's it. This is it
Like for me at least when I watch that teaser of like wow
I am gonna like hit the switch like I've dreamed about hitting the switch in the fucking millennium falcon and now i'm gonna get to do it
So like the switch so exciting. Yeah, both of these rides
it's yeah, it's uh, it's it's really something and it gives you like um, which it shows you how like
Think about how in in 1986 star tours was a satisfying
Yeah, uh, oh you enter the world of star wars and what they chose as representing that is totally acceptable and great
And the way that the films have grown and all the I mean obviously there's been you know
Many movies since then and the universe has expanded but the way like there is now need for
Totally different micro experiences within
Star wars it's almost a little like I mean obviously you could invent an entire park of disneyland size
That is all star wars sure stuff
Just true of harry potter as well, and you don't wonder like if there's already
Discussion of that or how you sure that people float those ideas. Yeah, I mean it makes sense
Yeah, I mean the one of the rumors for
Universal still unannounced third park in florida is like well
This will have the american magic or though it'll have some sort of fantastic beasts
Sort of element. Oh, I see
To to complement the the other harry potter stuff. Yeah, it is funny because like I think for years
Once they have the star wars ride in disneyland or disney world as a kid even you're like got the star wars ride
Yeah, that's it you and your kid had I don't think you were thinking well
They should do a ride about the 8080s and they should do a ride about
I want to fly the falcon and want to go to a street market and a restaurant with but end bar
right i'm interested in that like after the way cars land turned out and
So much what I like about cars land is just the place making and the level of detail
And that is a very important part of the star wars films
But if you're just watching it for the character stories, I feel like it's very easy to glaze over this sort of like, you know
dirty
breathing
Galaxy that surrounds these characters very interesting what they do with that in galaxy's edge
Yeah, and it's kind of a lot like we're talking all about the rides, but it does seem like you know
Look, how's it up? We've all done it. I was up at harry potter the other day
Uh, and like I didn't even go on the main ride like so much time you end up spending like i'm just gonna go down
This weird little alley and it seems like clearly they're trying to cut into that
Uh that piece of things and it's though
I think the crowds are going to be hellish at this thing
It's going to help in the long run that all right a lot of people are rushing to go to the ride
But a lot of other people are just meandering around
Side streets and looking in what that what's in this window and let's all just be in this shop for an hour
The toy darien toy shop you might be talking about. Yes, I am waddo's waddo's a brand of alien
I failed that test. Uh, i'll i'll try to have the right answer next time
Well with aliens too like with star wars aliens wandering around talking to you potentially
Engaging with you or yelling at you if you messed up the falcon like now, let me say this
I
Don't want to do that. I don't want anybody talking to me. I'm a guy that goes into a store
I don't want anybody bothering me. I'm like I'm a i'm afraid of being harassed by streetmosphere people
I think I made it through the brooklyn people in the window talking to me at universal and I even
Improved with them a little and that was fun, but they're at a distance some monster in my face
I don't know man. I bet though I bet the distinction in your brain is this and I could be wrong
but if it's like
A humanoid looking person with a little makeup or something or just you know an alien smock on
You probably don't want to deal with them. But if there's a full
Puppet man or like a vendor who's a big creature that talks. I think you're going to be all into that
Yeah, you like talking to like animal you like talking about robot animals and stuff
Sure, so if you're if there's a thing that doesn't look like a human
I feel like I might be into it interested in the mechanics of it and just watching it go by
I still am going to be more into like he's talking to a group of eight people or I watch it from a little distance
Right. I don't think I need to be talking to the guy
Though now i'm i'm recalling the video of you mike
Like yelling at kylo ren with specific dialogue. Yes. Yes
You will be all over that you will nail this thing
I had to psych myself up to do that though because I generally don't I feel too on the spot and I remember going
I'm gonna say something at kylo ren
And
I don't think I I didn't plan it out, but I was just gonna respond
I respond to whatever he says so I think I have to get psyched into it too
Because I don't know what you said I did I liked that that was just pure like 12 year olds
Yeah, I think I just was a contri contrary to him. I think I will never give in to the
Yeah, I think yeah, i'm trying to remember what I said and I
I remember I was like, yeah
I will never uh, I will never give up on the resistance or something and then he said something
Like I will rule the galaxy or something. Yeah, but what if you don't or something? I said something along those lines
Very simple. Yeah, good and it was fun and I was thrilled to have the video
So yeah, you want a video with you talking to star wars character? You know what?
Oh, sorry, I I say this that I don't like I don't like talking to the characters, but I was up at universal
recently
with with a friend buzz buzz and I did we did interact with uh,
Juice and I told him to have a gross day
I mean that's
I'm saying that I don't think he heard me
This is this is a larger maybe discussion about performers in parks
But I do think it's sometimes performer specific as well if I feel like engaging
Because some performers you go, this is a little too much or like I don't want to deal with this
But sometimes a person there or a ride operator impresses me so much. I want to engage with them
It depends you can win me over even if i'm sort of not feeling social or feeling like I need to perform or something
But if you have a bit or something that I like like we were just on guardians
It was the uh, it was the halloween overlay monsters after dark monsters after dark and a guy
Usually people are okay on that ride
They don't have fun bits, but this guy did a bit and the whole premise of the ride is that the monsters are out
Everything is going to shit
And like you just got to get up there get Groot and get down
But like be careful because monsters are gonna eat you this guy had a full bit
He had developed where he was a monster that escaped and stole someone's clothes
And like he was doing the whole thing. I loved it. I was like this guy's great
I went on it once and a guy was doing a different bit where he was like clearly in a daze. He's like
Uh, this isn't normally my job. Uh stuff is just kind of weird right now
I'm a janitor like he seemed really confused
That's kind of fun
I like kind of like that turns around and his shirt has a giant hole with burn marks on the back
And I was like, wow, they let them have some
Fun with this but this I wasn't like going back and forth with this guy
I was just but I was like more willing to be like, yeah and like I respond like
Excitedly responding to him. So I do feel like in any different parts of the park depending on what the performer's doing
I'm more willing to like go up to them or i'm more willing to banter
I think it'll be interesting to see how they incorporate like immersive theater kind of techniques while also making it
Palatable for a general audience and also doing it with like the biggest crowd influx
Maybe in theme park history for the immersive stuff
We should have a friend of the show and regular guest
Eva anderson on to give us a perspective of the immersive thing because that is also like you should be consulting on
The world or that um, what's it called in utah that the void people are making ever oh, yeah
Oh, I can't remember. I know what you're talking about. It's not everlane. That's not everlane. That's where you go for great quality
Everwood or something? I don't know
Um, and we get taught we there's more stuff to get to so we'll wrap up the star wars part
But there's the biggest thing we haven't even talked about especially for you
Of course is to see your old friend again your favorite character in fiction
Yeah, and I I think I dropped it in an episode a little while back
But this according to jim hill paul rubens is back as rex
Or at least they asked him which is a weird piece of news to give if it's not a done deal
But oh hopefully fingers crossed and yeah, oh any now. Yes, you're right all
Rules out the window if I can talk to rex for a while if rex will respond to you or something like
Yeah, I mean that would be the dream
Yeah, I mean probably he's just gonna be like a sunny eclipse style thing where he has a kind of a thing
Like a track I think so so I will like
Lay i'll just go home and while i'm falling asleep imagine the moment where he's like, I think you're cool scott. Yeah
I don't I will say though the mr
Potato i've never seen any i've never I guess looked it up even the mr
Potato head at the toy story ride. It does talk to you. Yeah, they're like customized
So there are specific things there seems like an area of these things where they can sort of tailor it to who?
Uh is in front of them, right?
But it's not yes not asking about your name or your profession
So maybe it's he's gonna say you're a cool guy, but you will still not get that scott. He won't say scott
Yeah, but he might say you're a cool
I'll film a bunch of video of him and edit all the sound bites when I can find two specific words that can form scott
Or i'll just pull it out of you know, if he said butterscotch and I could just pull scott out of that
Evermore park evermore park in utah. Sorry. It took me so long to hold that void
Companies vr. Yes, but it's not vr. It's not vr. It's like a fully immersive you interact with people
There's no rides and their sets
No, I think it's more like storytelling and an immersive play a friend of the show
Todd martin's risk wrote a big thing in the la times about it
Sorry, we'll cut this up but uh, I was you were doing a little bit of that last time
I forgot to tell you can you hear it? I can hear you. Okay. Shit. Sorry. It's okay. Oh, sorry. I'll cut that out. Yeah
Anyway, it looks very cool out there and also the voids
Rnd
Department is out there. So please have us out. We'd love to check it out. We would like to come out. Thank you
um speak okay, so
We we I would love to go there. Um, but speaking of another place i've never been
So i'm going to talk about a thing very brief, maybe not briefly, um, we've never been to dollywood
But dollywood is opening an expansion. Ah in 2019. Okay
And it is called wildwood grove. Uh-huh and it's like a pretty big expansion in the dollywood
In relation to the other like the size of the park I should say
Um, and it's got like it's very are you guys familiar with this a little bit or no?
Um, I not I saw a little it's like very colorful a lot of lights
Uh, there's a ride called the black bear trail where you it's a very kid ride where you ride on the back of a black bear
That's pretty good
sycamore swing which is basically just a swing ride
Uh like that big like a ship that goes up and down frog and fireflies, which is a kid ride
The mad mockingbird which is again a kid ride where you're right. It's a lot of animals
You're riding on a lot of animals, which is nice
A dragon flyer, which looks like a little bit of a coaster
But the whole thing is it's gonna have like very a lot of lights. It'll be very cool at night
What i'm extra excited about is
The new characters being introduced
Oh, there are three new characters. Oh boy. There's not a ton on them, but we kind of like that better
I feel like yes leave it as a mystery. You have to go over there in person to figure it out. So
meet franklin frog
What a person what a personality this happy inhabitant has
Playful and jolly this guy is more personality than your average amphibian
He likes crowds and is more than happy to demonstrate his riveting skills
So this thing mentions twice how good of a personality but then is not that specific about his personality is he has a lot of personality
Yeah, so they have to come back adventure and he's a real foodie and he loves content
Oh, he loves content
Uh, this is benjamin bear benjamin bear gives the warmest friendliest cuddly hugs in all the land
His happy demeanor to lead with in this modern day and age fair enough. He's gonna get me, dude
Uh, his happy demeanor is evident in his hugs. No wonder there's just not a more genuine bear in all the forest
Huh shots fired and all the other bears, yeah disingenuous bears, but no he's the most genuine bear again
This kind of just talks about his hugs twice and then he's genuine
And then the last two characters are flit and flutter
Uh, wait now are they bugs? They are like fairies. I think
In a land inhabited by hundreds of rainbow god damn it butterflies flit and flutter are ambassadors of beauty and grace as they make their way around
Wildwood grove wow you angrily deal with the flash site of wildwood grove
The famous catchphrase god damn it
That is dolly would not be happy with me cursing in the middle of this
One thing I don't put up with is wearing. Yeah, don't like swears. She don't like swears
Anyway, we were invited to a press conference for this announcement last year last year conference
Yeah, but they didn't realize that we were not in pigeon forage
We'd love to see pigeon forage
So i'm saying though that when wildwood opens I maybe I email again and we see if we can go meet
Uh benjamin bear and get one of his trademark hugs because you know where we can first hug damn it
I don't want some run of the mill. Yeah, the the 700th hug. I'm number one
And you know where we could stay in pigeon forage. I do margaretville hotel
So i've never been to speaking of things we've never been to I think this is interesting
We haven't really addressed lego land that much. I think it's come up on the show, but i've never been to either of them
There's one in southern california
And then there's one in florida and there's a few others around the globe
In florida, they are opening a full lego movie land with three new attractions and
Uh, I believe it is a re theming of of an existing land
But they they are new rides and I think it's notable to point out because it is like
Oh, this is a brand new land based off like a very successful box office hit with a sequel on the way
So i'm curious to see how that works out. I've heard people with little kids too
Tend to gravitate towards lego land. I think it's very affordable and very very fun for kids
Someone's just telling me they're like you gotta go to lego land. I was like, oh, okay
So people I feel like people speak highly of it. Do you know the rides or no? Uh, no
Okay, I do not. Uh, I I read about they're out there at theme park insider
I think has a rundown of them. They have hotels too. They have like lego themed hotels that look very cool
Sure neat. Um, that sounds good. And yeah, lego movies are pretty big franchise to have rides based on so that'll be
There's lego. Yeah, is lego batman involved or is that too?
No, I don't think I think it's mostly the main characters because I like the fun. I like I like that movie
Okay, but I like that
I like that
Oh, yeah, yeah, we saw it together and we were like, oh we want it more from the characters. Yeah
Well, if this can turn into a review of the lego movie then yes, I wanted to like I don't know why
harry potter characters show up and then they're like take over and like
Godzilla and non-batman characters when we get all the fun villains at the start, but anyway
Well, you've got a similar thing going on in the I I have recently been dissatisfied by the film ralph breaks the internet
Oh, I know you see I understand
the
Getting all the princesses together sure got it
but in the internet the
Princesses are in the internet and they're literally hits a point where like ralph's like swinging around a pinterest pin
And then all the princesses like rescue him in the internet
It is an internet problem and the princesses have to solve things are getting real people are real confused these days
Yeah, I also I mean that first like one of the first preview images where it's like they're in
What looks like a train station or something and there's all the different portals to like marvel pixar
And i'm like that's not that that's feels more dystopian than fun to me the way you have released it as like
Look at this. This is what we're leading with and it's like, oh, I don't know
Is that still in the movie?
What when they go to like the portals of the internet like the crossroads of the internet and they see marvel and star wars and stuff
Oh, yeah. Yeah
Happens like you like go down a hallway and there's a stormtrooper and there's yeah grumpy
Like yeah
finally
The general idea of stormtroopers and grumpy meat sort of not like one like passes by the other right the promise of all of that
Is so much greater than what probably ends up happening. Yeah, and it all happens so fast and also it's all predicated on
The the website excuse is that it's all promoting something called. Oh my disney.com
Which i'm a we do
We were theme park podcasters for hours a week. I've never heard of oh my disney.com
Hey, I guess hey it works now i'm talking about it. Yeah, I know about it
Honestly, if they had just said it's all because of disney plus or whatever, which is another
If the movie was the reveal of the streaming service that makes more sense to me
I think the problem with this and one thing that
the problem with this seems like it's it gets
An issue it's something wrong with what was good about the first movie, which the movie was specifically
Just video games and all of the characters from the video games interact and look they got sonic and they got
the street fighter people like yeah, the internet one it's
encompasses all
things
And so much and the internet at the bat present is a terrifying hellscape dark place
I mean, I'm concerned just the phrase the disney princess is on the internet. I'm like, oh those princesses aren't gonna
Google
Don't look at john laster's computer
I yeah
Yeah, I was at I probably said this before at d23 and I was watching their movie panel
Which is always like three hours long and it is fun because I like as you know
I like being in a big room with a bunch of people who are excited about stuff
So when i'm in the room
I texted everyone excitedly when they revealed rex was going to be in star wars land
To everyone in this room got a text from me. I think and it was every one of the room went nuts
As if like the rolling stones in 1972 are taking the stage
They were like and a friend will be joining us again in star wars land
It's rex and everyone went nuts and i'm like, this is great. Yep. I would have looked good thing. I wasn't there
I would have lost my voice. Yeah, you'd like penal mania for me
Rushed the stage and passed out
Smelling salt scott here
But we they were showing movie stuff and like
Boring movie stuff. There was that chris pine boat movie that no one but the people were still cheering and applauding happy to see chris pine
and then ralph breaks the internet and they show the scene with oh my disney and marvel and star wars and you could
Feel in the room that everyone was like
It's a bit
Crasse, okay
And then the princess scene which doesn't make any sense in the context
But then that played well and the audience then was won over and loved because it is fun
To see all the princesses together. Yeah, and it's like oh that just make that movie. What the hell is it doing in this weird movie?
Like this is fun. I get it
But you know what else is weird is that a lot of they frame the oh my disney thing as essentially
That's a disney fan site. So the the setting of all the disney stuff is essentially like a comic con hall
So you're in a convention center watching a film about watching a scene about a convention center about disney fandom
It's really i'm interested to see well if it's different though, because I don't I wonder
You know, that's weird. That's a weird. Yeah, like feedback loop. This is like a
second beat of a comedy a second beat of a sketch you're talking like
Where it doesn't line up a lot
Where stuff doesn't work like a sequel to a comedy movie and it's like well now
They don't work at walmart anymore
Now they all work at a water park and you get to see the characters with these funny traits
Do this thing and it's like oh kind of missed the mark. I like the first place that being said this was an
Unbelievably successful film. So I maybe i'm in the wrong. However, I did watch it with an audience
That was deadly silent except for when miranda singh showed up and that was rolling stones
Seriously giant reaction
but um, you know what let me let me shift things over to a
Super exciting area of ip we've been talking about kind of off the beaten path parks
uh, and in 2019
over in hershey, pennsylvania
there will be
Uh a thrilling new attraction with you know, we've complained about some of these what some of these rides are called
It'd be impossible to complain about the ride title
Reese's cup fusion
One word cup fusion cup fusion now if you recall on the hershey park episode with evan susser
we
Talked about a ride. Uh, uh, yeah, it's a ride called a Reese's extreme cup challenge
Which is kind of a shooting gallery buzz lightyear style ride, but that's like a extreme sports
competition kind of in like the the simpsons poochy
view of how to be cool for
Uh youths today and it seemed a little like odd and out of date though fun
I would love to go on that ride, but it's I didn't realize it's being uh,
Replaced by another it seems like probably more of an overlay
But the uh, this this new ride is called Reese's cup fusion and Reese's cup fusion challenges you
Let me take a breath here
Reese's cup fusion challenges you to protect the crystal cup
That gathers the world's love for chocolate and peanut butter and uses it to power the Reese's factory
so
We're not only halfway through the description. There is a crystal cup and the job of the cup is to gather chocolate love
in addition to this
Hershey park is getting a 150 million dollar new entryway called chocolate town
Not be confused with chocolate world, which is next door. I'll let it slide
It's a new arrival
Front gate 15th coaster restaurant bar patio ice cream parlor and confectionary scratch kitchen
I think that's where they built, you know, either they make chocolate from scratch or you make it a
2200 square foot starbucks store
Uh the largest kettle cord location at Hershey park a one-of-a-kind kisses fountain a new
Home for the hundred-year-old carousel and a flagship store
So they're redoing the entire entryway to the park
And a new coaster and this new thing so big year for well, you're coming in hot like out of nowhere
Hershey park having a mega year. Well, can I go right back to the ride real quick?
Yes, uh the cup that stores love for chocolate, is that right? Yeah, this is the world's gathers
Yeah, so I you know, all I have to go off of is this sentence, but I guess like
Um, I don't know. I mean they hear us on this podcast
Talking about treats and desserts and such and I guess that energy
In a monstropolis type energy gathering situation somehow
it comes out of our mouths or stomachs and
Uh is filtered and flies through the air all the way to pennsylvania
And it's all it all is stored in a cup and it powers
It um, yes the Reese's factory is not powered by electricity
Uh, it is powered by hand chocolate love chocolate and peanut butter love
Yeah, which is which great by the way because a lot of bad global warming reports recently
We need to find alternative energy and for sure the love of peanut butter and chocolate is fantastic
And it's an endlessly renewable obviously right if jason were to go toward this thing
Would it overheat and the whole place blow up because it couldn't store that much love for peanut butter and crystal is melting
Yeah
The cup is losing its shape. You get it. You understand now everything makes sense
There's a crystal cup and if jason walked up to it it would shake and shatter because
His love is too strong his love is the strongest on all in earth of all earthlings
He loves chocolate and peanut butter the most if that's probably true
I mean that's that might be true
I mean in the way that we're saying that like some of the logic is off and ralph breaks the internet the the
Logic behind this the game of the chocolate crystal is perfect and needs no more the crystal cup the crystal cup crystal cup
So you're protecting it on the ride you're protecting it
The I the only say the rest of the plot the crystal cup is under attack
I can't even get through that sentence. I'm so choked up
Yeah, these bastards are trying to take the cup in their own hands. The league of misfit candy. Is that right?
That's right. They're all they are also candy but like I guess
Weird they're bad. What's the thing from uh, uh voodoo donuts the the the box of uh, oh a bucket of misshapen
They're like a bucket of misshapen. They're all weird and they are not chocolate or peanut butter
Which is the only thing that the only things that Reese's traffics in well
Yeah, I first off I think the bucket of misshapen are benevolent creatures
but I could see the the
the enemies being like
Mary janes or burnt peanuts or circus pete like these sort of uh candies like oh
I don't want this if you go trick or treating they're like they're weird like novelty flavors that taste taste like poop or like, you know
Black licorice with chili spice. Yeah, they're they're like nightmare flavors
Maybe they should be like call them like bad and plentees like if there's some bad and plenty
You gotta watch out for mean and plentees
Mike and spike he's mean
There are a couple heavies
I would think there would be like grandma candy like wrapped
Boring sort of wrapped candies in a big dish or something. Oh that are kind of like
Sedate and like not is they're they're all time. Is this sure?
What is the flavor even they've been in there forever? They're 30 years old
They're like where there's a particular type of like chalky mint andy's mints. Oh, maybe yeah
Don't you say a thing about andy's mints?
He loves I do like andy well, I think i'm probably thinking something worse than what you're talking about
There's like if you leave them for a while. I see. Yeah, okay
Well, it's some bad grandma candy. They're bitter about having been trapped in a in a
Vase for so long and they want in on that rhesus factory
They want the cups power for themselves. So along the way you must zap the league of misfit candy members and save the factory
Which I like that that's good jason getting there and being like
military precision
Super driven like yelling at other people for not firing enough
Oh 11 year old jason would have been all in on that and also 33 year old jason is all in on that
Like slapping your dad in the face for not
Not taking it seriously if it didn't go well, though. I think you'd be like everyone out of the car
I'm doing this alone
I'll take care of all of these taking all the guns operating them with his toes when I get back
You're all being court marshalled perfect score
Let's hope that the crystal cup is never under siege again so that you sorry
Sex of shit don't have to be part of this army again
You have to wear your general's outfit too. Yeah on the ride. This is I can't believe how much
Came from two sentences about this
This is this is like meaty there's a there's a thick chocolate center to this little paragraph about Reese's cup fusion
Wow, maybe this is my new
VIP of the year. This is you like referring to
Mr. Toad is the underground brian eno of right? This is this is the cool. This is the eno of 2019
Sure, yeah new and experimental and using bizarre words that don't roll off the tongue at all lots of exciting things going on in
Pennsylvania also getting the first branded cartoon network hotel right outside of dutch wonderland. This is a smaller
Kid-friendly theme park not too far from Hershey
Yeah, it's an interesting spot for them to test out a cart, you know adventure time powerpuff girl cartoon network themed
Hotel, but certainly there is
I'm curious to see how that goes defunct land recently had a
an episode about the
Long-gone
Nickelodeon themed hotel in Orlando, which was interesting terribly unpleasant
Yeah, it seemed like it had some popularity
But then like a lot of these things you got to keep them updated
And if you're not doing that people kind of gravitate away from it. I know it's kind of
off of
Cartoon network, but still every restaurant in that place better be packed with szechuan sauce
They're in a lot of trouble. Well, it's not adult swim. No, no, sure after dark, but they're related. Oh, yes power
Right. There you go past 10 o'clock, right then szechuan sauce comes out
Of szechuan sauce. Mm-hmm. Jesus the police department is gonna hate that
Hotels gonna constantly be getting swatted by people not getting their szechuan sauce
Overrun is gonna be closed in two months. Yeah
What else do we got? Hey right here back in California?
And at at our
increasingly beloved knots
We are getting an overlay of the the rapids ride
It is now going to be calico river rapids and they're going to be
Animatronics on this thing is going to be a big old big foot
I'm really excited about this show scenes rapids with show scenes show scenes and tying it into the
mythology of everything else
Which is what i'm very excited about too. Yeah
Uh, yeah, so because now it's calico. There's a calico mine already there, but now it's calico rapids
So like that's all going to be in some big story universe. They're building as well, which is fantastic
And I love those rides and the animatronics are going to be done by garner holt who did all the animatronics for those other
There for the refurbs of uh those places. So it's going to be like a I i'm so excited those two I have
Those knots dark rides i'm so fond of yeah that there's essentially going to be a third
now, uh, and it's also real, you know ups the game over at
Grizzly river rapids at california venture, which is fine
But there's not much going on theming wise and now you got a big foot to grapple with over at knots step it up dca
Grizzly river run
What grizzly river run? It's not rapids. It's a run grizzly river run
Yeah, I would have had to double check that
Somebody just told me that there is a rapid ride. No. No, wait, there's a there's bare animatronics on a ride
in
Maybe it's not a rapid ride. Maybe it's like they're it's like big thunder in hong kong. Yes. Yeah. Yeah
There's a there's a crazy animatronic on that thing. Yeah. Yeah. Well, maybe i'll save it for that
It looks almost exactly like the one we have except with a big crazy. Yeah
Discovered that interesting that is yeah, because it's called something
It's a different kind of coaster different design sort of their their equivalent to big thunder in hong kong is very different
So different episode not on the not discussed on the big thunder one
What I think on on our live episode tony baxter talked about how he and his buddies just sit around and talk about how to fix knots
And I feel like maybe the solution is slowly re theming all the rides to tie it into
A one narrative or into a similar narrative one big old story just one year to like each year you re theme like
What's that horse ride where you're on a horse?
A pony express pony express. It's calico pony express now
Because they that ghost town alive interactive thing has been very successful for them, too
Um, and I believe that ties into the calico mythology
Yeah, the calico the calico extended universe. I love that. I'm in yeah
In general what i'm looking for in 2019. There's not a lot of details, but i'm looking forward to haunts in 2019
I'm looking forward to mazes. I'm looking forward to scare actors. I'm looking i'm gonna do horror nights
I'm gonna do not scary again
And we'll see what else i'm excited about that because that will result in episodes where I
Do no research and I just listen to you. That's true. That sounds great
So I ain't going i'm going on after haunt jason, what do you can you declare right now?
Will you go with me to haunts or will you not?
I'm like 50 50 right now. So you're not even you won't even commit to partial like going to a couple
But I thought even 50 50 on even if i'm going or not, uh, i'm definitely not going all in like you
I think I would check out a little more. I think i'm just gonna go a little gradually a little exposure therapy for me
So, uh, what do you think you would start with? What do you think?
Would you do horror nights or would you want to go back to knots and do half the mazes?
A little more of knots. Okay. I think horror nights is a bit pricey for my taste
Uh, okay now I see
Now I see what the real problem is here. You're scared of the money. Yeah, I don't know. I'm also
Dollars jumping out of your pocket
You know what I didn't do this year I
Was built right next to boney island and has been there a lot longer the ghost train
Which I think is a more whimsical. Oh, sure sort of thing, but also a little more sinister
So I'm curious about that
In terms of like big e tickets that we haven't addressed
There's a new harry potter roller coaster coming and I think for my money. I mean, i'm very excited about the star wars
stuff coming but i'm a little that's tempered by the uh,
Crowd predictions like and nervousness about the infrastructure holding out. Yeah, but this harry potter coaster
Looks like it could be incredible scott. I think I alluded to this on another show
This isn't just a launch coaster. This is a multi launch coaster
Oh boy what they're rivering about that this thing might launch you throughout the coaster, huh?
and is is
Seems to be on trend with the predictions of what are coming like this is a coaster
But there are multiple show scenes. Uh, so you'll stop is the rumor. You'll stop. Oh
And then interesting and then you'll shoot
Yeah, sounds cool. Yeah, that's that cool. I'm you know, i'm getting over. I think I have this is a fun little like
achievement if i've had I had I not been put into a corner by y'all and matt rogers and I felt like I had to
Overcome and I like I don't know. I think it truly as I've said before I think it was like a
Like a breathing issue and Aaron and Aaron pointed out
on
In credit coaster, I I conquered it. I did it but even doing it a second time. I was
Re-nervous. I was nervous again, and she said you know what open your eyes
I think when you close your eyes, you are imagining worse than is happening, right and potentially getting more disoriented
Keep those eyes open. I breathe. I think it was a physical issue
And i've uh, I figured it out. So I don't know. I'm more i'm more launched down at this point
I like I always have liked the launches but I went on
Rock and roller coaster last march like two or three times
And the third time I do feel like my body fully got used to it and got comfortable on it again
So I like I felt the transition my body was making and I liked it all the times
But the third time it was like pure joy as opposed to the first time which was fun
But I think I was like a little stiff a little whatever so like
I do think there is a lot of like your body being comfortable for some of these things
That's what I used to really like about the original version of the incredible hulk coaster is that there's dialogue and you can kind of know
What's coming when the dialogue is coming?
We have to figure out what the deal is and why we both had headaches on the new incredible hulk coaster
Yeah, because in theory it should be smoother. It should be much smoother. It's not I am a raise too many gamma rays
I also have not last time there's like hardly any story now. So that's kind of you think that's why you had a story
Your brain was an occupier disappointment
Uh, just for a personal thing scott. Do you have do you think it's possible to
Break mission breakout by the end of the year. Do you think that's even on the horizon?
I think it's a different thing
Uh, and erin was even honest with me. I was like feeling a little like braver and like maybe should I and she was like this is
This is this is a step above uh incredible coaster
uh, yeah, I think like I get pleasure out of the like once i'm past the launch and like
Uh, and if I can deal with the bigger drops I get pleasure out of all of it
I don't think when the one time I did a tower terror. I don't think I enjoyed any aspect of it
I just didn't like it the only reason i'm so pushy about it specifically and i've said this before it is
Of sensations on any of these thrill rides. It is my favorite sensation
On the roller coaster. I still get in places. I get tense or sometimes if the loop my head hurts a little bit or my
Stomach can't quite deal with it. I've gotten to the point now where the tower the towers it's pure fun for me
And like it doesn't like i'm not sore. I don't hurt like it's just so great
So, I don't know. Maybe i'm just different but I don't know. What do you do
Let me ask you. Do you like the sensation of a roller coaster more than you like the tower of terror?
oh
Um, or what what's your feeling? I don't know, you know, I don't really have a fear of heights
I do you do. Um, I think tower terror, especially florida
Yeah, I mean I just I like the dropping
I like hearing everyone screaming. I like the sensations and I like I I laugh through a lot of it. Yes
Uh, I just think it's delightful, but I do think I mean i'm not saying
Don't do it because i'm saying and have a panic attack and then i'm responsible but yeah
But I do think that's probably another like tense
Because I think initially I will say I think the tower the mission breakout will be easier because it's a launch
Oh sure as opposed to the other thing
So you won't even have as much time to tense up because I think that's you know, I I hated that on
Malabumer I hate
I did yes
To impress a girlfriend
Realized this in 2005. No, I did tower terror and
Oh, well, I did all of it but malabumers on outside
Yes, that that bothered me that that was my least favorite thing i've ever been
I've never been on one of the outdoor ones like that and I would have I would flip out on that
Okay, neither of you ever done doctor dooms fear fall. No, what i'll do you don't know about the fear juice
I know about the fear juice, but and I will look
He needs it to power his machine if we go in 2019
I will do it with you
All right
I don't want to do it and I think that is for sure a different thing
Than being inside feeling jackson five playing and you're in a room
I would flip out if I shot up on the malabomer for sure. Sure. Sure
Yeah, pretty pretty like naked. Yeah, you're feeling you're falling through the sky. You fell out of a plane
We said I hate the dangling. I hate the legs dangling that bothers me
Back to the the harry potter coaster. I mean not a lot has been officially confirmed yet
but there's been enough people have pieced stuff together from like overhead pictures and uh, someone made a
emulation, uh, or what it would be in like a roller coaster simulator program
Uh, someone also I think it's orlando park stop. This is a very funny thing over the summer
They kind of like connected all the dots and they put up a blog post end video saying like well from what we all know
And what the like?
Physical landscape is like this is probably what the coaster was and then apparently they got
Contacted by universal and said who leaked all this to you and they said no one leaked it
We just connected what was out there publicly and you have kind of de facto confirmed by confronting us
so, uh, yeah, uh, I'm still suspicious they somebody could have leaked someone could have leaked because it was
Very like they really seem to know
They were talking about who knows I don't know for sure
But it just but like multiple launches a backward section a drop section potentially where like the coaster drops
It's like just goes on another level or something
Set within the forbidden forest and hagrid will probably be there and some fantastical creatures
I think in terms of actual experiences. This is like might be one of the top ones coming
Yeah, that was quite a list you just gave that's all insane stuff and you gotta love like it's not this year
but uh, you know, we're we're getting mario kart stuff soon and I'd like anything where you're getting like
New things a ride is never done. Yes
pretty cool because it's such as i've said like the what the
engineering and the military grade
Technology has to go into this stuff. You're getting like these new
Experiences that uh, like shouldn't exist and can only exist because of billions of dollars being spent. It's so cool
Yeah, the rye vehicles for mario kart and for the guardians of galaxy coaster. Yep are all like multi-directional
Things where you can do a roller coaster but flip people around they're they're very actually very similar now that I think about it
So I was reading that I was a little late to recording today
I was saying because I was reading about patent applications and apparently the difference
So disney has filed a patent application for a roller coaster
ride
That looks very similar to gringotts and they're like, oh what's the difference? Well with gringotts the way they rotate the cars
Like it can only be rotated like in that area because the ride itself
The vehicle is pulling power from like charging stations in that area disney's patent
would be
Uh, the the power is coming from an on-board like battery or generator, which means the cars could rotate in like
turns or tight corners that aren't possible with the current like
gringotts sort of
Technology so we could see an upgrade of that sort of thing in these
Storytelling coasters, I think was that's what bob chapec called the guardians again. We're talking about 2020
But yeah, it's a coaster that like
You could put up a lift hill
But then you could tilt the car to the left if there's like a show scene of some kind happening
I don't know how you do that if it's a screen or if it's robots
And then you could flip it back or flip it behind
So like it gives the thing such a range of motion the thing that was coolest on the mario
Well many cool things but was that you could tilt it's basically a roller coaster track
And then the car built on top of it
But you could tilt it so you could actually make it feel like you were doing jumps
Because you wouldn't be able to see the track because it was so far down
So you tilt the car up and then you'd look like you would jump over like, you know, whatever a big space
on a mario teetery
Bridge or something like ramps like you do in mario kart you essentially can do on this ride
Right, so you would yeah because you would not be able to see the track
You're not be able to see you were elevated and it would just feel like you were flying spin it like spin out
As if someone wants to shell at you. Yeah, that's right. Oh, yeah, that's totally that pivot point
Or if you hate a banana peel like right. I mean i'm sure i'm i guess i'm not sure but
It remains to be seen how many cars can be on the track at once for mario kart
um, and then
But it's like if it was truly possible to have it be so
Flexible that with like augmented reality you could grab a shell and throw it and you could make cars spin out in real time
Oh, I mean, I don't know that they can do that, but i'm sure that was in a blue sky at some point
I think mario kart is a real like I don't want to say dark horse. That's a weird
Phrase because it's a big ride that's meant to be good
But I think it could sneak up in terms of and take over some Disney stuff for the best ride that exists currently
Yeah from there's a leaked picture of that from a year or two ago
um, and if it's if it's like that if it looks like the track that was laid out in this picture like it's
I can't imagine you wouldn't I won't want to like live in there
Yeah, guys, isn't it cool being part of like a we truly are in like one of the golden ages of this stuff
Yes, yeah
many times I feel like and we kind of it's it's fun to be an adult and be like
Remembering the stuff from our childhoods, which was a golden age
Right, and then it was it's sort of in and out whether theme parks were doing a lot or good
Through up until now and now we clearly are in one of the best runs there's ever been. Yeah, I mean uh,
The patents that universal filed a patent recently universal filed a bunch of patents one of them similar to the
roller coasters that rotate for show scenes that are
Popular is seemingly getting popular
Was like a ray a log ride or raft ride where you would have you could rotate?
The raft for show scenes
So imagine the Jurassic and not on a track because the pirates ride in shanghai does rotate to little show sequences
That's got a track underneath it. This would use obstacles like in a rapids and presumably water direction to
rotate the boat
to show scene so even if like none of this stuff comes to pass and like
This patent is exactly 100 with the ride would be even using elements of this
In like next-gen rides. It could be incredible. There's rumors
of a full jungle book
Like thing over in world showcase or animal kingdom like it could be either one but like a full using the shanghai pirates
um
Uh technology for like boats that flip around and can change and stuff
But like a full like jungle like cgi jungle book thing which sounds awesome. Geez and all this on top of
a patent being filed to have to make a crystal cup that is power that is
Gathers the world's love for chocolate and peanut butter
Well, you don't need to file a patent to love
You just do it you just feel it
That's true, uh, i'll say that uh past looking past 2019
Disney in 2020 and 2021 has stuff like the guardians of galaxy coaster and epcot the ratatouille ride
Which coming to epcot and the tron coaster coming in magic kingdom, uh, which in my head I was like
Some of these are they've already built these in other parks
Why is it taking so long the answer being the 50th anniversary of disney world is coming up?
So they're clearly trying to stack the decks for that. Yeah. Yeah
I was just gonna add about that guardians coaster at epcot that I think what did he say you can fit three spaceships earth
Spaceship earths inside the building or something or is it more like fights like a huge building
So like the roller coaster is getting big. Yeah
Um, yeah, there's a lot of a lot of crazy stuff and then what's good about it the future is that
Uh, and this is only for theme parks not in the future in general
That's all bad. But theme park future good, uh is that universal seems very aggressive, especially in orlando
Which is going to hopefully keep this arms race going
Yeah for a little while they have to compete with island h2o live water park
Right and in general sunset walk and the entire margaritaville establishment this could run universal into the ground
Two water parks in orlando with rfid based wristbands that only kind of work. Can you imagine?
Yeah, everyone's on the run golden age, uh, uh, we're in it. Well, we're very excited
It's gonna be a great 2019 and hopefully for this podcast as well
Uh, we have some we have some fun ideas already. I feel like of stuff that's got like more
More theme months and more more garbage. Hopefully we get to rent another live show. I have like a lot of
Big ideas that I don't know if they'll come to fruition, but at least if a couple of them do
That'll be fun. We won't say what those are but there'll be some live shows. There'll be some you know new stuff
Oh, yeah fun stuff behind the second gate the stuff for the patreon episodes
Yeah, um
and remember that our
Podcasts and our microphones are powered by your love
So we need to hear it. We need your emails podcast the right gmail
We need your itunes reviews those really spike those really make the crystal cup
That's in the center of the room while we record the podcast go nuts
Uh, and yes, but unlike
Hershey's chocolate, which we know is powered by the crystal cup
No one has any idea how the itunes charts works. They are a mystery and perplexing
And no way to tame them who knew there were this many video game podcasts coded as games and hobbies
Now you're bitter at the other. Yeah, you're mad about that. I'm just more confused
Uh, yeah, well, uh, we need maybe we need to be like the league of misfit candy and uh,
You know see if we if they have crystal cups that are somehow gaming the system
We got to take them and then we got more crystal cups and we're straight up to the top of the charts
Yeah, yeah, um, so you can help us in this endeavor also by tweeting at us or going to uh,
Our instagram or subscribing to our patreon podcast the ride.com. Uh, sorry. Sorry. No, no, no
patreon.com
Podcast the ride no colon and uh, so uh, yeah, that's it you survived podcast the ride
It's gonna be great 2019 gang. Happy new year. Happy new year everyone. Yay
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by mike carlson jason sharridan scott gairdner
Brett boham joe cilio and alex ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
And subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on facebook