FOREVER!
Warning, if the following podcast stops working,
switch it to beam mode and just flash some lights at it.
Then buckle up for fawning over Joe Roady,
multiple instances of travel channel voice.
And just when you think it's over,
the episode plummets backwards into a tangent
about a shady deep cable show.
This is Expedition Everest on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show hosted by three men
who fear and respect the power of the yeti.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined by Mike Carlson.
Yep, I respect him.
And Scott Gertner.
Very much right, and you won't hear any disrespects
in this episode.
Why do I assume the yeti is a male?
Do we know what the gender of the yeti is?
You know, I've read a lot about it,
getting ready for this.
I don't think I really saw that discussed.
Yeah, it's not specifically said.
Nor the abominable snowman in the Matterhorn.
Right, that's interesting.
Yeah, I assume, but I guess that must be
maybe just the sexist thing.
Because it could be like a killer female yeti.
Or a, yeah.
Well, I don't know, based on the size of that animatronic,
if it were male, that big old thing would be dangling down
and smacking riders in the face.
Oh, good point.
So, yeah, maybe it is female.
Yeah, you're talking about a dick.
You're talking about a big yeti dick.
Unfortunately, the hog stopped working
about 10 years ago as well.
They designed it, yeah, that wasn't gonna do so much.
That was C mode, that was C mode.
The dick comes out. D mode.
I was gonna say D mode.
I was just adjusting the levels, and I was like,
I got that D mode joke geared up, and then Scott did it.
But yeah.
Yeah, all set.
Sorry, grandmothers and mothers,
it's a little something we don't get to do a lot.
But we're still not considering this disrespect.
We won't go into D mode in terms of disrespect
of the almighty yeti.
No, we also fear and respect the almighty yeti's hog.
The damage it could do.
We're talking Expedition Everest today.
Yes.
The E-ticket roller coaster attraction at Animal Kingdom,
and I believe, I said this at our text messages,
our first Animal Kingdom attraction.
Yeah, that is weird.
Is what made me go immediately, yes, we need to do it.
I felt a lot of guilt.
What have we been doing?
How have we not represented this park
in so many weeks and weeks and weeks of shows?
Well, I think that's fitting,
because I feel like Animal Kingdom
kind of often much maligned.
So like, I don't wanna say unfairly maligned.
I agree.
I don't wanna say the redheaded stepchild,
but I think it got a lot of flack when it first opened
of like, not enough rides here.
There's not enough rides.
Well, I don't think that's unjustified,
and you're allowed to make that.
I did feel that when I went with my family
whenever it was open.
I guess we went in 99.
I just remember feeling like not enough to do,
too much McDonald's and not enough shade.
Well, yeah.
So the McDonald's partnership is very bizarre,
and we could probably do a whole episode about that,
or about Disney's various odd corporate partnerships.
But the shade, that I think has been rectified
by the passage of time, by trees growing.
Yeah, and that's a complaint you would've made
about Disneyland in 1955.
And California Adventure got that a lot.
They were like, why are these redwood trees so tiny?
And it's like, well,
because you don't just get a giant redwood tree.
You gotta let it grow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was just gonna say for like a kid,
because I think I had a similar feeling.
I was very excited about it.
I didn't dislike it or anything,
but when I went as a kid, it was very much like,
well, where are the rides?
And I didn't quite get it.
But I think if I had first appreciated it as like,
a 34 year old man who likes to sit around these places
as much as go on a ride,
I think I would've appreciated it
for its theming and everything.
But I get it why, if you're going there,
because you're like, I wanna go on some rides.
And then you like, there's like a safari,
and there's seeing animals, and what is dinosaurs?
But I mean, like when opening day especially,
it's like, isn't Countdown to Extinction
the biggest thrill ride,
the most exciting ride they have there is that one?
I think that was the thrill ride,
and Expedition Everest was like
the big thrill ride expansion sort of thing.
But yeah, I think one of the most thoughtfully designed
parks out there, I just think like you run into,
people have expectations now when they go to these places.
Yeah, well and I think it was,
I find in general the late 90s
to be an unpleasant time in the Disney parks,
with things like the Too Much McDonald's,
Weird Little Cheapo,
like I felt like they were cheapening out in some areas.
It was not, the golden era of the early 90s
was starting to decay a little bit,
and I cannot but wonder if Animal Kingdom
would have come out of the gate stronger
with more early 90s spending.
Oh yeah, well there's the whole,
And this is- Beastly.
Yeah, that's too much to talk,
we'll do that another episode,
but in case you didn't know,
there was going to be a whole thing,
a whole different fantasy area of fantasy animals,
and that had I think a crazy roller coaster
that went through a castle and dragons,
and there's a whole thing which,
this blows my mind, there was gonna be a maze
where you were gonna find I think a unicorn,
I believe, and you were gonna meet
a bunch of mythical creatures in the maze,
so you'd come over and I don't know what else
is a mythical centaur or something or whatever.
The minotaur I believe,
traditionally guards the mazes.
And then you would meet all these different characters,
and then when you got to the unicorn,
the unicorn would talk to you
using vibrations in the floor.
The idea was that it would be mentally,
like telepathically communicating with you,
this is how I understand it at least,
and they were gonna do it by turning the voice down so low
that you would feel what the thing was saying
and not hearing it,
so you would feel a vibration of like,
thank you for finding me.
So the idea was to make it feel like it was in your head.
It feels like it might have been unpleasant.
But yeah.
Yeah, this creeps me out.
This is like sex with dolphins.
But, well sure.
This is some weird vibrations and moods.
Everyone would have gotten very horny from the vibration.
Yeah, I think low frequency sounds
can sometimes drive people insane too,
like if I understand it.
Yeah, I mean, they're Imagineers.
I'm sure they had a cool way to do it
and it would have blown us away.
But there was a whole bunch,
there was going to be an area,
I think they probably also felt like,
well that'll be the part that has all the ride.
That'll be the exciting stuff in the rides.
This is the nature stuff that's real,
and you can see real animals.
And now here's our Disney fun fantastical area with.
Yeah, totally right.
That's the missing component, I think.
That was cut from the budget.
But the logic of the park is not dissimilar from Epcot.
Except in this case, it's like,
the story we're trying to tell
is the animal kingdom conservation.
And the way that Epcot is,
we're talking about the future and innovation
and also like worldwide cultures and stuff.
And when Epcot first opened,
it did have more attractions than animal kingdom,
I'm assuming, right?
That probably makes sense.
But added a lot more over the years
where it does feel more filled out now.
And certainly animal kingdom feels more filled out
with Pandora in there.
Yeah, well they've only added,
they've added three big things,
but they're big, they're big old deals.
And I haven't been in a very, very long time.
And I'm like, it's probably now at this point
the one I'm the most anxious to go to,
having not done Avatar
and having not done Expedition Everest.
I've not been on this ride.
And I'm dying to do it now.
Like having thought of, I knew it was cool,
I'm aware it was cool.
But just really thinking about it,
watching special about it, watching ride throughs,
and me being several percentage points braver now.
Ain't no launch on this one.
And I'm more increasingly okay with launches.
And it's a slower lift hill.
You're good with that.
It is not, the coaster itself is not overwhelming,
but like the magic tricks associated,
it looks intimidating by design.
Yeah, and looks very, looks very high.
It looks, I mean when it is, it gets up there.
Highest attraction, tallest attraction in Walt Disney World.
Yeah.
Six inches taller than Tower of Terror
and half a foot shorter than the requirement
to have a blinking red light on it
to alert low flying planes.
Right. Wow.
It's 200 feet is when you have to put that on.
This is apparently 199 and a half feet.
And they still, I like that they got it down to inches.
Yeah.
To just inch out Tower of Terror.
Take that Tower of Terror.
Yeah, one of my favorite things while being on it,
I've probably, because I hadn't been on it
until we went for the first time like five years ago.
I've probably now been on it six times,
I feel like six or seven times.
The best is that lift hill, not the best,
but one of the cool parts of it is that lift hill
and you just see flat Florida swamp everywhere
and then you see Tower of Terror poking up over here.
You see the Magic Kingdom poking up over here.
I've tried to see, I think I did see Universal
at a certain point, because that then.
Really? Wow.
Like the fourth time I was like,
okay, where's Universal at?
So I'm like looking and that's a far drive.
Maybe I just saw where it would be, I can't remember.
That's about 12, 13 miles north, I think.
I wanna say I kind of saw it,
but maybe that's just my memory.
But I found that to be a very fun game
of trying to find all the different peaks
in the whole theme park area.
That moment seems so incredibly dramatic and cool
and I can't wait to, I'm like,
this is such a priority for me now.
I really wanna go on there.
That too, there's no catwalks
on either side of that lift hill.
That's to me what looks very crazy.
It's just the track.
Yeah, that's great.
I've ridden this thing in the rain a couple times.
Oh my god. Lindsay and I did it
in the rippling, like pummeling rain.
And it, god, it was fun.
It was so great getting hit in the face
with rain on this thing.
I think I went on it,
because then the line got way short.
So then I think I went on it again in the rain.
I think I did that.
I remember going in 2012 on the very last day of a trip,
got up very early to make sure my bags were packed
and took the bus from Wilderness Lodge
to Animal Kingdom to ride a dinosaur and this.
Maybe just do a lap around the park
before I had to get back and eat lunch
and then get to the airport.
But I remember getting off this
and just being stunned.
That was great.
And then walking out of the park going,
and this has happened the last time I went too,
and this is the park I wish I spent more time in.
Yeah, I just realized now this is gonna be
one of the episodes where I don't think
I have much criticism.
This is one of those.
Yeah, I was thinking that.
There's not a lot of crapping on the thing,
meat on the bone, which we can do sometimes.
But I think sheer praise is nice too.
Yeah.
I think it's one of those.
The level of detail, there's so much to talk about.
Obviously.
And we've just been crapping.
We spent the earlier part of the day crapping on it.
I got shrunk the audience.
We gotta get positive, y'all.
Obviously we'll talk about the Yeti in a little bit,
but that's fine.
But yeah, as far as the ride,
it is like, it's one of those Disney rides, I think,
where it'll be up in 30 years and a kid will go
and assume it was built at the start.
They won't know when it was built.
It feels very tiny.
Big Thunder, when I was a kid,
I didn't realize Big Thunder hadn't been there
the whole time.
Yeah.
Feels like it always should have been there.
It'd be an important part of the fabric of the.
Right, even like Star Tours, I don't think I vocalized it,
but I knew that was, obviously that wasn't there
since it opened.
I knew that.
Well, it's like aesthetically different.
Nothing else in Disneyland is like that.
It's a movie and it's more angular.
Right.
It just feels modern.
But Big Thunder, yeah, it absolutely feels like
it could have been, I think the mountains in general
need to feel like they were always there.
Yes.
But even like Splash Mountain, I think I had an idea
that that was newer.
But yeah, but I feel like Everest,
if I was a kid and 30 years going on it,
I'd be like, oh, this was here.
Like, I wouldn't know.
I think that's always cool to feel like something
that truly feels like very timeless in the park.
And I think another neat aspect of it is that it feels like
this 10 times plused up version of the Matterhorn.
It all is rooted in the Matterhorn
and it feels like a tribute to it in a way.
And then we took this and took it to this level.
Because there was always question of when is the Matterhorn
ever gonna come to Disney World?
And there was talk of it going into a Swiss pavilion
in Epcot and it never came to pass.
And then this felt like,
I remember even the first time I heard about it,
it was even framed maybe a little more as like,
it's kind of an amended,
it's the Disney World version of the Matterhorn.
It's obviously so much more than that.
But it's sort of, I don't know,
it feels like a nice tribute
to this very foundational ride in the park's history.
Yeah, for sure.
And yeah, the Matterhorn, of course,
we did an episode on that, of course.
But that ride system makes the ride feel dated.
Even though some of the effects are new,
just for whatever, that ride system still makes it,
you go, this shouldn't hurt this much.
Because it was just banged together
by a bunch of grumpy guys in the 50s.
They did their best.
Yeah, a bunch of guys, they were all building
World War II planes and they're making a roller coaster.
But this is top tier technology
and stuff that no ride in the Disney park ecosystem
had ever done.
Never before this a Disney ride
that goes forward and backward, I believe.
Unless there's the Indiana Jones thing in Paris.
The small Indiana Jones coaster in Paris
briefly ran backwards for a short period of time.
But this runs forwards and backwards on the same ride
in the same experience.
And that was what set it.
I think we all watched this Travel Channel special
where we learned about the peace that makes this possible.
That it's this hulking, very special part.
So the point that we were talking about
where you can see all of the Swampland,
it rises to, your car rises to this apex,
sits up there for what feels like a while
and then comes back down the other way and goes backwards.
By the time you pass it, it has six seconds
for this hulking piece.
It's 200,000 pounds.
A 200,000 pound piece has to flip over
and turn around so that when you come back down,
you go down a different track.
Yeah, like a train when it switches tracks.
It's a full big mechanism that has to arrange.
So another thing, also as far as the weight is concerned,
one or two of the times that I did it,
that up at the top when you're stuck at the top,
that can pause for a long time.
Because if something, if a car is taking a while to load
or something, like any variable there.
So we were up there for like a minute.
Really?
Like a long time.
It feels, I mean, even when you're up there
just for the set amount of time, it feels long.
We're talking about like, at one point in this ride,
you are riding through the mountains
and you come to a point where the tracks
are like turned upward.
Like the Yeti has ripped them up
and you are at the top of a hill looking down on stuff
and you're just hanging there and it's shocking.
Like your expectations for a roller coaster,
like this is scary, this is shocking.
There's no more track.
I wish I could have a big pause like that.
If that's so, it's a new beat in a roller coaster
you'd never really see.
Absolutely.
I wish I didn't know that when I went on the first time,
but of course I had like seen videos of it,
but that does seem like such a fun surprise.
Well they were never hiding.
I mean in the Travel Channel specials,
it's in the opening credits.
But it's still like insane to experience.
And then that you go backwards and then forwards again,
like you keep switching and you're in the light,
you're in the dark.
Yeah it has and I think I've,
I don't know if I've said this,
I guess I've said this on the show.
It feels like, I feel like any ride,
I feel like it doesn't matter necessarily
about the length of the ride.
But I feel like to have like a really satisfying experience,
it has to have like three moves.
It has to have like three nice parts or moves to it
to make it feel like it's a satisfying experience.
Maybe the three is not the number.
Maybe just it's different pieces
that all feel like you've gotten a nice thing at the end.
Maybe it's not even, can you make a list
of like when this happened, this happened, this happened.
Yes, that's probably a better way to describe it.
Like in Credit Coaster, it's launch, it's loop,
it's in the really crazy drop in the middle.
Right, I think, and you had not been to Japan yet,
I think I said something similar on the Japan episode
about one of the rides and I said it was
missing a big something.
I don't know what that is.
But it felt like another thing would have made me feel
satisfied with it.
So this is one of those rides where you have
like such satisfying things and it changes it up.
The first lift hill is so cool.
The line, we'll talk about the line, the queue is awesome.
And then there's just such a variation on what it does
that even though the ride itself is actually pretty short,
I think, or is it four minutes, what is it?
I forget what the length is.
But it does seem long as far as roller coasters go.
It seems very long, but I don't think it's like super long
and I think it's because like it's sad,
like every piece is satisfying and then you feel
like you've been, you've done, there's been moves.
There's three moves on it.
There's three, now you're backwards.
Now it's this, now there's a big robot.
Now like it just, all of it adds up.
When you're also just exploring just crazy wilderness,
it takes advantage of the undeveloped nature
of a lot of the Disney World property
and it reminds me of the Beast at Kings Island,
which I've talked about where you're like,
I feel like far away from the park.
I'm just going around random trees
and no civilization is around me.
The ride is two minutes, 50 seconds, not four minutes.
It's so short, but it feels like such a long thing
because of how many different things and like,
your brain keeps getting stimulated
and then by the end of it, whether it's two minutes
or five minutes, if it feels like it's had enough fun stuff,
it feels good, I think.
It covers a lot of grounds too.
It's the ultimate, I was also thinking about how
compare this to Big Thunder Mountain,
which we all obviously like a lot,
but it's clearly in Disneyland or Space Mountain.
The Disneyland roller coasters are all about,
we don't have a lot of space,
but we're gonna turn you every which way
within this little piece of square footage.
This thing is so big in its scope and wide
and explores so much.
It takes advantage of how much land there is
at Disney World.
Let's start in the queue, I guess, a little bit.
I guess so.
I mean, even leading up to the queue, yeah.
Well, the Asia area section of the park is just,
I mean, all of this park is so detailed
and so thought out.
What else is in Asia?
I have a current park map,
current-ish park map in front of me.
Asia also has the Maharaja Jungle Trek.
I think that's a walking tour.
The Kali River Rapids is the other big attraction,
and it's where the Rivers of Light show is now.
Yakin Yeti, the restaurant is there.
I still haven't eaten there,
even though everyone says that's good.
Although Tiffins, I think people like better.
Like better.
Tiffins, I thought, was more by Pandora.
Maybe you're right.
I could be wrong.
Yeah.
What are the lands of Animal Kingdom at this point?
Pandora?
Pandora is what the world is about.
Asia, Africa, Pandora.
Yeah, Asia, Africa, Discovery Island.
Dino Land USA.
The Oasis, and yeah, Dino Land USA.
You know, that actually counteracts one thought I had
was that this is one of the parks in Florida,
excuse me, at Disney World,
that doesn't have, for lack of a better term, America Town,
because the Magic Kingdom has Liberty Square,
Epcot has America.
Hollywood Studios is pretty much just about
the history of American filmmaking.
It's all lip tributes to different parts of LA.
Different parts of LA.
Yeah, there's not a lot of French New Wave
in that film park,
but I guess Dino Land USA is kind of America?
It doesn't quite know.
There was like Camp Mini Mickey before,
which is what Pandora replaced, which that's something.
They really should do a Griffith Park section
for Animal Kingdom or a Runyon Canyon ride.
Just because you need the LA.
Yeah, an LA specific.
I need as many LA references as possible.
The Greek theater show building,
like you could have a show in the,
made like the fake Greek theater at Animal Kingdom.
I was thinking how the Grizzly Peak
is sort of a nod to Big Bear, really.
Uh-huh.
The Grizzly Peak recreation area
when you see signage about that.
So that's a little,
but I guess California Adventure entirely
is a little California nod.
Disney parks love California.
Yeah.
It's got more California.
You think they were designed
10 minutes down the road or something.
Oh yeah.
But not that here you traverse the jungles of Asia.
And yeah. Yes.
So, well see I don't know much about the line
because I haven't done it.
It's pretty boring to watch a video of a look.
God bless these theme park archivists on YouTube
who cover every nook and cranny of all these places.
But I'm not gonna sit and watch a video of the line.
Well it's themed to like you are traveling
to the Himalayas.
And of course the Himalayan Mountains
touch upon five countries in the world.
I have it right here. Go ahead.
Of course.
The thing that you wrote down.
Come on Jason.
Oh my God.
Time is of the essence.
Nepal, India, Bhutan, China, and Pakistan.
They're a very long stretch.
Very good.
And include of course the famous Everest among them.
But then there's this weird thing
that the ride is not meant to be on Everest itself.
No, you are in the Forbidden Mountains.
And we should.
And technically the name of the ride
is Expedition Everest Legend of the Forbidden Mountain.
Right. Yeah.
Because you need these things to be as long as possible.
Which is interesting because that is like a,
this is a Joe Roady ride.
Yes.
Imagine Joe Roady and then he was behind
Guardians of the Galaxy which also is a long title.
Guardians of the Galaxy.
Oh yeah.
It's got sort of an aftermath.
I do wonder maybe if that's his.
We'll ask him.
We have to have him on.
Come hell or high water we will have Joe Roady on the show.
So does he like a long title
will be one of the first questions.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's actually an interesting thought to bring up.
Although another Roady thing,
we have talked before about how his rides
tend to have a lot of plot.
This does not.
This is very simple, yeah.
It's very simple and is more world building.
So you're going through the office of a company
that does tours of these mountains and a Yeti museum.
Yeah, so here's, this is what I wanna say about,
actually about the line.
I'm not gonna describe this tons and tons of cool.
A thousand artifacts.
They're all real things they went and found.
They did trips to Nepal.
That they bought from people.
Right, they said they would go
and they would clear out like little marketplaces
and be like, well, buy all these bowls or something.
And people were like, oh, okay.
And they just take all these bowls and then put them there.
There was something interesting in that special tour
where they were talking about how they would take stuff
and then they'd have to make it look more beat up.
So there was a way to make like, they almost felt bad
because some of the things they would buy,
it looked too nice because it was new.
But they wanted to make it look more like,
oh, they had found this and it was on a hillside
for 60 years.
So they'd have to like dirty up something or,
that's very, we'll post a link to this thing.
Sure, sure.
Hey everybody, it's Scott here.
We talk a lot about treats on this show.
We love treats, we're treat boys.
But sometimes even the treat boys
don't wanna schlep all the way to a theme park
just to get the treats that we crave.
And sometimes we want treats that are healthy and homemade.
And that's why I'm excited about HelloFresh.
It's a meal kit delivery service that shops, plans,
and delivers step-by-step recipes
and pre-measured ingredients
so you can just cook, eat, and enjoy.
I had a HelloFresh delivery this week and it was a blast.
I had Presto Pesto Panko Chicken.
I had Beef Bibimbap and I had sweet and smoky pork chops.
I like that they spell it with the N and the apostrophe.
It's like Chippendale Rescue Rangers.
I like that combo.
But what I like more is that it was delicious.
And they help you through every step of the way.
They make it so easy on ya.
It's enjoyable, it's easy.
It's food delivered straight to your door every week
so you can enjoy cooking and sticking
to your New Year's goals.
You can branch out, you can get out of your recipe rut
and cook outside of your comfort zone
by discovering new delicious recipes.
So if you wanna do all that,
if you wanna take advantage of HelloFresh's
special offer for 2019 and get $80 off your first month,
go to hellofresh.com slash themepark80
and enter the code themepark80.
Same address, same code.
It's easy to remember.
It's my favorite thing and my favorite decade.
Hellofresh.com slash themepark80.
Enter the code themepark80.
HelloFresh, that's all.
Let's go back to talking about fake rocks.
So the first time I had been on it,
Lindsay and I were going through the main queue
and we're looking at all this stuff
and up until the fake newspaper clippings about the Yeti,
I went, oh, is all this stuff real?
Are these articles real?
Like, it does a really good job of easing you into the fakes.
Yeah, K-Fake, there you go.
So we're looking and I'm like, oh wow,
there's all these expeditions, huh?
So these explorers, they were never found again.
That's interesting.
Like I truly like, it makes me sound like probably an idiot
because you'd probably look at it again and go,
oh, that's, look at it,
it looks like one of those old Wests like photo,
like it looks like a fake thing you'd find
at a fair or something newspaper.
But like for a couple rooms, we're like,
oh, this is interesting.
Like, I never heard about this before.
That's the written kind of hidden story
of like the lost expedition.
Yeah, and then like there's an article,
another one was like Yeti attacks.
And I'm like, oh, okay, got it.
I'm an idiot, I'm an idiot, got it.
But it's so good, like it's such,
cause I guess it feels authentic
because of all the artifacts they've got
and all the different things they bought that.
Well, okay, so I mean, maybe we should talk about Rody
a little bit in general because he like clearly
is the guy driving the ship for these
like incredibly detailed, world traveling kind of rides
because Rody gets a lot of credit.
I mean, what is he, I don't, I never know the positions,
but he's sort of, you sort of attribute
all of Animal Kingdom to him on some level.
Yeah, he was the lead designer of this attraction
and I think Animal Kingdom at large.
Right, I believe so, yeah.
And then Pandora.
So like, I do feel like with Rody,
more than other cases, like other than
original Walt Disney Disneyland and Hard Rock Park
with, what's his name?
Big John Binkowski. Binkowski.
Binkowski. A boy.
This is, it's sort of an auteur park in a way.
And no park obviously can be made
or single-handed, because I'm not one for it.
But you, and he, yeah, I'm sure he would say
all of the hundreds of people.
Right.
But like, I don't know, he does seem
like such a major driving force behind.
And where it's like, and if you follow him on Instagram,
he is very much a world traveler and very detail-oriented
and you just, I just, I don't know.
It's hard.
He clearly is bringing so much of himself to.
Yeah, it's hard not to, yeah, if you just like
have a light understanding of him
or have looked at a few posts on Instagram
or seen a few interviews with him,
it's hard not to see him all over this place.
Like it's hard. Yeah.
And by the way, just to say, if you don't know
who we're talking about and you're vaguely familiar
with behind the scenes videos or park specials,
it's the guy with the earring.
Yeah, he's got the earring.
And then most people have got it.
You've seen him, you know him.
Yes. Yeah.
But yeah, I mean, it almost feels like,
I mean, obviously we've talked about
a lot of famous Imagineers, but it does feel like
now his footprint, because it's a whole park
that you sort of associate with his aesthetic.
So like, I don't know, is there any other than
Walt Disney himself?
Yeah.
Other Disney park where you're like.
Tony Baxter in Paris, maybe?
To some extent. Yeah, to some extent,
but it's still like Walt's, the original.
At Shubberyland is very Tony.
Yes.
Yeah, but it's just a land.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's interesting.
I wonder how he feels about that,
because it does like his, he has a part kind of,
like his voice is one of the parks.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Also gonna say, I found out a bunch of crazy
Rhodey stuff.
So this I knew, and I've interacted with him on Twitter
because of this, Joe Rhodey went to my high school.
He went to Chaminade, which is in West Hills, California.
By the way, the alumni list of this high school,
very strange, I mean, my favorite ones,
Rhodey and David Page from Toto,
who wrote two of my favorite songs,
Africa and Human Nature by Michael Jackson.
Also, didn't know this one, Dean Ween from Ween
went to Chaminade. Whoa.
Wow.
And wait, who else on the list?
I mean, several of the kids from Seventh Heaven
who were there when I went there,
and Jonathan Taylor Thomas went there when I went there.
One that I didn't know about, Linda Hogan.
Yeah, weird, right?
Hogan's ex-wife. Yes.
Linda Hogan.
Wow. That's crazy.
Star of Hogan Knows Best went to Chaminade
and an old Sky Gardener as well.
But I didn't, so I just thought that was cool.
And I think I learned he went there
because of an alumni magazine that I am forced to receive.
I don't think I have a way to not receive it.
I didn't know that his Disney story totally stems
from my high school Chaminade,
which is that he graduated Chaminade, went to Occidental
right before Barack Obama went there,
graduated from there, started working back at Chaminade
as a doing theatrical set design for the theater program,
which I participated in many decades later.
And so he's like doing sets for the plays,
and the sets for the plays are better
than they have any right to be.
They're just oddly complicated and very well done.
And he said the theater department at the time
didn't have very big budgets.
We made these rather impressive, elaborate productions
in terms of set and costume design.
And one of Rhodey's students, his father was John Zovich,
who was the vice president of engineering for Imagineering.
So he goes to see one of his kids' plays,
goes, what's going on with the sets?
Is super impressed, finds Rhodey, talks to him,
goes into Rhodey's office and says,
you're wasting your time here, kid.
You should be working for Walt Disney Imagineering.
And Rhodey's reaction, because he, by his own admission,
is like, I'm like a free spirit hippie world traveler guy.
Like Disney would hate a guy like me.
He takes the job and he is wrong.
They love what he's doing.
He's able to totally put his personality into everything.
And he's like a rising star there very quickly.
So had he not made crazy sets for my high school,
I don't know if it was in the same facility,
the Bob Hope Center where I, and he,
not an alum, Bob Hope.
No, no, no, Bob Hope Center.
I don't know why something's named after him.
Maybe he drove by the school once or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, close enough.
He woke up on the lawn once.
All right, rough night.
So anyway, he's like right out of the gate,
kind of like a valued imagineer.
First thing he did, there was tons to do at Epcot.
So he was a scenic painter for the Mexico Pavilion,
which, think about that painting in there.
Yeah, yeah, all these murals.
I don't know what he did exactly,
but yeah, murals are great.
That boat ride we love.
Worked on the refurbishment of Fantasyland.
Did concept art for Captain EO.
Worked on the Norway Pavilion.
And then eventually building up to working,
is he like the main guy on the Adventurers Club?
The beloved, now lost Pleasure Island attraction?
I believe that is right.
Was one of the main guys.
It was hard to find.
Pleasure Island stuff not cataloged as well.
We were saying the plaques and stuff
throughout Pleasure Island has a very roadie kind of vibe.
He loves his backstory.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Olani, I believe is also.
Yeah, that's him, yeah, for sure.
He was in charge of it too.
So I guess, and I might be wrong about specifics here,
but I think that in 84, Eisner has taken over
and he needs to pitch the Adventurers Club,
or maybe it's something else,
but I think it's the Adventurers Club, to Eisner.
And he comes into the pitch with an actual Bengal tiger.
And Eisner's like, wow, this guy.
He's got panache.
He's exciting.
So he gets on Eisner's radar pretty quickly
and they're talking about what is the ultimate thing
you would wanna do.
And I think that was Animal Kingdom.
Because it was like a trick.
Yeah, I was gonna say that's a real power move
and would come back later
when they were doing The Lion King
and they would always show the behind the scenes animator
sketching a lion just in a conference room.
Yeah, that footage is crazy.
I remember taking the tour of the animation studio
and it would have been Christmas 92 or 93,
I forget when, but I remember them saying.
And next week it's very exciting
because we have some real jungle animals coming in
and the animators are gonna draw them.
And I remember thinking, what's that gonna be for?
And there you go, clearly Lion King.
I think it was like, didn't he say something
like the biggest, that's the biggest thrill
is seeing an animal?
There was something along the lines of
he wanted to impress upon Michael Eisner
that this is as good as a ride
is seeing this thing up close.
Oh, gotcha.
This could be from a different meeting
or a different thing I'm misremembering.
Because that's another thing you appreciate
with Animal Kingdom when you're older
is like how close you are.
Like a zoo has a lot of barriers between you and the animal
and they made an effort at Animal Kingdom
to try and use bodies of water or natural like stuff
to make it feel like you are closer than you really are.
When we went on that safari the first time
a couple years ago, since I had been out in the late 90s,
I was like a little uncomfortable
by how close the animals were.
Yeah, sure.
They're like, oh God, this is.
What's the actual deal with that hotel
where they show you footage and it's like
a giraffe's gonna walk up to your room.
I don't know.
I don't know if that's true, if the giraffe really will like,
oh my, good morning Mr. Giraffe.
And he's up at your window.
I think there's still.
He knocks on the window to wake you up
and he pulls like the sun out with his teeth.
I haven't stayed there.
A cup of tea.
I think you're still pretty far away.
But it feels like you're a lot closer.
That hotel is amazing.
Wonderful restaurants, the design, incredible.
The main restaurant in there, yeah, is insanely good.
This is a quick side note.
I last night had a dream that I was price comparing hotels
for Disney World.
You were checking in your dream?
Jesus Christ.
This is not a lie.
I remember.
You weren't even there.
I remember figures too.
And you're not supposed to be able to read in your dream.
But I remember looking at a website
that's Yacht and Beach Club and it said like 7.25.
And I was like, too expensive.
And then I looked at Polynesian or something
and I saw like $300.
And I was like, oh, it's getting better.
So but I, as a very specific,
I woke up going, oh my God.
I'm thinking of the website to book Orlando hotels
in my dreams.
I want to help you George Washington.
Even your dreams are linked.
I wasn't even at the park.
It wasn't like, oh my gosh,
I'm at Disney World enjoying the rides.
I'm dreaming about booking.
The fact that you, well, cause you have,
you like, do you like booking for people from afar?
I do, yeah.
You've given them tips and that's one of the-
And then now to know that it's in your dreams.
I have never, I don't remember lately,
at least most of my dreams.
I don't have vivid dreams very often.
I usually forget them by the time I'm up.
Not this one.
I woke up and had, I have such a clear memory
of this like facsimile website that my brain constructed
in my head right now with the number 7.25
and then the Polynesian website with 300.
I remember it so clear, it's as if it was real.
And these numbers are, how accurate are these numbers?
Not accurate, the numbers are not, it would be better if-
What a wild dream.
Not so far off.
Not far off for the Polynesian.
That's a, that is a deal.
Yachton Beach Club is not 7.25.
Unless there's a suites.
Possibly.
You could have been looking at suites.
In my brain I could have been examining the suites
at the Yachton Beach Club and maybe, yeah,
if they were, it was like a big family suite,
it could be 7.25, so who knows?
So when you die, your heaven is a world
where you can sit at the right hand of God
and be his personal checker.
With a MacBook Pro, yeah.
Find me a-
Not even a cloud-shaped computer.
Not a fancy heaven thing.
No, like a 2018 MacBook.
How much?
It's an 18 inch, it's pretty light, you'll find.
Please, find me a good deal for the Caribbean beach.
Recently refurbished, Michael.
Please give me a lagoon view.
No.
Some, I have some roadie stuff.
So roadie, the theatrical background
adds to one of my memories, and Mike, correct me if I,
if this is someone else, please correct me.
Sure.
Isn't there a video of roadie playing the Dream Finder?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a video of him in the full Dream Finder,
get up, like talking to you, and he's so anime.
He's a very engaging speaker, but he's fully committed
to the character of the Dream Finder,
so that he has a theatrical background makes a lot of sense.
Yeah, a lot of people, not a lot,
but a handful of people in Imagineering,
different people have played Dream Finder
in different media.
There was a walk around Dream Finder for a while,
but then there's in different videos,
and there's been multiple.
Your next dream will be applying spirit gum to a beard
and placing it on an Imagineer's face
so he can play the Dream Finder.
Yeah, I don't get to meet Dream Finder
and fly with him in the flying machine.
Figma's not real.
No.
You're helping somebody into a costume.
It's a practical side.
You did get into the makeup artist union,
which is good, because they have good benefits.
In my dream, I did.
Yeah, in your dream.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, good for sort of a,
it's a nice little mixer at the end of the year.
Yeah, it's like I lived a whole lifetime in my head
of going to makeup school.
Yeah, and then you wake up feeling lost,
because you're like, that is a life I'll never live.
I'll never live, yeah.
You never can go back to that life.
Sure.
Dream Finder is, if we really think of Dream Finder
as much like Hamlet or Othello,
like multiple actors have taken the role.
Oh, and made it their own.
And it's the Joker now, of course,
is the new version of this.
And maybe, yeah, so many more,
hopefully, people will get to play.
Just jamming in another Joker reference.
Well, Jason, you were right on the money.
Well, yeah, look, the internet has been on fire
with that Joker joke, they've just been hammering me with it.
But he's talking about it.
Everybody's lighting me up on social media.
It's really hitting.
That Mike is or likes the Joker.
Is the Joker, I think?
No, just likes it a lot.
Oh, okay, just likes it a lot.
No, like your dreams, you don't get to be anything exciting.
You just get to be adjacent or trying to purchase it.
So, hopefully, all three of us will get to play
Dream Finder at certain points.
Yeah.
Well, we can, anytime we want.
Anytime we want.
Let's just do it, it's not even due for the podcast.
Next time we're hanging out,
let's all be dressed like the Dream Finder.
We'll go to a bar.
Everyone will be buying us shots
because they'll think we are so cool.
Yeah, I think, yeah, maybe a Patreon exclusive
is that we all do monologues as the Dream Finder.
Which is our take on.
Yeah, what is the-
The Dream Finder monologues?
Yeah, you know, the Dream Finder monologues.
Mine's gonna be a Tom Waits Dream Finder, I think.
He's kind of a grittier Dream Finder.
Oh, okay.
What if we all didn't tell each other what we were writing?
We all ended up writing gritty Dream Finder.
It's like a very lazy movie.
It's like how a lot of the superhero movies,
like a lot of superhero comics in the 80s and 90s
went through like this character but gritty
and then it kind of 20 years later hit the movie versions
and hopefully we're coming out of that.
Mine's gonna rap.
Oh, okay, you're going for a Hamilton.
Yeah, yeah.
Very, very good.
Pretty edgy, huh?
So the other roadie thing, I watched a walk through,
there was a tour, I guess there was a limited time tour
of Expedition Everest and sort of the surrounding areas
in Animal Kingdom and a very interesting imagineer, Colleen.
I did, they said, I couldn't catch the last name
but she was the head of character paint for Imagineering
which is not a term that I had heard before
but character paint is using color to tell stories
because they use dozens and dozens of colors of paint,
thousands of gallons of paint to paint Everest
and they said there's four shades of gray alone
to do the snow, to do the different gradients of snow.
But someone asked about roadie and they said,
well, Joe's not in the park right now.
He kind of splits his time between Orlando and Glendale
but even when he is not, he travels for Imagineering
but even when he's not working, he loves to travel.
So last we heard he's in Mongolia tracking snow leopards.
Wow.
It's a good Instagram also.
Amazing Instagram, very thoughtful captions.
He writes a lot too and posts his sketchbooks,
sometimes he keeps very intense sketchbooks and all.
It's interesting, I find it fascinating that story
with the high school because that's one of those instances
where he wasn't looking for Disney,
it's just happenstance that that happens
unless there's more to the story we don't know
but he isn't like Tony where Tony's a super fan
and he was on a collision course with his talent in Disney
because he worked there, he's obsessed with it.
Just by happenstance, this interesting designer man
gets swept up and then he takes to it.
I don't think, I mean maybe.
That's true, he wasn't romanticizing Disney specifically,
just he was into what he was into
and able to bring all those influences to the company.
Yeah, what I would imagine it was like,
yeah he figured out how to make it your own
or whatever you would, he figured out very quickly
okay, I can do what I like but here in this.
Yeah, it's like we didn't set out to be podcasters.
No.
We just love talking, we just talk about all this shit
all the time anyway.
You get drafted into it more than you had a dream to do it.
It's a calling.
Now checking, dreaming, doing, living.
Checking.
That is what it is.
I do, as I'm thinking about it now,
I do get an endorphin rush from thinking about
trying to find a good deal.
Like I'm thinking about it now.
Describe what you're feeling physically.
Well physically, I'm a little tired today,
my voice a little hoarse but if I think about it,
if I think about like oh, I'm gonna go to Disney,
obviously it's mixed up with the Disney World trip.
That is somewhere in there buried in the feelings
of the checking is knowing oh, I'm gonna get to stay
in the hotel, I'm gonna get to go to the parks.
But the idea of that website that doesn't work very well,
the Orlando, you know what I'm talking about.
Have you tried to book hotels on the Disney World website?
Oh, on Disney's official one?
It's clunky, it's like the same thing
that they've had it since like 2000.
It doesn't make any sense why it's like that.
My family has had good luck calling them.
Calling the travel.
Because Disney has a full travel infrastructure
and even Universal now has a pretty intense
travel structure.
But yeah, there's a whole confusing thing
if you have like, there's like discounts.
And at the time when I was a premier pass holder,
you have to go around, there's a whole way
you have to log in to see if there's a discount
that you'll get from being the premier.
And it's not easy, it's a whole clunky way
and then you can get like an extra 5% off
the normal sale price that you'd originally get.
So it's it's.
And now you're just turning into a big glass of wine to me.
Now I'm just leaving the building.
Your brain is trying to soothe you.
It's seeing something unpleasant in front of you
and it's like, well, what'll calm him down?
All right, got it.
To me, you look like a Breyers ice cream
at the height of the summer when it's 250 a gallon
or 250 a quart.
Right now, see we're in the middle of winter right now
at the grocery store, ice cream was like $6 a quart.
Nice.
Oh really?
Yeah.
It's that different?
It is that different.
$250 to $6?
Are you still.
Do you have like on your stocks app,
can you like, here's the price of gold,
here's the price of steel, here's the price of ice cream.
The price of ice cream.
Price of Sherbet.
Is that one of the cost of living?
Could I get that?
Like it's a loaf of bread, a gallon of milk.
Could we get ice cream in there too?
Do you always have, I think we've covered this,
you always have like a little thing of ice cream
in the freezer?
It depends on.
Okay.
This is a sincere answer.
That's all I ask for.
It depends on how much other sweets are in the house.
So if you got a lot of Christmas candy.
Yeah, I don't right now
because I have a lot of stocking stuff for candy.
Good time of the year.
Good time of the year, yeah.
So you have like, when you say candy,
is it like a Fannie Mae style or what's the other one?
Sweet?
Oh, no, like Dove bars or the Christmas tree shaped Reese's
or just like stuff you could fit in an actual stocking.
Cadbury bars are really good.
We're recording this, it's like two and a half weeks
after Christmas or so.
Is it that you, how much candy is in that stocking though?
Cause I went through my candy in the stocking.
Well, you have to remember my parents are divorced
so I have two stockings.
They're stocking each one.
And then my stepdad usually, my mom and stepdad
live out in Amish country and all of those country,
kitschy kind of Pennsylvania Dutch stores
are just filled with bulk candy and stuff.
Oh, so your stocking is like loaded up.
So stocking or like gift bags and stuff.
So do you ever have dreams about them getting divorced
thus creating a third?
A third.
I think. Assuming you would go visit.
I think I would have other concerns.
Yeah.
I'm not saying it'd be the first thing,
but just like to give you solace
in everything swirling emotionally.
Like, well, maybe third stocking.
Yeah.
Maybe, I had never considered that possibility
until this very moment.
It should not be wishing that.
I'm certainly not wishing those.
No, yeah, I know.
It'd be the only silver lining.
But you know, I will say I don't often buy
like a thing of non-pareils
or chocolate espresso beans for myself.
Although Mike has been with me when I have bought
a scoop of chocolate or espresso beans.
What am I talking about?
This is what you need.
You need a girlfriend or to get married
because then you've got in love.
That's your ticket to get divorced.
And now, this is, I'm just trying to design it
as many stockings for you as possible.
Also like how emotionally attached do you get to the,
the mother-in-laws, right?
I've learned from stand-up comedy,
the most insidious thing in the world
is the dang mother-in-law.
I learned that in driving school.
I had a driving school instructor
who was slipping in a lot of mother-in-law jokes.
I love that all driving instructors
trained in the borscht belt.
I also had like a-
Tricky roads up there.
I had, my driver's ed teacher also
was like a hacky comedian guy.
Like a type guy.
Have we talked about this in the show before?
I don't think we have talked about it, but yeah.
Is that a common,
because there is specifically stand-up driving schools,
but I think maybe in general they attract like-
That's interesting.
We're people who just want, like,
oh my God, I got an audience slipping in.
A small audience.
Yeah, yeah.
Of people who hate being there.
Right, yeah.
That's interesting.
All right, well I'll keep designing stocking plans for you.
Oh, thanks.
Doing math.
So yeah, so there's this Imagineering tour.
I was saying I watched this Imagineering tour video.
I thought all the talk about like how they use color
to tell stories and they had to like use,
the color red shows up a lot in the queue
and around Expedition Everest,
because as they say in the special,
it's considered a protective color.
So you'll see it in Nepal and it's around doorways
and windows in the corner of buildings.
It's very like subtly dusted on.
Yeah, kind of.
That's one, I feel, you know,
you could take the same structures of this ride
and have worse painters do it
and it would have 50% the impact.
Like there's such, these things are really
just beautifully touched up.
To the point they said in one of these videos that like,
you know, because they were using a lot of plaster
and trying not to use a lot of wood,
because wood is very rare around the Himalayas.
So wood is, they were saying you see it as accents
to buildings or on top of buildings,
but they don't have, so it's a lot more like mud and clay
and that sort of thing.
And there was like one of the colors of the plant.
They were trying to, they thought they had the texture
right to recreate it, but it wasn't looking right.
So the one time Rody went back to the Himalayas,
he asked them like, how do you do this
when you do the buildings?
And they were ladling it out.
They had been trying to scoop it out.
They were using like a soup ladle kind of thing.
And when they did that with the version they had recreated,
then it looked right.
So it's like that level of attention to detail.
Rare is the person who would recognize all of these
methods and why they're being done.
And most tourists, or what most people are going on
that don't really, just kind of washes over them,
but you'd be able to tell if it wasn't done
with this degree of detail.
You really could.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, God bless him for being so to the letter.
Yeah, and I think, and from my perspective,
I have not traveled a lot internationally at all,
but respectful to the cultures too.
I would be very curious to hear about how Rody learned
to travel like that.
So you're not like just the white colonizer,
Kool-Aid man his way, like Dr. Livingston.
I didn't know where you were going with that.
Just bursting into a country like Dr. Livingston in Africa.
I do like Kool-Aid manning as a term for being
not delicate in your arrivals and presence.
Yeah, I think it's a very useful term for Hollywood,
the way some executives or producers or writers behave,
where they just burst in and start shooting their mouth off.
Yeah, but let's not go ascribing negative qualities
to the Kool-Aid man.
No, the Kool-Aid man is benevolent.
He gives of himself.
He is filled with the delicious nectar.
Drink of my blood.
And he always brought a party with him.
So it's like it's not, it was destruction with a purpose.
I watched him just a montage of like 50 Kool-Aid man burst-ins
that I was so happy by.
I could watch.
If I wish there were a full 24 hours worth, I could watch.
Is he still bursting?
Are there new commercials where he's bursting through walls?
I don't know, they're probably all Geico ripoff now,
where they're just like odd and still
and awkward or something.
I don't know, I think there's been some pretty recent.
You know what I appreciate?
They were doing the burst-ins so early in the 60s.
It was probably so hard to do that stuff.
And he had the animated face.
How hard was that to do?
It's probably drawn on the film.
Yeah, easier in the 80s.
We'll get into who may, I would love to find out
the personnel behind the Kool-Aid man.
Oh, the Kool-Aid man.
Yeah, the madman kind of guys who are behind the Kool-Aid man.
Kool-Aid man never in a theme park or a ride?
I don't think so.
Seems perfect for something.
A weird out of the way thing.
So why hasn't Hershey hit up?
I don't think that's in the same umbrella.
No, I don't know who owns Kool-Aid.
Although speaking of company-based rides,
we're just a week or so, no, not even a week,
just a few days past the Consumer Electronic Show in Vegas.
And a lot of people were mentioning that Google
built a dark ride.
I haven't really watched it yet, but I don't.
I mean, I don't have the best opinion of tech companies
right now.
But they built a dark ride.
But they did build a ride, so I have to look into that.
So maybe they're good.
Yeah.
I lost my train of thought.
Yeah, I know.
It's a runaway train, just like the ride itself.
We're talking about painting and stuff.
Maybe we talk a little about the,
I think we probably all learned about how the mountain itself
was built, which this again in Matterhorn is the demo
and this is the full realization of it,
that they were able to, our beloved fake rocks
were in fake rock territory, and they were able to,
for the first time, use digital technology
to print the surface of the fake rocks.
And they're like, so every, it's all these slats.
There was a term for it, and I forget what it is now.
But like.
Terra bars or something?
Or not the scaffolding, because they had a very interesting
scaffolding.
Oh yeah, that's a different thing.
I mean, it's all these panels that are all applied
to the big steel structure, but they're all different
because they're randomized by computer.
So it's this very 3D printed.
They were able to specifically design the texture of all
of these many thousands of blocks of fake rock paneling,
and then installed it all, but then went in and covered
everything in tin foil in order to make really perfect
and randomized craggy rock texture.
So they laid that in and then painted it.
I forget how the tin foil came into effect.
All that stuff is just truly something.
If they put you in a room, how would you even know
where to begin?
It's so detailed.
That special really breaks it down in detail
of how crazy this job is.
How hard and insane it is.
You also in the special meet the people behind the sound.
And I think sound is a real, we haven't talked about this
much, but you really are in the Disney parks never thinking
about where the sound is coming from.
When a parade is in motion, seriously where?
Is it sometimes it's in the float?
Is it below you?
Is it in the street?
Is it hidden in planters?
It's very, very hard to tell.
And you're not supposed to know.
But in this ride, yes.
Sometimes it's below the track.
Sometimes when you hit that giant peak,
it's hidden in the rock work on either side of you.
And there's so much going on in terms of yeti sounds
and atmospheric sounds.
And this has to be a low rumble, so it's gotta be
this kind of speaker and go under here.
It's hard to appreciate because it's hidden,
but there's such crazy artistry to it.
I feel like there was a few years before I even realized
that that Indiana Jones vehicle engine is fake.
Like that's how, I mean again, maybe I'm making myself
sound stupid, but like after a couple years,
I feel like I was like, oh yeah, that's a gas engine.
That's obviously a noise to make it sound like a Jeep.
It's not like actual sound of the, obviously I think
I knew the stalling out was fake,
because that couldn't be real.
But I still think that I was like, oh yeah,
there's all these sounds that I'm just taking for granted
that are adding to the atmosphere of this thing.
And I didn't even realize it.
Well, and they said on Everest, they built steam pipes
in the station, but it's like built into the ground,
so that when the train comes up, it looks like it's coming
out of the train, steam, because like roller coaster cars,
you don't wanna build a steam generator in a roller coaster
car that you don't need there.
So, and then they had to, the woman talking about coloring
to tell a story, then on the train, they had to paint
in the soot that like, you know.
And they've talked about how they've wanted and allowed
like physical, not mechanical, but physical wear and tear
on the vehicles, because then it looks like a beaten up
old train, you know, as opposed to a shiny new
just built and installed in Florida.
And in the special, it's like super cloudy and rainy one day
and Rhodey's looking up excited, he's like,
looks even better, it looks like the real place now.
So this thing like, you know, incorporated the elements
in a cool way.
Yeah, and then it's like with the mountain stuff
and like big thunder stuff that's based in reality,
like it does, as long as there's upkeep you have to do to it,
but also it does get more character as the years go on.
So like it does add to it that it looks like
a little junkier.
Just as the trees grow and fill in gaps that weren't there,
and maybe that's the whole thing, maybe like,
well, I'd say definitely with Everest now
and much more recently with Avatar,
like probably Animal Kingdom seemingly is at its peak now.
It's like, whereas there's probably other parks
that have the opposite effects,
that come out of the gate perfect and shiny,
and then aren't kept upright or like.
Yeah, Epcot Center's gotten worse.
Hollywood Studios has needed like a reconceptualizing
of what it even is, but Animal Kingdom is only improved
and improved and improved.
It's a little like engine that could.
Islands of Adventure I think had a lot more detail
and certainly a lot more like port of entry kind of stuff
throughout or like in, there used to be those junk boats
that would go across the lagoon
and all of that's so quickly faded away.
I mean, I'm sure some of it you could chalk up to.
Islands of Adventure opens 99, September 11th happens,
and like Orlando took a hit hard.
I mean, Disney had hotels closed,
like they had so many issues.
Did something close entirely?
I think some of the smaller hotels,
some of the mid-range hotels might've like closed for.
You mean like temporarily.
Temporarily.
Right, right.
And then construction, a lot of some of the all-stars,
like their openings were delayed years.
Oh sure.
Like they were just left as construction shells.
That's another thing about this ride is that,
I've said it before, I think there was a real dark period
for theme parks after September 11th
with the tourism diving, with less money coming in
and just Disney's already getting cheap
and California Adventure was so cruddy when it opened.
Like think about the, like in the,
this is 2006 is when this opened.
Yeah, yeah.
Like what else was good in the parks leading up to this?
Like there's things, Mission Space obviously a big,
like super technological Marvel attraction,
but like not very well regarded.
Right, you said good.
Yeah, yeah.
What else was good?
An interesting swing, a big swing,
a big interesting building.
But Everest seems like something you'd make in a golden age
and it's surrounded by a lot of nothing
and a lot of them going, well let's celebrate the anniversary
because we don't have a new ride.
But this feels like, right?
It's like Disneyland was kind of garbage.
I can't think of anything they added from like 03 to 06.
Because when we went, when I hadn't been in 10 years,
the stuff that I hadn't gone on at that point was
Mickey's PhilharMagic and Everest.
And I think that's it.
I'm pretty sure that's it as far as new stuff
and I hadn't been in 10 years.
There might be one thing I'm forgetting,
but that's nothing, that's like two rides in 10 years.
Right.
It's crazy.
Yeah, so Everest really carried the torch.
I guess the Mission Space as well.
There it is, that's the last one.
But I mean, it's all on Everest in the 2000s.
This is the ride of the 2000s.
It carried the torch.
And yeah, it is interesting.
I would be interested to know like
how did they get it through?
Was it just because of the anniversary?
And then I guess maybe they also had surveys that said like,
you know, people would like a thrill ride here.
Yeah, I bet.
Maybe it was always part of the plans.
Maybe it was one of those like tier two will be there,
phase two will be this.
I think also, I wonder at that point,
cause I think they always intended to build
the Beastly Kingdom stuff.
Or at least for a few years too.
And I wonder if that was still,
I wonder when that finally went away for good.
Cause I think it was supposed to be where Pandora is now.
Yeah, I didn't come across a lot for this ride of like,
where did the idea come from?
Like what was the impetus for this
as opposed to like a different animal themed coaster
or something?
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know what you mean.
I mean, it's a, yeah, it's like a mountain,
which is a Disney tradition.
So I mean, that all makes sense.
But yeah, I wonder if what else,
I haven't seen anything about like,
what other ideas were thrown around?
It is, I mean, they had a land based, you know, Asia.
So like it makes sense to the Himalayas.
The Himalayas are in such a large part of Asia.
So like it's there.
It makes total sense.
Like why it is there.
Looking at a recent Animal Kingdom map,
I think it's interesting that if you look at
Animal Kingdom from above,
this is sort of at like four o'clock on a watch
and Pandora's kind of at like seven o'clock.
So nicely spaced apart.
You have like the E-tickets far apart,
which is good for crowd control.
Like good for crowd disbursement.
Sure.
Wow.
Yeah, this one has, I think this line is usually the sec,
well, I guess now third longest.
Although I guess sometimes the safaris get a little long,
depending on what time of day it is.
But yeah, I mean, these are,
this is a very popular obviously,
cause it's, I would assume,
this is one of those things that if you're a family,
you've got to go do this one.
Like this and the two rides in Pandora.
And this is potentially a family.
This isn't seemingly the most intense coaster.
No, it's not.
I mean, you go, last time I went on,
it is fast and like you go backwards
and I felt like that rocks you a little bit,
but it's not so crazy.
It's also like, I forget they say it on the special,
it's sort of deceptively,
the mountain is deceptively tall looking.
The drop is called force perspective.
And it makes smaller things look bigger.
Like that was the one thing about this special.
I was like, oh, we're getting a lot of 2006
travel channel narrator.
Manser's.
The guy that you don't know, Jack guy.
Like, what do you think this is?
How does this coaster's top speed compare to a dick going?
A dick's thrust.
A dick?
That was just the style of the times.
Did you catch what he said about roadie
when they first introduced roadie in the special?
No.
I forget.
Can you tell by the earring?
This guy thinks outside the box.
What if I had an earring?
That's pretty wild thinking.
Manser's.
You never did Manser's, right Jason?
No, I never did anything for Manser's.
That was a little before my time at UCB.
I was starting to fish because when I realized,
somebody at Funny or Die,
that their girlfriend or wife was the casting person.
Yeah, yeah.
I was like, is this my inn?
I started to try, but I think it was a little too late.
Oh, you were gonna try to be honest.
I wanted to be honest very, very badly.
But I was not, I've never been a pure actor,
so there's no reason why I would've done it.
I was just like, what strings can be pulled?
Look, I'll be a nerd.
I know I don't look like a bro.
You just wanted to be,
you wanted to join a Carnival sideshow for one day.
Yeah, yeah.
You wanted to be one of Mr. Barnum's freaks
for a single 14 hour day for a hundred special dollars.
I cannot stress to people,
do not look up the clip that I'm involved in on Manser's.
Do not look it up.
Don't try to find it.
I don't think Manser's particularly well archived.
I tried to find it the last time it came up.
I think it's off.
I think it's off the line.
Yeah, I even, you know what?
I don't think I told you this.
I bought a couple episodes of it.
To try to find it?
I forget why those.
I was like, based on your vague description of what it was,
I looked at what were the topics,
but nobody out there is really keeping Manser's super archived.
I was hoping to just run into it
and be able to show it to you,
but I couldn't, but I bought,
the only place that are available is on Amazon,
so I piecemeal bought three episodes of Manser's.
Now, it's great entertainment.
Oh, it's fantastic.
Regardless, but.
I will, I'll say this.
I'll tell you about one that I didn't do,
because this person you're mentioning who was casting
called me once and she was a very nice person.
And she said, all right, now you don't,
you feel free to say no to this.
And by the way, if people don't know what Manser's is,
it was a show on Spike TV
where it would answer like guys questions
and it would always be like about shit or sex or piss
or like something like a beer, you know, guy stuff,
shit piss, you know, sex, piss,
fist, the shit of the dick.
Like that was everything.
And so it would be like.
How much shit could your dick piss?
Well, hold on, Scott.
You got very close to what I was about to say.
She goes, all right, now you don't have to,
so every segment would be a different question.
It would be like, how much beer could you drink
before you died?
Like, would you blow up like a giant balloon,
like that girl in Willy Wonka, like stuff like that.
And it was like, she goes, all right,
so feel free to say no to this.
But would you be interested in being in the segment,
can you poop out your penis?
And I said, thank you for offering.
No, thank you.
She said, I totally understand.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, if only my number had been next.
I would have loved to have,
I don't know what it would have entailed, but.
The first time I did it, I was uncomfortable.
So that's why, especially I was like not,
I think I ended up doing like,
I was in the background of a bar scene that season.
And you know, you made a nice $110 for that, the whole,
that was it.
Sweet.
Wait, wait, I was just gonna say, what was the manser?
Oh, I don't know, I never saw the episode.
I do know who did it though.
But it had been turned down by I think over 10 people.
Whoa, I wonder what it would have had.
I would have, unless I, shirtlessness,
per oddly would have counted me out,
but this doesn't seem like it would require shirtlessness.
It could have.
They found a reason.
There was a lot of shirtless people.
Thank God, if it had been, can you shit out of your nipples?
I'm out for sure.
But.
I think the answer was yes though.
I think I did ask.
I think the answer was.
There would be like, well, you know,
look if a doctor went in there and redirected some pipe.
I don't know if that was the answer,
but it was something like.
If you had a switch track, all law, Expedition Everest.
If Joe Rody went into your intestines.
Well, that was going to say this is like turning Joe Rody's
inquisitive eye on trash culture.
And I would be, I'm curious to ask him like,
Joe, what's your poison?
What's your tread?
Like are you Vanderpump rule?
Do you bar rescue?
What's your garbage?
Like, no, you can't just.
You're not all flashed.
Read ancient scrolls all day long.
You gotta have something to cut it with, okay?
We'll see.
We'll have to ask.
That's the question number one.
What's your poison?
What's your poison, Joe Rody?
I love ridiculousness.
I love to see a laptop elevate, built on a giant scale
and to have a man serve as a finger
stepping from key to key.
Well, you can't argue with that.
I mean, I caught an episode or two of ridiculous
on cable over the holidays and it just bleeds charisma.
I mean, there's one word you're thinking of.
Very popular.
Yo, what's up?
I'm Rob Duda and this is ridiculousness.
And then like, he like, as much as he can make the sounds
technically without actually opening his mouth
and then like, and then the girl who just cackles.
She's a professional cackler.
I don't think I've ever seen an episode.
I saw an episode.
Ridiculousness is something else.
Oh, you've seen it a lot.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
I really like.
I saw one with one of the new Power Rangers,
with one of the Power Rangers
from the big budget movie Power Rangers.
Which, all five are such mega stars today.
So recognizable.
You can't avoid them.
Yeah, we're all into their personal exploits.
Anyway, Expedition Everest.
Back to Expedition Everest.
We have to find our trash in side tracks
because we just like this ride a lot.
Yeah, we're trying to find the Forbidden Mountains.
We have been warned off from going near it.
Well, the side, the story that we've missed
is that this was a railroad that was like a,
it was like a tea delivery route.
And like this isn't a roller coaster.
This is just a train where tea is moved from place to place.
But the Yeti did not like the train tracks
going through his mountain home.
So he tore it up or something.
But now it's back up and it's these two,
these two numbskulls, Norbu and Bob,
who are doing, they're taking the old tea route
and they've turned it into like a tourist thing.
And we're all Norbu's suckers.
We're all just a bunch of Norbu's.
Yeah, I didn't know that was the narrative
when I was in the line,
but I don't think that's so important.
This is a good optional narrative.
I think this is kind of where Theme Park stories
need to land is it's there if you want.
But if you want, if you need to just be changing diapers
for the whole, if you need to be feeding goldfish
to your kids for the whole line,
you don't need to know, you don't need to pay attention
to any articles on the wall.
Yeah, dad, let's look, okay, what is it?
Roller coaster, got it.
Yeti, got it.
That's all we need to know.
Well, it also seems like from what I read about
as they're researching this,
they found that there is kind of a spiritualism,
the right word, but the Yeti seems to exist as a concept.
I'll post a link to this from Mouse Planet
had this transcript of a talk Rody gave
explaining their theory behind the Yeti.
The other challenge that we set before us
was making the Yeti real, making a Yeti
that could both seem real and be this other Yeti,
the guardian of the mountain Yeti.
So we did in fact blend both of these ideas
into making our Yeti.
Most people in the Himalayas believe the Yeti is real.
It's not like Bigfoot.
It is not something that like six rednecks in a bar
think is real and everyone else thinks they're crazy.
That is not the Yeti.
When you go to the Himalayas,
it's really hard to find people who don't think the Yeti
is either real right now or was real a few years ago.
The Yeti is real to these people.
That's wild.
So like there is a spirituality.
There's like a, in the way that American urban legends,
the Bigfoot, the Jersey Devil are just kind of these,
you know, stories.
Like it feels like the Yeti holds more significance.
So is the Yeti real?
And how much shit could he piss?
So then they had to not.
How big is his hog?
We really like set that up perfectly
at the start of the episode
to talk about the Yeti pig-ass dick.
So how big is the Yeti's hog?
We asked this gorilla dick expert.
Well, extrapolating from a gorilla's penis size.
Whoa.
So there's kind of like a fleeting,
theoretical version of the Yeti
and then there is a Western version of the Yeti.
Like, oh, the Yeti is a big monster,
a Bigfoot type monster.
And they kind of had to make those both make sense together.
Like these local stories
and then translate that for a mass audience.
And that's what we're seeing in Expedition Everest.
So like a reverence had to be included.
It could not be some arbitrary just grr monster.
Although, once you're on the thing.
Well, they clearly ended up swinging some of this story
into Matterhorn with the way that now,
the abominable snowman now has more of this component
of he's protecting his mountain.
He's not just yelling at you arbitrarily,
he's being protective,
or at least that's how they explain the backstory.
And that's made a little more clear
with the added projection components
at the top of the Matterhorn.
And that's very much the,
he's not out for blood, he's being protective.
If we got to get off and explain it to him in his language,
he would understand.
So it makes sense.
He's not a villain, he's not a proper villain or something.
And there is a logic to the Yeti too,
because people have tweeted at him,
it's like, why is the Yeti not white?
And Rody's idea was that like,
there's nothing up there.
There's nothing at the snow-capped mountain.
Most of the Himalayas are barren and woods and forests.
And there's not food up there.
So it would probably be further down the mountain.
And one of the legends was that the Yeti could be invisible,
which if he was colored like the forest,
he would be invisible.
He would blend into the forest.
So there is a storytelling element too
to the color of.
He's like Predator?
Huh?
The Yeti is like the Predator?
Yeah, kind of.
Wow, that's awesome.
Which begs the question,
boy, Disney likes to expand their IPs
and stuff, some kick-ass Yeti movie.
Sure, and do they own Predator now with Fox?
Oh, I think.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, Predator versus,
Yeti versus Predator.
Yeti versus Predator versus Alien,
which they also own.
Because they got Alien too.
Yeah.
Time to add a third.
Versus Freddy and Jason.
I assume they own those.
That might be a different one.
Wow, yeah, that's interesting.
I have a question.
Does Joe Roady believe in the Yeti?
I feel like he would give you a little mystery answer.
I feel like he might not answer that all the way.
He'd give you a little bit of magic.
Which I guess that's what you want.
You spend enough time there.
You consume enough about this.
I would like to know,
because I have a minor fascination
with Sasquatch and the Grassman,
which is my favorite name for.
I don't know about the Grassman.
The Grassman is like Bigfoot.
But I forget what region they call him Grassman.
And there was a whole thing about finding the Grassman
on one of these channels.
And it's all just,
everyone's got their own regional version
of Bigfoot or whatever.
So it is fascinating to know,
for whatever reason,
this phenomenon has popped up
in different parts of the world.
I mean, it's not unlike religion,
where everyone has their own version of it.
But it's interesting.
I would wonder,
from a guy like Roady who's been
to so many different places.
I mean, not truly if he believes
that the Grassman is real.
But what has he seen?
What has he experienced with all the people
telling him about it?
I think his theory was that
a lot of these people,
a lot of the different ethnic groups had moved.
And some of the groups had,
over years and years,
had migrated from different parts of Asia.
And potentially parts where maybe
the great ape,
like giant apes may have been around more in the past.
So as stories get passed down the line
and as people move from place to place
and pass on these stories,
like there,
you can,
like the way storytelling works,
whisper down the line,
you can logic out that,
oh, that could be where the Yeti legends came from.
Right.
The Grassman is Ohio,
is Ohio specifically.
The Grassman, also known as the Ohio Grassman
or the Kenmore Grassman or Orange Eyes.
And then there's like drawings of specifically,
like this could be the Grassman
who looks kind of more like a Remwell.
It looks like Watto.
Whoa.
But then there's more like a Bigfoot type Grassman.
So it is interesting.
Truly, honestly, all this IP being turned into,
it's just kind of sitting there.
Jersey Devil,
no one's made like a Jersey Devil part of the movie.
I don't think I know about the Jersey Devil.
Oh, the Jersey, the story of the Jersey Devil.
Springsteen has a song,
or was he covering the song Jersey Devil?
I think so.
There's a hockey team, the Jersey Devils, too.
The Jersey Devil goes more back to like Puritan times
where it's like the devil impregnated a woman.
Uh-oh, whoa.
He means business.
The devil impregnated like Goody Proctor and the child.
Geez.
This half beast, half demon, half man.
It does, yeah,
feel like a dark universe of all these characters
is called for.
Yeah, absolutely.
All, yeah, no one owns these characters.
How big is the devil's sperm?
But I feel like- Is it pitch black?
Maybe it's just because it's older.
It feels like there is more of a story of the Yeti
than like Bigfoot.
Like I don't know what Bigfoot,
Bigfoot just seems like he's trying to get by.
There's more Bigfoot though than you realize.
There's more like Bigfoot mythology and stuff like that.
I think there is that.
We're gonna meet Bigfoot at Knott's soon enough.
Oh, it's so exciting, yeah.
So I guess Knott's is getting in on some of this
now that I think about it.
But yeah, it makes sense like Yeti
that there's probably a longer time
people have had to develop the legend of it,
which makes it loom a little larger, I guess.
Well, and then you have the legend of the Everest Yeti.
Yes.
Which is sort of the big thing about this ride.
And if you aren't privy to this,
if you watch this Travel Channel special,
well, that's okay.
So the Yeti, you hear the Yeti,
then at some point you see a projection,
kind of a silhouette of him tearing the track apart.
The whole thing is kind of a chase
in and out of the mountain,
voiding the Yeti, and then you come face to face with him.
And he is a gigantic animatronic
who is meant to swing and swipe at your car.
And in the Travel Channel special,
you see the programmer, you see Rody,
and you see this thing in action.
It is eerie. Unbelievable.
It is so surreal.
It looks like animation.
Is it 30 feet tall?
Like is it 30 feet tall, something like that?
Something like that.
Joe Rody is standing next to it,
and the scale of the hand, the claw,
like next to Joe Rody's head is staggering.
And yeah, it's like,
because I had never, it stopped working
by the time I went on it,
and seeing it in the special was actually
the first time I had seen it working in some capacity.
And it is like nothing robot-wise I've ever seen.
I don't think anything has come close to being him.
Trying to think.
It's so fluid.
So fluid, and the scope of it, the size of it.
The biggest animatronic imagineering ever made.
And it's, yeah, it's terrifying.
Like I almost, you know,
well, obviously I want it to swipe at me,
but I'm saying like,
oh god, I would have been so freaked out
with this giant robot,
which of course I want it fixed so it can swipe at me.
But yeah, it's terrifying.
Yeah, yeah, but at some point,
and maybe you guys know the facts,
I don't offhand, but it was pretty quick
into the operation of this thing, it stopped working.
I think it was on and off.
In the first two years.
It was on and off a little bit,
and then it just stopped.
Something like that.
I think it was around 2008 maybe.
Which, you know, as the recession is starting,
like Disney not exactly throwing money around on repair work.
At the 2013 D23,
Rodie said,
it's really hard to fix,
but we are working on it.
I was in the room for this at that D23.
Cause somebody, I remember somebody going,
when is the Yeti going to be fixed?
And he's like, I will do it.
You have to understand,
it's a giant complicated machine
sitting on top of like a 46 foot tall tower
in the middle of a finished building.
So yeah, so the problem with it,
that at least how I understand it,
is that they just,
for like, what they've done now
with the Navi Shaman of Song, for instance,
is you can pull the robot out if it needs maintenance.
They cannot pull the Yeti out.
It is built into the structure of the ride.
So whatever the problems are with it,
they would have to shut the whole ride down
and like rebuild the robot or something.
Like it's just, it's not easy to repair it
in its current state.
And some, and I bet the Disney number crunchers
might say, look at the line.
Do you see a problem with this?
Because what they did is that they,
the Yeti is there and the figure is very impressive,
but it doesn't really move and they flash lights at it.
And this is called the B mode,
or as fans have dubbed it online, disco Yeti.
Because lights are just flashing on it.
And I think the Disney argument is probably,
like the satisfaction with this ride
is still extremely high if we shut it down for a long time.
We aren't eating those people.
And like, are people complaining
beyond the fans who actually know what it's supposed to do?
And I see that argument.
However, now, having watched that,
yeah, it's incredible.
It's incredible.
We gotta get it going again.
I know he said periodically,
like I think maybe I figured out a way to do it,
but I think like the problem is,
is that whatever is not working on it is so bad
that I think it needs to like kind of be replaced,
but you can't take it out of the ride
without a massive amount of construction.
Now, eventually you'll hit like the 20 year mark
or something like 2006.
So we're at like 12, 13-ish years now.
So eventually you need to do major maintenance
on all these rides and shut them down
for an extended period of time.
And if I had to guess, that would be when they would do it.
Now, last summer, July 2018, someone said,
how about this Yeti?
Which I'm sure Joe loves hearing people say,
like what's the deal with the Yeti?
And he literally tweeted, we're still working on it.
Articles, people writing articles,
like the Yeti is being fixed.
And it's like, he literally said,
we're still, we're working on it.
Like that's it.
Like are people that hungry for clicks?
Like that, I guess so.
And also like clicks from how many people?
I guess a lot, I guess.
That's true, for how many people?
I guess we would click on it.
I'd be like, oh good, they're fixing it.
But like anytime he's asked about it
and he's pretty gracious, he's like,
yeah, it was an absurd undertaking
and it's not insane that it went wrong.
Yeah, it's so interesting.
These people are geniuses at making this stuff.
But then there'll always be something where it was like,
obviously this was a huge problem
because they didn't allow themselves
to have an easy way to fix it.
So you're like, oh, that seems like a crazy oversight.
Everything else is perfect in this,
for whatever reason they didn't figure out how to do this.
And then they learn the lesson
with a much smaller animatronic,
which is the Navi one on the river ride.
But then I don't know if you've heard,
I've got this from Jim Hill's podcast,
is that the problem with that ride now
that they're running into is that
the both Flight of Passage and the River Adventure
or whatever it's called, they're in the same show building.
They're on top of each other.
So if the fire alarm goes off on one,
they both have to empty the lines.
So that's another thing where you're like,
ah, these are geniuses.
And then there's this one thing,
which of course at the time they were probably like,
oh, it'll be so much easier.
It'll be one building.
And then no one ever thought of like, oh shit,
when the fire alarm goes off,
both buildings have to clear out,
which really is a big pain in the ass.
And people have booked their Flight of Passage
many months ahead of time.
That's how crazy this thing is.
Right, and people could have been in line
for Flight of Passage for two hours.
And because something went wrong in the other ride,
they have to evacuate the line.
I don't know if there's a system in place of them
giving them something to come back.
I don't know, but anyway, it's just interesting to hear,
there'll be one crazy oversight.
Everything else is almost perfect.
And then there'll be just one mistake.
Yeah, like 5,000 correct decisions.
Right, and then one that they never thought of.
Because they must have been like,
oh, this is a great idea.
We'll put them in the same building.
Because when you are doing unprecedented types of,
I think that's a thing that I really like about,
if a movie is having story problems,
you can look at other movies for inspiration,
you know how movies are generally supposed to go.
Or if a director drops out,
you can bring in another director.
Theme parks are every, I mean,
the really good theme park rides,
every one of them has never been done before
and to some extent will never be done again.
So how do you solve, how do you even think of the problem?
Right, exactly, how would you anticipate?
I mean, yeah, when we're saying like,
they thought of so many things,
how do they anticipate those 500 things
that could have gone wrong and they're fine with it?
And then the one thing, yeah, it is crazy.
Because yeah, ideally when you're building
one of these giant e-tickets, it's so original,
it's so interesting and creative
that the amount of challenges,
we don't even know, they're not documented.
There are weeks of just somebody going like,
oh shit, you know that thing we thought
was gonna be easy, it's impossible.
So let's fix it and then maybe that doesn't get documented,
they might even forget about it
because there's so many other terrible,
impossible things that they've overcome.
So it would be crazy to truly get a log of
from start to finish of everything,
not just the truncated version of going,
oh yeah, there's just a minor problem
with the paint for a month.
Right, right.
Because that stuff must happen all the time.
Like just these unglamorous, the unsexy problems too.
You see in the special that they wanted it to look like
there was snow blowing off the mountain
so then they had to figure out how to shoot mist out
so it looked like snow that was blowing in the wind.
I gotcha.
Yeah, so Yeti, I've heard like,
I think he was saying for a while
it seemed like they might be able to just sort of like
put a new arm on it or something
and like just sort of have the arm swiping
but it would be a different mechanism perhaps.
But I don't know if that's out the window.
I'm not sure where he's, we'll ask him obviously,
it'll be a 30 minutes of grilling rhodium.
What have you thought about, what have you tried?
Here's some ideas we have.
Yeah, but like I mean that,
I have to imagine it's frustrating that like you put some,
like you said, you put so much time and care
in all of this stuff and something goes wrong
and everyone just has the same stupid question
that they lose.
So Joe, we gotta ask, when are you fixing that Yeti?
It's like, cool, you're, like there were people that,
bless their hearts, the tour I was watching
where the Imagineers are showing them all this stuff,
there were clearly some knowledgeable-ish people
on the tour who was like, I have a very specific question
and the Imagineers were like, yeah,
I've been working at Fantasyland for about five years now,
getting that rebuilt, so I don't quite know the answer
to that or like, yeah, answering other people's questions.
So it's like, just if you're in a situation like this, folks,
be cool, be cool, play cool.
That's one that I don't,
having looked into this issue a little deeper,
I think I have sympathy for this whole Yeti issue
more than I did when we started.
And they pulled off an incredible ride
and even the Yeti itself is still very cool.
It's just not that one last.
Yeah, I mean, I'm trying to think too,
without the Yeti, it is still awesome.
Even if you took the robot out
and it wasn't ever part of it,
it's like, wow, what a great ride.
But yes, having a fully terrifying 30-foot Yeti
obviously would be the oomph,
the thing that really makes you go, wow.
But it'll be such an, when they do figure it out,
it'll be like, what a juice up of this thing.
When they added the fire effects to Big Thunder,
it'll be really exciting.
Everyone will be, and then it'll break in six days,
and then back to square one.
But they'll have hopefully figured out the system
to remove it or to fix at that point.
Although there'll be another problem they didn't anticipate.
Possibly, it's hard now too to take this down for too long
because anything you can do
to draw people away from Avatar
because the lines are still so long.
It would be nice if they open up another e-ticket
to Animal Kingdom, and then this could go down.
That would feel good.
But I don't think, this park honestly
is probably my favorite of the four right now.
I gotta get down.
I gotta see it with the new stuff and go on this ride.
It's all the things we've talked about.
It's like, this park ages the best.
It's an original park.
Interesting food and drinks.
It's interesting food and drinks.
It's just, the theming obviously off the charts.
Doesn't have weird vacant areas right now,
which all the other ones do.
And even if it does, it would probably obscure them.
Just because it's so filled with trees.
Beautiful foliage.
I could see if they ever, hopefully will.
But I think that may be in a lot of ways
this doesn't need it as much as the other parks.
So Everest will probably be open.
I don't know if there's any refurbishment on the schedule.
Yeah.
Probably not before the anniversary at least.
We were talking earlier,
we were recording another show about personnel on rides.
The person doing the Yeti Roars,
the voice actor, I think is very,
has very interesting theme park roles.
His name is Fred Tatasciore?
I am not sure how to pronounce the last name.
His theme park roles though include
Space Mountain Safety Narrator,
Star Tours the Adventure Continues,
he's a Gungan pilot.
And on Guardians of the Galaxy Mission Breakout,
he's Baby Groot.
Really?
Yeah.
Wow.
So Vin Diesel is not Baby Groot.
Apparently not.
He's the only one that didn't do the voice?
I guess, this says.
Cause I think they all are doing the voices,
or obviously.
I thought so, I mean the actors are.
Not they all, obviously the actors are doing
their own voices, it's not a different voice in their body.
But yeah, that was the credit.
He also has a lot of video game and animation roles too.
Cool dude.
Why can't I picture the Space Mountain?
What is the Space Mountain Safety?
Is he like the talking head?
Cause there's a guy in like the Space Mountain.
There's a guy in the queue.
Yeah, queue.
But I don't know if that meant Space Mountain
in Florida or Anaheim,
and I can't really remember Florida's.
Like Space Mountain is a, well whatever,
when he's explaining it in the video, I wonder.
Yeah.
I'm gonna look that up.
Oh it's that guy who's roaring a lot.
That's what it is.
Oh yeah, the roaring man.
I like a quick thing we didn't kinda mention,
is I like, much like on Splash Mountain,
there's kind of a fake out in the ride,
where it goes up and then you see the train shoot out of it.
So if you were just looking at the ride,
kinda like Splash Mountain where,
if you've never been on it before,
you don't know the geography,
so you might assume that that car is going in
and then pops right out the side.
Oh I see.
In the same way that I think Splash Mountain,
and I don't know if this is to be a fact actually,
is that once you go up and around,
you see the first drop.
And I would imagine if you've been on it,
you've never been on it before,
you might think that's the drop.
Oh sure, if you were all discombobulated, yeah.
And other being that other Flume rides are just,
you go up and then you come down.
Right.
So hiding all of the stuff inside.
Yeah and it's the same thing here,
where it's like all the stuff is hidden,
and I think that's kind of on purpose.
I think it's for sure on purpose,
because they mention in that special.
But yeah, if you looked at it,
you'd be like okay, I see, I go up,
I come out that thing, go around the side,
and that seems to be it.
But the whole fun stuff is inside.
You actually, they pointed out you spiral up that big,
to get to that lift hill, you kind of curve up the mountain.
Usually you spiral down on coasters.
So yeah, both that and Splash Mountain
really hide what's inside, which is awesome.
The other thing I found out,
I thought there was some sea reference.
I'm obsessed with Disney Society of Explorers,
I don't think there's any sea references in this line.
I think this was sort of before they were going
hall hog with the sea.
Or they were trying to focus on the authenticity reality.
So let's add some sea characters to this.
Let's bring it into the universe,
make it related so that it is part of the same,
adventures club and high tower.
Yeah, E Everest, what would his last name be?
No, it would be the Yeti.
Oh, the Yeti is a member of sea?
The Yeti's like the Hulk, he doesn't come out that often.
Oh wow, that's a whole new element
to see that there's monsters in the water.
Or it's Bob and, what was the other?
Norbu.
No, I'd rather have Yeti than Norbu.
Yeah, Bob and Norbu does not belong
in the adventures, or in sea.
No.
I heard a rumor that the new Soren in Tokyo
will introduce a new member of sea.
So how about that for a rumor?
Soren will have more of a story,
more of a backstory now?
Yeah, because it's different places.
And that a man named Patrick
is taking you on a plane ride?
Patrick A Soren.
What if it's just the emperor?
Of Japan?
Yeah, it's the emperor of Japan.
What if we tie together with the emperor's kiss?
Vi-fake attraction.
Another one of your most popular jokes from the podcast.
All right, I feel like you're not being 100% sincere
in what you said.
No, no, I am being 100% sincere.
Yeah, I think we'll tie it into the emperor's kiss.
If we were doing it.
But is the emperor in Society of Explorers and Adventures?
Feels like the emperor should be involved.
No, I think that's a conflict of interest.
Yeah, I think there should be a different club
that he should be a part of.
Another Disney shared universe club.
Heads of state.
Him, Teddy Roosevelt, Lincoln, Trump.
He's a head of state.
Is that a step?
All of the Hall of Presidents and the emperor.
And then who else is a president type in the parks?
I don't know, not off the top of my head.
Well, Mayor Jason.
Mayor Jason?
Mayor Jason, the princesses of Erin Dale.
Yes, I think that's right.
I guess all of the princesses do have jurisdiction.
They're all heads of state in a way.
Right, and they've all been, they all know each other
because we've seen it in Canon and the Wreck-It Ralph movie.
So just throw the other characters.
Well, they all know each other online,
but maybe not in real life.
They're like Twitter friends.
Yes, those are all their avatars.
Princess Vanellope did institute Medicare for all
for the Candy Crush Kingdom.
So she's done great things.
I mean, everyone needs it.
They're all using so much sugar.
She's kind of the AOC of...
Very much so.
Of the internet.
That's a good way to think about it.
Well, what else?
I don't know, it's just so good.
The ride is good.
We're talking about it.
I'm like, I wanna go on it right now.
Obviously, the plus up is have the Yetis dick
swinging around.
That's the plus up they can do.
You talk about separate mechanisms.
You could attach that.
It could be totally disconnected.
Circa Zong is the name of the mythical village
that you are visiting in the ride.
The actual location, if you type Expedition Everest
into Google, the first result is a Google Maps
like summary image, and it lists the Expedition Everest
location as Asia, Kisimi, Florida.
Yes, I saw that too.
That was fun.
Does it say Kilimanjaro or something too?
Or am I thinking of something else?
No, I don't think so.
But it's adjacent to Rafiki's Planet Watch train,
which recently closed.
I think it might open again though.
Oh really?
Yeah, that's another rumor.
That's a thing about Animal Kingdom.
It is in the southwest corner of the property
and can feel far away, but it's pretty close
to one or two of the hotels and Blizzard Beach,
but from the Magic Kingdom area, it feels far away.
Yes, that's true from there, but yeah,
depending on what hotel you're at,
it's not crazy out of the way.
Also, if you go two blocks away from Animal Kingdom,
you hit strip malls.
You hit Papa John's and Publix.
Well, and really close to that and Margaritaville.
The Margaritaville.
The village.
Which is pretty close to Animal Kingdom.
Oh, it's on that?
So I thought it was closer to like the other.
Well, when we go on it, maybe this year, altogether maybe,
we'll look for them, if we can see the Margarita Village
from the lift hill.
So I'll do my normal look,
but we'll look for those water slides and the.
Gas station directly beneath the water slides.
And yeah, all the beautiful houses and stuff.
So the real plus up we're looking for,
it's really up to the geography of Florida to give us this,
but we wanna be able to see some mediocre water slides
from this ride.
And until then, it won't truly be
the experience we're looking for.
Right, and hopefully it's not exactly in front of us,
in front of like on the other side of the mountain.
But we'll see.
Well, this will be an exciting thing to see
when we're there.
If we're there, if we go.
It's possible.
Yeah, I'd like to.
Yeah.
Well, we got expeditions ahead of us.
We do.
It's a hell, this is a very fun ride.
And hey, I just, the plus up I want is to go on it.
I'm really mad I haven't been on it.
You're in for a treat.
Yeah, it's been fun to talk about it regardless,
though my opinions hold no weight,
other than the pictures look very nice.
They're very nice.
And You Survived podcast, the ride,
thank you for joining us.
Hey, check us out on Twitter and Facebook and Instagram
and subscribe to the Patreon.
The second gate at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride
and the other specific commands.
I don't think we have any commands right now.
If you oddly have a back catalog of mansers,
do not scour through every episode
and try to find Mike Carlson at a bar.
Yeah, I mean, I could tell you what the segment is,
but I won't.
Maybe one of these days I'll tell you.
But it is, I will say that my parents,
I didn't tell them I did it.
And then one night at like 11 or midnight,
my dad woke my mom up
because he was just watching TV in bed.
He said, hey, look who's on TV.
And then it was the embarrassing segment.
Oh, come on, what are you doing?
What did your dad see you do?
Okay.
Yes.
Now what's interesting now, I wonder if anybody like
at the end of the podcast kind of like stops
when they go, okay, wrapping up podcast, the ride,
Patreon.
This is where the real hands.
They turn the podcast off.
It's possible right now.
People might have flipped it.
Half the audience is out.
They're just gonna plug their shit,
but we're getting a big revelation,
a big twist right at the end.
A big twist at the end.
So I didn't, my memory is that I didn't remember
what it was before.
I knew the pooping penis thing before,
but my memory is just sort of like,
there's a couple different segments you can come down
and do it, do any, well, we'll see on the day.
It's very casual.
And this is the first thing I'd ever been in professionally.
I went there.
I knew, I'm like, oh, it's a TV show.
They'll have hair and makeup and stuff.
And no, they won't have that.
I got there, I was wearing like a shitty
American Apparel green t-shirt.
That's what I'm wearing on the show.
No one even took a look at me to see,
because I remember my hair was a little messed up
and I was like, oh, I'm sure though,
they have a person to fix all that,
because this is a TV show.
And they did not.
So I'm sitting in this bar.
It was our bar, I believe, which is gone now.
Was it our, whatever, who, it doesn't matter.
It was a small shitty bar before it opened.
And I'm sitting just sort of in the booth.
There's a couple of other UCB guys I know.
And my memory is that the director or somebody goes,
all right, you, up here.
And I was like, oh, okay.
And then they walk over here.
And then somebody tells me that the man, sir,
we're going to be answering today,
is why should you never get a hand job from a British chick?
Jesus Christ.
You know this though, right?
No, I didn't remember.
I knew you were in one.
I don't think I, yeah, you must have told me that.
Maybe I didn't know.
They all have dirty Thames water on their hands.
So there's an actress,
like a model-y type lady.
She seems nice.
Very made up.
Very perfumed also is my memory of it.
And I am not given a script.
I'm not told anything ahead of time.
If you've ever seen the show Mansers,
most of what people do are bug their eyes out.
Yes, there's a lot of that.
A lot of mugging, a lot of that.
And circa 2008, reality TV production.
I think it's a little better now,
but still one thing has not changed.
The budgets are cheap.
Yeah, so.
The labor unions are not present.
Not present.
And it's a reenactment.
The lines are blurred.
It's hard to say what's going on.
It's in that reenactment zone.
So the director just says,
all right, so here's what's gonna happen.
And he's just like, believe it or not,
if you're picturing who directs Mansers,
that's what he looks like.
Believe it or not, you know, I'm sure.
Brett Ratner.
Yeah, I was gonna go with Ratner too.
100% this man looked like Brett Ratner.
He had a ponytail also as my memory of it.
And the kind of weight that is not
because you were born stocky, it's weight from drink.
Yes, it is, yes, it's Jack Daniels exclusively.
So my memories, he goes, okay,
so you guys are gonna make out for a while here.
And like, that wouldn't be comfortable to me.
Like now, Jason is showing me a picture
of a person we know.
We won't say who it is mugging for a Mansers bit.
So I wouldn't be like super comfortable with that now,
but I've been on a lot of sets and that sounds
like I'm bragging, but like I've been whatever.
It would be a little bit, but I'm fresh.
I'm 22 years old, 23 years old.
You don't know that screen actors guild
has certain regulations for like things like that.
Whatever, you're supposed to like give people a heads up
or something of what they're gonna be doing.
Is that okay?
You ask them, is that okay or whatever.
Oh yeah, the whole thing is making out.
Yeah, there should at least be in the email.
It should have been in the email.
It should have been before.
It should have been some warning of some kind,
even just like a PA walking over, hey, would you mind?
Just to say we need you to make out in a scene
and it is with a human woman, not with Minnie Mouse.
Yeah, because Minnie I would have been fine with.
It was a woman I was comfortable with, sure.
So I'm trying to remember exactly,
like this is almost 10 years ago.
You tried to black it out.
Yeah, I felt traumatized after.
The service of erasing this memory.
So my memory of it is that the woman
who was kind of not next to me at this point,
kind of on the other side of whatever the bar area,
like walked somewhere.
And then I saw a person come up to the director on the set
and he goes, what?
She has to make out with him.
She's an actress.
That's what she's here to do.
And they're having this conversation
and I'm just standing five feet away from this.
I'm like, this isn't a thing I'm supposed to keep.
Obviously she was like, I don't wanna make out
with this fucking loser weirdo.
It was you?
You were the problem?
Well, obviously the problem was the situation.
I'm just saying, she probably was like,
I don't know, what do we do?
I don't wanna do that.
I'm getting $120.
So he's so frustrated and he goes, well,
and then he just like throws up his arms
and he or the other woman, maybe both of them,
leave for a while.
And I'm just standing like under the shitty lights
with the camera people just like, so, I don't know what.
I'm like, what?
Like, well, get me, I don't wanna do this.
Like, I know this is a big mistake.
I don't wanna have to like, now somebody who doesn't,
I don't wanna do this either,
but this person is like saying she's not gonna do it.
Maybe she has the right idea
because he was like, fuck this thing.
She's talked into it.
Now you have to like, oh, this will be great.
Somebody who tried to leave.
Now we get to make out on camera.
So all that happens is she comes back on set
and then he goes, all right, we're ready to go.
And I was like, what?
There's no like, is it okay?
Is she gonna do, what is gonna happen?
I swear there's no talk, there's no rehearsal.
He just goes, okay, so here we go.
She's gonna be like kissing.
You guys are gonna be like kissing.
And then what's gonna happen is she's gonna like mime,
taking off, no, she's gonna take off your belt.
And then like, she's gonna like put her hand,
it's gonna be out of frame.
She's gonna put her hand like down there.
And then you're gonna smell shit on her hands.
Because the answer to the mancer
of why you should never get a hand job from a British chick
is that British chicks have poop on their hands.
All of them?
What?
Mary Poppins?
Yes, especially Mary Poppins.
She's got shit in that purse.
She's got shit in the purse.
When she's reaching in, what do you think's happening?
So, yeah, so.
Trump is our punishment for this,
for all the culture at law.
The cocky empire we all lived in.
Chickens coming home to roost.
Yeah, so, yeah, the answer, I guess,
this was based on some survey they took
where there was more fecal matter on British ladies' hands.
I don't know.
They did an unrelated survey of British women
and all the survey slips came back covered in shit.
Maybe this is something to investigate.
Overwhelmingly.
Next time we do a survey in England.
Soaked in shit.
Now I wanna know. Just paper soaked in shit.
Cause it seems like two directors directed most of the answers.
We're not gonna say a hand going to that.
I'm not gonna say their names.
No. You can look it up.
I wanna know if it was the director
who went on to work on House Hunters International episodes.
Or the director who went on to direct
something called American Guns.
There could be a good movie
or something called American Gun.
No, it's a television show about guns.
All right, well, we'll see.
Maybe those aren't the people.
Selling them to children.
Welcome to American Guns.
So this one's 500 bucks.
This one's cool as hell.
So what happens is there's no like,
we don't talk it over what we're gonna do.
There's no time to talk it over.
She just appears back on set.
The director goes, okay, let's roll.
Let's do this.
And I'm just so freaked out.
Cause I'm like, what am I supposed to do?
Like I'm supposed to.
No, that's not a healthy environment.
That's not a safe.
But any sets where someone feels unsafe, that's bad.
So I freeze up and the woman comes in
cause at first she was also,
the whole, a lot of these great scenes and skits
would be a very like nebbishy nerdy guy
and like a hot, like a beer commercial lady or something.
And that was this instance.
So it was like, she's gonna be like the aggressor.
So I swear we did maybe two takes.
It might've been one take.
She like walks up to me very half-assly
like puts her hands on my chest
and pushes me into the wall a little bit.
And then just puts her head by my neck
and just kind of goes up and down.
Yeah.
That's how you fake it.
That's how you cheat it.
Like.
Well, sure it is.
But I didn't know.
I also am like, this doesn't, this looks weird.
It can't look real.
But I'm still trying to be like, oh, I like this.
My face is like, I like this.
But this also, again, I want to stress
that this all happened within minutes.
So I haven't had a chance to recalibrate it.
I'm also very young and scared or whatever.
So she's like, her forehead's like hitting my neck
or whatever.
And I'm like, oh, and I'm like, this must be terrible.
And then she like does the belt.
And then I have to be like, oh,
like I have to make like a terrible face.
And now that I think about it, I think we did it twice.
And it just, I sat down and I was like, oh my, like,
it just felt, I had, I felt violated.
I felt like really fucked up about it.
Cause it was just so weird.
Like it was just, you felt like loss of control.
Obviously nothing really bad happened to me.
It was just such a mind fuck of an experience that.
Very, extremely tense.
Yeah.
So like I sat down and was like, oh my God.
And then a person we know was there and he's like,
hey, how was that?
Like that is pretty fun.
And at first I thought the person who said that was like
sympathizing with me.
Years later, I realized he was like, pretty good, huh?
Well, well.
And I won't say who that is either.
Jason.
You will when we stop recording.
I sure will.
But then to bring it back around,
you're trying to bury this from your memory
and from anyone knowing about it.
Yeah.
But your dad sees it.
So years later.
I don't even tell them.
Cause they reran this show.
Yeah, for years.
That was the thing.
I wanted to do it and strangely now I realized
this would have been terrible to do.
But by the time, I probably watched it in 2010,
watching three years old episodes of Mansers.
Were you going to spring it on me in a specific way,
like on a podcast or something,
or you just wanted to see it when you were looking for it?
I don't, I just wanted to see it.
I don't know.
There was no sneak attack.
I've seen it, cause we know other people who've been on it
and I've like, oh shit, that's so and so.
Jason's gonna look it up again.
I think I've searched in the last year or two
and it used to be able to,
you could see it on the Spike TV website.
Cause the big thing that you need to know,
but that I needed to know at the time was,
this is non-union and there's no thing
that says they can't run it forever.
So cool, so you're getting taken advantage of.
Yes.
It's a tent set where you're being barked at
and made to mate out with strangers
without asking if it's okay.
Right, or even a time, just a minute to talk,
go like, oh hey, sorry, this is weird.
Any preparation or reversal, anything.
No, nothing.
But this is on TV.
It's on TV, so yeah, a couple years in,
cause I think, I don't remember even the year.
It might've been 2009, it might've been 10 years ago.
But yeah, I think like in 2011 or something,
my mom called me and was like,
I was sleeping in bed, your dad was watching TV
and he woke me up and he goes, hey, look who's on TV.
And I think my mom just did one,
like a very mom thing of like, it was interesting
or it was okay and didn't say what it was.
And I was like, oh my God.
Cause I was hoping they hadn't seen it
because I didn't say anything about it
and it's really two minutes or something.
Have you found it?
Well, I haven't found the video,
but I found that they were talking about it
on the Bungie message boards, the software company,
and also the website I've heard about before,
bodybuilding.com was also talking about this.
Yeah, that's a web.
I've come across that.
A source of some very odd internet paraphernalia.
I'm sure it'll be like repackaged somewhere.
Okay, great.
All the managers and that'll show up
on a streaming service somewhere.
That'll be a big deal.
Hopefully Disney Plus, some merger will occur.
Oh my God.
Well, if you stick around past the credits,
you really got a nice treat here today.
Wow, what an epilogue to this episode
about a very nice one.
I'd also like to say that the Yeti Museum
was curated by Professor Pima Dorje.
Just to get us back on track.
Okay, and now we can say,
you've survived podcast the ride.
Expedition Everest edition and only expedition.
Nothing else weird on this episode.
Yeah, no bizarre upsetting confessions occurred.
I liked that.
That was like a little Andy Cohen after show.
We got into some salacious stuff
now that you're losing.
I would love it if we all took turns being the bartender
on Watch What Happens Live.
If this show got us to be like, you know.
Well, maybe we'll be like,
we could be on the network with Andy Cohen
and we'll follow him.
We'll do a show.
We'll do a theme version of his show,
but it's all theme park.
Hey, Jax, Jax from Vanderpump,
what do you think of Dumbo?
Yeah, which row are we talking in Credit Coaster, huh?
Are you a fifth row guy or more of an eight?
Sounds like a good piece of television, right?
Yeah, it'll be interesting.
I'll say that.
All right, hey, now we've done it.
Hey, I already said all the stuff.
You know what to do.
All right, hey, if you have any questions,
we'll try to give you mansers.
On our Twitter, hit us up.
All right, folks, talk to you next time.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
Forever.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.