Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains salacious details of Disneyland cast member 2 timing,
Wayne Zelinski's hunky son, and, if you asked for it, step-by-step details of the 3D glasses
sanitization process.
If the waddy way joins us to talk, Pista, or as the uninitiated might know it, Honey I
Welcome to Podcast The Riot, the only theme park podcast that will promise you at least 45 minutes of discussion on the Disney parks
Exclusive Eric Idle character, Dr. Nigel Channing. I'm Mike Carlson. Joining me as always Jason Sheridan. Hi and Scott Gardner
Yep, it's finally time to 45 minutes. I think is what we're gonna give to him
Uh-huh a lot of thoughts on dr. Nigel Channing and he factors into several attractions
How many characters can say that they're in more than one? That is very exciting
We were talking a lot about see Disney Society of explorers and adventurers
Which they have like like kind of connecting universe, but this did it before see this this ride
We're talking about today this character the imagination Institute
Yeah, world
expanded universe with II
you
Is very fleshed out? Yeah
He is an expert on this in many different ways
I
He seems surprised
What I said, but that's okay, I believe it in my heart
You know from the comedy group white women and the podcast nerd efficient ladies and gentlemen if he waddy way. Hey, how's it going?
Good. How you doing? Good. So you're particularly qualified today to talk about honey. I shrunk the audience
Yes, and why is that would you tell our listeners?
I'd say
for the year of
2007 I worked for Disneyland
Yeah, Disneyland the one in California the the only one that Walt has stepped foot in so
He has the magic right and I worked on honey. I shrunk the audience in Astro orbiter
I was there for the launch of Nemo and so I've got the suit and
You know, I was real loose with some of the rules because technically you're not supposed to wear your cast member outfits outside
But like I I thought the coat was so cool for the Nemo ride
So I took it like to one of improv show and like wore it on stage and everyone was like you look like Paddington Bay
Which would be very fashionable now because people love those movies they love it now, but this is back
This is when he was just in the books. Yeah
So yeah, and then let me see I never got to work Space Mountain everyone went to work for if you don't know
Space Mountain is like the cool Tomorrowland ride. Everyone wants to work space
I don't want that. Yeah, because it's it's the cool one and everyone loves sitting in the control room
So like when you wave at them and someone doesn't wave back
That's the one trying to be too cool for school like everyone when I when I was there
It was like Space Mountain was the git but that made it harder to get it right honey. I shrunk the audience Astro orbiter
I don't know how people I feel like no
Honestly like the jobs are kind of ranked how you imagine the cooler the ride the cooler the job is
So because you want to be working the cool ride, you'll probably have more people there Astro orbiter
Surprised me because I assume like oh no one's gonna be there
but Astro orbiter was pretty consistent in its like
Lines like people like it's it's still one of the quickest lines out of all the rides in tomorrowland
But like people would come for it and there are people who would come and go this is my favorite ride and I was like, okay
Like I'm not on your side even though I work this right were they older folks
it was like it was like
Middle-aged folks. Uh-huh. Yeah, so
Yeah, yeah, that's what I imagine
people always
would try and weasel in a way to try and like get you to talk about the people mover and more so trying to see if
You can get me to talk about the people who died on the people mover. Oh, right jumping from car to car
Yeah, it's like I one I don't know about that too. I was not working here that long three even if I did come on
Y'all know it's Disneyland. I'm not gonna talk about dead people
So so growing up as a kid like was that Disneyland a place where you were like, it'd be fun to work here
It was just like hey, why not? I'm no it's so I grew up out here in Southern, California and
Got there probably when I was like
1920 and like it just was known as like Disney is the easiest place to get hired
Like there's such a high turnover rate
They're like you need a job go to Disney and I think like I really need a job my best friend Wells and was like
Oh go to Disney
They'll hire you on the spot because they do their interviews and hiring like right there as a matter of fact if they're like
We'll call you back. You didn't get the job
So like so I was like, oh tight this I need a job it's very easy to get a job here
Let me go work Disney this thing we described as the dream
So, yeah, I went in and and like the key to Disney getting a job at Disney is exactly what you think just being like
you know a happy, you know perky person a
About you where you know you can because that's all the conversation is they're asking you about yourself and they're really just gauging like
how you can like
communicate while conveying like a happy attitude because the people who I saw got
Will call you later were people who were like very like here's why I'm good very busy, you know
business-minded and you know
People who like by Disney standards you assume they think they're ne'er-do-wells
Like there was a guy with like who was tatted up and I was like, you know, have you been to Disneyland?
I get it, but I'm not he was like now I'm gonna be in a costume like that. That's my goal. Oh sure. Yeah
So yeah, so I got the job there
and it's funny because like it's the perfect job for that age like that that like
18 to 20 because you're very malleable at that time. So like when they give you that like
Orientation pitch about creating the magic and how important it is you you buy in I was like all about it
I was like I got to create the magic and this that whatever and I was like all in I got I was so hyped
When I had the job that I went to what was that weird online game?
Disney had for a while where you were in the digital park. Oh, oh was it online or was it a CD-ROM?
No, it was online. It was like an online flash based
It was a massively online game where you would go to the different lands in every and it was like a
Park so they had adventure land tomorrow land and they had all these different levels based off of the rides
And I was so stumping us here
Signed up for an account and was just walking around the park and just like I need to learn this place
Virtual Magic Kingdom, yes
I was like, okay, cool
I'm like, okay, cool. Let me just get it and then I started and
Honestly Hista is for short which is honey
I shrunk the audience was the perfect spot for someone like me who was like a comedian because
Like I like they showed me the actual order stuff and I was like, alright cool
This is basic stuff and then they were like, alright
So for Hista you're gonna when you are the like lead scientist when you put on the coat you put on the lab
Coat. Yeah, you're in the lab coat and you go up there and you give the spiel and they basically were like you can kind of
Do what you want and improvise stuff. You just need to make sure you hit these points and I was like
Oh, I get to just go up there and be funny as long as I hit the point
That was like my favorite thing cuz I would just like and then also like it was cool too because it wasn't just from my comedy
Brain, it was like the comedy brain and indoctrinated by Disney brain
It was all about not just being funny but making it like a magical experience
So I still to this day think I was probably one of the best like head scientists
I believe I just you know one if you don't know by now, I'm a great comedian but two
Two I was like really committed to like not, you know breaking the bubble of what is Disney
So you have to know the mythology that you you're it's in your head that it is an open house at the imagination
Institute. Oh, yeah, and you were coming at it from that narrative point. Yeah, and what's an example of like?
Like what is something you do beyond just here walk this way? Oh, well when you're a head scientist
Yeah, you you don't let anyone in you are at the podium and you walk up to the podium and you're just like we're about to
have a presentation from
So what's his name? What is the character's name in the honey? I shrunk the out of Wayne Zelinski or dr.
Channing yeah
Channing is presenting an award to dr. Right the letter of the year award
Yeah, it was like this is gonna be great and he's gonna showcase this new
This new invention he has it's really exciting. We haven't seen it yet
It's the first of its kind and and you just we got to make sure we have the safety goggles cuz we don't know what may
Happen but this is this is history in the making y'all get excited and like making people cheer
It was it and and I I had a blast I had a lot of people come up to me
It's like man. I've done like this ride
I was like I've seen this before but like you have or have the best feel
I I do find like it that show kind of things like that when the cast member is really good when the presenter is really
Good and the thing is over. I inevitably lean over to whoever I'm with and go like that guy was really good, right?
There there's a guy there's just a profile on him a guy who's worked at the enchanted tiki room for years and he like
Gives it a hundred and percent waking up those birds that I have seen him before and it's like
Yeah, it does. It does add to the experience. It does make it feel very theatrical
It's it's also it's only it's also the only thing that can change slightly from ride to ride like a from
experience to experience cuz like
You know like like us we've gone a few times to these things
So like that's the deck can be like the difference in just like a normal ride versus like, oh wow
That was really great. And now I remember this particular ride over the other 50 you went on because
The performer Lord knows these movies
Run the risk of becoming very repetitive because it is literally the same thing over and over
So you have the slight it's almost like being a like an audience warm-up guy at a show date
Or like the host of the stand-up show the guy like keeping the energy up. Yeah, just set it up for the main show
That's that's something else
so you did it for
for a year for a summer yeah for about a year because I was I was there for a while and
Eventually my dad got me my day my day job, which was at the LA County Register recorder
which was right around the perfect time because
like I said
there is that period of like from like 19 to 20 where it's good and then like
Once the kind of like dust starts to settle the rose-colored glasses come off
you you you realize some of the stuff that just gets annoying like just that the
Kind of bottom-level infrastructure is basically run by kids like all your supervisors are not that much older than you
So it gets clicky it gets you know, everything it's almost like, you know college or high school part two
and and like the supervisors like when you're
Forget the the actual name again
But it's like they're the dudes in like these black
kind of pea coats and they they don't have anything that discern them working for a specific ride because they are
Even over your the the ride lead so you have your cast members
you have kind of the shift lead and then you have the like lead over the ride and then there's like
The leads who are over the whole land who kind of like mostly work in an office that you'd never see that's in the
Backlot area and those guys like they have that black pea coat
So even if you don't know who they are you you you know that there there's big stuffs and they know it too because if
You're a 20 year old in this pea coat and you know, you have this power. They're flexing, you know, so
So there was a immediate shift when I got my day job because I still like Disney and I like to have in a free
cast so I tried to like I was working for the LA County from like
Nine to five and then getting to Disneyland at six to work
I like literally driving down the five because I was in Norwalk. So it was pretty close to Anaheim
changing into my cast member outfit and
driving that and I was in and this
Obviously caused me to be late a little bit more my out like that hour
Especially during the week like only having like three hours really isn't worth the shift
But like I was able to make it work for a while
but my whole attitude changed like all all that bullshit was just
didn't matter to me because I
Knew that I got paid way more than everyone now because I have this like salaried government job
so like and and it's funny because that's where the power came comes from in any job is like the person who gets paid more you're
Like oh you're you're talking good. So I just I don't want to say I became the worst
But I definitely
Shift like shook the ecosystem because like people being like oh man watch out because you know, they're here
It's like I don't care like yeah, it's just like and I've always hated that kind of like high school BS, but I
respected it because like I
before I had another job needed that job and like also did enjoy and love working at Disneyland
But that was the one thing I hated was that kind of like hierarchy that was there
And so the moment I was able to step out and be like, oh, I don't need this and I know that I'm
Making more than all of y'all. Nah, forget y'all. You're not good. And honestly, it just like it made it cool
But it just became I was dead at the end of the week just working two jobs back-to-back
Yeah, really not making any money because I wasn't working enough at
Disneyland to like make it worth my while I was just really there for this free pass and it was like I could just
buy an annual pass
Like I worked at Universal Studios and I kept I stayed on the schedule and tried to not get shifts
So that I could park up there for free. It was entirely about keeping the parking
Yeah for a place. Well, I mean now we've we've ended up going to City Walk a ton. Yeah in the recent past
I'd like to have it now. It's oh
It's crazy to see the actual shift because remember they were giving out annual passes you brought a Coke can you were king?
Universal and now they refuse because they have Harry Potter and voodoo doughnuts
I'm like, oh y'all are just out of this. It was so funny. They swung too far too fast
Yeah, they're like you're not gonna be able we're gonna shut down Lancashire
There's gonna be so many people and then there was a slight uptick for Harry Potter and then everyone went back to their lives
Yeah, because we all just like live around like there's homes right next to it. I know it's it's they they have a decent
Annual pass right now with AAA where it's like 119
Oh, yeah, and then like I was like that's pretty close to like just a day ticket, right?
That might be the move for me, but I haven't I've yet
What's the room's consensus on the Simpsons ride we haven't talked about it. We haven't done an episode on it
Yeah, oh do we just stay to specific?
This is a comedy podcast we don't stay specifically
My feeling is I I really liked it the first time I went on it
but I think a joke packed ride is tough to
Stay good and fresh many many times over and they were letting the
projection quality lapse it was starting to get dim and
I just I think it came out of the gate really strong and now about ten years in I don't need to go on it
What have they read they did screens are different like they it's brighter now, right? I think they changed it
It's what I was early change spot. Yeah, the problem is I feel like it's the all the other rides that have been built since
Because everything's a screen ride everyone complains about that obviously we've complained about it, but it's like everything's a screen right now
So like that one seems extra
Okay. Yeah, I don't we don't need to go on it. I'd rather go on transformers. Oh my god better train screen ride for sure
Oh wait, I love transform. I was look
that was a real journey for me because you know, I've never been a fan of
Transformers I was real into Armada right when the movie series came out
I hated the design of the robots. I haven't seen a Transformers movie today except bumblebee, which is amazing
And I just always had this disdain for Transformers and my sister drug me on the Transformers, right and it changed my life
I was I was rooting for optimists for bumblebee
I was in it and I go on that ride every single time to date
I have not been on the Simpsons ride because I'm still salty of them getting rid of back to the future
Reason there was no reason to change it. It's timeless. I gotta say I think it's literally not timeless in that
That you in that ride you go to the year 2015 and we are now past 2015
So it would be I mean you could say that it's traveling to the past
Yeah, but into this other this 2015 back to the future because the future to them and we're going back to it
Makes more
You know they hacked a system with that name
We actually we talked about this and we I think we were thinking like let's just do a new one. Yeah cuz
My feeling was like I love the old back to the future
But we want to see this some of the characters we want some robots with the characters
Let's do a full new e ticket in this new crazy Universal Park. I don't think it's gonna happen
But I want I want Strickland and I want you want needles
Yeah, we want these character needles from back to the future to to be a robot
That's what we want people are pounding down the yeah universal demanding needles
I'll say this I think the the Springfield next to the Simpsons ride. Oh, it's amazing is great
Yeah, it's my favorite part. It's the only reason I'm not like
So militant about it is because those donuts slap they are great
So hard we are like look I'm on my keto thing right now
I was in the bathroom debating going to fud Ruckers or steak and shake
But since I don't have it with a bun steak and shake feels like I should just get a steak versus going to
Fud Ruckers. Yeah an actual burger bun. That's a weird side. No, no, I get it. Oh, these are issues
I'm ready because we're going on a team outing for BuzzFeed to
Universal and
I'm a hundred percent ready to break keto to eat that big donut because that's my favorite thing to chomp into when I go
So is that your favorite theme park snack overall? Would you put it number one? Is there anything else dole whip?
Do you like dole whip? Oh, I'm a big dole whip head, but don't whip is that thing where you know where it's like
It's consistent like like it's not something
I'll lose my mind over like if I had to run into Disney and I could only choose one snack
I wouldn't think to get a dole whip, but I I do think it is the best
But like I went to Disney during the Halloween and I got
probably
Six different churros because they had the
Yeah, yeah, cuz I had the candy apple and the orange I had the the pumpkin spice
I had the regular churro and then I had that red hot one. No
That one's pretty good. There's one more that I think I'm missing. So I think I had this many
Where are all these coming from? Where are they at Disneyland?
The they're all around now. Did I say sour apple? Yes. Yes, you did. Okay. Sour apple is in Tomorrowland
pumpkin spice was in right next to a haunted mansion and I got the regular churro there the orange one was in
adventure land and
And there was one I think in fantasy land. Maybe that's where the red hot one was
How are these flavors conveyed? Is it through the the dusting or
Okay, so so the sour apple which I think is like was probably the best out of all the newer flavors because
With that one they dusted on like a sour apple
Dust like sugar on it, but you dipped it in a caramel
So it was like a caramel apple and it actually did like taste like that
Then with the pumpkin spice it was like cream cheese frosting that you would dip into
Yeah, the only thing though is you have to pay extra for the caramel the cream cheese came with the pumpkin spice
Which you know, that's weird. Yeah, that's weird that that's not
That made me mad, but I still paid for it. The orange one was cool, but it was just kind of like just orange
Yeah, so so small. So I was gonna say I had a s'more one one time. That was good
No, that is a dipping like marshmallow. So yeah
So churro over Dole Whip, but does put Simpson's pumpkin or Simpson's pumpkin Simpson's donut is that top?
I'm getting make my flavors mixed up here. Oh
That's good
I think it may be my top because it's something that because I feel like all those other amazing ones like a dole whip is
When I'm walking by the tea rooms, oh, yeah, these are amazing. Let's go or like a churros like oh, yeah
These are amazing
but like I am actively thinking about those big donuts because I feel like for the price it has the value and
Has the size and as it because you know this big enough to wear like if I split in half with someone
I wouldn't feel ripped off because no number one. I hate sharing food, you know us in here with significant others
They like to share I don't I need my own get your own
We'll both have our own and when you don't finish yours because it's too big for you
I'll have that too Lindsay is like that but I'm not really so yeah the other way around
Yeah, I was like, hey, let's go split this. She goes no. All right. She's right. She's actually same with Aaron. Yeah, really?
Yes, that's funny. I don't like to split entrees
I like to share on trade you like to share yet just oh, let's just get one and we'll split and I share
Well, that's actually otter to me you share entrees but not like dessert. No, I'll share dessert
No, you share dessert with me. We've both shared desserts
We've both you and I and you and Jason and I and Scott and I have both shared the gray stuff in different times
Yes, but then Jason has also eaten after me Jason. I pretty sure ate soup after me once
Like yeah
Soup the soup was everything I was on board to the soup
I don't think I remember someone's I'll finish most because I could be wrong
I think he had a bit was like a biscuit the Jolly Holiday or something and I kind of like had a little bit of
It and I was like I had a couple spoons of it and you were like, yeah, I'll take that
That's my memory of a couple spoons and you were like, I'm not into this like yeah, whatever
Yeah, it depends like if it is a couple of spoons then yeah, I'll do it
It's like, you know past halfway point I'm like nah, that's that's that that's not
I imagine the remaining two
Spoonfuls of like tomato soup or something. That was what I went to and I agree. Oh, oh with more information
I understand it. Yeah, it wasn't. Yeah. Yeah, that would have been very weird if I was like, hey
I got like a a little thimble full of tomato bisque you want it? Yeah
I mean that I would because that would be so novel to enjoy
Where the thimble comes from my cabinet in his pocket the Disney provided was it a cup that got shrunk down by dr
Wayne's a lint ski to a
Hey everyone, it's Michael I'm breaking in to tell you about my favorite meal delivery service, it's called Hello Fresh
Achieving your goals in 2019 is easy as enjoying delicious home-cooked meals with Hello Fresh
Hello Fresh makes conquering the kitchen in 2019 a reality with delicious simple recipes
They do all the planning shopping and prepping so you can focus on enjoying this new year and a healthier you
Okay, you get fresh pre-measured ingredients and easy to follow instructions. It's like a six-step pictured recipe cards
They're delivered to your door. It's very easy to follow along. I like books with pictures and it's easy
It's made for people that maybe don't have the most cooking experience like me your host Michael
Alright all meals come together in 30 minutes max
Call for less than two pots and pans and require minimal cleanup all of that sounds great
Doesn't it now there are three plans to choose from classic veggie and family with the option to switch between
For when your tastes change you can change it up. Maybe you want family. Maybe you want to go vegetarian
You do whatever you want folks. It's up to you. Alright now folks
I like the chicken pesto very easy. Very simple very classic
I made it it doesn't taste like I made it. It tastes like a chef made it. It's pretty incredible
All right
Now here's where you guys come in if you want to take advantage of this special HelloFresh offer
Get $80 off your first month by going to hellofresh.com slash theme park 80 and enter theme park
80 you are going to be very glad you did remember hellofresh.com slash theme park 80 and enter theme park
So
I'm gonna just say this one anecdote then we're gonna jump right back into hista because there's something
I love bragging about that. Oh, yeah Disney people care about place
Jolly holiday had a good Halloween
Dessert too. They had like a black rose, which was this chocolate mousse
That was just black and it was good, but it was one of those things that felt like
too decadent for where I was like too decadent for
The theme park food really like this feels like I should have it at a restaurant restaurant
But I feel like that's kind of what Jolly Holiday not Jolly Holiday. It's the one that's in Fantasyland
Oh, oh your guest. Oh the red rose red red rose red rose tavern
Yeah, I had red rose feels like they're trying to swing for that fancier vibe
But I'm like, no, this is still too fancy for here, but it was it was good. Yeah
Now the thing I want to brag about
Always bring up I could not shut up about this when this happened
I knew Captain EO was coming back when because in the
Original like tour and orientation of hista there they show us like oh, this is the room where where the
The film is where we shoot it and they kind of showed us how the camera works
They're like you can't go in here. It's like and also
We also still have the Captain EO film and and this was back in like
2007 and I was like, oh
They're just gonna play it when he dies like when he dies they're gonna bring it back
Like why would you keep it? He was like, we don't know and sure enough like
Captain EO came back and I was like I knew it like I knew it the moment you were like
Oh, and we still have the Captain EO films
I was like great and I never got to see Captain EO when I was younger
So I was so glad I was able to go back and watch it and actually see it
Would you that's it's also weird that you were thinking about his death
But it's sort of a surprise when it happened. Yeah the year before you're I mean, I didn't expect it to come that fast
When he it was kind of like when he happens to die they're gonna bring it back
But we're saying when so when it when they did put it back in it was the original Prince
Presumably if that was sitting around. Mm-hmm. Damn. So that it wasn't even like some it wasn't some remastered
No, because it was very like analog poppy like grainy grimy
So yeah, hmm, you could tell you could tell and that's like in some just giant like you did you see it physically?
Or did they know it was like a mystery room almost because the film room and I didn't get to actually see the camera
There was kind of like, you know how in the movie theater, they'll have that kind of window and they get you
But like the room itself was locked and probably so some dumbass doesn't go in there and make it be so funny
So shine a flashlight over the whole thing. So like that yeah, that was completely off limits to us
Huh? Do you have any idea how big like talking?
Honey again, like how big that film was is that a regular thin little film stripper is some bigger like IMAX?
It was it was kind of if I remember correctly which I'm probably not I remember it being like it was like a different
Type of film because it was displaying like
Doubled images. Oh, okay. Yeah, right. Oh, so this is not your ordinary
Yeah, which makes it even more insane. There's I talked about this on it. It's probably won't be out yet
Or maybe there's a mailbag episode. I was talking about my cockamamie plan to propose to my wife
with a
Custom video I would make and play in this theater
This is a good way to practice a good person to talk to about this actually
I was like what if I could make make a little move that you think Captain EO is gonna start but then it's this little
Movie I make that culminates in will you marry me? Yeah. Yeah, and now I'm going well
How could I possibly have made something and run it through a film projector?
Yeah, that displays double image. I would have had to go to an optical lab
I would have had to like go
Talk to the people who shot the back to the future movie and like okay, so can we print it like I'm now I'm
Spending sixty five thousand hours a conference call with marketing operations and representatives of the Kodak company
Figure out how to do this
Is there any like when I present that plan to you you're like that you if this had been in?
2007 you're a person who would have like helped me with it. Is that completely insane?
The idea that I could have contacted more money than the engagement ring and probably the wedding
Why did I think I'll let you wear the lab coat and at the end say will you marry?
Like whoa glad the day is saved. Thank you so much and to my beautiful girlfriend in the audience
My colleagues has an addendum to what you just witnessed
If you'd like to join me in the the Institute of Eternal Matrimony
So you would have done if I had good now if I just gone straight up to you
You're you're an employee with some power, but I could like hey I have a thing
I want you you would you have had to run that up the flagpole
you I probably would have had to run it up the flagpole and I probably would have like
When I first started probably would have asked my lead who probably would have been like
But if you would have caught me late in my Disney career
I would have told you come back towards the end of my shift and then we'll make it
Norwalk money, I don't give a shit
also to like you you know like which leagues will let you do some like
Cool stuff as long as we keep it chill and which leads are trying to be by the book
So I'd be like, all right
Cool leads here and was like I'm gonna do some because like the only I think hiccup to it would be like
Like once we're letting people out we're letting people in like it's almost like simultaneous
So you would literally slow down that process?
But it would probably just be something as simple as being like all right
There's an extra presentation if we just step outside to the right. I
Okay, you can get her attention on the microphone and then all right
All right, so it's gonna be done with precision and you would been in the lab coat. I assume yes. Yeah
Which this is oh, it's a very different dream now the idea that I yeah, I'm sure
I'd love to
Institute professor it started out as like a cool movie playing in the Captain EO theater
Now it's like you're outside at the exit
Halloween adventure quality white like people are like just trying
to get by
Excuse me
They're reaching over you to dump their glasses
Although now 2018 if you reached out to like social because they have such a huge social media apparatus
At Disney now if you reached out to them and we're like, hey, let's talk like yeah
You can you do whatever you want with this video?
Like you can make this viral you can make this into a convert whatever you want
You would have to you would have they would have to be viral marketing for right? Yeah
Yeah, I have no desire for my proposal to be viral marketing
Now we know the terms I you were talking about food also. I want to ask about what's what was the what was the food situation?
As an employee there is a cafeteria or you slipping in getting food in the park. You can do either
Okay, so you there there is a cafeteria in the back which is like
It's like cafeteria food like they're not like whipping up what they're whipping up in the park
so there are but like it is gonna be cheaper whereas if you wanted like park food like it was like
Gosh, I'm trying to remember if I'm misremembering this
But if I remember correctly you were able to because the one spot is like if you wanted a burger
you can go to that Tomorrowland burger spot by Nemo and
But it was like the employee discount with a park food was still more expensive than cafeteria food
Oh sure
Yeah, I mean
Off kind of retrospect. It's like why didn't they just feed their employees for free?
like I know there's a shit ton of employees, but like
It's like why why were we buying our food?
And I think it's because now I'm in an age where I work for tech companies that do feed you for free
And it's like it's like yeah, why are we paying you to eat on our lunch break? You know?
Well, it's a perk. It's a perk and it's like, you know
To get people in the door it's an added benefit. Yeah, but with a company that makes how much money sure why not? Yeah
Yeah, yeah, being that like a Facebook or whatever has a cafeteria or like Dreamworks
Yeah, like that they have just a cafeteria if you're on that lot, right Disney. I don't think so. I think Disney you're paying for
Yeah, yeah, Disney. I um, I was like that ABC lot
I went in there and they had like a cafeteria you pay the comment
I guess some some jobs you do pay so it's not that obscene
There's subsidy all the studio commissaries are like a little subsidy like they're not terribly expensive
Yeah, yeah tech campuses that there's an expectation with the job that or people are being fed and I think in San Francisco
Restaurants were even having a hard time getting head chefs or sous chefs
Because Google or Facebook or all these campuses were just snapping them up. Oh, yeah
and I think it's because and I think that's why I kind of see the correlation is the
Idea behind tech companies feeding you is if you can just walk to a cafeteria and grab food for free and walk back to your desk
You're working there and I feel like it is literally impossible to leave Disneyland
To grab something to eat and come back in time to be your shift
So you have to be there which is why it's like then just feed us free food
Like don't you know we have no choice but to buy this food because there's nowhere else
Well, I guess you can bring your own lunch, but who does that?
Yeah, it's like being on set
It's like that's why they feed you on shoots and stuff because they don't want like the cast and crew
Going to a dozen different restaurants. Yeah, there's act traffic or an accident or like no. Yeah, but
But it was cool. The food was great. I always loved doing it, but it was this thing of like since you are
buying cafeteria food on a
Like a little bit higher than minimum wage budget you can very easily just be burning through the money
You're making right buying food there. Yeah, it's all good
It was how close did you live to Disney?
Like how long did it take you to actually get into work this I lived in Long Beach at the time
Okay, but Long Beach is very close to Anaheim in Orange County
So I was I would just take the four or five straight down and be able to hit it pretty quickly
So it was cool and you get to you know
K lot the cattel lot and just take the shuttle over but there that was a thing where it's like
you have to be there so much earlier because there's so much transportation because you have to get there and
Even though it wasn't that far you still have Anaheim Disney traffic
Yeah, and when you get to Kayla you have to wait for the shuttle take the shuttle in and then go backstage
And then make it to your land. So you had to make sure you you had to like be
In the parking lot probably like 15 20 minutes early just to be safe, you know, and you're not getting paid for that time
I know not at all and that's all that heads up
The clutch move is like to just go to the park on your workdays and just like, you know
Check in go in hang out at the park and then walk backstage when you're ready to go
But you can't just walk backstage
You have to walk out and go in through the employee entrance because it's all about keeping the magic up, right?
Weird and magical in the like corridors. Did you ever see?
like so some others some like secret prop or
Captain Captain Hook having a seizure or something
Was like on my first week working there
The first thing I see backstage is Mickey Mouse smoking a cigarette with the head off and I was like, alright
Well, the magic has changed for me forever
Now you always hear that was a thing that scarred Michael Jackson was he got to go backstage at Disneyland
Around the corner and a character had the head off a cigarette. I think he was old though when that scarred him
Yes, no, he had a number of hits said it was 80 late 80s
It is like just so jarring because you when you think about it all your life up until you that point
You've never seen the character with your head off. So you've never had to even
Bounce around that suspension of disbelief like you knew there was a person there, but you never had to see it
So seeing it it's like oh man and also like
Realizing that a lot of these people are hella short because these suits are so small go on. Yeah
Yeah, I would be unnerved though if I went out to get a picture with a character and go like how this goofy really smells like
smokes today
No, they wrote they're really good about like cleaning. Yeah, they for breeze the outfit before they go back out, right?
But yeah, that was like those were the big jobs are like your character jobs and those like speaking of the clickiness backstage is like
you know if you're in the cafeteria and you see like Cinderella or snow right or any of the
Princesses like you don't get to just go talk to him like, you know, I'm sure you can but no one does that
There's just like this unspoken rule of like oh, that's a that's a princess and usually like the princess are chilling and like they're
With each other or just by themselves
The hierarchy could you even identify the groups?
Like is it a mean girls scenario where you could be like there's the princesses over here. There's tomorrow land people over here
like yeah, because like the the hierarchy was of fairly
fairly simple split up to your factions which were
which were like
Like your lands so like, you know, I you everyone in tomorrow land kind of kicks it
The coolest ride are the cool kids of said land so the space mountain kids, you know, they're they're the cool guys
His day I was just the funny guy
so like I kind of commingled with everyone but also you you would meet people in other lands when you would do the parades because
like people from each land would all come together and
But then like then you had like the parade leads those guys were cool, which were essentially kind of like
Just pretty much leads who just also got to do parades
and then like I said the like the big like
land leads who like wore the jackets like those were the cool guys and
Then outside of that were just the older people who like this was a job and they were above that bullshit
And you just really didn't notice because you have like lifers
Which was like you semi derogatorily which are people who like they're like, yeah
I like work in Disney and this is gonna be my career and it's like oh you're a lifer
And then you have like
Retirees that was another big thing which were old people who retired and they didn't give a fuck about any of the like
Clicks or anything they were just their own breed and but they were kind of cool because you know, just old people stories
Sure, I heard that a lot of retirees like will do it for less for the money
But more to a like get out and about have something to do and then the perks for a grandkids
They get the discount for yep, they can buy gifts discount again and then they you get all those extra, you know
Guest passes you're like the coolest grandparent or uncle if you can get your niece or grandkid
Into Disneyland for free, you know, yeah. So yeah, the wheels are turning with all of us now. Yeah, we'll all be working
I'll see you guys it for when his to comes back his to 3.0
Yeah, I'll see you before my shift
Well, I think the way the way a certain point the way the annual passes are going it's going to make more sense for us
All to get jobs part-time at Disney to get tickets versus paying whatever
Dollars will cost in like five. I know
It's gonna be wild
Before we get deep into the ride my last question
Do you have like one specific day where something happened or a story?
Like is there a one specific story you remember from working there where you're like, oh, yeah, that was the weirdest day. Um, well
The it's the craziest story, but the story I have
Was like there was this lead who was a parade lead and this was a very important
crux to that that person's
Plan because he ended up like
Dating multiple girls at the park, but since they were separated by lands, they never knew about each other until
Yeah until like they kind of
figure one figured out and then they kind of like
Connected the dots and found out that this dude was like
Cheating with them and it was the it was like the perfect crime because if you imagine you're a parade lead
You can flirt with anyone in any land and then they go back to their land and you go back to the land that you are
And he was in Tomorrowland
It's like a rock star having like a girl in every city
Yeah, and that's basically what it was but then it blew up in his face like right as he was
He was leaving it was a whole thing. Well, he was living in the future
He was from tomorrow and and the concept of couples have evolved in society's change and he was a poly got
You know as a poly thing moved past only having one partner
Was he was it just in the Disneyland proper or did he have like some girls over in Hollywood land over a California adventure?
Who knows who knows because what the moment it like pops past like two it was like, oh you you were you were putting in work
You're just Wow, but like it's like when when you you I would never think of it
But when you hear you're like damn, yeah
That would work because there's no the way the lands are separated like all the lands for the most part
Go to lunch in different places because it'd be so much work to come all the way over to Tomorrowland
So there is like no way that this person would be talking to this person in like the way the friend groups are dispersed
There's no way that they're they like they could probably openly talk about like oh, I'm dating
so and so and like it wouldn't get back because they're like right lands apart
He could have like he could have had a girl in Paradise Pier, but she's so far away
You know, you didn't even find out about the other girls. Yeah. Oh, yeah
might still be dating right
Still hasn't found out
No, it's changed to Pixar pier. Yeah
Wow, that's why I do Paradise Pier and Toontown
That's this far apart as the girls get boss you bookend it right and maybe a critter country
You just you know spread them through sure Wow. Wow. Wow. I don't even think about that
Of course that happens. You get a job there. Yeah get to get to your parade. Yeah
Let's do it. Let's dive into the ride itself hista. Is it true that
Some website I saw said that with this abbreviation his stuff or any I shrunk the audience that the employees would call each other his stations
Yeah, I don't
At all
I read it and thought that doesn't sound
Right that doesn't that seems too lame for anyone to actually that might have been before or after me
But when I was there no one referred to each other as his station his station community had disbanded
Yeah, yeah, cuz hista is short like it could see people calling each other that or saying oh I work at his stuff
But like adding station makes it long again. And at that point you may as well say the full name. Oh man
Yeah, I would have totally said don't ever call me a his station
Give me a favor. No
Were you familiar with honey? I shrunk the audience before you started work actually. Yes, so I even though I never
Experienced captain EO before it came back. I did experience hista
So I was actually kind of high because I was like, oh I kind of like that
I was not a fan of being part of astral orbiter cuz to me that was always the lamest ride in tomorrow land and
There's been people since who have taken offense to that where they're like, no
It's not and it is fun
If you have someone because it actually does when you get into it and it's moving and the fact that you can control it up
And down while you go around is actually a nice little hit
but I think when you're going up against like Nemo submarine space mountain and
I think it makes it harder buzz light year. You have a like video games starts our tour. It's a stacked land
Sure, yeah last year orbiter moved from when it was up on top of the platform
Yeah, when it was just rocket jets you at least have okay. Well dumb bows down on the ground
Yeah rocket jets is way up here. It's a little more
Death defiant but back on the ground. I've never really understood the appeal of Astro orbiter
How do you shrink the audience though?
I don't think it dawned on me until like starting to read about the ride that it is it is book ended by
Like it replaced captain eo in all of the parks around the world Disneyland Disney World did
Tokyo Disney Disneyland Paris. So yeah a lot of the big
parks and then
They all came back captain eo came back after Michael died. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. And what a day
I'm sure I've talked about it. I got a hotel room
I made such when that log seeing that sign go back
Michael died you know, no, no, I was not celebrating Michael's death. No
But it did occur to me. It was in the back of my head on a sad day like oh, but you know what?
I bet and sure enough a couple months later. Yeah
Which you know, maybe I this is okay
This isn't just because it replaced captain eo or was counter to captain eo in any way
I swear that's not why but I will go ahead and say I am not a big fan of honey
I shrunk the audience I do I'm like I I found this thing
Kind of unpleasant and I sort of didn't do it past the first couple
Opportunities to do it. I will say as a child I did it at Epcot. It scared the absolute shit out of me
And I don't I think I just did it once and never did it again because I was terrified of it much like when I was
Terrified of captain eo as a child too when those monsters poked their staffs out at the screen and I had to be removed
From the theater by my mother because I was having a meltdown
So I will go on record as saying my memory of it is oh
Shit, there's mice at my feet. This is real. Oh my god. I hate this
Yeah, so that's my memory of it and I never I
Started going but to Disneyland when I moved out here right around the time of Captain eo coming back
So this might have been still there for one or two visits, but I think I was like no
Thank you. I will not be scared again. I I liked it cuz I like these movies
Okay, I'll say this I did not like the snake in the feet the mice I could tolerate
But when they're like, oh the snake is loose. I just did not like I didn't like the snake either
I really did not like that and even after I had done it a few times
I'm like, why do I always forget that snake is coming cuz I I I did not like it
But I as a kid I loved Rick Moranis cuz I was like sure I
Moranis I honey I shrunk the
Kid and I remember seeing I feel like we saw an advanced screening of honey
I blew up the kid for some every now and then my dad's company would get like
early movie preview tickets and then
And then as him as Louis Tolley, right? That's a character in Ghostbusters. Yeah, I just loved him
Sure, I loved him but I and I'll say this I never saw the first honey
I shrunk the kids because the giant bee scared the shit out of
It and you knew it was in there I knew it was in there in the tray in the commercials and I we did not
See it. I was so scared. I did see honey
I blew up the kid cuz I big things Scott scared of big things that didn't bother me as much
Kids getting small on insects. Ooh, I hated it. We didn't see it
So I think I was even going into this still with the memory of the first movie
With like giants of I didn't even like the Playland very much
I like the Playland. I did like the Playland loved the play. I
Like I never had the first I don't think we had the first movie on tape
But I feel like all my friends had it
So I will always end up watching it at friends houses in that first honey
I shrunk the kids is a little unnerving the second movie. The only unnerving thing is corporate malfeasance
Like he's trying to stay steal his inventions, right?
Well, and it's similar to it's scary in a similar way to Beethoven where there's like yes trying it
What what's the word like like it's like darts to tranquilize a dog or a baby
Like yeah, I guess I was freaked out as a kid by yeah, yeah, like scary needles and darts
Cute things and I'm trying I'm forgetting the actor's name, but he's the bad guy in Beethoven
He always played a good guy on TV, but he was a bad guy in that movie and he gets a Dean Jones
Oh, yeah, Dean Jones. Yeah, yeah mainstay Dean Jones. He's a bad guy and he gets all chest full of
Syringes at the end of Beethoven and it's terrifying
Even as a child I knew like that's justice you deserve 16 syringes
Daddy had a heart attack
Like Beethoven is pretty like oh, yeah, and also grodin falls through a skylight before that happens
Oh in Beethoven too
so like there's a very dark ending because Beethoven is such so light and like the David Duchovny part where they like
Beethoven no, he tangles his leash around the chair and they go flying down the street
Haha at the end Charles grodin eats shit through a skylight like Raphael in the Ninja Turtle movie
And then Dean Jones takes a chest full of syringes. That's there's different shades of gray different shades of justice
Yeah, well the good news though
I bet Dean Jones got high as shit right before he did that was like euphoria for five seconds
He was like Rush Limbaugh in his Oxycontin times a hundred
So he got it I bet he went out and it was like like it was like all the morphine in the world
Here's a bit of insight into my time scared childhood brain
And I just remembered we saw the Lassie movie in theaters, which had come out around that zone
Maybe it was like a 90s Lassie movie. Yeah, ninety-two ninety-three and I remember in the movie going
Oh here comes cuz my brain knew here comes the like climax of the movie
I didn't know it in that term, but I knew this is one like the scarier intense stuff happens
It didn't happen in Lassie
There was like no almost no resolution and it was just like sort of ended and I was so relieved
I remember feeling like oh the movie's gonna get like darker like scary now
It didn't the movie was over and I was so happy that nothing dramatic happened at the end of last
Oh, that's good. I heard there's that um what a dog's journey home. It's by the same guy that new movie
It's based on a book
Written by the same guy who wrote a dog's purpose. Yes, and the new movie
I was reading an article about it and they're like in theory
This is a feel-good family movie, but a major plot point involves a corpse
I'm like, whoa, what is yeah, what exactly is this movie? Oh, no
They also in the trailer give it away that the dog gets home. Yeah. Yeah, I noticed I was like what why?
Attempt to journey home
Unless there's like an addendum to that where like the dog gets a bunch of needles in the chest
How weird would it be that this was like some fever dream and the dog wakes up and was like you didn't make it home
Yeah, he's in like a kennel somewhere in the south or something. You are a corpse
Yeah, do you remember?
I always ask any group of people around my age about this commercial
Because it happened once in the middle of the night when I was watching MTV
I never saw it again. I always google it every now and then I could never find it
but there was a
Like it must have been Peter or something
but it was a commercial about like putting your dog in the cages the doggy cages and then like it was like
It's this like woman and she's like looking at her dog and she's like, you're my best friend
she was like I hope that if
If the like something like I hope like if the roles were
You treat me the same or something like that and then it just cuts to her in a cage
Freaking out and it's fucked with me for so long because it's like she's like
Like screaming for her life and no one's ever seen that commercial but me. What is it a commercial for? Yeah
dog in a cage
Be like
What was it liquid television was that that was the shorts the weird shorts on MTV
That could have just been a liquid television. No, that could be true
There is like as much as everything's documented on the internet a ton of stuff isn't yeah like there that rare
Like somebody was just telling me that I think it was little Debbie made something called like a tiger
Cake or something and it was like it looked like a tiger and I was like I've never heard of that or whatever
And he's like it exists
Nothing shows up and then you I did some digging and on a Facebook page official little Debbie page
It was like yes, we did have like people were asking questions
They're like yes, we did have this product in the 90s
But there's not a picture of it and I was shocked that there wouldn't be one picture of a product from the 90s
So like there's plenty of stuff
I feel like out there like a little very large product line a lot of variations seasonal variations, you know
You're like complicated things get lost
You feel very I know you you are sort of lobbying for a PR job at little Debbie
Well, I would just like because I mean you can get little Debbie's in Southern, California, but back east
I feel like there's a lot more variety of little Debbie's available. So I would like oh you mean little Debbie had more products in the east
Yeah, and a lot more like convenience store like single serving versions of those products
I feel like you just get the hits out here. You also had like Drake's caught like Drake's cake
Yeah, Drake's coffee cakes and that sort of thing. All right. Well, let's talk about
Too much, yeah
Comfortable with it. I just want to make sure we hit all the points cuz we've all case
So we've established if he did you like the ride or the juice into the show? Oh, yeah, I loved it
I when I was a kid, I loved the show. I thought it was fun
You know, I was I was big in 40 I liked Shrek 4d I like to be sure
So yeah, no, I never got scared and I was a scaredy-cat
But I think I was just so into the experience that did you like the movies? Did you see the movies?
Yeah, I saw honey. I blew up the kid honey. I shrunk the kids, you know
I did also think the bee the bee was weird. Actually the thing that was weird to me than the bee was the ant
I don't like that ant up close
Yeah, it's marked and it's supposed to be a sad moment I was like good riddance stay dead
Don't ever come back into my life again. Oh my gosh. It was so gross and he flew. Oh
Yeah, so that so yeah, so we have two likers and two haters sort of of the riotous kids at least
Yeah, I liked them. I liked the movies. I was a big fan of blew up the kid
Uh-huh, I like the blew up the kid fine
So sad when he touches that guitar and it shocks him
Oh, yeah starts crying like that made me so sad. Yeah. Yeah, you're right. That is very upsetting
Well, so this I always like to talk personnel here comes Scott's dry facts the personnel
It's right. Yeah. Yeah. This movie was honey
I think the audience was directed by the same director as honey. I blew up the kid
So he stayed in the family. You know, he knows the French as he knows Wayne Zelinski's voice
Also do honey we shrunk ourselves the direct
I'll get to that. Okay, let me take you through the honey
I shrunk a verse in terms of a directorial staff Randall Kleisner or not Kleisner Kleiser
crazy filmography, let me list his
I
Put this down to yeah, so really odd ones. So before honey, I should blew up the kid. He did Greece
This is the director of Greece. Oh, it's kind of crazy. You don't think more about who directed Greece, but it's this guy Randall Kleiser
Blue Lagoon was him flight of the Navigator
Big Top Pee-wee and then two of the most notoriously odd
TV movies of the 70s Don portrait of a teenage runaway with Eve plum from the Brady Bunch and
Boy in the plastic bubble with John Travolta. So Greece was his second Travolta joint
and then he did honey, I blew up the kid now the
but the most impressive name in the list of worked on this probably is
Dean Cundy who who shot it Dean Cundy was the DP. Did you guys know Dean Cundy's name?
I did often
His the list of the films he is shot Halloween escape from New York the thing he did all the Carpenters all
Three back to the futures Wow big trouble in Little China who friend Roger Rabbit hook the Flintstones Casper
Apollo 13 and Jurassic Park all shot by the same guy who also did the 3d spectacle
Honey, honey, I shrunk the audience
Then with his honey experience he went on to make his
Directorial debut with honey we shrunk ourselves and past that point his filmography
Gets really odd and spotty. It says it feels like honey like cursed him
So he went on to shoot Garfield both Garfield's he shot one of the worst films
I've ever seen which is this Reese Witherspoon
From a couple years ago that has this bland title. I can't even remember. It's really it's done by the kid of
Who's the like rom-com? Oh?
Is it Nancy Meyers is kid? Yes? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, see Meyers is kid directed this movie
I think I specifically horribly shot and you look up who shot this thing. It's like shaky and badly lit
Oh the DP of Jurassic Park
Like what a strange answer I'm not gonna lie I think I put myself on tape for that movie hey
I think that was a weird submission that came through UCB
And I was and and it said the name of the director and it specifically said like
Child of Nancy Mott, and I'm like what he listed it in the hell
Just tape yourself or maybe I googled it and and the Hollywood Reporter article just kept mentioning child of Nancy Meyers child of Nancy
I wish you'd been in this
Let me also say about honey we shrunk ourselves the forgotten piece of this this was a TV movie for like Wonderful World Disney
That oddly was written by Joel Hodgson of oh yeah, it's theater fame and Nell
Scoville who oh the letter wait letterman and like like one of the only letterman and Simpsons female writers
Yeah, I think she has a book out that's supposed to be pretty like she has a crazy like story
Her career she's worked on so many huge things sure sure and then but my the best fact about
Honey, we shrunk ourselves and probably the main reason to revisit it is it features a performance by?
Allison Mack perhaps better known as pimp Mac one of the leaders of the Nixxiom sex cult
How do you however you say that NX IV? Yeah, from Smallville
Yes on her rise to become pimp Mac
Is that what they called her in the cult? Yes?
Okay all the women
And they got branded a symbol that was like if you looked at it if you thought about what the symbol was it was the
Initials of the leader of the thing and then a am
for Alice and Mac
But she's also part of this wonderful
franchise the honey franchise
Anyway like top-tier talent and then the other one writer
Oh the writer well the Muppet guy Bill
Brady Big Bang Theory the co-creator of the Big Bang Theory wrote honey, we're gonna shrunk the audience
Who also went on to create the recent Muppet show on ABC and he wrote Muppet vision 3d
It seems like the movie version of the ball in Space Jam where the mom stars steal the power because it seems like he came
in and after that
Wildly successful and everyone else is as dark turns and he read Dean Conde
Still all the magic everyone before I know this is weird, but can we touch the script?
Hands on everyone
Moranis hasn't done a movie. Oh, that's true. Yeah, one of the last on-screen performances of
Moranis, but also but another guy who got a lot of power
After making this thing the pre-show was shot by Peyton Reed. Oh, yeah
Eventual director of Ant-Man and presumably he's oh he already is
I think he was involved in what they shot for Hong Kong Disneyland for Ant-Man
And presumably will be in any other attractions they do and rumors have been it's possible that
These theaters where honey has shrunk the audience once played will be home to some Ant-Man attraction down the line
So he was so this is Peyton Reed and shrinking well before his
Famous shrinking work and not his first theme park thing, right?
Didn't he shoot also the future of the ride the pre-show
He shot the pre-show of this and back to the future both of which are at institutes
And both of which are like high jinx and like long like it's more like broadcast camera
like people scurrying down hallways and trying to solve mix-ups, so
Yeah, there's there's a big commonality
Which is a funny thing that in if you view all of theme park world as one big narrative that there's the
Imagination Institute and the Institute of Future Technology
These are different things, but they both have open houses and invite people to come participate in their chaos 24-7
Yeah, well, we're just that one day that they happen to invite sure Joe Schmoe and to check it out. Yeah
Which by the way, so that's the like
The convoluted nature of the plot of this thing it is the open house of the Institute
While an award show during the inventor of the year
It is both an award show and an open house kind of a hat on a hat
Situation kind of two weird things going on that sure they needed both of them
And also if you're gonna open an Institute within a theme park
Just get like you need to know people are gonna be there and you need to prepare and you need to be safe
Like how is it catching them off guard that all these people all these regular people are flooding into the audience, right?
And it's not like Wayne Zelinski isn't a madman before this in canon
It's always chaos as Nigel Channing is reminded with newspaper headlines
He was so much chaos on this earth. Oh, everyone should have known this was gonna happen
Yeah, I have to say I want to know how dr. Nigel Channing got this job because he seems to resent
Imagination
In both because he shows up
if you don't know if you've ever ridden the
journey into
Your imagination the the second generation of this Epcot ride
Where the same Eric Idle character shows up and interacts with the character, you know about this
No, there's a separate ride that's only an Epcot with the same Eric Idle
Really character and it is considered to be one of the worst rides
People hate it because they love the original and this one sucks
Yeah, and he is so annoyed by a whimsical creature. You know figment that little purple dragon. Okay, that was the original
he's still on the ride the character but like the original was like this whimsical Dreamfinder man and
Imagination and there's a flying contraption and the newer version is like a very like sterile
Like figment trying to explain to Eric Idle why how smells were yeah
Toilet stuck to the ceiling and it's like weird and it's very 90s of like stodgy guy comes around at the end
like a
Yeah, I don't know Mrs. Doubtfire s kind of plot
Right and it's just it sucks and everyone knows it sucks the creator of the original ride hates it
Publicly talk shit about it with us on our podcast. We knew him. Yeah, he was like
I don't know how a toilet on the ceiling is
But it was so they must have thought it's Nigel Channing mania when this ride opened we got to get more Channing in the parks
Did you ever see people wearing Nigel Channing shirts Channing his name?
Not at all
Not a lot of merchandise
Need more Nigel merchandise
We really are slacking on that front. There's not a park star of Nigel
There is not a park star of Nigel the way we work though
I feel like if there was some Nigel merch would be like, oh shit. Did you see that Nigel merch?
That's a pretty good shirt. No, you'd be like, oh, yeah, we got to get that Nigel Channing shirt
So like they're missing out. Yeah, I'm doing that. Yeah, why is he so why is such a fuss budget in charge?
Yeah nation Institute and also like if he's such a pain in the ass character
Why was he in two rides? I could see putting figment in two rides figments awesome. He's a
Imaginative little dragon you love him. You want to buy a doll of him Nigel chant. What the hell like why I it's weird
It's a weird choice. It's fun that they're connected. It's fun that there he's in two different rides
He just had a weird contract. He was like if I do one Disney movie, I must do another
Question I have for you is and the big thing I think about with anybody works at a theme park is is repetition
Were you be you were like leading people in and out of this movie many times a day every day
Like were you being were you driven mad by hearing the same dialogue the same?
I don't know how if you had to stay and listen to know you didn't have to stay and listen
What you would do is after like because you know, like I said when I was hyped
I was in there watching and I was like, okay cool and I would try and like run up
Frazzled where it's like, oh sorry about that
Once you get used to it
you're like outside talking to the exit point guy and chatting it out and then like listening for it and then like you'll peek in and
Like okay, it's about to end and then you run up and do it
Okay, so you didn't have to like you weren't on the other end where you have to hear like hello and welcome
Yeah, you weren't like hearing that
rant every day not random a little same bit of dialogue every day
Okay, what about music like were you in some hallway where you had to hear done done done done done?
Yeah, that yeah that one you you especially if you were in the front you were constantly hearing that and that would get kind of old
But like you're also being at the front you're constantly being inundated by questions. I it's so funny, too. I'll never
Forget where like this like I was there on my day off and like this guy just like
Asking the cast member questions and I was like and it was really just like like I was like just talking to him
But I was like answering the questions and he's like, yeah
Uh, I'm I want the cast member to answer answer it and like I had to stop myself because I was like
I was like gonna be like bitch
I am a cast member was like one like I can't sass him and then in the same sentence be like
Oh, I work here you dumbass
Hey, you buddy. Yeah. Fuck you you asshole
Employee ID badge. Yeah. Yeah, like
So so I had to like eat it, but I remember being so annoyed but then being like, oh, yeah from his perspective
I'm just some Disney super fan who's just like trying to answer all of his questions. So
And so like at the time I just didn't think to be like, oh no, it's my day off
I work here and he's kind of busy because it was the thing of like
Whereas like you're you being a co-worker you're like, oh this guy's being annoying and like inundating you with simple questions
While you're also trying to cuz it was also like right before show was going in
So he's trying to hand out stuff and he's like just hounding him for questions
So I was just trying to help so it was so like it was like this weird mixed emotion where like I saw where he
Was coming from but also like I also know from my
Friends perspective he's being asked an asshole and then me my personal pride of like this dick dad
like sassing me like it was just so many emotions and
I I think I just like walked away
I think that was my solution or like I I did like I I did like a flex where like I
Walked back state like in
Oh
To subtly give him the information. Yeah to be like, yeah
No, I or like did something or being like oh it's so until here cuz I start like just to like
Tip him off without trying to be too aggro, but it was like funny
Where it's like, oh, yeah
when you're not in the because and that the I think the core that story was like I didn't know what I was doing because
When you work there whether you're in your outfit or not
You are still essentially a cast member because it still turns on and you still have that
Eagerness of being like oh, I'm gonna give you the information you're asking for right?
but like it's like it's like, you know the a more wholesome version of like
Cop who's off duty, you know?
I'm still do my job, but I'm technically not on the job
I remember being at the container store when I didn't work
I was working there at the time
But I wasn't on the shift and people would still ask me stuff because I had the air about me
Yeah, I knew what I was doing. So I would still answer and I'd be like, oh, I just trying to get through here
But then I'm secretly I'm like, they know I feel like this is where I belong and you would just hang out because
Stores cool place to hang out. Yeah
I
Big beer outside of the container store
About closet planning
For all my magazines in the bookshelf and no magazine. They're never gonna get out of the wrapping
You know if you think about it a beer can is a container. Yeah
Wow, man, I never thought of it that way Mike. Yeah, that's fucking cool. Wow. It's still funny
The fifth time you told that joke Mike
I'm punishing Mike with my joke. I'm putting this in your mouth. Fuck you Michael
Dare you say a beer cans a container? I'll take it. I deserve it
Let me ask when you were working there any famous people
Did you see any famous people enjoying this show while you were a cast member?
Uh, I not anyone enjoying our show there has never been a single
Famous person to go through our ride
But but but like Nemo just came so we heard of lots of famous people going
Over and seeing I'm trying to think of some I believe there was once a red hot chili pepper
We were real excited about
when Stephanie sure
and
Those are the first ones that pop into my mind
Were you working in Tomorrowland when the red hot chili peppers music was on Space Mountain and California Screamin
Do you know I'm talking about? No, I don't there was a year or so where
Their cover of higher ground was on Space Mountain and around the world was on California Screamin
Not because I would definitely remember that damn
I was gonna say I'd be very magical like summer the buzzing of people like oh my god
Did you hear the red hot chili peppers are coming to and it was it was bizarre too?
Right when those songs came out years later
Yeah, I also didn't know they did a cover of higher ground that was news to me
Well, I was a chili peppers fan as a youth so I knew all about higher ground
I probably heard it before the Stevie Wonder version
You know what they need to do is because I was I took my very first right not to brag
I took my very first ride on the Golden Zephyr a rarely open ride in California Adventure
Which for any Astro orbiters fans out there is a ride that goes round and round and then stops
What a blast but I was in my head playing the song right away
That's what they need they need to bring the red hot chili peppers back and put it in that ride and then I think the
Lines out the door I put that right a bit about this effort
So what I was dating like sorry the lines just we got to get going we can't we were leaving the park lines too long
For Zephyr. It's now it's two hours for Zephyr
Maybe next time and really want to get on that Zephyr
someday there was source for Zephyr jokes, I will have a
Weekly platform for Zephyr jokes. I mean we all have it now. We're gonna do an episode. That's two hours long on the Golden Zephyr
Actually there is because it is modeled after an older like an original generation
Model on an older generation
I'm in for two hours. Well, you know, there actually is two hours of material
Yeah, no seriously at least two hours if the gold not more, you know
You
Know what someone put me on a California adventure that I would have never went until like someone
Was like you should check it out was the Aladdin show
Into the right man. Yeah, it's a really good
I was like this is like a really good show that's just hidden here that you would not think to go
You know, it's like uh-huh almost like you would think you'd see it at any other like play, you know
Broadway caliber. Yeah
Like I didn't want to give it the full endorsement set
You know in case some listeners are Broadway heads and scoff at me, but yeah a Broadway caliber show
Yeah, 50 minute show and you get topical jokes galore. Yes
Kills every time
I've seen it probably ten times. It's all it's gone now. It's frozen now. Really? Yeah, and there's no missing all those genie
Donald Trump jokes. Yes. Well, he couldn't do Trump probably
I was joking remember I when I was working
It was the Super Bowl and we couldn't even ask people what the score was like they're like you cannot ask people you can't like
If someone was wearing like a team you couldn't be like go
Like you had like you couldn't because in the concept was was that when people are in Disneyland
You want them to be immersed in Disneyland? You want them to forget about the outside?
You could not exist yeah, you could not talk about
Super Bowl at all, but Jeannie could get away with like a dr. Phil impression
Yeah, you could get away with snooki joke. Yeah get away with the joke about Angelina Jolie's leg from the Oscars
I saw all three of those the dr. Phil. Wait, you mean when she like
Stuck her leg out in kind of a strut pose and then he did that Jim rash
Right after her and he did the same pose. Yes, Jeannie was there was a joke about that. Yes
Yeah, we would go that this is a side note
Obviously we I would when I say we would go I would force Lindsey to go or whoever was with I go
I want to see what topical jokes he's gonna do today and like that's one of the big ones who are like
Jeannie did Angelina Jolie's leg joke like I wanted to see how obscure he could get and I think that was maybe the most obscure
That was the most I think Jeannie would have a tough time in 2019
Because what material is out there that's okay. He can't do Trump. He can't do Kevin Hart. He can't do Louie
He there's no story in the world that you could that the Jeannie could make fun of it's just dabbing. He would just be dabbing
So where are we dropping boys he would floss probably and get just a standing ovation
Yeah, it would just people go nuts crying like in the Michael
Jordan Michael Jackson concert montages
He would do Justin Bieber stuff that would kill all the time or just still oh I
Probably still today. He would do he would
Dr. Phil he would I could go on and on about this
But he would do a when he would list what he couldn't couldn't do with his wishes
He would say and I can't bring people back from the day. He would do the dr. Phil voice
For some reason during that part and then like announced kind of like that
He was dr. Phil or something and the audience would think that was great. I'm dr
Phil he would say he would there was a couple where he would just be like something something something also like
Snooki and he like look out at the audience and say Snooki, you know
What and then everyone everyone I would always bring would just look at me like horrified during this part of this and I'd be like
Great
Anyway, that's that is two hours for sure that episode. Yeah, that was gonna go and go
Oh, but look at that. This is I mean with a live a breathing apparatus
Like the Aladdin show you can change up that material the set movie
Honey, I shrunk the audience trots out its jokes over and over to where I did it once or twice
Never needed to do it again when Wayne's
In the flying machine and then he crashes it into the inventor of the year sign and then the letters form nerd
That's not funny more than once. I don't think was it
It's not that funny
It was the 90s when like you could make fun of nerds or that was more of a really dates it
Yeah, the idea of nerd like your podcast is called nerd deficit
But it's like the word nerd doesn't mean what it meant in the night
It just means you're a pop culture enthusiast essentially that's really what it means in the old days it was like a cool down
But that was so yeah
So at the time because even at the time I was like didn't think it was that funny because I was like
I'm kind of like nerd. I like Dexman. So it's a science institute. So like yeah
And Wayne Zelinski if he existed in the real world's like true the greatest inventor of the century
Is you know messy results great family he'd be like Elon Musk or something now but better
I mean, it's just like he is a different you know, he would suck on Twitter Wayne Zelinski would just be awful on Twitter
Zolinski called me a cuck
In terms of repeating movie like rewatching movies in the parks
I will say like as a kid I was totally gay like I would rewatch the same movies and cartoons over and over
Again, so I didn't really think about like oh, we're gonna watch Muppets Muppets 3d again. I'm like no, we're here today
We're gonna do it or we're at Epcot. We're gonna let's rewatch
Yeah, we must say it says you to your beleaguered parents again. Yes, we're here
We're gonna do it
Well in Florida a movie where it's dark and air-conditioned
Parents like that you can get a few little you know some winks and get a little nap in very good point
But harder to do when the floor is vibrating and there's mice
Zipping around your leg like that all makes
All those things make this a tougher proposition. I don't ever do I mean there well, you can't do either of them now really
I don't do
The honey I shrunk and I don't do tough to be a bug
So I don't like all those little vibrates and you said the thing I think which I had the same thing
I hated when it would poke you in the back. It scared me like the
Yeah, I didn't like that. I'm I'm better about it now Shrek 4d pokes you in the back too
Which I got used to it on Shrek 4d. Yeah, I like I like the little nice in the snake. You're like
It's fine with it. Now. There's a version of it on the mummy at Universal. I can handle it now, but on the ride on the ride
Yeah, the scarabs
The one thing I don't like that gets me is the like darts and indie like because I'm like, oh really
Yeah, it's like yeah, I'm not getting shot. But if air gets in my eye does kind of bug me
Yeah, there's a ripoff of Soren in Canada that I went on and fly over Canada
That has way more like blast and stuff in your face and it fucked up my wife's eye
Like her like I really hurt she's like digging shit out of her contact no an hour after it was terrible
Well, I have definitely gotten ash in my eye from either phantasmag or the firework. Like I have definitely gotten like
explosion debris
It was funny during Christmas when
They make it snow
That was always cool seeing the kids be excited because like I'd love to do that parade
But then there's a point where like kids would start trying to put their tongue. I was like no that's so don't
It's not like not bag. It doesn't like it. Yeah. Yeah, it's also that we're shooting out. Do not put it on your tongue
When you were standing outside as the show was going on could you track how far along it was by like our first scream?
That's the mice does that feel not even by the screams, but the big sounds are like boom. Okay, you know, it's a sign boom
Okay, I guess and you can hear that last like zap when he brings everyone to regular size
It's like really loud would the show play
Pretty much the same way with most crowds like was there ever a variation where you're like, holy shit
This is really plain like they're laughing at everything or they're oh, yeah
There were times like where like it's crushing and you're like damn. Okay, I guess this is a group of people
We've never say right but 90% of the time like silence
Yeah, it was pretty much like, you know, just slight chuckles people doing it because you know, they're like, yeah
Doing it like there were like APs who were like, yeah. No, this is this is my jam I go
APs I've like grew to hate they're just so
Just cuz like they like they never approach the park with considering the fact
They're like, oh, I will be back here soon
This is this is that I can come back as much as I want as opposed to sometimes
This is someone's only chance to come to Disneyland maybe in years and I would see it someone I went to
interventions cuz like my girlfriend at the time that's where she worked and
We would drive
Home together so to kill time. I would just go there and play rock band or something
You didn't you didn't have somebody else in critter country or in?
Yeah
so and it was it was crazy too because so Disney has this
like program
where like
People from college get to work over the summer
Yeah, and then they go and that's when I first met her and I have like the biggest crush on her in the world
but I was like a little wimp I'd never wanted to tell her and she went back to college and I was just
Pined over her for so long. I was losing like I would just go like this back in my space
I'd go to her my space and be like, let me see what she's up to. She's in college right now
Man she's living it up and then like she like came back to
LA and I like lost my mind and so she was at Disneyland and I had an annual pass. I wasn't working there anymore
But like I was so I I would meet up with her there and wait for her
But like I remember sitting there and I was watching it was one of those connect games and there was this like
Young-ass kid who like was like waiting to play and there's these like two older APs playing and they looked back and saw the kid
and like started another match and I was like
What the hell are y'all doing? Also, it's like buy an Xbox you fucking dorks
Like it's not even like it was alright
Like it's an Xbox game move out the way and let the kid like you are old enough to purchase an Xbox this kid
Cannot you know that bugs me on Haunted Mansion when it's people who know the
Spiel in the elevator by heart and yeah, like hey some people in this room
It's definitely their first time here. Maybe let the beloved voice narration
Yeah, maybe let them hear this beloved
As opposed to you guy who comes every Saturday like maybe chill out a little
Chill all the way out that ride, you know, the more you think about it does get really dark
Oh, I can this is the perfect podcast to bring up this gripe. Oh, I
Think the Nightmare Before Christmas
Installment to that is always way too early. It should not
So much and everyone always argues like it's Halloween Nightmare Before Christmas is not a Halloween movie
Christmas is in the movie and the movie starts when Halloween ends
It is not a it's a Christmas movie and it should not be around in Halloween
That's the one scary ride at the like Haunted Mansion is legitimately scary and you make it not scary during Halloween
What sense does that make? Hey, I agree. We agree. I think I think you know this this issue had never occurred to me
But Molly Lambert brought it up. You're bringing it up. I am now thinking this is a movement
I think that they need to be heard on this issue, right?
And I've heard people in the I've like past conversations in the parks of people complaining about this or like, yeah
Did you wait the iron gosselin complained about that video?
What someone people are talking to him like people meet him in the parking garage or something and they're like what's your favorite?
I think oh, honey, man. Oh
I wish though
I came up with the solution the time it should be is at they they should like
Have it running on Halloween and then
Stop it like for a bit to make the change over even though there's no way it could be done this fast
But on the or have it closed up it to the point that you need to do these changes
But on Halloween like night at midnight you can switch it over
Exactly, that's when it should go because that that's when that movie begins
It's just all this Christmas stuff during Halloween and it just annoys me so much
I'm like this is it it's Halloween right now and you're doing like Christmas stuff
They could I think it takes two and a half weeks to switch it out
So in theory they could do that and have it running by
Mid November, but now I feel like they keep starting Christmas earlier and earlier
They must be not wanting any of the holiday season to be lacking in
Because if yeah if you think that it if you think on the fact that it takes two weeks that means you either have
To deal with two weeks being down
You have to deal with two weeks it being down during Halloween
Yeah, would be make would make the same party mad or
You would have to have two weeks during November it being down
Which is essentially a quarter of quote unquote Christmas time
Yeah, I mean it's me get it. I think we get the logic down right now because they have to take it all out
Yeah
So it's it's always down like two or three weeks at the start of the year
And I think they use that time to like do any other cleanup they need to do on the regular ride
Yeah, they're the problem is I think also is that there is a big and I don't know why I think this but an Orange County
bro
project Skellington
That wear the big Jack Skellington sweatshirts in the park
And I think they would riot if they don't have a Halloween
You want to get in this fire? I'll do it so we can do the fight. There's nothing though that I hate more
cuz then Orange County bros as a
La native it would be my personal Christmas present to fuck them up like I
candidly
We're getting into la oce
Watching you kind of like spin kick like ten jack Skellington's in the face
I would like to see that very much
Speaking of which that's the one thing that I think is right because and I don't know why no one seems to think this based
On the kids around it, but the walking around jack Skellington is
Terrified yeah, yeah, this is hate that face. What's going on like it looks nothing like
So far terrifying but kids are like yeah, I'm like that is
Horrifying the first time I saw it
I thought it was a fan made costume walker in the park and not a official Disney mascot
Yeah, honestly I did what if there was more of them?
Like one day you're at the park, and you're like there's a jack Skellington in every land
What's going on?
What a nightmare you're describing they need to make like a puppet jack Skellington that you can take a photo with yeah
So slender
But you can make the head look like his head
And like see easily I don't know my brother really likes nightmare for Christmas
I feel like anytime he comes to the parks or visits on me. That's a souvenir
He usually gets some sort of nightmare for Christmas thing, but I think even he would be like no, but the Haunted Mansion
You can buy the merch any day of the year
But I mean how often to get to see the Haunted Mansion so yeah
Take it out of play for like a quarter of the year. Yeah a bizarre
I think we should put this on a poll. I'm curious what our audience thinks about
Nightmare too early or not right like cuz I'm starting to think that's a good idea results gonna be like 85%
I don't want to tip it say what you think because I'm on the fact I could see the argument either way
But it's interesting to me. This is like this seems to be growing to a boiling point
I want to take the audience's temperature because I went for Halloween again, and it just like took me out
You know I'm filled with five different types of churros and chocolate mousse sure I'm like
Oh, I'm ready for the spooks, baby
And it's this cute Christmas song and you get a gift at the end for anyone who wants to make that trash argument
That it's still a Halloween ride you get a Christmas gift in October
Yeah, yeah, why it's Halloween you want a ghost to follow you home
You don't want a little day glow like a box with a bone
I'll even take one of Oogie Boogie's little freaks
Yeah, those little helpers that are because they're at least a nerve egg there. They are
Followed me home. I'd be like oh no
Too early for presents
We gotta get back tonight. I'll change
another 30 minutes
Well, you know what I'll say there's topics where I'm like, but we have to get to this we have to get to this
This is one of those are I'm like I don't fuck it. I really I honestly don't like this attraction
I like I like hearing about your yeah experience on it
but I and here's here's one thing that I don't like about it is that as opposed to
we're gonna spoil everyone be talking about Muppet Muppet vision soon, and I just rewatched that and
Muppet vision has cuts it has here's a big close and here's a wide and there's the depth of the room
And then you're in this void and then there's fireworks and there's all kinds of different tricks going on
and types of shots that
You know accentuate the 3d effects in different ways the the
Construct of this show it being an award show and having to stay in these big long shots for so long
I think it makes it dull
I think it yeah
And you and you're waiting and waiting for those things to get in your face like the hologram lion
Excuse me a hologram lion and it's not an aesthetic that sits
Next to the aesthetics of the honey movies him flying around on a little like hover pod doesn't like feel like the movies
Holograms were the thing in 1994 though like holograms were a star just the concept of holograms
I mean he's flying around a lot of magic. I it fits in with that
He's in a very similar vehicle to like Baxter Stockman in those Ninja Turtle video games
Yeah, and like a little flying machine, and it's like yeah, he never had that he's like a super villain or something
Yeah, yeah, Wayne Zelinski's just a guy right
Things weird I do like I mean Rick Moranis
Canadian right he's one of the SC TV when he says sorry everybody
He doesn't show up also till like five minutes into this thing
Knowing about and well he should be
You're watching this dull and why is there so much so why would you start the award show without him there like yeah?
The stage manager to like have made the check right like this isn't on TV
They don't need to start at a particular time wait for him
We don't want the fun of him showing up late and ruining the sign we want him to be on time
Yeah, walk out get his proper applause and that would be funny if you got if they rolled
There was like the the normal
You know
That would be a fun April Fool's yes like every like five or ten show would be great
Like it just shows one drops at some points like oh, I dropped my pen well that was the only thing that went wrong today
Yeah, yeah, everybody dropped it right next to the cloning machine. Thank God. It didn't go in it alright. Goodbye
I'll say this here's a gripe. I have Mrs. Zelinski
I mean I it's a set piece from all the movies you want to hear him say honey
I shrunk the blank and she faints. This is the third time now. You gotta get the fading under control like
Yeah, yeah
She needs medical. I think she has a condition my other thing and even as a kid
I remember this going like man girls go wild for Nick's elit's the Sun
There's always in like Nick has a girlfriend in the second in the first movie the second movie in this movie one of the helpers
It's like oh Nick like swooning over him
He's just some dweeb to Gary Russell in number two. Oh, yes
First big roles, but I'll say this quark the dog. I always thought was cool quark the dog with 3d glasses on a cooler
Yeah, yeah quark cool list I agree with that yeah quark the dog also though you could argue kind of a poor man's Einstein
Mmm, and we're talking institutes now. They're interested in the back to the future. Yeah, cork the dog
But it doesn't get big right yeah, yeah, but Einstein travels back in time
Have a an issue to bring it. Yes, that's and that's very cool. He's the first time traveler yes, so
Here's a fun thing about this attraction
We know it as of course as hista or honey. I shrek the audience, but in Japan this was opened as micro adventure
Love that name crazy name
Because of their presumably their lack of familiarity with the with that franchise, but in addition to that
I'm gonna show you guys some artwork. I found some concept art
No of my micro adventure and here is how micro adventure was presented to the Japanese public what you have here
There's a family that's getting hit by a shrinking ray
And then there is cork the dog with 3d glasses, but mainly a much much bigger Mickey Mouse
Well in this art it looks like quark is shooting them
Oh, no, I see the shrinking right now for a second it looked like coming out of coming out of quark
He spits shrink rays no no no this family is in Mickey Mouse's giant glove Mickey also has
3d glasses and so if you see this
You think this is a crazy shrinking world where you are going to become small and Mickey will carry you around
You know who does not appear in micro adventure or hista or any iteration of this Mickey Mouse
Mickey this is false advertising what a great the promise of that is so hot like that is so awesome
It's like you know that is you it shows no characters from the the movie at all
So you don't know what you're going with this family, and you're like oh my god
Mickey's gonna carry me around and Mickey has a different dog. That's not Pluto
He is a realistic dog and and then you get inside okay
Can't wait to be carried around the town by Mickey and then an open house of an award show hosted by dr.
Nigel Channing it begins in order to give an award to professor Wayne Zelinski who first tests technology of a
Hologram machine that may puts a lion in your face, right?
Bumbling guy gin being poor at science jobs
It's honestly if the Deus ex machina of this show was like Mickey shows up when you're small
I'll say I'll fix this and he picks up the audience and he fixes his shrink where a and he's like get get your shit together
What are you doing come on?
What's your life fix your life?
I do want to point out the Mickey in that photo doesn't look like the character Mickey it looks like a Mickey suit
Which which is even creepier even creepier, but even better like that's what I want
Like suited Mickey who doesn't talk to save the day and then I wanted to play the drums like in that special
I like and for that to be like 3d in your face
I've shown the breakdancing Mickey video to so much family over the break
And then we just had people over from Lindsay's work, and I showed that to them, too
She asked for she was like show them the breakdancing Mickey kills every time
This is your requested entertainer. Yeah, yeah
That in the McGruff songs. Oh sure yeah
So I'll praise this you know what I like
I like the little practical when they're holding you as the audience and then you see it in like the mirror image
Yeah, and you're a little tiny box with little people in it. I love that. That's great. I'd like that too
However, I'm tripped up by the logic of it that I know either shrinks
So what point does the feet and what part of it and it's separate?
I did the building is now like shrunk if you were outside the theater. What does that look like right?
What is like like this is just disconnected wall and some of the little bit of a leap to
Imagine that half the building I was shrunk because then you would have like seen the edges of like this is outside
This is tiny and how did the shrink machine know where the divide?
divided cleanly I
Just like that little practical. Well. Yeah, I do like it's a fun little trick when they take you up and show you yourself
That's great, but it's probably it probably misses
There's probably an issue in that they always show a packed theater
Imagine you ever had very hilarious when it's like a few people in there and it's this packed theater
Yeah, the show also is not in my mind structured to like have a big
Climax grand finale grand finale. It kind of ends with a whimper like that Lassie movie
I was talking about but I like when I and I liked it with Lassie a lot
But this now is an adult assessing it
I was like it really should be a fun big thing that ends where it's just kind of like whimpers out and
Now and with if you were went into it with that micro adventure advertising
Oh, you want some major happening at the end, right?
So it's like it's I watch it and like I liked some of the things but it obviously I can't experience it now again
So I can't fully assess it. But yeah, I was like, okay, it's a lot of the issue
Like you shrink I shrink and in what's happening is a giant British man is worried about me
Yes, it's not like you're going like it's not like you're on some fun adventure and it's like bugs
Bugs life or whatever is much more fun and there's antics and stuff. Yeah, like an animatronic Shrek 4d
You're flying everywhere and like stuff is happening and like this one you're just sitting down and everyone's like, alright calm down everybody
Let's figure this out
That's the narrative of the thing hold on everybody don't move don't move don't move don't get too excited and like no one really does
Move it's just like some mice running around and like it's just it's a little snakes opens his mouth at you
Yeah, so like nothing really bad happens. It's just like alright
We dropped a very tiny like battery or something like it's just like when you would if there's something like I dropped the watch battery
I was going to dispose of nobody moved
Step on it and then it's just like a couple minutes of like trying to find it and figure it out and then that's it
That's sort of the feeling of the right. Well, I feel like it's because it stunted itself in its design
I think it is because they decided it was going to be presentational
Yeah instead of something like Captain EO, which is a movie that happens to also be 4d
And I think that's the I think that's the same thing with the bugs life one where it's like everyone's talking to us
You can have all those effects with us getting poked in the butt and stuff and still have us moving about your world
Yeah, it's a show it never thought about that
Yeah
It's like one long shot and things have to be trotted out to you as opposed to cut to this cut exactly
It's more passive than active
But like you like you can see where the cuts are in the movie when like a thing rolls by like a they roll like a cart
By and it's clear that they cut the film there and then there's another shot. Oh, yeah. Yeah stuff like but like
There should be I mean this is I guess a plus it up idea where it's like
Why didn't a villain come by and steal the tiny theater and go on like, you know what?
I mean, you're in the real world with the box now. That's that's the crazy thing is like
They kept it in a way where they felt trapped, but you're right
It didn't someone could have stolen us and took us on an adventure when like gone out into the street
All out into the sewer
That's so much more fun and it seems like that's what they would do now and I don't know why they do it plus up
We have to stay in the auditorium or an inventor of the year award is being given out
Yeah, I will admire it for its realism because that is what would really happen. Everyone just be calm down
We're gonna figure this out and everyone will be safe
That's probably what would happen
But you we want a fun villain was there a villain in the first movie because I haven't seen it
I don't know the B was there a Dean Jones. I think it was just Wayne's incompetence
Okay, and and the bees well, let's get a crossover. Let's have a Biff Tannin's cousin or brother
Mmm, come over and like steal we'll make up a character. I'm gonna take this theater for a little joy ride
Since it seems like we're doing we're all on the agreement of like yeah, this could be plused up a little I have another
Plus up which might be able to be used for the series at large if we were to you know, plus it up now
I would like to see a an old man Logan sort of story of Wayne Zelinski. I would like to see like
modern
Rick Moranis comes back and maybe he's doing a symposium a presentation about his life's work
But he's bitter and grizzled, but he's got a fire up the shrinking machine one more time
You know would be cool is if like he there was some
Experiment that we didn't get to see that you could flash back to that fucked him up like Luke where like his hand shrunk permanently
Like there's a part of his body right? That's that's stuck and that made him like bitter and like I can't use the machine anymore
But now we need the machine but like Nick comes back or his wife had been estranged and he's like
Honey, you need to shrink again
Son of a bitch the name of the movie is honey. You need to shrink again
Works for me. I like that that's come honey. There is further shrinking to do
Yeah, I think there will for sure be another one of these movies. Yeah
Think like a year or two ago
There was like this article with Moranis where and he like said like it's like I don't think I'm done with acting
You know, I just took a break to focus on my kids
Yeah, and there and he was like in there getting older like almost hinting like, you know
Hey y'all can start inviting me to auditions again
I would love a Keaton like a Michael Keaton older Michael Keaton sort of resurgence for my for sure
Yeah, be a comedy or drama
I mean he talked we talked about this recently that he said he almost did a role
But it was like a really low-budget indie thing
You don't want to be in the desert in a motel for eight weeks or something
Oh, but I feel like credit when he said he was like I was offered a cameo in Ghostbusters
But he's like it didn't quite make sense and he's like, why would I just
Arbitrarily show up as this character that I did a couple times like he's the only
Sanity in this world
He's just chilling out up in Canada not doing awful cameos it good for Moranis
I say he doesn't have to do anything
He doesn't want to do but I think but if the right thing we'd all love to see him back
somebody needs to create the right vehicle for him and
I'd love to see him again. Yeah, I think he was as a kid one of the first people
I was like this is a comedy guy. This is comedy
This is a comedian like you see him in things and he's always funny. I like him you love him
Yeah, I know he and he's Fred or Barney Rubble and that's totally different than Wayne Zelinski
Oh, yeah, totally different than Ghostbusters. Yeah, he shows so much range and all those kids. Yeah
I think he'll never act again. That's a guess
I think he's good for him. Why do we keep saying like maybe but it's like maybe Broadway
I mean Daniel Stern does like a Broadway play every year
I feel like Moranis is like that's too much work. I guess he doesn't owe anyone anything. I think that's great. Good for him
I'd love to see him back. But what do we yeah, I don't think it's gonna happen
Yeah, and I don't think this attractions come I mean, I guess if they made another movie a good candidate to
Revive somehow in the parks, but it's really it's left this black hole
In all of the parks both this and tough to be a bug which aren't played on the regular
I mean it still is an animal kingdom, but and it's torn down in California venture. Yeah now it's gone here and
But like all these these movie theaters are in rough states. We're just watching Star Wars clips
Like and Pixar that's what's in Florida right now is a Pixar film festival
Yes, which is crazy like who what yeah why just like who cares they gotta find
It's it's like the way like big box malls are all starting to go away and we got a what do we do with all this space?
We need to like find a good use of Disney movie theaters, and I don't know what it is. Well unlike malls
They can't just stick
climbing
Jim in there
I mean, it's pretty short. There's not a lot of height. Yeah, they're not a lot of height
Figure out some sort of VR thing maybe because that malls are starting to do that
It's not a bad use
I think what's gonna happen is they'll get torn these will get torn down and the redo of Tomorrowland in ten years
But they will sit in a bizarre half space where we watch Pixar movies and Star Wars clips until then
There'll be a terrible state of disarray until then and then they'll just tear it down and finally put a ride there in a deck
placeholder yeah, I
Don't know if it'll be in it well depends when is Star Wars land done this year June
Yeah, I think that it's tomorrow. Let's probably next because while I was working there
We switched the color schemes because remember was the Taco Bell colors at first
Then after that we got the newer kind of hipper colors and then innovations kind of turned down and now it's a Marvel
Showcase I think that whole area is due for an upgrade
The world the big problem they have is a lot of the stuff that's kind of quote-unquote dead or not that great is
Sandwiching one of the most popular rides in Disneyland, which is
Space Mountain so it's kind of hard to like do big
Constructions because if you try and shut down Space Mountain even though they should because Space Mountain goes down so often that needs a whole
New remodel so I think they should take that opportunity to just take that whole corner of
And redo it and re like rework Space Mountain
You know I think with within that if they were to do that take that opportunity to just amp up
Astro-orbiter some more I like that it has the up-and-down controls, but it feels very old
Yeah, I feel like that's also part of the now appeal as the park grows in age
So I think put it back up on a platform like we go through
Re-vamp make sure everything's safe strong new materials on everything and
Lift that baby up make it like when that's a choke point for crowds
Yeah, like it backs up right around Astro-orbiter because it's not a big entrance like yeah originally was exactly
so you just pop that thing up and then make room and also just it like
One of the big things that people like to do is try and get on Astro-orbiter
During the parades and get up there if you have it even higher that it's a rat
I think it's a great idea. I just I guess I'm really negative today because I don't expect Moranis to come out of retirement
I don't expect tomorrow land ever be different. I'm really getting worried
I feel like so long got pushed back on the docket because that movie didn't do well
Oh, well, that's for sure what happened if that movie crushed. Oh, we would have already been
Our animatronic chasing us so sad
But also what a weird idea that the land was gonna get devoted to that like what that they thought that was possible
I don't know if we've been devoted to that but there would have been references for sure. Yeah, who knows?
The one thing don't I swear they just don't touch that beautiful like
Metal wall on the way up to Space Mountain
I'm talking about like on the wall like on the wall of Red Rockets Pizza port
Yeah, it just looks so 80s lax
Retrofuture space wonderful. I love that's what the thing well, I guess you were more probably on the other side of the theater
Maybe I'd want to work the load so that I could just stare at that
And I take that back. I said the burger spot was best. It's actually pizza port. That was the spot
Oh, yeah, especially for us because you just have that the pizza smells just hitting you
Stops, yeah, I gotta get this pizza for lunch
You know, it's the thing we didn't talk about is
last grab of details, I
Did kind of like that the flubber guy is in the line
How like there's the posters of who previously won the inventor of the year award and they nod to
Robin Williams. Yeah, what's his character's name like Martin flub you later?
Yeah, I shared universe idea work I like the imaginative imagination Institute as a concept
I like the logo I had a pen as a kid of the logo
This is this is one of those things where they could bring this back in some form whether it's on the Disney streaming service or
another ride where it's like bring back this and then bring back the mythology of the flubber and the
Nigel chant get Eric Idle back people are demanding people are demanding
Series there must be and then like well as Doc Brown did he ever do work at the imagination?
No, do not ask that question. Of course. He didn't
Bunkers of her Lloyd could be on the show. Yeah, they sure well, that's fine. He never left
Thank you. Just be this character who who like they basically are referencing
Back to the future but just vague enough so people know so yeah
He's been he's been working on a lot of time stuff and it's been interesting to see him get back to it
But we have to look to the future. I
Believe he's a doctor
And like a character in the show is called is like named Marnie and he can go like
It's like old man voice so it obscures it too much but you're like if anyone tries to sue it's like we sing Marnie
Marry
Just invented Rick and Morty
Well, what if there were characters that were kind of like right and Marty that'd be a
You
Know one more thing occurred to me any
Any experience in the in the glasses washing stage? What's what's the difficulty?
Oh, it's very if you've ever worked like a food service job
And you know when you take all the dishes and there's like a system of like you put it here it dips it
It's very similar to that where you actually put it through
like this there's like a washing machine that it goes through so
The reason that you're giving them back to them on trays as you just put the tray to a machine and then you
You sanitize it and then you wipe it down. So it's a whole process
So like the hista line would go I think it's like the pieces of Astro orbiter
Then you would go to the entrance then from the entrance you work the inside of hista
then from the inside of hista you work that the end of the line and the end of line you collect the glasses and as
the show starts you walk back to the
Area to clean them and then bring back some fresh glasses and bring them to the person up front. Oh
Never steal them
You didn't see the value in stealing a bunch of
Okay
Too into that nemo jacket nothing else. Oh, yeah, you don't have it now do you I don't know where it is
I had it but I have no clue where it is
Find that
Yeah, good trivia to your glorious days
Working in the park and thank you so much for for telling us about it. Yes, you waterway you survived podcast the ride
Thank you so much for being here. Hey, let's exit through the gift shop. Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, just check out nerd if it's in it drops on Tuesdays candy dinner with man
Appa DACA drops on Mondays, you know, just stick around got lots of fun stuff coming on
On the horizon so follow me at if you wide away if y in w a di we on Twitter and Instagram
Where I'll keep you updated about those stuffs when I can talk about said stuffs
Oh sure, and we such as if you ever find the jacket mainly the jacket. Yeah. Yeah, I will
Once we get off I'll show you pictures of I have pictures
Right we want to see those pictures for us and there's treats for you waiting on our Twitter tweeted out. Yeah
Your willingness to be public about
Yeah, check us out on Twitter Instagram Facebook. We have merch available at T public go to our second gate patreon patreon.com
Podcast the ride. Yeah, anything else gents? No, I think that's it. That's just yeah, and
remember
There's always as long as there's imagination in the world. There's no I there's no quote from another show
And let me just apologize that we didn't do 40 minutes of Nigel Channing maybe only 15
Well, we got it. We'll do a separate care, but there'll be a whole separate patreon episode about Nigel Channing. Yes
Yeah, so we'll do that promise promise. Yeah episode about a terrible character. All right. Got it. Bye. Thanks everybody. Bye
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson
Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boah Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts calm and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts
Spotify or wherever you get your podcast keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
At forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook