Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate,
which in a mere four months will have been open for longer than Hard Rock Park.
I'm Scott Garrett and you're joined by Jason Sheridan and Mike Carlson.
Hi there, Mike Carlson here.
Eat shit, Hard Rock Park.
We're just gonna keep dunking and dunking.
Just kidding, we love Hard Rock Park.
We love Hard Rock Park.
We wish we could go back in time and that is what we would use the time machine for,
just to visit that park.
We would go back, we would get Hitler and bring him to Hard Rock Park.
To enjoy it with us.
Melt his icy heart with the joy of rock music.
Although I'm now feeling like we're out to have a time machine.
I think one of my first stops might be what we're talking about today,
which to me is like one of the most delightful, odd attractions in theme park history.
And it's not the best documented thing in the world,
but luckily our guest was going to recreate it
through information and audio fax.
For sure in this, our most thorough guest about any topic.
And I'm so glad you're here to talk about returning to the show.
For the second time, he's a writer, he's a DJ and a general purveyor of cool shit.
It's Doug Jones.
Hi, thanks for having me back.
Yay, welcome back.
And our first guest on the second gauge.
Thank you for joining us across the Esplanade.
Much appreciated.
I'm so excited to be here.
But before we dive in, I know we have a lot to cover today.
Yes.
I just want to get a few things out of the way.
I had a feeling this might be the case.
Yeah, I was expecting Doug to call us out because generally when we get together or see you,
you have a couple things that usually you're like,
no, you said something was bad and it's good.
So I was wondering if that's what's going to happen now.
If I feel like strongly enough, I mean, there's dozens of things,
but sometimes something bothers me so much.
I just can't shut up and I'll text you immediately.
All caps.
The last one was Pizzarizzo because I think I said I trashed Pizzarizzo because it doesn't
have so much Muppet theming, but you said, no, that's not true.
You have to look for it.
It's not true.
I have so much Muppet theming.
I mean, and it's on the chopping block.
This is important.
It's just when the seasonal operation, which means that things are not looking good.
I feel like you're trying to bury Pizzarizzo.
I kind of am.
Yes, that's true.
One of my favorite, as far as express quick service goes and themed.
It's so well themed.
I wrote this down and this was a pizza riso was the thing you want to talk about.
Or is that just a side note?
I was going to get into that because there's something else I want to know.
No, I'm glad this came out too broadly.
I'll let you read your piece and then I have something to read as well.
Insanely about this issue.
In the monorail episode dated December 7th, 2018, Mike Carlson said, quote,
it's supposedly a Muppet themed pizzeria, but you walk in there and there's barely
anything that would let you know that it's Muppets.
I mean, the reference is not really a Muppet theme.
It's more specifically a riso the rat themed pizzeria.
And I sent you this photo that I was really excited about.
We were just there as recently as last October.
We spent the better part of an hour in there just exploring and admiring all the details.
You walk in, they've got the, there's Easter eggs in there.
The menu boards are like purposely, the little letters are like missile lines.
It looks like they're placed there by tiny rats.
That's a really subtle one.
But also there's this shelf that has a can of Wilkins coffee.
Anyone?
No, I don't know.
Is that, no, I don't want to guess and be wrong.
What is, what's, what's Wilkins coffee?
Oh, Jim Henson made like over 150 Wilkins coffee.
Oh, the commercial.
Wilkins coffee commercial.
Little stuff like that.
We were just talking about like Ralph, the early days of Ralph.
And I feel like Ralph was in old coffee ads and like pre Kermit kind of like weird amorphous
characters.
Okay, gotcha.
That's a nice little nod.
He was a pre Kermit.
He was also a character, not just a brand of coffee.
It was Wilkins.
He looked a little like Kermit.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
But my favorite thing, if I just had a, I don't want to spend too much time on this.
That's fine.
We have time.
Of course.
And we'll do a whole episode on it.
Pizza Rizzo.
Yeah.
But upstairs on the second floor, there's like a party room.
It's called Rizzo's Deluxe Supreme Banquet Hall.
And it's got a disco ball and a dance floor.
And they're like blasting like seventies music.
It's awesome.
We brought our food up there.
We watched like a group of British, like day campers have a hula hoop contest.
And it was delightful.
A hula hoop contest.
Yeah.
It was just such a good vibe in there.
I recommend even if you've been there before and you don't like it, try going in the disco
room and just hanging out there and tell me.
It looks like a banquet hall from like an Italian wedding.
Yeah.
I do like, I have seen pictures of that and I have to agree with you.
I like the level of detail.
It's fun.
It's a great, it's air conditioned and it's a great way to just relax and break up the day.
So I texted Mike a photo of the marquee that's outside, which I think is just delightful.
And he kind of shook it off and said, oh, it's just a vague reference.
Can I just talk about this marquee and then I'll get over it.
We never have to.
That's fine.
No, no, please, please.
The marquee says somebody got married, which is, you know, the song from a mother's take.
Take me in that.
Join us for the wedding reception of Gil and Lil, daughter of Will and Jill, son of Phil and Bill.
These are.
Muppety kind of joke.
Yeah.
Well, it's, these are the names of the, the people from the adage agency where Kermit goes
to work after he has amnesia.
He has to get a new job and start his life over again.
Oh yeah.
And those are his new coworkers.
When he's like acting all stiff and different.
Exactly.
And then they find him and he doesn't, you know, recognize his friends and he's got this whole
new life and, and you know, they miss piggy punches them in the face and then he snaps out of it.
Featuring DJ electric mayhem.
All right.
That's an easy one.
Playing the greatest wedding hits of all time.
B, Y, O, B and P beer and pizza.
That's a fun little joke.
All right.
But here's.
Is another thing.
Could I respond real quick?
Sure.
I will say as a theme park journalist, I did let the audience down because I realized now
I did not go to the disco room.
So that is an irresponsible comment for me to make overall about the theming.
If I did not get to experience the whole restaurant.
In my head, you, you walked in, you said this sucks.
He turned around and walked right back out.
You're not far off, Doug.
But I will also say what you're, what I'm responding to is I feel that the place feels
a bit cheap to me.
And if you were to go in and say, be our guest restaurant and what you're describing, like,
Oh, one of the meals is named after Robbie Benson, who did the voice of the beast.
I would be less thrilled than seeing where's my Rizzo robot.
Give me the Rizzo robot.
Give me a little more.
I understand.
That's really what I'm getting at.
It would be amazing if we walked in to the disco room and there's an animatronic
electric mayhem.
I mean, that's performing.
I mean, now I would love to see that too, but they're on a budget.
If you take into consideration what it was before, which was the toy story pizza planet,
it's definitely a plus up.
Yeah.
And that was a well rendered pizza planet.
No, yeah.
I didn't have the arcade.
No, no, no.
But there's an Easter egg within the marquee and I swear to God, then then we'll move on.
That's fine.
If you look very closely behind the letters, you'll, you'll see there's kind of like
fading in dust of what the sign used to read before it was a wedding reception.
And it says pot otter memorial service with tribute performance by the frog town hollow
jumbly jug band and Emmett otter jug band reference.
Wow.
So it was a week.
That is good.
It was a wake for the wedding.
Wow.
Those are great references.
And I, yes, you're for sure.
Right.
I missed it.
Yeah.
I missed that.
And you know what?
You're right that if we're, maybe we're finding that this is more of a budget issue
and that you're, you're mad at Disney for not being able to render an animatronic.
But if given the budget, these are clear Muppet fans.
Yes, they were doing, they did their homework.
They cared.
It's like, well, it's so sort of the theme of I, we, I should have approached it more
like we tried to approach Pixar Pier where we were like the animatronics, the Imagineers tried.
I'm sure they tried.
This is clearly a budget and the time issue.
These people love Muppets.
They try to put as much fun as they could do in here, but they just didn't have the robot money.
But okay.
At the risk of opening this wound wide up, wide open again.
And I don't, I really, I'd have no dog in this fight because I haven't been to the place,
but I'd be remiss knowing that you were coming in and with the fact that we got this email
four days ago, this just came up.
Really?
You on the way here to record.
This is from, I'm going to keep them anonymous so that a few does not break out,
but this is a person who works in the Jim Henson creature shop.
And this person emailed us about several things, but mainly to say first pizza Rizzo is not great.
Doug Jones is wrong.
You were called out.
I'm sorry.
And I just had to, I had to, it's so weird that we got the email.
Jim Henson company, then he knows what's going on behind the scenes and he's probably disgusted
by other things.
This guy probably goes beyond the theming.
I think so.
Let me say his, I think it'll reiterate points to say he's probably mad.
He's not getting his salary that he wants.
Let's face it.
He's got another vote to pick.
Or this is somebody who knows me, who doesn't like me.
What if I were to tell you it's Walter, the Muppet who wears the suit.
Well, here's it.
It does wrap around to a happy ending.
I swear.
All right.
I'm sorry.
I'll shut up.
No, no, no.
It's okay.
It's you'll be happy with where it lands.
The theming is not to the level it should be this as there's only some Muppet characters
hanging on the wall and some funny and quotes signs.
Now, do you, I like the signs that you just presented.
I think that I'm over that.
Fantastic.
That's very nice.
Now I cannot speak to the quality of the food as I love theme park pizza.
So you will have to judge for yourself.
So I guess so even he defends the pizza itself.
Anyway, even though Doug Jones was wrong about this whole name, he is right.
Definitive right and wrong.
But at least you're getting a good one here.
He is right about Country Bears being a good movie.
It is not that faithful to the attraction, but it is very fun.
And I used to rent it from Blockbuster a lot.
And the animatronics were done by the Jim Henson Creature Shop.
That's right.
So there you go.
You win some, you lose some.
All right.
I'll feel better.
I'll win some, you lose some.
You're right.
But this was your other yet because I think that dovetailed into we were talking about
several issues you'd raised and one being Country Bears.
And that I feel like we maybe need to explore Country Bears.
Oh, yeah.
We're going to do even as a commentary or something.
We especially as such a huge fan as Mike is of Country Bears.
Yes.
And I think because I've dismissed the movie because I've only saw it in clips.
And I said, this isn't right.
And that's not fair too, maybe.
We'll see, though.
Well, we'll watch it.
It is.
It's if nothing else, a technical achievement because it's 2000, 2001 CGI was in full swing
and being used on everything.
Yet they did it the old fashioned way because they know that's the way the fans wanted to see it.
These people are in costumes with people with remote controls, controlling their eyebrows
and their ears and their mouths.
They put all this hard work on it and no one went to see it.
So they were like, well, it's the last time we ever make a movie this way.
Again.
Yeah.
And now I think we should all feel bad.
I feel like you're trying to say.
I feel supported.
You haven't broken eye contact with me and I feel as if you're blaming me for the loss of.
It's all of us.
I didn't see the movie until this past year.
Oh, you really?
So it's a newer thing for you.
But I saw it based on people saying it's weird and it's strangely good.
Like when it came up in conversation, people spoke positively about it.
And I finally decided to see it for myself.
Can I program this at the Vista?
Do you think the Vista would let us do a Friday midnight?
One of the midnight movies where it's usually like, you know, a midnight movie,
sort of rocky horror thing.
No one will come to it.
I mean, maybe I guess if we're hosting it.
Oh, everyone will come then.
It's not come or I feel like we're like culty movies are getting, you know, I've,
I think I've been to more than one midnight spice world.
Like, is that right?
If that counts as like.
All right, well, let's do it then.
Then, you know, yeah, we have to stretch the boundaries of, you know,
I just watched I knew it at a culty thing.
I want to say how much I enjoyed Josie and the Pussycats.
Really?
I was skeptical of that actually having some good to it.
And I always heard there was this like subversive subliminal messaging thing
about the movie and I'd recommend that to nobody's seen it.
And I have not seen it.
I haven't seen it.
Because again, it's pretty fun.
Yeah.
Decent songs.
I'll also I'll say I've heard some of the songs.
Yeah, I always like the song.
Yeah.
You have another thing, too.
Let's let's let's dive in because I don't want to finally.
Look, yeah, I came prepared.
We knew this was going to.
But every time that you come on there, if there's anything that's that's burning with you,
please bring it up.
I'll write them down.
Yes.
Doug's correction.
You're Andy Rooney.
He has a segment within.
That's great.
And I love that Mike is canceled now.
Mike is canceled.
That's Doug's.
You're done.
I've got you.
I'm trying to get Kevin Hart moment.
No, hey.
Not that kind of cancel.
I'm impressed because.
More casual cancel.
I have to say, I'm really impressed that Mike got the odd or reference.
Yeah.
It's a good one.
And if you if you want to if you want to laugh really hard in Europe,
late watching YouTube videos, watch the Emmett Otters jug band Christmas blooper reel on YouTube.
I've never seen that.
They just like re-released the soundtrack, right?
Because of Paul, all Paul Williams songs are mostly Paul Williams.
That's right.
Yeah.
And they just put that like really.
I just added it to my iTunes or Apple Music.
In fact, great.
There you go.
All right.
We're friends again.
Well, speaking of friendship,
Doug, you just wrote a really great article for OC Weekly, correct?
Yes.
Called A Tale of Two Waltz.
That's about the friendship between Walter Knott and Walter Disney
and the way that the ideas of Knott's Berry Farm and Disneyland intermingled and went back and forth
in the mutual friendship.
And it doesn't seem like they felt competitive.
It seems like when Disneyland opened, it was like, well, this is going to bring more people
to meet and not like this will be this will be a good thing.
That's something that doesn't happen anymore.
Yeah.
Every every anyone in similar areas are natural and Disney and Universal.
Imagine Uber and Lyft saying, you know what?
Let's put our differences like that would just never that would just never happen now.
Well, now now the Universal and Disney World accounts have tweeted at each other bits recently.
That's something like someone's like, I can't wait to go on Space Mountain at Universal.
And they're like, oh, yeah, Universal says, sorry, I think I think you met CC
did Walt Disney World and they're like, yeah, we'll take it from here.
Like, oh, oh, so that's fine.
That's something potentially the same social media third party person.
Is tweeting at themselves, but still could be true.
Yes.
Anyway, I loved the article and I recommend anybody listening to look it up.
Thanks.
And you guys reminded me about that because it came up in
the episode where you're interviewing the season pass guys.
Yeah.
And I was like, oh, yeah, like I knew some of the stuff that Disney really loved the
Calico Mine Ride.
And I was like, there's got to be more to this story.
And that's when I started researching and came up around that same time I was approached
by OC Weekly to write something.
It was just perfect timing.
I was like immediately I was at Disneyland when I got an email from them and I wrote
back from Disneyland saying, here's my idea.
Like, like 30 minutes later.
Oh, you just have it.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah.
Wow.
Geez.
And not even knowing like the depth of what you'd find because it really is like there's
there's so much to it.
I know.
I found a lot of good stuff.
So including that, like I didn't this really fun detail about our beloved Tony Baxter
that he when the Calico Mine Ride opened, he left his shift at Disneyland.
He like snuck out to go experience this ride, which clearly down the line would become an
inspiration for for Splash Mountain.
Clearly.
Big Thunder.
And there's a photograph.
They found a photograph of him on the day of the opening of the Calico Log Ride.
Wow.
Just like kind of standing up on a rock trying to get a better view than all the other
spectators.
That's crazy.
Wow.
Geez, man.
That's cool.
He sees tread and true.
But as one of the aspects of the article is the well, the the Imagineer Raleigh Crump,
who is involved in today's topic, Knott's Berry Tales, who was that's a that's a case
of a Disney person breaking rank.
Oh, I think he was probably long gone from Disney by that point.
But like bringing a lot of stuff he wanted to do at Disney over to Knott's and not to
give away too much.
But I just Berry Tales factored into your article in a great way.
And I'm excited to talk about it.
Yeah, there's multiple Disney people working on Knott's Berry Tales and the people who
are not from Disney that worked on this ride ended up going right to work for Disney afterwards.
You know, because upon its opening in nineteen seventy five, construction and design broke
for the Walt Disney World.
I mean, for a hot.
OK.
Yeah.
So they a lot of these people who hadn't done much before went went right to work on
Epcot.
And oh, yeah, you said it.
You said it was Steve Kirk.
Is that correct?
That's right.
Imagineer, a guy who would go on to create Kitchen Cabaret, one of the best.
Oh, geez.
You still have it out.
Mike Mike for Christmas.
Just like the tea towel, the infamous character tea towel.
Nice.
That's beautiful.
Kitchen Cabaret Merch for Christmas.
It also create, you know, much further down the line, but design Disney Sea, which is
considered by some to be one of the greatest design theme parks of all time.
So this is where they got their start in in nineteen seventy four.
Wow, geez.
Now, I was a little caught off guard because we we Berry Tales had been mentioned
casually, like in conversation among us in the past.
It was mentioned when we were down at Knott's.
Of course, I was not in the best way that day, but I was under the impression
I hung out with you the night before you recorded that.
Oh, yes, you were there.
I forgot.
Drinking.
Someone else was drinking.
I didn't really hang out with you that night.
Now that I think about it.
No, I think we said hi.
We talked for a second.
You didn't hang out.
You were over at the bar the whole night.
I.
Yeah, I.
You were all talking to each other.
Getting out of the.
It's fine.
We won't get into that.
Yeah, we'll talk to friends who want us.
Yeah, that was very rude.
You mentioned it.
You brought it up.
I brought it up.
I didn't bring it up, but I think the the association with
the Berry Tales mentioned and the Raleigh Crump Association,
I was expecting more along the lines of one of our favorites,
the marvelous Marvel McFay, who was sold.
It was just a walk around character and a little stage show.
I had no idea until we got your term paper and the video link
and all these wonderful pictures that like this was a full dark ride.
I really detailed dark ride.
If I could quote your own article because you synopsized it in a wonderful way.
If you don't know this attraction and please.
While you're listening to this, look up a video, look at photos.
It's like you need some visuals to know why we're so excited about this thing.
But as you said, Doug, it is a wild, 100% original eight minute psychedelic
journey full of animatronic critters.
That says it.
And it's that's long for a for a dark ride.
That's very long.
Eight minutes.
So this is the this is such a big full experience.
And for really, we're talking about a guy who worked on the Haunted Mansion
and the Enchanted Tiki Room and it's a small world.
This is an opportunity for him to just really go for it.
Nothing holding him back at his time at Disney.
There are so much hurdles he had jump over to get stuff actually made.
Now, this is a unique situation where for the first time in his career,
he could do what everyone and he had no one to answer to.
And he really, really took advantage of that.
And it's also insane how quickly this ride came together in like
six months from one concept to completion, which is insane.
Jesus.
Wow.
I would describe like just you had brought over you.
What would you call this?
This the storybook, right?
Of the Knott's Berry Tales characters.
Yes.
Journey to the Fair.
So if you're not looking at a photo right now of this and you've never seen this before,
I would almost describe it like a very psychedelic color.
They look a Berenstain Bear-esque.
Yeah.
But they're like.
At least when illustrated.
Less so the robots.
Yes.
Yes, for sure.
But like, yeah, the picture, like the art for promotional use and stuff looks very thin.
But the robots look, I don't know how you would even describe it, but like it's like a kind of
a psychedelic-y Berenstain Bears with like a bear in an old straw hat or top hat and.
It's delightful.
They're delightful characters that, you know, I'm just barely old enough to have gone on this
when I was a kid before it closed.
It closed when I was like seven years old.
So I love these.
I love this ride so much.
I love these characters so much.
I thought this would become a huge thing.
Like all the other things I like.
I like, I just assume that everything would become a huge franchise and that soon we would
get TV, uh, cartoons and movies.
I love DJ Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince.
I had that, there's the first cassette tape and I, you know, that became a hit TV show.
So I thought everything I like is going to become a hit TV show.
Now this went away and I forgot about it.
I didn't think about this for like 20 years until suddenly it came up on YouTube.
I watched the ride through like around maybe 2007 and my mind was blown.
Like I was like, Oh my God, I remember this.
I didn't, it was not a weird dream I had.
This was an actual ride.
I had a similar thing with it where I think I've even said, Oh yeah, I went on this when
I was really young.
Then you sent us information closed in 86.
I would have been one years old.
Wouldn't have happened.
Then I, you, I put, you only put the dots together because they, it became a, some of
it became a walkthrough, which was still there.
The first time I went to knots in the early nineties.
I don't know when that went through.
So that's, but I do have a very distinct fuzzy hazy memory, but I think what's weird
is as a kid, I had, I was like, I had mixed it up with it's like it's underground and
it's little critters working on something in my head.
They were either Fraggles or Smurfs.
Like I've had this odd thing in my brain of like, wasn't there some Smurfs thing?
Well, there was, there was a Smurfs thing at Kings Dominion in Virginia, which I think
they did build at some of the other parks, but not for very long.
Some Smurfs thing, but no, I know, but I for sure remember if I like the, the, if I could
crystallize my childhood memory, I pretty sure it involves the chug a chug machine.
I think I remember a crazy Rube Goldberg machine and a bunch of bears kind of like rotating
around.
So I know, and I, and so I feel if you went on this one, it was an actual ride in the
full thing.
It must've loomed very strong in the memory banks.
I mean, it's, it's the sights, the sounds that had a great theme song, the, it, it smelled,
the ride smelled like boysenberry pie.
So all every sense is triggered and, and, uh, where to begin?
This there's, there's so much, uh, I, yeah.
Okay.
Well, so we are all right.
It's, it's 74 and Mary, Marion, not, uh, not's daughter, the daughter of the youngest daughter
of the youngest daughter, which we need to acknowledge that a Marion is Marion is the
name of a type of Berry and it's spelled like a Marion Berry.
So they named her clearly after there's no way they were like, well, we, what if we called
her Marion?
Not choice to pursue the family business.
So we like be looming over her from day one and to create a ride where everyone else,
all the names are also very, very based.
So, well, I don't understand, like there, there, maybe you can clear this up.
They had a giant space for a ride, but no ride.
Like this was because with this, the positioning of this thing is really strange and it's a show
building.
It's still there to this day where the ride voyage to the iron reef is.
And it's on, it's, it's all on the second floor of a massive show building, but that's what I
can, they built it and then weren't, didn't know what to do.
Why would you do that?
That's, that's odd to me.
They're taking a lot of missteps.
I believe it was an arcade, but there's this area, that area, and it was one of the least
successful things they've ever done.
It only lasted four years.
There is like this mountain where you climb onto the mountain, you go into a cave and then
there's nothing inside.
And he was just like, what is the point of this?
There's like, yeah.
So they were kind of, they were really looking for something to do with that, that area.
There's just people and like, you know, they look like what the gummy bears wear.
That's, that's an odd, like, and they're just people.
There's no, like, these are your new lovable characters, just somebody in a smock or whatever.
Yeah, very odd.
And there was, oh my God, just a mountain with nothing yet.
So there's this massive area of the park with no real attraction to justify it and they want
to drive traffic to it.
Yeah.
And thus, and, and, and also in this same snippet, I copy pasted from what you gave us.
That it is a 20,000 square foot show.
Huge.
Yeah.
And as you said, the dark rides in fantasy land are 10,000 square feet.
So this is twice as big as your Snow White.
So they have an opportunity to do something huge here.
And it just so happened, you know, one of the Disney Imagineering's biggest legend,
Rilly Crump has just gotten back from another project and didn't have anything going on.
Was he doing something?
Was he like making something in China that didn't happen or a Chinese themed attraction?
Circus World.
Oh, Circus is what I thought.
Yeah.
It's his pre or post Marvel McFay.
Do you remember what year that was?
I don't know.
I'll look it up later.
But he's this like, yeah, we've talked about him before, especially if you go back to our
Haunted Mansion, like Origins episode, our star slowly stepped through part one of Haunted Mansion.
Yeah.
He's so unique and psychedelic and responsible for Marvel McFay, who we really loved.
Seems like he has a thing for deeply earnest characters mixed with psychedelic,
a mixed return of the century.
And I found another thing.
Did any of you guys come across or have you heard in general of another
crump design thing called Tex Critters pizza jamboree?
I know I don't have any other.
I've seen that, though, but I don't know.
I don't know the story.
There's not much more beyond photos, I don't think.
And not a lot of.
And it's even unclear to archivists of this stuff where there even was one.
I think there was a giant one in El Paso, Texas, that was like a proof of concept to do more.
It was part of like a mini golf kind of thing.
But yeah, Texas is a dragon and joined by Foxy Roxy and Country Cowl and Skeeter,
the rattlesnake.
And they're just like, and knowing this style, it's weird that we didn't know about this already.
Well, like it's the most up.
We're all we're all rock of fire fans here.
We're all Chuck fans here.
So that he made, oh, my God, a pizza jamboree.
And the other one more Raleigh Crump thing that I forgot about until I read an interview with him.
Ernie Ball.
He was the designer.
If you get Ernie Ball guitar strings or other accessories, that psychedelic logo is Raleigh Crump.
Oh, Raleigh Crump is really like I think I probably said this on the Marmalade.
He like feels like there's he's like some regular cartoonist mixed with like Jack Kirby,
psychedelic 70s cosmic stuff like the color palette Kirby used and like new gods stuff
and all the way far out stuff.
It's like the perfect blend of it.
We got it.
We should get Raleigh.
We should figure this out.
He's still around.
We can do it.
Yeah, he's done exhibits and he just that big LA Times.
Todd Martin's wrote that big LA Times profile about him.
Oh, good.
Yeah.
Okay.
So he's he's free.
He's given free rein essentially to do whatever he wants.
It's a pretty IP free park.
So it's on him to figure something out, though.
There's also a lot of stipulations.
It seems like he keeps in a studio notes way.
He keeps getting thrown.
Do whatever you want, but it's got to be this and it's got to be this.
Yeah, he got a script that was just a very simple like a little boy and his donkey go
to the fair and that was it.
So he's like, okay, well, he started embellishing that script and adding things
and creating characters.
And then they test.
There are some bears in his idea and they wanted to test everything with like a marketing
firm is like the bears tested very well.
So then suddenly all the human characters on the ride became bear characters and foxes
and rabbits and stuff like that.
And then I think at one point he was just all right, let me do my thing.
No more testing like just telling them to go stop.
Well, I'll say he's also like, you know, I come from Disney and even with all the oversight
of Disney, they don't test stuff.
If Walt did whatever his instinct was.
And they also they had the opening lockdown.
Is that is that correct?
They had the opening lockdown and it was going to be in an area called the roaring 20s.
They were going to re theme that as as they're developing knots,
buried tails, that area turned into that.
They came up with the roaring 20s.
So they're building bolt.
They're building the ride and the new area at the same time.
So it also then become important later on in the story.
OK, sure.
He's going nuts on designs and empowering other artists to do great stuff and like
well, things are going well, but I don't know if this is the point to talk about the disaster
on the way to the opening of the ride.
The the little fire.
Inferno.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, he he had hired this guy named Tommy O'Neill, who had a company called Fantasy
Fair that did all the window attractions at Disneyland.
OK, and said, I want you to be my guide.
I actually build this ride.
And he said, I don't think I've never built a ride before.
I don't know about this.
Had to be persuaded a little bit.
They get them on board.
They need a bigger space because Fantasy Fair, his studio was in Hollywood on Santa
Boulevard, didn't have enough space.
They bought like a warehouse in Glendale on San Fernando Road that was approximately
20,000 feet square feet, the same as what the ride would be.
So they start building right there.
It got to the point where it was time to start moving stuff over into the show building at
And they got worried because Fantasy Fair was a non-union endeavor and and not hired
union workers to to make over the roaring 20s area.
So they said, let's wait till they're done with their work and then we'll move everything
over.
And Mary and not said, oh, no, it's fine.
I'll talk to them.
There won't be any problems.
Oh, and it's so it's the
Union people.
Yes.
Set the bill.
Someone on the union side set the building on fire as to send a message to the non-union
and there were like five fires, right?
Yes. March 27th, 1975, when when they're just a few like getting very close to opening and
they've already installed about 50 to 75 percent of their ride.
Fire breaks out and five different places and it's definitely arson and it's and they
never caught the person who did it despite the fact that she put up a reward.
It was definitely union people having a grievance with non-union people coming into their domain
and they only got a six week extension to rebuild.
They wanted open on 4th of July, 1975.
So they had to work like around the clock.
It's crazy.
I don't know how they do it.
I mean, also, Marian, you don't talk, right?
You pay.
That's how you solve those disputes.
Jersey expertise.
You got to pay them off.
Then they'll look the other way.
I don't know how it got done so fast without this, let alone with without a fire.
Let's say that it was from concept to completion in six months.
That includes the six week extension that they were given after the fire broke out.
The animatronics weren't so sophisticated, but they were animatronics.
Yeah.
I don't think, I think maybe the animatronics were the only things that didn't get burned
because those are the last things to come in.
So we're talking about the set pieces.
We're talking about the fake rocks.
We're talking about the chug a chug machine.
Oh man, the beloved fake rocks got burned.
Fake rocks.
Yeah.
Geez.
So they just pick up and keep working.
They get a minor extension and then they, all right, let's keep blowing in.
And they're just, you know, they're just staying up to three o'clock in the morning
every single night, you know, bringing over a six pack of beer and a bag of hamburgers
and just going for it.
God, that's how we get this show done.
I constantly have a greasy sack of hamburgers I just reach into.
It sounded like, yeah, the knots were like, no, we'll send,
people can enjoy the rubble.
They can enjoy the char if we're getting this open, even if it's ashes.
Yeah, so odd, but they keep, they keep going and it opens without,
stop me if I'm ever missing anything, but.
And the ride opens the 4th of July, 1975.
And it's awesome.
It's successful on the whole new roaring 20s of air is amazing and
attendance increases at the park by 52%.
And let's talk about the ride itself.
Yeah, yeah, it's it's just it's it's magical.
It's so much fun.
It's delightful.
This storybook tells the story of the ride.
And I was saying before we started recording, what if you had what a delight to like ride
this ride and get off like, I want a souvenir.
I want to remember that.
And then you had this great story.
It's like a really solid, nice piece.
And like the argument is so delightful inside.
Well, I imagine, Doug, you're saying like when you wrote it, you were like,
oh, there's going to be shows and TV things.
And like, I feel like any of the good, like exclusive theme park rides
that have characters that are only in the parks,
you're naturally like imagining the full world.
It's opening up your imagination of like what else is going on in this universe.
And so like this is a nice I mean, I'm assuming there's probably other versions of like,
maybe there was a Haunted Mansion book or something, but this is like you would take
here's a little more piece is a little extra.
Like taking part of the ride.
Oh, it's always nice to have something you could take home with you.
Sure.
But this actually is like a narrative.
This is a narrative at least.
Yeah.
I mean, it's similar to the ride.
I was talking about the souvenir book that they sold called Journey to the Fair,
Knott's Berry Tales.
It's one of the few bits of merch that you could you could find from this ride.
And you know, that Knott's style, it's like it's like a whole book that looks like the
Knott's logo.
Yeah.
That just like calming, curly Q kind of it like feels very it's just such Americana.
Knott's very much was like they were playing into the all the nostalgia around the
bicentennial 70s by way of old timey.
Can we start by talking about the names of the characters?
That seems to make sense.
Because we're following a family of bears to a fair is the basic.
That's the basic tenet of the ride.
Yeah.
So there's the would you even say patriarch?
That's the father.
What's the grandfather of a family's called?
Elder Berry.
Elder Berry is his name.
I was just looking for like what his title in the scheme of things.
What's the patriarch is?
Poppa.
Let's call him Poppa.
And then these are the adults, right?
These are the these are the parents.
Is that right?
Yes.
Okay.
That's Flapper Berry and Raspberry.
And then the children.
Girl sin Berry and Boy's sin Berry.
And they make up the notson Berry family.
The notson Berry heroes.
And I was just trying to figure out is Jason Moore Raspberry or Boy's sin Berry?
Because I could see him both berries.
You know what I mean?
I guess I Sunday to wake up in your boys and Barry and Sundays to wake up in your
grasp.
I think he's a Raspberry because Jason's a little bit of a stinker.
I think that's the answer.
I'm looking for a little bit of a stinker.
I guess correctly.
Yeah.
Well, but also you share some traits in common with the villain of the tale.
Well, you know, I am I empathize with crafty coyote.
Crafty coyote.
Yeah.
He's trying to steal all the pies, all the boys and Barry pies throughout the ride.
So you are crafty, I guess.
You're everyone in this story.
Very tales characters at once.
So we're in a world of bears and it seems like their lives are really guided and driven
by the promise of the fair and by making boys and Barry pies to show off and sell at the fair.
Perhaps the win first place.
Something to get guiding principle for the year.
It's such a simple story, but you know what's going on.
You've talked in the past on the podcast about how so many Disney dark rides at fantasy land
are confusing because it's like, OK, I'm on the Snow White ride.
Where's Snow White?
Oh, I'm Snow White.
OK.
And then it's and then it ends.
So suddenly this this this ride is clear.
It has a beginning, middle and end and a very satisfying ending.
And you don't have to think you just you just enjoy it.
You just enjoy some mild peril.
It's never too scary.
Right.
But the path to the fair has some trouble, but it all works out.
Not a big problem.
It's honestly I find the whole thing a little like it's kind of a proto Splash Mountain.
Absolutely.
Yeah, it's it's it's critters, it's banjo.
It's scary in the middle, but a big celebration at the end.
Because all the characters come together in the finale.
Because I'm like, when is America Sings open in the 70s?
And I feel like that's awesome.
I'm 10 years after this.
After this.
So this is before America Sings where all a lot of the characters from
America Sings ended up on Splash Mountain.
I wonder if that I like I wonder if there was some feeling of you guys kind of doing
a show with this this big like this country critter.
Also post country bear jamboree.
Right.
Oh, you're right.
Oh, well, this is kind of the area everybody's dancing in.
Because people love country bears.
That is a fact.
So we have our family.
We're going to head to the fair with them.
We're introduced to my favorite element, the chug of chug machine.
Like a good Rube Goldberg, which is so delightfully designed.
I was you know, you were also not only did you send us a big list of
big list of facts and notes about this attraction, you also sent us a video.
But you also said, please look at photos, because I think the video is not going to
give you the right idea.
And you're absolutely right.
Because the video is a little murky.
This ride was not like at least in a way we can consume this right isn't archived
in the best way.
But I flipped through those photos to Erin and she was like, oh my god, like in love
immediately, like seeing it lit and rendered nicely.
Cutest design.
So, so adorable.
It's it's important to look at everything because the details that there's so many
details and but it's also important to remember that it was not lit up like that.
Like it is in the right through video in the right through video.
They've got like the floodlight on the camcorder.
Right.
Otherwise, it was pretty dimly lit and just neon, neon, neon, like everything glowed.
And that is as we go through, we'll walk everybody through the right through right now.
So just keep that in mind that like everything was just fluorescent.
Well, we should we talk about the Raleigh Crump fluorescent light thing, because this
is one of the things that he wanted to do.
Like Disney was very particular with the way the dark rides are done.
And Raleigh had always had this this lighting style he wanted to experiment with.
And Disney just being stiff about stuff, wouldn't let it happen.
And he had to pay it off here.
That's right.
He he always wanted to mix blacklight with incandescent light.
And that's an idea he's kind of stole from the the Movieland Wax Museum right up the
street in Bueno Park.
Yeah.
And which, yeah, they were Disney was convinced it wouldn't work.
And he's like, there's a thing up the road that does it beautifully.
Right, right.
And isn't there this got to be something in Disney in the Disney universe that does
some amount of this.
Yeah, I'm trying to think like blacklight in general.
What's that lighting style in in Avatar?
The bioluminescence.
Oh, by the way, they're not afraid to use bioluminescent light.
Yeah, it's true.
I'm trying to think.
I mean, there's like a little like there's like blacklight stuff on some of the dark
rides on Splash Mountain has some dark some some regular lighting and blacklighting.
Yeah.
There's little pieces of it, but nothing, I guess, is as aggressive.
This sounds like it was a very aggressive because he wanted you to be disoriented.
Yeah, then we'll talk later on.
There are parts where he specifically is messing with your eyes to give up.
He wants you to like rub your eyes because your eyes are fucked up.
Yeah, that's something that Disney didn't never want to fuck up people's eyes on purpose.
Right.
Well, that's important.
And then also this Raleigh Cross section.
The thing where it's it's old timey mixed with 70s and but also like clearly there's like a
stoner appeal for.
Yeah, that's what so the Jack Kirby comparison I keep going back to is because it's like
he's a very it's a very classic cartoon style mixed with the time it was being created,
but being created by somebody who was an older man already at this point wasn't not super old,
but like what a 40s maybe 50s.
Yeah.
So like it's like it's old.
It's clearly from like an old classic sort of style through this new druggy psychedelic lens,
which is what is so cool about it.
OK, so where do we so we're the Chug Chug machine.
We're hearing that we're smelling the boys and very.
We're in the factory.
They're making the boys and very and the jellies and the jams.
Hard at work.
You know, everything's spinning around.
Uh, you've got the smoker 27, which is a reference to really he had his design studio
designer 20s, uh, 27.
OK, and.
And he was a smoker.
Oh, OK, sure.
Also like Jack Kirby, Jack Kirby famously showed on those big cigars.
Oh, yeah.
And when we say smoker, do we know what was really a weed guy?
Like we would assume, you know.
Oh, yeah, he's definitely.
While he was still at Disney, he was making drug related stuff on his own time
and like nudie stuff as well, stuff that he was hiding from Disney.
And then I there's like a story where Disney comes from behind his back
and he's like, oh, no, I'm fired.
And Disney laughs and pats him on the back.
He's like, keep up the great work.
I love it.
And then later asked like, hey, that the the those those smoke box,
smoke paraphernalia artwork, can you send me some of that stuff?
You were working on.
Wow, really?
Yeah, I never heard that.
Yeah.
Well, we all have to get high with Rolly.
I think that's the goal.
We do an interview with him.
And then we get high with him as well.
I mean, come on.
Yeah, that was I mean, that was one of the famously we were recording
this right around the time when Bob Iger put his foot in his mouth,
taking shots at Expedition Everest.
But a few months ago, he got a lot of flack.
I thought undeservedly for like implying that Walt Disney was a bit of a lush.
Walt Disney was a lush like it's called.
I call it space, babe.
Yeah, yeah.
So this chug a chug machine, which they is one of the things that completely
burned down Christopher Crump, Rolly's son was basically this was his only job
was to build this amazing machine that just had like spinning gears and gizmos
and ping pong.
There's a disco ball on top of it.
It's just incredible.
So that was completely lost.
So it took him six months to make it.
Oh, my God.
And then had me make it from scratch in six weeks.
God.
And then, you know, we go into the bakery kitchen where all these beavers are
making some freshly baked boysenberry pies.
And then we get our very first glimpse of our villain.
Yeah.
Crafty Coyote.
No, he's he's he's reaching for a rack of pies trying to grab the one on the very top.
And it was I believe that in the book and I don't remember if on the ride
it says it's a cooling rack specifically.
It's just like a series of shelves for cooling pies, which is a piece of furniture
I assume Jason has in his.
Is that true, Jason?
It does not maybe rack or two in the house.
A couple of different cooling racks.
I'll call you a pie lush.
That's fair.
Well, I am what I am.
So.
And like I said, the smell of boysenberry throughout all of this delightful.
Oh, it's so fun.
Yeah.
Crafty.
But now the threat is on.
Right.
You're avoiding crafty Coyote at all because as you enter the frog forest, which I love
this guy, like I assume you can't see great in the video, but I assume it's all like frogs
on wires that all like spring up at various.
They're practicing for a jumping contest.
It's also at the fair.
Right.
There's even a referee froggy.
He's judging them all.
That's great.
And there's just frogs everywhere.
It's just like so dense and incredibly detailed and everything's glowing.
And and it's it's incredible.
This scene, there's so many.
I do wish it's really.
Hey, you made the point to us.
Watching a video of the ride is not going on the ride.
And clearly that is the case with this.
I do wish that we could experience this thing like with the with the lighting and then the
sense the way it was meant to be.
Well, maybe we'll maybe we will someday.
We'll get to that.
Oh, good.
But now we head to the fortune teller camp.
That's right.
Which is in an enchanted forest, kind of a continuation of the frog forest.
And we see fortune tellers and makeshift tents with 70 psychedelic floor prints on them.
We meet all kinds of interesting characters in this fortune teller camp.
Well, my favorite name of anybody is Zaz, Zaz the owl.
There's a couple signs of Zaz.
Is that Zaz?
That's Zaz.
Yeah, OK.
Really like Zaz.
Yeah, Zaz is great.
I thought he would look for the first time I was looking through.
I look like a little bit like a wizard, but I mean, it's a similar.
He sees things.
He does conducts floating music instruments.
That's cool.
There's a lot of cool effects in this.
Sarah Skunk, who we meet, who's in a tent watching.
She's looking into her crystal ball, but she's not seeing into the future.
She's watching an old Western movie.
That's a funny little gag.
We meet that Thelma frog, who's a palm reader.
We meet Wanda Fox, who is standing on the side, her magic teacups that are spouting
intensive steam and an animated projection turns the steam into a ghost.
And this is a very cool visual effect.
So like, keep in mind, this is this is the guy who worked on the Haunted Mansion,
which has a lot of cool visual effects before you even get on the ride when you're just
walking down through the queue.
And here he is trying to to to outdo himself to or at least top top what he did on the
Haunted Mansion.
And in a pre digital era.
So you were these are effects that are tapping back into like turn of the century magic
and right now projecting on steam clouds.
Yeah, that that YouTube video is really cool.
So he enlists this magician named Leo Benke, who is a guy who opened up the Merlin's magic
shop at Disneyland and managed it.
It's not the current magic shop.
There used to be two magic shops at Disneyland.
Steve Martin worked at both of them.
He talks about this in his book.
He worked there was more than one.
He worked at both.
Yeah.
So he enlisted this this magician to help him like hash out these visual effects and
how they were going to pull them off.
And they're they're really cool, especially for nineteen seventy five.
They're pretty impressive.
We'll talk about more.
And there's more in in some of the upcoming scenes.
As we leave the Fortune Teller camp, we catch a glimpse of Crafty Coyote who's sleeping
off a tummy ache from all the pies he's stolen.
Oh, right.
This was my favorite part of the ride.
This is my favorite.
I was starting to jug sent that and then I was writing an email like I got to think of
a good Jason joke.
And you had already got an alert new message from Jason.
Yeah, you were right to it.
Yeah, I, you know, had a Shake Shack burger and shake at lunch, starting to feel like
Crafty Coyote myself.
Oh, I've noticed you've been yawning like crazy.
Oh, it's fine.
No, no, it's great.
No, the food you're not.
I know you're not like checking out.
It's just the food affects you.
You think it affects everyone?
I know, but more so you.
So it was a hearty milkshake.
But give Jason credit as he currently is not he doesn't have his shirt open and displayed
out and crumbs all over his belly.
No, I'm just for once.
Just hold up in a near fetal position looking at my iPad.
This scene with Crafty Coyote passed out to this to me is kind of like the the dog with
the keys in his mouth and from the jail cell pyres of Caribbean.
This to me is like the iconic scene that you go home with.
You're still laughing and thinking about it when you're when you're on your way home.
So then you enter the Thunder Cave.
With ominous signs telling to go back and beware.
And this is a part of the ride where it gets dark and the rocks are shining and they shoot
strobe lights on the rocks and into your eyes.
And this is deliberately meant to mess up your eyes.
Seizure, seizure.
You're going down a steep decline.
So you are actually going down onto the first floor at this point.
Oh, OK.
Oh, they do utilize that.
This is free nights and white satin ride.
I love it.
Disorienting dark ride.
There was a psychedelic ride before that.
Wow.
Crazy.
That's been which probably kids must have freaked out in that thing.
So it seems scary.
People must have had like an epileptic fit.
Must have.
It must have because we covered up at the time.
Right.
And like there wasn't a name for the thing they were experiencing.
And they're allowed to sit down and give them a glass of water.
It'll be fine.
Have a smoke, kid.
All these spiders are just like start lowering themselves over your head,
like just barely almost within reach.
And I know I would freak out.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Like bad trip waiting to happen.
Yeah.
This is Raleigh going, hey, ease off actually.
Be careful with those drugs.
This is when you got the bad stuff.
So the spider tail leads you into the weird woods.
Weird woods, which your eyes will still be adjusting to.
Exactly.
Weirder.
This is all those messing with your eyes was so that everything in the weird
woods would look even weirder than it already does.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I was just going to say like in that one Raleigh interview that came out recently,
he keeps like stressing how he wants Disneyland to be weird.
Like the word weird is like his favorite thing, I think.
Disneyland weird.
Exactly.
He wants everything weird.
So the weird woods is like he's getting his wish.
I hear what he's saying.
Of course.
Yeah.
Why not?
You know, yeah, it is a little odd that we are in.
I'm a defender of IPs more than I'm not, but I do, I don't know.
Like it does feel like maybe we've departed from the world where theme parks are.
Like this ride is going to be kind of this like this one artist's like singular.
Like we're going to let him just go to town.
Like you don't hear about like this designer who did the hell out of this part of Avatar or whatever.
It's very, I don't know.
Like given artists free rein would be a nice thing to keep alive in the Disney parks.
There's so many quality check levels now.
Do you get the delight that comes from, you know, creativity being the,
or no, what's the phrase?
Necessity is the mother of invention.
Is that right?
That's a phrase, yeah.
That is a phrase.
But I feel like so often in theme, a lot of the stuff that lingers in theme parks,
he's from like, well, we needed to do this.
We didn't have a ton of time or a ton of money.
And am I confusing things?
Is really crump the guy who did, who did make those like paper mache type animals in,
in it's a small world.
I think so.
Because like, I'm sorry if I'm mixing up facts, but like Mary Blair ish design, but then it's all,
it's like her and his like the animals had to be done extremely quickly.
Yeah.
He helped construct it, but the, the ride itself is from Mary Blair's designs and concepts.
She's pretty much like, they pretty much let her to go to town on that and do whatever she
wanted with that with very little input.
However, when the ride moved from the, uh, world's fair in 64, they packed it up in a
truck and moved it to Anaheim.
They had to create a new facade for the ride.
Uh, an exterior that wasn't at the world's fair.
And that's when they kind of brushed her to the side.
She had come up with a concept and they rejected it.
So they went to Roli and they were like, Hey, can you design the facade of it's small world?
And he did it based on her designs so that it would all be uniform, have a uniform look.
Oh, he felt bad because she was really upset that they rejected it.
So he actually consulted with her as he was designing it.
He would call her on the phone.
He'd send her a sketch.
Like he drew a little, he asked her, I think, draw me a little clock.
Like, how would you draw a clock?
And she sent to him.
And then he would just, he just put that right in as the clock is the centerpiece.
Oh, we missed all this.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Well, this is cause you know, uh, so next time you take a, a photo of the front of it's
a small world, hashtag Roli Crump, not Mary Blair.
And then he's doing all this after they just like destroyed his tower of the four winds
that used to be, uh, at the world's fair.
They did not opt to bring that to Anaheim.
Yeah.
He, uh, he went at work.
I mean, Disney passed away in 66 and that's, I think when he was like, you guys are, I'm out.
Like, uh, didn't like the direction that they were going in.
Uh, well, I think, you know, like, I think we've,
clearly our appreciation for knots has grown a lot while we've been doing this podcast and
the trip that we got to take there.
And it's occurring to me that for what we experienced about those mazes is that, you
know, those are like, those are seasonal.
They're not up all year, but like we were walking around those mazes with the guy who
did it and it was like, go to town.
And, and with the, so the, and I think in general, it didn't, weren't we talking to
somebody else who, uh, one of the people we talked to, I feel like was a Disney expat
who is allowed to do whatever or who has much more free reign at knots.
And that's why they like working there.
So I think not to be very wise to keep going in that direction.
And like, it does feel like where that spirit is still alive of this massive, uh, uh, you
know, show experience is a guy's singular vision.
And like, you know, that might mean it's a little sloppy or weird in parts, but it's
going to be like, like nothing you would experience anywhere else.
Yeah.
I mean, that more than even Disney, even the classic stuff that's original IP,
Disney is like multiple people.
Like how to mention is multiple people's vision all put together in a nice cohesive package,
but it does seem like this specifically, and then these, your mazes you're talking about,
like there's even more room at knots for like it just to be the auteur theory of, of the
ride.
Man.
Oh, they have to keep their chances.
Yes.
I mean, I'm sure there's of course always a million people that work on these things
and maybe some critical element was designed by not the person and you never find out
necessarily that that was, but it does seem like this is a little more pure role.
Like you can really feel rolly everywhere.
When it's what the sense that I get about like the vague, what I could tell about the
spirit of the Garner Holt shop and what they've done on the, the Reed vamp of the Calico
mine ride and, uh, uh, and then hopefully what's coming with the rapid ride that these
are more, these are more like a tour.
Yeah, maybe a tour theory.
Let's keep going that way.
But you hear about, um, uh, like at Pixar, they always talk about how like anyone at
the company is allowed to give their thoughts on current projects and stuff.
So there's like, obviously there's pluses and minuses to all of that stuff.
If everyone's talented in putting stuff in, you can make a fun, like I got haunted mansion
is two separate men's philosophy mixed in with Rolly's weird, cool, like, uh, leota room
and stuff.
But like it is, I guess you could fan as like, what is the Claude Coats version of it look
like?
What does a full scary haunted mansion look like?
Is it better?
Is the Mark Davis version better where it's kooky the whole time?
They're both sound pretty fun, honestly.
Yeah.
There's pluses and minuses to both of them.
But the clashes between people is what really keeps things interesting.
That's what's interesting for that thing.
But this is the, yeah, this one specifically is cause it's so much of like, I can, I can
feel the man's voice in it.
I can feel the person who made it to voice.
Yeah.
And the disparate elements he's pulling together in his brain.
I also like we're still in the weird woods and the, the, you pointed out the sign that
says you are entering the weird woods population.
Scary.
Said that's, that's up my, I really like anything where the, the, the fact is wrong or like
the wrong type of word.
This does, the weird woods does tie into what we were just talking about, the haunted
mansion, because haunted mansion began with the museum of the weird, which was Rolly's
weird idea that he had.
And everybody, all his coworkers, the other imagineers were saying, Walt won't like it.
It's too weird, Wally.
They're making fun of him.
And then sure enough, Disney showed up.
He saw his little, he had already gotten so far along with the concept art and the models.
Walt was like, yeah, this stuff is pretty weird.
So like Rolly, like that, this is one of my favorite haunted mansion stories.
I don't believe you told this on the first of many podcasts.
Maybe we'll get to it the next three or four part.
Who knows?
But like 22, we'll get to it.
He went home, dejected, came back to work the next morning and Walt was sitting in his
desk wearing the same suit he had on from the day before.
And he's like, Rolly, I can't stop looking at your, your concepts.
And you're just like, I didn't go to sleep last night because I can't stop thinking about
your, your, all this weird stuff.
Ended up like had changed his mind and ended up incorporating some of that from the Rolly's
museum of the weird.
So here's where he really got to take that idea.
He had, you know, years, years earlier and just go to town and make it weirder and more
imaginative than he ever thought was possible.
So we've got like evil looking purple trees, weird mashup creatures.
You got a llama giraffe hybrid and birds wearing hair, hair curlers and
unidentified creatures with red beards and they're making something called weird
juice in a, in a glowing bathtub.
Yeah.
Weird juice.
I want, I want weird juice.
Yeah, we should sell weird juice.
What a, oh man, I would be the first in line.
Like they're, they're not butter beer is weird juice, but I don't want it in a bottle.
I want to like, they give me, they, I pay money.
They hand me a ladle and I, oh yeah.
That's great.
Keith, the ladle, their souvenir.
The big K at the bottom.
Oh, that's so fun.
We passed by crafty Coyote secret lair and we realized that he's from the weird woods.
Sure.
Oh, he's origin.
Yes.
Little origin story.
It's like if you drove by crime alley in a Bababoo.
Exactly.
Oh, so fun.
And yeah, then this takes us to our grand finale, which is, is far bigger than any of the,
this is like almost half of the, half of the space of the, of the, of the building is the fair.
We reach our destination.
And, and this is just like sent, like sensory overload.
There's just so much going on at this fair scene all at once.
We see, we see a bunch of bears in a hot air balloon ride.
Dr. Fox is selling weird juice out of his medicine wagon.
And he's claiming all the different ailments that it will cure warts, hang nails,
baldness, cure all.
It says weird juice on there.
We see Wally the wirewalker, the tightrope walking rabbit.
We see a puppet show with, with, with bunny rabbits going on.
And the bunny rabbits that are marionettes are like juggling.
And that's a really cool, like visual effect to see a, a puppet juggling.
Uh, uh, Madam Wong bangs her gong and offers to read your fortune cookie.
Maybe this one would have had to change a little bit.
Sounds a little racist, but she was, when I did my deep research, I, I, I,
I read that she was designed by Doris Young, a Chinese artist.
Okay.
That makes me a little bit more comfortable with this concept.
And I like that she actually bangs the gong, that it is a practical, like the machine
hits it.
Yeah, that's cool.
So we have a lot of callbacks here.
Sarah skunk.
We see her again this time.
She's levitating Zazz the owl and, uh, and, uh, theta bears created a magic
card castle.
It's just like standing, a standing, a castle made out of playing cards,
not to be outdone.
The frogs have made their own miniature frog fair.
So they're getting, they're getting, they're getting in on
the fun too.
It's like a fair within the fair that we're already at.
Wow.
That's, that's an auteur fair.
Yeah.
You're right.
We see the Knotsonberry family who are posing to have their portrait taken
by a photographer.
It seems like they've just won first prize for best pies at the fair.
Elderberry is wearing a zoot suit looking mad foul.
Yeah, that's the first time the twenties have really come up with this for me.
It seems a lot more agrarian beforehand, a little more.
Yeah.
We're not sure what's happening in the, in the urban areas.
Maybe you missed us mentioned that the, uh, the mommy berries name is
flapper berry.
Well, yes, that's true.
Yeah.
Good point.
We've reached past that.
Uh, uh, crafty, uh, coyote has finally been caught and lands himself in prison.
A boysenberry pie just out of his reach.
It was like, ah, son of a gun.
That seems cruel and unusual to me.
Unnecessary.
Well then yeah.
Very.
I'd also like to point out of the, of the many visuals you sent us, one of the only
ones I, uh, uh, I've been able to put a saving in my document was the, the
wanted poster for crafty coyote.
He's described as tall, thin and hairy.
The reward for his capture is 5,000 berries.
You get bait and berries and you get all his other names.
Sweet tooth, hairy Fargo fats, chubby cheeks, Charlie, purple tongue, Tommy,
and red nose Nelson.
Okay.
Yes.
I know people are, I did go by purple tongue Tommy for a little while.
That is also one of my alter egos.
That was you.
Yeah.
You bastard.
Give me my berries.
No.
Fair enough.
I tried.
Um, I would love this suit.
Um, and this is not, this is raspberry, this suit.
I would wear it.
I think it's like a sailor suit.
Maybe a little bit.
That's boys and berries.
Isn't this raspberry boys and berries suit is more for Jason boys and berries.
It is a sailor boy.
That's for sure.
Jason.
You mean the father suit?
Yeah.
The father suit that the green, like a Christmas suit green and red and like a yellow stripes.
Like a yellow vest and this, uh, straw hat with the yellow flower.
Oh, I see.
That's, I like that a lot.
I may wear that.
Wear a straw hat with a yellow flower.
That's the question.
I mean, it would have to be something where it would be appropriate.
I wouldn't be suit man forever because like they didn't have to switch over.
Like if I was wearing that now, it'd be inappropriate.
But maybe if I'm going to find what, what would I be doing where I would go to functions
and I would wear this.
You get married in the, in a suit suit and a straw hat with a flower.
That might, well, this isn't a suit suit.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm mixing them up.
Not so.
Yeah.
I think we're looking at flapper berry, the mommy.
Would I wear that too?
That's not a bad thing.
I feel like if there was, if I was going to social fun, like if I was a Hamptons man,
that might be the perfect situation.
If I end up out in the Hamptons a lot with, you know, whoever's out there.
Seinfeld, Seinfeld, Spielberg, Russell Simmons, all the, all the friends.
Uh, I would maybe wear this.
I would wear this and I will do the full straw hat with the yellow flower.
But I guess like it would be inappropriate to wear around town.
It's a little.
I think the older you get, the older of a man you become, the more you can give yourself permission
to just dress nice.
And there doesn't have to be a specific occasion.
I agree with you.
I agree with that a hundred percent.
The sweetest episode.
Doesn't have to be just for going to the fair.
You know, you're right.
You're giving me more confidence to do that.
Cause I believe that is true.
If you feel good doing it, who gives a shit what people say.
I'm starting, as I approach 40 is I started feel more and more that way.
I see other guys who are, you know, 20, 30 years, my senior just going for it.
And I'm like, wow, you've got the right idea.
That's what I want to be.
Yeah.
I just slowly get it.
It doesn't happen overnight, Mike.
It takes a while, but I just, Jason, I were at H&M.
I almost bought this like flowery kind of jacket that was like, I was like,
I was a little too much.
I tried it on, you know, when I said the next day I didn't get it.
I went back and I bought that fricking jacket upstairs.
Yeah, we were there for a while.
But that's, you know what?
I'm wearing it now.
Trig yourself, Mike.
It's a statement piece.
It's a statement.
It's going to be a huge step the day I buy my first leather jacket.
I think that.
Oh, is that what you're like kind of eyeing?
I'm thinking about it.
Okay.
Yeah.
I just want to, I don't want to be 60 years old and wearing my Nott's Berry,
Mary Farm t-shirt, you know, that's.
My C plus is in common.
My plus is my C.
Yeah.
I want to get the most out of life when I'm in my final act.
Well, let's go.
We'll all check in obviously with each other in 10 years to see if I'm wearing this suit,
that raspberry and if you're wearing a leather jacket.
And if I'm wearing the boys.
And if you're wearing socks that say green treat.
My socks.
What?
That's the brand.
These two socks.
Oh my God.
These socks on the bottom.
Red green tree.
Red alert.
Jason's socks say green treat on the bottom.
Striped maroon blue and green.
Oh my God.
Not to be confused with the, with the fun socks that your mom gave you for this holiday season.
Right.
These are just different green treat socks.
Yeah.
Wow.
I haven't worn a sock that is not just a white sock in a long time.
And I don't know, maybe like a wedding.
So I'm yeah, I'll wear a black sock to go with black shoes, but I haven't worn like a
sock that says my salad is wine.
What was the, what was that?
My favorite salad is wine.
I think was what it was.
Yeah.
Or you know, a sock with yelling Vladimir Putin on it or the, with the wonderful things
available at the sock market.
I have a lot of colored colorful socks upstairs.
Maybe I should give it a try.
I think maybe yeah, you should set a goal too.
Like we all have of what will you be wearing?
So branch out my sock.
Yeah.
Okay.
So size.
So in 10 years, you'll be wearing some fun.
I don't know.
I feel like, I feel like weird socks are what people who do like dress like a pirate day.
You can go to Martin.
You can find a lovely multi-pack variety of socks at Marshall's or TJ Maxx.
They got some great stuff.
Happy socks or whatever.
These are the brand.
I mean, they're all probably the same conglomerate that just has a million lines,
but you can get some fun accent socks.
Do you have fun socks at home?
No, I have never gotten into that.
Not yet.
Standard black or white socks.
I am just, I don't know.
I don't know if they're for me.
I don't think that's where my clothing joy is going to come from.
I want to find it from somewhere though.
I should set a clothing goal.
Plus is up a little casual t-shirt and jeans look.
What's up?
Oh, a fun sock.
Sure.
Yeah, I hear you.
More jackets, maybe more like jackets.
Yeah.
Like not even the suit, but just like suit jacket types or more like a cool nylon,
nylon jacket.
Yeah.
Maybe more in the blazer zone.
Although I guess, you know, blazer can get you into like 80s standup territory.
That's true, but it's all combined with blue jeans and sneakers.
Yeah.
I guess I shouldn't dress like Jerry Zanfellow.
You got to pay the extra to take it to a tailor and make sure it's really properly fit.
And I think that the fitting can help.
I think whatever else you're wearing with it helps.
Yeah.
It all depends.
Oh, it's a fine line.
I think look how much the bears are making us want to.
The Knots and Barry family is our style guide.
Yeah.
We'll take a photo.
Our fit.
Our fit pick is just, just these guys, just the new look.
You know, you said a photo of like people dressing the bears and like this must have
been so fun for costumers to do to find crazy turn of the century clothes to put on these
bear robots.
The behind the scenes photos of the people like dressing the characters and building
this stuff are amazing because they're the most 70s looking people you can, you can picture.
And in some, I have to send you guys more.
I only set you guys a couple, but then, and a lot of them, they're like smoking or drinking
a beer.
Like it's kind of, it was just very, very laid back vibe.
Wow.
Hippie vibe.
So fun.
Yeah. You sent us the, the, um, a link to there.
There's a lights on ride through and you can kind of get a very general sense of the ride,
but there's no real soundtrack playing.
Yeah.
I hear a little sound here and there, but mostly you're the clicking of the robots and
every now and then someone will walk for walk through the frame.
Yeah.
I think that video, the ride through video was taken after hours and it was not fully
operating with the music and everything because you don't hear the theme song
and that theme song is playing throughout the ride.
And that was written by a Disney guy, a 17 year Disney veteran.
Oh, well, yeah, a lot of Disney folks.
I looked them up and, uh,
His name was Bob Bruner and he worked on, his credits include The Magical World of Disney, the TV series,
Gus, which was a favorite of mine as a kid, it's about the football playing horse.
Okay, sure.
The boat nicks, that darn cat, Blackbeard's ghost, and he also wrote the theme song for the computer
war tennis shoes.
I gotta look up all these songs, I don't know what those songs are.
Another Disney guy.
Wow, allowed to cut loose to do his thing.
Well, and at the very end, we haven't talked about the final musical performance by the
Jazzberry Band.
That's right.
They're great.
Another similarity to Splash Mountain, you see a band that come out of nowhere and just
performing and joining in on the celebration, and then we pass by the Knott's and Berry family
one last time and they're waving goodbye and singing the theme song as you pull back into
the station and that's the end.
It's a perfect ride.
What a delight.
So much style, so much original mythology not to be found anywhere else.
And how many rides are like this anywhere in the world?
There's so few non-Disney dark rides and because I was trying to think of a few, I think it's
probably why we like the ET adventure so much.
It's like not original mythology, although mostly because all that stuff's not in the
movie, but it feels very, you know, I'm so fond of that Hershey factory tour.
It seems like Efteling is overflowing with weird original rides like this and there's
not, I don't know, there's not a lot of this in America and Knott's had a real amazing
stab at it in the 70s and 80s in such a vibrant time style wise and so delightful.
Sadly, only an 11 year run and then that was it.
Yeah, it is so short.
Very short.
Had overlays though.
Had a very bizarre Halloween overlay which you can find video of on YouTube.
Yeah, it is bizarre because basically they keep all the foliage, they take all the characters
out, they keep all the foliage and trees and then just have teenage characters running
around which I think kind of contributed to the ride getting run down and like it did
have a lot of upkeep and I think having the Knott's thing year, the Haunt thing year after
year kind of started like at the same time that Haunt started, Berry Tales and Haunt
were both like 74, 75.
So they had the scary overlay year after year, every year that it was in operation.
I think that's one of the reasons it wore out so quick.
The only major refurbishment was in 1985, like right before it closed.
By then I guess the writing was already on the wall.
And that was generation one scare actors because these teens do not give a shit.
The people doing it now are so committed and so into it and there was literally a kid
like waving his arms, they looked like they were sarcastically haunting you.
God.
So this thing shuts down in 86, reopens the next year as Kingdom of the Dinosaurs,
which I will say I was fond of that ride.
I think that was a great ride.
That's a neat ride.
So it's not as if it was torn out for some garbage.
True.
And the same ride vehicles, which these little trolleys like with a little
light piece in the front and the same track.
Same track.
Okay.
You go down the same tunnel.
That's kind of like a time travel tunnel in that case.
Okay.
So at least it was replaced by something decent.
People claimed that for the first year of Kingdom of the Dinosaurs,
you could still smell the boys and Barry.
Wow.
How about that?
Delightful.
That's so fun.
I have been to an apartment where there were smokers for years living there and you do smell
the carpeting smells like smoke for you.
Oh, yeah.
So I believe that.
It's just the building smelled like the berries.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, King Kong's banana breath lost in the universal fire.
That fire can defeat the banana breath.
And for sure, no arson involved with that.
No, no, no, no, certainly a totally different thing.
But then it gets dicey because we were talking about, we've recently talked about
cranium command and how this was that buzzy the robot was taken and how strange,
how rare it is that a ride is just left sitting around with nothing to replace it.
That was one of the cases I could think of was that King of the Dinosaurs closed in 2004,
just sitting around for a very, very long time.
Over a decade.
God, wow.
And then to what end?
Were dinosaurs sitting in there?
What was it?
Was it storage?
Who knows?
But then eventually replaced by Voyage to the Iron Reef, which we went on together, correct?
Yes, we did.
Not Jason, but Doug and Mike.
Jason was played by the part of Andrew Grissom.
My understudy.
We're all collectively disappointed.
Yeah, now, so finally in the next generation is replaced by something a little rougher
because if you don't know that ride, it's a shooting gallery ride and kind of a 3D.
And steampunk themed.
Steampunk.
I will say, though, that maybe it's an ode to the weird lighting.
It is disorienting and your eyes have to keep adjusting into the weird 3D.
So there's a little nod to the past.
Raleigh Crump's note, I'm sure, is make people's eyes.
Fuck your eyes up.
Fuck everyone's eyes up on it.
That's a bummer.
I mean, look, you talk tours and bringing specific styles into the park.
That ride is that.
I just wish it didn't have to replace this.
For many years, this was this interesting dark ride zone in a park that doesn't really have them.
And I don't know, for it to become a screen ride.
I'm not always anti-screen ride, but no, no, no.
They got to be of a certain quality.
They have to be pleasant.
Of course, we'll do a full Iron Reef episode trashing it.
I'm sure very soon.
Very soon.
But yeah, I think we all got off and we were like, oh, like just not pleasant at all.
Am I making this up?
But did somebody like cut their hand on the gun?
I don't think we did.
I just remember the experience being bad as it possibly could have been.
The gun stabbed me.
There was a better non-screen version of this and it was still kind of chintzy in Tokyo,
at Tokyo Dome City.
I got to go there.
A sort of a voyage shooting game where you stand up on these vehicles and it's just all
slow moving like underwater robot things.
That's fine.
And it's a much better, it's still cheapy, but so much better than.
Sure.
I lost my mind when you were talking about Tokyo Dome City.
Oh, Doug, my God.
Yeah.
You will never come, you won't come back when you go to Tokyo Dome City.
You'll live in Tokyo Dome.
Yep.
Doug will take up residence in the Tokyo Dome City Hotel.
There was the big New Japan wrestling show yesterday, or I guess two days ago there,
and all the wrestlers are posting photos outside of right by Tokyo Dome City because that's where
the show was at the Tokyo Dome and all the nostalgia floods right back.
I'm like, oh, there's the hotel and there's the like.
Oh, yeah.
So I was getting a flood of Tokyo Dome City on my feed, Twitter feed the last 48 hours.
I can't wait.
I'm so excited.
But the the ride did not disappear entirely.
As I mentioned, some of it was turned, a mild amount of it was turned into a walkthrough
and I got to experience that very, very young.
I wish I remembered it better.
The Berry Tales Funhouse.
So maybe that's how they justify it.
Like we know people love this ride.
Don't worry, it's not going away.
We're just moving.
But it was a very condensed version of Berry Tales and you didn't see all the characters.
You saw maybe like 30 percent of the characters.
OK.
None of them were moving and animatronic.
And I when I watched that walkthrough on YouTube, I found it very disappointing.
And but 60 percent of the ride was taken home by this park employee named Dale Tetley.
So this is something I had a lot of fun researching.
I want to know who this guy was, what his story is.
OK.
I don't know how he worked it out, but he he he literally took it home.
In fact, two years almost to the date that the ride closed.
So the ride closed and its last run was on Halloween 86.
Halloween 88, he threw a party in his friend's backyard in Arcadia and all the characters,
Sarah Skunk.
The Crabby Coyote himself.
Dr. Fox made it a cameo at this party.
He set them all up in the same order that they appear on the ride.
Oh, my God.
And in the backyard, he set up like a rideable train.
Wow.
He could get on and he tried to recreate the ride and his friends.
And I just think that that's amazing.
What a party.
That's so funny.
So it's like, where are these where are these characters now?
In 2007, they took, you know, long after the Berry Tales Fun House closed.
They're supposedly storing some of these knots and Barry family in the storage facility
located underneath the wacky soapbox racers.
Another dearly departed.
Yeah.
Not that I enjoyed as a kid.
Found their way into a toy store in Ghost Town.
Oh, yeah.
And they were just finally.
Yeah.
They played the music.
They weren't animated, but you could see it was it was Elderberry and boys and Barry
and an unnamed raccoon.
That's fun.
So here's something I wanted to talk about, because there is the when I, you know, I forgot
about this ride for 20 years.
I in 2007, I started getting back into it and reliving it through YouTube and Internet.
There's like Barry Dash Tales dot net sort of fan fan a fan site.
This video that was on YouTube in 2007 was not the one that's on now.
It was a different one.
And it was there's a very funny talk.
You guys have talked in the past.
The people who shoot the videos talk over it.
I think this this has come up a few times before and say say things that are that are
worth talking about.
OK, this this this particular right through on YouTube had a voice that sounded almost
identical to the characters of Bob and Doug McKenzie from TV.
And we're talking about the characters played by Rick Moranis and Dave Thomas.
There are a lot of comments on the YouTube channel that that supported this, that that
they believe that that was really them, that they were there.
They were on the ride filming it and doing this little commentary over it.
Well, the video disappeared.
I couldn't find those comments.
I did, however, find an article from the Orange County Register around the time that some
of the characters were moved into the ghost town that talked about this video and how
they theorized that it was actually.
Wow.
Dave Thomas and and Rick Moranis.
Again, the video is deleted.
I spent a lot of time trying to track this video down and I found it.
Oh, so that's that's MP3.
I oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Shit.
Yes, you sent us a secret MP3.
Do not play before the show.
Right.
So I want to get I want I want to listen to it.
I want to see what you guys think.
OK, and then I'll tell you what I think this Bob and Doug McKenzie exactly.
Thanks for checking.
Oh, oh!
Thank you.
No, I'm not that good, eh?
This place is so freaky and I'm not sure about that.
I don't know, I know you've been watching Jumping Frogs, Gabby.
No, last time we're talking, we're talking about you.
I don't know, we're in the Gypsy Cafe.
I had an impression it was just a couple of funny guys.
Just, you know, I guess for equivalent for, I was too young to see Strange Brew in the
theater, but I saw Wayne's World and of course I haven't stopped quoting it to this day and
talking like Mike Myers.
Well, at the very end, I was looking for any clues that can help me get to the bar.
At the very end of that video, I don't know what character they're looking at, but one
of them says, it looks like Evan, and then the other one says, yeah, hey, it reminds
me of Evan.
So I'm thinking, hmm, that could be a lead.
I looked at the IMDb website for the movie Strange Brew and as it turns out, the associate
editor's name was Evan Landis and that could possibly be, I don't know if you're laughing
at me or laughing with me.
But this could possibly be the Evan that they're referring to, which would validate the theory
that it is in fact their actual Bob and Doug McKenzie.
And Strange Brew made during the, while this ride was open.
Yes.
Could have.
What year is Strange Brew?
80s?
1983.
I don't know that, I don't know those characters well enough to judge off of that audio clip,
but we do know people who worked with Dave Thomas before.
I did a show with Dave Thomas.
Yeah, could reach out.
Hey, do you have any recollection of riding this ancient, this extinct ride with a video
camera?
I'm thinking that a character looked like your associate editor.
Which somehow ended up on a DVD sold by the now defunct website Extinct Intractions.
Let me play a clip of them.
For real, these are the actual, because I haven't heard them do it in a while.
Welcome to the Green and Green corner of Great White North and look at this.
I'm Bob McKenzie and this is my brother Doug and this is Doug's new beer bottle.
Oh take off, eh?
It's a baby bottle.
Although it's not bad, eh?
It's like a condensed version of a Saturday night.
You have a little beer and a little sip.
Well, you be the judge.
Now, you're laughing at me earlier.
Now the look on your face says that you're not so sure anymore.
Let's go back to the audio.
Okay, we're in the Frog Forest.
It sounds like some dude though.
I don't think so.
The key, who do they say looks like Evan?
I don't know.
There's no way to know who they're talking about that looks like Evan.
But then we look up Evan.
This is at the end, this is at the fair scene and there's so much going on.
To the left, to the right, behind you, I don't know which character they're talking about.
But then we look up Evan Landis and he looks exactly like Dr. Fox.
Then we would know for sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's the only way.
So that's the final bit of proof that we need.
We have to interview, in addition to Roly Crump, Evan Landis.
If he's still around.
If he's still around, if he's still working, let's find him.
But how would he know that someone once referred to something looking like him?
You're right.
But wouldn't he?
Yeah, you're right.
So we got to get Dave or Moranis on the show.
I just think you just, next time you see Dave Thomas, I don't know what the circumstances
would be.
But just say something really subtle like, would you be interested in some weird juice?
And then see how he reacts and look on his face.
Look on his face, we'll tell you all you need to know and just leave it at that.
Can you give me some space, dude?
That's what he says.
We need to have Rick Moranis on and ask him only about this issue.
And not talk about Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
Did you ever go on the Knott's Ride?
No, I did not.
All right, see you.
Thanks, Rick.
We can do a match.
His first appearance.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, bye.
All right.
But now, but then there's one final bit of...
Yes, just when you think the story's over.
And this took some very, very...
A lot of digging.
But one of the...
He's now known as the biggest Knott's Berry Tales superfan, and he's one of my new friends
this past week.
His name's Albert Rodriguez.
So he purchased, as you may have heard two years ago, there was the Knott's Heritage
Auction.
And they basically auctioned off everything that was left.
This is the Elder Berry and a couple other characters and also some like...
Like technical books, like books on how to operate the ride and something that was called
a costume swatch book.
So I guess has squashes of the characters costume pieces so that when you restore it,
you can get it back to the same color.
I need that, by the way, to recreate that suit.
And one of the trolley cars, like everything they had left, they auctioned off.
And this guy named Albert Rodriguez purchased the rest of it.
So now between him, that guy Dale Tetley, I mentioned earlier, and this other guy named
Ken Stack, between the three of these guys, they've got about 90% of the ride.
Wow.
Like all of the components are in these three people's possession.
I'm talking set pieces and props.
And they even...
I sent you guys a YouTube video of this.
There's an effect.
I think it's a Theta Bear where she...
A candle raises out of its base, flips around a little mouse, pops out of the base, and
then goes back in right before the candle come back in place.
They have that and they've made it work.
And they're uploading videos to YouTube of it working.
Sounds familiar.
It kind of sounds like the story of the rocket fire explosion.
Yes, it does.
So they're planning...
They've put their heads together and they're planning on doing something with this.
And it's a project called Kooky Trails.
So I got a hold of...
I sent Albert a DM through Instagram.
I told him that I was from the OC Weekly.
Oh, nice.
I've only written one freelance article for them so far.
That's fine.
I've got another one coming out next week.
I'm already abusing my credentials.
That'll be...
What's that one?
What's the next piece?
I'll just tease you by saying, it involves a murder in a hotel on Harbor Boulevard right
across the street from Disneyland.
Oh, man.
I'm so excited.
I'll just leave it at that.
Look that up.
So anyways, I used my credentials.
I told Albert I needed him to call me as soon as possible so I can interview him.
Oh, yeah.
Which I am.
This was informal.
I'm going to formally interview him later.
Oh.
When this actually opens, I want this to be article in OC Weekly if they go for it.
Yeah, absolutely.
So Kooky Trails is kind of like they're taking all these bits and pieces and these characters,
refurbishing them and modernizing the story a little bit and working it into...
I believe they have also, I could be wrong, some characters from that Raleigh Crump pizza
restaurant.
What?
Oh, really?
They're going to just reunite all these characters under the same roof.
He told me, but he didn't want me to say on there where it's going to be.
Oh, wow.
But he says it's planned to open in summer 2020.
What?
Oh!
Yeah.
So that's something we'll look forward to and something we're going to...
He's hired a company called Adrenaline Attractions and you can look these guys up.
They just created a ride in somebody's, like a Christmas ride in somebody's house.
And they seem legit.
And this is being constructed right now.
This isn't just like, oh, we're going to do a Kickstarter.
We're pitching our...
This is actually...
They're doing it.
Wow.
Yeah, they're constructing it right now as we speak.
And in what other case, if Disney gets rid of a ride, that's the end of it.
That would never happen.
But it's not a situation that it is so, like it's just more tangible and more indie.
Somebody, you can recreate a Notts ride?
Unless the Buzzy Theft was to create Cranium Command in someone's living room.
And they wanted the real Buzzy.
I'm going to live inside a giant head.
Buzzy Theft, I don't follow.
Oh!
Oh, Buzzy from Cranium Command was stolen a few weeks ago.
I didn't hear about this.
I'm out of the loop.
Yes.
I went to Palm Springs for a week and I missed all the important news like this.
It's easy to dive into that.
You were even so worried on vacation though about it, so we didn't want to tell you.
We would have ruined the trip.
Oh, okay.
You would have been in tears the whole time.
But yeah, Buzzy is...
He was stolen.
Or you would have gone full spotlight and gone down to Orlando and found him.
You would have broken the story.
Or...
You're OC Weekly credentials.
Palm Springs is a pretty good alibi.
Uh...
Oh, man.
I posted photos and videos.
Also good alibis.
Good alibis is all I'm saying.
You didn't do it, Doug.
The guy who does RoboLite put me up to it.
He offered me $10,000 to steal so he could use it in next year's RoboLites.
You're as crafty as that crafty coyote.
Guilty.
Oh my gosh.
So there is hope.
And what is the name of it again?
Kooky Trails.
We will be broadcasting live from the opening of Kooky Trails complete with live commentary
from Bob and Doug McKenzie.
By then we will have established contact.
There will be Raz in it.
There will be Raz in...
Raz-berry.
Raz-y-berry.
No, it's Raz-berry.
Raz-berry, yeah.
Well, a big event...
Well, all right.
So 2020, a lot to look forward to.
2020.
Marvel and opening and Kooky Trails opening.
Right.
Your next preview center on the first podcast of 2020.
2020.
We'll have more information by then.
Yes.
And we'll look forward to that full interview.
This is the...
I feel like starting at the beginning of this episode, now I feel like we've arrived at
the fair with this conclusion.
Mm-hmm.
And we can also promise an exclusive interview with Theta Bear.
Only we have it.
Only with our stolen journalistic credentials from Doug.
Can I promise the listener that I will wear a Raz-berry suit to the opening of this and
Jason will wear her boys in berries suit, sailor suit to the opening?
I think I can, is what I'm saying.
This is, what do they call it?
Mutually assured destruction.
So like we have to do it.
All right.
The other will look very foolish.
So you and I will wear the outfit and Scott will wear some purple socks.
Fun socks.
You'll be in good company because the circle of friends that these guys know are all super
well versed in the Knott's Berry verse.
Is that a...
Oh yeah, yeah.
And they'll get the reference immediately.
And we're looking...
It does, I think I've said this on the Haunt episode that it not seems like they're ready
to get back into the Knott's verse.
Yes.
It seems like the new overlay, or not overlay, the new redoing of the Rapids ride ties into
mythology.
They're going to add to mythology.
They're going to bring back old mythology and maybe they're getting back on track and
getting away from just thrill stuff.
They know the fandom is there and they want to nod to it more.
And actually, well then the best thing that we can do, what the Kooky Trails guys will
for sure is if I show up holding a big open can of lizard lard, Theta is taking a big
scoop out of a can of lizard lard.
So that'll be the little...
If we need to get in, I'd suggest that as a password so only people in the know get
in.
Lizard lard.
How does Theta Bear make her cards levitate through the air?
You may enter.
Phew.
We practiced so when it happens for real, we're all set.
Wow.
A new ride opened up at the...
There was so much here that an entire new ride was hidden at the end.
What a blast of a journey through Nutsberry Tales.
Doug Jones, You Survived podcast the ride.
Once again, thank you for coming back.
Thank you for being our guide through and giving us so much...
But stepping through this with so much detail.
So much fun.
Thank you so much for having me.
What a joy.
I'm so glad.
Anytime you find a bear related theme park show or ride, please come back and show it
because it's delightful.
This was a good omen.
On my way here driving through Burbank, or do you not want people to know where you are?
We've already said that.
We at least had a drive through Burbank to get here.
Yes, great.
Great cover.
No, no, Mike lives in Bear Bank.
I saw a bear, I swear to God, a bear float and it was from, you know, just a few days
ago they had the Rose Parade.
Oh, right.
And it was a bunch of bears and a log cabin.
I did not watch the Rose Parade, but the float looked amazing and it was just in a random
parking lot on the corner.
And people were getting out of their car and taking photos of it up close.
And it just kind of blew my mind.
I'm going to have to now go see what that was all about.
Right.
But this was just meant to be a very good time.
Can we end with the lyrics?
Oh, yeah, please.
Absolutely.
Make sense to me.
All right.
Welcome one and all.
Y'all come have a ball.
Things are very fine riding on the old Knott's Berry Line.
And I think that says it all.
This was this episode was sweeter than a boysenberry pie.
Thanks so much, Doug.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Thank you for listening to The Second Gate.
See you next time.