Hi, I'm Lindy Katye.
And I'm Kelli Nugent, and we co-host the podcast Teen Creeps.
We talk about YA Pulp Fiction, but this week we took a little detour
to talk about the 1996 classic The Craft.
And we were joined by our movie expert, Oscar Montoya.
Yes, yes. Hi guys, thanks for having me.
So fun. We covered a lot.
We talked about how Ski-O-Rick is hot now for some of us,
but also maybe this is the last time we'll ever podcast together.
We talked about what we would do if we had the power of manna within us.
We talked about the real black girl magic, which is never aging.
We talked about how the scariest part of kissing someone is if you are wearing a heavy lip
and the lipstick is gone after you kiss.
We talked about wet pet San Pablo.
We talked about Frieza Balth being truly a goddess.
Legendary.
So if any of that appeals to you, which it does and should and also does,
you should check us out this week on Teen Creeps right here on the Forever Dog
podcast network, wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep it creepy.
Forever. Dog.
Warning. The following episode contains a mercurial casino magnate, a guest crushing parade,
dozens of animals wearing neckties and two elderly men in sweaters playing God with their pencils.
Yabba Dabba Doo.
It's the Fantastic World of Hanna Barbera on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by Mike Carlson, Scott Garner
and Elroy Jetson himself, Jason Sheridan.
Let's get it out of the way.
See, I thought you were going to go with a line about a double decker salami and cheese sandwich.
I could have done that.
That's something that he's after in the show.
In the pre-show, Yogi is eyeing a guy's sandwich in the queue line.
It's tempting to say you have boo boo aspects, but I think Yogi has the greater hunger.
So you have to merge some characters to make it work.
And I am a little peckish.
So I've said to your that you're a peckish.
I describe you as that.
Yes.
Yeah, I enjoyed that.
That's great.
Okay.
I felt a little bit like blunt, but I got like I was trying to be clever or something.
I'm like, I'll just call Jason Elroy.
Don't stop there, Mr. Barbera.
Yeah, I know.
Well, thanks so much for Mike for drawing both of us at the
before we started recording.
Sure.
Filling in our body and using the paintbrush that contains all of the colors.
Of course.
But not erasing us because then you would get a lawsuit from the Looney Tunes,
Warner Brothers animation for that gimmick.
You're talking about like the...
There's that one where they draw Daffy Duck and then they erase a little.
Oh, the famous one.
I see, yes.
The cartoon where it is coloring in.
Yeah, well, we're talking about some gags that are in the pre-show of today's topic,
the funtastic world of Hanna Barbera.
And I'll go ahead and tell you guys right now,
the vast majority of what I have to talk about is the pre-show.
I'm very pre-show focused.
Yeah, the pre-show is the more interesting part of the ride.
To me.
No, but I would agree with you because I spent a lot more time looking at that.
I watched the ride itself, which is a 3D ride.
It's very universalish in its tricks and its 3D simulator type thing.
But it's fine.
It's fine.
Yeah.
All right, everybody, we're going on a fine ride today.
I got very interested in the history of the company, Hanna Barbera,
because they really saw every iteration of animation in America,
like post-war, I guess even some pre-war or some during the war America.
Well, that's all news to me.
This will be stuff that I don't know.
But really fast before we get into all that, Jason, you're talking about studios and lawsuits.
There's a big thing going on right now that I wanted to address that our listeners might
not know about.
A little bit less smooth of an agreement than the one between Universal Studios and Hanna Barbera.
I'm talking about something that's going on right now with a place called Fox World, Malaysia.
Malaysia.
This is a really fun story that's fun for us to listen to, probably not fun.
Less fun for the residents of Kuala Lumpur.
Or an hour or so outside of it, which is where this park is being built.
We're going to have to put the pause button on what exactly is going on,
because I think nobody's sure at this point what's going on.
But yeah, this is intended to be the first Fox theme park in the world.
They've licensed their properties to other things, but they've never specifically made
an entire Fox World.
In 2013, they set out to do so and reached out to a company called Genting, Resorts World Genting.
The list of what they have done is very long.
There's a ton of, but it's mostly international stuff.
In Singapore, I believe they are mostly owned or entirely on Universal in Singapore.
Here in America, they own the Fox Woods Casino.
Norwegian Cruises, they're ultimately the parent company.
But they're mainly like a casino entity.
And their main, their most ambitious campus is in the mountains up above Kuala Lumpur.
You have to take essentially what's the Disney thing, the Skyliner.
It's those kind of cars to get up into the mountains.
The gondola.
The gondolas, yeah.
To get to this magical world of a giant casino.
There's indoor skiing up there.
There's already an indoor theme park there called Skytropolis, which is confusing that a sky
themed park would have a roof on it, but that's what they went with.
They have the void there.
There's all kinds of crazy stuff, but the crown jewel of it was to be Fox World Malaysia.
However, in the last few months, it has all fallen apart with a series of lawsuits that
goes both ways.
Fox v. Genting, Genting v. Fox.
And we were passing this link around because of a couple pretty interesting details of what
Fox is alleging.
Feel free to say what I mean.
I can say, well, I just the variety article has a wonderful sentence in it where it says,
in a counter lawsuit filed on Wednesday, Fox alleges that the project was doomed
by Lim Kok The, the mercurial chairman of Casino Conglomerate Genting Malaysia Bearhead.
Now, who among us has not been fooled or tricked by the mercurial Lim Kok The?
They say he's been around for thousands of years, inhabiting new bodies and being reincarnated,
tricking people left and right.
It was just a little like I sometimes like the journalistic language of like these dry
reporting articles end up with these weird turn of phrases where it's like, yes, that is not too
judgmental.
That's it seems quote unquote objective, but like the mercurial chairman really makes him sound
mischievous.
The Mercurial Malaysian Casino Chairman Lim Kok The you think has a ring to it that it's hard
to be objective about, right?
Yeah, it's well, you know, this brings me to my bigger point, which is that we came across
an article that is very much on the Fox side of things, presumably because it was in a
Hollywood trade.
So they're going to take the side of the studio and the evidence they present admittedly is does
not look good for Resorts World Genting.
Some of the things that they said that the lawsuit alleges is that there are cars on some
rides with bubbling paint.
It's set to open by the way, they've pushed back the date it was going to open several
times.
The original goal was like fall 2017.
Now, and then they just kept keep kicking it down the curve was maybe looking like February
2019, clearly not going to happen.
So bubbling paint on a car is a problem.
There was a ride built without an emergency exit.
That's my favorite detail.
Even though all of the plans that they had looked at contained the emergency exit, somehow
they're walking around the physical space and there is not one.
Well, the bubbling paint, they just call Pixar peering it.
We allow it when it's companies we trust.
Sure.
They at least built emergency exit.
Well, those were the last we've ever had to try one.
They were already there.
They didn't have to build new ones.
When are they going to plus up the emergency exit?
They need to add Garland's voice to the Midway Maniac.
This way!
You can do it!
They I would think that we should do an episode on emergency exits is a certain point.
Maybe.
That episode is not forced by some traumatic events that we participate in.
That would be an important one.
Let's make it our decision when we do the emergency exit.
The between trampling.
Oh, no.
This is too real.
I feel like it's extremely possible.
Yeah.
Will Star Wars Galaxy's Edge make it a year without a death?
I don't think the ad ad is going to fall on anybody.
It's just sure correct.
The rides don't seem like they're that dangerous.
But the massive humanity, yes, very.
Yeah.
Extremely possible.
Will it be us?
Could it be us?
Time will tell.
It wouldn't be the worst way to go.
At least I got to see half of a fake cliff.
But I didn't make it in.
But and then, well, I'll save my my two favorite things for last.
Amazingly, this is not my favorite shitty detail.
A ride called Scrat's Nutty Adventure based on Ice Age was built with visible
patchwork on the mountain facade, not Galaxy's Edge quality.
No.
And then also there were parade floats built that were so wide that spectators would not
fit on the sidewalk.
It's amazing.
This is so great.
And the problem was flagged, apparently.
They said, isn't that going to be too wide?
Hey, don't worry.
And then they brought them in and they did fit down the street.
Yes.
But without any room for anyone to stand on the street.
And I think in the legal document, by the way, I read both legal documents.
Not word for word.
There's a lot of legalese in there.
I'll go to law school and then be able to fully comprehend it.
But but seeing that explain that, like, you know, there was no room for spectators,
thus defeating the purpose of a parade.
So I'd seen that in the legal document, but I also enjoyed imagining, like,
look, honey, here comes the parade.
Oh, God.
No.
No, what was do we know what the float was?
I don't know.
I mean, it's something Fox affiliated.
So it could have been.
I'm hoping, OK, there were going to be things in this park centered around the film epic,
an epic features my favorite character, my favorite anime character of the last decade,
the famous Nimlu voiced by Steven Tyler, which I may have talked about before.
If I haven't, there's this EPK that I love where he where Steven Tyler says,
I've always wanted to be one of those animated characters.
I got my wish.
I'm I'm Nimlu.
And then he scats for a while.
Which one was epic?
I only know it because I saw it randomly in a hotel room.
It oh, well, the characters I watched a press conference of the announcing Fox World Malaysia
and a bunch of characters come out and a voiceover person is like, please welcome Scrat from Rio.
You know, Pepe.
I don't know who's in Rio.
And then like and then the leaf soldiers from Epic.
Oh, I do know this.
I forgot one of my things at my old job.
I used to have to put like master archival digital copies of 20th century
Fox under multiple levels of encryption on hard drives to ship across the city.
I don't quite know why they weren't sending these digitally,
but I remember Epic in a dozen different languages.
So anyone got if anyone found out what happened to each leaf soldier
before the events of Epic played out.
So what I think maybe like they were the park didn't has not opened,
but there was a strong risk of a child suffocating on the Nimlu's big foot.
So you can't open a park in those conditions.
And then finally, the one I actually grazed over this, Jason,
but you pointed out the best detail in the article, which is the the show.
Oh, yeah.
That there was I'll just read from the legal document
demonstrating how little thought it gave to the integrity of Fox's intellectual property.
Genting proposed taking some of Fox's most significant science fiction film properties,
Alien Predator and Alien versus Predator,
and using the main characters in a cruise ship style dance show
featuring a dancing alien and predator.
I mean, there's so many levels, one that they're concerned about the
integrity of alien and predator and alien versus predator.
We all know Alien versus Predator.
There is no film with higher integrity,
more integrity per second than in anything else committed to celluloid.
And the other thing, what is the phrase cruise ship style dance show?
Now I have been on one cruise in my life, actually a Norwegian cruise line cruise
many, many years ago.
No, Genting thanks you.
And I don't I guess it would just be like, all right,
we're going to have a dance contest and maybe limbo and maybe like people join along.
Oh my God, like a conga line with the predator.
With the predator.
I mean, that's all I can think of.
When they say cruise ship, doesn't that mean like kind of almost a review type show where
it's not a full Broadway production?
Oh, that's possible.
Yeah, I see.
It's the greatest hit.
That's sort of what I think.
But maybe I'm wrong.
Who knows?
I think Disney's trying to do more like full musicals on the cruises.
But so would have been like a history of Broadway as done via Alien versus Predator.
The xenomorph.
The xenomorph sings, we're in the money.
He like picks up the like the fit like in 40 seconds treat picks up and like, oh gosh,
it's a nickel.
And that's how they go.
We were in the money.
The xenomorph would have sung like would have like like,
like because it never has a voice in the movies.
That's true.
So they have just done a fun, funny voice.
I bet you could fake it.
I bet it would start like that and then clear, clear it's the road.
And then it's got a beautiful.
Oh, slime in there.
Sorry.
One chorus line of people.
Right at the moment, the little mouth comes out and sings, we've got a lot of what it takes.
Holy shit, you should be writing this.
Yeah, the idea that this was going to be a bad show.
No, yeah.
Get over yourselves.
This would have been great.
Every every it would have been viral.
People would have been talking about it.
Yeah, the audience would standing ovation for the little mouth.
Alien and Predator doing the floss dance, hitting the dab.
I mean, people would have been losing their minds.
I got like all of this.
So many of the stuff we talked about and liked and like the commentary we did on the parade.
It's like so much of that is fallen by the wayside because companies are concerned about the
integrity of their intellectual property.
It is so boring.
Yeah.
Bullshit.
I'm a big proponent of the Star Wars holiday special.
I wish things were that fun ever.
I mean, does it suck?
Yeah, but it's such a blast.
I don't want to weigh in either way.
I don't hate the new movies or the prequels as much as anybody, you know, whatever.
I will say this.
I would rather watch the Star Wars holiday special than any of one through three or seven and eight.
Or solo a Star Wars story.
Sure.
I don't think we'll ever have a fun Star Wars movie ever.
I don't think it'll ever happen.
I'm making damn sure.
If they did a holiday overlay of Galaxy's Edge, of Life Day, of the Wookiee Holiday
life, people would lose their minds.
Like doing like just a purposefully kind of campy, like just for this, we know that it's
a little silly.
I mean, look what Spider-Verse did.
Spider-Verse had fun.
They put the fun on to Spider-Damn.
He gets to have fun.
But Miles Morales can still be vaguely serious.
They need to like find like if there was a if just for the holidays, Cantina overlay of Life Day.
Of course.
And it's a little like it's a little show over in the corner.
Yeah, that would be wonderful.
I don't know.
I think Star Wars is going to have to really had it like money wise, head into the toilet
before we get fun stuff.
Yeah, they have to like be throwing everything at the wall.
Yeah, because that's when fun stuff happens, which I have a perfect transition back to
Hanna Barbera, but I don't know.
Are we done talking about Malaysia?
I forgot a tiny bit more.
Yeah, let's go more.
Then I'll remind me of how good the transition would have been.
OK.
OK, so we'll go up and keep going with Malaysia.
I'm still going to give you the transition point.
Well, yeah, maybe give it to me again or whatever.
We'll keep talking about Fox Malaysia.
OK, well, you know, there's not much more to say other than just a couple points.
I it was, as I said, very one sided seemed like Genting's problem.
However, Genting was the first to sue Fox.
And I read that legal document and what that paints is a picture of a giant conglomerate
that is not being responsive, that's not being helpful, that's not giving like
style guides of characters and logos.
They didn't even like send a proper 3D rendering of what the 20th century Fox
you know, the sign with the searchlights.
That was going to be the big fountain at the entrance.
They didn't send like the specs on that.
So it got built weird because they had deadlines to hit.
And they were like, this is wrong.
Well, why didn't you send us anything?
And they'd, you know, like they'd say things like this character is too chubby
or this shade of yellow is too saturated, but then not provide the proper color to use instead
or presiding more precise direction.
If anyone listening has ever dealt with a major company of Fox level and can imagine
that company being very disorganized and unhelpful, I can believe this very easily.
Oh, yeah.
Putting all of the blame on this place and like noting things to there's all this stuff
where they like rejected an entire attraction design because they didn't like where the
AC unit went or they'd go like, where are the speakers going?
And they were like, well, we don't address that to like three months down the line.
Rejected. So the park being a disaster and not opening for many, many months, very,
very possibly due to Fox like incompetence and and things like them saying we want a
Percy Jackson ride.
And they thought of a Percy Jackson ride and then changed their mind and said,
never mind. We wanted this to be an Independence Day ride.
Not an easy change to make.
However, it would have resulted in the attraction Independence Day defiance.
Hell of a ride.
I want that ride, whatever that is.
Well, and so let me tell you then, like this whole thing, this is beyond just like,
you know, as a couple attraction, this is like a 25 attractions, at least.
And about a year ago, we did a whole like what if there was a Fox theme park?
Thanks to the Disney merger, a lot of it was going to be there.
There's alien rides.
There's something called Aliens Terra Forma.
There's the epic hummingbird flyer.
There's ESD Global Defenders.
You of course know that in the second Independence Day, ESD stands for Earth
Space Defenders.
Yeah, we all know that.
I watched that.
I watched that movie all the way through.
And it's not great.
Once the giant alien starts chasing the school bus driven by Judd Hirsch around the desert.
Hurry, Judd.
As we go back to Area 51.
Is that what the ride is?
You're on the school bus with Judd Hirsch?
I mean, can you imagine?
Oh, man.
There's a robot Judd Hirsch driving a bus and then you have to load onto it.
That would be amazing.
And he has to keep like breaking and adjusting his glasses and popping heart medicine.
Talking about his son, David.
He's very impressive.
He knows everything about cable.
I wish he was around now, but we didn't get the license for him.
There was a ride called Big Weld's Zeppelins.
You know, Big Weld, guys, obviously, Mel Brooks's Carrick beloved.
A CEO character from Robots.
Oh, of course.
You're going to meet Big Weld.
There was a Planet of the Apes thing.
There was a big water show called the Century City Lake Spectacular.
There's no lake in the real Century City.
What could that be based on?
Don't know.
The general notion of Century City existing.
And a Night at the Museum shooting game.
Their midway mania was for Night at the Museum.
So all of this stuff was getting prepared.
And I'm sorry, there's more here than I even realized.
There was going to be, OK, let me spell this out.
A ride built by the company Dynamic Attractions.
And what this was going to be was very much a Radiator Springs Racers.
And it's even in like a canyon area, which they have built.
There is this fully built canyon and a track on top of a hill in Malaysia.
And it was going to have this special type of ride vehicle that can do jumps and is articulated.
What I'm saying is this is the Donkey Kong ride vehicle.
And it was going to open there first for a ride based on Sons of Anarchy.
Yeah, I mean, that's not a bad idea, honestly.
But yeah, and they built this entire canyon.
This is Ice Age Mountain, like a coaster that goes in and out of the mountain.
Yeah, the concept already is cool on the Ice Age.
Thing I would love to ride the Sons of Anarchy,
Colin riding down this road, e-ticket attraction like that.
The name I don't know.
I'm guessing that's the first lyric of the theme song.
I mean, that is crazy.
This dynamic attractions, not a dog like a two bit dog and put it's a real themed entertainment.
Yeah, design company.
I think this park was going to be good.
It seems like claustrophobic, like it's jammed into a very small space.
But there's overheads.
And what's so crazy is these gondolas have been passing over the construction area for months.
So anybody can get up there, take pictures of this thing.
And it looks better than California Adventure did on day one.
So anyway, what ends up happening is Fox is not happy with the quality of things,
but Genting is blaming them.
And I don't know.
I hear what they're saying.
They seems like Fox was kind of difficult.
And then suddenly Disney swoops in.
We're buying Fox.
Wait a minute.
Sorry, you're building a theme park with a casino company in a casino,
like next to a casino in a casino town.
I don't think so because apparently I didn't know this.
Disney has a lot of problems with casinos in general and has tried to push them out of Orlando
and anywhere near Disney Park.
Yeah, they're part of a massive like group in Orlando trying to keep casinos out.
Oh, really?
Of Disney and various other businesses trying to keep them out.
I see.
Are there casinos on the Disney cruise ships?
I bet not.
I would have to think not.
I guess not.
But most cruise ships usually do have them.
Do we know why Disney is trying to keep the casinos out?
I would imagine there has to be some sort of reason of like,
it's not some altruistic reason.
It's probably some reason of like.
I would think optics at the very least of like Mickey Mouse,
like Mickey Mouse on tokens or Mickey Mouse.
Oh, well, I understand like not having a Disney family thing.
But I mean, like just having casinos around.
They don't have.
It's not only that they don't want casinos around.
When they bought Star Wars and Lucasfilm, they got rid of all slot machines.
Oh, interesting.
Related to Star Wars.
So they want zero crossover to this area.
Okay.
I guess you're right.
So maybe it's morality, quote unquote, but it's yeah, I know it's got to be something more like,
you know, Orlando's case, they just don't want the competition
for people going there instead of Disney World.
Right.
But is it like the casinos then have to like,
we'll end up giving more like taxes to the local government?
You know what I mean?
Isn't there some there's I feel like there's always some secret reason of like,
if people swoop in all of a sudden, like those people are going to be giving the government taxes
and the Disney will have to pay like there's something.
Somehow it raises the wealth of the state and now the minimum wage goes up.
Or right.
There's some tricky thing in there.
That's what my guess is.
But I could be wrong.
Maybe it's just a holdover thing from years ago.
I think so.
So in order to uphold their family friendly morality, they have to break billion dollar
contracts and leave theme parks sit rotting on top of a mountain.
So there's all this back and forth.
And now what you have is a fully built, good looking theme park that's just like, well,
I don't know, we're going to keep building it and see what happens.
And it's a possibility that another company like Universal or maybe even Six Flags moves in
and just has like, you know, it's like moving into a house.
You didn't have to pay for the construction of.
Is there a chance that it just becomes a freestyle music park?
Oh, man.
Well, if we keep going, I mean, come on.
Why?
Maybe this is the place to launch.
Well, yeah, Hard Rock Park 2.0.
Because, yeah, you could do like turn the sons of anarchy ride into the leader of the pack ride.
I think there's a lot of.
Change.
And it doesn't end too well, though.
That's not we could change.
I mean, happy and we're changing.
Or it's like toad and you end up in hell.
That's true.
Truthfully, I'm not quite sure how sons of anarchy ended.
I've only seen like stray episodes here or there.
Oh, but we don't.
We're leader of the packs.
The IP.
Yeah.
Your goal is to be not the leader of the pet.
You don't want to be the one who dies.
Yes, exactly.
So the unlike creator Springs racer, the loser dies.
But at least you get a song written about you.
And I also think with a mountain, with a coaster weaving in and out of it,
perfect place for Led Zeppelin the ride to.
Of course.
You've got all kind of in the mountains.
No, it's like like exactly.
But it's perfect for that.
And then you've already got a zeppelin ride.
You just convert.
What's his name?
Hotbot.
Mel Brooks, his character, the Brooks, a tron.
Big Weld.
Thank you.
That's a zeppelin ride already.
Yeah, I think it's easy.
I think it's easy.
Let's get I mean, I know Bingkowski didn't buy.
He wasn't responsible for freestyle music,
but maybe he could put us in touch with the freestyle music.
Or no, no, wait, Bingkowski.
We got to get Bingkowski.
What am I saying?
Of course we got to get big house.
And you go and he's probably already like on top of a mountain in Malaysia.
He's like been living in solitude for five years.
Oh, yeah.
Meditating and like and, you know, perfecting his martial arts skills.
So he's going to be like, like, excuse me, are you are you John Bingkowski?
And he turns around like, yeah, right.
Like the nomad who like I used to be.
I haven't been for a long time.
That name in a lifetime.
Excuse me, sir.
Are you made of pure light?
Yes.
I've been up here meditating for so long.
I'm just pure energy.
I mean, I'm going to toss out a new generation ride
because it's perplexingly such a huge hit.
Bohemian Rhapsody ride just based on that one scene
that's been going around Twitter the last few days of like the they're at a restaurant
and there's just so many edits.
There's so many cut to everyone talking.
I know exactly what we are.
We're a band for outcasts and anyone who feels like an outcast
because we are outcasts ourselves.
What is this?
Boy, I don't this was this Oscar winning.
I don't know.
I still haven't watched it yet.
So you're saying I mean, one of is probably some other mountain that is, you know, it's
scaramuchas layer.
I don't know who's considered the villain of the song, but he mean rhapsody.
But you know, you meet all of them and you do.
And there's a dance show where you learn how to do the fan dango.
Well, it's a cruise ship style conga line.
And then you are turned around and given a mic stand and you have to do the live aid
performance.
Remember, you haven't played together in many years, although that's not true.
Now go maybe.
OK, instead of Alien versus Predator, how about Freddie Mercury?
Not Freddie, the villain of Freddie.
Freddie Mercury versus the villainous music executive Ray Foster.
Oh, he's played by Mike Myers, not a real person who existed in real life.
Oh, man.
Really?
There's fictional people in this, too.
Yeah.
And I'll get some greener when I get home.
No, no, I haven't seen any of it.
Oh, my God.
It's a composite character, to be fair to the movie.
Based on generally the idea of a bad executive that could exist.
Based partially on the real head of the record label and based partially on Chairman Lim
Cock-Thay, who also found time to say Mercurial.
Oh, wow.
You know, very Mercurial.
Freddie, I would say.
You know, every time like there's some funny business in the theme park world and there's
plenty of funny business in the domestic parks, the American parks.
I try not to, you know, I try to be cognizant of like a Western worldview.
And it's like, look, not every theme park outside of America is a scam.
There has been a number of scams.
That said, there's a big announcement recently about Lionsgate opening in Asia Park.
And I meant to tweet this out recently.
Have we seen any updates on that Times Square, Lionsgate thing from our very first episode?
I don't know.
So it seems like Lionsgate Asia further along than a Lionsgate Times Square.
This is the type of I think I said this on our text chain.
I said this is the type of project I imagine we could have a shot at designing.
Maybe not this level, but something overseas with some properties, like just some very rich
person like is fooled into somebody else by getting us.
And then we just designed the whole park and the whole thing falls apart very quickly.
Maybe like literally it opens and all the walls just collapse.
It's like they didn't hire any engineers.
They just hired us.
And then they like fly us out and we're like, oh, great.
We'll supervise the engineers.
And they're like, no, it's you three.
You're building it like something weird like that.
I do feel like that's possible where we get hired to do something.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, that's what I said.
There was another, a smaller indoor thing that the Marvel theme thing that fell apart
in I believe Thailand.
And it seemed to mostly be like one or two simulators and then a large shop and some
very, very poorly made statues.
But it cost a lot to get in.
You had to pay essentially to get it.
You were essentially paying to go into a large store.
But a significant amount of money based on like this is what the average resident of
Thailand makes in a day.
You had to pay that to get into this glorified shopping experience or something.
They're like, well, it fell apart.
We don't know what happened.
And everyone else is like, yeah, we know what happened.
Sure.
There is something weirder about the foreign ones or that the universal Dubai where they
built only the gates and then none of the rest.
So it's just a field with the universal.
Okay.
So there's some pretty funny, really funny ones.
This is all episode down the line, like all of the bizarre collapses.
But yeah, not all of them are like they even the Fox lawsuit mentions how we trusted this
place, Genting, because they did a pretty good job with universal Singapore.
It's fairly well regarded.
So what happened here?
So Genting, we don't know exactly, no.
But Genting did a good job.
It's not.
Maybe they did a good job.
But on the flip side, you talk about us building the place.
According to this thing, buildings would get built like many feet taller than the facade
that they were stored in.
So that makes me feel like let us add it.
So yeah, I think we could build this thing.
Well, it seemed like they also too were kind of harkening back to the original Disney method
of like build it.
It doesn't work.
Okay.
Scrap it.
Rebuild it.
Like a little more finding it on your feet.
Yeah.
With construction, that's kind of a weird thing to say.
It's really weird because it seems like there are several buildings in this park that were
fully built.
They had complaints.
They had to tear it all down.
Still, Disney tries to repurpose a building instead of rebuilding it from scratch.
That's so weird.
Yeah.
How they have the money to just...
And there's a lot of the lawsuits that are going around are all like they're in the
billion dollar territory.
This is so much money we're talking about.
Uh-huh.
Next, don't make this mistake again.
Any other studio, call PTR Construction.
Us.
Yeah.
I mean, we've heard...
We get some rumblings.
We get some emails that some Imagineer types listen to the show.
But do any very rich, Saudi princes listen to the show?
Do any Mercurial leaders listen to the show?
If that's you and you want your own theme park and you want it to be designed by some
real experts, contact us at PodcastTheRide at gmail.com.
Our official email address.
Subject line.
I am a Nigerian billionaire prince interested in helping you with your endeavors.
I have 30 million dollars in a bank account for you.
PTR, come to Brazil.
Help us build Bolsonaro land.
Now, we'll let the offers slide in.
Let's open every email on all of our computers.
Viruses be damned.
Mike, that transition you were...
Take us to that transition.
That was 20 minutes ago.
DJ, run this back.
We were talking about how Star Wars wasn't going to be fun until it tanked.
The Hanna-Barbera characters are in this spot right now where they haven't been used in
interesting ways.
They just haven't been used in a while in any big media.
They've been used in interesting ways in the comics.
We talked a little bit about this before.
You had a copy of something that caught my eye on your table.
Yes.
It was a graphic novel where Snagglepuss is a gay playwright.
He's like a very like kind of...
Truman Capote type.
Huckleberry Hound is gay in it and he's like his good friend.
It's like a very heavy...
It sounds like Snagglepuss.
You think it's going to be fun and silly, but it's a very heavy story.
It's good.
Wow.
There's a cool...
I haven't read it, but I suppose a cool Flintstones thing that I think Tom King wrote.
Yeah.
There's a Rough and Ready comic where it's like the Sunshine Boys.
Oh, that's great.
Really?
They were the stars of an old TV show and they're getting back together even though
they kind of hate each other, which I didn't realize Rough and Ready was the original Hanna-Barbera
TV show reading about this.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, interesting.
So Hanna-Barbera is in that spot right now where they haven't been...
There isn't like a big Hanna-Barbera movie in the last so many years.
No.
Yeah.
So let's have some fun with them.
Absolutely.
Why not?
Loosen those reins.
And I would love to take a crack at...
I was a big Hanna-Barbera kid because they made...
It's like 50 years this company making cartoons.
The rise of cable TV, I feel like the Hanna-Barbera stuff was just in syndication all the time.
Until it kind of all got vacuumed up by Turner and used as the backbone to start Cartoon Network
because the Hanna-Barbera cartoons were the main stuff on Cartoon Network and even,
I believe, helped Cartoon Network start to make their own original stuff like Johnny
Bravo and everything.
Let's just for...
In case there's kids listening that might not even know what Hanna-Barbera is,
let's list some of the main properties.
I mean, their first thing they created Tom and Jerry.
Is that right?
Yeah.
That's how they made their name, making the Tom and Jerry cartoons.
Oh my gosh.
So it wasn't their company, but there...
No, they were making them for one of the studios.
I forget whether it was MGM or Paramount.
So they were making it for one of the...
They were making all this stuff and then struck out on their own with a third guy.
Gotcha.
To start their own company.
Now, the interesting thing is there, the budget for the average Tom and Jerry short was about
$35,000, I was reading.
To make a five-minute rough and ready, maybe the Tom and Jerry shorts were like seven minutes,
five-minute rough and ready short, their budget was $3,000.
What?
They kind of got known for the limited animation style where it's like a cell,
you would only be animating like the top half of Top Cat or Snaggle Puss,
but the bottom half would be stationary.
Maybe people aren't walking if they don't have to walk.
I feel like I associate Hanna-Barbera with the chasing that repeats the hallway
or the Scooby-Doo thing.
What's rough and ready?
Rough and ready, when they...
It was a cat and a dog.
Yeah, they were like, I don't have a...
Oh, that's a tiny picture.
If you can see that.
I'm so far away from it.
It's comically small.
That's the one on Wikipedia.
What am I going to do here?
It's a cat and a dog.
Cat and a dog, I mean the big Warner Brothers things, Flintstones, the first prime time cartoon.
The Jetsons, another prime time.
Cartoon.
Huckleberry Hound.
They did a lot of...
This didn't dawn on me until reading about it.
They had these longer length shows and then they had other shows where it was like
three shorts packaged together.
Because I don't always know.
Obviously there was the Flintstones and the Jetsons,
but a lot of these other characters, I don't know where they live and how they existed
where even the characters in the ride, Dick Dasterdly and Muttley,
I wasn't exactly sure how they factored in.
They were from...
So some of these things were...
Wacky racers?
Wacky racers.
They would just start churning out stuff.
Once the Saturday morning cartoon boom started,
Hannah Barbera was just churning out characters and shows.
It's crazy because if I just...
We've mentioned the big ones, but if these names...
McGilligorilla, Johnny Quest, they had a Laurel and Hardy show.
They were a space ghost.
They had Birdman.
They had Shazan, which is like a genie man who I think is the
model for Robert Smigel's Shazang cartoon.
Oh yes, that's my favorite.
The scene where he beats up...
They did a Fantastic Four cartoon.
They do wacky races.
They did the Smurfs.
The Smurfs, originally a Belgian comic adapted into a cartoon
by Hannah Barbera.
They did Laverne and Shirley in the Army.
What?
And the Fonzie and the Happy Days gang cartoon.
And they did Partridge Family 2200 AD.
Hold on.
What?
We should go...
A little familiar.
It was overwhelming reading everything Hannah Barbera made.
Like part of that...
Again, a tiny graphic I'm going to show you, Scott,
but it's obviously Jetsons with the Partridge Family cartoon.
Wow.
An insane...
Also possibly the impetus for another Smugle one that I love,
Lady Smith Black Mambazo and Hatter Smith.
In the top 10 of Smugle.
Even in the 90s, I didn't realize they did Swat Cats.
They did Swat Cats.
They would play Swat Cats commercials in the line for the
Fantastic World of Hannah Barbera ride.
And Swat Cats was just like a Ninja Turtle ripoff,
Biker Mice from Mars or just anthropomorphic animals,
but they were like tough guys, animals.
Also worth mentioning the studio if you're in the Los Angeles area.
I don't remember which building, if it is the literal LA Fitness
at the bottom of the hill on Barham, below Universal Studios,
but right under Universal Studios.
Either it's the LA Fitness or the adjacent buildings.
The buildings are there, but it's not Hannah Barbera and hasn't been for a long time.
But like, yeah, they were next door neighbors of Universal Studios.
And the buildings around there are very like 60s mod.
So you can't imagine this is where the Jetsons was made or whatever.
Okay. Yeah.
The Wikipedia page for Hannah Barbera had a picture of the studio building
in like 2007 and mentioned it was in the Cahuenga Pass.
It might have still been at that point.
Yeah. So I don't, it looks really neat and it's crazy that,
and they were there for a long time until they got absorbed into whatever Turner entity.
You're not even aware where they ended up.
Hannah Barbera owned for many years by Taft Communications.
They came up on the Kings Island episode.
That's right, which is why they were featured.
That was their first theme park featuring was in Kings Island.
And then Taft got bought by Turner and then Turner got bought by Time Warner.
It kind of gets murky in the 90s.
Yeah, they trade hands a lot and their theme park history changes a lot, which is why it's,
you know, the fantastic world of Hannah Barbera ends up being their like primary theme park entry.
They exist in all, there's a bunch of odd little rides, but this is probably the most concerted.
And there's a lot of bizarre, like Flintstones is all over the map and there's this Flintstones
park somewhere that just closed. But this one's, this is probably oddly the main way the Flintstones
exist in theme park worlds, even though they're only a third of the ride is the Flintstones.
I really, I wish it all's maybe account for that very possibly people do not know this ride and
I wouldn't blame them because it's been closed since 2000 or something.
2002, it was open a lot longer than I thought. It was an open day,
Universal Orlando attraction, the kids attraction in addition to E.T. and the Nickelodeon Studios.
And it closed in 2002, so it was there 1990 to 2002, it's like 12 years. And that's also about
how long the Jimmy Neutron ride that replaced it lasted about 11 years or so.
Gotcha. Yeah, it's, it's, I did not know existed. I never went to Universal when I was young.
So I'm not kidding. It was, wow. I love this ride. Yeah, it's pretty large to me. And I probably
wasn't willing to go on any on everything there. And I was probably scared of some of the things
I did. I'm not, I think the first time I went, I was not, I did not brave jaws or maybe it wasn't
open yet. It was in that period where it was closed. But yeah, this was a opening day attraction,
one that worked for kids. And as the defunct land episode about it really pushes one of the
only rides that had no problems opening day of Universal Studios, because all of their major
attractions were big old disasters because they were all attempting all these things mechanically
that were probably outside the realm of possibilities for the industry at the time.
And this thing was like, it kind of helped the park through the first,
the rough first couple of months because it was, it was fine. It was the one you didn't have to
worry about. Yeah. I read a little about this in that, that Disney versus Universal Sam Genovese
book. I here's a from it. He says, Peter Alexander came up with the idea of a motion theater in a
conversation with Barry Upson. Alexander said, you know, these theme park attractions don't make
any sense. It's like every time you want to change out and put a new television show on,
you have to buy a new television. Let's see. He continued, yeah, he changed out the,
some of the props and we would have something new. So like, this was like an early, if not the first
motion theater ride. And like, sure enough, when it was time to change out this for another ride,
it took them less than six months to swap out Jimmy Neutron for Hanna-Barbera. Oh, no kidding.
And then, yeah, so the full history of this space at Universal Studios started as Hanna-Barbera,
became Jimmy Neutron and today is Despicable Me, Minion Mayhem, which one day we will get to in
seven parts, nine parts. We'll, we'll determine that at a later time. But the, but if you go on
that, so this Hanna-Barbera ride we're talking about never made it to Hollywood. Yeah. But the
Despicable Me ride did. So if you've been on that, but not any of the rest of what we're talking
about, you may know that as opposed to Star Tours, where you're in a cabin of a, of a simulator,
this one is like a big theater with a lot of little cars, which is how, that's how the
Despicable Me ride is. And that's how this Hanna-Barbera one was. So instead of the whole
theater moves all at once, it's like benches and like two or four, I'm not sure the, the
how it works exactly, but like. Are the seats the same or have they changed? Like is it the same
basic configuration? Do we know? I think same basic configuration. I'm sure they've changed the
actual vehicles over the years and they certainly changed the aesthetic, but it seems like the
modular nature of it. Like if one of those benches goes down, if one of those ride vehicles goes
down, they just put a tarp over it. You just don't go in that one. Oh yeah. Good. Sure. So
I can see why this did work so well. You're saying opening day, cause it's like, well, it was built
to be modular. It was clearly built to be simple. Very like, yeah, very mechanically friendly and
also, and, and mom friendly because there was, if you didn't want to get shaken around, if you did,
if you have a problem with motion sickness, they have benches that don't move. So you could just sit
up on the front of the bed. I think it was in the front. You could just sit and watch the movie and
not get shaken around, which I remember my mom doing. My mom and little brother definitely sat on
some benches at some theme park rides. Sure. I was going to say it's mom friendly because my mom
goes on still to this day about how good the Hanna Barbera cartoons were. Those were like her favorite
cartoons. She loves Top Cat. She loves McGilligarilla. She's, she, she'll tell you about it. She'll tell
you about Top Cat. We got a big DVD set of Top Cat a couple of years ago. Loves it. Now I'm not
sure I've ever seen one second of Top Cat. Top Cat is fun. I like Top Cat. My mom was also,
she said she was physically, she attracted to one of the cats on Top Cat when she was young.
What is supporting cast members? Not Top Cat himself. But I forget which one it is. I can look
it up. He had a whole gang of cats because they were all like kind of cool cat. Like they were all
up to mischief. They wouldn't do anything like real dangerous, but they would mess with some cops.
I think Hanna Barbera has some attractive characters throughout because obviously
Daphne and Velma and Scooby-Doo. Sure. And I think, hey, you know what? I think those guys are lookers
as well. Fred. Hey, Fred's a classic all-American, Lunkhead, prom king. And I'll say this. I think
I'm not specifically super attracted to Judi Jetson, but I think Judi Jetson is a well-rendered
character. And I'm a big fan of the Jetsons movie. Oh yeah. I was going to say I like that too,
about the devastation of mining ore for sprockets. That's right. That's a dark movie. Oh yeah. And
it's sort of like dealing with the natives or what, like those little creatures who it's actually
robbed. I forget the mechanics of how it works, but. Yeah. Isn't the first thing that they move
their house up from the pollution? Is that right? There is a shot. Yeah. It's not the start of the
movie. I haven't seen it in many, many years, but isn't that the first- It's not really commented
on that much. But isn't that what it is? Yeah. One of the first shots in the movie. They just rise
above any smog because they're on that weird house. Oh, okay. I don't know if I've ever put
that together before right now. Now that is, that movie was coming out around the time this ride
was opening. So there was what we would now call synergy that was happening. And I'm wondering if
they thought like, well, this is the start of a Hanna-Barbera film renaissance because like-
Maybe Flintstones was in the works. I mean, it was probably for sure in the works.
Yeah. At least, yeah. Though if maybe as a live action thing instead. The feature length Tom and
Jerry movie came a few years later, which I remember seeing in theaters and liking as a kid.
I have zero memory of that. Did I see that? Probably, but I'll be honest with you,
never a big Tom and Jerry fan. Didn't care for it as a kid. I find them sort of unpleasant for some
reason. Yeah. And in the movie, I feel like they didn't really, they just, there was, and now here's
a big Tom and Jerry cartoon. It wasn't really like elevated. Yeah. And they talk, I mean,
they talked in the cartoon later or the newer cartoon as well. Yeah. I think that's right.
But it's like, it clearly we're like, well, what are we going to do? Like these were short
cartoons where they would just beat each other up. Uh huh. Uh huh. And then they're like, well,
I guess they talk now. And I think that nothing, nothing ever really grabbed me about it. I used
to, and here's why I was extra mad at it. It would air right before Ninja Turtles. Oh, God,
be done. Oh, so you're resenting anything that's not so extra. There's an extra level of frustration
I think of when I think of Tom and Jerry. Did you guys, I think I knew TV schedules. I think I could
tell what time it was, uh, uh, by what was on TV. Like before I could tell time on a watch face,
I could go like, well, it's about 10 30. Cause uh, the Muppet babies are on and that'll be on again
at two. Uh, I do. Yeah. I remember the patterns like that. And I definitely remember that run and
Stimpy was on at 11 on Saturdays and I have to go help my dad like sweep up outside. And I was
always eyeing that clock. Like I better be in by 11. Right. Um, and I think Rugrats, I think it was
Rugrats 10 Doug 10 30 or maybe, oh yeah. Yeah. Which again, what, like what a run those three in
a row. I would remember too, and I can't pinpoint exactly what, but I would remember the blocks of
commercials would air in the same order. And I'm like, I don't like this commercial, but there's a
toy commercial coming up. I'm very fond of. Oh, maybe I, I know what you're saying. I do know
I think there would be, yeah. I think they would like play stuff. Yeah. In a row. No,
that does seem familiar. Now that you say that for like X-Men toys or Batman or toxic Avenger
too, I was really obsessed with the toxic Avenger toys based on the short-lived cartoon. Did you
like the cartoon? I liked the cartoon too, but the toys were very, the toys still look good.
Did you have the toys? Yeah. Okay. Do you remember any of the carrot? Cause I'm not,
I had no nothing of the toxic. I don't remember any of their names, but I remember being
a little grossed out by it. Little gross. Can I say, oh, and going back to a sort of like heart
throb, Hannah Barbera, please, I would like to shout out the, the object of Judy Jetsons affection
in the Jetsons movie, Apollo blue, the space rock star, which in general, I feel like I've caught
the people who had like childhood crushes on Apollo blue. And in general, the, all the, like the
songs from the Jetsons movie, I think are fantastic. It's these, there's this one, especially
that I think, cause Tiffany, the pop star, the voice of Judy, they would have recorded the actual
woman, Janet Waldo, who voiced Judy and then kicked her out of the movie cause they thought
they could sell more tickets with Tiffany. So Tiffany did songs and that's good. So they got
that. But Tiffany also then had to speak and her, I don't, I'm not sure puberty had finished
because her voice is cracking the whole time. It's like her voice is really annoying in the movie.
Wow. It's really strange. How old was Tiffany when she was putting out songs? Not sure. Very young.
Yeah. Really? I don't think I ever realized that. Young enough to, for her to get a lot of
horrifying stalkers and a documentary about those stalkers. I think we're alone now.
That plot in the movie is based on an old episode of the Jetsons, I think.
It's like my mom's favorite Jetsons episode, which I will, she'll tell you all about.
Judy is obsessed with a singer named Jet Screamer. And it's a very similar kind of a thing where it
like, and I think my mom liked it so much because like, I think she identified with Judy and being
obsessed with like rock and roll men. So this was sort of a Bobby Sherman stand in. I don't know
what style Jet Screamer was, but. He was, can we see this tiny graphic? I sure can't. And no,
no one at home can see it at all. You can see it even worse than me. Tiny photos. Those Jet
Screamer pinups you're after. I'm getting bad luck with the pictures. But I just, like this,
this one music video that's like Judy and Apollo Blue falling in love is so fucking awesome. They
like turn into like Cubist paintings and like, and like a like a like constellations form. And
then it turns into their into their face. It's like, it's so rad. I name checked it when I was
pitching Moonbeam City. Like I wanted to look like the Jetsons movie. I really like the Jetsons movie
aesthetically and to bring it back to the ride. One thing that I like is that it's an early combo
of 2D characters and 3D environments and it's pretty dated, but not horrifically. So you can
just tell it's from an era from a bygone era, but it's like not, it's kind of cool. And I think the
rides that way too. I like it. Yeah. Cause the 2D animation looks like classic Hanna-Barbera
2D animation. And then the CGI environments are very basic and stylized and kind of caricatury,
but it's not trying to be realistic. It's not trying to be photo realistic. It's just trying
to be cartoony and like a sort of like the, it reminded me almost of that a little later,
but that video game vector man, just a bunch of ball. You were a man, but he was just made up of
different balls and you could change shapes. And it was just like very simplistic CGI.
I was impressed because I was watching it and I was like, if somebody said this was made in 2000,
I would have been like, oh yeah, of course. Like I wouldn't have like doubted the technology,
but like 90 is pretty impressive. Like for it to look like that, which yeah, it's early.
Work from Rhythm and Hughes, a major like a CGI studio. I'm confused on my history. I just know
they became a major operation in the nineties. I don't know what they did.
Or I wrote down Rhythm and Hughes too, because Rhythm and Hughes just a few years ago was kind
of infamous because they did like award winning work on the life of pie movie. Oh, that was them.
That was them. And as the movie was winning all these awards, Rhythm and Hughes went under.
Wow. So like they're winning Oscars and like people are like getting severance checks and
packing up boxes. Like, yeah. Horrible. Oh my God. That's terrible. Well, gee, well, hey,
great. We're everything from life of pie to the Jetsons part of the ride. Good work.
I also really like the, I like the Scooby Doo zone. And it reminds me of like when you go into the
the castle part of the ride, it feels very much like Bowser's castle or like a Mario car level.
It's really neat. And I also now while you can tell some things up, like the 2D characters don't
blend perfectly with the 3D. Like it does feel like one thing laid on top of the other. However,
you got a 3D ship spinning all around and your camera view is changing and bending and everything
to animate the perspective of these characters and particularly Muttley and Dick Dastardly.
Like that they're like you're tracking them flying around just like the perspective that
these 2D animators had to keep in mind. Many of whom went on to work for Don Bluth.
Not long after this, I don't know. I'm just like, I'm very impressed by the like people might look
up this riot and go, this looks stupid. What are they talking about? But I think, but for the era,
for 1990, 1990 and Sylvan Bluth company working on this, oh, okay. Working on this. Some of them
they were in Ireland at that point it was saying. And then some of the animators came to Burbank to
work on this while the rest stayed in Ireland to work on the dreaded Rock-A-Doodle. And maybe that
other thing, Dinosaur in Central Park. One of their other things. Troll in Central Park. I think I saw
in their credits. There was a movie called the Troll in Central Park. They were making like two
other movies at the time. But now we're back at Dinosaur story. Maybe it was we're back.
These are weird. Yeah, these are, there's a whole genre. There's almost of these kids movies.
Hanna Barbera was doing some of these kind of kids, lost kids movies too. And yeah, Don Bluth
company. Yeah. Weird time. And you can't like, I feel like some of these things, like you knew that
they were bombs. You know, people did not like these movies. Today, I feel like the PR machine
for every, in my mind, there has not been a bombed kids cartoon in two decades because you're
like getting screamed about. You're getting screamed at about them so much. I'm like, I don't know. How
much, if you ask me, how much did Smallfoot make? I don't know. Probably a $1.2 billion. I have no
idea. I don't know. What was a hit or what wasn't a hit? Was Rango a hit? No idea. Maybe that one
wasn't. Let's assume it was. Yeah. If it was, if it's a cartoon from the last 20 years, it was a
gigantic hit. Everything. And you also hear all these stats. Every, every movie that comes out is
like, no, that's like seven times Jurassic park. Is it? What do you, how could that be? That can't,
but they're not in, it's not $94. It's yeah. Maybe. I don't know. There's, there's, there's how they,
there's cheats. I'm pining for those days back when movies could eat shit. Yeah. Back in my day,
there were unpleasant movies that scared young Jason and young Scott and young Mike. And then
they lost money and people got fired. Yeah. People should be fired. What am I nostalgic for?
Okay. Yes. So it was a troll in central park. Some of the state in Dublin and some of them
to work on rock a doodle and a troll in central park. So Don Bluth, he bopped around a lot. He
was at Disney. He made his own company. That company went under. He made another company. And
then I think he went to start the Fox animation. That word video game too.
Oh, dragon, dragon's layer. Yeah. I think so. I could never figure out how to play that.
I would put a quarter in and I was just like, what? It's a cartoon. I was confused too. Yeah.
It was like one of those weird Sega CD games or something where, or like that Scotty Pippin
basketball game where like it was so impossible to play. Like it was like a video. It was video of
Scotty Pippin and it just obviously didn't work. Like it was just like a strategy based game or a
turn based basketball game with Scotty. Every now and then my mom would order a Nintendo game off
QVC or the home shopping network and it would just be befuddling. Like I'd be like, what is this game?
And it'd be like a puzzle thing or I feel like there was a matchbox one that we had to send back
because it would stop working after the first level. Nothing frustrated me more because I always
put the blame on myself. This is my fault. You're not smart, Scott. You're fucking up. Any better kid
could outsmart this game. Maybe a lot of these games were impenetrable. Yeah. I think there was
a lot of garbage back. I mean, there's still a lot of garbage games, but yeah, I think yeah, you would
rent a game from the store and you would know nothing about it. Maybe Nintendo Power had a
blurb, but it would be just the controls were horrible. Stuck in a corner on the James Bond
Jr. video game. Like not even a 10th of the way through the first level and then you're just stuck
with it all weekend. I feel like Nintendo 64 is the first system where we're self-aware enough to
know that this game is bad. It's not your fault. It's because this game is poorly made. Like
famous one, Superman 64, Mission Impossible at Nintendo 64. Famously bad games. Oh, that game
was fun. Mission Impossible? Yeah. I beat that a bunch of times. Oh, Jason, Mission Impossible is
horrible. Stop bragging. We were so excited for GoldenEye and Mission Impossible. GoldenEye came
out first and then Mission Impossible kept getting delayed and Mission Impossible blew. It was so bad.
It was like very close to the movie, which is like a terse pot boiler and not exactly
filled with video game like ask scenes, you know. It's a noir game. It's just about mood and pacing.
You could do nothing in that game. You change costumes a lot. GoldenEye could shoot a scientist
in the head. You could go in different cool places. You could really like have a lot of freedom.
You had one gun. Sometimes. You had one gun. You couldn't turn around and you could barely do
anything. The whole idea was you're supposed to sneak places and you couldn't do. It wasn't fun.
No, but you could do the break-ins. You did do the wire scene. It was fun.
No, we're going to look up this game. I'm going to get this game and you're going to play it now.
We're going to play GoldenEye and Mission Impossible. It's not even a contest. It's
not even the same level. I just remember. That's the most unfair thing you just proposed.
We're going to play what everyone agrees is the best of the era and then this thing.
We'll just play Mission Impossible. It's garbage. It's horrible.
GoldenEye might still be the gold standard for me because I had all the Bond games that came out
after that too. The other GoldenEye game and the World is Not Enough video game. Very similar to
GoldenEye, but it wasn't as good, but it was more detailed. It was like, oh look, you can see him
reloading. I can get a dirty used copy of Nintendo 64's Mission Impossible for $470 with free shipping.
Oh, we could Twitch that. Sure, we could. Is that theme park related? Maybe?
Maybe. Tangentially.
Tangentially. It talks about Mission Impossible 4.
Paramount Park will have a Mission Impossible. There's going to be Mission Impossible rides soon,
I think. Also. That would be cool.
We've been waiting long enough. Well, I'll look into the cheapest way I can get.
Let's get back to the fantastic world of Hanna-Barbera. I would like to start talking
about this, my beloved pre-show. I don't think I knew how much I liked it until rewatching it.
It's such a blast. You get into a line where you're watching Hanna-Barbera clips. What was that one?
The Cats show? The Ready? No, the crazy.
Swat Cats. You're watching Swat Cats clips and you're starting to wonder, well, how are these
dazzling cartoons made? That's what I'm here to find out because my entire day at Universal Studios
Florida is about finding out how movies are made. I'm trying to just do an educational museum trip
and then the real things from the movies keep interrupting my knowledge. Very frustrating,
obviously, but maybe this one will be different. I'm going to learn how cartoons are made.
It's very on point with the early universal premise of ride the movie. Learn how this stuff
is made. Learn, then ride. Learn some more. I don't remember what The Room was like,
but it was sort of like, I feel like there was like a rocket. It was like a weird, odd cartoony
room. You meet a yogi who wants to eat a sandwich. He's eyeing a sandwich.
Boo Boo reminds him that these people aren't just here to see him eat a sandwich,
that they're here to learn about how cartoons are made. He's like, oh, really?
Also, I was very, the yogi voice, not great. Not the classic, I think, what's his dog's butler
did yogi and he had just died and was replaced. Some of the Jetsons people died. Mel Blank.
Mel Blank had just died too. I was immediately listening to the video. I was like, that's not yogi.
Yeah. Yeah. No, it was a latter day yogi, but you do, I was going to say,
you do get a couple of original voices in this. You get Gene Vanderpil, who played Wilma and Rosie,
the robot, and you get Casey Kasem. Who jetted up until a few years before he died.
Wow. Really? Yeah. He was still, and it's him in taking Matthew Lillard to task in the commissary,
in the famous scene in Looney Tunes back in action, which I say just because I only learned
about it like a month ago. I find it very funny that- They did that.
Wow. Looney Tunes landed the Matthew Lillard cameo. Hell yeah. Also, not the original Dick
Dastardly, sadly. It was like Michael Bell, who's like a prolific voice actor, but only was Dick
Dastardly in this. I didn't know Dick Dastardly was Paul Winchell, the voice of Taylor.
Oh, I missed that. That's cool. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Great. Great voice actor.
Only on this podcast will somebody go, yeah, did you know he was, it was Paul Winchell?
And I'd be like, whoa, that's awesome. Holy shit. Wow. Paul Winchell.
I got one more in this area too. In this ride, it's an early performance of Jeff Bergman as
Fred Flintstone. Jeff Bergman's a guy who does a ton of the voices. Nah, he's like one of those,
like Cory Burton in the Disney world who does pitch perfect versions of the origin of the voices
from the forties through the seventies and beyond. Yeah. Like Billy West with Looney Tunes.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. This guy also was Bugs. I don't know why it's Billy West sometimes and
Jeff Bergman sometimes. Yeah. I'm wondering. I don't know. I don't know the answer to that.
But he's Fred Flintstone in this. And when he started taking over the beloved voices,
maybe the first one that he jumped on was Jeff Bergman took over as the Pillsbury Doughboy
for Paul Fries. Did you know that? The ghost host in the Haunted Mansion was the Pillsbury Doughboy.
I think I went down the rabbit hole a couple of years ago and was like, oh yeah, wow, that's crazy.
I don't hear that at all. Yeah, I don't. He does have a couple of voices that are way out there
because he's Ludwig Von Drake too, which I would never have thought was the same as a ghost host.
So like he does have some range there. Also, Thorol being Tony the Tiger blew my mind.
Thorol Ravenscroft being Tony the Tiger. So like these guys would go back and forth between doing
these Disney jobs and then just cereal. Yeah, I guess a lot of them are cereal.
And I think Paul Fries was the Toucan. It was Toucan Sam maybe too. Oh, that sounds right.
But that was, don't call me on that. I'm not totally sure. Can I try something real quick?
Yeah. Oh, your carnivorous. Oh, now I fucked it up already.
That was going to be that Pillsbury Doughboy doing the ghost host dialogue.
Oh, try it again. Your carnivorous.
Your carnivorous paler betrays an aura for moaning. Nothing says lovin'.
I have been doing, this is a whole thing with Lindsay and I, for years I've been doing this voice,
but he's very, she goes, he's very cloying. She sounds like.
Nothing says lovin'. Well, we know what this sounds like. This is Olaf.
Well, it does sound like Olaf. Yeah, it's basically, I have like four moves.
Is this room actually stretching? I'm a bad snowman. Nothing says lovin'.
Sorry. All right. I just had to do the owing and awing about these voice names.
We had to get it out. But anyway, so Yogi realizes he needs, we need to get back. We need to get on
track. We got to learn how cartoons are made. Because he doesn't know how
ammunition is made. He like fucks it up so hard. It is pretty funny.
I know, I like it. Absolutely.
Yeah, it goes out of his way to say it wrong. Yeah, Yogi's funny. And so he turns it over
to a different monitor where we're introduced to Hannah and Barbera themselves.
This old man in sweaters and Oxford shirts. And this is like, I don't say this slightly,
pretty neck and neck with Michael Eisner in terms of like wonderfully lovable, stilted acting from
people who are not on camera very often. I love anything like this. And these theme parks obviously
are full of this. They're close to Spielberg, you know what? You got the ET adventure right down the
street. I've been underrating this Hannah Barbera video for a long time. Excellent pre-show.
They're both like 80. I think one of them died at 95 and the other died at 92.
No, one of them died in like 2001.
I mean their ages. They died at 95. No kidding. Yeah, you're right. 2006 or 2002 as well.
And they were connected to the company that shared their name pretty much I feel like until
they died. Like some stuff, like the one who was still alive was given a creative consultant credit
on that the Tom and Jerry movie. So I don't know that they were like hands on with everything,
but for a company that was sold to like two or three different major communications concerns,
like they never walked away. They never walked away. Yeah. Huh? Wow. Well, and they were hands
on on this thing obviously and appearing in it. And so when it cuts to them, they are as heads of
animation studio or want to do, they are surrounded by their characters of Fred and Barney and Scooby
Doo and George and George and wait, who's the Jane, George and Jane Jetson, Jane, his wife,
Jane, his wife. And, and they are all, it's this weird angle because you're looking at Fred and
Barney from behind and they're all waiting for orders from their creators and they're being told
like, okay, Fred, you get it. They need you on stage four. All right, George and Jane,
remember to take your scripts this time. As a precocious child, I thought that was very funny.
Like this is not the first time, like I'm sure there's Looney Tunes stuff where they're sitting
around in a break room waiting for something to do. But I always liked the joke of like
the cartoon characters going to a soundstage to work like they were actors. Yeah. All sitting
around a trailer, checking their phones, doing their taxes. And they don't speak. They just
lovingly wait and listen and then just dopey Fred and Barney just turn around and walk away.
Okay. And then once the characters have been cleared out, they start talking to us and they're
very warm and reminiscing about the wonderful times making cartoons and they're looking at
storyboard. Well, they tell you how cartoons are made. Well, cartoons are a series of drawings all
done in rapid order to make it look like it's moving. And then they show us first, it starts
with the storyboards. Oh, remember that old villain Dick Dastardly? I sure do. I guess to
remind you of who Dick Dastardly is, but his Wacky Racers was 20 years ago. I'm still not even sure.
There was a new Wacky Racers. It's Wacky Races, right? Races. Isn't it Wacky Races? It might be
Races, but I always called them the Wacky Racers because they were the racers. I don't know if I
could be wrong. I remember there was a whole- There was a newer one a couple years ago.
Not a couple years ago. Around the 90s time, might've been a couple years after. I remember
there were 3D cartoons in the morning at like 7 a.m. And I remember because I had to set a
tape for it. And I think there was a new Yogi Bear and it was 3D and you had to get your
glasses off a cereal box. Now that was definitely a thing that Fox Kids or Wernher Brothers Kids
would program 8 to noon, but then there would also be cartoons from 7 to 8. And I always like to try
and- I would always miss them, but if I was up really early I would see them and it was always
something weird. It was like, yeah, Wacky Racers 2.0 or some shit. So yeah, there was new- So kids
should've kind of known who Dick Dastardly is. Dick Dastardly shows up. He wasn't the most
popular character. I think he shows up in the one where they steal the spruce moose.
What? Is that- they steal a plane and they meet a bunch of other cartoon characters. Am I crazy?
Dick Dastardly kind of a go-to for like if there's a crossover he would be the bad guy. He's like
Loki in the first Avengers or something. He crosses over. Oh, he straddles the worlds. Absolutely.
So yeah, they're reintroducing Dick Dastardly. But he had been around or he was going to be
around soon. I don't know. It's interesting. They're taking no chances. I understand. People
come from out of the country. They don't know Dick Dastardly like we do. He's clearly a villain,
like just in his mustache and his look. He's got a Snidely whiplash quality. I was going to say,
he is sort of looks- in my mind he just looks like Snidely whiplash. It's the same design.
And he's kind of a pre-warrior. Like a real gangly- past a certain point, tall characters are fine,
but the ganglier you get, you're probably a villain. If you're short and stout,
you're a villain maybe like Mutley. Wario is short and stout.
Mm-hmm.
Boris.
Waluigi.
Oh yeah, Boris is bad enough.
Waluigi is ganglier.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. So these are the original Wario and Waluigi essentially.
And then they're deciding how to demonstrate the process of animation, which is many drawings
put together. And how do they do it? By drawing Elroy Jetson, which they do. And he comes to life
on the piece of paper and is alive as Fred and Barney already were, thus negating the information
that cartoons or many drawings put together. So they have overturned- well, either you do lots
of drawings and you photograph them rapidly or you create a living being. And Fred and Barney
are alive today and they were just in the room, but Elroy does not exist until we make him exist.
Like I don't-
But now he exists and now he can walk around. We have a living boy in the pages.
Don't forget my anti-gravity backpack.
Oh, look at him go. There he is.
He's got the personality that we all know. But well, all right, once you draw a cartoon,
they're only alive for seven months and then you got to shoot them and start anew.
It's like the end of the-
Seven months they start to feel pain.
It's like the end of the prestige.
You run them through the prestige machine.
You got a pile of Elroy Jetsons in tanks. You got to buy all these tanks to keep them in.
The last Elroy has to murder the new Elroy has to murder the previous Elroy.
All right, hop to it, Elroy. Blast him with your jetpack.
Shoot your flames onto your clone.
So to backtrack, they set out to draw Elroy Jetson. Let's draw Elroy Jetson. Great. It'll be easy.
We've been animating the Jetson since 1962. I like them assessing that it will be easy to do it.
What should we draw, Bill? A new character? No, that'll be hard.
Draw the 28-year-old one.
Well, remember back then when our friends Fred and Barney were still hocking cigarettes in between
commercial breaks?
Those were the days.
Now we got to leave it to other characters to teach kids how to smoke.
I kill to draw Joe Camel, my favorite cartoon character.
It destroys me. We didn't make him up.
We've been animating the Jetsons since 1962.
Has it really been that long? It sure has.
Yep, but it has all been fun. It sure has.
They have now said three times within 30 seconds, I sure do. It sure has.
It sure has. These delightful old timers, so much sure.
They're so sure. That's the thing. When you get to be that age, you are so sure.
We're all racked with doubt at all times, but these guys are so sure.
They know. Is there ever a pre-show with two older guys in it?
I don't think so. I think the oldest people at Theme Park anywhere.
What if they're dead? Hitch was in his.
But not custom, not original.
Maybe Charlton Heston hosted the earthquake ride.
I don't think he was older, though.
I don't think he was older.
It sure has been a fun ride.
I sure did torture Janet Lee. I drove her to insanity.
The sexual harassment fun? It sure was.
I sure did harass many.
So anyway, they draw Elroy. He's alive before he has a body.
He requests his jet pack as Jason's or his anti-gravity backpack.
Backpack, I think. Cool.
Which he doesn't really use.
I thought that was going to be a Chekhov's gun thing.
It's like, that's how it'll get away.
Yeah, they're setting up nothing there, huh?
Nope. They sure are.
They sure are. It sure doesn't pay off.
Then they explain that animation is also done via computers these days.
Which, once again, they present a fact and then illustrate the opposite of that fact,
which is that, like, why computers do the animation today?
Let me show you.
Then one of them has magic in his finger, fires the magic into the corner,
and creates a big weird space computer.
In fact, Elroy says, it's the spaciest.
And then the computer draws Dick Dastardly's ship.
In 3D.
In 3D, though they are in 2D.
But then 2D Dick Dastardly pops out of it.
Yes. Correct. But you get mix-ups like that when you shoot magic out of your finger.
Well, sure.
So he comes to life, he says that he's tired of being called old Dick Dastardly,
and he requests to be the star of the next Hannah Barbera project.
The next project.
A ill-defined TV show, short subject, doesn't matter.
Yeah, educational thing.
Kind of a big ask.
Yeah, absolutely.
Not unreasonable.
You don't just demand to be the star of things, especially if you're more of a character actor.
Right.
And they correct him right away, and they say, you can't, Elroy's next,
followed by Fred Flintstone, and then the other one, then Scooby-Doo.
And they kind of were right.
Jetsons movie, then live action Flintstones, then eventually live action Scooby-Doo.
They get a slate.
It goes in the order.
I don't know that that is how they intended it to make out.
Might have been accidental, but it's right.
I have a feeling that if the Jetsons movie was a huge, huge hit,
we would have seen Hannah Barbera feature movies like that.
The cartoon, the new updated version of their style?
Updated version, theatrical, because it was a theatrical release, right?
Yeah.
I believe I saw it at the mall I talked about on a past episode with the waterfall.
Oh, yeah.
Nice.
What a day.
I think I saw that when I know I had that and the DuckTales movie on VHS.
Oh, yeah.
I have a lot of affection for those because I could just watch them over and over again.
Those are good ones for sure.
Wow.
Well, let's make a video.
Let's make like a weird YouTube conspiracy video where they point out how this predicts
the order of all the movies coming out and that somehow something in the Hannah Barbera
right also predicts 9-11.
Predicts 9-11.
So Scooby-Doo, we'd love to break rank, but Scooby-Doo is next and he is not satisfied
with this answer so he kidnaps Elroy and takes him into a swirling vortex.
Dick Dasterdly and Mutley come to life and abduct a child.
They abduct a child who they don't know.
They've never interacted before.
There are some interactions in this ride.
George Jetson knows Yogi, but Yogi and Boo-Boo don't seem to know Scooby and Shaggy.
Well, it depends on if they've been summoned to the same
taking of orders meeting by Hannah Barbera.
So if Flintstones meets the Jetsons, which we have to briefly mention at least,
was a couple of years before this.
I think that's right.
The Yogi Bear thing I was thinking of was called Yogi Bear and the magical flight of the Spruce
Goose.
The Spruce Moose was a big plane in Tailspin, another show I liked a lot.
But the Spruce Goose is the real plane.
This was a 1987 animated made-for-TV film produced for syndication as part of the
Hannah Barbera Superstars 10 series.
So again, they were just churning stuff out for syndication.
This show featured Yogi Bear, the Flintstones, the Jetsons, Scooby-Doo, Huckleberry Hound,
and Top Cat.
But just A-listers in this ride.
Just Scooby and the Flintstones and the Jetsons and Yogi and Boo-Boo.
All right, Fred, you're next.
Then Scooby-Doo, then the Partridge family from the year 2060.
Then Secret Squirrel.
Then Laverne and Shirley in the army.
Then the Wonder Twins.
Then Apollo Blue, Space Age rock star.
Hannah Barbera also, I think we may have mentioned earlier, responsible for not just
the backboat of Cartoon Network, the early backboat of Adult Swim, Space Ghost Coast
Coast, The Brack Show, Sea Lab, and very limited animation on a lot of those shows.
A lot of archival animation that they just redubbed.
But it shows you how I feel like the original intent was let's design some characters who
were cool and compelling to look at because we will not be animating them too much.
And that ethos made it into obviously Space Ghost Coast to Coast and some of those other
shows.
And they are, it's a real credit to that the designs are good because that's all you're
looking at.
Yeah, well, and a lot of that credit goes to Alex Toth.
Toth or Toath, the renowned.
T-O-T-H.
T-O-T-H, renowned comics artist and designer for Hannah Barbera.
Really?
Did a lot of work and widely regarded as like one of the best draftsmen in American comics.
Yeah, it is funny because Space Ghost does look cool.
Absolutely.
Just him smiling when it just cuts back and forth between silent shots on Space Ghost.
That's fantastic.
Yeah, really funny.
So anyway, look, there's a pecking order.
Dastardly breaks it and kidnaps a child and they go into a vortex and then the computer
machine explodes.
A computer that was created by Hannah Barbera out of thin air five seconds ago.
Then it's sparking and lighting the room on fire.
They reacts to the explosion for so long because it has to cover.
I love it.
Yogi dialogue.
I pause just of them like reacting to obviously like nothing and it's just so funny.
Please look it up if you don't know this.
The highlight is when is it Hannah is that the dark haired one?
The way he trots out of the room.
Yes, like cartoon character.
This like cartoon like jaunts to get out of the room.
If you know what that sounds imagine that sound but visualized.
Yeah, really funny, but I think it's funny on purpose.
I think that's him.
Let me get out of here.
He's having fun doing that.
It's really fun.
It looks like a prestigious thing.
They invented a machine that caught on fire and then in their own office and then they say,
let's get out of here.
They just abandon them.
They burn the place for insurance money.
We spent so much time with them.
I really wish they just went on the ride with us.
That's the problem.
The only problem I can see with it is setting them up so hard in the early part of it.
Wow, we're going fast.
We sure are.
Wow, I feel like we've been traveling at 15 miles an hour.
But that'll be easy.
There's much more difficult speeds than that.
There sure are.
If they were commenting like Statler and Waldorf.
Oh, yeah.
I also want suited characters.
Walk around.
Of them.
And one to tell me like, boy, Scott, you're a handsome young lad.
You sure are.
Oh, they should have.
Keep working on your drafting skills, kid.
If Lucille Ball is still walking around, they should have Hannah and Barbera walking around.
Yeah, we got to repopularize them as characters.
Are there other instances of them doing this thing?
I think they would introduce stuff every now and then.
I don't have much of a memory of the two of them introing stuff on VHSs or DVDs.
And I think the memory would have lingered because as we've established in many episodes
of this podcast, I care about that stuff way more than the actual Louise.
Much more.
Much, much more.
Yeah, so I would have thought I would have remembered these kindly old men.
Just like Elroy's dads.
Elroy's two dads.
I think I would remember that.
But I feel like there is not that much of them doing this, but I could totally be wrong.
They introduced me to the concept that there could be two dads.
This is how I learned.
Oh, yeah.
Yes, and they made me an open minded.
Very progressive, Hannah and Barbera.
So now you entered the ride.
And you know what?
You guys take it from here because who cares?
The fun is kind of, the real fun is over.
The real fun of watching two old men.
Two sweater men.
Explaining basic amination concepts.
I always thought this was a funny, like, you know,
Boo Boo says, like, what's our, how do we power this thing?
Like, what's our source energy?
Like, and he makes up some, you know, anti-matter rocket fuelers.
And then Yogi goes, a big old rubber band, Boo Boo, buddy.
And it is like you are putting a slingshot and it's shot out.
Like, I thought that was really funny.
I like that.
Yes.
A big old rubber band.
I have a question.
Where is Yogi during this?
You hear his voice.
He's commenting and you're on one of 60 rockets inside a room.
So where's Yogi?
Well, I think the logic is you are in one rocket.
You were specifically the rockets from the outside of the building.
Oh, which Yogi is in.
Which Yogi is in.
So you were in the rocket with Yogi.
Oh, interesting.
This was really, I do not remember these giant children sitting in this horrifying marquee.
Yeah, they're scary.
Is that me?
Is that what I look like?
That's you.
These mannequin dolls that were just on the outside of the universe.
That's you in your childhood crush, Scott.
That girl.
Yeah, she's kind of a looker.
Yeah.
And then these A-listers, the Hanna-Barbera A-listers.
George.
George, Scooby, Fred, Yogi, Boo Boo.
And most of whom have ties.
Most of whom have ties.
Hanna-Barbera's characters were professional.
That's what I like at the end of it.
Yeah, George clocked in to a job.
McGillicorilla had a tie too, didn't he?
Yes.
This was a period where people respected each other and dressed right.
Did Top Cat have a tie as well?
I think he had a collar.
He had a collar?
He certainly had a hat.
Back when people wore hats.
They had a collars only policy in their cartoons.
You didn't get also a mark against Dick Dastardly.
Sorry, Top Cat only in a vest.
Still pretty sharp.
A waistcoat, a purple waistcoat.
Pants they don't care about.
In fact, no Anna-Barbera characters wear pants.
Right.
But as long as your shirt is nice.
One of his friends had it, like a kind of a makeshift tie.
One of his gang.
All right.
Huckleberry Hound, respected lawman.
Was he a policeman?
He was a sheriff, wasn't he?
Oh, Huckleberry Hound had a bow tie.
Wow.
He had a bow tie.
But then sometimes he would wild out as El Cabong, right?
That was his alter ego when he would hit people with his guitar.
That is right.
This is very interesting to me.
Hanna-Barbera and ties.
Yeah, I'm looking at a big picture.
The average all I don't think had a tie.
They also did the Banana Splits cartoon.
They did so, I mean, yeah, a deep dive.
Hanna-Barbera here, I'm looking.
Smurfs.
Oh, it looks like they did a Richie Rich cartoon as well.
One of the Richie Rich revivals.
El Cabong is just a, that is just a Zorro.
Oh, okay.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
What I'm, I just went to a website called nowinnow.com having Googled Hanna-Barbera ties.
And this is a time and money saving trick.
Because as this says, think about how your torso, arms, legs change when your expression changes.
When your face is smiling, the rest of your body reacts.
Or if you're like turning to look at something
and like a lot of the difficulty of animation is the boring like middle parts.
So this was like a way around having to have their head do the same thing as their body.
Oh, interesting.
Like the tie is a reset point.
Interesting.
So it's, it helped with the limited animation.
I guess so.
Interesting.
Because there's like, there's a dog on here with has like a neckerchief.
Snaggle Puss has a little bow tie.
Wally Gator has the collar.
That's what you were thinking.
And let's talk females.
Wilma has pearls.
Jane has a big triangle on her neck.
Everyone has something on their neck.
Yes.
And doesn't Daphne have a little neckerchief as well?
I think so.
Maybe Velma as well.
Sorry, El Cabong was not Huckleberry Hound's alter ego.
I think it was a horse.
Oh, but no, what was the horse's real name?
The horse was also a cowboy.
Oh man.
There's so many Hanna-barbera characters.
People are going to be pissed.
People have probably been so mad this whole time.
But I'm correcting myself in real time about the thousands of Hanna-barbera characters
that are out there.
There's a lot to keep straight.
I think it was smart of them though to just stick to the big ones for the ride.
Because I think kids now in King's Dominion and in the Virginia Paramount Park,
you could meet I think Top Cat was Pink Panther.
Yeah, Pink Panther?
Is he Hanna-barbera?
I don't know about that.
If you were mad before, you're really mad now.
But Huckleberry Hound was definitely welcome.
Oh, and Kong Fu Louie, right?
No, no, no, no, no, Kong Kong Fuie.
What did you just call him?
Kong Fong Louie.
It was Kong first of all.
Kong Fu Louie.
Oh, okay.
That's what you said.
Which is a thing too where you say instead of Kong Fu, you always say Kong Fu for some reason.
I don't know where I got that.
Kong Kong Fuie, I liked watching as a kid,
but now I'm realizing there's got to be something problematic about it.
Oh, yeah.
But it was like Scamming Carruthers I think doing his voice.
I think all representations of Asians and Asian Americans in all media of the 20th century is fine.
Let's say there's no need to re-litigate anything.
I'm sure if you go back, there's not a bunch of bizarre wardrobe and teeth.
It's all fine.
Marvel Comics famously, I just learned this recently because Marvel Comics announced
they're doing a Shang-Chi, the master of Kong Fu movie.
You said Kong Fu again.
I think.
It's fine.
If we stop every time I say it.
But what they wanted to make was they wanted the comic rights to the Carradine TV show
that was very popular in the 70s.
Kong Fu.
Kong Fu, yeah.
They could not attain those rights, but what was affordable was the rights to the character Fu Man Chu.
They created a new character named Shang-Chi who was the hero son of Fu Man Chu and often
feuded with his father.
Shang-Chi has stuck around and has been on the Avengers and the comics and stuff.
Marvel is making a movie out of a character that dates back to like,
I don't know, let's make the Carradine people don't want to do it.
See, we can get Fu Man Chu and then it's his kid and he's good at karate.
He was a copyright work around character.
As we have learned, the ties are neck work arounds.
One of the hardest things to draw is a neck.
I guess, yeah, if you're like an aspiring animator of hand-drawn animation,
just put a tie on the character.
Make it easier on you and the people overseas that will be animating it.
Or a pearl necklace or like some prince art in your apartment, a big prince ruffle collar.
Oh yeah, that would be great.
It doesn't have to be a tie, but just something on the neck, an ascot.
And yeah, also if you want to look sharp when you go out, wear any of these things.
Quick drama growl was the horse cowboy.
Oh yeah, yeah.
So many characters, unbelievable.
It is crazy how many characters they have.
Yeah.
Like the library is pretty insane.
But some of them like, writing about Hanna-Barbera pretty open of like,
all the animation studios were just stealing from each other at the time.
And everything's based on old movies.
Yeah, and everything's based on old.
Okay, the rubber band launches you into the world of the flat stones.
Bedrock.
You avoid it, the elephant slips around.
Let me say this, as soon as we got into like this area,
and this will be like in the first couple seconds of the ride,
I really got a podracer vibe, an episode one podracer vibe from this thing.
Because it's sort of like, it's sort of dirt and canyon.
Like a Tatooine, before you get to full bedrock,
it's like a little Tatooine-ish and you're in kind of a little podracer.
I think that this ride in general has some
pre- qualities of the Simpsons ride before the Simpsons ride.
Yes.
That there is, that it's a chase of a villain,
I guess as is the Back to the Future ride.
And that there's weird, it's a world that you know as 2D, but rendered as 3D.
And I find it equally exciting, just on some base level,
that you're on a ride and getting a grand vista.
And as in the Simpsons ride, when you're hearing the real theme,
or the kind of the glow of the Simpsons,
and you're going to fly into Springfield,
hearing the big Flintstones theme, which is a wonderful theme,
and you're entering bedrock, I think that's actually an exciting moment.
Also, you're kind of doing, it's similar to what you're saying the Simpsons is,
you get to go up the dinosaur.
I hope everyone knows what we're talking about.
Our listeners are young, but maybe know this weird stuff.
The opening of the Flintstones is like Fred's leaving work.
If we're now going to start explaining shit.
I know.
I'm just trying to think of what we're making people out.
You can find most of this shit on YouTube uploaded.
You guys know the Flintstones, I don't want to be like, I'm not talking down to you.
Let me throw this out there, because I'm sure Disney Plus
will pay the way for the Disney short back catalog of all the Mickey cartoons
and Silly Symphony stuff.
Do any of the streaming services have the Hanna-Barbera library up?
It's a good question.
I don't know.
Does Warner Brothers have, I mean Cartoon Network has some version of it,
but I don't think there's a big one.
In the night, there was Cartoon Network and there was Boomerang,
and that's where they later put a lot of the older cartoons on the Boomerang channel.
I think Boomerang is now an app with some archive stuff.
There's something called VRV now, I think.
That's where the Flintstones live.
We're going to start a VRV ride to bring them back.
Isn't that where some See-So stuff landed?
And some anime stuff.
There's anime on there, but there's Cartoon Network stuff on there.
It's very confusing.
I don't know where the hell you watch anything anymore,
and that's why nobody sees anything anymore,
as opposed to all these shows that were just on all the time.
If you didn't grow up with Flintstones and Yogi Bear just on,
you might not know about them.
I don't disagree, Mike, with your premise.
You might have to explain the Flintstones,
but we also operate from a world where we assume our listeners know
the names of every bear in the country.
Sometimes I get out and I start to think,
like, what if just a random person walked by the apartment right now
and listened to what we were saying?
Would they know what we're speaking?
And then I start to go, oh, we should fill them in.
But it's like, why would I even bother?
What did Griffin Newman say to us that his girlfriend said that
she listened to the podcast and that it was as if this is like listening
to a movie podcast where you have no idea what movies are?
Right.
You have to be acquainted to movies in general.
It looks like you can watch 24 seasons,
332 episodes of the Flintstones on Boomerang.
So Boomerang might be the way to do it.
So Boomerang is the way to go.
So if you're so inclined.
Boomerang is yabba dabba doomerang.
Yabba dabba do is a phrase that is yelled when the clock goes off
and Fred has to, Fred is leaving work.
He's a construction worker.
But the clock is a bird.
Just to catch everybody up.
The animals also have jobs.
The animals have jobs and you run into some of the animals with jobs.
And they're resigned that it is a living.
Yes.
But yeah, they don't leave though.
They don't leave.
And actually this brings me to something I was going to say about the,
not to jump around too much, but at the end of this ride,
you go into this little room of interactive games
that's themed to some of the places that you've been like Bedrock and Space City.
Where do they live?
I don't know the name of the jetty.
It's not as memorable as space rock.
Scooby-Doo just was like an itinerant wanderer.
So you were just in a spooky graveyard and then a spooky castle.
Yeah.
A haunted amusement park, which we're already in an amusement park.
So that's what it's supposed to be.
A haunted amusement park.
Not that one.
Not the one in the ride, but that's just common where they are.
And hanging out with Dick Van Dyke and the castle, that big castle that you go into
looks a little like Cinderella.
Oh, you think it's maybe a little dig?
Maybe it's a little.
I think it might be.
Yeah.
The stones are black.
Yes.
Yeah, I see what you're saying.
I can see that.
Now, I look, I'm entering into 90s standup territory if I break down too much logic of
the Flintstones animals and their jobs.
However, I would like to point out specifically that in the thing after this,
there's a keyboard that you jump around on like big.
And when you step on the keys, a different bird squawks a note.
And there's a video where they squawk the Flintstones theme.
It's awful.
It is awful to listen to.
And that's like a coordinated song being played by this bird organ,
let alone just the claptrap, a bunch of kids stepping on it.
I'm going to go ahead and say I think maybe the worst place to work in 1990s.
Oh, yeah.
Studios must have been anywhere near this fucking bird organ.
But all right, all the Flintstone animal jobs don't make sense.
But in this case, there's nine birds and they all have to wait for a key to be stepped on.
And they have to hit a note and they can't do any other note
because or else the thing won't work.
And this is how music was made in Flintstone times and then recorded onto a different stone,
which was put on a turntable and played by a different bird by a bird's beak.
Which I think they did once an episode.
They got a lot of mileage out of that gag.
The bird beak on the record?
On the record, yeah.
Yeah, I believe so.
Maybe seven times.
Yeah, and what always disturbed me is that the animals were always aware of this horrible
existence.
It's a living joke when they would dump garbage in the bird's mouth.
Wasn't that what they would do?
They'd dump their garbage in their bird's mouth and go, it's a living.
And he'd look over at you.
Or like the one, isn't it like a is it a hippo or a dinosaur where Fred punches his time card
at when he's leaving?
I forget.
I think in the movie it's a hippo.
Yeah.
Chonk.
And it's like they're all like they're all self-aware and they can talk,
but they're like just my job is to buy time cards.
Eat garbage.
And eat garbage.
Which to be fair, what the cavemen are eating at that time is probably close to garbage.
Yeah, that's true.
So it's probably OK.
It's not like highly concentrated sugars or anything.
It's probably stuff from the land at the very least.
And once again, like with the paradox of Goofy and Pluto, where Goofy is their friend and
speaks, but Pluto also a dog is that they own.
It's similar where Dino can't speak.
So he's like a dog.
However, probably has a better situation because he doesn't have to work.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, as opposed to Fred's bulldozer, he operates that is a brontosaurus.
But his car is just a car.
His car.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, they have to run.
That's where they get a taste of their own medicine and have to make it function themselves.
If you were a dinosaur who could speak and move things and build objects,
why wouldn't you just build a better big world for dinosaurs to live in?
Yeah.
Keep humans out.
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense.
Also, it doesn't make sense why their car is into dinosaur.
Yeah, that's true.
Because like a bus is an elephant, probably.
I think I think there's a bus elephant in this ride.
Can we agree the settings of the Jetsons and Scooby-Doo do not have the level of detail
that bedrock does like bedrock?
I feel like a living, breathing place.
The Jetsons living situation interesting.
Yeah.
But I don't remember.
I always remember they always had lots of gadgets that would serve their needs.
But George was always fucking up.
He would try to do a treadmill and it would go too fast and he would eat shit.
Yeah.
He's like any of our parents dealing with tech.
Except Rosie.
Rosie was good at her job.
Rosie is tech.
She is tech, but she's also an employee, technically.
That is true.
And kind of one of the family like Alice.
Rosie is Alice for sure.
Yeah.
It's a very similar dynamic.
And she's kind of like the to go in further back the character Hazel.
Sort of like a maid with attitude.
She almost she kind of sounds like Hazel.
They were just stealing from each other.
This is what we did in the old days.
We stole from each other.
Yeah.
But you get up.
The ride ends in space rock.
They were in the space rock.
I mean, the Scooby Doo segment is fun.
There's not as like I said, not as much of a living breathing world like bedrock.
And also it's just Scooby and Shaggy.
Yeah.
None of the other.
No Fred, Velma or Daphne.
Yeah.
Disappointment if you like eye candy.
Or Scrappy Doo.
Yeah.
Sadly.
And no great Gazoo.
No great.
Certainly no great.
Character from the Flintstones.
Yeah.
Also, all alternate people who could have been mad like Dick Dastardly that
that's maybe a plus up.
Yeah.
All of the left out characters and all of the fan disliked characters all team up together
and kidnap a different child.
That's fantastic world.
What was Dick Dastardly's end game abducting that child?
Holding him hostage to be the star of the next project.
Until he got a contract?
Until he got like a sag contract?
Yeah. He was holding out for sag minimum.
Yeah.
Once like $920.
Yeah, sure.
It is crazy.
Gazoo would have been perfect for this ride because he can make any he's like Q on Star
Trek. He can like make anything happen.
So like you could really like because this is as fine as this ride is.
It's pretty by the numbers.
Maybe it's because we've sort of seen versions better now after 25 years.
That's maybe true.
Yeah.
Like at the time it might have been all cool.
We're now in this land and we're in this.
But like it's very like, OK, now we're in a very sort of boring version of bedrock.
And OK, now we're here and there's nothing like no surprises, no fun.
Story wise, yeah, you go through like this haunted house and graveyard and Scooby and
Shag. You're there and then you get transported to the future somehow or to space, whatever it is.
And because the whole time, the zoo quippin and transportin you to places and like changing
you into different things.
The real hero of this ride, though, is Rosie.
Rosie has an extendable arm and she plucks Dick Dasterly and Muntley out of the car.
Oh, yeah.
And that lets George catch Elroy and then she puts him back in the car.
And then they plow into an amusement park ride vehicle and that are surrounded by police.
Boy, we got to just synopsize the basics of the ride more often because, man, what a story.
And Dick Dasterly ends up with a wig on his head.
Boy, what a rough run for him.
Yeah.
He looks silly at the end.
Looks so silly with that wig.
The Jetson scene, I think visually is very like there's a lot of moving pieces in the
Jetson scene.
Yeah. And that future amusement park is cool, though.
Is that a thing from the Jetsons?
I don't know.
Or do they have to kind of manufacture a new place?
They would go to anything in like it's a gym, but the future it's a restaurant, but the future.
So I'm sure there was like the state fair, but the future.
Judy went to an amusement park with Jet Screamer.
Like that has to have happened in that episode.
I don't know.
I'll call my mother.
Judy was constantly going on dates.
That's fine.
What's wrong with that?
Jet Screamer one day, Apollo Blue another.
You sound like her dad or something.
Well, I just when is she getting her schoolwork done?
She's fine.
She's got straight A's.
I thought Elroy was the smart one.
Who said Judy wasn't?
Judy was smart, too.
I mean, I guess they're both.
I mean, they.
She's like, hey, let's hope they got Jane's jeans and not too many of George.
She was George.
George had a good heart.
It wasn't the brightest one.
Yeah, that's true.
Always making Spacely, Mr. Spacely mad.
Well, Spacely was he was a tyrant.
Yeah, that's true.
He was.
Yeah, he was like, uh, uh, the Elon Musk or Bezos or like a Howard Schultz kind of dumbass.
Howard Schultz.
Sure.
Michael Bloomberg.
Spacely was there ever a Spacely for president?
Hmm.
That would have been a good movie.
Oh, I wonder.
Yeah.
And like a predictive like that.
Would like this move, this thing that was going around of this old TV show that predicted
Trump and the character's name was Trump and he swindled a town.
Like if there was a Spacely episode that predicted everything beat by beat.
I'm just going to Google Mr. Spacely for president.
What is that called?
There's a dark Andy Griffith movie.
Oh, yeah, it's like that, too.
Face in the Crowd.
Is that right?
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
Yeah, yeah, I've seen that.
Did you do?
I didn't know this.
Do you know Mr. Spacely's full name?
No, I don't.
Cosmo G. Spacely.
Oh, I feel like I did.
Now I'm mad.
Yeah, Cosmo.
Of course.
God damn it.
And then the other character was Mr. Cogswell, who owned the other company,
who I think was nicer.
Remember this guy?
There's a tiny graphic for you guys to look at.
I do remember Cogswell.
He was not.
Yeah, he was always smiling.
Yeah, he was not like Mr. Spacely.
Spacely and Slater, like the same guys.
Yes, the 100% the same guy.
Yeah, Mr. Slater was Fred's boss.
What an interesting construct that was.
And it is still in entertainment where it's like, well, if you work in this industry,
there's your boss, and then there's the rival company.
Like there was always a Pepsi Coke situation.
This implied that anyone works for a company or has the luxury of working for a company
and staying there for more than nine months.
We're recording this amidst massive layoffs.
Massive media layoffs.
You wish any of these BuzzFeeds had just the clean, simple, there's a mean man like Slate.
But hey, I've been here for 25 years.
Not bad work if you can get it.
Yeah, yeah.
Boy, everybody should be jealous of Fred.
Fred and George.
Good, honest living.
It's a living.
That's what's going to happen to our generation.
We're all going to have to start working as record players for richer people.
We're going to have to bite records with our teeth.
Someone's going to put garbage in my mouth for $8 an hour.
You're going to be working for Howard Schultz.
My mouth full of Howard Schultz's garbage.
I'm going to be drawn in and out of being for a rich man's amusement.
That sounds fun.
Yeah, you got a good job.
No, because I start to learn pain in seven months and then I'm erased.
And you have to kill the other one.
And then I come back.
That's right.
So will you really be you because you're a copy of a copy of a copy of you.
And Mike, when you you'll eat garbage and say it's a living,
but it won't be as fun as in the cartoon, like you'll try to say it.
It's just cough blood because a tin can scrapes up your throat.
It's not as fun as in the cartoon.
Can I say a thing?
I'd like to the ending in this ride when like Yogi lands on like a big cushion that says the end,
he seems like visibly winded.
I'm happy for him.
He can get comfy.
Thanks for joining me here.
Like he's just like so he's kind of out of it.
Like it's like, oh, I like that.
It's this took this did a number on it.
He's going to go rest.
Are you upset that it's a thread left hanging that you don't know whether or not he got the sandwich?
Well, I'm just happy he's freed from the the tyrant, Ranger Smith, like Ranger Smith.
Was his space like kind of kind of the same dynamic because he was always trying
to chase him out of the Jellystone National Park.
Yeah, I mean, I guess Yogi wasn't supposed to be eating those pick a neck baskets.
Right.
No, he was that Ranger was just like a joyless man.
If they were I don't I didn't see the new Yogi bear, which is a couple of years old.
Did anyone see that?
The movie?
Yeah.
Oh, it's good.
The voices of Dan Aykroyd and Justin Timberlake.
Yes.
It's so good.
It's really good.
I'm going to be sick, man.
Could it be that he still steal picnic baskets?
Because I feel like that would be a modern studio note of like,
he can't steal the baskets because that makes Yogi a thief,
but he could steal the baskets and give to the poor or if you have to root for.
Why are we rooting for Yogi?
He's that it's theft.
What he's committing is theft.
Yogi is committing theft.
The Ranger is Ed, right?
Isn't the guy who played Ed?
He's the character Ed.
Yes, from the show.
From the show Ed.
And then of course, noted psychopath TJ Miller.
Oh, yeah.
This podcast goes there.
Why not?
I don't know that that is so big of a swig.
No, I don't.
Yeah.
Look, he might admit to such himself.
Sure.
Yeah.
And while the studio, the note that they did have to take about the picnic baskets
is that they had to contain crystal head vodka.
Well, sure.
Did he sound like Dan Aykroyd?
Was that guy Milky Bear?
He kind of did a boo boo boo.
He did do a voice.
He sort of did.
Do you think he and Murray ever get together and go,
man, we were just a couple of dreamers once just
running around the streets of New York, high as shit.
And now I'm Yogi and you're Garfield.
Can you believe it?
We really made it.
I mean, those characters have brought joy to generations of people.
So I hope they're respectful to those intellectual properties.
And hope they are aware.
And if they get together, then maybe they're having this whistle moment
and then they bump into Amy Poehler, who is, of course,
a Chippette.
One of the Chippettes.
Yeah, I couldn't come up with it.
Is she Brittany?
Is she Althea?
What are their names?
I'm falling out of my cartoon facts.
I can't remember.
I think as a kid, I was like, this is preposterous.
There are the Chipmunks and the Chippettes.
You weren't into the Chippettes?
I know I liked the Chippettes, just the conceit bothered me as a kid.
I was like, so there's three perfect female doppelganger.
This is were it only that simple.
Were it only that simple?
Yeah.
Jeanette, Brittany and Eleanor.
OK, I like them as characters, but thinking I like the Chipmunks and the Chippettes.
And Dave had a lot on his hands raising three Chipmunk boys with no other as a single parent.
Did we ever meet like the Chipettes version of Dave?
Did they have like a female Dave or were they part of Dave?
I don't know.
Was she in love with Dave?
Well, no one was in love with Dave.
That was probably the problem.
He's in love with his work.
Who was sadder, Dave or John?
John Arbuckle.
I think Dave's more aware of being sad, which is sad in its own right, but John is not self-aware.
He doesn't realize what a cruddy life he has, but also he gets like a girlfriend, right?
Yeah, Dave's got a girlfriend.
He's got a steady thing going on.
John or Dave?
Not John.
I think John had flames on and off.
Yeah, John's got it.
John's got curls.
Dave had to manage those Chipmunks' career too, and that's another headache.
Yeah, and that's the scene I'd like to see in the movie is like,
do you have any idea the sacrifice I've made for you?
I've given up everything.
I haven't had sex in 20 years.
Every day, contracts, booking stadiums,
getting the rights to cover songs for you to sing because you don't ever write original songs.
Driving all night to get to state fairs.
Chef or owning dates with your exact equivalents.
And then there's a scene with the Chipmunks are in the room with,
and I can't think of the Mike Myers character from the Ray Foster.
Ray Foster.
A bunch of Chipmunks in a hit band.
Teenagers will never bang their heads to a bunch of Chipmunks.
Christmas time is here is how many minutes long?
It's a musical opera.
I couldn't go as high as the Chipmunks.
Well, we ended up on another the wrong cartoon characters.
We ended up with the wrong.
And we also look, there's probably a lot more we could say,
but I'll be damned if this is the longest episode of I guess.
Or that doesn't make any sense.
We're about two hours.
Boy, well, I guess now's the time any.
Well, I boy, I gotta say, guys, I had a fun time.
I had a fun time.
I sure did.
Did I have a good time?
Yes, I sure did.
Well, two things I want to say.
Well, one, in terms of a plus up, a plus up for a different ride.
I think they should have done the Simpsons like this.
It should have been CGI Springfield and 2D Simpsons.
Yes.
I think that would have been very interesting to see with 2007, 2008 era technology.
Great.
I think it's a little weird that there's I get why they did it,
but isn't it surprising the first time you went on it
when you get up to the top of that hill and like, whoa, what?
Yeah, I think.
I think CGI.
I think I don't remember if I thought that it looks like the
Treehouse of Horror episode where their computer or comers, at least computer animated.
All right.
Yeah.
So I thought about that, but then it's like, yeah, seeing them that way the whole time.
I get that they're thinking like, oh, three dimensions makes you feel more like you're in it,
but it doesn't really.
It doesn't.
As long as the background kind of has some dimension to it, I feel like.
Here's my other thing that makes Fantastic World of Hanna-Barbera stand out from
all other theme park rides.
When this ride closed, Paramount Parks got the license to run it in their parks.
Oh, right.
So this showed up in other parks.
Canada's Wonderland.
Canada's Wonderland and the other Paramount Parks.
And then when that license expired, it was replaced with SpongeBob SquarePants 4D.
The film also showed at Kentucky Kingdom with its original name, the park at Moa
under the name Yogi's Big Rescue.
And for one.
What a diss to the other characters.
Yeah.
Make it Yogi's thing.
And then it showed up Pigeon Forge, Tennessee, baby.
Dollywood under the name Yogi's Wild Ride.
Hey.
2007.
That's a late arrival.
For a while.
Wow.
2009 was when the Paramount Parks kind of got stripped of all the Paramount and other
licensed stuff.
Huh.
Universal's trash is Dollywood's treasure.
Treasure.
Hey.
All I would say is I want to underline how much I love the Great Gazoo and I want him
in more media.
Get him in there.
OK.
My plus up is just that you get to the next land or you get to the next room.
You get into the vehicle and the screen comes on and it's Hannah and Barbara again.
And they say, just kidding.
You're just going to watch us eat our lunch.
And then they're silent for a minute and a half.
And then finally like, boy, this horseradish tastes good.
It sure does.
We've been eating horseradish since 1962.
Horseradish and sardines on rye.
Is there a better lunch?
I ain't found it yet.
They, I sure ain't.
And then I'll make you happy, Mike, and the Great Gazoo can show up.
All right.
Thank you.
And they're like, no, hey, can't you see we're eating?
We sure are.
And then he goes away.
Oh, sorry.
Keep eating your slop, dumb-dumbs.
All right.
You survived Podcast the Ride.
That was a blast.
Thanks for joining us on this fantastic episode.
And there's a whole new world of fantastic content over on the second gate,
patreon.com slash podcast, the ride and check us out on Instagram, Twitter, Facebook.
Hey, Reddit.
We got the somebody set up the Reddit for us.
Yeah, reddit.com slash slash r slash podcast, the ride.
And our Reddit is still nice and it's fun.
I think I think no one's being a monster on there yet.
No division.
Facebook group too.
Also very nice.
I would say let's do this fun thing.
We were talking about this.
Rate and review us on the Apple Podcasts, but let's do a little fun thing.
Once you obviously give us five stars because that's the quality of this.
If you were making a character, what kind of neck wear would you put on them
to make it easier on the animators?
Make the old man draw you better.
Would it be a scarf?
Would it be a stethoscope?
Maybe it's a doctor character of some kind.
You tell us in the Apple Podcasts in the comments section.
So say five stars.
Great podcast.
I would add a dickie like Big Bird wears when he's dressed up.
Five stars.
Oh, yeah.
Info always accurate.
They remember their cartoon character names perfectly.
And I'm a boa man.
And if we didn't touch on any Hanna Barbera characters, obscure ones or popular ones
that are your favorites, I'm going to say this tweet them at us because I am so cute.
Now I'm worried I'm going to spend the next seven days just going down Hanna Barbera
wormholes.
And I would like some assistance of finding oddball Hanna Barbera.
I am worried there's a big one that we missed, but we'll find it.
We'll talk about it later.
Maybe we haven't done one lost and found episode.
Maybe we'll cover some of your favorites.
There's a lot more Hanna Barbera theme park stuff.
Like once just crawling around, like you'd find little things.
And I don't know if I were to go down that rabbit hole, how much there is, but just
the Flintstone thing that closed like in the last couple days is this weird roadside attraction
thing that was around for 50 years.
And there's got to be something in there.
Like we'll touch up on this.
Probably rats and raccoons in there.
That's all that'll be there soon enough.
They love to eat that trash.
It is a living for them.
It's a pleasure.
It sure is.
Thanks for listening, folks.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production, executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.