Hello, ForeverDog listeners. Before we get to today's episode, we have to tell you about a new
must-listen podcast from ForeverDog called the American Arts and Culture Review. Since they were
little kids, host Whitmer Thomas and Clay Tatum have shared one dream in common, to host an NPR
style podcast reviewing the best in film, television, art, fashion, and jazz music. And now,
at long last, with the help of a Casio keyboard and a one-man studio audience,
Whit and Clay have finally achieved their goal. Sort of. The American Arts and Culture Review is
like NPR for the end of the world, a twisted and surreal journey through the week's most important
works of art. If you're a fan of Hollywood Handbook, the podcast for laundry, or a woman's smile,
you'll love the American Arts and Culture Review. Find it wherever you listen to podcasts. New
episodes every Thursday. ForeverDog.
Warning. The following podcast may contain a robot with a musket, harrowing info about Scott's
childhood optometrist's office, and hopefully not an interruption from that devious star of many
GIFs, Constantine. Griffin Newman discusses foolishness we would like to see as we talk
Muppet Vision 3D on Podcast the Ride.
Hey, welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast about theme parks hosted by three guys who refer to getting laid as capturing the all spark.
I'm Scott, you're joined by Jason Sheridan and Mike Carlson.
I mean, we're always talking about getting laid for one thing.
That's for sure.
I mean, obviously we'd love to use that phrase in and of itself, but then.
Yeah, well, I refer to myself during intercourse as Evac.
So yeah, of course I'm going to want the all spark.
I want to get the all spark if you know what I mean.
It makes all sense.
Yeah, Mike Carlson here.
Life's all about getting that all spark.
Anyway, and today we are really happy to have, I think, a pretty stellar guest and topic combo.
Let's introduce the guest part of that equation, you know, from the tick and from his podcast,
Blank Check, it's Griffin Newman.
Hello everybody.
Hey.
Thanks so much for being a requested guest.
Yeah, truly.
When we've thrown out, who would you like to hear and who's somebody in podcast world
you think might be into this stuff?
Your name has come up with a lot of likes.
I dropped the line to you like many months ago.
Yeah.
Just being like, I would love to do this whenever I'm in town next.
But I felt like I was getting a lot of requests from people to go on this.
Oh, no kidding.
And I was like, I don't know what the interest is on their end,
but I certainly am going to try.
Well, thanks for making a point because you're out here for a little bit from the East Coast.
Yeah, thanks for making a point.
Which was coupled into a Disneyland trip.
So I'm like fresh off of a trip in the parks, off the takes, hot piping, hot takes.
What a change.
How many people are forced to take a trip without having like an after show
to go over their opinions on the trip?
And I don't like doing anything without an after show.
I think if Chris Hardwick has taught me anything,
I model most things in life off of Chris Hardwick.
Yes, we all should.
Especially when it comes to personal life.
We're all soldiers in the Hardwick's army.
When it comes to capturing the AllSpark, you need advice from Chris Hardwick.
Yeah, yeah.
It feels like it's a good outlet because I was just like loading up on things.
And even like I got a walk off.
Oh, that's right.
I was so excited where I was like, I have a place where I can say this and it will mean something.
Yeah, we can get an oh, yes, explain your walk off.
Got a walk off on Astro Blasters.
Wow, that's interesting.
It was a trip for two days.
It was raining a lot.
OK.
So there was a lot of erratic behavior on a lot of the rides.
And especially like the rides that are more outdoor kept on shutting down
because I was constantly checking the app, trying to see the lines on things.
So many things were temporarily closed.
Dean gets to do Radiator Springs Racers.
Oh, no.
Because it would be like closed during the rain and would start up again.
And there'd be like a three hour wait.
Right.
I'm going to wait for it to die down and then it would start raining again.
And it never.
OK.
And a lot of like little because I ended up there.
Were you there yesterday, too?
I was there.
No, two days ago.
OK.
I was there Tuesday, Wednesday.
I did a little like rain trip with so crowds would be low, which was great.
I had not done that.
That's a boy.
That's a tip.
If you can endure rain because it's it wasn't that bad.
It's like it's not super windy or super cold.
So it ended up being great.
I noticed a lot of the anything that's outdoor and that whips you around like Gadgets
Go coaster or the goofy Sky School.
So you missed you missed that kind of stuff.
But those are those are acceptable.
All of those I thought were skippable.
Radiator Springs I had not done before.
Right.
So I was kind of looking forward to and I was sort of trying to couch it with my girlfriend
because I was like I complained enough about the Cars franchise to her.
She's had to speak and listen to me speak too often about how much I don't think cars is great.
Not even that I hate it, but I'm like it's just so marginal.
Divisive opinion.
Exactly.
That I just think it was like I couldn't be like and we really have to go on the Cars ride.
But I kept on being like, you know, people say it's pretty good.
So I guess we should go on it just for the sake of like thrownness.
Oh, you had to like easy you were like prepared for a hypocrisy argument or something.
If you were too enthusiastic.
Right.
Exactly.
So I was just like waiting for the wait to be short enough and that that never happened.
But Astro Blaster seemed like one that wouldn't be affected by the weather.
We go on it.
We're halfway through and then it just stops abruptly.
Wow.
And then they announced like please wait for employees to come for cast members to come
aid you and the lights went up and we were there for probably 12 or 15 minutes.
Did you rack up points while you were waiting?
No, they wouldn't let you because that was my first thing.
Really?
I could be hitting the charts right now.
Yeah, because then you get the photo or at the end at least.
Right.
At least I want to go off, you know, 9999 or whatever.
But no, it was like 15 minutes where all the lights were on.
It was crazy when all the lights were on how much it just looks like like a local carnival
spook house or something.
There's so much like, you know, that's not like a super complex ride in terms of the
actual structures itself.
Feels like most of the effort was put into like the game system.
So then when the lights go up here like this is just like a bunch of plywood cutouts
and we stopped right in the room right after Zerg.
So I was like we stopped in the Zerg room.
I'd be like really studying Zerg and I'd have something to look at.
Probably one of the more impressive components of it in a sort of a chintzy ride.
Otherwise, it's just a bunch of like non-moving cutouts and then they had to like it felt
like a like a school sort of fire drill where they waited and they let everyone out one by one.
They made us all line up against the wall and they had to march us out single file line.
And they were like everyone stay please.
And one guy and his significant other was trying to get a photo with all the robots.
So he kept on moving around in the line back and forth to be like, excuse me, I just need
I'm all about these robots and was taking photos of him with the cutouts.
Which aren't great photos.
Right.
The lighting must be terrible.
And the lighting is terrible.
And you're just like, oh weird, those are like vents.
Those are like lighting grids.
Like all the things that are hidden by the black lighting.
It's just kind of a nondescript warehouse now.
Right.
And also if you never like we're all so we're all busy when we're going on that ride.
If you like stop if you weren't shooting and you just stopped.
I'm just going to watch this time.
You'd be like this is the lamest ride ever made.
Because if you go like between the game ones it's like I think Men in Black is probably
more interesting as a ride as a space.
Certainly Toy Story Mania is doing a different thing.
But is more visually engaging.
Astro Blaster's really like got the advantage of being the first like shoot them up kind of one.
Yeah.
So it didn't have to try as hard.
Exactly.
Right.
I think the novelty was pushing them.
Sure.
Yeah.
Well it sounds like this walk off is not like a this is not a thrilling one.
It was a boring one.
Sort of functional.
Because I was like they might let us through like a weird back area.
All right.
An employee break room.
And instead they just marched us through the ride back through the main entrance.
It's something.
But when you said walk off my mind raced with all the possibilities.
I started like really like shaking with excitement.
Yeah.
We got one free fast pass.
Okay.
They like gave us a fast pass that we could use on anything else.
But not on Radiator Springs.
No because that's what we tried to do.
We were like tomorrow we'll go to California Adventure and we'll use it on either radiator
springs or guardians of the galaxy.
And they were like limited to the park.
Yeah.
To go back to Disneyland.
Oh bummer.
And Disneyland with rain was pretty fine and nothing had a crazy long wait.
California Adventure has so few big ticket things that especially when one or two of
them are shut down because of the rain if a credit coaster and like radiator springs
are down then everything else goes so up.
On the wait time.
Yeah we did not have as much luck nearly as much as is in main Disneyland.
Yeah Disneyland really like the rain felt like a life hack.
Like we had really figured something out and I was like I can't even imagine how
much it's going to help us at California Adventure and it didn't.
Yeah.
And we ended up there's a big stretch of just like I split a corndog with my friend
in terrible terrible storm.
Just like that was the moment.
Hold on.
I'm sorry I'm describing it as a bad start.
How does that work?
Are you just passing it back and forth and bites?
Are you dissecting it down the middle?
Hmm.
That'd be one way of doing it.
By length or by width?
Where were you splitting those?
Wait now I'm confused which is just down.
No no no like kind of at the at the stick.
So one one of us took the sticked half and the other the other one took the non sticked half.
Okay.
Oh so you weren't sharing it like lovers just handing it back and forth.
No no no.
Or lady in the champ style if you took it off the stick and each started on one end.
Yes.
Without the stick that's but with the stick somebody is choking.
Sure sure.
Somebody's smaller than stick.
No yeah we both agreed we only each wanted half of a corndog.
We made it work but it was a weird sad like going to a restaurant that was barely open
and getting hard silverware and then just leaving it out on a rainy trash can.
Did you mobile order to get it or did you wait?
We waited in a lack of weight.
Okay.
Yes.
Got it.
Yeah so it wouldn't have impacted us either way I suppose but I'll I'll you'll get me on this
mobile ordering train.
I will you mobile order at Starbucks.
I've seen you do it.
I did it and then I heard you murmuring to Jason behind oh well now.
Yeah.
I'm like see he likes mobile ordering.
Once again I'm not against doing it.
I was against doing it in the one scenario where we were 10 feet away from the actual place.
I was just didn't want to like figure I was walking.
I didn't want to.
No I know I just like I like the early adopt I like to be an early adopter as you know.
Yeah.
I like to it's fun for me.
Do you do you like mobile stuff did you do any of that at Disney?
I just did it to check the the lines and everything.
You didn't do MaxPass?
We didn't which I feel like maybe might have held California Adventure it felt like it really
would have been worth it.
There may be but not main Disneyland.
But Disneyland we had a pretty good run of it.
The mobile ordering thing I was a little scared to do.
I mean it also is that thing sorry.
That's okay.
Where it's like it never felt like ordering by mobile would have saved me time.
This was my argument in the one case that I've been scolded for many times over.
We're 10 feet away from the restaurant.
Yeah.
We ended up tied we tied we literally tied.
We tied with food but then I said of course in the most smug way possible
I didn't have to wait in line though.
Here's where I saw oh this is how this could be an advantage.
Let's say the Dole Whip Stand line is really long.
Sure.
And you go okay cool I'm going to place a mobile order while I'm in Enchanted Tiki room.
Yes.
And when I come out it's just there waiting for me.
Certainly.
I save time but otherwise it was just like there's one person or no people there.
Sure yeah.
I don't know if I'm going to time out correctly getting to the place maybe it'll be cold by the
time I get there.
True.
If I'm standing six feet away then it's just like me wrestling with the wi-fi.
You hear that argument for sanity.
He's saying one person in line which I would say yes I would probably wait in the line if
there was one person in line.
You say there's a hot ticket item.
I'm just saying.
Sure.
And I'm just saying it's fun I'm just saying I like it and it's fun.
Sometimes too you want to see the sample item like if you don't know what it's like oh what
what does that look like.
Yes that's true.
They have like those weird they're like rubber versions of the food sometimes.
Or sometimes they just prepare one and leave it out for eight hours.
Well I'll tell you my biggest complaint I had with the food thing is I get the app.
I'm seeing oh online you can order in advance to the place of reservation whatever.
My girlfriend the whole trip was Jones in for cheese fries and I was like there has
to be a place here where you can get cheese fries but they don't let you search by item.
Oh yeah I know.
Which I think would be very valuable if you could search because so many of the little stands are
like specialized to one or two things.
Yeah that's a good idea.
And you're like I want a hot dog but like golden horseshoe might not have it.
Let me search for that.
Then I would have a hundred percent did it and I was just there going like restaurant by restaurant
clicking on the menu.
Yeah.
Would this and they seem to have chili cheese fries and I guess I could probably ask for that.
But it's unclear if you see that it's a burger place or a chicken finger place that still doesn't
clue you in.
Yes.
That still doesn't tell you is this the kind of place that would have cheese fries.
Right.
Did you find cheese fries?
We didn't and that's why I come to you guys and ask you can you think off the top of your head
is there a place with cheese fries on the menu?
As soon as you said cheese fries my mind started racing and I said huh I don't think.
It seems so obvious and I was like there are enough like burger spots and hot dog spots and
I looked at some and it was like she was like look I don't know if this exists.
Ideal.
I would love cheese waffle fries and the one in California venture the bear.
What's the bear restaurant there or it's the other one that's like the aviation themed
restaurant.
Oh smoke jumpers.
Right.
So like they have waffle fries and then they had chili cheese fries but they were regular
fries.
I think you could have asked.
It would have had to be an ask.
Yeah.
And that always feels like a little like you know I don't know if like what do you think it is an
okay thing to like go up to the stand at Disneyland and be like hey like off the menu is this like.
Yeah they do like they have gone into a little like secret menu items every now and then and
they are willing to customize especially because there's so many allergen worries nowadays.
So we're vegetarian or vegans.
There are secret menu.
There are mozzarella sticks secretly at stage door cafe right next to the golden horseshoe.
But that's not on the menu.
So there are a list of a few secret menu items not cheese fries I don't think at least I've
seen.
So I do think it's possible you could have gotten it at a different.
I think you could have ordered the chili cheese fries and asked for it without the chili.
Yes.
The question was could we do like the double ninja move of being like I see you have regular
chili cheese fries and plain waffle fries.
Can we get your cheese on waffle fries.
But the game that we took was at that point we pretty much done everything in California
adventure.
We wanted to try to do another thing or two at Disneyland proper.
It was our last night.
We were going to drive back to L.A.
That night and she was like let's abandon ship.
Let's go to Disneyland.
I don't want to be around her anymore.
Radio Springs is like too long.
And I was like I believe I can find us cheese fries at Disneyland and went to stage door
and it was like the same thing where it was like not there.
And I kept on going to places where I thought like this might have it looking for similar
menu items.
I think the menus are more flexible than we realize because if you look like a lot of things are
tricked like kind of tricks like they're tricking you into a value meal but you can get everything
on a card.
It just doesn't say that on the menu.
Sure.
We do a lot of hack.
You might have taught that I didn't have to have apple slices.
There was a lot of that.
There was a lot of like oh this place has burger and fries but it doesn't have fries
as a side.
Right.
But I bet the side is a la carte.
It's not on the menu.
Yeah.
I think there's a lot of tricks to make you try to spend three or four dollars more.
And if you just ask I think I will try next time.
I will.
A la carte fries they would probably charge you a buck or two to add cheese to that.
But I'm sure you could do it.
Let's try.
Let's figure it out.
You guys having the hometown advantage you're more confident in doing things like that.
And I was like this is not my place.
I don't want to overstep.
I'm a visitor.
You were especially I mean you were you were not just a guest of the parks you were
staying on site.
So they want to keep you happy for your vacation experience.
I don't want to order the incorrect thing and then when I walk away they immediately
call up Disneyland Hotel and go like this guy's a problem.
Red alert.
Evict this man.
On watch.
I think you'd have to do a lot.
I do overreach you in operating on John Gotti rules.
This was a great sign of respect that you tweeted at me and asked what is the best ice
cream option at California Adventure.
We kind of marginally fucked it up.
No I think you did all right.
Like you ordered because I said ice cream Gotti over here.
Oh I don't want that Nick.
Yeah I don't know.
Claire Bell let me do some Claire Bell's greatest ice cream in the world.
All of the ice cream locations.
Claire Bell's, Gierdelli's, Gibson Girl.
I said either a sundae from Gierdelli or the ice cream bars that you can customize.
And you guys got a Sunday Sunday.
I'm sure that's good.
Because they use the frozen banana chocolate bananas as ears.
You get that weird little sculptural sink that also looks like the pants of either Mickey
or me.
Mashed up the concept of the kitchen like everything in the kitchen sink with Mickey's
pants.
Yeah or Minnie's skirt.
Yeah.
You took the pants home right?
Oh.
Oh Chris.
So you could have at least brought them here.
I know.
Jason would love to eat his ice cream out of pants every night.
We were like looking we were like this is such a fun thing.
I could put this in my bathroom.
A little soap dish.
What if this was your like jewelry like all the applications.
So then I went and I was like would you mind washing this out so we could
take it home.
And the woman said we are not allowed to wash them but you can bring it to the bathroom
and wash it yourself.
And the closest bathroom was a little bit of a walk.
So I was like walking with this thing that was covered with like chocolate syrup and
residue like holding it out like this.
Uh huh.
Well that's weird.
Sometimes they will there will be a disposable like bowl or container within that.
So you just throw that out and you are left.
They were not doing that.
And I also feel like a lot of restaurants because I'm a big guy where like if
for five extra dollars I can get the collectible glass I will get the collectible glass.
And I feel like a lot of these places like Rainforest Cafe or whatever they will say
I'm going to when you're ready to go home give you a new one.
I'll give you a clean one.
Yes.
You paid for the glass I'm not going to make you take home this one that's got sprite lining
on the inside.
Although Mike brought home a bubble gum shrimp glass that was covered in sprite lining and
crystal sugar.
And you still haven't washed it to this day.
I think it's been washed.
That's when you were in the car because I drove you back here and you were licking the glass
in the car before we realized it was non-alcoholic.
And that's the one way you washed it.
Well I sort of realized it but I didn't want to say until we were on the show.
I sort of realized it when I then double checked when we were here.
We were like fairly early in our day.
I went through the trouble of carrying it through foot traffic to get to the bathroom
to wash it out which probably took a full five minutes.
Like I was taking paper towels.
The one at the entrance or the one over by the what's the
further down the street I guess.
Got in Hollywood area.
Yes.
Oh it's by the what's the not mural but it was near the fake movie posters.
Right.
It was near what we call the baby rave which that Disney Junior party there the bathrooms near
there.
Love that name.
So I was like standing there like wiping like I looked like a dad who was like trying to
deal with a dirty diaper and I had like.
You thought there was an imaginary baby in the pants.
I looked really like irritated.
I was trying to get like the syrup out of the cracks and I came out and I was like I
did it and then we walked for another minute and I was like I don't want to carry this
around.
We have another six hours.
I don't want to carry this around.
Becoming abundantly clear why people suggest that you come on this podcast.
We're on the same level.
I was saying to them before you got here that I had recently listened to your speed racer
episode as a movie I'm very fond of.
Masterpiece.
Yeah and I was I looked this up today because so the episode length on your show is an hour
and 58 minutes.
The movie itself is two fifteen so just seventeen minutes shy of the runtime of the movie.
We now unfortunately have gotten to the point where most episodes are longer than the movie.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah we're we're well past that.
Yeah which is will be no problem with this thing because the movie is very short.
Yeah of course.
We've already surpassed it but this is a very brisk podcast.
It's extremely yeah.
Very lots running.
I asked if we could push this up and you were like well you know if it's a concern we could
always keep it tight and it's like I'm not going on podcast the ride to do a sixty two
minute episode.
If I'm coming here I'm coming here to play.
Like we're doing full fledged.
I don't want to be in any sort of rush.
Yeah you know the day also tell I know you got to get out of your tongue but you steer
the ship if you need to leave but because obviously we and it's a good topic too.
I brought my luggage here and I'm leaving for the airport from this apartment tomorrow
morning.
I'm here to record.
Oh okay.
All right.
What was the thing I was going to say about carrying around the thing?
Oh well you I mean just you saying it's clear why why people wanted you to be on this podcast.
My my two friends Ben and David who I do the podcast with I invoke like theme park stuff
a lot and they just don't fucking get it.
Yeah.
And I was trying to convince them because we've covered avatar and we're similarly kind
of like some order you might like into like the weird world building of avatar that no
one actually loves.
Right.
Unless you get the sort of Stockholm syndrome that folks like you and I are are susceptible
to like your ironic investigation into the marginalia makes you just love it.
Yeah.
Which is I've answered this question before a friend of ours was like I've listened to
a lot of this podcast.
Do they like avatar or not?
And I was like I don't know.
I don't think we're clear anymore.
Well wait have I gone on the record about this?
I have never seen avatar from start to finish.
I don't know if you've ever seen it.
That's not very mighty of you.
No it's not.
You must Sivako rise to the challenge.
I think that's what that means or it means I see you I can't remember.
It's on demand a lot.
It's on I see it as an option on planes sometimes.
Like if I'm watching movies on my iPad on like American Airlines and I'm like this would
be very funny to see avatar for the first time.
Yeah.
On my like seven year old iPad screen.
It does feel like every airline was like whatever they're asking for it's worth the
money to get a 10 year licensing deal for avatar on every flight.
Yes.
People are not going to stop rewatching this thing because it is no matter what airline
technology they have avatar is always an option.
Avatar and when I flew for Christmas all the mission impossibles and I'm like well I'm
not opening the book I brought to read on the plane.
Yeah but I well what do you where do you land?
If you had to chart the avatar appreciation.
I mean I like I think I love it but I also don't know that I would stand here and argue
that it's great but I also fight people who say that it's bad.
Like I feel like sometimes now people are like you know world's biggest avatar fan like
pointing over to me and I'm like because I think it's like a pretty respectable like seven.
You know.
That makes you a go to the mat die hard.
Right.
Just because nobody is that.
Right I'll admit like I don't know like the Navi phrases like you do.
There are other things I've gone deeper into but I do feel this deep appreciation for I think
just the functionality of the thing.
I think it's a very functional movie which sounds like a backhanded compliment but it's
like that's just like Karen showing you what he can do.
I never watched the movie and go like man I really want to learn about this world
but then when I went to the theme park I was like I get this like this kind of works better as
a sub land in a theme park than it does as a movie franchise.
I mean I think cars of that as that way too.
Yeah.
It's fun to walk around Radar Springs more than it is to maybe sit down and watch a cars movie.
Right and my girlfriend has not seen any of the cars movies because of my searing hot
they're okay takes but we are walking around Radar Springs and she was like this is incredible
and I was like yeah what you don't even understand is they're basing it off a very specific like
the spatial relations between the buildings is exactly what it is in the movie and she was like
I don't care about any of that this just looks nice.
Yeah.
And she just interpreted all as like this is like fun theming.
This is just a cool Disneyland idea.
Gotcha yeah yeah yeah so it's almost like we're in this weird world where the movie is just part of
the bits one building block of a general universe that's been created.
Right.
Maybe that's where Avatar has landed where like yeah do you like Avatar yeah I like the theme park
I kind of like the movie Avatar it's like not even the primary.
The theme park is good and then the promise of the next five movies are what I really like.
Yeah I mean I'm I'm in love with that I just I love how it feels like someone made this joke on
Twitter but like Cameron with the Avatar sequels was just like the principal in Breakfast Club
where he's challenging Bender to how much detention he wants
and like he announces I'm making two and three and everyone's like I don't know if we really
want to see him he's like okay four like he just kept on doubling down the more people were like
no one cares about this franchise anymore he just increased the threat.
And they're going to be giant hits and I like I you can't bet against this maniac.
You can't and everyone's going to like them when they come out five years later everyone's
going to go that sucked and 10 years after everyone's going to go it kind of rules right.
I mean like I feel like we're back in the period where everyone agrees that Titanic's the best
and I feel like there was that arc of just like well it's Titanic and then everyone's like
Titanic's stupid like why did we all fall for that and now everyone's like come back around to like
I guess it's like a modern classic. What a bizarre he makes these things that are these living
organisms that their their appreciation changes throughout time and their perception.
They have their own ecosystems. Yeah right right. Yeah he I don't know what it is what magic that man has.
Sounds from all the stories I've ever heard a maniac a crazy person. Yeah but like he always
wins. He always wins. He always. Mike's going to be coming in we're going to come in one day
in a couple years and Mike's going to be wearing like the seed bearer t-shirt right.
One of them is called the seed bearer. I mean I'd rather wear a Navi Shaman of Song shirt from the
Orlando ride because it's right specific but if the seed bearer ends up being on the ride somehow
yes I will have a lot of seed bearer merch. Some of the avatar merch from World of Pandora in
Orlando looks very much like the wildlife t-shirts that kids would sell as fundraisers in school.
Did anyone else ever encounter this? Yeah I know you talk a lot. You mean just like a shirt with like a like a
creepy panther on it or? Yeah. With like a panda or like dolphins or you'd see them at aquariums. Like a sort of dramatic oil painting of like nature.
You would bring like a thing home and show it to your parents and then they go I guess you can get
one of these and then like you'd mark down what you want and bring in like a check for $25 and it's
just some scam. It was a scholastic book club where it was like oh but they have like Rugrats bookmarks this month.
Yeah and it's just to fleece your parents out of more money. There's nothing other than that.
Or the um did you guys sell pizza kits? Pizza? What? Nope. These kits you would get up like you would
okay it was like a box you would place an order and then a month later you would have to come
and pick up or the kid you bought it from their family would have to bring this to you it was like
a box and you open it up and it had like the crust and the sauce and the cheese and the pepperoni
so you could make pizzas or garlic bread at home so but you were paying an insane yeah we would
They were big hits like yeah people would sell them. Would you just sell them to like family?
Your town's local economy ran solely on pizza kits. I don't even remember what we were fundraising for
now that I'm saying this. Did you sell them to your family or would you like be on the street corner?
My dad would take the orders to work. We'd take them to like church. We'd sell them to other people
like other families like neighbors and stuff. Was it like a branded like was like Prago making these
pizza kits or was this like a company that just sold those? This is just the pizza company their
one product is all the ingredients for pizza in one box. Because eventually because people would
in Salisbury, Pennsylvania a lot of fundraising is selling Hershey bars is selling like boxes like
the candy out here there's that candy company. Toblerone or I don't know. I feel like that was
the thing where it's like you're gonna buy a bulk box of candy bars and you sell them to raise money
for the school or whatever. Every so often someone would be like I'm sick of doing the candy fundraisers.
Let's up the ante with the pizza kits. How big and heavy were these boxes? Incredibly big.
Because each one would make three pizzas work. Right because it feels like the whole idea is like
well like one kid can very easily carry 50 Hershey bars. Yes. Right. But like you could carry what two
pizza kits at a time? Yeah they were the size of like those candy bar suitcase. Each one was the size
of one entire suitcase. You wouldn't you wouldn't go around selling those you would just have an order
and then they would come up and pick pick up your boxes of pizza kits to then deliver to your
customers. If you had to take them around from place to place? Yeah but you know when you're
like 11 or 12 you don't have a car so your parents are just delivering pizza kits.
It would be both easier and less cumbersome to deliver actual pizzas. Yeah. Oh yeah.
Tastier. Yeah. You need more money off of it. Better margins. Yeah just go to a local ranch because that's another option.
You go to like Little Caesars or Domino's or Pizza Hut. You get a bunch of hot and red. You load them up in the car.
But like you can arrange that like they can write that off on their tax and like the business and
it's like okay did everyone go go order pizza Friday night at this Domino's and we get like
5% of that night's orders or something. I just want to circle back around to the fact that we got into
this topic with you saying or you know those pizza kits you sell as a kid. Well the t-shirts. I've never heard that.
I know 10 years worth of weird childhood stories from you and I've never heard that. So here's the thing
I was testing the water the the wildlife t-shirts that people got that. Yeah. People understood that.
I was like well maybe I'll push my luck with the pizza kit. Yeah well you're just more familiar
because you have three pizza kit pizzas every week. Sure yeah. And that's good breakfast. When you go into the office in the morning
you carry all your papers in a pizza kit and not an adashake case. Yeah. Is it how big was it compared to like a White Castle Crave case?
Because a White Castle Crave case is kind of like this size. Much better margins. Much better margins.
Rankings snack briefcases. What do you think the size was?
Okay like you know when you buy a poker kit like you buy the suitcase with the chips and cards and the chip
holder. Yeah. That sort of. I'd say about that size. And like the fold out like felt lined playing service.
Sort of yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Sort of. Well I this is a side. I don't have children. We don't have children.
But when I think about having children I do think I'm gonna get so annoyed when it's like the kid brings
home a form and it's like we have to sell 20 pizza kits. I'm like what the fuck. Like I don't want it. What?
Yeah because you're an adult and you know they do not. It's a made up need. It's not. It's fake.
At a certain point my family did go like all right dad's gonna sell half of these at work and then
we're gonna buy the rest. Like we're gonna. Well you stockpiled pizza kits? Yes stockpiled pizza kits.
And then we don't have to. That's Friday night pizza night for a couple months. Wow.
We gotta get a picture of the. I gotta find what this looks like. I'm sure it's still in business.
Here. This grift that people were running on your Philadelphia area schools. And then popcorn. We never thankfully sold
popcorn tins. Well that makes more sense to me than the pizza kit. That was a big with the boys scouts
would sell popcorn tins but we always just defaulted to the candy bars. Yeah. But in the wake of following
the success of avatars 2, 3, 4, and 5 people will go around selling kits of Navi food. Do you know a name off hand?
I can't remember. No I don't because the sole canteen. I'm trying to think of they don't really have fun avatar names.
What's the name of that drink they have that's like the slushy boba tea drink with the little fruit burst bubbles.
I'm so sorry. Because when I went to World of Pandora I was like this is the best thing I've ever tasted.
I went back for a second immediately. The next day we went again to World of Pandora. Wow. Got two of them.
So I had like four within the span of 24 hours and after the fourth one I felt so bad that I went and took a nap
in my friend's car in the parking lot. Oh man. Jason. In like a tired dad. 80 degree weather. But I like had the sweats.
I thought I was gonna vomit. Yeah like I flew too close to the sun.
All right it's called Joe Corby's. Since 1981 Joe Corby's pizza kit fundraising and the main results
are Little Caesar's pizza kit fundraising. So Little Caesar's has gotten in on this racket.
Wow. So a character who's eluded us up until now, Joe Corby will appear on the Patreon as a character episode I think.
We will look into this Joe Corby character. People love this like oh well I'm gonna order some of the
the cheese bread like the garlic cheese bread which my mom hates garlic but we were like
we really like that cheese bread but then the whole house smelled like garlic for days because
it's just so potent and greasy. Yeah and you're just storing the raw ingredients. Yeah. Can we start a
fundraiser on the podcast using Joe Corby's pizza kits? I don't know why we raise money.
It's the fans getting pizzas to Jason.
I'm gonna run this by UCB to help with the financially. It sounds like a better business
strategy than whatever they've been doing for the last year. Having your students sell pizzas to the
Pessar and Joe Corby. Joe Corby doing Ask Cat. You're less of a UCB person. Yeah not so much.
Jason I find that you're in that position now where like friends and family members who like
know you do it but don't understand the structure are like hitting you up to be like can you please
explain to me how this place is losing money. Like I think I keep getting that question that's like
I don't understand this. Isn't that the place where you pay to perform?
I think my mother is so unclear to what was happening. Yeah. She saw Harold once and she's
oh yeah very nice. Like I don't think she I don't think it was like registered what we were doing
or because she was like oh so you like kind of talked about that stuff before and then
I was like no it's all improvised and she was like okay like skeptical still. Yeah. Still doesn't
know about paying versus not paying. Sure. I do like one thing at UCB a year maybe maybe two and
I and I'll end up talking to my parents and then say oh yeah it was good you know I did this bit
at the at the UCB theater and it's as if for those couple words I started speaking Swedish
or something. They cannot in like how long 12 13 years they cannot retain the words UCB theater.
They will not stick in my parents brains. Which isn't a complaint. That's fine. I don't need them
to know those words. I guess like in New York there was nothing like it before it happened. Like you
didn't have sort of other comparable like you know IO or groundlings or any of that. So like UCB is
like is like what band-aids are to adhesive strips. Oh you're like doing comedy you know. Oh okay.
Oh it's that much like fundamentally. So now I feel like everyone's asking me like how is that
possible? Don't they own comedy? Well I think New York is a much more theater centric town. Right.
Maybe. I mean out out here and out here it's just everyone's just talking industry
bullshit all the time. So like I don't even know how much because there's glasses seem to be doing
just fine. But I think I mentioned it to my dad because like something came up in like a flipboard
or whatever news aggregator he was reading. It came up or I was like or I did it preventatively.
I was like by the way if you. Because every because he every now and then you know a news
story will come up. Yeah. And he's like oh I saw you guys you know or I'll send an article where
we got written up or he saw like oh I saw wild horses got a write-up or something and he I think
I was like by the way if you see any articles about UCB. If you see anything written about that
place where I've invested a decade of my life. Yes. Like assuring you was a good strategy.
Right this is going to pay out in some way. Yeah the actual doing shows like really doesn't affect
any of this nonsense. Like I had a past guest at the show Brad Evans and I were talking about like
yeah this is we have shows to do this week like doesn't really have any crossover with like poor
questionable financial. No it's fair. The doors might not be open when we get there but
that's it as long as they're open we'll do a show. I'll say this not trying to like take the steering
wheel but I was saying to a friend like I was trying to explain to friends outside of comedy
but it's like seen a bunch of my shows over the years and it knows when I was going through classes
and everything but how crazy it is what's going on with UCB and she said you know what needs to
happen Muppets need to put on a fundraiser. She was like that's the clear answer is like that's the model.
Oh yeah yeah. The Muppets have to save the theater. Right yeah yeah yeah I was that's what I was
thinking yeah on the topic of theaters that have a lot of trouble. Yes. It's a little less exciting
of trouble than canons and explosions but yeah you want to get into it Muppet Muppet Vision 3D.
Probably one of my 10 favorite movies. I don't doubt that that's true. I have that with theme park
movies. It's a great film. It's a truly top to bottom great film. Well it's a great director.
It is personally directed by Jim Henson and it's one of his final products on this earth.
Right I mean it's this and the Disney World Special I feel like are the last two things he oversaw.
He died 10 days after the Muppets go to Walt Disney World air. Wow yeah yeah oh my god.
Yeah so yeah to that end this thing it truly and we will get into all of it but it does it does feel
to me like it's very important in Muppet history because it's maybe like the the kind of the last
hurrah like the last great thing made by the original group. There's been good Muppet things
since but like the actual Henson's alive and everybody all the original guys are around.
It's very special for that reason. You know he dies and Kermit's voice immediately changes along
with other characters but it comes such a clear demarcation point. Yeah I like Steve Whitmire's
Kermit. I grew up with you know like that being the the voice that was making new shows and movies
constantly so it wasn't as alien to me even though I was also obsessed with the Muppet show. I was
watching all of it together but I feel like people are like oh it's the point where like he dies
Kermit starts sounding weird and then the other thing is it becomes of an emphasis on I think
because now it's like his kids taking over and they're like I don't know what do we do like put
him in other people's stories. Yeah well I am a big fan every Christmas Eve I watch Muppet Christmas
Carol. It's a great movie. But Kermit is supporting cast at that. Yeah like Bob Cratchit is supporting
like cast. And the model changes and it's like you have that in Treasure Island and then even a lot
of the stuff like they did there was a VHS I used to watch it was like a straight to video Disney
movie called like Muppet Fairytale Theater or something that was them doing like Three Little
Pigs and all that sort of stuff and then you have like Muppets Tonight which is like I don't know
what what if like Arsenio hosted the Muppet show. Way later that would have been hip in 92. Right and they do it in like 97.
Yeah but there is a Prince episode on that one. Which is really good. That's good. And in saying that it exists there's such little Prince
dude he never like hosted SNL or was in a sketch on SNL but he's in sketches with the Muppets. And that episode is so much about the symbol and the whole
artists probably know him as Prince Bruja which I didn't know who Prince was before watching that when it
aired and when my father explained to me Prince I was like oh and this is like the funny Muppet bit is that
he can't use his own name right. Because it sounded like a crazy Jim Henson concept that a man's name becomes a symbol.
Sure yeah. You thought he was like in the world. It's like the intricacies of like IP lawsuits.
Yeah and it was all to yes you see son he's avoiding a Warner Brothers contract that he didn't want to sign.
I watched Muppets Tonight every week when it was on. I watched it and I was so happy there was a
regular Muppets thing. I think at that point Nickelodeon and Nick at night it was one of those weird crossovers
where they would show the Muppet show in syndication on both. Because I would watch it every night on that.
So I'm so excited that like oh and now there's there's new Muppet stuff and the host of Muppets Tonight is it
Clifford? It's Clifford. Clifford yeah. Right. And he apparently in story as I was reading about this I didn't realize the joke is that
he is the host because no one else wanted to host and Kermit's title on Muppets Tonight is producer.
So Kermit takes the Lorne role on Muppets Tonight. It's a shot not situation where in the first episode of
Muppets Tonight I forget who the guest is on the first one but they realize oh the show's about to
start and we don't have a host and everyone starts leaving so that they don't get stuck with the job
and Clifford's on the cell phone with his girlfriend. He's like putting in the time with his
girlfriend to be like no baby I still love you and then he like looks around everyone's gone he's like
well I guess I'm hosting. Yeah. And Clifford's whole kind of premise is that he's just sort of cool.
Like he's sort of like a Ryan Seacrest where it's like this guy's appeal is that he doesn't really
have a personality. That he's just kind of genial and slick. And came out was not an original
character for that came out of the Jim Henson hour. Right. Which is also where Waldo was introduced.
I always thought Waldo was an original character from Muppet Vision 3D. He was not. He was around.
Right. And Bean Bunny comes out of they did a special that was like a bunny themed thing.
It was like an Easter special or something but then they used him and Jim Henson hour as well.
I mean that's the other weird thing about Muppet Vision is it's like it's the last pure Muppet
thing but it also features all these sort of like what Jim Henson was trying to make happen if he
stayed alive another 15 years. Sure. And maybe he could have more thoroughly. You felt like he was
trying to push Bean Bunny up to like top tier. Yeah. Because Bean Bunny is a big like emotional
core of a Muppet Christmas Carol too. Like he is a street urchin. He is the what day is today boy.
Right. And he's got he's the protagonist of Muppet Vision which is like a bold move.
And apparently I found some interview with a behind the scenes person who said the initial
Jim Henson pitch was almost entirely Bean Bunny. He was clearly going all in on Bean Bunny.
Do you sense you don't like Bean maybe? Well you know I always loved Bean. OK. And I feel like I'm
a small person. Yes. I was always the smallest kid in my class. Jason I don't know if you can relate to this.
So I always was into the sort of scrappiness of Bean Bunny. You know more so than Robin where it
felt like the thing was like he's a kid. It was like Bean Bunny is trying to fight to sit at the
adults table. Yeah. And like A they don't view him as an adult and B he can't reach the table.
Like it was both a maturity and a size thing. Bean Bunny too reminds me a lot of we just had the
Trainium Command episode with Buzzy the protagonist of that. And Bean Bunny and Buzzy both just trying
their best. Right. Trying to. Which I always like. I always like the sort of underdog thing. Now I
feel like now reading stuff and even what I was like getting at the time when I was very young
people were like Bean Bunny is like maybe the first tip off sign of what's going to happen when
Disney has the Muppets. Like Bean Bunny feels a little more Disney than Henson even though he was
a Henson character. And it's because the the special account I forget what it's called but it's
called like the bunny picnic or something is like very earnest and it's just like these adorable
bunnies and everyone's like okay this is like you know it's like an Emmett Otter it's its own lane
it's not Muppets canon. Then they transfer Bean Bunny over and the bit with Bean Bunny aside from
the fact that he's like the underdog and trying to be taken seriously is that he's kind of like
annoyingly cute. Yeah. That's a component that doesn't really register with me at the end when
he says what a cute ending. Yeah. Like okay I guess if I was around other Muppets media at the time
where I guess his thing was that he called things cute but that when you watch today many years
later and like I'm a little hazy on why this is happening or what the point of Bean Bunny was.
Well Bean Bunny feels both like a sort of Ewok-y like let's make the cutest character we can that
appeals to small children in the mainline Muppets continuity but also Henson trying to comment on
those types of shoe horned in like Cousin Oliver, Scrappy Doo. Oh and like Cousin Oliver he like
causes problems and get out of here and right right which all of those characters I always loved
like I was excited when a Cousin Oliver episode came on. I didn't get why people shit on Scrappy
characters. I see now why people don't like Bean Bunny and probably were more anti Bean Bunny because
they were like this is starting to look like they're priming him to be the guy. You know?
Huh. People were upset I feel like when Elmo joined Sesame Street. Right. Which I was always an Elmo guy.
Was a phenomenon. Yes. As opposed to Bean which I feel like Bean did sputter. Was Bean in any of
these new Muppet movies? I don't remember. No but I think Bean is more endearing than
Walter. Well Jason of course. That's my opinion. Let's have the Walter conversation. We're gonna get to Walter but I guess we'll do it now.
Is there any yeah is there any fondness for Walter in this room? I like Walter but I also think it's tough
because Walter's appeal is that he's a cipher. Yeah and doesn't know yeah what am I what's the point of me?
Yeah like I think whistling is the point we found out. Right. It was whistling. Right and even I was like
you know I like Walter's arc but like how am I gonna fit him into Muppets most wanted? I was like
I still think he's like an enjoyable presence. I think he's a nice guy. I like his enthusiasm.
I don't think they really did fit him into Muppets most wanted. He's in it and they don't totally have
like a plot function for him and there's a little bit of a weird status thing where you're like well
he's like a fan like even if they let him into the group he's not an equal stature with Fozzy. Like
he's not gonna feel comfortable. When they there's this shot in in Muppet Vision 3D where they're
standing in the black and it's it's Fozzy Kermit and Gonzo and that may as well to me be like
Captain America Iron Man Thor. Like these are the these are the core guys. These are the guys.
Right and that's a thing that keeps not to jump around too much but that that is my
thought revisiting Muppet Vision 3D is how odd it is that yeah through the 70s and 80s it is
it's the main well I don't know it's if it's you'd say three or four I guess four with this biggie.
I would argue it's like the the Disney thing with like here are the big five here like the main five
and Roger Rabbit comes and goes but the primaries stay. The four who are locked are like Kermit,
Fozzy, Gonzo, Piggy and then I feel like usually the fifth default is Animal. Sure. Even though he's
from the band he's technically part of that group he exists more outside of the band than the other
unit and he's a small doses character. But he's a Muppet baby too. Right. Animal over Rolf?
Well so Rolf obviously starts out. Oh okay. Yeah I think Rolf starts out as like clearly because he
was the original Muppet and it was like you know Kermit, Fozzy. I would I would argue it was like
Kermit, Fozzy, Piggy, Rolf, Scooter and then like Gonzo starts to develop into being more of a guy.
Gonzo knocks out Scooter. Scooter comes a little more functional you know than like a big five kind
of guy and then I think Rolf sort of falls by the wayside. I think especially after Hanson dies no
one really knows what to do with Rolf. No. It's similar to the relegated role of Grover in The Rise of
Thelmo. Right. A little bit of it. He's still around. He's not not around but less prominent.
Rolf is a real casualty I feel like. I think so too. Rolf is such a good character and kind of almost like
confidant whereas like Fozzy sort of his confidant later. You get the sense that Rolf's kind of like
the fact that Rolf started out as like Jimmy Dean commercials that was the character he brought on
late night shows. Like once he establishes the whole Muppet family Rolf still feels like the
old timer. Like he feels a guy who's one generation ahead of them. Yeah. Yeah. And he's like investing
less in it while everyone else is freaking out backstage about the show. Rolf just kind of does
his thing because he's been around you win some you lose some and like you know his role in the
Muppet movie as him explained to Kermit like you know relationships they're son of a bitch you know
you're gonna go around the block a couple times. He's the music guy. He's the GE Smith. Right. You know
there's different stress with the cast members but he's just got a guitar to play. Right. My job is
the same week after. Hey I got a gig baby. The show doesn't go on because it's Ray. The show goes on
because it's 11. That's right. You know he's just part of the band and he just goes. I'll always happily accept any reference to that line.
But that's the thing he's so much of a vibe character that I think he's it's so tied to the
Henson performance that when he's gone like no one else playing Rolf pops. I think there's one really
great Rolf gag in the first Siegel bobin movie where he's like why don't you say how including the
montage how you you met up with me and it's him taking a nap in a hammock. Oh that's right. That's
so funny. Rolf Rolf you want to come with us? He's like uh yeah sure. And like I was like that's a good they
identify what Rolf's vibe is. Right. Don't worry. Not that it's that he'll never raise a stink. He's mellow. But I think Grover's a similar thing
where it's like it's so tied to to Frank Oz that when Frank Oz stops doing Sesame Street
fake Grover doesn't click as much. Yeah yeah yeah. Well that I was saying there's a bigger thing where
in this like you said the odd stress of of Bean and of Waldo Seagraphic the spirit of 3D
and then Rizzo who was around a lot in the 80s but is less so now. I think Rizzo was was dancing
around that five spot for a while. I think for a while really especially when he and Gonzo were
like a comedy duo. I love that. Rizzo's in the five. I found Bean Bunny endearing but I very early on
in childhood I was like Gonzo's my guy because he's weird and I'm a little weird but he's funny.
I now as an adult I have no idea what Gonzo's game is. I think it's just that he's weird and he
fucks the chick. Like it wasn't until I was older. That is the joke. I mean that is the joke.
Yeah he's got several games and they're all very complicated. Yeah. But he's a character and I have
to say in this one I forgot like he really he really pulls off that sweater vest. Like he looks
good in that sweater vest shirt combo and that's a hard look to pull off. There's a Mickey toy
behind you that Mike has here. It's like suburban Mickey and it's similar to that. A guy we know a
little more casual or like or just seeing a guy in his work clothes. I kind of like. Yeah he looks
sharp. I have a plush of that also. Oh really? From when I was 18 and went to M. James Dewey
or Hollywood Studios. Yeah with the sweater vest. So I got mixed feelings about sweater vest Gonzo.
Because it's part of phenomenon that was them trying to sort of like gentrify Gonzo a little
bit. You know I think they tried to make him a little more like quirky than like thoroughly
weird. And so that was like part of the like we're gonna put him in like a checkered suit or we're
gonna put him in a sweater vest and now he's kind of just like your wacky uncle. Right. And he
becomes a little more professional because the thing I always liked about classic Gonzo was like
he's on a totally different wavelength than everyone else and everyone's like God be with
you. Go out there fuck that chicken eat that tire. Like whatever it is. And even like his formal
wear when he isn't in his like daredevil sort of performing jumpsuit it's like this really shitty
sad sack crumpled purple suit. You know like he's a guy who like doesn't even know how to function
in polite society. They like domesticated Gonzo. They did. Domesticated is the word. That's true.
That's better than gentrified. I mean yeah I knew what you meant. Yeah. He was like kind of craggier
and more like crumpled up too. Yes. He does it does feel like an like an awkward like
adolescent like prepubescent Gonzo and then he like grew up and got a little handsome.
One of his early games too was that he was very sad. Like early Gonzo on the Muppet Show
is like he's a sad sack. It's the saddest Muppet song that he sings in the Muppet movie. Yes. I'm
going to go back there someday. It's just insanely sad. And Paul Williams is like that's maybe the
version I think of Paul Williams singing it with Gonzo. Yeah it rules. And it's awesome. Yeah.
But he's high status in this. Very. Like all of Gonzo's stuff hits. I mean a thing that I
recognize now but I really liked as a kid there's a lot of funny lines in Muppet Vision 3D and I
think that's a thing that when when Henson died they look like they're so in the pre-show when
Sam Sam Eagle yells like would you stop this foolishness God that says what foolishness would
you like to say? And I just nails that line. That's sort of Borschbelt vaudeville thing. The Muppets
were always very tied to that. They were very like old school entertainers. I feel like slips away a
little bit post Henson death and I think especially like you know they sort of pull out of the Disney
deal but they keep doing Disney adjacent stuff without fully selling and I think everyone was
trying to like domesticate the Muppets in general. Like just play up the sort of like cuddliness and
the sort of like they're they got great spirits over the sort of scene. You know. Whereas they
grow out of like you know they were they were weird and there was that other group that was on
the first season of SNL. Right. And that was super weird like nobody really connects to that but then
the Muppets show is a very strange comedy show. It's not like I love Kermit and you hug him.
They're like it's just immersive hippies that are doing like a traditional show and movie but like
you can feel the like weirdness. You can feel their like counterculture stuff. And they're like broken
outcasts. Like they're all sort of represent different kind of types archetypes and entertainment
and showbiz history and they all don't fully succeed at what they're trying to be. And so
all they got is each other and the stage and like that's it. And then it becomes like you're going
to see them play the roles like you know it's it's they're doing Treasure Island or Muppets Tonight
is like kind of a slicker show. You know. Which I don't like as much. It's a pretty good show within
the world of the show. It's just like cool music video here. Let's all rap with Coolio. Right. And
nothing goes wrong which is what you want out of the Muppets. It's such a difficult thing to do
because Frank Oz has like recently trashed all the new Muppets stuff again. Yeah. And like he's
always like the writers don't understand the heart. And I was like I don't know. They probably don't
understand like what you would do. But like what are you supposed to do also? Like how? He's got a term he uses
that I think is really good. And I don't agree with all of his trashings. I think he's right on about
some things. I think other things he doesn't give enough credit. And you know he when Disney finally bought the
Muppets they went to Frank Oz and said we want to bring you back and get the old school vibe back.
And he was starting to develop a movie that I don't think was like fast track but they were working on it
when Siegel came in for a general meeting and was like I want the Muppets and they pushed Frank Oz out.
Whoa. He was going to do the last like unmade Henson movie idea which was the cheapest Muppet movie ever.
Right right. And the premise is that they let Gonzo take control of a movie. Oh my god. And the first 10 minutes are the most expensive
movie ever made and the movie stops and they tell Gonzo they've run out of funding. And it's the
Muppets having to improvise a movie for the rest of the runtime. That's so neat. And they like recycle sets.
Like characters playing multiple parts. Like trying to just get to the end of the script.
God that's it. That's the kind of movie that if it came out when I was nine.
Would have blown your mind. Yeah I would be talking about it every day.
Right. Wow. Wow. Yeah it's great because like they tried with that Muppets show and it's like
basically like the office. That show's a nightmare. Okay. Few things make me angry.
We've got to talk about that because I never realized this. Muppet Vision is written by Bill Prady.
Who would go on to be the co-creator of that like bad Muppet show and Big Bang Theory.
Right. That's the thing. So when they announced that he was doing the ABC Muppet show everyone's
like oh they got some Big Bang Theory guy. And he came out and started like pounding his chest and
he was like I got the bonafides. I worked with Jim. I was a big Muppet guy. Like trust me I get it.
And then you watch that show and I don't know whether it was his intentions got modeled. If
a network came in with things. If he was trying to update it in the way he thought. But it was so
maddening because they had just done two movies that fully reintroduced the iconography and the
format of the Muppet show. Yes. And it was like it's on a plate for you. Just they got the theater
back. It's in the narrative. Dual weekly show. That's a variety show and it's the exact same
thing with the exact same theater. Instead it's Kermit is corny for a different pig.
Like that was a story like. It's Baz Larry Sanders is what it is. Yeah. And the joke is that they're
all kind of depressed in the office and Fozzie is like the mono joke writer. Yeah. Or he's the
sidekick. Gonzo is writing mono jokes. And Kermit's just sort of like the ripped torn character and
he's broken up with Piggy. And you're like this show is just like their hearts not in it anymore.
It's a show about the Muppets not enjoying putting on a show. And there's a lot of like
too sad. Like the stuff in the Muppet movie is sad but it's sort of like deep heart sadness that
we all experience. Whereas like the sadness in the Seagull Muppet movie. Yeah. And then this show
is all just like depressed and just vague depression sadness for like it's not enjoyable
and it doesn't like say anything and it doesn't speak to you. It just makes you. They maybe try
a little too hard to hit the like the Pixar right in the feels buttons. Yeah. But I do think the
area in which they're exploring the sadness is the same sort of like existential loneliness of
these Muppets and the idea of like they got nowhere else to go if they don't got a show.
Whereas like the ABC show is just like now they've sort of just become cynical and jaded.
They're in showbiz and they're just sort of forced harder than they are. I remember watching the
episode and there's a scene where it's like mockumentary Fozzie turning to the camera and
complaining about the traffic in L.A. And I was like no one wants to see this. This is for nobody.
This is for podcasters. Yeah. Weird. You know I can I talk a little bit about about Steve Whitmire
because I uncovered a big treasure trove of stuff with him or not. Not a treasure trove. It's a
trove of mud. It's very upsetting and sad. Can you fill into like what he did what his Muppet.
Yes. So Steve Whitmire is really an all star of Muppet Vision 3D because there's such big
performances such major performances from Rizzo especially in the pre-show. Bean Bunny is really
the heart of it as we said and he's the 3D character while the sea graphic. A really good
in Muppet Vision 3D. Jim Henson dies after making Muppet Vision 3D. He takes over his Kermit. He's
a couple years ago. I didn't know it changed but he got fired a few years ago and it is just a
terrible situation between him and the Hensons and they see some of what you're talking about
about how that show is so weird and depressive. They seem to put some of that on him. First of
all they say Steve Whitmire. That he pushed Kermit to more of a sad sack vibe. Yes. Yeah. The quote
Hui is Steve's performance of Kermit has strayed far away from my father is one of the H sons
from my father's good hearted compassionate leader of the Muppets. Steve performed Kermit as a bitter
angry depressed victim. Worst of all in the last few years he had not been funny or fun.
Recasting Kermit is long overdue. Really harsh but then he keeps going and he's talking about
what his dad did and how what he had there was a wry intelligence and a little bit of a
character element. I don't think so but then also it seems like Whitmire did not like the ABC show
as we do not like it and he was in there going Kermit wouldn't do this. I've been playing Kermit
like he was there's something where he lied to Robin about who he was seeing or something
and that this fight was apparently enough to be the catalyst for getting Whitmire out of there
altogether. Well that's one of Frank's whole big things is that they don't listen to the performers.
That was one of his big complaints is that the performers know better than a lot of the writers
and they don't listen to them. That's what he says. But it's also tough because you have like the
performers are still inheriting other people's characters and those characters become so rich
because it's like they're doing them over years in different projects and they built up the sense of
it. Now I think most of those performers have really like grown up with these things studied
these things lived these things. I like most of Whitmire's Kermit stuff. I will say not setting
my sources here but I've heard from from close people in proximity to this situation.
Whitmire's wife was his manager and apparently at some point post Disney still started saying like
you're the Mickey Mouse. Like anything you ask for they have to give you and so anytime there was
any Kermit thing he would demand two first class seats. One for him and one for the puppet. Then
he would go to the airport downgrade to business and pocket the cash.
No! That's a great hack though by the way. That is really good. That's like you hear about the
the band Sue asked for like really nice red wine or something and then Axl Rose has like a full
wine cellar. So they would give him a seat for the puppet? Correct. This is a Costanza move.
His wife was kind of like a Lady Macbeth figure and that she was like you cannot ask for enough.
And then eventually they said. This ties into another quote that I found. So then I like
now the site is offline but there was kind of like a sub blog spot like you know Whitmire's
truth report essentially and he says some stuff that does sound I don't know like this is
interesting hearing all this because you see reading both sides of it I felt more on Whitmire's side
especially with stuff like this. Creatively I'm pretty down with Whitmire's side of the story.
And then when I start hearing about the the business demands of things. Yeah yeah yeah which
is what they said they accused him of unacceptable business conduct. What you just said does seem to
line up with that. But so here's what he said about Jim which is so there was apparently I mean it
seems like to get Muppet Vision 3D going with Disney and the deal in general that it was like
a very strenuous difficult deal that was weighing on Jim and the family and not really fully sewn
up by the time they started filming the thing. A lot of people kind of theorized that the deal
killed him. Yeah yeah. That's why I read that. Oh god. The obvious thing is you know Jim Hansen was
a Christian scientist when he got sick he refused to see anybody by the time he saw a doctor it was
too late like he kind of made his own grave in that sense but people say that the year or two
that he was doing all the Disney negotiations that he was thinking about selling that he was
working on Muppet Vision all of that he like physically changed that he got so worn down
by the thing and I think he kind of psychosomatically started dying. Well and think about what he was
doing before that all these oddball like labyrinth Jim Henson storyteller the Jim Henson hour like
all these weird experimental. He's following his own muse. Exactly. And he owned the thing you know I mean it was kind of incredible that it was like he was able to carry these properties this this
group of characters over different mediums and different bosses but he always had control. He pointedly Muppet St. Manhattan was supposed to be the last thing he ever did with the Muppets.
Really? He was like I've said what I need to say that's why it ends with them getting married.
Oh. And that's when he starts doing like labyrinth dark crystals start building up the workshop I want to do stuff for other movies you know.
Ninja Turtles. Right yes so then like Jim Henson hour is him kind of conceding and being like I guess I gotta give him a little bit of Kermit to do what I want.
Oh. We'll do a storyteller segment but it's also going to be hosted by Kermit and Fozzie and Gonzo.
That's what I was not really familiar with the Jim Henson hour too much and I was reminding myself because Waldo's in it and stuff and he is pretty clear about like so half of the show will be in Kermit world.
Correct. And the other half will be this totally original thing.
So he's still trying to ride that line.
It's a platform it's a space for me to experiment with whatever I want.
Gotcha.
And even the Muppet half of it's very like cold like it's like them running like a UHF station.
In this one limited digital environment that's not nearly as expansive or creative as the storyteller world.
And the band is called Cold Foam is that right?
I think that's correct.
It's got a different it's not the electric man it's got Clifford in it and it's got.
That's where he came from.
As a band member.
Yeah.
Oh so I think he's sort of in this zone where he's like I guess the people want Muppets like I can't be selfish.
I got to keep them going.
Let's sell them to Disney.
They know how to maintain characters.
I'll remain involved creatively.
This is like Jay and Silent Bob strike back.
It is.
It's very much like he thought he had walked away but the public is like please we love them.
The viewers universe is not closed.
It's closed when we say it's closed.
But anyway like they're from from this blog spot or whatever I was like from Whitmire.
He says that like he and another one of the primary Muppet performers were having a lot of difficulty closing their contracts.
And Jim was very much on their side.
For Muppet Vision.
And he was really talking.
Jim is defending them and saying you know like these are my guys.
I picked them for a reason.
And Disney said that's not somebody to his face.
Whitmire says he saw this.
Somebody says that's not how we do business.
If Mickey 1 won't do it for what we offer then we move on to Mickey 2.
And we keep going down the line until somebody will do it for our price.
So day one of shooting Muppet Vision.
It's Whitmire and one of the other guys.
Deals have not closed.
Several lawyers.
Three studio attorneys.
March onto the soundstage interrupt production and demand that those two sign their contracts immediately.
And then Whitmire goes on to compare this to how the Henson family is treating him now.
He says did they tell me my business.
Did Jim say your business conduct is unacceptable.
Did he accuse him of brinksmanship.
Wow.
A word that the Henson's used on him.
No Jim said with everybody in view looked at the attorneys square in the eye and slowly quietly said get off my set and never come back.
Then he turned back to Steve.
And Steve said I'm really sorry to have caused a problem especially on this big day for you.
The first day of Disney.
And he said Jim said I would never want you to sign a deal that you're not comfortable with.
And then he died.
It does feel like that was like he was living in this sort of business world.
You know a very structured sort of franchise driven business world that he had avoided.
Muppet Show famously no network would pick it up.
And he went to like Lord Lou Grade who put up all the money and it was sold in syndication.
Has anyone ever seen footage of Lord Lou Grade.
He looks incredible.
Oh my god yeah he's like a crazy like prosthetic character.
He's like if you like hey can you do like a Orson Welles impression.
Well because Orson Welles.
What took it too far.
Orson Welles in the Muppet movie I believe his character's name is Lou Lord.
And he's the studio exec who gives them.
Oh my god.
The rich and famous contract.
That's and that's why it's a similar character.
Right because he's like this is the Orson Welles of my life.
Like this man has that sort of weight.
And he's just very British.
Really he's like Hitchcock is what he is.
But he yeah I think you know Henson had always found these very
generous sort of benefactors who believed in him.
And then from that point on he could sort of write his own checks
or just go to a place and go here are the terms.
You know I want to do a movie.
You just give me the money and you get a Muppet movie.
And I think having to deal with to use the lingo like a place like Disney where they
he views the Muppets as face characters.
They are very tied to these performers.
Right yeah.
And to them they're like doesn't matter who's doing the hand.
Doesn't matter who's doing the voice.
Can't we dub it in later.
You know that sort of thing.
I said it before it is like what George Lucas is going through right now.
George Lucas going nuts because he thought he was selling to Disney.
And they're going to kind of do his ideas and he'll be around and help out a little bit.
And it's like they were like get the fuck out of here George.
We don't give a shit about what you think.
And he's like obviously cranky about it and he's had to be scolded by them.
You kind of have to imagine I mean if he had closed the Disney deal they would have done
a similar thing to Henson and it probably would have been tragic.
You know.
Yeah he would have had the same he would have what did Lucas called Disney white slave.
He called them white slaves.
Charlie Rose.
Which is inappropriate of course.
Yes and Charlie Rose laughed.
That's what happened.
Oh my god.
So clever.
Is anyone else like oddly sad upset forlorn.
Ever since you dropped the news that you think it's the deal that killed him.
Yeah.
I feel like this is like the most like vulnerable I've felt on the show.
This is so upsetting.
Realizing that is what's happening with Lucas.
Forlorn?
Forlorn.
Yeah the great man.
Let's make sure this is good forlorn in case Lauren listens to this podcast.
I say my prayers at night before bedtime.
I it's like please let us please just give Lauren strength.
Well and when I go up to the plate with my bat ready to hit a homer I point to the
the bleachers and I say this is forlorn.
You know whatever 30 rock is.
It's forlorn.
Yeah no I've heard that before so my sadness about it is already.
No it's really striking me and just realizing and not only not just to say it's like
it's the Star Wars syndrome but this is the syndrome in a lot of things and it's the sad
side of IP and things and everybody going no Harrison Ford is not what's important about
Indiana Jones.
Right.
And I'm like no I don't think that's right.
I disagree.
And it's like no you're just a nerd complainer malcontent but I don't think I am.
I think I just like the stuff I like the way it is.
Yeah it all depends though because this is so tough because there's versions of characters
that like new versions like Adam's family movies new versions of those characters
totally different actors.
Pretty good movies.
True.
And that people like and there's other like the new whether some people like Star Trek
JJ whatever.
But you also go I mean there's the weird thing of like with the Adam's family it was
a comic first like it was the strip so everyone is just doing their take on the drawings.
It's like the Muppets though especially because they're they I take on it they look exactly
the same.
Yes.
So it's like if any like as if Leonard Neamey it looked like Leonard Neamey but the voice
was different and he acted a little different.
It's like hard to do that like you can't reinvent that as easy.
I also think the other thing with the Muppets is it's like when you see people playing the
Stooges you know or like the Marx brothers or something.
It's like yes these were characters you can dress people up like them they can do the
voices they weren't playing themselves but also it's like a thing that was developed
in multiple mediums for years and years and years where it was just in the bones for these
guys.
Sure.
And you go like Kermit was on like local TV before he became like a commercial star to
being like a guest on like Ed Sullivan.
Yeah.
There was so much evolution with like Henson working that out and the way that all these
guys did like the vaudeville circuit before they got movies.
Or even just Letterman and Carson's career trajectory where they're like going on to
bigger and bigger hosting gigs.
Yeah right but it's like you spend a lifetime just honing this sort of thing what the energy
is and what the rhythm is and all of that.
Yeah.
It is like somebody like taking over Johnny Carson's skin versus taking over Mr. Spock.
It's like if Leno did Carson.
Yeah.
Like if he took up The Tonight Show and was like and of course I will wear the Carson
wig.
Right.
And say weird and wild stuff.
Yeah it's different but they're both fictional characters but it's different.
Right yeah.
Spock is an easier just put the ears on somebody and he can do his own take on it.
Yeah.
For whatever reason Kermit is so developed as a human as a character as a person.
And also the fact that it is like it's like if George Lucas also played Luke Skywalker.
Yeah right right.
That's an extra thing too.
I know that Walt voiced Mickey Mouse but I never felt like he was very territorial about
that.
He probably did it because he didn't want to pay another person $10.
Yeah you're right.
And he very quickly let other people voice Mickey Mouse.
And I think Kermit really became Henson and I think it's just like you lose the voice
and the guy who's writing everything and the heart of the thing and the technician like.
Yo yeah.
You can't do okay I don't mean to be like there can't be a new and like I said I've
liked Steve Whitmire.
I like a lot of Whitmire stuff.
Yeah there's been good Mumpet stuff in the last couple decades but you can't say no not
the cast and we don't want their ideas and we don't and Frank Oz get out of here and
even a new person who has the recognizes what the spirit of the old ones was.
No we don't want that either.
And like you can't say no to all of it.
And I think it's I'm starting to realize like why is the why have the Muppets been so messy
ever since Muppet Vision 3D and it's it's everything we're everything we're talking
about.
I don't know what is the source but clearly Disney is a problem.
Ironic because Disney because Muppet Vision 3D which we have alluded as alluded as mostly
so far is really good.
It's so good.
It's very good.
And I think there there's a moment in this that I think like epitomizes what I like about
the Muppets and it's that moment when they're standing in all black.
Also side note the band and Jim Henson our was called Solid Foam not Cold Foam Solid
Foam which I think is a joke but yeah we'll come back to that.
It's a conundrum.
So it's it's Fozzie and Kermit and Gonzo standing in the black and Kermit yells hey Sam
and Sam Eagle like sticks his head or he opens a door in the black.
This is the black void door.
A black void door and he said he asked him like is the finale ready and he goes like
yes it's a glorious three hour finale and Kermit goes you got a minute and a half and
Sam like goes and like slams the door.
His gasp is so funny.
His gasp is so funny the minute and a half is so funny.
The other thing is and I watched this a few times this one sequence like I think the
puppeteer didn't quite get the door open with Sam.
I think he gets it open halfway and then gets it all the way but they use that take.
Yeah.
Oh interesting.
I don't know.
So it's a little messy.
Yeah so it looks a little messy and it could have been a conscious choice.
It could have just been like well no one's going to notice that in the long run.
I think here's all those guys where it was like about the feeling above all else.
Yeah.
Performance is good you want to keep that like as much as he tried to advance stuff
technically that wasn't the end game.
Like he never went up his own Lucas butt you know.
Yeah right.
Yeah but you talk about the messiness post-Hensen and it is a thing where like they never had
someone who was so clearly steering the ship after he died.
Like there's no Kevin Feige.
There's no Kathleen Kennedy.
Like Brian Henson's sword takes over his default but it wasn't like he was the head writer.
Yeah.
I want to keep up my dad's legacy then they sell this weird German company
and then even at Disney it's not like there's someone protecting the Muppet brand.
They sort of go like anyone got anything they want to do with the Muppets?
And they handed over to whoever.
That's the case to like any idiot in a meeting.
Like that you could just like and we do have the Muppets remember.
Like weird why?
Why is it so just like whatever no one has any ideas.
Well all of the franchises are running into this of like well who's like Kevin Feige is
a one in a million.
He's like kind of got a clear thing but like the DC.
Like there literally hasn't been a guy like him in a hundred years.
But like Star Wars seems a little on rocky ground right now.
Certainly the universal dark universe like was dead.
Well it's over.
I don't know really.
I think that thing's going pretty well.
One movie and it's over?
And that thing's still on the track.
So maybe it's going to come back.
And then like you just read.
I'm sorry to side tangent.
Did you guys read that piece on how like the universal had given up on the dark universe
and how which one Kurtzman is had like asked universal to build like all these offices that
were like decorated with giant sculptures of the monsters and artwork and murals and now they're
just empty and they have like a whole floor of offices that are all monster themed with like the
memorabilia and creative artwork and all this stuff and they're just like no one's in there.
It's just an empty floor.
Well that's a friend of the show and rabble rouser Jack Allison has pointed out like so
many companies that are having financial funny or die or you see me.
They just keep buying bigger buildings or running big offices.
It's like just don't do don't do that.
Regular office or like a fucking we work is fine.
Well it's also the universal monster thing drives me crazy.
I'm just going to say this very quickly because I say it any chance I get.
It is such a slam dunk that universal who pretty much has Jason Blum in house just goes
Jason Blum here's 40 million dollars make five monster movies.
Yeah make them at the same budget level you get interesting talent make them actually scary.
Instead they opened with like an Annie Lebowitz shoot like a photo shoot of like here's the stars.
Here's all the.
It's so much before the horse.
Because everyone is just pan everyone's just panicking like the Marvel there's 20
Marvel movies and they're all make money.
Okay we got 20 movies here we go.
Johnny Depp what is Javier Bardem right Angelina Jolie.
Oh Angelina Jolie.
These are the movies and then the first one eats shit.
It's so funny.
It was also Tom Cruise one.
It's the one it's the guy we all like.
But like he kept on doing these interviews where he was like you know the tricky thing
is they're horror movies but if you're going to make temples they can't be horror films so we have
to figure out how to adapt them to adventure films.
That's not true.
It's not fucking true because like fucking get out out grossed the mummy you know so like make
them actually scary.
And let them be like I like your thought about them being a little like lower budget because
all those original movies that still like you could still you could show a kid now the old
Frankenstein or Dracula and it would affect them and they're like weird and slow.
Has to be the monster like a good atmospheric director you know get good actors to play the
humans.
Sure like the thing is just give me like a good monster design you know and an interesting
vibe and all of that.
I'll say this too I mean I this just me bring back Frasier bring back Brenda Frasier.
Let's get let's reboot that mummy.
I thought you were suggesting that you bring Frasier Crane into the dark universe.
But like I watched I watched like the first 20 30 minutes of the Tom Cruise Mummy movie.
And I was a little stoned and normally I like everything when I'm stoned and I was just like
what the fuck like they found a bunch of sarcophagus is under London.
It's like it's the mummy.
Yes start in Egypt.
Are you insane?
What's wrong with you?
He become I haven't seen it does he become a mummy.
That's the ending.
He's the mummy right.
He's the mummy.
It takes a movie to get there.
He dies he falls out of a plane dies wakes up in a body bag and everyone's like yes
spoilers for this two year old.
Is he a bandaged mummy at the end of it.
His eyes turn a weird color.
He's handsome 57 year old mummy.
He's not a you want a fucking guy.
Bandages.
Yeah you want the bandages.
In a skeleton face if it was revealed.
Yeah.
Anything have the thing that's in the title be in the first 10 minutes of the movie.
Look how much people love Spider-Man Spider-Verse right and that's the thing I liked about it.
The most here we go Spider-Man Spider-Man.
I get it you don't need to which was sort of my thing.
I don't I'm not a big hater of the of the Seagull Muppets.
I like both of them a lot.
I actually don't like I like that film a lot.
I think it gets better.
Okay.
My feeling was like all right the pieces are back together.
Now can we be off to the races and have fun which I guess they did and it's up to the viewer is was
that fun or not for me it was not terribly fun.
I found it murky and I still didn't really want to be in this Russian prison.
The tee up was do a new Muppet show like that's a perfect for the time we live in a kind of thing
like because the most success weirdly Disney has had with any Muppet stuff since buying them is
when they do like oh it's like the Muppets singing Bohemian Rhapsody.
Yeah.
And it's like put that in the context of a variety show.
Sure.
Where you have musical sections and sketches and things like that you can have excerpt.
This is a sorry quick little side issue.
This is a thing I've I think this overlaps with my opinion about Will Ferrell at this point.
Do these things have to live as movies?
Sure.
Because clearly people love Will Ferrell when he's on a talk show.
Yeah.
Or hosts SNL.
Doing some short form or some oddity like the stuff he does with Funny or Die.
The Muppets people if they show up on SNL or a talk show.
Yeah people lose it.
In some small or those viral videos.
Yeah.
Those are all still extremely successful.
Do all of do the things that we let do we have to force these giant tent pole situations.
I don't need the Muppets to be like crown jewels in the Disney Kingdom.
But I think what you need is one clear creative head.
Yeah.
Who's like whether it's something in the theme park whether it's having them on a talk show
whether we're doing a short form this or that you want like one person who's like a comedy writer.
Yeah.
Who's like keyed into their voices and is like I'm overseeing that all this stuff isn't dumb.
Are you pitching yourself for this job?
This is like my dream job.
But I also think like I was gonna say when I sit down and I go like pine this guy if you
could do anything in your career what would it be and I'd be like oh I'd love to create like
the new Muppets like I'd love to just like create a world and cast characters like that.
Happy time murders got it.
Right.
You know unfortunately I was replaced two days into filming.
They took the film in a very different direction.
Replaced by Brian Henson.
No but I do think it's one of those things where you kind of couldn't
do it today in the same way because it would be front loaded it would be like the goal is
to make characters that could last for 50 years and bring in this much in merchandising you know
per year and the fact that it was like so homegrown and evolved slowly over time.
Organic I'd say.
Yeah.
The best the real quick the best this is another theme park thing we'll eventually talk about this
actual film I think but the best thing in the Muppets in the last 10 to 15 years for me is the
show in Orlando that they do the great moments in history.
That's what I've heard.
And it's so great it's like 10 minutes long it's putt they come out it's funny it's all the same
it's great it's like that's the pure that's the most pure they've felt to me in years.
Do we know who's responsible for that?
We do.
We met one of the gentlemen.
One of the Knots guys.
That guy we met at Knots.
Oh I met him.
You met him.
Yeah.
Oh cool.
It's like a theme park guy wrote that and not like a comedy person.
I mean I'm not sure how many people work he was just one of the main imagineers on it so I don't
know who if he actually wrote I forget did he write the scripts?
Well we have to go find him and interview him.
We'll have to ask.
But there's five different shows they do too so it's like.
Oh that changes from there?
Yeah the show's changing like they show up different places in Liberty Square.
Sometimes they're in different windows and sometimes it's a whole different narrative
it's it's so great.
Isn't there like a rumor going around they might do something like that at the sort of
threshold point of Galaxy's Edge to slow down for traffic?
From a Muppets thing?
Yeah to do a Muppet like elevated window show like that because you because it's right by
right where Muppet Vision used to be in California.
That weird abandoned now here's we're constantly screening trailers for the Nutcracker.
You were saying a show in California Adventure as well?
I've heard both.
I was thinking you were talking about because there is a I've heard from Jim and Len Jim Hill.
You're familiar.
Oh are you?
Yeah I used to read Jim Hill Media a lot in high school.
Of course.
I can't believe I ever hear that phrase from anyone that I'm talking to today.
Like so there were there were other high schoolers staying inside and checking Jim Hill Media.
Wonderful because the rumor I've heard is that they're going to do it to kind of
entertain people online for Galaxy's Edge in Hollywood Studios.
The people who are waiting there to try to get through the gates.
Right and they're waiting there for six seven eight hours.
At least they'll be entertained.
Not Disneyland that's not on the cards for Disneyland.
You're saying also there was a rumor over in California Adventure they were going to do it.
I did hear something about like a new Muppet thing floated but I feel like that's I haven't
heard it in so long I don't think it's going to happen.
Yeah Muppet Adventure 3D kind of died a slow painful death in California Adventure.
It took so long to get it over there in the first place.
It's so stupid that it kind of like.
So like 2014 it became like the Frozen sing-along show and then after that it was just like either
Pixar shorts or like movie pre.
I think it's literally now like Nutcracker and the Four Realms like it's a trailer showcase.
Permanently Nutcracker and the Four Realms.
I mean we all love the Nutcracker and all his realms.
How would you guys rank the realms if you had to rank the realms?
It's like choosing a favorite child.
Yeah good point.
I like the gumdrop realm the best.
Yeah definitely.
I assume that's all candy paste.
Definitely yeah.
Spread sounds like a realm yes.
But it didn't open in California Adventure until like 2001?
Well it was an opening day attraction.
Okay yeah.
But the rumor was always that it was a big hit out of the gate at Disney MGM Studios.
We got to get it to Disneyland and the rumor was always that it would replace Great Moments
with Mr. Lincoln.
Right a touchy subject I understand.
I completely think it should have been done.
Like it would be gone by now.
That would be like a weird hole and maybe you could have brought back Lincoln by now.
But for sure in that time.
Because then it just you know you wait 10 years put it in the other park with by the way into
by the way a shittier looking building.
I think that brick building where you see it in Disney MGM Studios.
It's one of the best things you got going for it.
It's such a wonderful place and quick little detail.
When I was growing up there in Thousand Oaks California there was the optometrist's office
where I had to go as a kid and get my like eye drops and vision checked and stuff.
And the optometrist's office was this big brick building that to me looked like the Muppet Vision 3D building.
And it made me want to go get eye drops and go to the eye doctor.
It was like an otherwise very unpleasant experience.
I was like oh I get to go to that building that reminds me of Muppet.
There was nothing fun inside.
No no no.
Just the outside.
Of course you have to get your eyes dilated.
It's one of the worst.
I hate that still to this day.
I find it very satisfying.
I'm like a hip and a bandaid on.
It's something nice about it.
And then you get the glasses which are kind of like 3D glasses.
Sure.
The eye doctor glasses.
That's how you worked your way into enjoying the eye test.
Yeah.
Yeah yeah yeah.
This feels Muppet Vision adjacent.
That's how passionate I am about that.
I think that Muppet Vision building is so nice.
And then anyway my point was it gets out here.
Does it go into the grand beautiful Main Street Opera House?
No it goes into some junky square building.
It's so generic.
The sign is worse.
It's just kind of slapdash paint everywhere.
Probably the justification being you know it's Muppet.
So they just threw it together.
It's a sound stage.
It's just a sound stage.
But it looks like a bad 90s sound stage.
Like it doesn't even have a classical old timey Hollywood architecture.
That whole corner of the park like especially in the early versions of
California Adventure was like a very watered down MGM Studios.
And even had a lot of the same sort of font and signage and stuff.
And then it's just kind of like morphed and mutated over the years.
Like they've had big plans that have been scrapped or like oh the budget didn't show
up and that sort of thing.
But like yeah now that theater is just kind of yeah like you said Nutcracker in the Four Realms.
It's so depressing.
And it really is just like you can tell it's designed for something.
Yes and that little store that little stand next to it used to be all Muppet stuff.
Like fun Muppet merch.
Which even I went to MGM Studios last fall and I was so excited to buy some Muppet merch.
It's low.
That store has maybe one wall of like four plushes.
It sucks.
I was there like 10 years ago.
It's mostly Jack Skellington that store.
Yeah it sucks.
10-11 years ago filled with Muppet stuff.
Like I got a shirt with just Beaker's head on it.
And I always check compliments on it.
That was all I wanted.
The problem of course I like I'd love to blame Disney's easy but the problem is I'm sure that
most tourists go in there and are more likely to buy a Jack Skellington doll.
I know the numbers back it up.
Like on Questway there's a reason why they do that but it still feels disrespectful.
I agree.
Because the thing's still called like Muppet stuff or whatever.
Yeah and the fountain I was like the fountain outside.
That whole area used to be called the Muppet's Courtyard.
It is now called Grand Avenue.
And they're sort of like a topsy microbrewery sort of thing which is one of the ways they'll
placate the masses while they wait in six hour lines.
And Pizzeria is a fucking disaster.
That place is an upfront.
Hold on.
This isn't necessarily us.
This has come up on the show before and in fact I don't know with the timing but if you're
interested in the further dissection of Pizzeria, subscribe to our Patreon.
Have you recorded a Pizzeria episode?
No.
We will.
But it's a subjective debate because it was trashed on this show.
I trashed it.
Our friend Doug Jones sat and stewed at home listening and recently came on the show and
he was mad at me because he was there in Florida and he texted me a picture of him in front of
me which kind of gave a response or something, a couple lines or whatever.
And I think I disrespected him by doing that and then he came on the show and you'll hear it.
Yeah, that's pizza Gotti is not.
Pizza Rizzo Gotti is not.
So he came on to take me to task about Pizza Rizzo and he's very passionate about it.
So I guess if Doug Jones come at me, the pizza is garbage and the theming is an upfront.
How do you not do like a pizza down the line, the pizza rev or all these places down the line,
pick what you want, make your own pizza.
It's the worst hockey puck pizza.
Although they put that in now in downtown Disney out here, like the Vianapoli where you could just
get slices to go.
Now it's like that sort of Chipotle, like make your own miniature pizza.
I got to try that because I'm a little skeptical.
I feel like it's like cafeteria, like heat lamp, like it's just their box and they pull it.
I didn't eat it to be fair.
So I don't even want to after what Doug and I got into, I don't even want to say anything if I'm not
informed because he pointed out there's a room and you'll hear this if you go to the Patreon episode.
There's a room upstairs with a disco ball and I did miss that room.
I think we didn't go upstairs when I went there, but I thoroughly explored the downstairs and saw
nothing that made me feel good.
I agree with you, but I'm saying I have to now go back to Pizza Rizzo and when I go, I will do
probably an official review with Doug of Pizza Rizzo.
I'd also like to tease that if you go check out this episode, we also get a ruling on Pizza Rizzo
from someone who works in the Jim Henson creature shop and I don't want to say either way which way
they go about it, but let this be an enticement to go.
I'm not sure if it'll be out yet or not, but go check it out.
Pizza looks like the 1996 theme park pizza.
It's so bad.
That pizza planet was always so disappointing that I was like, I have no problem with them
replacing that in the hopes that maybe they build a proper pizza plant somewhere else.
It's nice that there'll be a Muppet restaurant there.
At least it seems like they're affirming their commitment to the Muppets.
Rizzo's gotten a short stick in recent memory.
He's barely represented in the Seagull movies.
I love pizza.
Give it to me.
I talked my whole group into, we must eat lunch at Pizza Rizzo.
Which is funny because Mama Melrose around the corner is good.
My family loves it.
We always have a good view.
We have to support the Muppets, especially after this poor showing at the gift shop.
We need to show them that there's interest in Muppet theme.
Does everybody know that there was a world where in a bigger Muppet area,
that space was going to be something called, there's concept art that I'm looking at right now,
that very building is labeled the Swedish Chef's Video Cooking School.
There's a giant balloon of his big head on the top.
It was going to be a whole land, right?
That's the part of the land where there's going to be a whole big ride.
I feel like we can't even get into it in this one.
I know.
But if the listeners don't know, Muppet Studios, this is the most disappointing thing of all.
The Muppet Vision 3D was to be but one part of the greater area where also this restaurant
and the Muppet movie ride, a parody of the great movie ride with Muppets front to back,
a Frankenstein scene going haywire and all the Muppets are in Peter Pan,
it's Miss Piggy or something and she's too big and the rope is breaking and that kind of shit.
So making fun of what they would go on to actually do,
like parading, like we'll put the Muppets in classic stories,
the ride parading that idea which then became what they actually went on to do.
What they do earnestly.
And there is a video somewhere, shout out to Rob Plays on YouTube, we made a little video about
this, but in that there's a clip of Jim Henson even talking about that ride and his framing of
it is so wonderfully simple where he just says, you know, it's a ride about showing the process
of making movies, only all of the information is wrong.
That's so funny.
And you also go like how in this many decades has there still not been like a ride that's a
parody of rides and the Muppets are the perfect vehicle to do that.
The Simpsons is the closest.
Oh you're right, you're right, that is the closest.
That gets there, but that also feels a little more cynical maybe I want to say.
Sure, sure, sure.
Which is maybe the beauty of the Muppets that it's,
I like the Simpsons ride.
They were sort of like, you know, the Muppets are sort of like commentary and meta and subverting
before the 90s where commentary and subverting becomes much more cynical.
It had to be a negative slant on the thing.
Like this, people, it always hit when Rizzo comes out as Mickey or when Waldo turns into Mickey at
the end, people ate that shit up.
I specifically remember both of my parents dying at it who don't have the same sense of humor
whatsoever and the whole family is literally laughing out loud together.
Such joy from that and a lot of other parts of this.
The Muppets always felt more dangerous than like the Disney characters, just a little bit.
They felt just a little bit edgy.
But not dirty.
Not dirty, so like when like Rizzo's making fun of Mickey it feels like a little dangerous.
Like you get like a little edge, you know?
And when Waldo turns into Mickey at the end.
Yeah, well, I want to say this.
I think Waldo is the Pizzeria of Muppets.
Waldo is the one thing that really doesn't age for me.
I was going to ask worst Muppet of all time is Waldo.
It's Waldo.
It's Waldo with a poet.
I'm not sure.
I totally I don't hate Sesame Street.
I don't hate Waldo that much.
I don't either.
I kind of don't like.
Well, I like him, but I hate to put him at the bottom of the list.
I don't hate him, though.
I do have an answer for this and I don't you know what?
Anyone feel free to send me something that negates this and I don't even have a hatred
of this character, but I will say that I felt very on the outside when they started using
that shrimp all the time.
Pepe.
I don't I never saw what was the source of Pepe that was funny.
Suddenly he's just around aggressively too much.
They made a big play for him to be one of the big five in the early 2000s.
This is when they had sold to a German company and no one knew what they were doing.
And I think Rizzo seemed a little too 90s and they were like the 2000s new millennium.
It's all about Pepe.
I think a little Pepe goes a long way.
I agree.
I'll say this.
I don't I don't care for Dr. Bunsen Honeydew's negligence because Bunsen Beaker.
Sorry, Beaker always ends up paying the price.
And I think that's.
Wait a minute.
This is funny, though.
Yeah, I mean, it's funny.
It's funny.
Wait, but you don't hate him the most.
No, I don't hate him.
I just don't care for his last attitude towards lab.
So you find his behavior kind of cruel, kind of cruel, kind of cruise.
Is he your least favorite Muppet, though?
See, I think he's a great straight man.
Yeah, I always loved on it.
You're being funny now.
Do you hate that he doesn't have features that he's just like a he has like no hair?
No, because that I actually think makes him special.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't know if I have like a least favorite Muppet.
I'm not sure that I totally hate a Muppet, but I just don't really get.
This is my Pepe theory.
Pepe is in Muppets tonight.
He's part of a two person act Seymour and Pepe.
And they're like the doorman to the studio where they film and Seymour is like a big fat elephant type.
Who's kind of dim and Pepe is sort of more the like wheeler dealer type.
And it would always be that they would stop the celebrity guest who was trying to come in.
It was sort of their version of scooter knocking on the door and going five minutes of show time.
It was like Pepe being like, I need to see ID or whatever his thing was.
And they'd always get into like a fight with the with the guest.
And so I think Pepe was like kind of worked as part of the duo.
And the Muppets from space, the weakest of the Muppet films, they bump Pepe way up.
Seymour is gone.
Pepe just kind of becomes a little stinker.
But in a bad movie, Pepe kind of pops.
And I think it's because it's like here is a character being played by the person who developed him.
Like the one like the original one that we love.
Right. Because that's like the movie where Frank Oz isn't puppeteering anymore.
He's dubbing in the voices later.
OK. Dave Gould is still doing gonzo, but they've kind of, as you said, domesticated him a little bit.
Pepe feels a little more pure.
So I think when a German company is buying Muppets at a point where they're that dinged,
they go, Pepe's got a little heat.
Like there's a little torque on Pepe.
We might be able to run with this.
And they start leading with him in merchandise and stuff.
But maybe they pushed it a little too.
Way too hard.
He did like Long John Silver's commercials.
Oh, I remember those.
Yeah.
Well, let's talk about the original Muppet duo, Statler and Waldorf.
Yeah, two of the greats.
Two of the greats.
Here, they're animatronics.
I think that's great.
I think some of the elements that make Muppet Vision 3D stand out and make it repeatable,
as opposed to like Honey, I Shrunk the Audience, which we talked about recently,
you get a full size Sweetums walking around.
You get a Bean Bunny animatronic.
You get Statler and Waldorf.
The Penguin Orchestra.
Chef with a gun.
And then Chef with a cannon.
Specifically, Musket, which is the funniest gun.
The funniest gun.
Musket is such a funny gun.
He's nonsense language.
I thought his nonsense speak was just hilarious as a kid.
Do you know the effect of the damage to the theaters?
Damage to the theater is really good.
Statler and Waldorf, by the way, when I got older, I realized,
oh, they're both named after hotels.
That's a joke.
But I found out another thing.
The Statler line of hotels was the first mid-range line for tourists and business travelers.
And Waldorf and Historia has always been like a super fancy hotel.
So Statler and Waldorf, I think there is an extra joke in there too.
In the contrast.
They're mismatched.
Yeah, they're not Waldorf and Historia.
They're Statler and Waldorf.
I'll throw out a couple more quick takes on why I think this has better repeat value
than something like Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
A, I think it's one of the few, if only, theme park movies,
won't include live shows, right?
Theme park movies that has an emotional arc.
I'm not saying it's more in peace, but the Bean Bunny thing,
you actually kind of get the stakes of what this guy is trying to prove.
They set up the sort of pressure of mounting the show, the big finale, the tribute to America.
And you know what?
All reshoots, all post-Jim.
Interesting.
And Frank Oz took over as director.
Wow.
Yeah, that was all like, so everything in the black void is reshoots.
Really?
And that stuff's all super fucking good.
Really good.
Another thing is, I think it's some of the best application of 3D technology I've ever seen.
I think it's still, that first gag where the logo comes out of the door is one of those,
oh, it actually feels like it's invading my space.
Yeah.
And the joke of it being a cheap gag and that you're supposed to buy it,
you're supposed to be like, oh, I'm seeing an impressive 3D movie,
and then it's just a guy with a stick, but the guy with a stick looks really good too.
Really good.
It's really impressive when it turns.
The flying pie still looks good.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Even on like a YouTube rip, that still looks good.
And again, a great one-two punch where the pie hits Fozzie in the face and Kermit says,
Fozzie, that's terrible.
And Fozzie goes, you're right, it needs more sugar.
Funny and for everybody.
I also don't know how they do the pie exactly because it seems like it's CGI,
and then at some point in an invisible cut becomes a physical pie
so that frosting can be on Fozzie's face.
And I don't, there's some weird little pops, something happens that you sense there's a cut,
but I don't really know how they bridge that gap from computer to real.
I was trying to figure that out too.
Yeah, you can't really tell.
It still looks great.
It's pretty seamless.
And I also feel like when I was, I used to watch, what was it called?
Inside Disney, the show that was on the Disney Channel.
Disney World Inside Out.
Yes, was that what it was called?
Probably both titles were shows.
Right, it was that show that George Foreman was like a correspondent on.
That's Walt Disney World Inside Out.
Right, okay, so I used to watch that obsessively,
begging my parents to bring me to the park.
So I was like, I kind of had every ride spoiled for me by that show before going on it.
So by the time I finally got to go to Disney World, it felt like sort of like
seeing my favorite band in concert and demanding they play the hits.
But I remember Muppet Vision was one of the few things where I was like,
I don't feel like I've seen all of this.
Yeah, they did not exhaust, you maybe knew about the pie,
or you maybe saw, we surrender, we surrender.
It's got a pretty healthy length to it too.
I think it's a get a real show there.
I had no sense going, I know that never was spoiled for me, the salute to America.
Or what's the name of it to say the real thing?
A salute to all nations, but mostly America.
Which is a good joke.
I have a whole section of my notes just labeled Sam the Eagle.
Sam the Eagle I think is the MVP of this.
He's a killer in this.
All those, and it's all, that's all that 70s Muppet subversion where it's kind of
Goofing on Superlism.
Exactly, exactly.
If they had a show on the air right now with a good writers,
I'm could imagine the stuff they'd be doing with Sam the Eagle.
Yeah, maybe a good conduit actually.
You need Sam the Eagle.
That's picking up merch, there he is up there on Mike.
It's not, it's from this really good line of toys, Muppet toys made by a company called Palisades.
Can I throw out something super nerdy?
I was so active on the Palisades message board.
Oh wow, really?
I am listed as a special thing, so I'm one of the packages.
Which one?
Wow, I believe it's the Pigs in Space play sets.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Do you own them or do you just, you were just
You got all the Puppets, Palisades?
Oh yeah.
They're incredible toys.
Incredible, unbelievable.
It's taken all my willpower to not, because that's the only one I have,
but I have a lot of other things upstairs from, but like it's, they're so good.
They're incredibly good, yeah.
And that company, they had like a very active message board and they would like solicit fan
sort of feedback on things and try to gauge which things.
Wow, that's wild. You really have thrown it down in the ring here of your credibility when you
message board poster.
That comes up on your Ang Lee Hulk episode.
Your co-host is giving you grief because you mentioned like, well on the
action figure message boards I frequent.
Yes, yes, right.
Which he thought is like the nerdiest pull I could have.
Not that I'm thanked on the package of an action figure when I'm 14,
because I want to spend more time in that message room than parties.
But I was listening to that episode, it's like get to the Pearl Mother stuff,
get to the Pearl Mother, like the Toy Biz Pearl Mother Marvel, like so much of this stuff.
Well we got into it also with, weirdly with, we did a Batman, an 89 Batman episode recently,
which Toy Biz had their rights to the original Batman and that sort of gives them the cachet
to make the play for the Marvel deal.
So it's like Batman not succeeding would have led to Marvel going under weirdly.
Oh my god, poor Michael Jackson bike.
Yeah, wow.
Wow.
Where was it?
Salute to all nations, we were talking about surprises in the movie and I really love that
that's just its own odd thing that the characters play into, but that isn't really, you know,
it's not like we have to make the finale some like recognized, they all sing Rainbow
Connection or something we've seen before.
Yeah.
It's really its own thing and I love those vacant dumb dolls.
A small world comedy.
It feels like a small world parody, which is another little snarky thing that's fun.
And I also like that, you know, if Sam the Eagle is a commentary on nationalism,
that it feels, and he's the only one taking this seriously, I need to make a really important
little number at the end of the show and he roped in these clearly dumber muppets to help him.
Like where did he find all these dummies to march around and dress as colonial people?
Right.
He got the most brainless idiots to follow him, which also feels like a fun little subversive
message or something.
But that's a good point that it's not a greatest hits compilation, you know?
Something like Honey I Shrunk the Audience, which is like so first and foremost kind of
like a skill show of all the effects they can use.
They feel pretty well integrated into this because they're the muppets, they can call
out the fact that it's like a theme park attraction, that it's gimmicky, but it's also like they're
like a commentary content.
It's not just Rainbow Connection in 3D, it's not the same routines, you get a little muppet
labs, like they're hitting all the basics but giving you new spins on them.
Right, and you can't get it anywhere else.
No, and in fact, you always see like Kermit on the firetruck at the end, you are looking
at 1990 MGM Studios.
And another really good 3D effect when he comes towards you with the ladder, feels like
he's there with you.
That must be a robot or something, that has to be like a mechanized version of Kermit.
Another thing I want to say, I love the sets in this thing, that main, that like Victorian
atrium where this takes place, why is it, why does it look like that?
I love that it does, I love that they're not in, in keeping with how much I love the building
itself where the thing takes place, I like that they're not in some like, you know, some
goofy kind of digital world.
They're in that long, long hallway which gives you the depth and that's another thing about
it.
I think there's good 3D movies that are full of, you know, CGI and maybe shot digitally,
I don't mean to count out that that stuff can be good but this is, I looked it up, 65
millimeter and it's, it is like a beautiful analog film on beautiful real sets with
amazingly crafted real puppets.
It's very real and cool.
I'll say another real nerdy deep cut with regards to the sets, the Palisades Muppet
Labs playset is based off the Muppet Vision Muppet Labs because the Muppet Labs on the
show is very generic looking and they were like, everyone has this memory of Muppet Labs
because those segments were so good but the only one that was kind of visually compelling
on its own, it's that weird sort of like, it looks kind of like H.G. Welles-y.
Yeah, and Beaker really takes a beating on that, like weird river, water wheel sort of
mechanic.
Huge labs.
It goes over so well.
So funny.
Do you have that playset?
I do, most definitely.
Do you have all of the toys?
I don't have all of them, I'd say I have a majority.
80%?
This is what's depressing.
I would say I had 80% at one point and now I probably have closer to 60%.
And there are a few things I gave up that I really regret.
That's harder to have like toys in New York with much smaller, you know, apartments and all.
Very true.
Do you have the Jim Henson Palisades toy?
I don't and that's a big regret.
It's very expensive now.
Of him?
There's a Jim Henson toy that Palisades made who I don't know how you got it, I don't know
if it was commercially sold.
I believe it was the Collector's Club.
I believe it was one that they all belong on.
You had to join and then yeah, there's a kind of cartoonish Jim Henson.
It's really cool looking.
This is a precedent for the Michael Eisner merch that we're talking about.
We were talking about it.
A couple weeks ago, how they should start making Michael Eisner merch.
Here's a question for you guys because I feel like you bring up a lot
how creepy Eisner was in this time period when he would do on camera stuff.
Would you insist on being like the Uncle Walt introductions hosting the specials and all of that?
I wouldn't say creepy as much as just yeah, like kind of so yeah.
When you were younger, did you feel like Eisner was working for you?
Because I remember I would watch Eisner present like Wonderful World of Disney and be like
it's Michael Eisner.
He's the magician himself, the man with the keys to Disney.
And my dad would come into the room and go,
God, can you believe Michael Eisner keeps on wedging himself in front of the camera?
And I'd be like, what are you talking about?
He's Michael Eisner.
I am completely on your side of things.
That's absolutely how I felt.
He's magical.
And have I really declared on the show before that I literally there was a time where if you
asked me in like a school report or if somebody asked what do you want to be when you grew up
and when I was probably this is probably like eight, nine years old.
My answer was I want to be the CEO of the Walt Disney Company.
Really?
Great answer.
I'm sure I could show you some report I filled out where I'm like, I'm going to be the next Eisner.
I said like, I'm going to be an animator for Disney.
That was like the Disney answer.
I might have been my answer at one point, but there was some window where it was.
It was.
I wanted to work in the team Disney building with the dwarves.
I don't think I don't think at the time I could have articulated that I had affection for him.
I don't think that that was ever.
About articulating affection now for anyone.
That's fair.
But I'm just saying at least I can maybe recognize it, but I do have it and I know now.
Yeah.
But I couldn't I wouldn't have said ever like, oh, I love that Michael.
Oh, Michael Eisner is cool.
I would have never said that.
Because we've all heard stories about Walt being prickly.
But when you watch him host and stuff appearing on camera, you're like, yeah,
you did project a good formative warmth.
Yes.
My parents like we I think we all agreed like, oh, Sunday night, got to watch the wonderful world
at Disney.
And there's of course, Michael's here and they could say this week's movie is very special to me.
And I just kind of moving rigidly with his ruddy face.
Anything where he's reacting to something unusual happening.
Goofy, what are you doing?
He seems genuinely upset.
Hollywood.
I'm messing my office.
It was a gem of the 1930s.
I walked past him on the street once.
I'd say maybe about seven or eight years ago.
I was walking with my mom near Central Park and she said, Griffin, do you see who that is?
Because she knew how much I idolized him when I was a child.
And I went, no, who is that angry, monstrous looking man?
And she said, that's Michael Eisner.
And I couldn't believe it.
And he was a show tall.
Yes.
Yeah.
Really, really tall.
And B just looked kind of like he was like muttering to himself wearing like a clean suit.
But he looked kind of like red faced and angry.
I don't think it's out of the question that way.
He's on the podcast by the end of 2019.
I mean, we would we would like that.
Let's try.
We got to try.
I don't think it's out of the realm of possibilities.
It'll be so nice.
It'll be the easy, the most like just gushing thing he's ever been a part of.
And any little dirt.
I mean, if he gives a speck of dirt, we'll just lose our minds.
Don't you think at this point he would be so appreciative of people who had nostalgia
for when he was introducing TV movies?
I would think so.
I think so.
Because I mean, I think about like I was saying, like my parents probably,
I believe also liked him because they were old enough.
Right.
That they grew up with the wonderful world at Disney when Walt was introducing stuff.
So it's like, oh, now Michael's the head of the company and he does that.
We'll do a whole PowerPoint presentation for him on different merch that he would approve
of himself, maybe like we would just be like, how do you think about this doll of you?
I mean, he should have a vinyl nation at least.
At the very least.
But I think I said it should be like a hundred dollar figure, a hundred dollar like.
Oswald over there.
If we put you on a T-shirt and we can bulk order from T-public, would you come back and sign
like the show?
Well, we're going to sell as merch.
That you on the podcast, the ride T-public page will become the exclusive.
Yeah.
License source.
I mean, the licensing.
You should sign a deal with him and say, we want to be, we want to have the exclusive rights to
Eisner.
Eisner and Marvel McFay.
Forgottable.
Six.
They're sitting around.
Give it to us.
By the end of 2019, I think we should also declare that we will retain the right.
We will find a way to buy the rights to Astroworld's Marvel McFay and his animal.
Yeah, that feels like there's some meat on that bone.
I mean, I think you could really flip that and make a profit on that.
I also think that with the battle, there would just be tracking down who has the rights.
I keep.
It's persistence.
I have so many notes to myself of stuff to do.
It's like, find who owns Marvel McFay.
Can I ask?
Which has to be Six Flags.
It has to be Warner Brothers, honestly.
But it's probably so buried in like a deep file.
I mean, there's this thing not to bring it back around to a self-serving thing, but Ben
Edlin, who created The Tick, which was like an independent comic book published by his
local comic book store, he retained the key rights to the characters, but then did the cartoon show
Fox Kids and they retained anything that was created first in the cartoon show.
So a lot of supporting cast, not taking Arthur, but a lot of supporting villains and heroes
Fox Kids owned, which then Disney bought.
So Disney has all these supporting characters.
When we do like conventions and stuff and people are like, hey, any chance of this?
And the answer is like it's somewhere in a file at Disney and they can't be bothered to get on the
phone to agree to a deal.
Right.
It's not worth it to them.
Chairface Chippendale.
Chairface is still, is in the comic first.
Okay.
That's what I thought.
Yeah.
Chairface is in the comic first.
This is the case with a lot of stuff, like maybe not a lot, but like Ninja Turtles, for instance,
there was an Archie comic series that I loved and they made up some of those characters are
kind of just floating in owned by Archie maybe still because they've now been in an
into like it's these weird limos.
They're never going to use them.
Disney is not going to do anything with like American Maid or Dinosaur Neil.
There's no interest there.
I don't know.
We should roll into Disney Plus and see if we can get a spin off.
Dinosaur Neil show.
I have wondered like, yeah, why haven't any of the live actions had American Maid?
You had such a cool costume.
Right.
Because Captain Liberty and Batman Well were both workarounds for Fox Kids having the rights.
Oh, it sucks.
And then Disney by proxy.
Everyone needs to wake up and realize what they have.
Marvel.
Marvel McFay might be like owned by someone who died and their like niece never went into their.
It's just in a safe deposit box.
They might be lost to the ages.
I'm all right.
So that means Disney must own Eek the Cat, right?
Can I get the cat?
I think Disney has Eek the Cat.
Oh yeah, Eek the Cat.
Who owns Louie Anderson as a child?
Disney.
I think it's Disney.
It's not Louie himself.
It's not the actual child.
Louie does not own the image of his father.
Louie Anderson does not own the image of his father as a cartoon.
Disney owns the first nine years of Louie Anderson's life.
They own his memories.
He can't reference them on a podcast without flipping them a check.
If he goes through an old photo album, yeah, technically he has to.
They get residuals.
We're over the two hour mark.
Let me get to a couple of things.
One really thing that really depressed me when I read it and I didn't realize it.
2004 Disney takes Jim Henson's name off of the show because they bought the Muppets.
Wow.
They don't have to do the license.
Let's say all this.
Muppet Vision 3D was made in a period where Disney was trying to buy the Muppets.
Jim Henson died.
The deal went bust.
They did it as a license thing.
Even then, there was a strong possibility that the movie would not even be put into the parks.
The family was so sour on Disney by that point.
Frank Oz was a person among other people.
The public deserves to see the last thing Jim made.
That was the emotional trump card that got it into the parks.
Yeah, they had to pay a license thing.
By the time they bought it, then screw this.
It's like if Pixar doesn't need to be up here anymore if the deal, the license deal went away.
The main reason I was reading Jim Hill in high school was I was so interested in he
was the only guy writing about the business dealings of the Muppets and Pixar.
It was that more than the theme park stuff.
Before that, I had never been a like imagineering rumor guy.
I liked the parks.
And then through trying to track what is Disney doing with the Muppets,
I started getting keyed into all of that stuff.
But it was like the last thing Eisner did when he was already on the way out of the company.
They had negotiated his payout and his exit.
He bought the Muppets.
And it kind of felt like it was a vindictive thing to be like that was my waterloo.
That was the one I could never, the Moby Dick I couldn't catch.
And then he saddled Disney with the Muppets and Disney was like we wouldn't have money.
We don't know what to do with them.
Now we're stuck with this expensive purchase because Eisner wanted to stick it to somebody.
To dead Jim Henson.
They'll be back on Disney Plus.
Like it's all hands on deck.
That's everything they've said sort of.
But that's that weird sort of that period when, well what?
I mean I guess do they buy the Muppets after the California Adventure Outpost opens?
Yes.
Because it's 2004.
Yeah so 2001 is the opening.
Right but then there was a long period where they just weren't doing anything with them.
No one had an idea.
It wasn't like get them so we can do this.
No they did Muppet Wizard of Oz for Wonderful World of Disney.
And they did like one Christmas special.
That thing with Quentin Tarantino.
Oh yeah.
He has an actor in it.
There's a good talk show appearance.
You won't believe who he plays.
Oh boy.
Take one guess.
I don't know the world of it.
As he says somebody's dad, he's Gonzo's dad.
Quentin Tarantino.
He pulls out a sword, pulls out a cantana.
He threatens Kermit.
Yeah.
Right he wants to make a kill bill with Kermit.
And the movie grinds to a halt to cut to him in a conference room
pitching Kermit on a martial arts epic.
A dynamic location if ever there was one.
A conference room.
There's an endearing and weird interview with him on Conan talking about it.
Where he gets to take a picture with a couple of his favorite muppets
which are Janis and Rolf I believe.
Then he talks about having a crush on Janis.
Excuse me.
He probably took a picture with Janis's feet.
Well that's weird.
Oh no.
Can I say something sad about Janis?
Do you guys know the fact?
Oh I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Okay in addition to that miserably this is the final work of Jim Henson.
This is the last Richard Hunt.
The last Richard Hunt.
Richard Hunt died.
Richard Hunt was very sick while this was being made.
Richard Hunt is the puppeteer behind Scooter.
In this production of Scooter, Statler, Beaker and Sweetums.
But he died of complications from HIV AIDS.
And he was sick by the time they were shooting this.
He dubbed the voices but he was not on set puppeteering.
He was actually one of Henson's sons as Sweetums.
He was only 40 years old.
Super young.
So both, Statler and Waldorf passed away almost immediately.
That's wild.
And there's one pickup line in there somewhere that is not Henson.
That somebody else doing the voice.
But other than that it's the last time the two of them.
But so he was sick and they knew it wasn't looking good by the time they were shooting this.
So on the way into Miss Piggy's musical number two characters go from the atrium world into her music.
They like ride a bike into her musical number and that's Janis and Scooter.
And that is a tribute to Richard Hunt.
I always noticed that in the background of the shot.
But I didn't realize.
That's why it's them.
You always hear about there's a whole generation.
And her team might look totally different today if a whole generation was not just devastated by AIDS.
Scooter is another one like Rolf where there wasn't as clear of a game.
And when the performer died there was no character.
And all of these really.
I guess you see Sweetums.
Yeah and Sweetums was more visually distinctive.
But like in the same way that Rolf was kind of like an old timer.
Scooter was just kind of like a nice kid.
Yeah.
So much of it was like that was apparently the character that was like closest to Richard Hunt.
His sort of vibe and his energy.
And then when people just do a Scooter impression now.
I mean they worked them a little bit into the modern movies.
It just kind of feels like well it's like nice that they're acknowledging he used to be important.
But Scooter's like the original Walter.
They are kind of the same just a guy.
Scooter also.
Dependable guy.
He's a big fan.
Also trying his best.
He is like the practical producer.
He's the.
The.
Scott Adset.
30 Rock.
Yeah.
He's the what's the title that associate producer.
That's the one that's either given out as a vanity credit or they did everything to make a movie happen.
There's no common ground.
The idea with Scooter too is that there is a Muppet named JP Gross who is like their Muppet tribute to
Lord Lugrade.
Who owns the theater and demands that they hire his nephew to work.
And everyone's like Jesus Christ nepotism.
And Scooter shows up and so Scooter's kind of got like a chip on his shoulder to prove to them
that he can like he can fuck with the Muppets you know that he can like carry his weight.
And so like you know Muppet show is not very serialized.
But in later seasons they start to let Scooter every once in a while have a musical performance.
And Kermit always has this like would you believe it.
One of our own our little gopher wants to do a little song and I thought it was always very endearing
this like quiet narrative of like Scooter earns their respect and occasionally they let him sing a
little song.
Wow.
That's great.
He's a good guy.
This guy's a good guy.
There's a lot of heartwarming aspects.
It's a shame in that newer ABC show Scooter's whole thing was that he was just addicted to nicotine gum.
Like like Marin.
Scooter was the Marin of the show.
He was beaten down by too many failed pilots.
That's what that show feels like.
Fuck pilot season coming up again.
Don't put your industry bitterness into the Muppets for God's sake.
If they can't have hope then who can?
Wow.
What else have we what have we missed?
Oh Constantine.
Okay so from Muppets most wanted.
And this lasted like two years from like 2014 to 2016 or something.
Or no I think the years might be wrong.
It lasted a while.
They stuck in a Constantine segment into the pre-show.
Which is interesting.
The pre-show was already great but it was Constantine of course the Kermit with the mole.
Evil Kermit who's now become just a meme.
Yeah who's now just a meme.
He's just like oh wow the show.
Like he said something.
He takes over and does nothing.
And then they just cut back to a few minutes later in the pre-show.
I have to interrupt.
It's the very which the trope I usually like like who are taking over the fee.
But then he doesn't he just talks there's no point to it.
And it really shows the lack of cultural impact of Constantine or any of the new movies.
That was in the parks for two years and I only just heard about it yesterday.
Yeah I had no idea.
It's also it's weird that now the actor the performer behind Constantine's
is the one who took over Kermit.
And the whole bit to Constantine is this is a very bad Kermit impression.
Which I like Constantine.
But it still was an odd choice to be like the guy who did the purposefully bad Kermit
is now doing real Kermit.
Has there been a big thing with his voice as Kermit already?
They've done like a couple of these like YouTube like Muppet Musings.
Uh huh.
Where it's like a fucking eight minute not eight minute.
Second video where it's like if you don't look out for life it might hit you in the
back of like whatever dumb sort of like.
Hi ho what up fam.
Make sure to click here here and here to like and subscribe.
I like that.
That's like they you know made a big deal like it was such a news story about like
firing Kermit you know which everyone turned into like an emotional thing not really knowing
the intricacies of the Whitmire thing.
And then they were like here it is.
Finally the first debut of the new Kermit and it was like a video where he's like oh
hi didn't see you there and then like walks away or something.
I don't think they've done anything with him since.
Yeah.
What a rough property.
Kermit drinking the tea.
Yeah.
Has had more of a cultural impact.
Truly.
Than a lot of the newer Muppet stuff.
It's that and the Kermit facing Constantine with the hood which is like a parallel to
the like Spider-Man pointing at himself.
Yes.
It's any sort of shadow version of yourself.
Those are the most impactful Muppet things and they're things that the audience has taken
back like that the audience has remixed and used.
Yeah it's very odd.
I like the Constantine song.
I think that's my favorite thing in either the two new movies.
Yeah yeah that's the main thing keeping me afloat on the new movies of the songs.
I think songs are fantastic.
Songs are good yeah life's a happy song.
Yeah I like that song.
I'm just down the only reason I'm down on the first single one is because like I was just
so depressed at like Kermit in his mansion alone.
Yeah.
Being a sad sack.
It like bummed me out so much and I was like this is it.
It's a bummer.
I don't like this.
All your favorite Luke Skywalker, Kermit, all of these guys are.
Look we have never talked about Last Jedi and today will be no exception.
No.
I will not talk about it.
It's way later.
There's nothing bad that happens when you talk about Last Jedi.
I will not talk about it at all.
I might love it.
I got a good feeling about this.
The listener might know I love it.
We don't know.
I was talking to someone who's like an editor like a big sort of entertainment but like a higher end
website and he was saying he still keeps on getting pitches where people are like I just want you to
know I got a hot pitch.
I figured out conclusively why the Last Jedi is bad and from like respectable culture writers
and he's like I don't want to litigate this.
It doesn't matter.
It's a while later and there's another one coming.
Maybe save your energy.
People are coming at it with the energy of but I'm finally going to win the argument.
It's an arm wrestling match.
It's a year later.
All the arguments from the original trilogy and the prequels have been settled.
It's so creamy.
I'm sure it'll go away soon.
We all know who shot first and it's always interesting when it gets brought up again.
Let's keep going over this please.
What have we missed?
We sort of breezed past the pre-show other than quoting some lines in this Constantine thing.
The three monitors.
That is such a clever.
If you never got a chance to go on this and please let me shout out Martin's Vids we have
before this great archivist of these videos.
God bless this man who took the three monitors that are in the pre-show room
and stitched them together.
It's sort of a reconstructed version of how these things work.
There's so much fun with the three monitors where
sometimes it's the same image on all of them and it's gonzo dancing and you think it's three of
the same but then one drops something and the pattern deviates or you watch the characters
cross from one to the far left one all the way to the far right one.
I think that stuff's super faulty action between the three monitors.
I honestly don't know how they did it.
Did they line up three cameras?
Was it that simple or are those three different takes?
What a weird thing to have to direct.
That's a good pre-show.
All the props, all the ACME corporation.
There's a waiting area.
It's so fun.
When I'm watching the video it's just packed full of stuff.
That's the rewatchability or whatever you would call it.
Not rideability but that's why there's so much stuff and so many little things.
You don't get tired of as much as other comedy theme park stuff.
I was going to say you guys talk a lot about and it's really made me think about how hard it is
to write theme park comedy because you need things that can play to everyone and that can play for a
long time.
I feel like Muppet Vision 3D is the most purely successful comedic attraction.
Maybe it is.
Yeah, I think that's great.
With the right IP to do it because the puppets have always had their funny kids into parents.
Those jokes still play.
You go see it at MGM studios and the audience still laughs a ton.
And they have a little bit of an out in that some of the jokes are growners on purpose.
And then you get Statler and Waldorf as a commentary on Wasn't That Bad.
They're the greatest comedic conceit of all time.
Being able to have a Statler and Waldorf baked into your show where you can win back any bad joke
by commenting on it and acknowledging it.
And how fun that if you're seeing Muppet Vision for the ninth time that your eyes can wander and
like I'm just going to stare at those Statler and Waldorf puppets doing nothing for a while.
Let me just pick one animatronic penguin to watch for a while.
I like this is just a fun thing.
I didn't it's just a thing like it makes sense when you hear it.
But it's like they have three arms when they wave the white flags at the end.
It's obviously a separate arm.
It's not their puppet arms.
So there's just separate arms that come up with the white flags.
Oh, interesting.
And there's three.
You know, yeah, yeah.
Well, no, I'm just saying they have three arms.
So they have their two normal arms and then they duck.
They can't get an animatronic to reach and grab a little pop and hold it in their chest.
Sure.
So I read it and went, of course.
Oh, that's cool.
And a similar thing to that.
It's multiple Swedish chefs.
And they're all on a big turntable.
So when one is done with their specific task, it all rotates.
And number two is up and number three is.
That's great.
I'll say this because we talked about like, oh, yeah, there's Muppets coming to Disney Plus.
I think we like have all agreed like go back to the Muppets.
The core they're putting on a show.
Lot of hearts.
And I think the thing to look at of like, well, how do they can the Muppets comment on like the
like the current showbiz, all the nonsense streaming sites and like there's a new Netflix
thing every day.
The example I would point out is the new run of Nancy comic strips where it's like the
the core of the characters.
But there's all of this like Nancy adding movies to her queue and never watching them.
And it doesn't it feels modern and it hits on like modern anxieties and stuff.
And it's like.
I think that's a great example.
The other one I've been thinking of this whole episode is at the Disneyland Hotel, they had a
channel that was just playing those new Mickey Mouse shorts over and over again.
And I have been dismissive of them just because I was like, this looks like some unnecessary
redesign of all the characters.
But those things are actually funny.
Yeah.
And they actually give the characters like a personality again.
After like decades of being like Mickey can't be too much of any one thing because he has to work
as a thing that can sell bath towels.
You walk like he gets angry.
He can be petty.
Yeah.
Like they're funny gags in them.
And those have a guy.
Those have a guy overseeing them all.
And he's like an animation life.
I think it's a Rocko's modern life guy.
Oh, you feel the fact that they have like a clear voice and a take and a comedic sensibility.
And you need to have someone come in who like gets the history of the thing, but also isn't
just trying to recreate it.
Yeah, right, right, right.
It's tough.
It's very tough with the Muppets of all the things I would like to work on.
Muppets sounds cool, but it feels like the most daunting to me.
I would be terrified.
But it's like, yeah, it's like Batman.
There's been a million great versions of Batman.
Right.
Like all different things, but it's like Muppets.
I'm like, I don't know what the hell.
I don't know what the secret is.
I don't really have the answer.
I feel like I don't like, but I don't know what.
I think the other scary thing is they need to develop a lot of new characters.
Like I think you keep the main core, but I think you need to get some performers creating
their own characters that they own fully.
And so often the new characters are plot functions.
I mean, like Walter's a plot function.
Constantine's a plot function.
Right, right, right.
Let someone workshop something until they come up with a fun voice, a fun character
design and mix them in with the classics.
I got a big one.
The next Muppet thing cannot be a cameo fest.
Every single Muppet thing ever since Jim Dot.
There's one person.
How about that?
Like I think everybody likes the host of the Muppet show.
Or like we like Prince on Muppets tonight.
But all of these movies are just like and then Elizabeth Banks is herself and Jack Black
is himself twice.
He shows up once and then they build to a giant cameo at the end that ends up being
Jack Black again.
Right.
It's one of those infuriating things that like stops me from liking that movie more.
But I think it really does damage the IP.
What is this new Muppets about?
Well, it really it puts a lot of holes in it if it's dependent on Ty Burrell coming
in, then you have it's not an IP anymore.
And the cameos are good in the original movies because the gag isn't look who it is
doing this.
And I feel like there are a lot of them in the new movies where it's like why is Sarah
Silverman playing the waitress who sits Amy Adams at a table in a scene with no Muppets
in it?
Why is James McAvoy randomly like the delivery man for UPS with no lines?
You know, and they're like a weird level of like is the joke supposed to be?
I can't believe they did this because then you have like there's the scene in Muppets
at Manhattan where Kermit and Piggy are fighting in Central Park and like Gregory Hines comes
in and tries to mediate the fight.
And as a kid, I had no idea who Gregory Hines was.
But I was like, this is a funny scene or this guy's giving a funny performance.
Just the poster of Muppets most wanted.
One day I went down to Disneyland right before that movie came out and they were giving out
puzzles that were that poster.
And nothing glues it more to that year that it's like, look, it's the Muppets and Ty Burrell
and Tina Fey and Ricky Gervais.
That's just like stuck in like the 2010s.
Gervais is especially giant because that's the last moment where we had tolerance for him.
But Jason, were you offended by him?
Were you offended by his presence?
That must be the problem.
I mean, you guys, this was very enlightening on Blank Shack.
I found out he's an atheist.
Well, let's not say that too loudly.
It's kind of like The Last Jedi where it's a little too hot for people when you discuss it.
He doesn't want it getting out there.
Yeah, you guys are a little chill about it.
Sorry if I'm blowing up your spot.
Yeah, he's going to be upset.
Well, let me say this in all that.
What's one thing that the pretty successful timeless Muppet Vision 3D does not have cameos?
There's not one cameo in the thing.
Yeah, I don't know.
I think that helps it.
It's a flea Muppet experience.
Yeah, I agree with what you said.
Give some Henson people license to create new characters.
Bring on some young, excited comedy writers who loved it growing up.
I'll say that around people I've met around UCB and the comedy community.
Big, big love of the Muppets.
That's my thing.
I just go like-
Muppets, musical theater, professional wrestling.
It all makes sense that then people grew up liking this stuff and now I want to be theatrical.
I also feel like the best model for the modern Muppet show is Comedy Bang Bang.
That's the vibe of that thing of just the chaos of people storming in.
And Aukerman kind of is like a Kermit figure where he's just trying to hold it all together.
Not a sad sack.
Little put upon, little stressed out.
There's people in it as themselves, but there's also somebody doing a character.
They're doing their thing that they're good at.
It's not purely-
There's this great clip.
I saw, I think, the Museum of Moving Image in New York City opened this whole Muppet wing
and they acquired a lot of the Henson archives and they have this incredible permanent exhibit now.
And when they acquired all that stuff, Frank Oz did this event where he spoke about his
history with the Muppets and they played a bunch of rare clips.
And they had this one clip that was outtakes from them doing a bit for Sesame Street,
a show that's ostensibly supposed to be educational.
And they can't get through the bit because they keep on cracking up.
And there's another one like that where it's for Emmett Otter's Christmas,
where it's outtakes with them riffing but in the puppets about things going wrong on set.
And you get the sense that these guys were making each other laugh.
They were having fun doing the thing in the same way that good comedy podcasts and bit shows do
where it's like they're trying to break each other as much as-
Yeah.
It was an organic-
You want that vibe to Muppet stuff.
Yeah.
And if it can't be the old people, the people who did it before,
like the way SNL regenerates, it should be people who have a camaraderie and a shared sensibility.
But that's why I think you need to go half new, half old.
Sure, yeah, that makes sense.
Bring in a bunch of new people so people can have the fun of exploring the characters,
making the new discoveries, adding new depths onto them.
I was a PA at a comedy festival like 12, 13 years ago now, and Puppet Up was one of the main shows
and that was their adult sort of improvised puppet. And no matter how you feel about that
sort of thing, they were gifted improvisers and they were like Henson Light, because I started
talking to them about working with Henson stuff because I was like, I mean, 2007,
not great for Henson stuff, but I was like, hey, a lot of shows out, TV shows on DVD,
are we going to get Muppet Babies DVDs? One guy was like, we're working on it.
I just feel like there's such a rich library there. And I feel like if Henson had lived,
the Henson studios could have kept growing and growing.
And I know some people who work on Sesame and Henson and these sort of adjacent things,
who I forced to become friends with me so I can shake stories out of them and stuff.
And so many of them are just like, yeah, the landscape isn't great right now.
We all got into doing this because we love this stuff and now we're kind of doing stuff
that doesn't feel totally on point. You know?
Hummer.
Heidi, shaking up an entire culture is very tough. And you know, like,
Disney was in such a rough run post-Walt because there was so much what would Walt do and not
let's do something for God's sake.
And I feel like the Roy years kind of mirror the Brian Henson years.
The relative who understood the person a lot and didn't necessarily have the same vision
for the creative aspects.
You need an Eisner.
You talk about puppeteers breaking each other up and bloopers and stuff.
You ever seen the bloopers from the Muppets at Walt Disney World?
No, I don't think I have.
Oh, man.
It's all very good. But the first cup, the first minute of it or so is Fawzi and Fawzi's mom
doing a scene with Eisner and he keeps fucking up.
And they're like, razzin' him. And you're going, oh my God, this is like,
he's trying to do like a hostile takeover of this entity.
And the actual characters are down on their knees at the Grand Floridian
giving him shit.
I mean, it's like an actual Muppet villain trying to like kick them out of the theater.
Yeah, yeah, very much so.
And then you put then in the actual finished product is this crazy thing where they all like,
he gets like a little bit of he gets a stain on his shirt from Fawzi and then all the Muppets
run in and then they've torn up his clothes instead of fixing it.
And then they run out and he turns to the camera and goes, they're here.
The actual villain in that show is my boy Charles Groten, right?
One of the best human Muppet performers. He always knew exactly how to kind of move the
Muppet wavelength.
Yeah, the great Muppet caper. That was before Muppet Take Man?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's the second one.
The answer is, so no cameos except for Charles Groten.
Except for Groten.
And Michael Eisner.
Siegel wrote him into the Muppets and he turned it down.
He wanted him to play the same character from Great Muppet Caper and he was like,
it's not the same without Jim.
I don't want to do victory lap stuff.
Groten also, I think, you know, famous for being a little cantankerous.
Oh, sure.
But it is true that it's not the same without Jim and there is this, I do have this bittersweet
feeling talking about this thing that like, it is, I don't know, it's this like, it's like this last
stop of what train you thought was going to keep going and going.
It's a bummer.
And I think it's really special for that reason.
Yeah, I really worry about the threat of them getting rid of it at Disney World because it
feels like it's such an important cultural moment in the history of these characters.
Yeah.
Especially because it is the swan song for a lot of these people in the eras and the techniques
and all of that sort of stuff.
I know we've already been going for seven and a half hours,
but have any of you seen the Defunctland video about what the plans were to do after
the Muppet takeover of the park?
Yeah.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Where they were going to re-theme everything.
It was the year after Mickey's birthday.
And they were going to take the year off.
Right.
The characters are going away for a while because they're exhausted.
It wasn't Mickey's birthday.
It was the anniversary.
The 35th.
Right.
The big five are going on vacation.
The Muppets are taking over.
Right.
And they were going to paint the castle green.
Wasn't it Kermit the Matterhorn or something?
Yes, that's what it was.
The Matterhorn was going to have Kermit eyes be painted green.
Yeah.
And they were just going to work them in all over the park as if they were poorly running the place.
Like animal chasing people around in Pirates.
I like this idea.
It sounds so much fun.
That is so much fun.
And of course, it would never happen.
It certainly won't happen now.
No.
Like when everything is so watched and gone over with a fine tooth comb.
Yeah.
I mean, just to reiterate this one last time, that's what startled me about watching these
Mickey shorts in the hotel was it felt like they weren't as closely guarded as all the Mickey stuff.
Yes.
Of the last 30 years.
And I wish they would similarly kind of let go and be like, we're accepting pitches from anybody
on Muppets stuff.
Someone come in with a take.
I think they're kind of doing that with those Looney.
There's like 200 Looney Tunes shorts or something.
And they've all been farmed out to different animators and comedy writers and stuff.
Cautiously optimistic that some good stuff will come out of that.
So that and Disneyland app, say where your cheese fries are.
Let me search by item.
That's really smart.
We'll find the best cheese fries location.
I will vow to you.
We'll find the best place in Disneyland resort to get cheese fries.
I want to be able to crack open the app, search cheese fries.
It goes, here's where they are.
I mobile order.
And the time it takes me to walk to that stand, then the item's ready.
There should be a way to reveal secret menu items on the app because I don't think those
mozzarella sticks are available to mobile order.
I don't know that they are.
There has to be some secret you touch on the app.
The interface is not very helpful unless you know exactly what you want and from where.
Yeah, they need to do some upgrades.
Which at the Anaheim Park, a lot of people do go regularly.
So kind of get that.
But for people who haven't been there much or been there before at all,
if you have a kid and the kid's breaking down, it's like, I want cheese fries or I want a burger.
Put that search, universal search in there.
Or if you have a grown adult son who you're hanging out with at Disneyland who's breaking
down, I want cheese fries.
It's also a problem.
Sure.
I think also they should add a Jason's picks filter because I'm here waiting for you to
tweet back about the ice cream tips.
And I was driving back and forth from a bizarre commercial audition.
I don't blame you and I hope the audition went well.
I was replying to you in the drive through of a Taco Bell.
I just feel like I know like you have takes on all of this and I want them to go to you
and put a little Jason banner, you know, on the items that you would order from each place.
It's like a video store giving their person that works there, give their picks.
Yeah.
The Treat Master General has decided his decree.
Reporting for duty.
Wait, wait, wait.
See every scoop.
That's good.
That's pretty good.
Right?
Wonderful.
You know what?
If I had put based on what I knew about you and your nerdy leanings and your work,
I would have put money on the fact that this episode would have been a two and a half hour.
Yeah.
And I'm glad it was.
I had a great time.
Griffin Newman, you survived the ride.
What an honor.
Come back.
Come back anytime.
And I don't even like cutting it off.
I feel like it's just like it's a card issue at this point.
It's a it's at some point that it's going to it's going to just burst into smoke.
It's like a muppet item.
Just for safety.
Yeah.
But thanks so much for being here.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
I would tick season one's available now on Amazon.
Season two will be coming out semi shortly.
OK.
Next couple of months.
I don't know if I want to officially say when.
Sure.
But I'm not waiting to promote season two.
I'm plugging season one.
Get people thinking about it.
I want people thinking and me and Giffin.
We want to get American made in there.
I know.
Turn off Jack.
Take a break from rewatching Jack Ryan.
I know.
America has Jack Fever.
I want them to move over and get Lyme disease.
This is Maisel isn't the only marvelous person.
And Arthur.
Isn't the only neurotic Jew on Amazon Prime.
Let's get a little Arthur representation going on.
That's what I'm waiting for is the big like Arthur meets Maisel.
Oh yeah.
Full stones meet the Jetsons.
You got to do that.
You got to learn how to talk faster though.
I can talk pretty fast.
Speed it up.
But watch that please and Blink Check with Giffin David.
Wherever you listen to podcasts.
Yeah.
So happy to have you.
What else on our end?
Like we said for hot pizza riso.
Hotter than the pizza itself which may be lukewarm.
That's what it sounds like.
Go to Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
We can have it out by the time this comes out.
Yeah probably.
We'll figure out that math.
And check us out on the regular stuff on Twitter, Instagram, RT public.
Rate and review us on iTunes.
Did I miss anything gentlemen?
Five stars on iTunes specifically.
Please.
You're right.
So good.
Help keep this little this Muppet Theater running.
And just everyone's respect the ice cream Gotti.
Let's start.
Send Aaron a text to start drawing up that shirt.
Get the ice cream Gotti.
See you at Everett Scoop.
All right.
See you next time.
Bye-bye.
Forever.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Sileo,
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.