Five, four, three, two, one.
Cast the Ride, The Second Gate, your exclusive home
for details on Disneyland's lesser boats.
I'm Scott Gertner, joined by Jason Sheridan
and Mike Carlson, how you doing guys?
Hi, yes, doing fine.
Jason, are you particularly excited
about talking about a boat?
Yeah, you know I am, Michael, you know I am.
As Jimmy Buffett's famous song says,
there's something about a boat.
Something about a boat.
And those, as Brian Wilson's famous song goes,
is a sail on sailor, which is not applicable
because we're not talking about sail boats.
So we're, all this sailor could be on a keel boat.
We're talking about keel boats, the Mike Fink keel boats.
Now, when we started talking about
what the Patreon was gonna be, a long time ago,
I had this sea ticket idea, a way to, you know,
kind of quick and dirty acknowledge
some of the odd little attractions.
And this to me is the ultimate one.
It's like the main one, I kept name checking.
Let's do the episode about the Mike Fink keel boats.
Because to me, just from that name,
it just like kind of sounds odd and obscure and sad.
I don't like, not, the lack of familiarity
with what is a keel boat and who is Mike Fink.
You're not familiar with the King of the River?
I was not until now.
Now tell me how much you were, or you, Mike.
Mike Fink was one of Jason's favorite characters
in fiction, of course.
I feel like I used to catch the Davy Crockett,
whether it be the TV show or the re-cut versions
in the movies on the Disney Channel,
especially back in the early days of Disney Channel
when they were mostly showing like,
library content, their archive content.
I feel like my dad, my dad certainly,
the child of the 60s and 50s, like,
he knew Davy Crockett would tell us
when we would go to, oh, it's Davy Crockett.
You clearly, clearly, King of the, yes.
King of the Wild Frontier.
Mike Fink is King of the River,
even though in the boat race, Davy Crockett does beat him.
It was a nine, 10, 11 year old,
did you know who Mike Fink was?
Was the name familiar?
It was not to me.
No, not really.
I would see it around like Disney World, maybe.
Like, if it was on the boat or Tom Sawyer Island,
I was probably like, oh, that's probably Davy Crockett's
friend or Tom Sawyer's friend or something like that.
That's exactly what I thought.
It just, totally intro at these are,
this was a kind of boat that is along the rivers of America
in both Disneyland and Disney World.
These boats circle Tom Sawyer Island.
And I hear Tom Sawyer and I hear Mike Fink.
And I thought Mike Fink was like a little buddy of Tom Sawyer.
I thought that until I started researching this episode.
I just never looked into it, but I was like,
he's like a little, he's a little scrappy guy.
Hey, I'm Mike Fink.
He's like some little weirdo who wants to catch June bugs
with Tom.
Yeah, he does sound, in my head,
he was always like a little kid or something.
Oh boy, I'm Mike Fink.
It's his little curt name, Mike Fink.
Mike Fink sounds like Willy Wonka kid or something,
or Mike TV.
Like it's in my head, I guess that's what the connection is.
I don't know if you why, and the voice I'm doing
has a little bit of that attitude.
He's like a little pipsqueak.
Yeah.
You can't trust that ride.
Maybe he took too many tickets from ya.
But he's, no, in fact, is a Davy Crockett character.
But which makes more sense to me because I was always like,
why would a little pipsqueaky kid have a line of boats?
Right.
And did Tom Sawyer, were there a lot of boats around?
I guess so, right?
Tom Sawyer was, did he go on river boats?
I don't know much about Tom Sawyer.
Jason, you were childhood friends with him?
Tom Sawyer and Huck Finn spent a lot of time around.
Rafting.
Rafting and river boats and stuff.
I think Huck Finn got into more mischief.
Of course, Jim took that raft down the river.
Sure.
That's a con man.
Fell into like a Romeo and Juliet,
Hatfield, McCoy situation, ended up in the middle of that.
Keep going.
Tom Sawyer, I read Huck Finn in high school.
I never, I haven't really read Tom, so what, maybe like.
Yeah, I know a lot less about Tom than I do about Huck.
Yeah, is the book, are the books less good?
Is it one book?
I don't know, boy.
I can't tell.
There's two books.
There's also, there's Tom Sawyer came first
and that was more a children's adventure.
Huckleberry Finn was always more, which were a book.
At some point, there was also like a Tom Sawyer agent
of the US or Tom Sawyer.
There is a thing where he is like a spy.
What, really?
And that is how they justified having Tom Sawyer
in the Leave Extraordinary Gentlemen movie.
Cause Twain wrote a story about him as a spy?
Where he is like a spy or an intelligence,
like in the, you know, something in the army, like.
So it marked, everyone's complaining these days
about people, too much IP, leaning on stuff,
but he was using his own IP.
He used his own IP.
And old Tom Sawyer as a spy.
That's interesting.
I didn't know that.
Joey on Friends.
Yeah.
Doing some continuing,
he's one of the Extraordinary Gentlemen?
Not in the comics.
In the comics, the comics are very much like a tribute
to like British Pope of the various century,
19th century, 20th century, 21st century.
The movie, they're just like,
it's all these book people and they're all bad ass.
Like that's how it gets translated
into a big Hollywood movie.
I see, I see.
Well, in this case, we are talking about Mike Fink,
who is not a fictional character, but in fact, real man.
And there's a lot of fun to be had
in talking about the real man, Mike Fink,
but let's go backwards and talk about the attraction
a little bit.
As I mentioned, a very early attraction in Disneyland.
It is a, it was an actual sea ticket.
Some of the things that we talk about
with this name construct premise,
or were done beyond the ticketing system.
This was an actual sea ticket,
and I think it was a very good way
to dispose of unwanted seas,
because the other boats along the rivers of America,
the Mark Twain, the Columbia,
and the Davy Crockett canoes were all Ds.
So this was a little,
and I think it was probably hard to find good seas.
I don't know what else was a sea,
but you know, sea feels like a thing
probably from my mom's era.
You talked about like the stress
in trying to get rid of the tickets you didn't want.
I'm sorry, just interrupt.
So it's the Adventures of Tom Sawyer,
then the Adventures of Alckivarri Finn,
then Tom Sawyer Abroad,
and then Tom Sawyer Detective.
Whoa. Yeah.
Really? Yeah.
If you haven't read that though.
I haven't read it, but I think it's in the public domain.
Detective. I think you can find it pretty easy.
In what era was he a detective?
Like significantly later than,
are we talking about a- Oh yeah,
I think he grew up a little,
yeah, I think he's a little older.
Is he as, is it more like 16
or more like hard-boiled 65?
I am not 100% sure.
We gotta get back to that.
We gotta- We gotta revisit.
No. The Tom Sawyer franchise.
This feels like a big budget movie franchise
waiting to happen.
Yeah. And it will,
once somebody realizes it's up for grabs.
I had the same thought though
when I was going through all this Davy Crock
and Mike Fink stuff too.
I go, oh, this is ripe for a comeback,
for a Disney comeback.
Yeah, true.
And it seems like they should be
trying to figure out how to do that.
I think Disney in general needs to figure out
an old West thing.
Oh yeah.
Cause it'll justify building more stuff
in different frontiers,
putting characters into Frontierland rides
as they briefly discussed with the Lone Ranger,
but it didn't play out the way they wanted it to.
So the rock is Davy Crockett?
Sure. Sure.
Davy Rockett?
Davy Rockett.
You know, we give all these parts to the rock.
Let's not count out John Cena.
Let's not count out- Oh yeah,
I would never count out John Cena.
And there, that's the end of the list of movie stars.
Or a 60 year old Tom Cruise.
Yeah, yeah.
But he's picking those IPs carefully now.
Post-Mummy. Yeah, post-Mummy.
You also, we might want to think about a,
maybe there's a comedy,
Will Ferrell, John C. Reilly,
Tom and Huck.
I'm a grown Tom and Huck.
Okay, all right.
People want all the public domain characters
played by Kyle and John.
Recently mentioned Clifford.
If they go a Clifford route where they are Tom and Huck,
but they are playing 10, 12 year old Tom and Huck.
Ah, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And they have to figure out a way to do a selfie stick
within the world of Tom and Huck.
The good thing if they get Tom Cruise
is that he will spend six months
learning how to pilot a keel boat.
Well, and also- You'll really learn.
How to trick people into painting a white fence.
Sure.
He just starts going up to people on the street and like,
hey, could you, hey.
Hey, Aunt Polly has me doing this.
And it's really fun.
Well, in my mind, he was still playing David Cragut.
So you see him as more of a Huck Finn.
Tom Cruise is Huck Finn.
Oh, yeah, that one, yeah.
I don't know.
Unless it's Huck Finn Revisited or something.
All right, it's Huck Finn Revisited.
He's playing both.
So we're a little limited in our knowledge
of the David Cragut verse and the Twain verse.
I know he was born on a mountain top in Tennessee.
Some might call it the greatest place
in the land of the free.
I'm fairly confident he killed him a bar,
but what age, that's what's not coming to me.
Yeah, citation needed.
Yeah, I mean, I want to say only three, but I'm not-
That is an exceptional age to do that.
So it's probably, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I could say that'd be worth bragging
about in a song.
Well- Scott, let me ask you,
do you have any memories of writing the Mike Fink?
You say your mom was trying to get rid of the tickets
when the ticket book, do you have any childhood memories
writing the Mike Fink keel books?
I do not, I don't think I ever did it.
And I think I've only done the David Cragut canoes one time
and I did find it sort of unpleasant.
It's unpleasant.
I did it once too, yeah.
Yeah, my shoulders hurt.
Oh, it's brutal.
It hurt hours afterwards.
The teens that do and the 20 year olds that do that
are jacked by the end of the summer.
Jacked heroes, yeah.
They are just in such good shape, I bet.
Cause yeah, I did it with my dad and mom
a couple of years ago and we were just like, oh.
Yeah, it's hard.
I want to say I did it with my grandmother potentially,
which seems very odd.
Like that could have really wrecked her.
I did it a couple of years ago
and what ends up happening is the adults in the boat
do the real heavy lifting.
Like, I mean, the guys at the ends,
the cast members do the brunt of it,
but then the rest of the adults, like the kids get like.
Like the kids fall off very quickly.
And rightly so, cause it's hard to paddle a boat.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, you know, one thing about the Mike Finck keel boats,
I didn't really know what the experience was exactly.
And mainly you pilot around the rivers of America
and you see all the stuff that you can still see
on the other boats on the Mark Twain of the canoes.
But there's a little bit of Jungle Cruise jokiness to it.
Like they make fun of the Davy Crockett canoes.
The guy goes on a run about like, oh yeah,
that real fun ride where you're right down
in the stinky water and you're getting an upper arm workout
and oh yeah, oh, that's my favorite by far.
He kind of roasts the canoes, which is a little fun.
And that's the guy on the roof
with controlling the big paddle.
Yeah. Is that right?
Yeah.
I actually wait, I'm a little fuzzy on,
I just watched like a video
from somebody on the inside part.
I don't know that I know how it was, how it's piloted.
Is that what it is?
Is it a guy up on the second level?
Cause I asked my dad, I was like,
I have a memory of riding, we rode these, right?
And he's like, oh yeah, we rode these often.
He didn't register with you?
I know, but I have a very specific memory
of riding around the river in Disney World,
but being lower, not being high up like the Twain
or the sailing ship, being lower to the water.
Though that must be nice.
And that was this.
And then when I looked it up, I was like,
oh, I remember these ships.
Yeah, I do remember these going around,
but there was a guy who would stand
on the top of the roof kind of thing
and he would control this giant paddle and stuff.
Cause it was not on a track like Mark Twain.
It was more like the canoes or something.
What I saw, it is free floating.
Cause you would have to dock over on the side
and it wasn't just on a set track.
So there was a good person controlling it.
It was kind of the appeal of it.
That if you can get in that lower level,
but this boat by the way, if you haven't seen one,
is a double decker.
So the bottom level inside this kind of shack thing,
you're lower to the water like the canoes,
or you can sit up on top of the roof
where I guess the driver is.
So it's two different kinds of little experiences.
But if you want that water proximity,
if you want to feel that cold rush going by,
but you don't want the workout of the Davy Crocker canoes,
then the Mike Fink keel boats are for you.
And if you want some mild jokery,
as I said, he roasted the canoes.
He also made fun of the Hungry Bear restaurant
and said, I hear their food's so good,
they throw it to the ducks.
So you're getting little,
that's what I was not sure about was
what is the character of the ride experience.
And there are fun little jokes from the driver
and the one that I watched.
I'm impressed by a guy having to pilot
a pretty particular type of boat,
but also being funny and playing a character.
Because like Jungle Cruise, it's on a track.
And they are like, I think they're making it go and stuff.
Controlling speed.
They're speeding, right?
That's it.
Which is something, but this guy's actually controlling
and they have to do the jokes.
I'm impressed that they even poke fun at stuff.
I feel like if this started now, it'd be like,
well, we cannot make fun of the Hungry Bear restaurant
because people will not want to eat there.
We just changed the menu and we really need people.
We need eyes on this new menu.
People are upset about the fried green tomato sandwich
that has been gone for years.
And Lindsay still talks about it
and people are upset about it.
It is crazy that they haven't brought it back
because people love that sandwich.
Do you know what we're talking about?
I never do.
I'm aware of the existence of this.
I never did it.
People love that.
But yeah, if people are demanding a food item,
doesn't Disney always capitalize on it?
So yeah, roasting now, I feel like roasting
one of the restaurants they might not be into.
Yeah, well, it's just, we're really pushing the meal deals.
I mean, feel free to mention the meal deals.
Apple slices for the kids.
You can bring that up.
And what's the yogurt I drank or the applesauce I drank?
Oh yeah.
I drank applesauce out of a packet.
A squeeze pouch.
And it's called like bar piss.
They call it something foxy.
Yeah, it was from Tomorrowland.
And it was basically like I had a,
what's the Capri Sun with apple juice in it.
With my kid's meal.
Anyway, not a subject to be mocked.
So this double decker bus,
you get to go on with a fun foxy guy.
It's one of the first additions to Disneyland.
It was opened on Christmas 1955,
the literal day of Christmas.
And it was a kind of an in-demand attraction
as the Davy Crockett episode
in which the keel boats factored into,
which was called what?
Davy, well, Davy Crockett's keel boat race,
but I think it was packaged into something else,
the river race or something or other.
But this was, I guess, a moment,
this race is a moment that loomed large
in the Davy Crockett franchise.
And they wanted to get it in there
to the park in its early days.
And in fact, they used the literal boats,
the two boats, there were two keel boats,
the Gully Whumper and the Birth of May.
And the two boats that they put in
were the literal boats used in the Davy Crockett episode.
And Birth of May was Davy's
and Gully Whumper was Mike Finck.
Yes, that's correct.
You got it.
Yeah, they had their own boats.
And there's slight differences between them.
I wouldn't pretend to know
even having researched this lightly.
But yeah, the fact that it is a real,
they just were putting tourists on a real prop
from this TV show.
Well, that's like how they had the organ
from 20,000 Leagues, the movie,
and then they had it in a walkthrough attraction
for many years and then they just took the organ
and made it the organ in the auto mansion.
Sure.
Well, we have an organ?
Oh, I guess this ballroom has an organ now.
It's weird to think of things being that scrappy.
Like, well, the studio has this lying around,
so let's put it in the park.
This is their version of the Frozen ride.
Because the Frozen ride, they have to like,
how are we gonna put this thing?
All of a sudden, Frozen's a giant hit.
Because from what I understand,
Davy Crockett was a big hit on TV all of a sudden.
And it was like Davy Crockett mania
and merchandise was selling
and like they had, what's his name?
They played Davy Crockett in the parks.
In like a fest, fest park.
Of course, you're here.
Now a proud member of the Fest Parker wine club.
Oh, really?
You joined the club?
We joined the club.
I am a fan of their wines and the tasting was excellent.
Wow.
It's a beautiful facility up there.
Actually, up in Los Olivos, where I recently took a trip.
And in fact, it is the winery scene
in the big breakdown scene in Sideways,
where he pours the spittoon all over himself.
Oh, how about that?
So it's actually a little cruddy
for this very nice winery that they had to like,
almost like stand in as like a crappy one.
Right.
But it's a beautiful property with lots of little nods
to fests and little like etched skin caps everywhere.
That's great.
It's lovely up there.
If you're in the club, it sounds like
we have a Patreon episode coming up
where you prepare a tasting for us.
Oh, absolutely.
Now you're demanding treats.
Well, I'm just-
Suddenly you're on board with wine.
I'm just planting the seed.
I suppose so.
Hey, who am I to say no to drinking wine with the buds?
Sounds like a blast to me.
And then I'll do an episode where we go down to 7-Eleven
and I find what new treats in their private label line.
You can add all the 40 cent coupons.
Because you're a member of some sort of 7-Eleven club
that we don't know about?
They're a club you have to have the app
and then you get like, it's like a digital coffee card.
It seems so complicated.
I have not joined the 7-Eleven club.
I don't go there that much.
We did all right before recording take advantage
of our ShorePoints.
Yes, ShorePoints.
Jersey Mike's food rewards system.
Which we are all a member of the ShorePoints club.
All of us, yes.
And my wife.
Yeah.
And when I got my first free sandwich,
I was extremely proud.
Yeah, it's a very thrilling moment.
I remember when I had my first free sandwich too.
Man, if we didn't have to record after,
I probably would have just gotten some tasty cakes
at the checkout.
I forgot they have a big selection of tasty cakes.
Oh yeah, right.
Tasty cakes?
Oh, tasty cakes.
The pride of Philadelphia.
These little snack cakes.
Butterscotch crumpets and peanut butter candy cakes and stuff.
Probably would have just taken one of those,
gone home, woofed them down, had a nice little nap.
When you say nap, you mean go to bed at four o'clock
and wake up at 10.
Stay there.
Yeah, well, what better way to combat a post-sandwich nap
than by talking about-
That Mike Finke always-
Is 1800s history.
Which is what I'm gonna dive into a little bit
because I wanted to know,
let's not just talk about the character Mike Finke.
Let's talk about the real man Mike Finke.
Jason, in our last Sea Ticket,
you talked about the tortilla factory
and uncovered some fairly nefarious stuff.
Get ready for more nefariousness.
Mike Finke is something else.
So he was a real captain of keel boats,
a big brawny guy along the old miss in the old Ohio River.
If you wanted to, you know,
I don't know if you wanted to cross
or go downstream for a while,
you had to talk to guys like this,
make some deal with them.
He knew how to tame the river.
So he was a necessary person to have around,
but maybe not the most savory man.
Now he is kind of a, you know,
he exists in sort of this,
adjacent to Davy Crockett,
he's kind of a rootin' tootin' tall tale kinda guy.
And there's some fun stories about him.
Why it was said that he could drink a gallon of whiskey
and shoot the tail off a pig at 90 paces.
And he claimed he could outrun, out hop, out jump,
throw down, drag out, and lick any man in the country.
And that's all fun.
That sounds like Daniel Boone.
That's the Americana that we like.
The stories about him riding a moose like a horse.
That's fun.
Wrestling an alligator, okay.
Drowning wolves with his bare hands.
Okay, that's good.
We're getting more questionable.
I hope he needed to drown them.
If they were attacking him, I guess it makes sense.
If it was in self-defense,
and sure, that's still rootin' tootin',
but don't just go murderin' wolves.
Not the most efficient way to defend yourself from wolves.
And if you can shoot a pig from 90 paces,
why not just shoot the wolf, put it out of its misery,
instead of drownin' it slowly?
Shoot a wolf from five paces.
Yeah, 10 paces easier.
Yeah, yeah, don't put yourself out.
Don't walk so far.
But when you start looking into real tales about this man,
they were actually documented in newspapers.
They're less savory.
There's stuff about him, you know,
sayin', oh, I'm gonna shoot a ponytail off an engine.
That doesn't sound good to be shootin' it Indians.
There's also, there is this one story,
I'll say it really fast,
because I told the long version to Erin,
and she was like, do not tell this on the podcast.
But the story is that he saw a child with a heel
that was kind of a big weird heel.
It was kind of grotesque,
and he decided to take care of it
and shoot the kid in the foot.
What?
And when he was brought to jail for this,
because the kid dropped to the ground screaming murderer,
he said, well, you know,
I was just tryin' to fix his foot
so it would fit into a nice genteel boot.
What's the long version of the story?
There's just worse, more graphic details.
Do you wanna hear that?
Cause I kinda do.
I don't know.
I think I got it.
I think.
Can you give me one really horrible detail about it?
What I'm dancing around is that this was a slave child.
Oh my God.
Oh, nevermind.
It's truly hideous.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
This is not nice.
This is not, and the idea that this is routed around
to be folksy. Jesus Christ.
He wanted his foot to fit in a boot.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
So I maimed him.
And this one's not like a tall tale.
There's like a, in a St. Louis newspaper,
it's like man arrested for.
Jesus.
Yeah.
Shooting.
This is like, this is the actual version
of the murals in Pawnee City Hall on Parks and Rec
where they all commemorate ghoulish historical events.
It's not nice.
So think about that.
There is a ride named after a man who did this.
We got a hall of presidents though.
Well, that's full of chicanery, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, they did a lot more than maim one kid's foot.
All the presidents collected.
So anyway, you know, this one's back into folksy territory.
He had a good friend named William Carpenter,
who was also a keelboat man.
And they were said to have amused themselves
by shooting cups of whiskey from each other's heads.
It was William Tell style.
So they'd go 90 paces and then pull out their guns
and try to shoot the whiskey off each other's heads
without even making the cup move.
It just, then you just get the bing
and then the whiskey pours out onto their head.
That's fun and folksy, right?
Sure.
I like that.
But then things were all well and good
until these shooting sparring partners, Mike and William,
they said why they started sharing affections
for the same Indian girl who, if I had to guess,
I would say she did not share affection for either of them.
And was she 11?
Very possibly.
Probably?
You know, the more whiskey you drink,
the more you can't tell.
Not a lot of details, thankfully, but.
Because Pocahontas was like,
I learned this not too long ago.
She was like 12 or 13 and John Smith was older.
Yeah, my fifth grade history teacher,
because I think Pocahontas had come out before,
in that summer and I started fifth grade
and she was pissed about that movie
because she was like, we do American history.
Okay, so then take the Pocahontas movie out of your head.
She was so mad that she's had to correct all of this
odd stuff that was changed for the movie.
Right.
Yeah, you know, there's that thing,
there's that kind of snarky thing about how all the,
you know, Snow White and all the grim tales
are like actually full of horrors.
Right.
You know, yeah, she got her foot lacerated
and you know, it was crippled or whatever.
Like, that's the, I don't know, I don't need to,
of course, dress up the Little Mermaid,
make it a nice story.
I don't need it to be full of trauma.
Right.
But when you're taking real history and making it full.
Sanitizing it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and just not acknowledging things.
And I think they also, then, isn't the Pocahontas sequel
straight to video about like, then she came back to,
she like goes back to England or something.
Didn't she go back to England in real life?
Well, she went to England with them in real life
and ended up marrying.
But in far more of a kidnap manner.
Whoa, okay, if you think that maybe kidnapping
a 12 or 13 year old girl, maybe, yeah.
I guess I could see that.
Use the word kidnapping, yes.
I think you could put up, yeah.
Did eventually marry an Englishman, but not John Smith.
Yeah, I also watched some weird special
that was like promoting Pocahontas
where Disney got a bunch of like school kids to,
tell the story of Pocahontas.
And then one of them towards the end,
like, and John Smith was killed.
I forget the details, but they actually oddly
do tell real stuff, but.
Right.
Cute and kidzzy.
A man accused him of cheating in a game of bar room poker
and put a knife through his skull.
He was dumped in a whiver, no thinking.
Even by pigs.
Just around a whiver, man.
He was murdered.
The real grandmother willow was cut down,
fed into a chipper.
So Mike Finck and William Carpenter got in a fight
and they were at odds for months, but then Mike said,
hey, why don't we put it aside and play our old fun game?
Let's shoot whiskey off of each other's heads.
They set one of these games up 90 paces,
shot, Carpenter falls to the ground.
Whoops, oh, I missed.
He was, he was shaking around.
What was I supposed to do?
Our game.
If only he hadn't jumped slightly,
I wouldn't have hit him square in the brain.
So he passes it off as an accident,
but William Carpenter's best bud Levi Talbot,
he thinks something's fishy.
He lets months go by and he's like,
I think old Mike Finck was playing dirty there.
Mike Funk, Mike Funk.
That's the way to bring the ride back is to,
yeah, make it kind of a funk cruise.
Make it more of a-
King of the River dance, right?
Wait, when you think of funky, you think of river dance?
No, I'm trying to think of King of the River.
Oh.
What goes with river dance, okay.
Well, one can be Celtic dancing
and one can be George Clinton.
I just like the idea that if you were like,
yeah, you know, I'm really into funk music
and Jason and his set is picturing Michael Flatley's
load of the dance.
He's like, yeah, that is funky.
Those guys know how to get funky.
And most of all, it's fun.
So this guy, Levi Talbot is like,
something's not right here.
Almost immediately Mike Fink gets drunk and brags,
I shot him on purpose and I'm proud of it.
Levi Talbot immediately takes out a gun
and shoots him in the heart.
So Levi Talbot gets vengeance for his friend,
William Carpenter, and he lives happily ever after
until several months later he drowns.
I love the barbaric nature of the crazy 1800s.
The barbaric nature keeps going in what I think
is the cursed tale of Mike Fink
where everything surrounding it is very grim
in that when his story is committed to celluloid
by Walt Disney in a fun riverboat race scene,
where do they film that scene?
But in beautiful Cave-In Rock, Illinois.
Oh my gosh. Oh yeah, yeah.
You know about Cave-In Rock?
Yeah, a little bit. I don't know
how close that is to you.
I mean, I know what it's famous for.
You mean today? Today.
Well, yes, of course, today.
Well, not anymore, but for many years, the home of.
The gathering of the Juggalos.
Yeah. Indeed.
So today in the 2000s, it's best known as the place
where people peed on a watermelon
and threw it at Teela Tequila.
But back in the past, it was a home
to river pirates and murderers.
And in fact, one particular cave was the hideout
of the Harpy Brothers, commonly known as America's
first serial killers with over 40 kills to their name.
These guys went around Ohio and Kentucky and they,
you know, they like killing and maiming.
And they eventually caught up with like a river pirate gang.
And they everybody had a shared interest in murdering.
But the Harpy Brothers were so aggressive in their murdering
that the river pirates were like, hey, maybe you want to get out here.
Maybe go somewhere else.
So this is giving us a bad.
You're giving us river pirates a bad name hanging around with us.
Look, we don't believe in we believe in killing the people fast.
We don't believe in stripping them naked and throwing them off a cliff.
Jesus gave in Rock, Illinois, the home to a lot of crazy stuff,
which in that light, Juggalos, all is forgiven.
I mean, yeah, we had a fun race wheel.
They had helicopter rides.
Oh, yeah. Helicopter.
Oh, helicopter rides.
Those videos.
You'd have to be a net and hole to not enjoy those videos.
That's the blue.
They go forever.
I also well, as always, like in today's day, like how how like 10 years ago,
how when you like when Juggalo culture really was revived, you were like,
oh, my God, this is the dumbest, worst thing ever today.
In the light of the last couple of years in this country,
I love you, Juggalos.
I want to hug.
I guess the Juggalos are allies.
They marched on Washington the same day.
Same day as that.
One of those not the women's march, but a different march.
There was a like a hate march like an under like a Juggalos where they were marching
because they're on the FBI list.
Classified as a gang.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I know.
I was saying concurrently to a hate.
I see. March.
No, no, I think it was a good it was a good march.
No, no, no.
It might have been concurrently with a hate march.
And then people were worried like Juggalos were going to get into it with the
the all right people or whatever.
Or or you were hoping that this they would take care of it for us.
And we can really celebrate the Juggalos.
Do you want to take care of this? Help us.
Yeah. No, I love I look all their artists all watch their Western movies all day.
They're big money wrestlers.
So anyway, a lot of stuff going on at Cave and Rock,
where the where this great keelboat scene was filmed.
Jason, as you alluded to, there is a race
between Mike Fink and Davy Crockett and Mike Fink loses the race,
which brings us to the Disneyland ride, which to sum up
everything we've learned so far, this is a ride named after
an old drunk murderer who lost a boat race.
And with that, let's take a little let's take a quick little break.
Jason, I'm taking your pattern from the last episode and you you threw out
a little like fun little questionnaire segments and I figure, well,
that must be the pattern. Let's do that.
So I'm going to pose a little thing to you guys.
A little refresher after all that 1800s murdering.
And this is called Select Thy Sea Vessel. Oh, you guys both.
You have the day off and you're in a hub of water sports,
be it Lake Havasu, be it Key West, wherever you want that to be.
But what you can rent any boat you want.
What are you renting? Are you a sailboat guy?
Are you a keelboat guy? Are you is it a kayak? Is it a jet ski?
What's your ultimate water sports day?
It is. There's a multiple choice. No, it's free.
No, it's open ended. Any any vessel you want to ride?
OK, it's I would rent. I have an easy answer for this.
It's it's this it's the Lagoon by Disney in Disney World,
and it's driving around the boat from Thunder and Paradise. Oh, nice.
So like a nightboat style with massive interior, the massive room.
And it doesn't make any sense.
It's like Mary Poppins's bag or something.
But it's driving on.
I really should know the name of the boat from Thunder and Paradise,
which is, you know, should the whole code
the Hulk Hogan syndicated show that was supposed to be like the new Baywatch,
which boy, if there was ever a Baywatch episode waiting to happen,
it's Thunder and Paradise. Yes.
Hulk has some problematic stuff recently, but at the time, no one knew.
And it was just everyone was in love with Hulk Hogan.
And everyone was certainly in love with Jack Lemmon's son,
the other star of the show, who you cannot watch the show
without just constantly like seeing a vision of Jack Lemmon
laid over his son's face and going, ah, didn't help that he his birth name
is Johnny Lime.
Well done.
The boat's name was just Thunder.
OK, that makes sense.
And Hulk Hogan played Randolph J.
Hurricane Spencer, Randolph J.
Hurricane Spencer, Chris Lemon as Martin Brew, Brew Baker,
Carol Alt as Kelly LaRue.
And then, you know, some other people.
That's sort of a hell in test where she doesn't get a nickname.
Right. She isn't fun.
Films what at MGM Studios and on Bay Lake with the Polynesian in the background
and Floridian in the opening, especially.
You can always see a hotel in the background.
Yeah. Yeah. And if it was a hit,
the NWO may have never formed in wrestling because he didn't want
to necessarily be wrestling anymore.
And if that had been a big hit, he would have just been an actor.
Wow. So how about that?
So, you know, he might have been like transitioned out.
But yeah, I think he was like trying to like make a rock thing,
like get out of it.
Well, I believe I think this was on
Jim Hill podcast that Hogan just kept getting them to move the shooting
closer and closer to his house.
Yeah, he did not want to leave Florida.
I think a few people still Kevin James has that too, right?
He has like a big building right by his house where he shoots
or where he shot that sitcom.
Isn't that over now?
Kevin can wait.
We wasn't filming a studio.
It was only I think it was filmed in New York.
It was built sound stages for it.
Right. He only had to drive 10 minutes down the road.
Yeah. Oh, so that's nice.
Yeah. He seems like a great guy.
Well, Jason selects the AC.
OK, well, you know, the more I thought about it,
I've never ridden a jet ski.
I'd be curious to do that.
But I think on a lake, I'd feel more comfortable.
But once you brought up fictional stuff in Florida,
I was thinking like, you know, what would be cool?
We ride this cigarette boat out of Miami as dawn is breaking with.
Is it Crockett and Tubbs and Crockett?
But Colin Farrell, Jamie Foxx, Tubbs and Crockett.
Oh, while encore, while the Jay-Z,
Lincoln Park encore is playing like in Miami Vice, the movie.
And everything is that odd blue, blue,
glowing blue from digital video technology of 2006 or whatever.
That's crazy. The answer does it like I would have thought
you were going for like Riverboat in the bayou, like I like a true
Riverboat experience. You're on the veranda veranda.
You're like sipping a mint julep.
Oh, that's how I dress as an old timey colonel.
I feel like I feel like seven kids.
They're all around you. Various interests.
I you know, I didn't want to say sailboat because I don't I'm not good with knots.
I'm really I was late learning how to tie my shoes like well, after everyone else.
I think I was I was very late time.
I think you, Michael, taught me how to when you showed me how you tied a tie.
I think that's what it's like.
Is that right? Yeah.
Oh, interesting. I don't even remember that.
So yeah, I am your father.
You are. So but Riverboat.
Yeah, I mean, Riverboat sipping a jewel up.
That could be nice, too. Yeah.
And I might have snuck in there as a decent.
Yeah. Well, I've always been interested in fan boats, not interested enough to ride one.
I just like the idea of them and that they're out there.
I probably should write a fan boat at some point in my life.
But, you know, my answer is I spent a lot of time in Newport Beach.
Oh, yeah. I didn't live there, but my dad took me down there all the time.
He had a little sailboat stored down there and the name of the boat was Drunky
with two E's and I was always so delighted to climb aboard Drunky.
Wow. Bury the lead on that one.
Bury the lead, Rummy.
Yeah. Where did I get it from?
Wow. No, excellent.
Excellent name.
You know, I, you know, he had to he had to let the boat go
and it was probably decaying beyond repair.
But if I could, if we could get the old Drunky back and get me and my dad
on the water and in absence of that, Mike, you've joined me on a on a pontoon.
Oh, yeah. Very fun.
Excursion, I think.
Chase, you were invited.
I think you just weren't around, right?
You weren't on the pontoon.
And I'm forget it. Yeah, I think I was out of town.
I was not on the pontoon.
You know, I don't turn down.
I didn't invite you.
You know, I don't turn down a chance to get on a boat.
Yeah, yeah.
You load that up.
You got I mean, in my head immediately, you got to ride like the wind.
You got some Miami sound machines, some one, two, three.
Come on, baby, say you love me and since some some Mike McD sweet freedom,
you load up all those songs, gets some pop, some champagne.
And I think you let me play Fins from Jimmy Buffett.
I think that was where you drew the line.
Fins is the F.S.
Fins has shown up on some like summer mixes for me,
which is the only acceptable Buffett song to me.
Right. It's the only one I can tolerate partially because of the fun dance
that goes along with it.
It's got a great dance with a little fin on your head.
You don't listen to he went to Paris and think about your life.
Well, I haven't yet.
Maybe I'm missing out on something big.
Jason is big on the slow Buffett songs.
He's big on the really contemplative ballads.
He likes fruitcakes.
I will play for gumbo.
Cheeseburger paradise, because you really got to think about
what you want on your burger that day.
Lots of different kinds of burgers.
It's not one kind of hamburger.
It's pretty heavy. You have to limit it.
It would be good if Buffett like I watched that Springsteen
Netflix thing recently, and he does a very slow, acoustic
12 string born in the USA.
And it's like, I was born in the US like it's very different vibe.
And it would be great if Buffett did a similar cheeseburger
in paradise, like a minor key mournful cheeseburger paradise.
It really puts the context like put a different context on the song.
You make you think it was the that he's like a ghost
and the cheeseburger killed him. Yeah, exactly.
There's suddenly a subtext to it. Sure.
I rewrote it. So now it's about a cheeseburger kill me.
I'm a ghost. Here we go.
I wrote in two seconds.
Just change the game to me.
Well, let's climb on back the keel boats and
talk about the actual ride again, the the the drunk murdering
boat race loser ride.
It's so you see you got two boats, Gully one per birth of May.
As I said, it's for this fun little jokes.
They open this thing up in Disney World to people seem to like it
because it added to the the kinetic energy and energy of the river
to say thing we often say about over in tomorrowland.
And some people feel like the the river isn't the same without
without those boats going around.
I also learned from my friend, Dennis McNicholas, that there I asked
if he had any memories.
The keel boat, he never he never went on it, but he does remember
very specifically that there was something that there was a shop,
a little little store, a merch stand called Keel Boat Shop.
And you might ask what they sell keel boat shop.
I would they sell they sold exclusively haunted mansion merchandise.
And OK. And in fact, when you looked it up on the map,
it would say keel boat shop, your home for all the best haunted mansion
memorabilia. So it was never related to the keel boats.
I don't know why it was eventually it eventually was renamed
Ichabod's Landing.
And now it is storage.
So that's the story of keel boat shop.
And that was that in Florida or that was Florida, where I believe
the boats left from Liberty Square, which is where the haunted mansion is.
Yeah. And now they have that.
The the memento mori is the haunted mansion shop and is hugely successful.
They were like, oh, now they're very committed to a haunted mansion store.
Crazy that it took them that long to build a haunted mansion based store. Right.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
Well, but keel boat shop had you covered for a while.
Well, that's true.
The other thing I learned that's very strange is that, you know,
you had to be more than just a funny comedian and voice actor to drive these boats.
These were pretty serious vessels, harder to pilot than.
Yeah. Then some of the bigger boats and and certainly more so than Jungle Cruise.
And apparently the boats were powerful enough to operate as tugboats
if the train or the Columbia.
Whoa. I didn't read that. Isn't that odd?
I don't know if that ever happened.
I don't know if they were ever employed for that.
But yeah, it would serve a practical function to rescue the Mark Twain.
The motors were that strong.
I guess. I don't know. I don't know how tugboats work.
I mean, it's just kind of momentum and yeah.
Yeah. I don't know.
It's like how a pickup truck can drive, like pull a giant parade float.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
And now they have to attach a canoe to pull it.
So you have to have some tourists pull the twain into dock.
They start yelling for guests. Come on.
We need your help. We need our strongest guests.
So keel boats running without incident, never that popular,
but a good eater of sea tickets went seasonal around 1994,
not operating all the time, just in peak seasons and one dreaded peak season.
Something happened at around 5 30 p.m.
on May 17th, 1997, the gully whomper began rocking from side to side.
It was loaded with 49 guests.
The normal capacity is 32.
Yeah. What happened? I read about this too.
Like what? No one has a good answer for why.
Not even by off by three or four. Yeah, right.
Like, oh, OK, we can fit your extra couple of people from your party.
It's like a load 15 moron.
Yeah, I don't know.
Asking for trouble and trouble they got.
It rocked back and forth.
The gully whomper tipped over, dunking a boatload of guests
into the rivers of America.
I also heard stories of like people from the canoes
jumping out of the canoes to help people. Right. Right.
As there were kids and a pregnant woman.
And now everybody was fine and the injuries were only minor.
But they did have to go to the hospital.
People went to the hospital and you're done for the done in the park
for that day and your clothes are wet.
And some of the dirtiest water there could ever be.
Seems like one of the incidents where you end up with a settlement
and then a black car like a lifetime Disney pass.
I hope so.
But they're like they can be cheapskates a little bit.
Yeah, maybe. I don't know.
I that is a question.
I mean, I'm assuming once stuff like this happens, there's an NDA sign.
But some agreement is reached.
And I would love to know on any of these incidents what happened.
Like, did they get what do they get?
Learning more because those NDAs don't last forever.
Isn't there a period?
I guess it depends on each NDA.
I don't know. I don't know.
For more stuff to start getting released.
Mm hmm. Well, that's the Stormy Daniels with that.
No, that wasn't that it ran out.
It's that she was just she just broke it.
Screw it. Yeah.
So maybe Michael Avenatti can look into this stuff for us
and find out what these people got in exchange for being dumped
out of this boat because it was overloaded.
Very reliable litigator.
Well, he just he digs, you know.
Well, I don't want to distract from the doings of our next president.
Yeah, good point.
Let's let's let him have eyes on the prize.
So that was it.
That was the end of this at Disneyland.
They didn't repair it.
That was it was done.
And I wonder if it was without that sea ticket thing.
Maybe the popularity just wasn't worth it.
It was I don't know, Disneyland.
The accidents not that common also.
And that came out.
And I think they're probably just like, well, let's not even
these things are tainted.
Let's not slow capacity to.
Yeah. So it's like requires special training for these captains.
And yeah, it just wasn't worth it.
Labor costs, because then you have to train and pay the people more
because they're doing more.
Yeah. Yeah. But, you know, more transportation is nice.
That's the only that's the only downside.
It would have been fun to go on these.
They do feel like a little more of a to do not fully canoe level to do.
But you got to the canoes and like the raft to Tom Sawyer.
You got to wait in that little area.
I don't know. It always feels like I feel like I guess what I'm saying
is I wouldn't go on these a lot if they still existed.
Yeah. But it would be nice to once in a while go on them.
Yeah. And we like our once in a while attractions and idea.
This would be in the mix, especially now where I go so often
and would be looking to, you know, mix it up and sure.
And off the off the beaten path. Right.
But they are no longer.
And in fact, the the boats are not around.
You could they're not see fairing anymore.
The gullywumper, one of them, the one that sank
or the one that tipped over was installed as a prop along the rivers of America
in 2003, where it slowly deteriorated and sank into the land of the rivers.
Oh, so then.
But there's a gullywumper there now.
I yeah. And it's I believe it's a recreation.
2010, they put it there because like, OK, that was when I first started.
I mean, I've gone before 2010, but I think around 2010, 2011,
I got an annual pass and then started going a lot more.
And I always remember it being there because I didn't go a lot before.
OK, yeah. Gotcha.
Well, yeah, I think it's labeled the gullywumper, but it is not that actual.
Yeah, OK. Because it sank and I guess is just out of there entirely.
But what of the birth of May?
Yes. What of the birthday?
And I know, Mike, do you know?
I don't know. Oh, boy.
I was really hoping you wouldn't figure it out.
I figured it out. I know now. I forgot.
Well, then let me know.
I know. I know. I know. I know.
The other boats, the birth of May
suddenly in the early 2000s was listed on eBay for a fairly small asking price.
Yeah. $15,000.
And from that eBay listing, it was bought by Richard Kraft.
Richard Kraft, the man who behind the that's from Disneyland
Gallery, who we interviewed on the show and who who sold off all that memorabilia
and who took us to Club 33.
But didn't sell this.
He did. In fact, I checked in with a craft.
I asked, what is the deal?
He alerted me to the documentary that was made about them
finding craft land in which he takes you to see the boat.
Now, at the time, it was at a storage facility in La Mirada.
And he walks for so long.
He just walks and walks past like covered thing after covered thing.
Unclear if it's all his.
But I wouldn't put it past him.
He unfurls a sheet, gets up on the deck and dances and dances and dances a lot.
They devote a lot of the documentary to him dancing on the boat.
Now, he specifically said he was not didn't ever go on this.
It seemed weird and sad to him as I was sort of my thinking as well.
But when it came up for auction, it was, you know, it had to be done.
The price was good.
Yes. You can't beat that price.
Even in even in 2001 dollars.
His idea was to have it craned over his home
where he and eventually build a lagoon in his backyard.
He wanted to do a little like picnic area with the keelboats of the centerpiece,
like the chicken of the sea ship in fantasy land.
And after a few meetings with various engineers and his business manager,
reality kicked in.
And it has been in storage ever since.
So the dream of a lagoon installed in his home didn't work out.
But he did. Yeah.
This was one of the things that spurred that auction was that he had.
So as he told us, there's so much stuff
it was just sitting around that he never even got to enjoy.
He had no end that to move that thing.
He never got to enjoy the the the birth of May in his own home.
So he sold it and it was part of the auction.
Apparently, at the auction, there was like a cutout of it, like representing it.
They never moved it in the sports authority, but it was sold.
And I don't want to say the name, but I did hear the name.
And it is to like a very to a major, major Disney collector.
So it seems possible that this could end up
being available to see at some point in time.
Yeah. When you said craned over his home, I imagine it being
put on top of the home and like an Admiral Halsey,
very sort of set up where you could just look out from the keel boat.
Oh, I like that. Oh, like it's a little.
Oh, that's a cool idea.
Yeah. A little like, what do you call the little like port?
Like the little crows nest. Oh, there you go. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, man. Having all crows nest in your house. Awesome idea.
Yeah, that'd be great.
Well, he missed out.
Should have done. I'm sure smashing a big hole into your roof
and perfectly installing an old boat in it is more cost effective.
Architecturally sound in a state known for earthquakes.
Yeah. And I feel like I know he lived in like the, you know, in the hills.
So like, yeah, should be fine.
The boat should slide down the hill and take out people along the way.
We get a few more Patreon subscribers, a couple more Jason.
You'll be able to finally afford this and buy it from that collector
and then you'll be able to do that.
Great. And assuming that the price did not go up.
Yeah, no, it stays the same.
Which we can trust being that in that auction, you know,
a plate would go for four thousand dollars.
Yeah. And then when I say a couple more Patreon subscribers,
each of them are pledging five thousand dollars a month for this content.
There's only one person who could do that, and it's Richard Kraft.
Yes, that's true.
He wants the boat to be back in good hands.
So that's that's the story.
The fact that it ended with a character we know. Yeah.
I don't think I realize when you said when it was sold at auction,
it was that auction. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. It was in because a lot of these articles left it at it's just in storage.
Nothing ever began.
But at are the right below where we were performing our now legendary show.
And yes, we did walk around the floor a bit.
And we're calling it.
Yeah, I don't know. There was just so much stuff there.
And I thought about going the last the last day or the day before it ended.
But there there's social media updates were so like
the line is to venture.
I know. I didn't think we did.
I was worried we wouldn't get in for our own.
I would get it. Yeah.
And also like some of the people who bought like like now we know some of the
the giant D from the Disneyland Hotel that was the big centerpiece of it
is in David Copperfield's airplane hangar in Las Vegas.
And another a couple of the small world dolls were bought by
what's your name? Chris Jenner. Yeah. Right.
And given to Chloe.
Chloe Kardashian.
Yes, because we were that that's how cool and with it we are.
We were texting around Christmas trying to figure out which card.
It's like, wait, so close. No.
So what? Who had which guy?
Which which boyfriend or husband had the sock company?
Oh, no. And then but who's with Travis Scott?
Like I like I know all the weird facts about the Kardashians,
but I can't remember which one has the incredibly successful makeup.
Yeah, which is a legitimate entrepreneur.
Is Scott Disick the one with the sock company?
No, I think because Scott Disick was the one who was on vacation.
I think it's Rob Kardashian.
OK, fine. Fair. I don't know.
That could be right.
But then one of the women bought in bought a big share of it.
I don't think that sock company is doing well.
That's too bad.
All I know is that Chris Jenner bought these dolls and Chris Jenner
is did the only bit of Kardashian related media that I care about,
which is a song for her own birthday party called I Love My Friends,
in which all of her friends bizarrely yell at the camera.
She she loves you.
She loves you.
And some and one of the friends, of course, is Ornithal James Simpson.
Of course, a montage of shots of the Kardashians and OJ Nicole together.
A blast. Look that up if you've never seen it.
Oh, so good.
And there's a lot of good, you know, there's a good I Love the Farm,
not very far impaired.
So too many good I love right to even get into.
But let's let's bring the ship back to the dock.
It is sorry it is Scott Dissick has the sock company.
Hell, yes.
I was right. Cool.
Yes. In November, Chris Jenner, quote, bought half of Rob's sock company.
Rob.
Sorry, Scott. OK, it's impossible.
Where to how do you even begin?
I have a quick plus up.
I want to bring if you bring back Mike Fink when they finally bring booze
into Disneyland, which to Star Wars, it'll happen.
And I think it'll slowly roll out everywhere.
How about some whiskey on the Mike Fink in honor of the great,
horrible man, Mike Fink himself?
And then people could like pretend to shoot it off each other's head.
That's fun, right?
You have a sip of a nice little sip of whiskey.
You're going around the rivers of America.
Does anything sound better than that?
That's not to me. Sounds real nice.
Sounds real nice.
And you could like take if they set up like an animatronic
that you could like that would you could perfectly shoot down from 90 paces.
Yeah. Well, yeah, let's get that Root and Toot and spirit back in there.
Memorialize this great murder and man.
And anything else?
Oh, you know what I should say, though, it was not called Mike Fink.
They were called the River Rogue keel boats in Euro Disneyland
in Disneyland, Paris.
And I don't think they're gone.
I don't think they run them very often, but I don't think they are.
I think they are.
Officially retired and the Florida one ended.
But they did run it longer than Disneyland.
OK, right. I think that 2001.
Yeah, yeah, I made it made a little longer.
So, yeah, now I'm just glad that the that Mike Fink,
the legend of Mike Fink is conveying the best image of America.
Yeah. Over in France. Sure.
Yeah. Well, hey, thanks for the thanks for the ride.
You survived a perilous trip
with old Mike Fink through the rivers of America.
And you're leaving with all your limbs intact.
Thanks for thanks for listening to podcast the ride, the second gauge.
Let us if there's worse boats
you want us to talk about, make us aware,
you know, those Epcot boats are coming at some point.
Yeah, they have to.
And because the the thing I joked about this recently,
the the boats that leave you at the back entrance of Epcot.
Well, those are different boats than the boats that cross the lagoon.
The Illuminations Lagoon. Yeah.
Two different kinds of boats.
Yeah, well, I love the boat from GM to anyway.
We'll talk about friendship.
We'll get to it. Thanks for listening, folks.
We'll see you next time.
Yeah.