Five, four, three, two, one.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to podcast the ride, the second gate.
We're here with our guest Jenny Nicholson to talk about one of the most important topics
I think we've ever tackled in our theme park, you know, podcast history, sunny eclipse.
This one's been looming.
It's a big one.
Jenny, I think the first time you're here, I just thought I'd watched the first video
of yours I'd watched like, oh, she knows about sunny eclipse.
Right, the top 10 lame things to do at Disney World.
Which was that number one?
He was number one.
Yeah.
Wow.
He took gold.
Geez.
If we're talking, well, what's some rationale for that?
What was some of your reasoning?
I mean, my favorite thing about Magic Kingdom's Tomorrowland is the ambiance and I think he
represents that really well.
He's a constantly performing animatronic act.
I love animatronics and I love being near food.
So he delivers on all fronts.
I actually, there's very little I can eat at Cosmic Race.
Yeah.
They have kind of a lame falafel burger and even the toppings bar can't save that one,
to be honest.
They were robust toppings bars.
So yeah, so in case you're listening to the second gate and for some weird reason you
don't know who sunny eclipse is, I don't know if it could, I am curious.
There's no way.
If you're a listener and you're subscribing to our Patreon, do you not know Sunny Eclipse?
If that is the case, be honest and tell us.
I'm just curious what the percentage is.
You're shaking your head no.
He's like the queen of Disney World.
Queen the performing artist, not Queen Elizabeth.
Wait, so what do you mean by that?
Like everyone knows him.
Oh sure.
Oh yeah.
Everyone.
The band from that great movie that just came out.
By this point, potentially Oscar winning film.
Yeah, in the film about Sunny Eclipse, contractually the space angels need an equal amount of screen
time.
So it really messes up the editing.
Space angels' husbands are jammed in their weird side stories.
And they don't care.
Mike Myers will be playing the same character though, oddly enough.
A little finger is there also.
An alien who sings about burgers.
It'll never work.
Teenagers will never bang their heads to the.
And the space, the angels also, they're not into partying like Sunny is.
I just want to make sure that like they're very responsible.
They're family men.
That's what they buy heads over.
It creates a lot of dramatic tension.
Sunny went wild, but not the space angels.
So Sunny Eclipse is?
He is an alien lounge singer.
From the planet Zork.
The city of U-Nork.
U-Nork City.
I've been working for a guy, Dennis McNicholas, to be working for a Sunny Eclipse fan.
I told him we're doing a Sunny Eclipse episode.
And I just learned that he's from U-Nork City.
And he said, oh yes, on planet Zork, I believe.
Man, oh man, what a good man.
And he's several times now sent me selfies with Sunny.
Which I encourage.
We're getting this already a little bit.
People do, I think, send us photos with Sunny.
Which keep them coming.
I'm really happy people have been sending pictures of my favorite bear, Truffles the
Bear from the Rocky Man Chocolate Factory.
But if you're with Truffles, I want to see it.
And if you're with Sunny, I want to see it.
People will send me selfies with Sunny as well, ever since I mentioned him in the video.
They'll say, I'm working through your list.
And they'll send a pic of Sunny.
I want to say how much I appreciate this.
Whenever you first saw Sunny, probably as a little kid.
No.
In some way.
No, my first visit to Florida, I was an adult.
Oh, right.
Never mind.
I'm making an assumption there.
Oh, you weren't even, oh really?
You didn't go until.
Oh, then that's an interesting perspective.
Yeah, there was a lot of retro stuff I never got to see.
My first visit was mere months after they closed Maelstrom.
We had in fact booked our Fast Passes for Maelstrom.
And they were canceled because Frozen was announced.
What the hell?
They didn't even give us a good for anything Fast Pass in apology.
They didn't promise you front row VIP seats.
No, they just took away our Fast Passes for Maelstrom.
And I've never forgiven them for that.
Geez, that's harsh.
It's hellish.
It's harsh.
They should pay.
So yeah, I don't remember what year that was, but I was an adult.
That's like five years ago.
I was grown.
Wow.
But you knew about it.
You made a point of go.
Or was it a surprise to you?
I had heard about it.
Okay.
And I needed to find it.
So yeah, it was like really high on my list to find.
He's not.
He hasn't been there that long.
It feels like something he's been there since like 95, right?
Okay.
That's pretty long.
94, I think was 94.
That's a long time.
Tomorrowland shift.
To me, that's like when the world started.
If like, probably listeners know all this as well, but like they, I think it's safe
to say Tomorrowland 94 in Florida is the most successful of the Tomorrowland shifts and
remakes.
Partially because it has a lot of personality to it.
They imagine this really specific kind of thirties meets future jets and Z.
It's like, it's this bustling future metropolis that's kind of self aware that it's a sci-fi
parody world.
And so it's really, it's so much fun.
And those little details, I think it's like, okay, like I don't think we care about this
so much anymore, but how Tomorrowland, I'm sorry, Toontown has all that you can pick
up the phone or you can open the lid and it talks to you.
I would love even more of that.
Yeah.
And Tomorrowland does have that stuff.
They have a little bit.
You can pick up phones.
They don't anymore.
Oh, do they not anymore?
They just permanently removed the phone and the robot and apparently it was confirmed
that they're not returning.
Oh, that's so good.
I know.
Well, that makes me worry about Sunny.
Can Sunny possibly stay there?
It makes me worried about Sunny.
They're going to put a screen and have like, you know, Vanessa Hudgens dance party.
I'm too old to know who's on Disney Channel anymore.
Probably Meghan Trainor.
She's just in everything now.
No, no, no.
They did refer.
They just refer and he's there.
And he's still there.
I mean, the next time he breaks, will they decide he's not worth fixing?
That's my ongoing fear about Sunny.
It's like Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
Sure.
Stay healthy.
We need you.
It's exactly the same thing.
It's pretty much just like Ruth Bader Ginsburg.
It's important to me.
One to one.
Yeah.
It is lightly attended every time I've ever been.
And I'm always the only one in there that looks like I'm paying attention.
Yeah, I'm worried we're going to see on like an exit survey.
Like one of the questions, did you go to Cosmic Ray's to see Sunny Eclipse?
And if enough people say no, they'll stop refurbing him.
Maybe they'll make him a statue.
Oh, yeah.
I see that.
Or make it so only the mouth moves.
The problem, we're getting, I guess, ahead of ourselves worrying about this before we
will celebrate him after this.
But yeah, I think there's a there's a thing with robots in front of a spot that you can
eat.
We have not done a full tropical hideaway episode, but we just, Lindsay and I just won.
And Rosita does like little jokes every minute.
And it's odd because she's a little too loud and it's a little too loud.
But she also like it seems odd that she's just gotten all of a sudden.
It's like blurts out a joke and then goes back to being silent.
Like she's crazy in front of an audience either.
Yeah.
And they don't want I think I think the thing with that is they probably were like, we can't
do a full show because we have a limited amount of space.
And they don't want people to linger.
And we don't want people to linger.
Whereas Sunny does a full 30 minute show.
No one lingers.
And it loops.
I think there's probably a way to maybe make the show more like turtle talk or something
where like there's some interactivity.
But then I think they have the problem of like, then everybody comes in.
Yeah, they want to turn over those tables.
They don't want people in huge waves coming in for the show.
Yeah.
And I also have some personal theories that we can maybe get to later about why the show
is a little less attendant than it should be.
Interesting.
Nothing that smart.
We're in a related territory also.
Obviously robots performing in front of places where you can eat.
We're in a territory close to Chuck E. Cheese's.
And we'll do.
We're going to spend probably a year of episodes on Chuck E. Cheese.
Do you guys have a local Chuck E. Cheese?
And does it have robots?
It's right over here.
That's a good question.
I walked by there.
I went to Subway and I walked by there and I was alone and I was looking peering through
the window, which is weird enough when it's an adult man looking at Chuck E.
Yeah, when you're an adult man you can't do that.
But I was just, I mean, I was casually peering.
I didn't do the full cup hands face against the glass.
You did have a cold.
So that was the week you were breathing exclusively through your mouth.
There's a big face.
And it's been cold.
So you're wearing a trench coat.
Someone on Twitter should just tell us like in SoCal, I would love to sign one that still
has the four animatronics set up.
If any still exist.
Should I yelp it?
I don't know if you can take it.
I think it's going to take you a minute to decipher it.
I've been to the one in Fullerton, like my friends and I straight up went inside, played
games and bought a pizza.
And they had the modern one Chuck set up where it's like a very modern looking Chuck E. He's
like Slim and Sonic the Hedgehog S.
And it sucks.
And yeah, he sucks.
And there's just one of him.
This is Studio C is what you're describing.
I think that is what it's called.
And part of that is that there's a green screen where your kid could pretend they're on TV.
It's before the green screen.
It's just one Chuck E. The new one is I think just going to be some kind of tube with an
image of Chuck E displayed on it.
Like a hologram.
So there won't even be the one robot?
There's no robots.
They're phasing them all out.
No, no, no.
I want to know though, is there any of them that have just the original outfit characters?
Because I think most of them at a certain point were converted to like skateboard Chuck
E.
Right.
Which like he has his like blue and green shirt and baseball hat on.
Entertainers should wear tuxedos at all times.
I think I do remember the tux and tails Chuck E.
Sure.
He would be in a tux once in a while, but the one I grew up with was just the classic
red and yellow and the bowler hat.
Right, I think so.
He was a huckster rat.
He was a jerk.
Oh, you're right.
The bowler hat.
He was like a carnival barker.
Yeah, he was like a shady character and that's what was great about him.
And then they like poochy him up.
And it had like a grubby city vibe kind of.
They had like a cityscape like it was a late night show behind the set.
Yes, and they would do those loops of like the fake Chuck E. shows and stuff.
Yeah, it would cut the TV and then you'd see like puppets or something.
Yeah, so.
So yeah, I'd love to find one with that.
That's what I want.
I feel like in the Midwest there are more that haven't been touched so much.
I think in California they update them more.
I think so.
My hometown one, which was in West Hills, California at the Fallbrook Center, was hung
in there for a while.
I actually don't know if it shifted to Studio C and I pray that it hasn't.
Yeah, but like it made it a while.
So I did have a place where I could go see Helen and Jasper and.
Yeah, Helen Henney.
Helen Henney.
Jasper T. Jowell's.
They're still merchandising Helen Henney.
I know this because I subscribed to a Chuck E. Cheese fan YouTuber and as soon as they
made it, he had to go buy it and do a plush review of the two sizes that came in.
Oh, wow.
So a new Helen Henney plush.
Is that do they sell some stuff at Chuck E. Cheese or is it just the trick?
Because my family found this out at some point.
It's like, OK, that's 200 tickets.
It's exactly that.
You can save up tickets or buy it.
And I think that's not true of all their stuff, but that is true of Helen Henney and the Chuck
E.
If you follow me on Twitter, a couple like a month or two ago, I Uber E delivered a Chuck
E. Cheese pizza.
I would do that.
I would so do that.
And it's because I got a credit card that comes with $15 of Uber credit a month.
And I was like, well, I have to use it even though I haven't been using Uber.
So then I was like, I wonder if I could use it at Uber Eats.
And you can.
And then I was like looking through the restaurants and I was like Chuck E.
Cheese. And I was like, that's weird.
That's amazing.
Yeah, because no one it's like Rainforest Cafe.
You don't think, oh, the food.
Why would you do that?
I clicked on it.
Terrible.
Yeah. And I was like, OK, get a pizza.
And then I noticed it said free item.
Choose free goodie bag or free Chuck E.
Plush.
So you could get a free goodie bag or Chuck E.
Plush. Which one did you get?
The Chuck E. Plush.
But it's skateboard Chuck E.
And it's not.
I was thrilled to get it.
I mean, it's not Helen Henney.
Yeah. Where is it?
Upstairs somewhere.
It's not. I mean, later.
Go get Chuck E.
I have it all. I'll show it to you on Twitter too.
It's not a visual podcast.
It's on Twitter.
If it was a Munch or so, I'm a big Munch fan as well.
Me too. I loved Munch.
I loved it. He was so.
I mean, he was just the Grimace.
They just stole Grimace.
Oh, yeah. No.
But Grimace had been my favorite McDonald's character.
Right.
Well, Slash, he's also the he took the position of the gorilla.
Oh, the gorilla. The keyboard playing gorilla.
Yes.
Did you know Creative Engineering is selling plush characters of their classic characters?
No.
But they're so limited run that I think they're like two hundred dollars.
Geez.
Oh, you're talking about the rocket fire?
Yeah.
Oh, you.
Lindsay pre-ordered for me the Billy Bob bear.
See, that's next level because, yeah, they are not cheap.
They are.
It's one hundred and fifty dollars.
Yeah, because I saw they were making that.
And I was like, I would buy those.
And then I looked at the prices and I was like, oh, I would not buy those.
Oh, you can get it for one hundred and twenty five.
But the one hundred and fifty one comes with a head that comes off.
That's the you can see inside the head.
Right.
So it's like skin removed.
That's pretty, pretty next level.
So, yeah, that was my Christmas gift.
It was the preorder for that.
When does it ship quarter to?
Oh, yeah.
Is you get a wild.
I think he's like low key kickstarting it and trying to sell as many as he can
before he bulls orders them.
What's this guy?
This is this guy who used to work for Mondo.
Really? I thought it was the guy that actually did the robots
that was making this happen.
Unless there's we could be talking about two separate lines of rocker.
The face was more like a doll.
And the one that I've seen is like a plush.
Yeah, this was.
I think the plush are the ones that are by the guy who's still doing the robots.
I bet that's right, because, yeah, this only he's only had the Billy Bob out
right now as for preorder.
He's I think he wants to do all of them.
Yeah. Eventually.
But that's the one I have not.
I don't even think I've seen the plush.
Now that you say it.
Yeah, I don't know how recent they are, but I went to his website recently
because I wanted to see about tours and.
Oh, right. I want to do it.
It's a whole thing, though.
I think he's like I think it's.
Yeah, it's a it's a full day endeavor and it's it doesn't seem organized.
It seems like you go to his workshop and he improvs showing you around.
Yeah. Oh, man, was that today?
Yeah, exactly.
Like you show up and he's looking unwashed t shirt and I don't know.
Maybe it's great.
I think he was selling a lot of them as five nights at Freddie's birthday parties
when that was still really big with kids.
Oh, yeah. Which is a pretty cool idea.
Appalizing. Yeah.
That's not a bad idea.
It's a pretty cool idea.
But it had its moment and now I think it's over.
My big Chuck E.
Cheese memory is that like that was the place my brother and I were like,
we got our report cards today.
We did good.
What do you say?
I wish we did that.
I feel like we I only went for like birthday parties and stuff.
Yeah, me too.
For a very limited time, the Chuck E.
Cheese was right in the same shopping center as a comic book store.
So I was like, let's kill two birds with one stone while we're here.
That was as a kid.
I was always like my mom's like, all right, I'm going to go to the mall to do some shopping.
And I'm like, do you want some company?
And I would just go like, just leave.
I was like, I'm going to go to the comic store, the bookstore and stuff.
And my mom is clearly smart to have in a mall, though,
because you can have it as like a free childcare service.
Yeah. Oh, oh, not the Chuck E.
Cheese, just the comics.
You were just telling us about the mall.
I feel like Chuck E.
would be great to have in a mall.
There is an Eagle Rock.
The mall has a Chuck E.
Cheese in it.
I feel like I've only seen them outside.
Yeah, it's outside, though.
It's not inside a mall.
I don't think I know.
No, it is.
Yeah, well, then I'm thinking of a different one.
Then, but my eventually the compromise was like, all right,
we'll go to Chuck E.
Cheese, but let's just eat at the pizzeria down the road that we like
instead of buying expensive bad pizza at Chuck E.
Cheese.
We'll awful just flour and.
Sometimes I crave bad pizza, though.
Sure. That's true.
It brings you back.
Sometimes you're like, I want a fairground pizza.
And that's basically what Chuck E. has.
This is very similar to Cosmic Ray's, a terrible restaurant.
Well, yeah, you're right.
We went on a tangent, but Chuck E.
Cheese is equally entertaining.
Yeah.
It's like by point just being that to like the idea that Disney has its
own version of the animatronic endlessly flapping to disinterested people.
Right.
To eat, get their bus, their trays and get out immediately.
Like, what is the why do I I just I think it was a more magical world
knowing that a rat like in many strip malls and places that you're passing by.
There's there's robots.
Yeah.
Stores are so boring.
Everywhere is like Coles or Ross.
And not like one robot, like four to five giant robots.
Yeah.
So many with history and stories.
Characters.
The one guy makes the pizza.
Yeah.
You're not just seeing.
Yes.
They're like and this training videos you can watch where he does.
Yeah.
Recipe.
Those are the greatest.
Did you guys ever go to a rocky and bowl ankles or is it just called bowl?
One time.
It is the faintest memory.
I was so young.
I only remember like one of the arcade machines was like a log that would light up and there was a spooky owl inside.
And it scared me.
So it stuck with me.
That's all I remember.
It must have been like two.
It's pure magic.
This stuff.
It's so neat and weird.
And I also I think it's also that it's experiential.
Like you have to be there in person.
I mean, you can watch videos of these things.
But that like before YouTube, especially that Sonny Eclipse is doing his eight song set and the only place that you can witness this this once it in the back of a mediocre burger place in Disney World.
Yeah, it's the only way you have to go there and see this weird thing.
But it's a fully fleshed out mythology that you have to sit in one spot to get to learn his lore.
Yeah, yeah.
About his backup singers and his hometown and everything.
It's also like kind of out of the way in a weird way in Tomorrowland, because I remember missing it.
It's not even the first room with tables.
Like, yeah, right.
You have to keep walking to the tables that are around Sonny.
And it's not on the main drag.
It's like kind of in this weird back.
It's as you're exiting.
Yeah, when you're exiting toward Fantasyland by like the teacups.
That's one of the things.
I think the first time we went back like three or four years ago, I think we missed it in Tomorrowland.
And then we're like next time we went back to Tomorrowland on that trip, we're like, oh, yeah, where was it?
Where is he?
So I bet most people don't see him.
Yeah, I had trouble finding him and I was trying to.
Eighty five percent of the people don't find him, which makes it cooler now.
Yeah.
But it also makes his audiences sadder.
It does.
And I guess that's what's so cool about him is like there's literally no reason they had to put him in because it's not a good enough restaurant.
The people are lingering.
No.
They're just going to eat it immediately.
Leave.
And I believe it was there before Tomorrowland 94.
Really?
Before it was done.
I think the restaurant was.
The restaurant was.
Yeah, I think that's been there for a while.
And so was Sunny there?
Did they have Sunny?
No, Sunny came along with the Tomorrowland redo in the 90s.
My family, I remember we liked Sunny for a little while because in addition to burgers, they had cheese steaks.
And as Pratt Philadelphians, we were in Pratt.
We were like, these aren't bad.
Wait, but a Philadelphian would want to eat cheese steaks when not in Philadelphia?
For every meal.
It was at the time the food in Florida was so much pizza and burgers.
That's true.
Any little like, oh, a submarine sandwich.
Oh, a cheese steak.
Something different.
Thank God.
That's true.
Well, of course, this restaurant had the three bays.
The burger bay.
The chicken bay.
The chicken bay was the third bay.
And didn't they even have a pizza bay?
So they were hitting all the boxes of things that they have at theme parks.
I don't think they do pizza anymore.
All the greatest food.
I don't think so.
But of course, they thought it would be too on the nose to have pizza.
An infamous Sheridan family story.
So of course, it had the topping bar.
Don't tell me you just went and got toppings.
OK, hold on.
I've heard that on the Life Hacklist.
I've been like, now who would do that?
Last year.
So my God bless my very patient parents, but they would take turns
being yanked around by me crisscrossing the park.
And one night it was my mom's.
I was yanking the whole family around the park and my dad and brother were starving.
And my dad finally was just like, we're going to get something to eat.
And my mom and I weren't really that hungry.
So like we I dragged her off to somewhere else in the park.
And Cosmic Rays was usually open later.
So we went and did it one last ride or two or so.
And then we met that we'll meet you, but we'll come back here when we're done.
We came back.
They were still eating their food because they were slowly to end.
My mom was like, I'm a little hungry.
I don't want to buy anything, but realized she took a plate.
You could make a salad just going down the toppings bar.
You could construct a salad.
Tomato and onions, tomato and lettuce and onion and stuff.
And my mom still tells its story as victory and my dad.
And I kind of got it at the time.
And I'm sure now if I asked him, he would go like, Jesus Christ, what are we doing?
Like, and but my mom still was she's like, that's what I figured out.
You could make the salads at the bar.
I've heard that literally on the status life hack lists where it's like
you can just eat the toppings.
They won't stop you.
It's like those life hacks where it's like in and out.
You can put a lemon wedge and some sugar packets in a free water.
And it's like, just buy the two dollar lemonade.
I don't.
Yeah.
So they had at least bought a bunch of food because they hadn't really eaten in a while.
So like, and we would go back there often.
And because I was fond of study eclipse, I'm assuming they did not hate him
as much time as we spent there.
But yeah, I do remember my mom victoriously telling that story.
And my dad, I'm sure being like, Jesus Christ, what's going on?
I got a popping salad.
If I was like life hack mom with like nine children where, you know, you visit once a year
and you're like, we're going to spend nothing on this vacation.
I would just bring in like those Hawaiian rolls into sunny eclipse and then like
you either buy one thing or just buy nothing and just topping bar it up.
Sure.
Sounds really good, actually.
Customize your Hawaiian bar.
The wine rolls.
Probably better than that flavorless falafel burger.
That sense.
It was so dry.
Yeah.
Do they still have that?
Yeah, it's the only vegetarian thing they have.
And they also kind of just slathered it with like ketchup and mayo and onion straws
and mushrooms and whatever.
And nothing helped.
They think they also were like they had a stunt burger for a while, like a pizza burger.
Or like a pork pork.
You call it a stunt burger?
Like some sort of like Instagram.
Like a gimmick burger.
Like a gimmick.
Yeah, a gimmick burger that was like universally panned.
Like in the last few years, like people like, oh, Jesus, what were they thinking?
The thing with like gimmick burgers is you're supposed to mix it up often enough that no
one has a chance to like remark that it's bad.
Like with the gross pizza of the day, they'll do a pizza port.
Oh, we did that.
It's hamburger pizza.
Yeah, we had that.
Which is the total reversal of the cheeseburger or the pizza cheeseburger.
Yeah.
Just keep flipping them back and forth.
Yeah, my sister usually gets the weird pizzas when we go to pizza port.
And sometimes she likes them.
So I don't know.
Yes, sometimes they'll do like garlic chicken pizza with barbecue sauce and ranch instead
of tomato sauce.
That seems okay.
Yeah, that's okay.
Well, I just invented the next specialty.
That's pretty okay.
All right.
That's like a CPK barbecue chicken.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
So if we haven't, if you haven't been to see Sonny, if you aren't intrigued by the
fact that it is a bad restaurant, especially for vegetarians, that's not enough to get you in the
cheese sauce in a pump.
Also, this isn't like regulated by any sort of system.
You can just go in there.
You can bring food and sit down.
So like, don't let our trashing of the menu dissuade you.
Sometimes my friends would just go in there for a sit and just like watch Sonny Eclipse.
Totally fine.
I say my friends, but like I would be doing it and I would just be bringing them with
me.
And usually I wouldn't tell them where we were going.
I would just be like, oh, there's a good place to sit down.
And they'd be like, it's that robot alien you're always talking about.
Yay.
I believe when it is like packed, packed, they, there was someone finding you a table.
So they might be a little, I've never seen it like that either.
I think as I was like in the heart of August, summer and like, yeah, it was a busy season.
Yeah.
Peak summer.
So they send a mater de into cosmic gray.
Wow.
Yeah.
That's impressive.
Now, well, one thing is that, you know, yeah, we're watching he's, he's this, he's this
Lizzard and they do flesh out this mythology where the restaurant you're in cosmic rays,
starlight cafe.
It's not arbitrary.
They tie it all together and he talks about cosmic ray and working for cosmic ray.
He's employed by cosmic ray.
Don't mistake him for the owner of the restaurant.
Yes.
He's entertainment.
Confusingly, it's not Sonny Eclipse's restaurant.
He just works there and apparently for not a lot of money.
In a real world sense, it makes more sense that he doesn't own the restaurant.
He's entertaining that opposed to the Chuck E cheese model in like theme park vibe.
You feel like he'd be the face of it and the owner and everything.
But what a difficult job that you're the entertainer at all times, all hours of the day
and the owner.
Yeah.
At least Chuck distributes the cooking task to Pasquale.
And also Chuck doesn't perform all day.
I think he performs on the hour or something for like a good 15, 20 minute show.
It's not a loop.
Sonny Eclipse never stops.
Never stops.
Imagine the wear on that animatronic.
Yeah.
Constant and he moves like a pretty good amount.
He rotates his whole body.
His arms move a lot.
He's much better than a Chuck E cheese.
I think his toes tap too.
It's not a cheap looking thing.
No, he looks good.
He looks so much better than and the room isn't bad,
but he looks so much better than everything around him.
He does.
It does feel like he deserves a better space to perform in.
Have you seen the videos of maintenance mode Sonny Eclipse?
No.
Sometimes they'll have like a school talent perform on that stage.
And I believe I saw a video where they were retracting him into the ceiling.
Yes.
He goes up.
He goes up into the sky.
It's amazing.
Everyone's like, I think there was a comment on the YouTube video,
like the space angels are calling him home.
It's beautiful.
Coming for you ladies.
Highly recommend looking up a video of that happening.
Sonny, please don't die on your way back to your home planet like Pucci.
Yeah.
My people need me.
Wow.
You know what's funny?
The voice that I just did was sort of like a borscht belty, almost Chuck E.
Cheesy thing, which in my, I think until I went back and rewatched, I assumed that's
his voice.
But if I'm doing a real Sonny Eclipse impression, it's like, hey folks, I'm Sonny Eclipse.
Yeah.
He's a lounge singer.
He's like a Sinatra or if we're being a modern, a Michael Buble perhaps.
Very true.
A little fun fact I learned is that the man who provided the voice of Sonny Eclipse has
never seen the animatronic perform.
Yes.
That's a great segue into my deep dive on the voice of Sonny Eclipse, the performer
Cal David.
And I'm excited for this.
So Cal David, yeah, he does the voice.
It's sort of unclear if he truly wrote or helped at all writing the songs.
I highly doubt it.
He didn't write the lyrics for sure.
I don't think he had anything to do with it because he was-
I think he's a session singer.
He's a session singer.
He was recruited by George Wilkins.
Do you know about all that?
Yes, I do.
I mean, you might have more information than I do.
Maybe a little.
He wrote, you have in front of you.
George Wilkins, his main claim to fame is he wrote all the Teddy Ruxpin music.
He has all the Disney stuff too.
Oh, sure.
Well, I mean, first things first-
What, like Disney TV shows?
For the tapes and for the TV show, he wrote 150 Teddy Ruxpin songs.
At the time when they were really cranking that property, three to four a week.
When they had Grubby-
Constantly.
That's wild.
When they had Grubby, the best Teddy Ruxpin character.
I don't know about Grubby.
I found out recently he looks almost identical to Skippy, which is pretty rad.
Oh, he does.
I know.
I was shook.
I was shook when I found out.
That's wild.
I was like, I could buy this.
It's like having Skippy, the animatronic.
Oh, cool.
Also, this is a side note.
We can't get sidetracked because we're already too sidetracked.
Oh, no.
Hanna Barbera had a show called Hillbilly Bears a few years before Country Bears.
What?
Interesting.
So that's interesting to me.
I was trying to figure out where the first bears that were Hillbillies came from.
I was like, oh, okay.
So Hanna Barbera, George Wilkins, co-writer on the California Screamin' song.
Is that right?
And it's tough to be a bug.
And The Great Outdoors was written by him.
Ain't nothing but The Great Outdoors.
All the Country Bears Christmas songs is where it's from.
And then George Wilkins was like the protege of Buddy Baker,
who is a co-writer on Haunted Mansion stuff and a bunch of other Disney stuff.
That's crazy.
And this guy George is friends with Cal David.
That's why he's in there.
Cal David.
Everything's intertwined.
We've got Stippy and Grubby.
We've got Buddy Baker.
Actually, there's a reason I don't own a Grubby.
And it's that it only works if you hardwire it to a working Teddy Ruxpin.
You can't just get Grubby.
They have a symbiotic relationship.
It is symbiotic.
You have to wire them together.
So Grubby is really just a display piece unless you can hack him somehow.
There's some enterprising hacker out there.
I need some animatronics expert to make me an Alexa hookup Grubby.
Oh man, somebody's got to be able to do that.
Probably the guy, the Rockafire guy can do it.
Oh, he would do it.
He'd probably do it for a hundred bucks.
Yeah.
Chris Pundo and he'll do the job.
Cal David.
So Cal David.
So did you read about his early?
Scott, so excuse us now for some old man baby boomer rock stuff that we love.
Do you know what I'm talking to say here?
I don't know.
So Cal David is from Chicago and his first band is,
hold on, let me find it's Cal David and the Exceptions.
And it was formed in 1962.
What's their hit?
Well, I have it here and it's good.
I don't think it was a hit, but it's like, I think it's maybe their most famous single.
It's the only one I think I found on YouTube of Cal David and the Exceptions.
But he was in the band with, I'm trying to find, sorry.
Wanted to just be the New York song when he starts playing the lyrics and all.
He invented the New York concept.
Very specific set of talents.
I have this idea about an opposite city.
This guy.
Everything's upside down.
It's wild, man.
Denny Ebert, who I did not know.
This guy, Marty Greb and Greb will later join the Buckinghams who had a hit.
Marty Greb sounds like a fake space character you write.
Yeah.
Marty Greb, the mayor of Tomorrowland.
Friends with Grebby.
Yeah.
Big information score is that he was in this band with Peter Satara.
What?
Now we're talking.
Now we're talking from the band Chicago.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
A Chicago music buddy of Peter Satara.
He was Cal David and Peter Satara were in a band together in the 60s.
And it is, I have too many tabs open on my computer, both Sonny Eclipse related things.
Computers, we'd start smoking.
I have the Cal David song.
Hold on.
With Satara?
With Satara.
It's called Chicago, my man.
Real good.
Questions 67, 68.
This is a little more like kind of blue eyed soul, like Gary US Bonds type.
Okay.
Which I'm way into.
Who's singing what you're going to play me?
It's Sonny Eclipse.
What?
He's singing.
Okay.
Early Sonny.
Or this is early Sonny Eclipse.
I'm just realizing if I-
We're going to find out if the voice is an affect or if it's just how he sings.
I'm going to do it on my phone because I don't want to get like,
IMs or anything right now.
Sorry about this, Phil, Phil, Phil.
I'm realizing-
Well, here we go, here we go, here we go.
Got it.
All right.
I've listened to this song, by the way, maybe 10 times in the last 24 hours.
Are you going to sing along though?
It sounds exactly like it.
We'll go to the chorus.
Does it sound like Spotify or anything?
I don't know.
This is so new that I'm...
And Satara's on this too?
That's what I...apparently there's so little information though about...
He handled this.
And the title is Day Dreaming of You?
I'm gonna look this up.
Peter Satara and Sonny Eclipse were in a band.
Yes. Sonny Eclipse is a talented guy.
Insane.
Yeah.
Well, when I Googled the guy, one of the first Google images was a photo of him arm-in-arm recently with Jimmy Vivino, leader of the Kona.
Wonderful musician, wonderful guy. What's that?
I wanted you to say with the Sonny Eclipse animatronic.
No, I guess he never met him.
He never met him.
I listened to an interview years ago with the guy who composed the music for the Marvel Super Hero Island area music.
Sure.
And he was like, yeah, I've never been down there. Never seen it.
My kids are almost teenagers. They'd probably like it.
They'd probably like to go down there.
I don't get that.
Yeah, I don't either.
And I didn't know because I had heard he'd never seen Sonny Eclipse, but I didn't know if that was dated information.
Maybe if he said that in the early 2000s and he's been since.
How would you resist?
Yeah, it is.
Okay, so you've been a voice of a robot for over 20 years.
Yeah.
As of June 7th, 2018, Cal David had still not seen Sonny Eclipse.
I know because I listened to his interview on the Tiara talk show.
What?
This is a show that I don't think exists anymore.
How many views?
127 views.
No.
There is an interview and I have not listened to it with Debbie Reynolds on this YouTube channel.
Oh my God.
It says Debbie Reynolds and then there's a Disney connection.
How many views on that one?
140 years.
No.
It was that low.
So I was like, oh my God.
Old people don't understand what online numbers to look for.
They're like, a hundred. That's a lot.
Well, Cal, God bless him. This interview is exclusively about Sonny Eclipse.
This has nothing to do with any of his music. He has had a long career.
I'm sold. I'm going to be the 128th view.
I knew the audience could be 129.
So Kaiser Permanente, Tiara Time, whatever it's called.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We got a lot of homework for you on this Spark Hopper day.
So Cal is honestly, he is a great sport in this interview.
Good.
He's like Skyped in.
This very nice sounding girl is asking him just exclusive Disney and Sonny Eclipse questions.
He's had a long career of like playing.
And I'm sure he remembers nothing of that recording session.
You know, you he he remembers more than I would think, because he's kind of like an old blues guy.
Basically, he plays blues. He's still playing.
He plays out in like in the desert.
He's in.
I would go see him live if he played even one Sonny Eclipse song.
We have to figure this out.
I would do it regardless. I can have him sign my Park Stars.
We have to figure it out.
Could we go make this happen?
Yeah. Well, that's so.
So I found where he plays.
It's it's this.
I have too many tabs open and I'm getting mad.
I can have a birthday party at Chuck E.
Cheese, but book my own performer and it's Sonny Eclipse.
So can you imagine he's performing next to a barely active robot?
Yeah. Oh, my God.
It's super meta, but it's really going to bring the house down.
We could make him do all the jokes, but then write him some new jokes.
And he would know the voice of Sonny Eclipse.
Comedy dream.
He plays. OK, here we go.
It's Vickies of Santa Fe in Indian Wells.
So he's like, yeah, it's Palm Springs.
So he just lives in Palm Springs and he plays.
He's been with his wife, Lori Bono.
I think is how you pronounce it.
He's been with her for like 40 years and they played together.
Married to Bono.
Oh, a Bono and and Laura and she is one of the angels.
What?
So we could get is that how they met and fell in love?
No, but it would be a great story.
So she I always shipped Sonny and one of his space.
Sure. Of course.
How could you not? Yeah.
He said that. So in this interview on this Tiara show, he says that his
that his wife at the time had a group of singers with her.
She was in them, I think, called the Brunettes.
And it was Lori Bono, Patty Brooks and Amy Weston.
Those are the space angels.
So we have the names of the space.
We can keep researching deeper and deeper.
We can look up the lives of all the space angels.
We're going to have to go do a deeper dive.
You need to come back in a couple of months.
You guys need to have like a crazy, like beautiful mind thing on your wall.
Well, Mike already has all these printouts with red yarn connecting them all.
Newspaper clippings from like yesterday.
Mike's going to be hauled away to an institution saying too many tabs, too many tabs.
Mike bought that new monitor from CES.
That is like the length of the desk that you can make a horizontal or vertical.
All Cal David related. Did you guys come across?
They recorded these songs like at George Wilkins House, I believe.
I think I saw something about the space angel like they recorded him, recorded them all.
Yeah.
And they didn't know in that moment that they were going to record one of the most popular albums of all time.
Yeah, we didn't know what we were doing.
We're just kids, missing out on you know.
Yeah.
Cal in that interview did remember a lot of it.
What?
And he seemed like kind of funny, like, aha, I think he called the joke.
So again, if you don't know, Sonny will do a lot of bad puns in between his songs.
And I think Cal said he goes, you know, I'm a little more urbane than Sonny, but you know, those jokes play well in Disney.
Like he seemed like he was like a pretty, he was game.
I want to see him live.
He remembered the, he remembered the songs and she, because she asked him what his favorite song was.
And he said.
And he knew the name of one of the songs.
He did.
I'm impressed by that.
Yeah. And I'm trying to, again, too many tabs here.
I've got one that I'm hoping it is.
It's the.
I do too.
It's the second one with the angels.
It's the little, what is it?
What are the names of the songs?
Hello space angel.
That's the first space angel song, right?
Okay.
That's where he introduces them.
Yes.
It's the second name.
The song does somebody have the song?
I was going to say out in space.
The one where it sounds like he wants to have sex with earth.
Loves the center of the universe.
There's bright little star.
It's bright little star.
That's his favorite.
That's my favorite Sonny Eclipse song as well.
So you and Cal are on the same page.
Yeah.
And he's singing about a long distance relationship with perhaps a space angel.
And he's saying that like that your light is shining on me,
even though we're far away from each other.
We explicitly said that his backup singers, the space angels,
the fact that I learned from your video,
I know this fact that the space angels are disembodied backup singers
because they are not represented by robots.
They're invisible.
And he sings an entire song about the lore of how he met the space angels
and reestablishes that they are invisible.
And that's why there aren't any more animatronics.
It's not because they didn't want to build more.
It's because the space angels are invisible because they're from space
and they're angels and they sing backup.
Yes.
And one day he was at a show playing by himself
and he heard the voices of the space angels and they've been with him ever since.
What a delight.
One of them is his wife.
And Hello Space Angels is my favorite.
I'll put that out there.
That's a great song.
Yeah, that's the yeah, that might be my favorite too.
The space angels.
What about his title song, though?
The Hello All You Earthlings.
My name is Sonny Eclips.
That's good too.
That one's a bop.
Yeah, that one's good too.
You can dance to it.
My number one is Out in Space, which I've also seen referred to as Bossa Supernova.
At least that's the genre that he says that the song is.
And I like it because it sounds to me like a sort of a world music attempt
that Todd Rundgren might have made in the early 90s.
Like he's really Sonny's playing in 90s Rundgren territory.
So Scott's in.
Yeah, I don't like you, Norik, because the lyrical like gymnastics
give me like secondhand nervous sweats at the idea of him having to get the lyrics right.
It must have been that must have been the sweatiest part of the recording session.
Oh, I'm sure.
I always think about the songs in terms of how much Sonny was sweating while he was singing it.
If yeah, it was a bright little star, probably the least sweaty.
The more just like kind of bluesy barely changing keys, you're probably good.
But yeah, there's like there's a lot of lyrics jammed in.
Let's talk about that.
It's a lot of tongue twisters as well.
As we said, Sonny Eclipse is from you, Norik.
Can you read aloud a portion of the lyrics like a middle verse?
I have the lyrics in front of me.
A little lazy.
What's going on here, you know, city is like an opposite city.
And you think that it's just a throwaway fact about him.
But then you get an entire song about where he comes from.
And let's just say that you Norik City is a topsy turvy place.
It is.
It's a little bit of an inside out version of the New York City we know from our plan.
Or should you say upside down, upside down or downside up?
Oh, Mike, would you like to treat us?
Yeah, I mean, I were to begin.
I guess I'll just start with the first.
So he says you, Norik, you, Norik is my hometown.
You, Norik is upside down and every single part of it is underground because up above the surface, there's nothing around.
When then there's a backup like we're talking about all over town.
And then, I mean, I'll just keep going, I guess.
I mean, I could do the middle verses.
He'll just switch around the opening syllables because it gets dense.
Yeah, that's true.
I should go like central grand.
Well, right around when I get interested, especially when he starts talking about sports,
the Unorc Yanks, if I got that correct, they are who are green and fat and always get beat.
But it really it gets it goes double speed when he starts talking about how he takes around the town.
Caxi tabs.
With a C, Caxi tabs.
Right.
It's so stressful.
You're like bothered by.
Yeah, by him having to perform this song and get all the wrong lyrics correct.
Yeah.
All these fake words.
Caris Andelin blues scales.
He's got he's got no problem.
You're right.
He's a professional.
He's got a very active mind.
It was a problem of their own making.
They didn't have to do this.
No, he could have just sang about backwards and upside down concepts without jumbling the words.
Without jumbling the words.
I like the Borsch Belt jokes, but you know, work does make my skin crawl a little.
What do you mean?
From a comedy perspective.
Oh, my man.
I like the planet Zork.
Give us some more phrases.
We got Caxi tabs.
Yeah.
And if you can't hail a Caxi, then you maybe could go down to the way sub station.
It's all real.
And you can take that to a number of places.
You could go to Av Parkinou.
Oh, God.
You could go to Harnegy Call.
No.
Or maybe you want to check out the Doll War Historia.
What?
Wait, I missed a part of something.
I forget.
You know where we really need to go is Squaddison Merr Garden.
Oh, I thought you were going to say we should go to Pyre M. State, which was climbed by
hairy old Kong King.
Oh, God.
It might be good again.
I might change my mind.
And maybe, but you also got to go see the Big Green Lady, the Libber of Statutey.
Oh, I'd like to just I mean, I think from this song, you get a pretty big, you know,
view of Unark City and all of its culture and all the stuff to do.
But he did miss a lot.
I mean, I would like to hear him sing about Min Lanwell Miranda's musical about
Alexander Hamilton.
Yeah.
You know, or like some of the culture, some of the great films made about Unark City.
I mean, Skartan Mortese made so many great Unark films with Robert Rodero.
Of course, this great character, Bavis Trickle, who then his famous phrase, you
mock into T. Are you mocking the T.
You know, the female filmmaker, Ali Wooden and her movies, Han Matan and Hany
Hall.
But, you know, it's also it's been an interesting time in Unark City.
Have you noticed how there are never protests outside of Tump Trower?
I mean, ever since he went up the escalator, Drondald Tump to announce his candidacy.
I could keep going.
Sure.
Yeah, keep going, please.
I mean, really.
But the the main thing is the Unark is in the shadow of the 11 nine that day.
The one tower.
No, I'll always forget 11.
No, I was wondering if he was going to go there.
Yeah.
Well, it's Patreon, you know, these are the hard core.
Yeah, you get a little blue.
It's like Sony's light show.
That bastard, Lynn Bodden.
I will say.
The quirky alien.
Since he drove those trains into the single tower.
I mean, the city is at least under confident leadership with the DILT Babassio.
I think he's a better mayor than Jude.
I will say that he's more of a good guy than all frulling on his supportive tump.
He's very much in a mess.
Well, and also and let's you know, we also should salute the bravery of Captain Bergen Seller who drove his boat into those dolphins and had to go in for a crash rising.
Did you say was this an all nighter?
There's a lot of coffee.
That's all you've got?
A couple days grand in and out. I think I'm tapped out. But again, we'll hit this all again in three months and we'll all have more time to remember great stuff about Unark City.
Of course.
When we have Cal on the show, obviously.
Oh, he'll love to hear.
Yeah, we'll do all of it for him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He'll do those lines.
I'll feel.
Well, we can if we're going to build a set for Cal to bring Sonny back in Palm Springs.
Right.
Yeah, we can like expand that.
I feel like a puppet would be doable.
Hmm.
Yeah.
A Sonny close puppet or gorilla style with a hologram.
Right.
Is there a do we have enough listeners in Palm Springs to do a live show?
I thought it would be just us.
Oh, okay.
Fine.
Sure.
Just an audience of like four people.
A private engagement.
But you do like rent out a venue and you don't make it clear to him that it's not going to
be like a full crowd.
But he's just like, whoo, space angel.
We want to give him the real Sonny Clips experience.
If he's married to a space angel, he can bring at least one of them and we can put her behind
a scrim.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, she's still invisible.
Yeah, she has to be invisible.
She will not have her day in the sun.
She cannot be seen because she's a space angel.
All of his live shows are listed as him and his wife.
Oh.
Great.
So they're still performing together.
Where are they playing next?
Where and when?
In Indian Wells.
But when?
Like soon.
Like next weekend?
Yeah, like that.
Hold on.
Let me find that date.
They play often.
Yes.
Can we make requests?
They're playing in three days.
They're playing March 2nd, March 9th, March 16th, March 23rd, March 30th, April 6th.
They have a residency.
They just have a residency at Vickies of Santa Fe in Indian Wells, California.
Oh, my God.
I have to go.
So if you're just a Disney nerd in Palm Springs and you haven't gone to see.
Sure.
It's all.
And maybe do the.
I mean, if we don't book him, we could pick a night that we're all going to go.
Like all the Diz fans in the area commute over to sunny Eclipse town.
I honestly think to like, if you could arrange that, all you've got to do is relearn one of these songs.
We can get like those I Heart NY shirts, but they say I Heart YN.
Oh, my God.
But it's an upside down.
Yeah, I upside down heart.
Why?
And yeah, I mean, that's fantastic.
Reminiscent of the kind of thing that Lon Jemmell would wear.
And then the back is like a tour list of all the different cities he plays at.
Sure.
Oh, wow. Yeah.
Ass, longelus.
Zebulon Nebula or whatever.
Oh, I see.
OK.
It's not all backwards.
Yeah, or it could be.
Yeah, it could be.
It's a mix.
Some are outer space and some are.
Yeah, off Langelis is definitely.
Did anyone read?
Did anyone read about his son eclipse's cousin and where he's from?
Oh, the Japanese one.
Officer Six.
Yes.
The one that works TSA.
So yeah, in case you that's actually the first one.
The Star Wars episode, Star Wars episode a while back.
Oh, yeah.
He existed before Sonny.
So, so.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
So we had an interview.
Cal David said they showed me what Sonny would look like, but they were showing me he knew
he was like it's from Tokyo.
It's the flesh colored one.
Yeah.
So he goes and then they showed me like a mock up of what he would look like with the
hair and the jacket and stuff.
This is a drawing from the one of the imaginary coffee table books.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
You can see his full body.
It's a little unnerving to see all of him.
Pink sparkly jacket.
Is he wearing pants?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He's got white sparkly pants on.
And Cal David knew.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Cal David knew the name Captain Zzix.
What?
Wow.
He says he goes, I think it was.
Oh, he's so much more in than me.
Right.
He goes, I think it was, even though he's never seen it, he's like, I think it's.
I think he's being coy about not seeing Sonny.
I think he's been a lot.
I think he's been there a lot.
Officer Zzix.
Excuse me.
Oh, excuse me.
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He sounds way too invested for someone that didn't bother to go see the show.
Somebody wrote Cal.
I copied this.
Hey, Jenny Nicholson.
Thanks for putting me number one on your list.
Yeah, yeah.
He mentions it in the podcast.
Officer Zzix was the, if you didn't hear this in a previous episode, when you left, no longer
there, but when you left Star Tours.
I don't believe he's there anymore.
Is he there?
I don't think he is.
Wait, now I'm turning.
We were just there.
Yeah, you would have freaked out if he's not.
I guess I didn't see him.
No.
When you left Star Tours, the Tokyo version, there'd be a guy checking you out, like the
passport guy, and he looked exactly like our favorite alien, Sunny Eclipse.
It was the same mold and everything.
Yeah, he was either customs or like lost baggage counter or something.
Yeah, he's got like a bank of monitors behind him, and that seems like some of the delight
of Tokyo, and some of what they brought to Tomorrowland 94 was these oddball characters,
like the chef in the Pan Galactic pizza board.
Yes, they have a full show in there.
Oh, that's right.
It's a Sunny Eclipse, but on steroids.
It has a whole set.
Yeah.
It moves around.
It interacts.
I'm six weeks away.
I'm so close.
It has a whole pizza.
I'm going.
You're going in six weeks.
I don't have any immediate plans to go, but I want to go real bad.
I'm so, so excited.
And that's the kind of, that's where I do need to build the time in, because I'm going to
want to watch the whole loop of this pizza show.
Yeah, you're going to need a lot of Japanese pizza.
I had one pizza the one time I went to Japan, and it was like, it was not good pizza.
They put corn on it.
Corn and shrimp.
It was like sweet tomato sauce and corn, but it wasn't like a corn pizza.
It was like, it's a pizza, a normal pizza.
And then you got it and there was corn on it.
They just think that's normal.
I studied abroad in Germany and at one point the school ordered pizza.
Oh, hooray pizza.
The pizza came out.
The pizza had tuna on it.
Just like canned tuna on it.
See, corn was like, I'm for it.
Eating tuna pizza.
In New York City.
She made New York because it's upside down.
Yeah, that kind of shit might fly in New York City, but not here in Earth.
That's some kind of upside down world pizza.
It was also on Sunset Boulevard at Bossa Nova.
Restaurant Bossa Nova.
I've had that.
Anyway.
But there's a blog that calls him Captain Zizik as well.
But this claims, and I don't know, I haven't seen this anywhere else, that Captain Zizik's or whatever is from Juneurzy.
What?
Across the ridge.
Is that real?
What is the site that you're on though?
It's a Disney blog, Disney hipster blog.
I don't know if it's goofing on it or not.
It must be goofing on it because that doesn't sound like an okay phrase.
Like is Juneurzy, yes.
Yeah, a little bit.
I think that, because I found some Officer Zizik's info that I don't think was trustworthy because I think it was on some sort of like fan canon site.
So that's what I'm more, I'm skeptical of Zizik's info.
There is little Zizik's info.
So everything else I've said, I'm very confident in this podcast.
But yes, that one, I agree that source is maybe not the most reputable.
But I will look into it.
And when we do the next episode about Sunny Eclipse or the Officer Zizik's episode, I will have more hard facts.
In terms of reputable, do you have to call out one of the songs in the lineup?
I am of course talking about Starlight Soup and Salad.
It does not appear that for a long time, if ever, soup and salad have been a feature.
Perhaps a salad bar or a side salad, an anemic one that comes with it.
Definitely never soup. I don't buy that for a moment.
No, I don't know that they got full menu.
They just don't seem like a place that would have an infrastructure for soup.
No, this sounds more like a diner or like a sit down, like a place where you're ordering a platter.
It's some kind of bougie fantasy, Sunny Eclipse, where they can serve salad and soup.
But Janie, I do have good news for you.
Oh, good.
It appears I do not see the falafel burger.
I do see something called a plant based sloppy joe.
That sounds worse.
Yeah, that's potentially dicey.
The falafel burger is like lacking flavor.
A plant based sloppy joe sounds like something that goes for flavor and the result isn't good.
I don't I know it's real hit and miss with plant based or fake beef or a plant based beef crumbles,
tossed in sloppy joe sauce of diced onions, yellow mustard, ketchup, garlic and brown sugar.
All the things I've like yearned to eat.
Fuck you. That's an awful phrase.
Yeah, no, like every time I've thought about like meat based foods like, oh, I'd like to eat that.
Sloppy Joe has never made the list.
But what if I were to tell you it came with fries?
I mean, it's pretty good.
Pretty good.
They should bump it up to onion rings if I'm suffering a vegetarian sloppy joe.
Fair, fair.
Three sides minimum.
Just give me some flatbreads, you guys.
Any other we're kind of going song by song a little.
Any other songs that with the song you were the most fond of?
Great little star, a lovely little love song about the space angel.
That's really nice. That's wonderful.
I did I write it down?
My top or bossa nova and you know, you're not so fun.
There's a wait. Is this in the soup and salad one?
I just wrote down the lyrics.
The menu is from outer space, including the fries that might be the one that's just about cosmic rays.
Yeah, I think that's like try the burgers and stuff.
And there's a line about cosmic chicken meat, which is almost as unappetizing.
As plant based beef crumbles.
Actually, yeah, plant based beef crumbles.
I'm kind of sold on it now because it sounds like something from a future like a grim future.
It does.
Where they're like eat your protein capsules and your plant based beef crumbles.
The world of food pellets.
The future is now.
It's in Soylent Green.
That is Tomorrowland.
Yeah, we talked about the Beyond Burger and Impossible Burgers.
Both been pretty good recently.
So I don't know. Maybe it's one of those.
I'll give the beef crumbles a go.
Give it a try.
What do you think a Yorkian tastes like?
If you were to take a...
We shouldn't be killing anybody of sunny species, but...
If we did, do you think sunny is delicious or zizzics?
Probably like a really gamey sausage.
I think honestly rubbery.
That's the best answer I could come up with.
Best case scenario, a mediocre hot dog.
And even to Jason, that's not bad.
I don't...
Yeah, like that was...
When we did the live show, I kind of forgot to eat right beforehand.
I realized there was a hot dog cart right outside.
When we did the That's From Disneyland thing, there was a hot dog guy outside the Marshalls.
Oh, you did a show at That's From Disneyland? That's fun.
Yeah, that's what we did at the Tony Wexler show.
Did you frolic around first and like touch things?
We went through it a couple of times.
Yeah, yeah.
I only went out there once, but it was a great exhibit.
That was very, very well done.
Yeah, yeah.
The hot dog left a bit to be desired.
I'm surprised there was a hot dog cart near it.
It was like an abandoned mattress store or something.
Or sports authority.
Yeah, sports authority.
A Petco and like a Marshalls or a Ross.
Not a logical place to park a hot dog cart.
Not a logical place, but also I was not the only one getting a hot dog from that cart.
Okay, maybe they just went there on show nights.
There is a mall food court half a block away.
So that was the other thing.
Tony Baxter not in the hot dog line.
He went to Bob's Big Boy after the show.
He did go to Bob's Big Boy after the show.
Did you guys go with him?
We did not.
Why not?
We're not sure, honestly.
We expected that we would be best friends.
You just spent two hours talking to us.
You aren't going to immediately take us to a restaurant.
That's the fantasy.
I mean, if you already know where you're going, you'd think you'd go.
Anyone for Big Boy burgers?
Maybe he's seeing friends.
He was with friends.
He was with a group of friends.
Okay, then that's weird.
The Van Eten Gallery heavies were trying to get us out of there so quickly.
Yeah.
So next time we'll go with them.
Did you guys get anything from the auction?
It was a little too...
I didn't even look at what stuff sold for.
I was afraid to.
Yeah.
Who got the sea monster?
See, that's what I understand.
These things go up for sale and then you don't find out who got them.
As if anyone would buy that and not immediately post on social media about it.
We've seen some.
Did Stamos clean up everything?
Yeah, probably.
Yes, friggin' Stamos.
Friggin' Stamos.
The D, the big D from the Disneyland Hotel went to David Copperfield.
That's the level of rich they had to be.
That's fine.
And then the other one, Chris Jenner bought several Small World dolls.
I wouldn't have suspected Chris Jenner would be interested in that.
Well, the daughter.
I forget which one.
They're going to put it in a nursery or something?
Well, she Instagrammed the two of them.
An early case of a Kardashian with creepy music things operating without being acknowledged in a palatial home.
I feel like at least the theme park stuff, you can't even be salty about it.
Because even if it's someone you wouldn't assume would be interested in it, you just have to be like,
Well, I guess they are interested in it if they bought it because I'm sure it wasn't cheap.
I can't imagine.
I guess they must love Small World, so it's kind of charming.
If you needed Jenner and Copperfield money.
I know.
That's rough.
And to imagine, when they were first sold, I think the Sea Monster sold in its prior auction by Disney for $4,000.
Wow.
I know that someone bought the shark fighting the octopus and the two lobsters for $2,000 for both of them.
Geez.
And it was literally just a D23 auction that not a lot of people attended.
And it wasn't really a thing yet to collect theme park memorabilia.
So everything sold for pretty low.
Well, those guys, the crafts, I think were not.
I'm sure it was always expensive.
The crafts are extremely wealthy, which is probably why he got all of it.
You're making me think how much I would like to own the Astro Organ.
Sunny Eclipse, the Astro Organ.
Oh, would it come with Sunny though?
So you're saying you hope they decommission Sunny.
And so you can buy the organ?
Well, I don't want to wish that reality.
If I could buy any object from Disneyland, it would be the Curly Lamp in Toontown.
Oh, nice.
I would love that.
Oh, yeah, that is a good one.
Yeah, I used to always take my picture with it every visit.
And now that I live locally, it seems a bit weird.
So I don't think I have in a while, but I should catch up.
Yeah, that's good.
I'm trying to think what have I said?
I wanted that country bear sign from the auction, but obviously that went for so much money.
It's a small thing, but I would like in the Star Tours line, the frame that you pass through that's lit up and then the slats.
If I could just get one of those that's in one of the doorways in my home, I feel like I'm passing through a Star Tours call.
Yeah, that's good.
Let me see here.
And Jason's would be a mediocre hot dog.
Yeah, just for the sake of clarity, I would give the hot dog cart another shot.
I don't want to talk about too much.
I'm working hard.
Real quick, I for more David information, not his only appearance in the theme park.
Oh, you're kidding.
He did in Epcot Center, a little thing called Goofy About Health.
Oh, I've heard that from the Wonders of Life pavilion.
Wonders of Life.
And he does like a blues song, which we'll post a link to.
I won't play it right now.
He does a blues song about health and he tells a very he's very amused by the story.
He tells it on that interview about how I think George Wilkins was working on it with him.
And he has to say like he has to warn you about like smoking and stuff.
And then George Wilkins was like, when you sing cancer, really smile, really add, making him a lot happier.
And he's like, he was so delighted by the weirdness by that direction.
Wow.
So that's not. Yeah.
So he was he doesn't realize he was really into these jobs.
He see. Yeah.
He does seem like he was like, I was a funny.
I think he says it. He was like, it was so fun working with George and it was a fun.
I wonder if everybody lies when they say that, honestly.
I don't know.
People love to just be like, oh, it was a long time ago.
I don't even remember what it what it was like.
And it's like, really?
Or are you just like, I feel like people say that when they think the work is like beneath them.
Yes.
And they want to like play it cool.
Or they're like, oh, it's just a session singer.
But like with him, it seems like he's just like, yeah, it was really fun.
I remember all of it because I spent days working on it and it was a cool opportunity.
Well, the fact that it's this long, that it's this half hour program and you can't just like.
It's a long session.
I don't think he could have just banged it out.
Yeah. Like you said, musical dexterity.
It's probably a day per song, even though it is a session thing or singing thing.
Yeah.
I think it probably took a little search time.
It is. It does.
I was thinking he was going to be like cranky about it, but he's obviously he agreed to do the Tiara talk show.
Yeah.
He had to have some idea that the interview.
He was waiting to talk about it.
Yeah.
So all right.
He's doing these shows all the time and I bet he's like if he's doing shows every week, he's changing that up or he's improvising.
He's keeping that thing interesting.
Are you going to speculate that at least once he performed a Sonny Eclipse?
Well, that I don't know.
But I think if we were to.
That's probably a legal thing.
If we were to make that request and get a lot of people out.
Specifically to see it.
I mean, it can't just be the four.
Yeah, if we've sold out the room or whatever.
This honestly seems like this could be a magical thing.
It could. And then do a Q&A at the end.
Yeah. Yes.
I like.
But.
Imagine the love of this bizarre specific thing bouncing back at it.
All you have to do is perform.
Learn one of these songs.
Yeah. Relearn one of them.
I'm sure we could commission an instrumental.
And then we all get, you know, like I'm never going to Coachella.
Dear God, I don't want to deal with that.
But the idea of a Palm Springs escape to hear music that I love.
How delightful.
And this would be like a mini Coachella.
It's only one song long.
It's very comfortable.
I can sit.
I'm not going to get exhausted.
So.
You can call it Chelkoa.
Chelkoa.
Featuring Sonny.
I would like to hear some of what he's playing now.
I mean, we need to pay our dues.
He'll incorporate one Sonny Eclipse song as his finale.
It's his set.
And then he learns a Sonny song.
He learns one.
Maybe just the intro song where he's singing, my name is Sonny Eclipse.
Yeah. Yeah.
This is the place you can get a little, this is where he plays.
It's like every couple of days.
I feel like you could fill it with what?
Like 150 people.
Yeah.
That's what it looks like.
Pretty decent size.
I feel like there are that many Sonny Eclipse enthusiasts in the area.
Yeah.
That feels doable.
And people, I think LA people are going out.
I think so.
Yeah.
I think a big caravan shows up.
People don't want to hear about caravans in the desert, but wrong word.
Oh no.
But yeah, a lot of people are going to come see this thing.
That's what I'm trying to say.
And they're going to be full of love.
And worse comes to worse too.
There's a huge annual pass holder, older scene.
So I think maybe try to sell it to hip young people first.
And then if you still have tickets you need to move, put it on a Facebook group.
I'm sure.
Because the old folks on Facebook.
If there were APs that go to Disney every day because they're retired, they would do that.
I think so.
Yeah.
He plays, to answer your question, it's mostly blues.
It's almost exclusively blues that he plays now.
I think there's a version even where he just does a blues version.
He can do it in whatever.
Whatever style.
Yeah.
It just needs to be.
Because I think, because he can, I'll say this, I was listening to him do a couple different covered, while my guitar gently weeps, a bunch of other stuff.
The guy can wail.
He knows what he's doing.
So yeah, I think let him do his set and throw us a little ball.
And however many he's willing to do of Sunny Eclipse.
I mean, Bright Little Star, there's a lot of longing there, like we said.
So that might be the natural choice.
But is that going to get the crowd swinging the way that the Sunny Eclipse song would?
Or Hello Space Angels.
It's like you want to hear, it's like hearing Sergeant Pepper's Only Heart.
You want to hear the theme of this musical concept.
Exactly.
That maybe one's the main, in the main set, one is the encore.
Ooh.
Sure.
I want to, you know, however much or however little he wants to do, I just, to go to the desert and pay homage to Sunny.
I would do it.
This is my version of a vision quest of a mescaline trip.
Are there any eclipses coming up?
Because imagine.
Oh my God.
If it was the same days in Eclipse and then you go out in the desert and watch the eclipse and it's, there's no light pollution because you're in the desert.
Whoa.
I know.
So the, so magical moment number one, eclipse in a beautiful place.
Eclipse with Sunny Eclipse.
This is so smart.
Okay.
We need to coordinate.
First step, look up eclipse.
Second clip, second thing, talk to this guy and see if he's willing to do it.
And sell t-shirts.
Yes.
And then, well, we could do t-shirts first also.
I heard YN.
Also, really the eclipse is like a unorthodox opposite.
Instead of the heart, it's a sunny eclipse face.
Yeah.
We could just do like a Rodcast the pie.
The pie.
Rodcast the pie.
Those are going to really fly off the shelves.
I don't know.
And the colon.
The the.
Yeah, yeah.
And the colon is flipped upside down.
We could honestly.
We could go to one of these regular shows.
Oh no.
Okay.
So we are back.
We just had a little bit of a break.
We got so excited about this potential live show that a glass was shattered.
We had a little bit of a literal break.
There's a literal break.
A figurative and literal break.
I think one of the space angels pushed it off.
Yeah.
It wasn't my elbow.
It was a space.
It was a space angel.
They got so excited at the prospect of a new gig.
Yeah.
Sure.
And shattered your commemorative sunny eclipse tumbler.
Your commemorative dime a dozen high ball glass.
No, you're one of a kind.
You shitting on the glasses.
Jason was really shitting on the glasses.
Mike's cruddy old.
The lenses too.
The old glasses.
That's even worse.
So mean, Jason.
The roast master private.
I guess that's true.
I never really do.
You always wear that big uniform like Jeffrey Ross.
Of course.
Yeah, sure.
We know.
Up on every recording.
I mean, there's not too much left to say really.
Let's make this happen.
I think this is a, I'm too lazy to do this, but this sounds like the culmination of a
great documentary.
Oh yeah.
You know, like I feel like there's some story of the guy who didn't know he was big in Japan
and then went and played in Japan.
And it would be one of those documentaries that's like about you trying to contact him
the whole time.
Just talking about it.
So it's like, it feels like the beginning of the documentary is unnecessary.
Right.
And then the end is you succeeding, which could have just been the documentary, but
yeah, you need to pad it.
It's a very my date with Drew situation.
Yes.
It's all chasing something and it's all about us.
It's you and your personal journey.
A movie I've seen at least twice because that guy went to my college.
And then came back and screened it.
Oh, wow.
Gee whiz.
So yeah, we'll make the movie.
We'll make the show.
It all happened for real.
Yep.
Yeah.
I don't want to, I, I, there's only one thing in my notes that was not said and it was something
that you brought up, Jason, this bizarre line about it's a small world.
Oh yeah.
He starts playing it's a small world.
Oh right.
Right at the end.
Instrumentally.
Right.
Yeah.
We were talking about this the other day.
At the end he starts playing it's small world and he says, why did I start playing that
tune?
We use that on my planet Zork to break the enemy.
Wow.
Which is.
That's a mean spirited joke.
It is a mean spirited joke.
Like it's a really dark joke because like the armed forces and the intelligence communities
of the world have used music to torture people.
Like playing songs on a loop.
David Lynch also funnily enough, their AV club did a series about like what song do
you absolutely hate?
And David Lynch's was it's a small world is a nightmare.
A man known for making movies that are waking night bears like eight small worlds.
People always pick it's a small world.
Always pick small world.
But they should really be picking the holiday overlay of it's a small world.
Yeah.
I told you about the people that got trapped there, right?
No, I don't think so.
It was one of my experiences when I was working in complaints and it was Christmas time and
a family came over and said that they had been stuck there for 40 minutes inside of
it's a small world and that chaos erupted and they started the story by saying and it's
the Christmas song.
So you know, it's more annoying.
And I was like, right?
Wow.
Like I was already on board with what they were telling me.
I was like, of course.
Of course.
And they said that people were like wetting themselves, falling out of the boats, climbing,
haphazardly over the side of the flume and panicking.
I guess what happened is the ride broke down and the intercom system also broke, but nobody
outside realized it broke.
So they had been saying announcements like, we'll be with you shortly.
Like stay calm.
But everyone inside just thought they'd been abandoned by God and they were trapped.
There was lawless in there.
And so yeah, there was panic.
People were tumbling out of their boats off the side, falling to the floor below, running
into props, scrambling out the exit and wandering aimlessly into the backstage area, not knowing
how to get back to the park.
And usually you hear like a wild tale and you just think someone wants like fast passes.
So you have to like call the attraction.
So like I went in the back and I called small world and I was like, I've just heard like
a strange story.
And they were like, it's all true.
Oh my God.
Horrifying.
So it's true.
It can break.
I just think break the enemy like that.
That actually gives him a lounge singer like level like Frank Sinatra's connection.
He did a tour of active duty.
Is that required on the planet Zork?
Possibly.
Well, there's no draft in America.
So there has to be an opposite.
Yeah.
Every every 18 year old.
And who is the enemy?
That's what I'd like to know.
Who is the enemy?
It definitely gives him a layer of darkness.
Like so much more.
Sinatra's relationship with acknowledging that it's not peace times on the planet Zork.
Well I guess they're probably at war with corthneria.
Yeah.
Among other.
He was mostly on the OSU shows.
You're right.
He wasn't seen in any action.
Yeah.
Like Cobb Boat.
Yes.
So there, I mean, what else can you say?
Like you think he's doing Voland Stalart?
Like John, like Voland Stalart?
Like John Wayne?
Sorry, Juan Jane?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I guess their, their intelligence has not been compromised by the uviat sovian.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Tough one.
We got one to get in the show before someone brain breaks.
Crazy joke to get through all the layers of Disney.
Platamir Booten.
Disney okay.
Platamir Booten is a great alien name.
That one went down smoother.
But hey, let's get it all back on stage.
Let's get the space angels.
Let's talk about the enemy.
Let's learn about Unorc City.
We will write Unorc material as we already have.
This is going to be great.
This is going to be a thousand times as good as the desert trip as the McCartney Stones.
This will be the greatest Palm Springs concert of all time.
And that's saying something.
He's putting a lot of great stuff out there.
So yeah.
Well, I guess, okay.
So Jenny Nicholson, you survived podcast The Ride twice in one day.
Whoa, I park hopped.
First ever.
The first park hopper.
Yes.
This is like being the first person in space or something.
Are we going to talk about plussing up Sunny Eclipse?
Oh, yeah, we missed that.
Is there a way?
Yes.
Okay.
Oh, yes please.
It's all set.
Bring all the animatronics from Stitch's Great Escape and put them as his band.
Oh yeah.
I'm Skippy on a keytar.
Oh my God.
Although he's also, he's maybe a good, he's sort of snouty.
He could play a woodwind or something.
That's great.
Absolutely.
Wow.
Yeah.
And then the donut eating one and the robot that was Tim Curry.
Oh, sir.
Sir.
Yeah.
I say take the restaurant out and just make it its own show.
Sure.
Or what if, you know, Stitch's Great Escape is kind of, you know, hey, let's not even
move all those robots.
Let's put them in the Stitch's Great Escape.
Oh, just having them perform in that venue.
Yep.
New committed venue.
Although I like dinner and a show.
What if they plus up the food?
There you go.
And then it was an actual lounge experience.
That'd be great.
And it's a whole.
And they have drinks and like, you know, waiting tables.
Like it's an actual table dining experience.
Geez.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm into that.
That's good.
Tarminis, hand matins, all the drinks you can name.
Oh, Mike is preventing Edwin from getting into any microscopic broken glass.
He is throwing himself on the ground.
Rolling on the ground like he you can pick him up.
I can't, but he's going to.
He gets weird.
This is I mean, this is like a wild night at Cosmic Ray's making a topping bar salads.
I'll let you guys finish the show alone.
You have to stay with.
Oh, no.
Mike has to finish from afar.
It's fine.
You can chop across.
Well, so if you if you did this episode first, make sure to go over to the main feed to listen
to both of them.
If you did interventions and you're coming here, thank you so much for listening.
If you did it the opposite way, a New York way.
I don't want to answer.
They're both great in their own ways.
Which episode is more worth watching?
Both are worth revisiting over and over again.
Cycling like a sunny eclipse loop.
Or orbiting.
Yeah.
Constantly.
Just let these episodes orbit around your ears.
And as soon as this is done, check out interventions, then listen to some clips again.
Yeah.
A sandwich.
Spend a full day park hopping.
Delicious falafel sandwich of content.
So we like to think of it.
Jay, thank you so much.
What a blast.
Thank you for having me on both of them.
Yes, please come back any time.
And yeah, thanks for thanks for subscribing.
And I, Mike's over there, so I don't know how to stop the recording.
There's no way.
It just is what it is.
Oh, we're stuck.
We're trapped.
We didn't mention Jenny.
You are also on Patreon.
Are you?
I am also on Patreon.
Patreon.com slash Jenny Nicholson.
Do you have that?
Probably.
Okay.
Well, if not search comes up really easy.
That sounds like my URL.
Or search my name.
What does it say you're making?
What's your little like?
Jenny Nicholson is.
I think just videos.
I didn't try to clever it up.
You didn't do something.
I didn't try to be cute.
I think it just says videos.
Sunny Eclipse is making Astro Organ jams.
Oh, if he was, let's get Sunny Eclipse on Patreon.
We should.
He could commission space songs.
And we can, it pays for.
For a new space organ.
Sure.
Astro Organ.
And like quicker teleporting abilities for the.
For the space angels.
Great.
So donate.
We take public transit.
Keep keep on our Patreon.
Donate to Jenny Nicholson and to Sunny Eclipse.
Yes.
All right.
I'm going to figure out.
We'll see you in Palm Springs.
Yeah, we'll see you in Palm Springs.
I'm going to figure out how to stop this crazy machine.
Bye bye.
Bye.