Hey there, ForeverDog listeners, I'm Michael Wolff.
And I'm Colin O'Brien.
And we're the hosts of America's loudest podcast, LITERATI!
Sorry, sorry, we are recording in the library.
LITERATI is a podcast about books and the idiots who write them, featuring real readings
from some of your favorite authors.
And some of your favorite comedians pretending to be authors.
Mostly that one.
Plus, we dole out tons of amazing, unsolicited writing advice because we believe everyone
has at least one great novel in them.
Hey, just last week, I had to get a novel surgically removed from my small intestine.
I accidentally sat on my bookshelf and now I have three good novels inside me.
Very impressive.
New episodes of LITERATI are premiering on Monday, February 4th, and every Monday after
that until we die.
And that is contractual.
Stick around until after the show to hear a special sneak preview of our interview with
comedian Josh Sharp reading under his pseudonym, Clint Dimples.
And be sure to subscribe to LITERATI on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your
podcasts.
And that's the end of that chapter.
Forever, dog.
Beware, on the following podcast adventure, you'll come face to face with pigs wearing
wigs, majestic Ringo stars, Dutch theme park acid trips, and condemnation of Mike's spending
habits.
Jackie Johnson joins us on a safari to Walt Disney World's Animal Kingdom.
Please don't feed the animals.
It's podcast the ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men whose podcast
mission to review every piece of Disneyland will not be complete until they figure out
to get made up at the Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique.
My name is Mike Carlson.
I'll volunteer to do it if you guys don't want to.
But I'll ask my cohost, Jason Sheridan, would you get made up at the Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique?
What would be stopping?
I think it's for little girls.
Yeah, but money has no age.
I think they would take your money.
I feel like adults probably have gone there.
Scott Gardner here.
Is Disney the most progressive place?
This I don't know.
There were issues with the same sex dancing in, but that was in the 80s.
Now there's Gay Day and that's fine.
But I don't know.
The makeup.
I think it's just child versus adult, actually.
It doesn't actually have to do with like, they would put us in a dress because I think
they probably would.
I think it's just more of like, this is for children.
The Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique is for children.
The costuming aspect, I think they probably wouldn't have the correct size, certainly.
I think it's a size issue more than anything else.
Yeah.
Right.
Okay.
We should bring our guest in on this.
This was a little bit too old to our guests.
I was trying to think of something.
But folks, you know our guest from the podcast, Natch Butte.
Ladies and gentlemen, Jackie Johnson is here.
I'm so excited.
This is the best Sunday ever.
Wonderful.
Thank you for being here.
You tweeted out that you're going to be on the show and a lot of people were excited
and that got me excited.
But also, somebody did mention the Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique as we missed the topic.
I feel really sad.
I've actually never even been in there.
Such a letdown.
Were you aware of it though?
Yes.
We'll get into it.
But I had never even stepped foot in a Disney park until I was 22 years old.
So I missed it.
Because I would have eaten that shit up honey.
It's like glamour shots but Disney.
My two interests combined baby.
I would have loved it.
I don't know.
I'd have to go in there.
But I think we could fool them into thinking Jason's a child.
Well they were experimenting.
They shaved you, you know, put you in like a little beanie cap.
Because they can't.
That is big lolly.
Get him a big lolly.
Right.
Give him a huge lolly.
That's that forced perspective that Disney is so famous for.
They weren't doing like boys, you know, girls be princesses.
Boys will make you look like a pirate.
Is that the deal?
For a little while.
Maybe still.
Yeah I think there's something like that.
But I assume now there's flexibility with that.
I'll call them out for like gender neutrality.
I'll be like my motherfucking kid wants to put on a fucking Tinkerbell dress.
Sure.
Absolutely.
They, you know, don't care.
So pop that dress on and let's get the fuck out of here.
Sure.
You're talking about Jason.
Yes.
I can play a bitchy mom.
I don't know if you've ever seen my home goods commercial.
I have not seen your home goods commercial.
I'd love to.
So you're Jason's mom in this scenario.
Yes.
If they put up any fight at all.
I'm sorry but your son actually looks like a full grown adult.
Excuse me.
He has a hormonal condition.
You know, whatever.
Yeah, yeah, that plays well.
I'll do whatever.
We don't need to do this until we're like sort of at the end I think and scraping sort
of the bottom of the barrel for stuff to talk about.
Right, you've run out of other things.
We're even older so it's even a tougher.
Yeah, we're in our late 50s I think by the time we're out of this.
That's how long this goes.
Yeah, I think so.
Maybe we'll actually have a real child at that point that we could force.
A couple years.
If that would be okay.
I don't think I'll be ready then.
Yeah, so we'll figure that out then I think.
We don't have to like solve it.
But it's still the scenario, even with the actual child, the scenario is still to get
Jason to do it.
Yes, not our child of ours.
Yeah, just Jason.
It just fleshes out the illusion of you as the mom that you have a second child.
Yes.
A baby and one with a condition.
Yeah, we'll get there.
Well, I'm glad we have this all planned out now.
So no Disney parks until 22, but you're into it now.
Yeah, so I grew up in Dallas and we have Six Flags over Texas.
We have Six Flags Hurricane Harbor.
So that's where I was all summer long, honey.
All summer long, I was up in Six Flags, riding the rides, eating the nasty food, getting
sunburned.
I was in Hurricane Harbor going down all the slides.
Do they have an annual pass?
Yes.
Did they then?
And that's just what you had?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
And I actually was a total wuss until I was 13, 14.
My best friend, Lauren Campbell, dragged me onto a ride.
I was like, I wouldn't ride any roller coasters that had any loops.
I wouldn't ride anything.
I was like, the Runaway Mine Train, which is a really fun ride.
I don't know if you all have ever been to Six Flags over Texas.
I haven't, no.
And nowhere have we covered it yet.
We'd like to.
Yeah, y'all should go.
And then because, you know, it's what I grew up on.
But and but yeah, my parents were cheap and they never took me on vacation, you know,
broken home, all that.
So by the time I was when I moved to L.A. is the first time I went.
And I'm telling you, I felt like a child.
Though the wonder in my eyes, I had never seen anything like Disney before.
It was so beautiful.
It's so thoughtful.
The Q experiences, all the visuals, even the employees are nice.
I mean, Six Flags employees are like horny teens, you know, trying to get through their
damn day for the most part.
Right.
And I rate because they have to work and they would rather just be horny.
They would rather be doing the other half of their brain.
Exactly.
Summer jobs, you know, mom made him get out of the house.
And I was just like, this is amazing.
I stayed from the very beginning to the very end.
We rode every ride.
I mean, it was amazing.
I went with two of my sorority sisters.
But I have an interesting perspective to be here because I'm not the I'm not the biggest
enthusiast like y'all.
I have the perspective of being married to one of y'all.
I am married to a theme park nut, an enthusiast of the space.
OK.
Like lifelong, like lifelong.
And there is no park unturned.
I mean, we will detour 30 minutes an hour to get to park every trip we go on.
I have to negotiate how many theme parks we go on trips, you know.
So I've kind of learned to appreciate it more through him.
I've always been.
I like it.
But like when I listen to this show and by the way, I am a listener podcast.
Thank you.
Shout out to Steve Brandano.
Sure.
Yeah.
Hi, Steve.
We maybe Howard Stern will come up.
Who knows?
Michael and I share that another weird niche fandom.
But, you know, I love experiencing the parks with my husband, you know, and like I've gotten
more into it because of him.
So, so will you do you like see his face on our faces when you're like, is it sound?
Does it feel the same?
Is it feel like obsessive?
Just appreciative, you know, and that's another thing.
I guess again, growing up only going to Six Flags, which like Six Flags has like, I'd be
like, oh my God, look up dirty old Batmobile bleach from the sun.
Whoa.
I thought it was cool.
But then you go to Disney and you're like, damn, the game is strong.
I mean, it's on a whole other level.
You know, you didn't know it could be that way.
Your standards were lower.
You feel happy.
It truly is the happiest place.
I took my father, who had never been to Disney as well, a few years ago, and I saw his face
do the same thing.
I mean, he was like, I looked over him and it's a small world.
He had the biggest smile on his face.
You know, it was amazing.
It was like, it truly is magical.
And I think because we all go all the time and we are childless people in our thirties,
we kind of lose that nostalgia and that magic.
But it really is a magical place.
Yeah, we agree.
And it's a treat.
It's a treat.
It's a privilege.
It's important to remember that too.
The worst thing is when you get into the perfunctory, you know, it's all about the math and like,
okay, well, if we cut through here, we save five minutes.
And all right, so we can get on this at 335.
I think we've probably all had moments of that of like, wait a minute, are we forgetting
to have fun?
Although I will say almost every time I still am just like pure giddy happy lost in it.
Yeah, there's always like one or two things.
I think at the end of the day, you're like, well, that was great.
It becomes weird too, because we're so obsessed that it literally could just be like going
on a ride at night or something.
We're like, wow, we never did that before.
Which I mean, it gets to like, we're playing in the margins here, actually.
But there's still like, your brain is still processing.
That lets you find a lot of new little magic wrinkles.
Yes, for sure.
You know, we came out of Alice in Wonderland while the parade was going on.
So we were right above the parade during the outside party.
Little tiny like, sure that changes it up.
We've talked about how we rode and I've done this once or twice before.
We were a big thunder while the fireworks were going off and it's like, whoa, I can't
believe the fireworks are happening on the roller coaster.
It hit this bend like perfectly almost the fireworks.
It almost went left to right as did we and it was so romantic for Mike and I.
I'm not very significant.
We were together. We were alone.
Wow, that's so romantic.
And also you can get the ash in your eye at a high speed velocity as opposed to just
standing still and getting ash in your eye.
You get to take something home with you.
Yeah, it feels different with thrust.
Yes.
Yeah.
You know what else adds to the magic as you age and also to kind of help make the experience
new again is to get fucked up.
Certainly.
Well, sure.
I don't drink alcohol, but I have overdosed on marijuana at Disneyland several times.
Oh my.
To the fact that I was like, we almost got a room at Grand California.
And I was like, we have to get out of here.
Oh, you have to like chill out.
It was really, really bad.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
We've talked about this a little bit like bad trips or whatever.
I've never been high at Disneyland.
I think I'm afraid.
I don't want to have like some bad.
Oh wait, I'm afraid.
Except for Downtown Disney.
I got too high in the Rainforest Cafe.
I think I mentioned a long time ago and it influenced my decision to not go to Chapman
University.
Oh, yeah.
I don't like Ganaim.
I don't want to be here because of a unrelated because because I had a bad time at the Rainforest
Cafe.
If you can imagine that.
Hmm.
Impossible.
Most most times.
Have you all ever done like I know people that go to Disneyland on mushrooms and crazy shit
like that like acid.
I've only had marijuana at my own at Disney.
I would never do it.
I can't handle it.
This is not a big like a puritanical thing.
Yeah.
Just truly like I'll lose my mind.
So I think yeah, you're a stressed out weed person.
I can't I've tried try it.
Maybe if I could try it once a year and then it just doesn't it's not going to happen.
I don't think somebody and everyone is always like you're not doing the right thing, bro.
You don't know what you're doing.
And it's like I think I'm good.
I think you have no desire to learn no desire to learn I guess but I would love to learn
but I yeah, it makes it so much more fun.
Really?
Okay.
Oh my God.
It makes it you laugh.
Everything looks awesome.
I mean, I've had some of the best moments of my life probably.
Do you remember any specific any specific highlights or is it all kind of a blur?
No, I got specifics honey.
So when I went to Disney World for my first and only time in 2015, we were stopping there
before we went to the Bahamas and because again every trip I go on we negotiate theme
parks.
So I never been we did Animal Kingdom, which we'll talk about.
But then we took we drove to Magic Kingdom, right?
The you take that boat over.
So we pop some candies and we got fucked up and you know, I will talk about this.
I guess but I'm not like a big food drink enthusiast because I don't eat anything and
I don't drink alcohol.
So like I don't care about food.
I only eat food to live so I don't fall over.
So but I you can there's we'll talk about it maybe but I have some Instagram accounts
for vegan food at Disney.
So I had this burger or like a veggie burger and I piled it's like, you know, a little
salad bar kind of thing.
I piled so many damn pepper Cheney's on this burger pepper Cheney's lettuce.
I was eating it.
It was the best fucking thing I've ever eaten and it might have been garbage, but I was
like, this is so good.
So then we went on we went on the Space Mountain and the Space Mountain at Disney World is
single riders in a line.
Yep.
And rough.
Yes.
So my husband is behind me and I hear him laughing so hard that he's crying and then
I start crying laughing.
But then I start thinking oh my God, my head is going to get lobbed off because it's in
the dark and you get paranoid and I'm like, I'm going to die.
So I'm thinking I'm going to die and I'm crying laughing.
It was such an intense amazing experience and I it was so fun.
She loved it.
I mean, I that's the thing.
If you if you OD it could get really bad and this was like borderline too much.
The other really bad time was at Disneyland and Tortilla Joe's and we we always go to
Tortilla Joe's we get fucked up.
We go to Tortilla Joe's we load up and then we like go into the park.
We were fucking gone.
We way overdosed.
And that's my advice to everybody out there.
Be careful with your dosage of marijuana.
Be careful with your dosage.
We had drank this can of quench and I didn't know but drinking marijuana actually makes
you metabolize it way fast very fast.
Yeah.
And we made like Arnold Palmer's with like teas with this lemon can of course.
I you know the like table side guac service.
Of course.
I wish I could interview the guy that did our guac because it felt like he was there
for seven hours and we were losing our minds and Adam is my rock and like he keeps me safe
and I actually don't even know my way around Disney because he's a tour guide.
So I just like grab onto him.
I don't know where I'm going up because he keeps me safe.
He was a mess and I was like what's going to happen like this fucked up wind up leaving.
We didn't even eat our food walking around the park panicked didn't ride anything and
I was like we got to eat.
We got to eat.
We got to eat and I don't know if it's your body telling you to eat.
You know the munchies.
It's like does your body tell you to eat because food will metabolize the marijuana out.
That's a new theory that I got well fucked up in that moment or is it something else?
But I was like eating those Mickey pretzels Mickey pretzels Mickey pretzels popcorn popcorn
because I'm vegan and there's not that you know don't whip don't whip pretzel pretzel.
I mean I couldn't stop eating.
I was like I got to help.
I got to stop this.
We were there for hours didn't write a damn thing.
Whoa.
So just wandering just wandering.
Huh?
It sounds like a nightmare.
Yes.
It was a nightmare.
These bad ones don't seem worth the good ones.
Good ones are describing sound very nice.
You got to be careful because I don't want to it's illegal.
You can't and I don't like breaking rules.
You cannot Disney is straight like you're not supposed to have like like even if you were staying at the hotels like on Disney property.
They do not want marijuana despite it being laws.
Yeah, despite it being recreationally legal in California.
And if you were staying at the hotel like you can wheel in a case of beer.
Right.
That's fine.
Which seems kind of silly.
But of course.
Yeah.
But like I smoked out the Grand California in one time.
I forgot that before the return of Captain EO.
Look at you.
We made a night.
I stayed at the Grand.
We and several other me and the balcony.
And Katie I think just in the room and it then it reeked and it was in a non smoking room.
Yeah.
Well brazen.
But that's that's the how much I love the EO.
Why I'm willing to break hotel rules for it.
But I didn't.
I and now I don't remember.
I must have been really light with it being afraid of a bad trip because I don't remember
even any specific.
I just got to be careful.
I never overdosed after that.
But because it's illegal I get fucked up prior to entering and I and I don't smoke smoke.
So I have to use edibles and things.
But after that I learned the lesson to be way more moderate with.
Yeah.
Also be very careful with like the security is so intense.
Like they have caught people at the metal detector.
I've seen somebody on our Facebook put a photo of a guy that was dressed in disguise and
he caught people with edibles.
Oh yeah.
And it's like a dad and like a turkey leg t-shirt like over.
Yeah.
It was a plain clothes.
I think maybe I've told them this on the show.
The only theme park that's ever happened was that I had a friend in town and my friend
loves to imbibe with the weed chocolate.
So we he made me take some and we went to the House of Horrors at Universal Studios.
Oh hell yes.
And I had a headache after that.
Chucky attacked him with a knife and I lost my mind.
See I always get fucked up before I go to the haunted things.
Well I can see that you were.
We had a couple.
Now I'm in the haunts now.
I had a couple beers before and I do think that seems fun because my my thing with Disney
is just in the middle of the day to Carthay, Manhattan's one and one is fine also.
But if you do too you're really that's good.
You lose a goose.
You're ready to go.
That's the refresher.
Then you're then the whole park is fresh and new again.
That's what I'm saying.
You know alter that mind baby.
Yeah.
So that's my version of it possibly getting like a beer on the over by the Chinese food place.
You like you just like getting high on grenadine.
Yeah.
Well that is true.
I like the cherry.
I like the alcohol.
So if it was just a bottle of alcohol so alcohol so cherries, I think that would be better for me.
Just eating the cherries.
Is that an off value?
Is that an off menu item at the car thing?
Can I just get a bucket of cherries a bucket of cherries, but they've been lightly soaked.
Yeah.
So there's a little bit of alcohol content.
Mainly mainly if you're with a plaid tour guide if you're with a VIP tour guide, they'll give you that.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Have you all ever done those?
I got old money bags has yeah, I didn't pay.
How much is it?
Is like 500 an hour or something something like that?
Yeah, it's not.
Yeah, it's it's everyone can get it too.
I didn't realize that until a year ago.
Yeah, Jason's qualification for being a money bags is knowing someone with money.
Yeah, right.
Oh, Mr. knows a money bag.
Hollywood Hollywood Carlson probably would have been the better.
Jason's that would have been the Jason's also like I maybe like he'll see me like in a different pair of pants.
Like I have three pairs of pants and when we can be like, oh, someone's doing well.
You would have a cutting Jason was like, you're a bit of a clothes horse.
Aren't you?
That is all you rotate your closet a lot.
I know, but no one else has ever said that.
I'm just saying like no one else has been like, huh, is that new?
Like maybe that's I know.
You're adding that judgment in there.
I am not adding that judgment in there.
I was trying to pay you a compliment.
Just did a couple seconds ago.
What the judge?
Oh, the judgment about the clothes.
Yeah, about the clothes.
OK, so you you judged me in different ways.
No, that was an observation.
The clothes are sure that was like a compliment.
The clothes horse was benign.
The other ones definitely had a definitely with judging.
Oh, yes. You're very cavalier with money and I worry about you.
I was being honest, you know, my I think.
I think my role in the podcast once and maybe I view it sometimes
as being something of a referee between Mike and Jason.
And here's what I'll say.
Yeah, that does.
That I do when you tell that I do hear the judgment.
And I feel like that judgment is familiar to me.
However, I've also heard Mike tell stories in which judgment is added
that was not there in my version of the original story.
So I think there could be fault on both sides here.
That is my official referee call.
I need a whistle for these in the future.
That sounds like you're not your everyone wins.
I think yes.
Everyone is right and wrong.
Very diplomatic.
Yeah, so fuck both y'all.
That's my real thing.
Yeah, that's fine.
I'll take it.
He'll go around.
So Jackie, were you like way into Disney as a child, just the movies
and stuff as well?
Yes, definitely.
Nineties kid.
I mean, Little Mermaid, Lion King, Aladdin, that kind of sweet spot.
The music.
Yes.
Yeah.
And I had wanted to go to Disney, but again, never got taken.
I mean, in Texas, you're smacking the middle.
Exactly.
And again, we had six flags.
So I always wondered why or if Disney ever thought about doing a Texas
outpost.
That seems like a good it's in the middle.
I don't think it would split the audience of either California or
whereas it weirdly they were trying to do the one in Virginia, which I
think would cut into Florida.
But like Texas, it feels like also there be some massive piece of property.
For sure.
Perfect for Disney.
Texas cut a big old cattle ranch down or something.
You know, that shit over a skedaddle.
I feel like we're not going to get another like state park.
They're going to do much more.
Like there would be like 10 more China parks before we get like another
one in America.
You mean from scratch?
Yes.
You think unless they start buying up, unless we have you know, there was
the rumor that they're going to buy knots.
I could see that sort of thing occurring.
They become a Westfield of would there be like a shuttle like underground
between the two or something?
Well, they were talking about a Monterey a lot when they was a 10 years ago,
15 years ago, 20 years ago, I think.
20 years ago.
Yeah.
How cute was that Monorail in Japan?
Oh, yeah, very cute.
Oh, you done Japan then.
So like everybody in 2018, I went to Tokyo.
I went in a couple of nights.
This is the Japan time in everyone's lives.
What is that?
Yeah, what's happening?
Somebody went and then everyone was like, oh, I should do that.
I don't know.
Literally every motherfucker in LA went to Japan last year.
Everyone, dozens of people.
If I throw any recommendations, there's like the like three page
dense, dense tome email.
I feel like I have this from 12 people, which is great.
I'm so excited.
This is all wonderful.
But yeah, it is what's in the water.
Why are we all?
I don't know.
What are we after?
I feel like it hit critical mass in the last couple of years.
I do feel like maybe my parents or other people like a certain generation.
It's still kind of like Japan is kind of a strange place to go.
Right.
But really, Japan has been here all along.
Mario has been here all along.
You know, like there's so many different things that like are part of our culture
and then anime and all that's like everything makes sense to Doc Brown in 1955.
In 85, he knows the Japanese make all the best stuff.
So like I feel like we finally like as a culture been like, oh, yeah, there's a bunch of cool crap there.
And then you go there and it's like, this is very familiar.
This is like very similar.
Tony Baxter was talking about how like the culture there is very similar to American culture.
When they build a Disney there, like cute is a thing that resonates with the people there
as opposed to France where they shun cute when you get past five years old or something.
So it's like we went there and we've been listening to especially I've been digging deep with Japanese city pop lately
and like Japanese rock and roll.
You're like, this is just a parallel universe where it's the exact same sound as our pop music.
So it's like awesome because you're like, this sounds like a Neil Young record that never came out,
but it's Japanese people and they're singing in Japan or Japanese.
Overwhelming that it's like an entire you mean I'm not even done with cool pop culture, especially in the 70s, 80s.
Yeah.
So how do you even begin?
I don't understand.
So yeah.
And then with Japan, of course, the added thing of like there's a Disneyland there and then it's like a really good Disneyland.
And also like what you think?
What was your time?
It was good.
I know you haven't been I know you don't want to know.
I thoroughly enjoyed the podcast to ride on it.
I was I texted Mike.
I was like driving and just and just nodding my head being like, yep, yep, yep.
It was really cool.
We did not go as extensively as they did, you know, like going to the damn Auntie Skunk's Cafe and sitting for two hours.
We didn't do that, you know, we were we only had two days and we really like hustled.
Yeah.
And that's we had we got an amazing flight for people that are curious about going to Japan.
Black Friday, Singapore Air.
We had round trip tickets on Singapore Air, which is a luxury airline for three hundred dollars.
Wow.
That's crazy.
The catch is it was only for a week.
So we made that trip count.
I mean, we because I also went up to see the snow monkeys up in the Alps of Japan.
Right.
And that took a two days and then we did a real con up there was awesome.
And then we had, of course, because I married Adam McCabe two days at Disney negotiated and negotiated.
I was comfortable with non theme park.
Yeah, of course.
Yes.
Sure.
You know, we only did two days.
We did one day at Disney and one day at Tokyo Disney Sea.
Well, how'd that go?
Was it hellish?
So explain to me.
You need a lot of time.
Please lay it on thicker.
Please.
I don't think this is a constant thing of like how many days do you spend there?
And I remember when I think Adam was talking to you, Mike, and he said you only need two days and you were like,
what we're doing for, you know, but again,
we don't sit at Mama Skunk's Cafe like we don't go in every goddamn bathroom.
You don't look at everything.
Is that right?
Mama Skunk's Cafe?
What's her name?
Her name, I believe, is Grandma Sarah.
Grandma Sarah.
Hello, honey.
I don't know. She was not a skunk.
She was like a bad, bad.
A possum.
Possum.
Okay.
Well, y'all know what I meant, damn it.
Yeah, we did.
I didn't know.
Yeah, but you know, it's it was awesome.
I think Tokyo Disney Sea is my favorite Disney park now.
Sure.
But Animal Kingdom second.
Yeah.
Which do you want to start getting into it?
I mean, we can also we can tangent forever.
I also just want to say that y'all have to go to Efteling.
Okay.
I know.
None of y'all have been?
None of us.
Jason, you ever been?
No, I've never been to Europe.
Y'all gotta fucking go, man.
Is there a deal?
Is there a Black Friday deal that you know of?
I don't know.
Okay.
You just because you fly into Amsterdam.
Oh, what is that one?
Norwegian Air.
Have y'all flown on Norwegian Air?
No.
Norwegian Air is the spirit airlines of Europe, but not not that bad.
Right.
It was actually really nice.
It's no frills, but you can get cheap flights.
Yeah, like $250 to Europe from LA.
You can get cheap flights.
They do Black Friday, but they have sales all the time.
Get on their email list.
I'm going to run that.
We're going to I want to do a Europe trip soon.
I'm going to run it by my business manager over here.
Okay.
On the couch and I'm going to see if I can afford it in the next couple years.
I'm going to get these stack of Chase Visa cards on the couch next to me.
I'm just going to pay the credit cards.
It's next to the payday loan form to pay for the...
He was crushed by all his credit cards.
All 250 choked him.
That would be a fine way to go.
See, that's what I thought why so many people are going to LA because
or going to Japan because from LA it's usually less expensive to fly
to Asia as opposed to flying to Europe.
Interesting.
You can get cheap flights.
Yeah, there's a couple Twitter accounts that are like just have constant sales and stuff.
So yeah, Norwegian Air and Singapore Air Black Friday if you want to go.
And we almost got these cheap flights to Bali.
Really?
Because I was like we got to plan a trip for 2019.
Where are we going to go?
Adam wants to go to Switzerland.
I was trying to do Norwegian Air and it wasn't really working.
To get out there, but I was like it was so cheap to go to Bali and I was like,
oh we should do this, but I didn't done research.
I love planning.
I love a good itinerary.
I love a good plan.
Sure.
What did you tie Efteling into with your negotiation theme park?
Okay, on our honeymoon.
So for our honeymoon we did London, Paris, Amsterdam.
Wow, wonderful.
And Efteling is if people don't know it's older than Disneyland by a few years
and the rumor is that Walt went there saw and said,
oh I got to do this in America and kind of ripped it off.
That I just saw the weekend this weekend that was debunked.
Oh interesting.
There's no record that that he was there, but I have heard that.
Yeah, I don't know.
You're right.
I just read it.
No trip log in his lifetime of.
I mean they saved everything else.
So it wouldn't surprise me if there if there was but it doesn't seem like it.
Interesting.
That guy that guy on who on Instagram stories who works for Disney who's always answering questions.
Okay.
Said he had never come across that.
Huh?
Unless he's just covering for his favorite.
Oh, yeah.
He could be could be covering for the narrative like no, no, it's never what no waves for the bench that we bought.
The historic Griffith Park and that is the tail.
It would be funny of like the historian that finds like the Walt notes from Efteling and the pictures of him there and like thinking and he's like I must burn this.
The mother world like least like least.
Oh, yeah.
I feel like I read that they also like helped Walt.
Oh, man.
Some of the planners or ride people were involved in Disney, but I don't know.
Well, and what I've learned now is that this place Garner Holt's animatronics, which is responsible for like all these great animatronics and knots and also what do they do in Disney?
They did Jack Skellington and the new dragon and phantasmic.
The monsters in Tokyo, right?
Oh, I think so.
And what's the other one?
Mystic Manor.
Do they do and they've done a lot of they've done a ton of animatronics for Efteling as well.
So if you feel Disney vibes there now, it could be the Garner Holt thing.
Yeah.
So they and that made me want to go really bad.
I didn't know.
I feel like I had heard it presented or I was like, is this some like preserved in Amber weird Park from the past and hearing that they have cutting edge stuff to it's both.
It is very much.
I mean, you're literally in a forest in the middle of the Netherlands.
I went in the fall.
It was so gorgeous.
I mean, it's not like Disney where you're in like a suburban area and there's homes and you're turning in.
I mean, the ride to get to Efteling is probably the craziest ride that you'll go on there.
I mean, because you take this crazy bus from a subway stop out of Amsterdam and it was nuts and everyone warned me, but I don't want to ruin it.
If you've been Efteling and you got there from from Amsterdam, you know, it's just the bus driver and it was full of people like Dutch people on their way to work and living their lives.
And we're two childless 30 year olds from fucking America with our luggage, you know, schlepping it there.
But it's crazy.
But it's a beautiful park and it's fantasy fairy tale.
And you're immersed so deeply because no one's speaking English around you and nothing is in English.
It has really cool fun cutting edge rides, but it also has like classic old wooden creatures and the lighting is beautiful.
And once again, Amsterdam, I was fucked up.
But but not that much because the weed in Amsterdam didn't work on me because I'm a California stoner.
I'm not really I don't really even smoke that much.
You needed the corn syrup.
You needed that American corn syrup additive.
The GMO on Santo shit.
Yeah.
Do they sell weed at Efteling?
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah. And and I like I said, we didn't smoke it.
I don't think you're allowed.
And I'm obviously not going to break laws internationally either.
So I had like an edible cookie or something and it was OK.
It was really light.
It was nice. I would have liked to up it a little bit, but it helps.
It helps enhance the experience.
That seems like a place to do talk to any of the boom Chicago people.
Any of our friends at Boom Chicago is a comedy show in the Netherlands or in Amsterdam that a lot of friends of ours from like
the upper citizens brigade go over and perform at.
They go on acid.
They go on everything and the stories are insane.
I don't want to name names in case anybody's embarrassed, but we have friends that have gone to Efteling like fully fucked up on like crazy drugs.
Do you OK? I'm not asking you to name names or not, but I'm here's what I'm curious about.
Can you can you name something in Efteling that you think would be particularly frightening while on acid or something or something that factors into one of their stories?
There are some the Dutch are a wild bunch.
There's like spooky stuff at Efteling.
There's a lot like weird moody rides.
There's a ride called.
Oh, what is it?
It was this one ride that everyone told us to go on.
It's sort of like a madhouse.
OK, I don't want to ruin anything, but that would probably be a pretty weird experience.
There are some like ghosty things, kind of haunted mansion ask things.
And crazy rides like roller coasters and thrilling things.
The flying Dutchman, honey.
Do you know anything about Efteling?
No, I'm not in any spoiler territory, but I'd like to go someday.
What's up with flying Dutchman?
It's a water.
It's like a haunted.
Oh, haunted pirate ship water ride.
Well, all right, and they do crazy.
I mean, y'all got to go.
If you're a theme park head and you're looking for a trip, y'all got to go to Efteling.
Now really cool.
So so let me for just the very boring practical nature of it.
So how do you get there?
Because I have heard it's far away.
So but you can take this magical bus from Amsterdam.
I'm not going to lie to you all.
It was a little stressful to get there and I had been warned that it was and I had emails
detailed from from again, friends of ours who did Boob Chicago like OK, you turn left.
You're going to see a green light go three steps forward.
I mean, I had really detailed emails.
I remember we were leaving our hotel in Amsterdam and our fucking Internet and our phones just
stop working.
And it's one of those things where it's like you don't expect that to happen.
So we were totally boned.
So we missed a train, missed a train and like screw us up.
Finally, our phones are working.
We get on the train because Google Maps is really helpful in Japan.
I mean, we did y'all get a portable Wi-Fi?
No, mine was just my I have the plan that it's fine.
I got a portable Wi-Fi ahead of time.
And so you basically have Wi-Fi all the time, no matter where you are, if you're underground,
up in the mountains, up with the snow monkeys, wherever you are.
It was really helpful.
My phone was 100% connected all the time.
Google Maps, you type in, I'm going here.
It'll go, OK, turn left, get on this train.
You're going to take it three stops.
You're going to get off here.
It's a must for like, you know, dumb Americans.
OK, good to know.
So I and everyone's again, we're privileged.
So everyone does speak English pretty much.
And that was true in Tokyo.
And in the Netherlands.
But you get off a train and then you walk down and you go up and you say, I want to go to Efteling.
And they'll go, OK, you get on this bus.
And you do.
But, you know, if you miss them, you have to wait.
And then if you can't find the stop and you miss it and blah, blah, blah.
And then they drop you off at a certain location.
And it might not be.
We were staying at the hotel at Efteling and we had missed that stop.
So we had to carry our luggage through the entire park.
And it's double the size of Disneyland.
And then we're like schlepping luggage through the park, you know, and then we had to go back to the front to start over.
Like my feet were so sore that day.
Like you were you walk a lot.
Yes, yes. But it's true.
But yeah, well, I think we were talking about topics with you and I think Efteling was it was an option.
And we were like, I don't think we can do it justice until we go.
You have to go. Yeah.
And thus we landed on Animal Kingdom, which we've covered.
We were talking. We just recently talked about Expedition Everest and realized we have no.
Have we not done an animal kingdom ride of any kind?
Right. And and here you bring this up as a good chance to talk about the place overall and the broad strokes of it.
Why Animal Kingdom? What's the animal kingdom?
OK, so I am an animal nut.
And I don't get I don't get many interactions with wild animals because I don't believe in a lot of them morally.
I don't like zoos for the most part.
I don't like interactive animal like the fucking porcupine cafes and shit.
I'm like, no, let those porcupines go.
It's not OK. You're OK with Grandma Sarah's cafe.
Grandma's. What's it called?
Anti skunkies. Actually, after listening to the episode, I watched a YouTube on it and it does look really cool in there.
It's very cute. Which park was that?
It's in Disneyland. This is Splash Mountain Restaurant, essentially.
Oh, neat. OK, OK.
And fun fact about opossums I learned recently, they look scary, but they are unlikely to have rabies because their blood temperature is too low.
Good to know. I saw opossum last night going down my street.
Yeah, you could have kissed it.
You could have been friends with it.
You could have kissed it. They might fuck you up, but you won't get to get rabies shot.
You could have drank its blood.
Yeah, sure could have.
So I don't believe in most animal interactivity things, although I will say I did go to the snow monkeys in Japan.
If you have time, it's amazing.
Really, really?
And then I did go see the swimming pigs in the Bahamas.
And it was the best moment of my whole life.
I sobbed when I saw them.
It was like a big moment.
We got engaged right before that, but it was like beautiful.
But I got read to filth over it because vegans love to come for each other.
So my wedding was written up in a vegan magazine and I got like, I can't believe you did that.
And then I was just like, oh, it's like there's so many levels to people's beliefs and things.
And part of me was like, oh shit, should I even talk about animal kingdom because there's animals and they're captive?
And I'm like, no, you think shit's going to the people.
No, because your degree of followers.
Listen, here's where I'm at now with it.
Okay.
Our our animals, especially the animals in Africa are being hunted and killed.
Most of them are on endangered species list.
Disney treats them well.
I've done tons of research, which we'll talk about when we get to the they treat them well.
They're breeding there.
They're keeping them safe.
Is there, you know, an aspect to it of like people driving cars past these animals?
Sure.
But at this point, I'd rather these animals be safe and alive and healthy and monitored than being free and shot and killed, you know,
right?
Yeah.
Sure.
May have saved the white rhino population.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So, you know, it is what it is.
I think I don't go to zoos typically because like animals on like big fake fiberglass rocks make me sad, but they brought in so many species of plants.
It's all real grass.
You know, we'll talk about it when we get to that part.
But I'm going to give it a pass.
And if you want to if you want to come for me, go ahead.
But you heard it.
You heard her vegan.
Yeah.
Bring it on.
Could you imagine this is what you get canceled for Jackie going on a theme park podcast?
Our first guest got canceled.
I would be honored to be the first cancel guest.
We'll see how far I go.
Well, if Bugsy didn't get canceled, you're probably fine.
Well, he's dead.
He's a skeleton.
He was canceled by being alive.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's the thing.
I was like in thinking about this park as a whole.
I remember that it was I think people like Pito was upset when it opened and there was that general concern.
I like you and you'll see it on a list.
You'll see animal Kingdom on lists of controversial things.
Disney has done to have animals in captivity.
But if you unless they're doing a good job covering it up or something, it's not like there are tons of stories of awful things happening to animals.
I do think that they are kept up well from my mildest of research.
It seems like you've done more potentially.
So that's good.
I wanted to make sure again, like I won't do dolphin swimming.
It's I think it's so wrong.
Dolphins sonar goes off like crazy.
They shouldn't be in confined areas.
Like I think it's torture for them.
If you go on vacation in your hotels, like let's rank dolphins.
I'm sure I would literally weep with joy.
I mean, imagine how amazing it would be with that poor animal.
You know, I have a lot of issues with things.
I don't even think dog breeding should be legal.
I think it's fucked up to make dogs have babies and then sell them.
I think that's fucked, you know.
Yeah.
But did I go on Disney's Safari?
Yes.
Amazing.
Okay.
You know what?
This is what it is.
Okay.
Do your research.
The Kilimanjaro Safari is what you're talking about, which I went I hadn't been on it in years and then we went on a couple years ago and I was like, are they allowed to get this close to us?
Like I mean, isn't it crazy?
It's crazy.
It truly is like a real African Safari, but in Florida.
Yes.
Yeah.
And I've always wanted to do a Safari, but they're so expensive.
How much are they?
I mean, tens of thousands of dollars.
Okay.
And again, you have to be safe.
There's a lot going on in certain territories and things.
I'm sure you could probably get a cheaper one, but because I used to be a dog walker.
We kind of talked about this when I got here.
I had a client who's like very wealthy and they went on one and it looked like just the most amazing like but it was how much who knows, you know, for some comfort.
I'd imagine you're paying a lot of money and you're popping those pills.
You're worried about malaria.
There's a lot going on.
Yeah.
No malaria in Florida, baby.
Orlando is fine.
It's safe.
Yeah.
Which does just a brain eating parasites.
And sinkholes.
There's stuff to worry about.
Holes.
Yes.
The sinkhole.
There's a spot by the Magic Kingdom where they can't build a hotel because they kept sending beams down to test and the beams wouldn't come back.
And spit up like in the middle of Epcot one day.
The beam, the beam shooting through the air beam Kano.
Yeah.
So it's a yeah.
Say where is the animal and it does well.
So so on the Safari thing, this is pretty like animal Kingdom basics, I guess.
But if you're listening and you're not a super nerd, the whole thing about this ride, you see this wide variety of animals and they get very close to you.
You're like, how are they?
Could they just lunge?
But there are there are natural barricades set up.
They designed this area so that this moat is here or this little like stopping mechanism is on the ground, but the guests can't see it.
So actually you are safe at all times, but in a way that is not cage oriented.
And it's this is something Disney has pioneered and that I think other I'm not totally sure.
I think other like zoos or nature parks have started to do it.
Right.
Isn't like like, yeah, huge leap forward in this industry to actually plan things in a smart way and not just like, yeah, it's a bunch of fences.
It'll electrocute them if they touch it.
There was also concern like how would they, especially for the safaris, get the animals to come towards the people?
And like they figured out tricks like, well, if you put the tree that has the draft favorite kind of leaf on it that is like candy to them and you put that on a lazy Susan and you rotate it towards like where the path is, they will come towards the the tree and the guests.
It's really, they really thought a lot about that.
Cause how do you remember when you were little and you went to the zoo and like you'd be like, oh, that's supposed to be a hippo, but you couldn't see shit.
Yeah.
It's like they thought about all that.
There's like hidden food troughs, hidden water things that will make them come closer.
And it's crazy how close they come.
Yeah, they get very close.
The only thing that's bad, I feel like, is they say don't like yell at the animal and everyone does.
Yeah.
Right.
Both times I've been on it.
It's like, don't I feel like I can't even yell.
It's not taking pictures because I don't think that would bother, but it's like, don't call them to the car.
They tell you at a certain point to like lower your voice and not say anything and stuff like that.
But then there's like a giant heavy vehicle, you know, going through.
Well, you had like one of the person, cause there's also about this thing, the Kilimanjaro Safari.
It's the most impressive job.
Like to do it.
I'm so blown away by the people who do it, who have to do the announcing.
Like it's like the jungle cruise, but they're driving a real car through rough terrain.
Right.
Which I just learned is like a giant flatbed truck that they modified.
So it's like a, it's a difficult vehicle to operate and they're telling you the plot and everything too.
They're telling you everything.
They're asking questions.
They're like putting the car in different gears.
They're waiting for other cars because maybe there's an animal on the track essentially and they have to wait.
They're doing so much and it's seamless.
Yeah.
And you're like, whoa, what a skill you have.
I wonder what training was involved.
I mean how long they had to train to get that job.
It has to be the most impressive of all, like the ride operator job.
Yeah.
And when the ride first opened, there was like a storyline that there were poachers, which makes a lot less sense.
I don't like that.
Yeah.
That you were like, you had to chase the poachers.
You were like, we got to stop these poachers.
Oh, now see I've only, I did it with that overlay and I don't think I knew it's not there.
I think that element of it is gone.
So I might like it more now because I found that unpleasant and literally all I can remember about it are terrible tinny sound effects in that Jeep of like poachers like coming in on the radio.
Am I remembering this correctly?
Like that they catch the signal and like, yeah, there's some crackly.
Where did I get them?
Watch out tigers.
I think you also are likely to see more animals now, especially because like that park is open later.
Now that was a big thing.
Like noise is a big concern with all these animals.
Animal Kingdom used to close much earlier than the other parks.
Once they got the Pandora World of Avatar in there though, I think they realized like, well, we need to keep this park open a little later.
For the bioluminescence.
And then they added the Rivers of Light nighttime show.
And so and then they started experimenting with like later in the evening safaris with some lighting and like, you know, you get more nocturnal animals out or animals who sleep at the hottest points of the day come out.
So yeah, the parks open.
I checked it was like yesterday or today was open till eight and like every other park was also open till eight.
Okay.
Yeah.
Also like fireworks.
They started doing fireworks in the recent past and people were concerned about is that a problem fireworks near the but apparently they're separate.
They do remain in the animal kingdom?
No.
No, I don't like that.
I think they did like a new they got in some they got checked on because there was a New Year's Eve fireworks.
But like the Rivers of Light nighttime show has like no fireworks.
They don't have a regular fireworks thing.
But they have a church in front now of the tree of life.
I'm fucking done with fireworks.
I don't think so many fireworks.
I'm fucking done with that.
Wow.
That's been my take.
We had to say controversial opinions a while ago.
Once you've seen one you've seen them all they're loud.
They're pollutant.
They really stress dogs out.
I mean if anyone's a dog owner and you know a busy area during 4th of July is a fucking nightmare.
That's true.
Let's can we stop with the fucking fireworks or do them like once a damn week or something?
I don't know.
There's it's more of a concern for the local area.
You think I just think they're dumb.
I think they're overrated and I think they're very pollutant and loud and they stress things out.
They stress out animals.
I think that will I think there'll be a time when they're replaced by drones.
That's what it feels like it's going to happen.
Well, there's a sparkly drones like a hundred and fifty drones that shoot up into the sky and make like design like whatever.
I would love that.
I mean they're totally like tested it and stuff.
I'm down for that.
Whatever like cool thing design they would make in the sky would be now drones.
But you can't float them over people's heads right now is the problem.
There's speculation and for Anaheim we're going to at least for a little while see less and less fireworks and more and more drones or projection any kind of stuff as they claim backstage buildings for expansion.
Oh, because they used to fire them off from back there.
But now they'd land on our ashes would land on the galaxy.
Of like a office building or a parking garage and like cast members could like go into their parking garage and be like really close and watch.
Jesus I hate to be such an aggro dude about this, but I love when I love when the fire shoots up either in World of Color or in the one of the old Disneyland shows.
And it's usually like accompanied by the Star Wars theme and they just shoot flames into the sky.
I'm like, this is awesome.
Yeah, it is pretty cool.
I was going to say if we are getting to a less fireworks centric time while he's still on this earth, let's allow McCartney to still do it during living.
Living like that.
You know, he bless his heart.
We don't have much more Paul McCartney touring most likely.
So pure math.
I'm finally going to go for longer than anybody thinks.
Same, but I'm here for that.
So this is actually the perfect segue.
Last night, because Scott and I went to see Ringo Starr a couple of years ago and you were there.
I was very high.
I was crying laughing.
Y'all were so funny.
I just don't remember.
It was such a beautiful night.
Y'all were wearing your little Hawaii shirts, you know, Margaritaville.
I was laughing my ass off.
At Ringo Starr?
Them two, it's Scott and Mike.
I don't think we were wearing Hawaiian shirts in Ringo.
No, you were in my mind, okay?
Don't ruin this for me.
I think you might be remembering.
You were!
Don't you think Scott, you were in some kind of Hawaiian shirt?
Very possibly.
I have a photo somewhere.
I'll pull it out.
I was probably, you know, yeah, hey, I was probably something sort of like 60s psychedelic-y or something.
It was really fun.
So I looked last night and I was like, are there any instances of Beatles at Disneyland, specifically Ringo?
We have a rare case of visual aids on the television.
I found a blog, we'll post this, of all Beatles and Disney related photos.
Oh wow.
Good for them.
What's the blog?
Disneybeetles.tumblr.com.
Wow.
And there's some, nothing amazing, but some pretty cool.
So here's John.
Yes.
John wore a Mickey Mouse shirt.
Yeah, pretty classically.
And John also dissolved the Beatles officially at Walt Disney World.
At the Polynesian.
Oh my God.
He signed the papers saying Christmas over.
I didn't know that.
At the, yeah.
Well wait, now I heard the other rumor that the papers were delivered but there was a
problem, so it was signed in another location in Florida.
Oh, not at Disney World?
Yeah, not at Disney World, but he was at the Polynesian.
But there's a picture, one or two pictures go around, it's like here he is at the Polynesian
and it's a different Florida.
John dropped the pen and thus the papers had to be signed elsewhere.
I don't know why I'm debunking everything today.
That's okay.
Jason, you're in house every day.
This is honor.
Jason ruins everything.
I spent like half a day.
I gotta grow my hair out, I'm gonna do that.
I gotta give you the hair left.
Yeah, I spent like half a day reading about the-
That's the contemporary there.
Yeah.
Oh, the contemporary behind John Lennon.
There's a couple-
Grace.
John is at Disneyland, here, with a monorail driver, 1974.
It's really funny that John Lennon went to Disney World.
And there's the Eton Square.
He's at Disneyland too in these photos too, so like he must have kind of liked it.
John stayed at the Polynesian.
Here is Paul, 2009.
With his younger-
On the Autopia?
Yeah, on the Autopia with his young daughter.
Wow, cool.
Do we know for sure that's Paul McCartney?
I mean that could-
Yeah, look at the mouth.
You think he was singing his famous song, Red Rose Speedway?
Yeah.
And not the better car-related song he's written.
Certainly not Baby You Could Drive My Car.
No, we all think of Red Rose Speedway.
Now look at this.
This is Ringo Starr in New Orleans Square with a plaid.
I mean, is there a greater photo than this?
He's dead now, hard.
Yeah, real big hat.
Thor is dead.
And they have like Ringo and his children walk around Disneyland in the mid-1970s with their plaid, Linda Allen.
The plaid is named.
Plaids have names.
Yeah, look at that.
Wow.
This I don't know.
Linda was lovely.
She didn't see anything there.
Oh, that's them in the costumes, like the I Am The Walrus-y shit.
They're saying that's the Beatles in those outfits, but who knows?
Then there's Muppets, and that's cool, but that's not what they should have this on here.
Sean Lennon just has a Disney shirt on.
That's cute.
I love the idea, because I love niche Tumblrs.
Like celebrities in Disney shirts, I think that's a fun Tumblr.
Yeah, yeah.
Look at Ringo eating a popsicle or an ice cream at Disneyland.
That combines all of our interests.
It sure does.
That photo is the nexus of Scott Mike and Jason.
There's not too much more on here.
You went right past Winnie the Pooh recreating Abbey Road.
Yeah, but that doesn't do much for me.
There's some cartoons here.
You're looking for authentic Beatles content.
How about this?
Paul in a Grandma Mickey sweatshirt with some sort of chalice.
Wow.
Yes, I think probably we all have grandmas dressing similar to that.
That shirt is sick.
The collar is the grandma thing, especially about it.
This is from like 80, I think it says.
Do y'all ever go to those Disney after dark special nights or whatever?
I'm going to 90s night next month.
Oh, you are.
I'm so excited.
You'll have to report back.
Speaking of celebrities in Mickey clothes, I got this sick Mickey sweatshirt at a thrift store.
When I was buying it, the woman goes, you know who used to wear this sweatshirt?
Not the same exact one, maybe.
But Princess Diana.
There's a photo of Princess Diana.
If you Google Princess Diana Mickey sweatshirt, she's in this white sweatshirt and I have the same one.
And I'm wearing it.
Disney's 90 night baby.
That's great.
Wow.
Throwback to the reign of Princess Diana.
That's right.
So there's Paul with little Farrouza Balk on the set of Return to Oz.
Wow.
Paul was on the set of Return to Oz.
I don't know what the hell that's all about.
Strange.
Yeah.
And we all know Paul was on the set of Pirates 4.
There it is.
There's the people's princess.
If you Google Princess Diana Mickey, the picture comes up.
No kidding.
Right here.
Cool.
She has, I think that's Harry on her back and he's wearing a Mickey sweatshirt as well.
Do we think that's at a park?
No, maybe not.
I don't think this is, but there are photos of her at Disney World also.
Wow.
Here, we'll throw this to the audience too.
If you know, send us your favorite photos of your favorite or least favorite stars wearing
Disney sweaters.
What's that?
Sweaters.
I'm into sweaters almost more than anything.
Have y'all seen celebrities at Disney?
Like with their guides?
Here and there.
Do you ever find out that you were there the same day when you, like I was just, I saw
Mark Hoppus was there the same day as me and I was like, oh man.
I didn't say hi.
Because you went to a Blink in Vegas, right?
Yeah.
You're like a Blink diehard?
I'm going again and they're doing like this back to the beach fest or something in Huntington
Beach in April, May.
I'm going again.
I gotta get my Blink fix.
You know what's my favorite?
I forget if I've said this on the podcast before that the, I have a hazy memory of that
I may have as a child been going, been in line for the teacups and that into the booth
the announcements are made on the teacups.
I think maybe Tim Allen got on and made the teacup announcement because I think it ended,
I think it was, it was kind of confusing what was going on, but I think it's possible that
he, an announcement was made and then he did, ha ha ha.
And the, and people in line went, oh, but maybe I just didn't understand what the hell
was going on.
Yeah.
If anyone can vouch for Tim Allen's whereabouts throughout the nineties.
They would have probably had to pay him for that.
You know what I mean?
If I were him, I wouldn't give them my voice for free.
Oh, yeah.
I mean, Disney's paid him quite a bit of money.
Yeah.
But maybe he's, I don't know, maybe he was in a good mood on a vacation.
Maybe he was tripping and feeling like giving it out for free.
Do you think there's so many celebrity voices at Disneyland?
Like the monorail, isn't that Billy West?
Is that Billy West?
No, I don't think so.
Is it somebody doing a Billy West impression then?
It's a similar, I hear what you're saying.
Yeah, it's similar.
But then they have like some of those people.
Like Neil Patrick Harris does one, right?
Well, he's gone now.
He was the running coaster.
Credit coaster.
In credit coaster.
So he's been replaced.
But yeah, there's like little things.
A lot of those people don't get any much money for it because like people in the video, like
Patrick Warburton is in two different rides.
He's on Soarin' and he's on Star Tours.
Is he on a third one?
Am I misremembering?
I don't believe so.
Okay.
Yeah.
So like there's, yeah, there are like a lot of things.
I didn't realize it was Neil Patrick Harris until I think a year ago or something.
He was like five, four, three, two, one.
But were I?
He probably just did that on his damn iPhone in his bathroom and got a million dollars.
Possibly.
The final picture though, real quick, is Julian Lennon, which is the greatest photo with Space
Mickey.
Space Epcot Mickey at Epcot Center with Spaceship Earth in the back.
Wow.
Looking just like his father.
Yeah, I mean I probably wouldn't have even known that wasn't him if you had to say.
So we'll post a link to this.
Follow along with this Tumblr.
Before it gets taken down for whatever Tumblr rules that take down everything now.
Disney sues him and every beetle widow sues them.
Yeah.
It's sued into the ground.
Animal Kingdom.
Let's get back on track.
Yes.
Kilimanjaro Safari, as we talked about, which by the way, I didn't know this fact that that
ride is bigger than the Magic Kingdom.
The square foot.
Oh wow, I didn't know that either.
Because the track is like two miles.
The largest attraction in any Disney theme park.
Wow.
No kidding.
Yeah.
And there's a cool video of what you were saying, Mike, of the cars getting stopped
and where is all of them and it's all along a track and there's little light up dots and
somebody's nervously monitoring at a computer and seeing where the Jeeps are and it is exactly
Jurassic Park.
It is so excitingly a Samuel L. Jackson scenario.
So you get if you want to be a real life.
What's his name?
We I know Nedry, but what's Sam?
I can never remember his name.
If you want to be a hold on to your butts, man, get that job.
Be the Jeep monitor at Kilimanjaro Safari's.
But yeah, I why would this ride another go?
Because I did it in this unpleasant poacher era in which there was a fake dead elephant.
No, yeah, I think that's got to be going.
It's upset.
But at the same time, this is the reality and people need to know.
And I'm like a dark kind of because they brought that up on mine.
At one point they were like, this is the white rhino.
They're almost extinct, you know, and then they even said, which it pissed me off so bad.
There were elephants in there to have the African elephants in there and dangers.
And they were like, if you really want to help the elephants recycle your electronics.
And I was like, if you really want to help the animals, don't eat them.
I mean, that's all there is to it.
The more our society normalizes animal cruelty, the more people are going to hunt them, eat them, kill them and mistreat them.
And that's just the bottom line.
And that's like my angry veganism.
You get off this ride where you're like literally looking at these beautiful animals and they're like, have your turkey leg.
Have your fucking burger.
You have flame.
Look at the animals, eat the animals.
This one's OK.
This one is it.
I hate it.
Reading about the restaurants, I'm like for a park called Animal Kingdom, all the best reviews restaurants are barbecue locations.
They're like, it's just it doesn't.
Once you see that and you're like, yeah, this is fucked up.
You can't unsee it as a person.
And that's just another hypocrisy of our society.
Sure. So while you like this park, it is a park of hypocrisy.
Well, they all are.
I mean, there's no such thing as a vegan park.
They do have more options of food.
You know, friggin California Adventure is like vegan out.
You can eat vegan good food there, not just like fries, which, oh my God, Tokyo, Japan starved my ass off.
My wife's in trouble. My wife's vegetarian.
She's in trouble.
I starved through Japan.
Any advice?
Anything we wouldn't know?
I mean, I have lots of I did a whole map.
I did a whole map.
Again, the Google Maps, I can say to y'all.
But did you were you like we're just thinking granola bars.
Let's just load up.
But you're used to it.
You know, I'm used to it.
Like I said, food isn't a big part of the tourist experience for me.
Unfortunately, it's just how it is.
But it's really difficult.
We're very privileged in L.A.
I forget like that.
And then I go somewhere else and I'm like, oh, I don't have rice.
Oh, the rice has been, you know, beef stock.
Cool. I will eat this pickle.
I'll eat a pickle and die.
It's boiled in beef brine.
I mean, it is depending on where you are.
It's really hard.
But there was maybe vegetable curry in Tokyo.
There was. Yeah, it's vegetarian, though.
Well, it was actually vegan.
So vegans pass.
That's right. Yeah, it's hard.
And then, I mean, that's a whole other story.
I we went to when I went to see the Snow Monkeys in Japan, we were staying in a Rio
Khan, which is like the traditional Japanese hotel, which if you have time to leave
Tokyo and go to a Rio Khan, it's so cool.
It's worth the trip.
You don't have to go that far out, but it's really cool.
And I had written ahead and told them I don't eat meat.
And they were like, but I guess to them, fish isn't meat.
Oh, no.
And they started serving me the most fishy fish of all the fish.
You know what I mean?
Like a little whole fish on a plate with his little eyeballs looking at me.
They served me a bowl of little tiny squids.
And I don't know if they were raw or if they were boiled.
But like Adam, my husband popped one into his mouth and I saw him like chewing it.
I was like, how is it?
And he was like, very fishy.
And I just moved stuff around my plate.
And then I felt terrible because it's a part of the culture to like not be
disrespectful and be like, I'm not eating that.
You know, it was just I was very hungry.
It was really not.
I also think I'm going to have two meals every meal as I am given what my wife
cannot eat. So I'm going to try to get the weight down.
Does Erin eat fish?
No. Oh, OK. Yep.
But she's going to look the other way on stocks.
Stocks are going to be tough. She's just going to.
You know what? I don't know what I don't know.
Same way, because part of me was like, I'm in a different culture.
I don't want I want to I want to try things, you know, whatever.
So I definitely had fish in Japan.
I had to. You know what I mean?
Every stock is everything.
I did my best to ask about things.
You know, it'd be so crazy.
I was like, is there anything in this rice?
And they go ask and they go, there's pork, there's beef and there's chicken.
And I'm like, they put pork in everything.
You know, and fish, they put fish in everything.
It was like in on The Simpsons when he's like, is anything without meat?
Possibly the meatloaf. Right.
Or when they go to the all you can eat seafood place in March goes,
is there anything without fish in it?
And they they and she goes, I'll just have the tic tacs in my purse.
He was excellent choice.
I felt I was just like, well, it's fine. I'll see the tic tacs.
That's all real. Oh, boy.
So good luck.
It's hard. Can I guess is the topic of
of animals and generally
like a disconnect of what's an animal and what's not.
I've watched several several specials did this, but especially one.
There's a in preparation for this episode, I watched some Michael Eisner
intros and stuff, which, you know, a classic hello always does me good.
But there's a really good one.
His intro to an animal kingdom special that Drew Carey ends up taking
the reins and posting.
But Michael kicks it off.
Hello. And then he talks about he he he says he says how Disney's
connection to animals has been part of the company for over seventy five years.
And then it cuts to Mickey Mouse.
And I'm like, like a drawing like, yeah, like a scratchy drawing.
Yeah. And then Steamboat Willie.
And I saw other things that said, you know, and with Animal Kingdom,
Disney's love affair for animals continues because as Walt said,
it all began with a mouse.
And I guess Mickey is a mouse.
But isn't it in the Safari Park?
Don't you feel a disconnect with that Mickey Mouse is an animal like my
if you had to describe him in ten words, I don't think animal would be one of the words.
He's essentially a person. He's a cartoon.
He's one of us, but he has big ears.
He's a person with big ears.
Well, and Disney did all those nature documentaries that like baby boomers
would have grown up watching on TV and like the people who would be paying for
a trip to this park would probably fondly remember.
Yes, that would be the connection to Disney and animals.
To me, it's weird to go.
It's Michael Eisner in an African village shopping and people are in the
people are in tribal wear and there's the dung dung dung dung.
And then they're telling me that, well, I don't know if you knew this,
but Disney likes animals and then it cuts to a 1920s mouse on a steamboat.
There's just an aesthetic disconnect here.
Specifically, I believe because I watch that special too.
And this is what I'm going to say. That special is rough.
We like these specials.
They're yeah, this one's really, really hard.
A lot of public domain, do do do do do kind of like music, like comedy music,
like comedy music. Yeah.
Now I get there's some very good music in it too, like Ladysmith, Black Mabazo,
Lebo M from the sings the song from the opening of the Lion King movie and musical.
But then there's like this like slapstick music and like some really very odd
like guests show up.
Paul Rodriguez and Jane Seymour and her family, a lot of family forced in there.
A fourth Maori, there's Tia Tamera, Taj and then you saw the fourth one.
There's a fourth Maori.
Fourth Maori is a lie.
It also like I think that is Eisner.
The opening is Eisner walking through the Harambe section, the Harambe village.
And it is so populated with background actors and like set dressing and stuff.
Like it looks like a full interactive theater thing.
And later, Jane Seymour and her family, and I feel very bad about this,
but they meet the mayor of Harambe Village, Joseph Botoa.
I'm sorry, Joseph.
I'm going to, as I've said before, I will be rat fucking all of the park managers
when my reign begins.
Welcome to Harambe. Meet the mayor, Jason Sheridan.
Jumbo, welcome.
But yeah, I think that some of that, I don't remember much interaction,
interactive element.
They felt like they were really pushing.
Like it's a living, breathing thing.
And I do think this park has a lot of character and is of any of them in Florida,
living, breathing thing.
But I'm like, who are all these people walking around for this special?
I feel like they're later on.
Yeah, little too thick.
Does anyone have any information, memories of the opening village of Harambe?
Or is this a mystery to us all?
This is no Main Street, I don't think.
No, I've been twice or a couple of times in the last few years.
This is in the Africa, the section of the park.
It's where, what else is there?
This is where the Kilimanjaro safaris leaves from.
This is where you board the train to go to Rafiki's Planet Watch.
Which is over now, right?
It's reopening.
Yeah, it's reopening.
Everyone thought they were, they announced they closed it,
and now they just announced they're reopening it in the spring.
How about that? Rafiki's Planet Watch?
Anybody?
I listened to y'all's episode on the Kilimanjaro.
Ever.
Yes.
And I like that this park only has like two or three big rides,
and the rest is kind of chilling, looking around,
looking at animals, you know.
Because of where I'm at in life, you know, I don't need those crazy rides.
You know what I mean?
I don't need to get a head rush and fill like shit for two days.
I like just easy, I love going through all the animals and looking at them.
And again, I guess from someone who doesn't really go to zoos often,
you can go up to that glass,
and there are gorillas on the other side of the glass like five feet from you.
I mean, not like a foot from you.
Oh, yeah.
And you can just sit there and watch them.
Look at the bats.
Did you see the bats?
No!
The bats are so close.
The bats are, I forget, if I forget which, it's the walkthrough tour.
I think of the same when you're talking about,
but there's a couple like of those little rooms,
and you just go and you just stare at bats like three feet from you,
and you're like, these are terrifying.
Bats are so weird.
They're just hanging there, and you're just like fascinated.
And also, there's holes, there's like netting to protect you,
but you're like, I can pull my hand through here.
They put a lot of trust in people.
Yeah.
Because I was thinking that being,
I don't know if you all are like this,
but I have sort of a dark vision of things where I'm like,
oh, I could just throw this at someone.
Oh, I know, all the time.
You could throw a damn camera at an antelope and hit them.
You're saying?
They couldn't stop you.
They could remove you from the park and sue you or whatever,
but they trust these people going through that safari
to not jump out and grab a lion or something.
Is there a name for that?
Because I have that, where it's an impulse to do the worst thing you could ever do.
You don't do it, but you see it in your head.
They say that's healthy, to have like, this thought is crazy,
and then you actively recognize yourself not acting on it.
Yeah, I do that constantly.
It's weird.
It's like fantasize about if, now I could do this, is what you're saying.
Yeah.
The Starbucks is closed.
There's no one inside.
I could drive into it.
What's the harm?
I've never had that one.
You never just wanted to destroy a storefront?
That wouldn't matter so much.
I feel like I used to have it when I'd be in band
and I'd be watching the different symphonic band play,
and I had my trumpet waiting for my part,
and I'd be like, I could fuck everything up right now.
I never got close to it, but I would get away.
This probably seems like part of my character.
I would get away with telling other kids to do bad stuff in high school.
I would say, hey, it would be funny if you,
when you were signing your slip that said you practiced,
if you signed like Hitler, and he would do it.
I would get kids to do stuff because I was too scared to do it.
I had bad instincts.
That isn't as bad as driving your car through the Starbucks.
No.
You didn't get anybody to go full reference.
Again, no one's in there.
They're insured.
I'm insured.
Go to the drive-thru first.
And what's the name on that?
Hitler.
Then drive through the store.
Get your jollies off.
And play a ripping off-key trombone solo.
Let's combine all of these awful things.
That would be so funny.
And a little lying loose in there, too.
It would be so funny if you just, oh, when the saints...
in the middle of the day.
What's the worst thing I could do now?
Play when the saints go marching in at an inappropriate time.
Now, in terms of worst-case scenario, thinking,
I did find out an interesting thing about Animal Kingdom.
It is the only one of the Disney parks where the bathrooms have doors.
Think about the other Disney parks.
You walk into the bathrooms.
It's kind of an entryway, hallway sort of thing.
These bathrooms have doors.
In case an animal gets loose, you have a place to hide.
So, now, there is not really any record of incidents of animals getting loose, thankfully.
But there's other parks with doors.
It's just maybe all the bathrooms have doors in it.
Yeah, maybe that's it.
It's something like that.
Disney has doors on bathrooms.
Disneyland, I guess.
Typically, they're just open.
Yeah, right.
I feel like, yeah.
More likely.
But Animal Kingdom designed actively with doors.
The day where the shit goes down and everybody's huddling in an Animal Kingdom bathroom.
The Jurassic Park day.
Yeah, yeah.
But don't you think they would shoot that poor thing with tranquilizers so fast?
Yeah, I think there's probably extra guns at Animal Kingdom.
The problem is they're all different animals and they all have to coordinate sort of with themselves
to probably be an effective human eating situation.
They'd all have to somehow communicate to each other, today's the day.
Right.
Because I could see just a pack of rhinos going nuts and they'll tranq them.
All the animals would have to lose their mind.
Collectively come together and say, May 5th, we're going.
Which might be a thing that they'll evolve into.
Yeah.
Like generations from now, the animals also develop a like, we gotta get the hell out of here.
Which especially the better kept animals at Animal Kingdom who are like,
or have it better than the caged animals at other zoos.
Right.
Yeah, maybe they're more, that's where the singularity, that's where the animal's singularity is.
Yes, the animal singularity.
The animal singularity, yes.
That'd be more likely to happen at like a shitty zoo.
Maybe so.
Yeah.
Where security is less.
But I don't know, maybe these Animal Kingdom animals are smarter.
Maybe they're evolving faster, so in a hundred years.
And if some of those crazy crocodiles from the swamps start making it down there,
maybe they start unlocking cages with their teeth and letting their buddies out.
Are there like three Dr. Dolittle movies in development?
Like if people get inspired to talk to the animals, you know.
We must kill these films before they wreak havoc.
The good news is we won't be here in a hundred years.
Sure, maybe not.
Oh, maybe not.
Maybe not.
Uh oh.
Because of global warming.
Oh wow.
From Animal Agriculture.
Yeah, that's true.
I'm sorry.
Hey look, it's a park with a conservation message and this is an episode with a conservation message.
Yes.
Which said that is a thing that sets some of these attractions apart that even the Rapids ride has is about deforestation.
Which I was watching this with my wife and she pointed out, oh yes, clearing out a bunch of forests for industrial purposes.
You know, like a theme park.
It is a little weird to be, yeah imagine, forests coming down.
I think there's a time and a place and entertainment is important and art is important.
And you know, keep some forests up, take some of it down for things that are going to serve us and then keep a balance.
Yeah.
You know.
Especially in Florida where like for every plot of land Disney does something, two of it affects like swamp or marshland.
They have to do something to counteract it.
And they have, right?
Yeah, yeah, quite a bit.
They've covered their ass.
They got a PR team on this.
Tons of trees, tons of plants and stuff added for Animal Kingdom.
I remember that when I first went.
Like these trees are a little thin.
Sort of the same thing with later 20th century islands of adventure and California adventure.
Like the early pictures make it look so thin in terms of trees because it takes like a decade for stuff to really grow and fill in.
But like Animal Kingdom looks beautiful now.
Yeah.
And especially now with all the trees are helping it.
But Animal Kingdom is the only one I don't know my way around still.
Yeah.
Which is interesting.
If I landed there right now, I wouldn't know where Asia is as opposed to Dino Land USA.
I know like vaguely where stuff is.
But like I like that aspect of it is like it does feel a little bit less structured than a theme park.
Even though it's of course structured like theme park.
It's just I don't know.
They do a good job of sort of blending everything and making me kind of in my memory be like, I don't remember where I see Everest over there.
I know where that is.
But it's like you're exploring.
It is an actual jungle.
I would imagine too like when Animal Kingdom started, there were the grand plans of like what we were talking about going back to like the mayor and like locals and this.
And this is what I was telling you that Jason the other day is why we got to go to Star Wars land first couple of weeks.
Is because they had such grand plans and vision for it.
And then within a couple of weeks, they're like, oh, this isn't sustainable.
Uh huh.
Like all this insane stuff.
Right.
This is because they're talking about being able to barter with a robot at Star Wars land.
And it's like, that's going to go away.
That's not going to last for a week.
Like three weeks.
A kid will stick a pencil in its eye and it'll short out.
Or like a dad will be confused.
He just wants to buy an item.
It's just like the robot won't give me the price I'm looking for.
And then he freaks out.
And then it's a viral video.
If the card has a chip, you must insert the chip.
Well, no, it's a Disney credit.
I have points on Disney bucks on the credit card.
Dad melts down and strangles robot.
It'll be like a viral video and then they have to pull the robot out.
What are dollars called in Star Wars?
Damn it.
I just want a Diet Coke.
I'm so tired.
We do not have Diet Coke here.
I know.
Yes.
I've been told that at every location.
Why you can milk Diet Coke from this beast?
I don't want to milk it.
Diet C-K-E is available.
Is that the same thing or is that a different call letter for a robot or droid?
They're not called robots here.
Droid is the correct term.
I think this is me.
I think I'm going to be this.
You might be the main guy.
Yeah, you might be.
I'm going to bring it all the way.
And not have a getting a Diet Coke.
I love people watching at the parks.
I love the dads that you know or have to work and they just had to go for the family.
You can see their mind racing in their heads as they were.
They're like Winnie the Pooh Mickey ears.
They're just like, I got to get back to the office.
McGillicuddy files are due.
I love it.
They all work in the 50s.
The Florida one, I think, is you see more of it because I feel like I see less of Cranky Dad and Disneyland.
I see more of somebody who I might profile as hating Disneyland, but they have a big sweatshirt on, a big gaudy Mickey sweatshirt on or something.
You kind of overhear them talking and you're like, oh, they're a nerd too.
Yeah, I don't know if Florida has as many townies as we have.
They don't.
Yeah.
You see more, I think, of Dad on vacation who has no strong appreciation for this and is just exhausted.
There's so many people that from around the area that have passes that just go and get a dole whip and go home.
You know, or that kind of thing.
Yeah.
Ain't it grand?
That's the best.
You know who took a vacation to Disney's Animal Kingdom was Sabrina the Teenage Witch.
Oh, I didn't know that.
There's a full Animal Kingdom episode of it.
She doesn't go to the other parks.
It's entirely a lot of the show.
Thirty percent of the show is in a hotel is in a fake Coronado Springs hotel room and the rest is in Animal Kingdom.
And I love a good TGIF Disney World episode.
This is a rough one.
Yeah, it's not.
I think this might be some of why I didn't really like Animal Kingdom for a while.
These I didn't like the specials as much.
Not a very good TGIF.
There is a very rough B plot where the two aunts are digging in Dino land USA, which is an area where you where kids can like excavate and they find a bone.
And I guess a real bone is what we're led to believe.
And one of the aunts said one of the answers, I've got to find out more about this bone, which is like that's a great promo line.
This week on Sabrina, I've got to find out more about this bone.
Which aunt is it? Caroline Ray?
It's the other aunt.
The other aunt that I don't know the name of.
Brodrick, I want to say.
My dream role, a witchy aunt.
I'm getting up there, you know.
I love those aunts.
I thought they were very funny.
Me too.
They were great.
Oh, and the cat.
Yeah, Salem.
Salem was my favorite.
Yeah, I also thought it was very cute when they all wished the Netflix cast good luck on their show.
I thought that was very charming.
That's nice.
The thumbnail down from the Disney World episode, the very next episode has RuPaul in it.
So they had fun bands and stuff.
I feel like the monkeys were on Sabrina.
Wait, is Sabrina on Netflix?
It's on Hulu.
Okay, good to know.
Sabrina on Hulu.
Check it out.
I used to watch.
I was very into the show when it was on.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Rough Disney World episode, though, I have to say.
The bone comes to life with magic and they make it a Neanderthal who's running around the park with them.
What?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's an odd choice.
Yeah, really strange.
See, and you barely get to see, a lot of it is Sabrina running around the nature outskirt of the party.
You don't get to see rides.
They don't talk about dinosaur.
They don't go on it.
It's a rough.
Give me my sweet park shots.
Let me see characters riding a ride with no jokes for five minutes.
That's what I want in my theme park episode.
This park, the way the lands and everything are broken up, it does start to slip a little
because it's like, ah, the oasis when you walk in.
And then Discovery Island, which was originally called Safari something, where the Tree of Life is,
the big centerpiece of the park, is on an island in the middle of the waterway.
And then you have Africa and Asia.
And then Dino Land USA.
Had to get America in there somehow.
And then eventually Pandora, the world of Avatar.
Yeah, it's a strange breakdown.
Continent, continent, weird side road attraction, and then a place beyond the realm of imagination.
You know what's so interesting though is that I never even thought about that.
I wonder how many people even notice that.
How many people know the names of these things at all?
I'm usually just looking around, being like, oh, that's cool.
And I do have to give them credit.
There is a full bag of like, oh, Dino Land USA was made by Chester and Hester.
It was a roadside attraction.
Like all the dinosaur, like the Cabezon dinosaurs in California.
They did put some thought into it because they're like, well, we need to put some kiddie rides in here somewhere.
Yeah, they found a way to justify it.
But I was reminding myself of the not built, what was supposed to be in Dino Land USA, the excavator.
Oh, yeah.
The excavator was like a mine car that takes you into the dig site and things go haywire and you go through.
It's like kind of an advance of Big Thunder Mountain, where you go through some of those dinosaur bones and here you go through a full, you know, long, fully enveloping dinosaur skeleton.
And then you get attacked by like a robotic dinosaur.
Like it's like a crane or something that looks like a dinosaur.
Like a dinosaur. The concept art is super cool.
And they they were going to do it.
This was going to be one of the major attractions of the place.
And then Countdown to Extinction came up, which was a tie in to the movie dinosaur that was coming out.
And they could use the same track as Indiana Jones.
That was going to be cheaper.
So we didn't get this cool Dino roller coaster.
That's so I think that would have like notched up this park.
Yeah, from out of the gate a little stronger.
But they had to spread the word about the tale of, you know, Aladar and Kron, our friends Aladar and Kron as voiced by D.B. Sweeney and Julianne Margulies.
Dinosaur is a weird.
Yeah, we should do.
We should watch.
We should do a dinosaur commentary.
We shouldn't flick dinosaur.
That I feel like was one where my family just silently agreed like that summer.
Like, well, we can skip this one, right?
Like no one was jumping on that.
Yeah. Yeah.
You skipped it then.
Yeah. I mean, you like Grandma Auntie's Squirrel Badger Cafe.
She's Grandma Auntie.
Animals not represented.
Not even an animal.
She's a big aunt.
Grandma and an aunt though.
Of course you could.
I would imagine.
Who knows?
Did you like dinosaur when you went?
I did.
Dinosaur was cool.
Expedition Everest, very cool.
Sure.
But my favorite, favorite, favorite thing was the Kilimanjaro Safari.
I loved it.
OK. I did mention this.
So I was at this park with my friend who is a former Imagineer.
She was a very current non-Imagineer.
Anymore.
So we were hearing all the commentary from the Couture guy.
She was also telling me things and I was so I was so interested in one thing.
She had said that the giraffe, I think giraffes are so cool.
I mean, really, these animals are fucking crazy looking like this warthog jumps out and you're like, this is a damn pig with a damn wig on.
It's like a wig, a big crazy gray wig.
It's like shoved at the bottom of the wig bed at the UCB prop closet.
You know what I mean?
Sure.
Every mod team has worn that wig at one point.
This damn pig shoots out with a damn wig on.
I mean, animals are crazy.
Yeah.
And giraffes are cool.
And she told me that the giraffes at Disney's Animal Kingdom are some of the only giraffes in the whole world that sleep lying down because they know they are not in immediate danger.
Oh, wow.
And that made me cry.
And I thought that was so sweet because, you know, maybe they are in a park, but they're safe.
Well, they're not going to get shot.
They're not going to get eaten.
And I love that.
And I even quoted that in my wedding vows because I was I said something about like, I feel like a giraffe at Disney.
Like I'm saying it was cute.
That's amazing.
But in that moment, I like really like that really got to me.
You know, that's so interesting.
Because it's so crazy.
It looks like those lions are going to eat them.
They're five feet away.
You're like there's a lion on a rock right next to them.
But they are there's hidden barriers that we can't see.
I wonder if they ever go over there and sniff at those giraffes.
You know, it's really interesting.
That would be a question for like an Imagineer of what are the protocols in place for things like how fast is someone deployed?
What is the mechanism to deploy?
If someone if one wanders into a wrong spot, but they don't, I guess, you know, I mean, they because lions are only active for four hours.
And then the rest of the time they're sleeping.
Well, so it's crazy.
And the women are the hunters, not the men.
Is there?
Sure.
Hey, let's say shout out to the those temperature controlled rocks.
Also, isn't that sweet?
I think that's sweet.
How does that work?
If it's cold, they do they warm the rocks and vice versa.
They cool them down.
Those are those got to go into our fake rock Hall of Fame.
Yeah, yeah.
And so, yeah, those are very special fake rocks.
Yeah, they have a purpose beyond making some dorks in their 30s freak out.
They help animals.
The lions lay on the rocks.
That's delightful.
It's so sweet because they really are just big old cats.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
They really are just big old cats.
Oh, no, go ahead.
I was going to say, did you all see the aquarium like the fish in the tank?
I think it's called the it's not at the rain forest cafe.
Yes.
Beautiful, wonderful appetizer deals.
No, I'm just you know, it's crazy.
I've never been to the rainforest cafe ever.
There was one in Dallas and it was so popular.
There was a line out the place and I was just like, I don't like lines.
Oh, yeah.
This is the wrong topic.
I haven't been to.
I haven't been to the Navi Avatar land.
Satuli.
I'm not going to stand in line for two fucking hours.
I'm 34 years old.
I don't care.
You know what I mean?
Like, I can't think of anything.
Mike, counterpoint.
Counterpoint.
Briding on the back of the mighty Akron is something that you never forget.
It is a journey that people literally gasped after they were done when we went out the first
time.
Very emotional and I would argue very emotional.
Very emotional and I would argue very worth two hours.
Really?
The Avatar?
I would.
Yeah.
Wow.
See, that's really interesting.
That's good to hear.
You know, I waited in line for Blink 182 to be the very first person in.
I did that.
Was that the recent concert or before?
Yeah, the one in Vegas.
So you were up in the front of the pit.
I was at the very front, right?
Under Mark.
How is the mosh pit now at that?
And what's the age group?
Zero.
Zero mosh pit.
People our age?
They don't let you mosh.
Oh, interesting.
They didn't at this particular event.
I mean, you're in the casino.
Right, right.
You're in the palms.
But is it people in their 30s?
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Next to me was like a chick my age.
It's all kind of our age, people.
I was shocked because I saw a replacements concert a couple years ago and there's all
people older than me because that was a band that was popular when I was not born or very,
very little.
Yeah.
I don't even know what that band is, I'm embarrassed to say.
Oh, well they're like a cool, they're like a culty, a cool band, but they're really,
really good.
I think that the hype is not too much for them.
They're really great.
But they reformed and there were a lot of baby boomer types there and all of a sudden
they started, there's like a group that started like moshing.
So like dads were like smacking into each other and then like some dads were mad at
the dads moshing.
Yeah.
And it was a whole like scene developed at the palladium.
I was like, what the hell's going on here?
I love that.
When I saw Blink at the forum a couple years ago, there were kids sitting in front of me
and they knew every word and they were probably 16, which is when I, how old I was when I
saw Blink in concert.
Sure.
So because of YouTube and stuff, fandom has grown into all genres for everything.
Right.
But y'all, we, did y'all go to Ringo last year?
No.
Okay.
Y'all went to two years before?
Yes.
We saw, we saw the lineup with the Todd Rundgren, Richard Page.
Who else is an all star?
Richard Page.
God, what an angel.
Hell yeah.
Richard, Richard Page, that ties it back together.
Richard Page sings America.
Spend your golden way.
That guy from the Ringo band, the singer of Mr.
Mister is sings the American Adventure Epcot song.
Oh my God.
I didn't know that.
There you go.
Ringo was repping Disney.
That should be on the account.
Post a picture of Ringo and Richard Page.
More all star content please.
That man has the voice of a fucking angel.
Again, I was very high.
I was weeping during his songs because I don't believe in God, but that made me believe in God.
I was like, this person is blessed.
The vocals of Richard Page?
Are you kidding me?
Wow.
He's an older man, but he sounds like he's 20.
You're talking like QT.
You sound like QA, a lazen.
Yes.
Broken wings.
Check out his solo album.
Check out OCOE from his band, Pages in the 70s.
I'll cut myself off now.
I'll never stop talking.
I'm impressed.
OCOE.
Check it out.
But anyway.
He's amazing.
Yeah.
And y'all need to see Ringo and the all star band if they come through town ever.
It was a best concert.
Hey, theme park fans, check out Ringo and the all star band.
That was what happened to me in that concert.
Yeah.
He's in this deep, not famous culty band called Pages.
They're not even culty.
They're so obscure.
This band, Pages, and he was setting up one of his songs, one of his Mr.
Mr. songs.
And you know, I used to be in a band called Pages.
Woo.
Me only.
In the entire Greek theater.
One person.
And everyone's old too.
Like everyone had many more years to know that.
Yeah.
And absorb it.
Even more sad.
And they did not.
And I'm, yes, somehow me in my 30s, I'm the only person giving him love on this.
I'm going to look that band up now.
Please check out Pages.
His voice is incredible.
I mean, it moved me.
Oh, you're all saying the whole Pages thing.
I missed him this last round when Ringo was back in LA last year.
He wasn't in the band anymore and I was bummed.
Oh, he's out of the band?
He was this round.
Yeah.
It was still a great show.
The men at work guy is now in it.
Oh, he was in it a long time.
Colin Hay.
He was great.
He's lost in and out of the All-Star band.
I did a whole bonus episode of my show, Natch Butte, which is a fucking makeup podcast about
Ringo starring the All-Star band.
That's how passionate I was about this.
Oh, yeah, I listened to it.
It was a bonus episode I did and I started crying because Ringo has overcome so much.
He almost died as a child.
Couldn't read, was poor and look at him now.
He's flourishing.
He's truly inspiring.
He's not signing autographs, but other than that, he's living by the face I love to go
back to the...
But you know why he doesn't sign autographs?
Because they would end up on eBay and he would rather sign things that he knows are going
to go to charity.
So he only signs things for charity now.
He should have said...
He was saying that it was an angry moment, he said, when he made that video.
Yeah, because he was mad because he saw Gattari sign it up on eBay.
He explained it on Howard Stern.
Okay, so no deforestation.
Be careful with our animals and don't sell Ringo's merch.
And no more autographs.
Peace and love.
This episode is really like one of the circuitous tracks and trails you can take around the
animal kingdom.
Well look, we're going to break off on these rides.
Please, just individually.
In fact, here's a little tease.
I think we can say we're soon going to do an episode about one of the shows.
And I don't want to say what show, but we don't have time to go into it because there's
so much to get in there.
I mean, it's got two worlds and one family.
How can we possibly fit this into an already two hour episode?
I'm excited to learn what this is because I have forgotten in this moment.
Even Jason doesn't know.
Oh boy, get ready.
Buckle up everybody.
But hey, what do we fit in before we wrap it up?
I got a roadie thing.
Yeah.
Joe Roadie.
Yeah, so I kind of was wondering about why does everything look Asian?
Especially in the continent of Asia.
There's so much of Asia that looks like Blade Runner, that looks like the future.
And I was trying to figure out why all this older looking things.
And of course, Joe Roadie is on record.
They reached out to local craftsmen, they'd carve animal statues and do roof work, and
they learned how they built buildings.
We talked about that on the Everest one.
And he has a very interesting quote about aging, which was the idea behind it of making
everything look older.
And I'm lost.
I know I swiped it.
Okay, we created this motif of age of erosion.
It reminds us that no matter how great our efforts, nature is the most powerful force
around us and we should respect it.
It's almost a moral tale.
So I think that is very fascinating to look at the park through that lens and see, oh yeah,
the park, the nature of the park just keeps growing, but everything has rust painted on
or faded elements to it.
So it's always reminding you of the temporary nature of our structures, but the nature itself
will keep thriving.
This is great.
Hey, Joe Roadie, as we've said a little bit before, this is kind of the culmination of
his aesthetic at this point.
The park in general was this guy, Avatar is this guy, Expedition Everest.
He's a legend.
Did you go on the Tower of Terror in Tokyo?
Hell yes.
Twice.
Do you know the character they have, Harrison Hightower?
That's modeled after, imagine, Joe Roadie, who's a very earthy guy, so it's a Joe Roadie
guy, so it's a joke that he's this crazy capitalist monster.
Oh, so it's playing against type.
Scott, you don't know about the Tower of Terror.
I know about generally Harrison Hightower, but I don't know the story.
It's so fantastic.
It's really cool.
If I get up the nerve to do it.
At least go to the line.
At least do the queue.
Oh wait, you don't like drop rides?
I'm in no drop.
Yeah, I hear that.
I've started doing the launch.
I've come around on the launch.
It's going to be hard.
It's going to be hard, still.
It'll be hard, though, if you're in the line, you're trying to explain to somebody who doesn't
speak English, like I'm just doing the queue.
I thought about this.
Right, right, right.
And they're like, right this way.
And you're like, ah, the exit.
And then you're on the ride.
I think you can pull it off.
But it's a little less scary than current Guardians.
Correct.
I have not been on it, to be honest.
Well, no, I guess you know what it is.
There's a, I'm trying to think.
There's a couple months now where they do a bunch more drops.
What we found on it was that it was too short for us.
It felt like the original Tower of Terror ride profile.
And it felt like 90 seconds or a minute.
And we're like, that's it?
So then apparently there's a couple months when they try to attract like teenagers to come to the park where it's like called like something more, blah, blah, blah.
And it's more change up ride profiles and it's more drops and stuff.
And it seems like it's, but I don't know if that's happening now.
I swear.
Teenagers love to drop.
But I was like so mad.
It's fine there during the teen months.
I think it's all teen specific.
These teens will be the death of me.
But you have to see the pre-show and everything.
And just the queue itself is unbelievable.
At the very least, once you get to like the loading area, just like run backwards and like.
I bet there's some kind of exit area.
There has to be.
There has to be, yeah.
Or just have your like translator out and says like, I need to leave.
They'll know enough.
I pissed my pants here.
What does this say?
They shut the ride down.
That translator app doesn't work that well.
I got into a weird thing with a girl and I wish I could remember it.
She showed it to me and it said like lion lubricant or something.
I was like, what?
And she was trying to tell me that I had my shirt on inside out.
My tag was out.
It was because she translated Japanese to show it to me in English.
And I was like, oh, thank.
I didn't know what the fuck she showed me.
I was like, Adam, it just said lion lubricant.
I was like, what?
I just go like smile.
I didn't know what she was trying to tell me.
Yeah.
We had some success with it, but it wasn't perfect.
I'm trying to go through just like last anything I wanted to get in.
There's probably a lot more we could talk about with the beastly kingdom.
We've alluded to a little.
There's supposed to be a mythological world that was kind of too expensive to get built.
Avatar sort of in its place now.
That's what represents the fantastical side of nature.
And that was going to be the thrilling more like kind of element that some people thought was lacking where you'd get a crazy ride.
Roller coaster there.
Right.
Yeah.
Really good road.
Now there's Everest.
But there was not a big thrill ride.
There was in his dedication of the park mentions like a land of all animals from, you know, lions to dinosaurs to dragons and stuff like men like tips it like previews it.
And then dragons are in the logo too.
Yeah.
It's a very like the Hakuna Matata silhouettes of animals walking in a line and right in the middle is a dragon.
Where's that dragon?
And try to get a dragon out of that boat ride.
And I don't think I forget if it got built or not.
Yeah.
But it's been removed if there ever was one.
But I think it's interesting that there was Camp Mini Mickey.
That was another land, another land that sounds odd.
And that was always meant to be temporary.
They're like, yeah, we're going to put something better here.
And I believe that's where Pandora is now.
We'll do it.
We'll break off.
That'll be the sleepiest second episode.
How many of you have been on the Pandora thing?
Just Mike.
Just me.
OK.
So we don't.
Yeah, we got to we got to build up to that.
We're not qualified.
We can't do that episode yet.
We haven't wept the tears that Mike is wet.
Right.
And but they I have faith that my co-host will Sivako rise to the challenge.
With cushioned insoles to withstand the standing in the line for it.
Even with a fast pass.
Yes, of course.
Let me say this fact that I learned about this dragon roller coaster that was supposed
to be built.
The the synopsis of the plot is very odd to me.
Well, you know, there's the good side of Beastly Kingdom in which you meet a unicorn.
And then there's the bad side, the evil side dominated by Dragon Tower, a ruined castle
home to a greedy fire breathing dragon who hoarded a fabulous treasure in the tower.
So it's a money.
Stealing dragon.
Grubby dragon.
He knows about money and takes money.
But also blatantly the plot of The Hobbit.
Oh, yeah.
This is their way to do like an off brand like without paying the money.
The Tolkien money.
The castle was also inhabited by bats who planned to rob the dragon of his riches.
Got it.
Dragon stole money.
Bats want to steal it back.
That would have been so cute to see little bats with like one little doubloon in their
feet.
Yeah, little Bill.
Little rubies.
One little ruby in its claw.
You the bats were to enlist us, the guests help in their scheme.
And so I think you were going to ride in a bat.
The vehicle was a bat.
I saw a concept art that seems to support this.
So, yeah.
So you are right.
Well, we're us.
You're I'm me.
And I met a bat who wants to rob a dragon who robbed other humans.
Got it.
Great.
Let's go get that money back.
Rob from an animal and give to another animal.
Does the unicorn ever come back?
I don't know.
Bats do.
Are they cutting me in?
Why am I helping the bats?
Oh, the unicorn was a different ride.
Yeah.
You met a unicorn in a maze.
I can't quite talk to you.
Unicorns.
Oh, right.
Through the vibrations.
I heard that on your last episode.
Yeah.
That's very dolphin.
That seems like a very sonar sort of I think.
And I'm creeped out by dolphin sonar.
And thus I'm also creeped out by unicorn vibrations.
When you said when you described that last time, I was like, oh, I don't like this unicorn.
I would have been interested to see what they did, though.
I bet it could have been cool.
Yeah.
There was also supposed to be like a Fantasia kind of boat ride with like animal scenes
from like the same Fantasia segments.
I wonder how much of that was like, oh, Fantasia 2000 did not do well.
So put that one back in the drawer.
People didn't want to do the graduation march as a ride with.
Have you seen that segment?
Is that?
It's Donald Duck is Noah and he's leading all the animals under the boat and it's to
the graduation theme.
And Disney's trying to say, well, you know, that piece existed before.
It's only we recently who have made it the graduation song.
But it actually is a piece that like no, no, no, it's the graduation song.
Well, it makes you feel like why are these these animals are graduating?
We're at an animal graduation.
What do you mean graduation song?
Vitamin C?
Oh, I also was thinking about vitamin C. I don't know.
But as we go on.
Vitamin C, listener of the show, Kia Burton is in the music video for our good friend
is the in the music video for she's in the kids choir.
That is vitamin C Friends Forever music.
That better be in the Twitter bio.
That's such an iconic.
Yeah, that is more.
I'm kind of outing this.
I don't know if she was trying to bury this fact.
Have you ever seen vitamin C in concert?
I haven't.
No, neither.
I don't know where she's at.
I don't know what she's up to.
Good Halloween costume.
Die the hair.
Yep.
Well, now everybody has orange hair.
You know, is that true?
Everyone has.
Brightly colored hair.
Everyone went to Japan.
That's true.
They go hand in hand.
Yeah, I wanted to say real quick.
Did you ride the Beaver Brothers Explorer canoes in Japan?
No.
Well, something I did that you didn't take that grandma.
You skunk weasel cafe.
That's the Rivers of America canoe.
Yes.
It's the pedal.
You should do it.
OK.
What's the deal?
You're in a big giant canoe and no one speaks English and they tell you to row.
And it's just a really fun experience of like not knowing what's going on.
And you get tired.
I mean, you have to really row.
I've done it Disneyland.
Yeah.
It's exhausting.
It's exhausting, but it was really fun.
I had a really fun time.
I see beavers.
I don't think I saw a beaver.
I don't know.
That's just a name.
But it's just the proprietors immersing yourself in a group of people.
And they're not all people from Japan.
I mean, you never know.
You know, it's people from all over the world working together to canoe this boat.
And you have to say the commands.
And it was just really fun.
I don't know.
I liked it.
You learn a word that you all know?
I do.
But I can't remember what it is.
I was going to watch my Instagram archives and like because I was filming part of it
because I was laughing so hard.
I was like, this is so funny.
It's Japanese for rise to the challenge.
Yeah.
I was going to say, Scott, the justification of that Imagineer ago or the animator ago
and like, well, the graduation song was around before we took it for graduations.
That is a leap so big you could only make it on the back of the mighty Akron.
That was where you like.
You did have mighty Akron leap in time.
Yes, I did.
Yeah, I was very pleased with it.
You did.
Yeah.
What else do we have to fit in as the gates close for the now extended hours of Animal
Kingdom?
I've never been to the Yak and Yeti restaurant.
I need to go there.
When you talk about that eventually.
I haven't been to any of the good restaurants.
I'd like to.
People say that's a very good restaurant.
So Tully Canteen also supposed to be very good.
Tully Canteen, very good.
Yes, I can confirm that you can get like a protein bowl or you can get quinoa there.
They have like a lot of options.
You can get quinoa and tofu.
And that's one of their most like progressive quick service Disney World restaurants.
I mean, Disney could be if Disney like gets the Impossible Burger like they have them
in California Adventure.
They do have it now.
OK.
Yeah, it's not Beyond.
It's the Impossible.
Wow, really?
Because the Impossible is a better one.
The Beyond.
It depends.
I'm not mad at a Beyond because I do.
I'll eat a Beyond, but it's Impossible is better to me.
Let's see.
But I think Burger at the Lamplight Lounge.
Oh, so they're up on the trends.
It's still on the nicer.
If Disney could buy in bulk enough to bring the price down, that people would try it.
And so they could like get people on these things a little bit.
I found the Impossible Burger to be more seamlessly fooling of me.
Like that's not the right sentence.
But Fat Burger has it here and I had it and I was like, oh, this is I'll eat a Beyond
Burger, but Impossible really like felt like they got they're close.
It's really good.
Have you all had the Carl's Jr. one yet?
No.
What is that?
I think it's called the Beyond Star famous Beyond Star Burger.
But I've had two of them now and I had never eaten a Carl's Jr. in my life until this week.
OK, so you endorsed that one.
I was inspired to go after the Super Bowl commercials because Hyundai famously took
a jab at vegans in their commercial.
Oh, right.
Of course.
And then Carl's Jr. had a commercial for their new vegetarian burger.
So I said, fuck Hyundai.
I'm going to go buy Carl's Jr. at Burger.
And it's good.
It is OK.
Yeah, I'll try it.
And then we've talked, of course, about Taco Bell being a very good option, especially
with the app.
Yes.
You changed my life with that app.
This is what I want to hear.
You have changed my life with that app.
And I said it when I was on Doughboys.
Yes.
Thank you.
That Taco Bell app, you can grill your friggin seven layer burrito.
It changes the game.
You can modify anything.
And you don't have to wait in the line.
You don't have to be an asshole and say you're out loud.
They just have to sigh inside when they see it.
Exactly.
Oh, God.
Get that Taco Bell app.
And there's also free stuff on there all the time.
Like free drink, free taco.
I'm like, hell yeah.
Sure.
There used to be McDonald's in Animal Kingdom, right?
Yeah.
Which is what?
Which is, yeah.
Which was like, I don't know, it bothered me.
But just the fries?
Remember when they were selling just the fries?
That's right.
That was our...
It was a weird licensing.
Was that called Restorontosaurus?
Was that there McDonald's?
Wasn't there like a...
Now I'm getting confused with the dinosaur sunglasses hot in California Adventure that
was right by the fry stand.
This was a credit time.
I didn't like any of this stuff.
Bad specials, bad TGIFs.
I'm fine with the McDonald's, but I don't know.
It felt invasive in the parks.
They even called it, in California Adventure, they called it Burger Invasion as a little
jab at...
That was the Imagineers way of getting back at this forced McDonald's entry into the
parks.
But yeah, I'm anxious to go back to Animal Kingdom and forgive the late 90s bummer sins
of the...
Yeah, you gotta cleanse.
Right.
Because both of the times I went there in the last decade, I did not go into Animal
Kingdom at all.
I clearly owe it a visit.
You definitely owe it a visit.
I do think it's good that they, kind of in the territory of things that are good about
They don't use plastic straws or plastic lids for fear of it getting in the animals' habitats.
Okay, I like that.
It's the only one of the four parks in Florida that does that.
But they're kind of de facto saying, yeah, this is bad.
Anyway, ignore these other three parks where we do this.
Because there's animals all over those parks.
Yeah, there's birds and cranes and ducks.
There's animals everywhere.
I saw a cat at Tokyo Disney.
What was the cat say?
It was a little kitty just hanging out and we tried to pet him.
Sure.
Probably dangerous.
Wait, let me say this weird fact about, we've been talking about animals at the parks.
One of the things in the corner of Animal Kingdom and their conservation efforts is
that they've significantly raised the population of Guam Kingfisher chicks.
What do those look like?
What are they?
Don't know.
But they were almost on the way out.
And in Animal Kingdom, they are thriving.
So wonderful.
Love that.
Life will find a way.
That's not from The Lion King or any...
Circle of Life.
How about that?
There you go.
Beautiful.
Circle of Life probably played too much in all of the specials and all of the build-up.
I think they maybe overestimated.
I think it's impossible to underestimate how much people love and don't get tired of Let
It Go.
I'm not one of those people.
I got tired of it quickly.
But clearly they have not hit the ceiling on Let It Go.
Circle of Life, they seem convinced.
Like, yeah, we can have full performances of Circle of Life in every special for a decade.
I agree with that.
I could see Circle of Life all day, but I don't give a shit about Frozen.
Did y'all hear about the theory about why they made Frozen?
So people would stop Googling Disney's Frozen head?
So to cover up the conspiracy, they wrote a movie called Disney's Frozen so it would
be found on Google again.
To hide the fact that Disney's head is frozen.
I feel like I could find it on Google right now though.
Well, you have to change the search history to only show articles before Frozen came out.
We'll look into this.
So they also have to make a movie called Commie Hater.
Distributed from Disney being Commie Hater.
Coming Summer 2022.
But it's a Dean movie.
That's just a last name.
It follows William Commie Hater.
By Josh Gad.
Did you hear the rumor that they're changing the name of Disney Plus to Gad Plus?
Because it's all Gad all the time, baby.
I did hear that.
I think that's true.
The biggest brands in the industry right now.
Netflix, Apple, Gad.
Gad.
I have a final question, I think, but it should be the last thing before we exit to the gift
shop.
Does everybody else have anything else?
I'm good to go.
I just really quick want to say because my podcast, NatchBeaut, is all about skincare,
beauty, wellness.
Oh, yeah.
I want to tell everybody that if you are a theme park head, you got to wear sunscreen.
I don't care if it's overcast.
Absolutely.
I don't care if you're at Florida and it's raining.
When I was there, it was raining all the time.
It was very foggy and cute and fun.
You got to sunscreen up every day.
And at night, you got to wash your face.
Wash your face.
Wash off all the pollutants, all the dirt, everything that hits your face, the old sunscreen.
So keep that skin fresh.
Definitely put a moisturizer on at night after a big day at the park.
Very good advice.
I need to do that more.
Specific theme park skincare.
Sometimes I do it, sometimes I get lazy.
Y'all better wear it every time.
Do you sunscreen, Scott?
The last time I was there, even though it was overcast, I got a little bleary and I
think it was because that sun was creeping in there and I wasn't wearing anything.
So I'm thinking, your advice is resonating with me.
Please, everybody, no matter what age you are, everybody, put that sunscreen on before
you hit the lines.
Any recommendations, brand wise?
I mean, you know what?
I'm a bougie bitch.
So I like that Sephora price point.
I'm all about the super goo.
Those are at the parks.
Those are at the sun.
You can get one at Universal City Walk or Disney.
Downtown Disney.
Sephora is there.
Oh yeah, there you go.
Because I don't like, on Attribute, we only do non-animal testing products.
So a lot of the like Neutrogena's and whatnot, they test on animals.
So we're all about kind of the, you got to look at it.
I like Super Goop and Kula, C-O-O-L-A.
They're both at Sephora, Ulta, that kind of price point.
Great, good, high quality ingredients and all kinds of different ones, depending on
what you're looking for.
If you want a mineral, if you want a chemical, if you don't know what the fuck that is, listen
to Attribute, babe.
I'll tell you.
Wow, cool.
That's good specifics.
Yeah, yeah.
Listen to Attribute.
Does it matter when days anymore?
I was going to be like, it comes out every...
Comes out every Friday.
Friday, like us.
Oh my gosh, okay.
We'll just head on over there right now.
The fun day, Friday, you know?
Yeah, that's where the coolest podcasts...
We have crossover fans because tweets were coming in.
Oh yeah, I saw that.
People were excited.
Well, I hope you liked it.
I hope we did it at service and we'll get to Bibbidi Bobbidi Boutique.
I'm down to all try and go, I mean, whenever y'all want.
Oh yeah.
I have fun.
Whenever y'all want.
Oh yeah.
I have questions for you probably off air about my scalp and about my moisturizing routine,
but that's...
We'll do that later.
It's too far.
Listeners, if you're upset that you didn't get to hear this on air, let us know.
Dry?
Very dry.
Yeah.
How often do you wash your hair?
Well, here's the problem is that when people say don't wash your hair a lot, wait a couple
days, it gets worse if I do that.
It gets way worse.
You got to train it.
I've tried.
It's unsustainable.
Yeah, interesting.
I think I almost knocked over his microphone twice.
This is a problem that's been plaguing me for years.
Yeah.
Same.
It's a problem.
It is.
We'll talk about it later.
We'll talk about it.
My final question though is if we had to populate Ringo's All-Star Band with Disney characters,
instrument playing Disney characters, what do we think?
Oh boy.
Sonny Eclipse has got to be in...
Sonny Eclipse is in there.
King Louie is in there.
Some of the Aristocats band who are not racist stereotypes are probably session guys.
Okay.
Is there a bear in there somewhere?
Does he play an instrument?
He does in my head.
Maybe he's just like the Mighty Mighty Bossdones dancer guy.
Yes, the hype man.
He's dancing back and forth.
He can probably play a jug.
Yeah, but there's like a jug.
I was going to just put a country bear in there.
I'm fine with that.
A country bear.
That's fine.
Or is it just the country bears with Ringo in front?
God, I would love that.
It's maybe the cleanest.
Yeah, that works maybe the best.
I would love that so much.
But can Richard Page be there?
He's part of the Disney family.
America!
Ringo and the All-Stars, man, you've got to get Golden Dreams into the sun.
Oh my God.
We would go every time.
And start touring.
Yeah, okay.
Tour with the country bears.
Ringo, again?
Well, I'm having trouble limiting it.
I want Ringo, with his vast wealth, to next time he goes on tour, pay for a Rock of Fire
explosion and a Chucky Make-Believe band and the country bears.
Let's get a Muppet and the Kermit playing the band show.
Oh yeah.
Sunny Eclipse.
On the banjo, Kermit the Frog.
Kermit the Frog.
He could put, Ringo could put Kermit the Frog in the All-Star band and nobody would bat an
eye.
Nobody would say that's weird.
He perfectly fits into the lore of the band.
Absolutely.
Yeah, why not?
Could we get some of the like, under the sea animals in there?
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, the Duke plays the flute.
In the clam.
The Duke playing the flute.
The flute plays the, well, I don't remember.
The crab playing the harp.
Give me a hand and fall, here we go again.
And then of course they have to play octopus's garden when they bring on the undersea.
I'm getting tired.
This is the finale.
Octopus, they all leave, you think it's done, but then my undersea friends.
There they are, flounder and best friend.
A hippo opens its mouth and a bug, a crab, a shrimp.
Getting his teeth.
Yeah.
How do we make this happen?
Well, do we have to make these animals alive?
Do we have to breed these animals or are they all robots?
Is it easier to make Ringo a cartoon?
He's already been a cartoon in various guises.
Sure.
And he's been on Shining Time Station.
So there's Ringo Shrinking technology available.
Maybe the easiest thing, you know, you could take all these robots and you could take them
on a tour with Ringo or you could just make Ringo a permanent part of the under the sea,
Ariel's undersea adventure ride.
Now that is my favorite of all these ideas.
Yeah, Ringo lives in the under the sea right now.
And it's old Ringo, it's 80 year old Ringo.
I think he's in the peace and love position and he's singing.
Is there a scarier song he can sing with Ursula or does he just do a duet?
I admit that in the past I've been a nasty.
Oh boy.
Ringo doing poor unfortunate souls.
Poor unfortunate souls.
If he turned the no no song into like a dirge.
Yeah, sure.
He could put no no song in.
He could scary that up.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't take souls no more.
It kind of sounds like a Ringo song.
Yeah.
In a way.
That was very easy to go into.
Poor unfortunate souls.
And then on Kiss the Girl, Ringo's kind of peering through the bushes with like Sebastian
and Flounder, like making sure that it happens.
You know what?
Kiss the Girl could be a Ringo song.
They're all really, they're all physically makes Disney songs as it is.
Sitting there across the lake.
Short phrasing.
Can't hold a note out to save his life.
Oh God, please is there a cover somewhere of Ringo singing Kiss the Girl or Poor Unfortunate
Souls.
Wilson has covered Kiss the Girl.
He has an entire Disney covers album.
So Ringo, take a cue from your friend Brian Wilson.
Give us what we all want.
How have I not heard that?
That's like, because my husband is a tiki head.
That's like combining two interests once again.
If I'm not into it.
I'm a giant Disney head and a giant Beach Boys head and I don't care.
And you're saying not to listen to it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So that doesn't get the Scott stamp of approval.
But Ringo, please live the rest of your life in the under the sea ride.
Yeah, we're all agreed, including Jackie.
Jackie Johnson, you survived podcast the ride.
Oh, I'm so happy.
Thank you so much for being here.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Well, I think you know, I think I know.
Well, you already plugged a little bit.
When does this come out?
I don't know yet.
We got that.
I'm not sure.
This exists outside of time.
It doesn't matter.
Perfect.
Coming up in March.
Well, I am doing a skincare collab with a company called Lolli Beauty and it's a fully
sustainable organic food grade skincare line and we're doing three products.
So if you like skincare, you can head to the next boot Instagram, my Instagram, Twitter,
listen to an attribute, national.com.
Go anywhere because I'm really excited about their products.
They're all pink.
Pink is my favorite color.
It's called the Nashville pink collection.
So it's available now.
So check it out and listen to this.
Wow.
Great.
You folks, check us out at patreon.com slash podcast.
Right for this second gate full of even more magical content and I'm sure more Ringo bullshit.
Yes.
That's so tricky.
I was worried there wouldn't be more of me.
Check us out on Twitter and Instagram and there's a Facebook group and I don't, Facebook
and Reddit are sort of separate from us, but where they're existing and happening and I'm
glad they are and they're nice places.
Check them out.
Yeah.
People seem nice.
We, Jason and I actually approve people for this Facebook group.
I don't know.
Is that right?
Yeah, that is.
Yeah, because there's the Facebook.
Bots will get you if you don't do that.
Yeah.
We fortunately avoided that.
It is our group.
Well, it is our group.
Oh yeah.
The group we set up.
It's more active than I am though.
I take a look at it.
I take a look at it a little while.
Administering Facebook groups is confusing and not very clear.
The actual software is odd.
That's why the election went the way it did.
Yes.
But the people are nice.
Everyone's nice in the group.
Yeah, everyone's nice.
It's great.
Everyone's nice.
Keep being nice out there.
We will catch you on the next podcast ride.
Peace and love.
No more autographs.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe
Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram, at
and liking our page on Facebook.
Hey there.
Congratulations.
You made it all the way through that episode.
Wow.
We did not think you were going to be able to do it.
We barely could.
It was touch and go.
Yeah.
Anyway, now that you did, Michael and I have a pretty cool surprise for you.
We are going to get high.
What?
Come on.
What are you talking about?
Let's light up that joint, baby.
No, Colin.
Without listeners.
That is not what we do.
Litterandi is a pretty cool thing.
We're going to get high.
What?
Come on.
What are you talking about?
That is not what we do.
Litterandi is a podcast about books.
It is not about getting stoned.
I thought we had a special treat for you.
You do not even smoke weed.
You freak out and get paranoid.
I thought we had a special treat or surprise for the listeners who made it to the end of
the episode.
Yeah.
We are going to play them a clip from our show.
How would we get everybody high?
That does not even make sense.
Honestly, I do not really listen to podcasts.
I did not know.
That is true.
I am guessing they had the technology to do that.
No, they do not.
That is such a weird...
Colin, we are not going to get anybody high.
We are not getting high.
Okay.
I actually think that you should not be promoting that on this podcast.
Yeah.
Okay.
Fine.
But if you want to get high at home, sure do it, but we are not promoting it.
Neither here nor there.
We are going to play a clip from our podcast with Josh Sharpe.
Just listen and enjoy that.
And get high.
What?
With that in mind, we would like to take the pressure off of us for a second and introduce
you to the reader of today.
He is a recent NYU dropout.
And we know that means a recipe for success.
Oh, yes, indeed.
Dropping out of school and into our hearts, we have young novelist and self-proclaimed
genius Clint Dimples for you.
Enjoy.
Hello, my name is Clint Dimples.
And this is a piece of short literature that I call The Story.
There was once a girl with deep brown hair who lived with her grandfather in a small
cabin upstate.
Though her parents, who had been professors, died eight months before in an automobile
accident while returning from an academic conference on the viability of the universal
basic income, the girl was of a happy sort, her optimism only fading to melancholia on
nights such as these when the rain shuddering at the windows made her wish for her mother's
arms.
The story goes that the grandfather, a wiry man with a great beak of a nose, had just
climbed the old stairs to her attic bedroom when he heard her quiet sniffles.
Is everything all right?
He asked the girl.
I'm just having trouble sleeping.
She said it's hard sometimes.
Yes, I know, said the grandfather.
Maybe a story would help?
The little girl nodded, and so the old man began.
There once was a girl with deep brown hair who lived with her grandfather in a small
cabin upstate.
Though her parents, who had been professors, died eight months before in an automobile
accident while returning from an academic conference on the viability of the universal
basic income, the girl was of a mostly happy sort, her optimism only fading to melancholia
on nights such as these when the rain shuddering at the windows made her wish for her mother's
arms.
Her grandfather, a wiry man with a great beak of a nose, had just climbed the old stairs
to her attic bedroom when he heard her quiet sniffles.
Is everything all right?
He asked the girl.
I'm just having trouble sleeping.
She said it's hard sometimes.
Yes, I know, said the grandfather.
Maybe a story would help?
The little girl nodded, and so the old man began.
There once was a girl with deep brown hair who lived with her grandfather in a small
cabin upstate.
Though her parents, who had invented the soda stream, were murdered eight months before
while leaving a Papa John's pizza in Bridgeport, Connecticut, the girl was of a mostly happy
sort, her optimism only fading to melancholia on nights such as these when the rain shuddering
at the windows made her wish for her mother's arms.
Her grandfather, a wiry man with a great beak of a nose, had just climbed the old stairs
to her attic bedroom when he heard her quiet sniffles.
Is everything all right?
He asked the girl.
I'm just having trouble sleeping.
She said it's hard sometimes.
Yes, I know, said the grandfather.
Maybe a story would help?
The little girl nodded, and so the old man began.
There was once a girl with deep brown hair who lived with her grandfather in a small
cabin upstate.
Though her parents, who had been professors, died eight months before in an automobile
accident while returning from an academic conference on the viability of the universal
basic income, the girl was of a mostly happy sort, her optimism only fading to melancholia
on nights such as these when the rain shuddering at the windows made her wish for her mother's
arms.
Her grandfather, a wiry man with a great beak of a nose, had just climbed the old stairs
to her attic bedroom when he heard her quiet sniffles.
Is everything all right?
He asked the girl.
I'm just having trouble sleeping.
She said it's hard sometimes.
I know how that is, said the grandfather, with the trouble sleeping.
Is that why you sleep on the roof?
The little girl asked.
Yes, that's why.
That's why I sleep on the roof.
I see, she said.
And no other reason, he yelled.
Okay, cool, fine, said the girl.
Will you tell me a story?
Hmm?
Said the old man.
A story.
Oh, yeah, sure, right, story, yeah.
Oh, I can do that.
And so the old man began.
There once was a girl with deep brown hair who lived with her grandfather in a small cabin
upstate.
Though her parents, who had been professors, died eight months before in an automobile
accident while returning from an academic conference on the viability of the universal
basic income, the girl was of a mostly happy sort, her optimism only fading to melancholia
on nights such as these when the rain shuddering at the windows made her wish for her mother's
arms.
Her grandfather, a wiry man with a great beak of a nose, had just climbed the old stairs
to her attic bedroom when he heard her quiet sniffles.
She said it's hard sometimes.
Yes, I know, he said, scratching at his big fucking beak nose.
Maybe a story would help?
Sure, Grandpapa, but what's happening to you?
Whatever do you mean?
He asked.
Your nose!
It's turned into a beak like that of a bird!
And sure enough it had, the nose, ossified into a large yellow beak.
Squawk, said the Grandfather, Squawk, Squawk!
As feathers, deep blue and red feathers, began to shoot out of his back.
Squawk, he said, Squawk!
Why Grandfather, the little girl cried, you're turning into a bird!
A real fucking bird with a giant fucking beak!
It's amazing!
His feet now claws.
He reached over and stood atop the girl's wrists.
Then he flapped and flapped until he started to rise.
Over the bed, clutching the small girl beneath him.
His great wings swatting at the walls, he tilted his feathered crown forward and burst,
beak first, out of the large attic window.
The girl hung below him as they made their way up, higher and higher, until the house
was but a speck below them.
She looked up.
Thank you, Grandpapa.
Thank you.
Thank you for transforming into a big fucking bird and taking flight.
And then the old man let forth a mighty Squawk, spread his wings wide, and the two soared
off into the warm night air, floating and finally free.
The End.
What a lovely story, said the little girl.
But I must ask, was the grandpa in that story, the one who turned into a bird, was he supposed
to be you?
Me?
The old man replied, whatever you mean.
I mean, said the little girl, that maybe it is you who wants to be a bird?
I'm asking in part because I know you like to sleep on the roof.
I told you about that already.
I just do that because I like it.
No other reason, he shouted.
Well, sure, said the girl, but the way in which you chew my food up for me and our winter
trips down south, it just all makes me think that maybe you want to be a bird for some
reason, which, to be honest, is sort of a ridiculous notion given that you're a grown
man.
And so if you actually want to be a bird, well, I don't know, maybe you're just crazy.
OK, story time is over, said the old man.
I'm turning off the lights now.
It's time for bed.
He pulled the chain on the lamp and all was still.
I know you have to use the ladder in my room to climb onto the roof, Grandpa, said the
little girl.
So you can turn the lights back on and get it if you want.
OK, I'll turn them on just because I want to turn them on.
How about that, said the old man, fumbling for the chain.
There we go.
They're on.
The lights are on.
Oh, and look, it's the ladder I need to get on the roof.
You know, I better go up there to check on some of the tiles and the roofing and other
things.
Not to sleep, just to, you know, check it out.
I just you won't mind turning the lights off once I'm up there, you know, just in case
I take a while.
No, Grandpa, of course not.
All right, he said.
Here I go up the ladder to check on the tiles.
Night and night, I'm almost to the top.
Shutting the hatch behind him, the old man sat down on the roof, pulled his knees to
his chest, then looked up to the sky and quietly sobbed.
A pigeon landed on his shoulder and the man gently scooped the bird in his palms and pulled
it close.
Not today, he whispered, snot running down his face.
Maybe someday, but not today.
The end.
What a sad story, said the little girl.
I feel sad for the man in that story who told that other story, the man who wanted to be
a bird.
Yes, the old man replied.
But sometimes it is the sad stories that give us comfort, that remind us of how lucky we
are to have what we have.
Your parents left you with a great fortune and you should take solace in that.
She nodded.
Yes, but I still miss Mom and Pop.
She paused.
Grandpa, do you think they'll ever find who murdered my parents in front of that Papa
John's Pizza in Bridgeport, Connecticut?
The grandfather thought for a moment.
No, I'm almost certain they will not.
He drew in a labored breath.
I was very careful.
The girl looked up at him.
You were what?
I said I was careful.
He stood up over her bed.
And what's more, I'm not like the old man in that story, pretending to be something
he's not.
At the time, you know who I really am, little girl.
I murdered your parents outside of that Papa John's Pizza in Bridgeport, Connecticut.
The girl pulled back towards the wall.
You what?
Why would you do that?
Because I wanted that SodaStream money.
And with them gone, now only you stand in my way.
In one quick motion, he removed the knife from his sleeve and plunged it into the little
girl's chest.
He pulled her close to his face and whispered, Let me hear you squawk before you fly away,
little bird.
Let me hear you squawk.
Stop, stop, stop!
The little girl shouted.
I don't like it when the stories turn scary.
I'm sorry if I gave you a fright, said the old man, catching himself.
I just thought a little adventure story might take your mind off things.
Yes, but a story about a man who tells a story of some other man who lies in yet another
story as a way of revealing that he's murdered a little girl's parents when I'm here sad
about my parents?
What are you thinking, you old kook?
And what was all that bird stuff?
You're right, you're right, the old man replied, standing up from bed.
I guess I just got away from myself.
He backed out of the room.
Good night, it won't happen again.
He opened the bedroom door and tumbled into the dark, empty vacuum of space.
The house fell away from him and he slowly drifted, naked now to his boxer shorts, earth
far off in the distance.
A chorus of male voices, hundreds of them, came at him from every direction.
You've done well, my good and favored son.
Squawk, know that you are good and strong and that your cock is mighty and powerful.
Squawk.
And as he crossed into the black hole, his every atom splitting into more energy than
powers our son.
His frozen form on the event horizon, trapped for eternity, was that of a man, arms spread
wide and reaching for something greater.
The end.
I don't get it, said the little girl.
Come to think of it, said the old man, me either.
He gave her a kiss on the head.
A nightingale landed on the windowsill.
He pulled out an old Luger he'd stolen from a Nazi during the war and then he shot the
bird dead.
The end.