Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast is an exciting showcase
of many innovative products that will soon be available
in your home.
From the Apple Newton to Earthworm Gym 2
to an Encyclopedia Britannica on your computer?
Yes, it's a great big world of interventions
made possible by Compaq Computers,
Kaiser Permanente, Marotta Electronic Components,
and presenting sponsor Jenny Nicholson,
only on Podcast The Ride.
The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast
hosted by three men who are all corporately sponsored.
My name is Mike Carlson.
I'm sponsored by Sycamore Partners, owner of Hot Topic.
I'm joined by Jason Sheridan.
I'm sponsored by the Darden Restaurant Group,
who own fine establishments like Olive Garden
and Red Lobster.
I'm also, of course, our co-host Scott Gierdner here.
And I'm sponsored by the Fest Parker Winery,
of which I am a proud member.
I'm looking forward to receiving my first mail shipment,
the first one I got, of course, when I went up there
in person to Santa Ana's, but I'm looking forward
to some nice summer varietals.
That's great.
And we're all wearing clothing that we
were given to, given by the corporation.
Like Brock Lesnar wears Jimmy John shorts
when he's wrestling.
That's just how we do it.
I'm wearing wine is my favorite salad socks, of course,
as always.
I am wearing Jimmy John shorts.
I'm also sponsored by Jimmy John.
Fair enough.
Let's just bring the guest in.
Let's find out who she is sponsored by.
Folks, you know her from her YouTube channel
that has her name.
It's Jenny Nicholson, friend of podcast The Ride.
She's back.
Hello, I'm back.
And I'm sponsored by Rainforest Cafe.
We're going to make a comeback.
It's going to be fun.
They can pull it out.
Yeah, yeah.
They got a couple of tent poles.
Do they come back at downtown Disney, though,
or is that ship sailed?
No, they haven't yet.
But do you think they could?
Do you think they'll pull in a roll up sandwich?
I mean, where else are they going to go?
I think carbon taxes.
Everyone's like, oh, carbon taxes,
that's going to help offset environmental damage.
I think the carbon taxes are going to help bring back
the Rainforest Cafe.
I don't know about the actual rainforest.
I think the time is right for T-Rex to come in there.
T-Rex Cafe.
Take advantage of the closure and bring in T-Rex this time.
Oh, sure.
Yeah.
When has the West Coast had a T-Rex?
That is their other very similar restaurant?
Yeah, it's where it's dinosaurs instead.
Have you been?
I have.
Oh.
The one in Florida.
Most times I've been to Florida.
Really?
Oh, really?
You make a bone of it.
The menu is the same, but everything
has dinosaur pun names.
None of it's good.
But there are dinosaurs all throughout.
And they are owned by the Landry Restaurant Group, who
I have a very checkered history with.
Oh, yeah.
Who also owns Bubba Gum Shrimp.
Yeah, there was a Point Snafu and City Walk Saga.
When Jason, we were at Bubba Gum Shrimp,
and Jason wanted to collect points from our check
for his father's Landry's account.
And when the waiter came back, he brought it.
And he said, oh, you had a $25 credit on there.
I just applied it to the bill.
No.
And Jason's face went white.
They can't do that without your permission.
Well, it apparently happens automatically at Landry's.
Just like all the City Walk happy hours immediately
shut down at 6 o'clock because the computers make it do that.
His father worked hard year after year for those points.
And then he just took them out from under him.
They would have been worth more if you had saved them.
Yeah.
So what a nice way to give back to your father.
That's the millennial version of buying your parents a home
is paying them restaurant points.
Sure.
Yeah, that's the best we can do.
At the T-Rex restaurant, were the dinosaurs cool at least?
Did they have?
No?
OK.
In my opinion, a mediocre dinosaur animatronic
looks much better than a mediocre elephant animatronic
because I've never seen a dinosaur.
So to me, I'm like, oh, yeah, sure.
That's what it looks like.
So your recommendation is just go for the drinks at T-Rex,
maybe not the meal.
No, because then you're just in the bar section.
You want to be sitting among the dinosaurs.
Or maybe the ice caves, which is also a section.
That's cool.
My experience was always stick to the apps
because the entrees were never that great.
The apps were usually reliable.
Yeah, you can get like three apps
and share them with your one other friend,
and then you're good.
Perfect.
When Dick Van Dyke was in the parade at Disneyland
and I went down alone, to validate parking,
I got a cheeseburger to go at the bar.
At Rainforest Cafe.
At Rainforest Cafe at Downtown Disney.
I didn't know they offered to go.
That seems counter to their entire mission statement
of providing a rainforest experience.
Yeah, it doesn't make sense because why would you
go if you're not going to get to enjoy the sights?
No, certainly not for the food.
I ate the food on the five,
and it was maybe the worst cheeseburger I ever had
or had had in 10 years maybe.
How it was so bad.
No, you could even get like a French onion soup
and be like, oh, this is a bad French onion soup.
I didn't know there was such a thing.
Right, they can screw up the easiest dish,
the most idiot proof dish.
Bad bread.
My friends Tyler and Kia, listeners to the show,
just went to Disney World for the first time together
and their trip report that I got from them,
they brought up the T-Rex Cafe, which they went into,
smelled the smell, and turned around immediately.
I might be misquoting them,
but I believe what they said was that it smelled
like airplane Salisbury steak
and 100 children all at once.
That's fair.
You get your food and it's lukewarm,
but you waited 40 minutes for it.
It's like that vibe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where food lands when it's not fresh.
You're looking at T-Rex.
You're looking at an Iguanodon.
Which they got to do all of that stuff.
So if that's what you're going, so maybe my,
I haven't been there myself,
but maybe my T-Rex Cafe tip is walk in, walk out immediately.
But then you don't see all the dinosaurs.
But maybe you go in, pretend that you're looking
for a family.
A family where you drop something.
My mistake, they're not eating at the place
with the dinosaurs.
I don't know how they communicated that wrong.
I'm sorry, they appear to be in the hot air balloon.
Well, as you were.
Well, I don't know if you guys are Rainforest Cafe fans,
but they have a jungle storm that makes all the animals
go crazy every half hour or so.
At T-Rex, it's a little darker.
It's a meteor shower.
So all the dinosaurs start screaming for their lives
and you see little meteors on the ceiling.
It's great.
I mean, so they're reliving the extinction over and over
again?
Yeah, they're caught in a loop.
Oh my God, that's a hell for them.
It's the restaurant at the end of the Cretaceous period.
Some future race will be doing that with us
at the Human Cafe.
Oh yeah.
They'll be fondly recalling our extinction.
The animatronics of Abraham Lincoln,
they don't understand how time works.
They think Abraham Lincoln was next to Genghis Khan,
was next to Christian Bale.
When the asteroids start falling, he goes,
four score and seven years ago.
And everyone just says their thing.
Everyone's famous phrase were their dying words
in the meteor shower.
Aerosmith is there.
They only know what they've gleaned from the parks
as far as his significance in history.
Nixon was the base player of Aerosmith.
Heavily stylized Tim Allen is there.
It does feel like they could, like how Pleasure Island
was like, you can ring in the new year every night.
This should be called the Extinction Restaurant
and you can relive it.
I thought you were gonna say all of downtown Disney
should be the end of the world every night,
which would be great.
Honestly, that's not a bad idea either.
It's even better than New Year.
I think there's at least two,
two Quarry Doctorow sci-fi novels that take place,
like end of the world in the theme parks.
Okay.
Yeah, I feel like that is a real,
I read his one book, Down and Out in the Magic Kingdom,
about people competing whether to plus up
or keep the haunted mansion as it is
a thousand years in the future or something.
Really?
Yeah, this is real.
That's some nerve shit. And you can read it for free
under creative comments license
because he puts out all this stuff for free.
I'm just talking about a Joe Roady supervised experience
where we get to live the end of the world
over and over and over again.
That's what I'm looking for that would tie into C.
But it's sanitized, it's not like,
because in a real end of the world scenario,
people are robbing each other and hurting each other.
And this one, it brings people closer.
The improv actors are weeping and hugging each other
at the end of the night.
It might be like a-
The old women tucking their kids in like a Titanic.
They're all wearing different religious garbs
to demonstrate that they've come
from different walks of life,
but now they're brought together by this tragedy.
Oh yeah.
It would probably be cathartic, honestly.
Yeah, and the whole audience is just drunk off their minds.
They're like, yeah.
And then you get out and you're like, I'm alive.
And now I have the rest of my life in front of me.
All the bachelorette parties there are living it up.
And then they all feel good about getting married
and they're like, you know what, it's great.
Ryan's a great guy.
And they're like, everything's gonna be fine.
The perspective from that fake apocalypse
really taught me something.
Yeah, I mean, this is really a good-
The motto of T-Rex Cafe is Ryan is a great guy.
I mean, I guess you can tie that all together, yes?
Yeah.
So we're gonna talk eventually about Innoventions
if we have to, I guess.
Yeah.
Oh, let's get into it.
Let's talk Innoventions.
Let's just get right to it.
We all are just chomping at the bit.
Thrumping like T-Rexes.
Talking about it, everyone is.
I, like, if you're listening to this,
you probably know what Innoventions is,
but just the primer, you go into Epcot Center
before you get to, well, just past, I guess,
Spaceship Earth.
You go left or you go right, and either way,
there's Innoventions waiting for you,
and it's where you go experience all the products
that are coming down the pike.
And in Disneyland, it was the thing in the Circle Theater
that now is where you go meet Kylo Ren or whatever.
And I'm gonna be totally honest with you,
I didn't realize until I started researching this
that it had closed, that we don't consider
what's there now, Innoventions.
No, they took the sign down.
It's gone. Okay.
I didn't know that.
It has apparently been renamed at some point
the Tomorrowland Expo Center.
Yes. Didn't know that.
With Star Wars Launch Bay on the bottom.
As many names you can give any building.
As many names.
And shut down attractions without making it clear to me,
a theme park nerd podcast host, that it was closed at all.
Yeah, kind of like the wonders of life
being called the Festival Center,
it's always a great sign when a building is named
a building first and then what's in it second.
You know you're gonna get a great attraction.
Like if Splash Mountain was in Pavilion Building West,
presents Splash Mountain, you'd be like, hmm, okay.
Featuring Splash Mountain,
presented by Fidelity Insurance.
Yeah.
I feel like we're getting a little ahead of ourselves
and if, because first off, we need to explain that
Innoventions is the combination of inventions and innovation.
Yeah.
A robot told me that.
A robot told me his name was Michael Eisner,
he was the head of the company.
Look, you could see a whole making of,
preview of Innoventions in Epcot from like 94, 93.
That we, do you guys both watch this?
Jenny, have you ever seen this before?
No, I haven't seen that.
It's on YouTube and it is really something.
Oh my God.
Everyone who speaks in it
seems like they're doing so at gunpoint.
Every vice president of marketing,
every senior vice president of executive outreach.
It is just dull person after dull person.
And which I guess, I don't know, like what happened?
Why did Michael Eisner think this was a good idea?
I think his idea was, we've gotta pimp up.
Either Epcot or New Tomorrowland.
We have that whole building and we ran out of money.
What can we do not only for free, but for negative dollars?
Where we will pay us to put things in our park.
So I think that was the driving innovation behind it.
Real innovation.
I mean, what was there before was called CommuniCorps.
And it was about communication stuff.
I don't understand the Epcot logic.
I understand the Disneyland logic where they had a building
and they had emptied out.
But at Epcot, why get rid of CommuniCorps?
Yeah, CommuniCorps looked, I watched the Bright Sun films
like walk through about CommuniCorps.
And the little smart one robot.
Love smart one to little robot.
Smart one, yeah.
Smarty, smarty one.
They had, they seemed to start something called
the Person of the Century award
that I'm not sure if they ever finished it.
Like around 1990, CommuniCorps was where you could go
to vote for Person of the Century.
I don't know where or how or any details.
We'll get to it in the CommuniCorps episode.
But I don't know, I don't think they settled it.
Because by 2000, it had long been in interventions.
And interventions no longer cared
who was the person of the century.
Maybe they just mailed a plaque to whoever won by that point.
They tallied up the existing votes.
They were like, okay.
A couple of coupons.
Marie Callender's gift certificate.
They had a contractual obligation to announce a winner.
They just had to put it in like a local newspaper
in a bottom corner.
Technically it was published.
No, no, no.
It's in the Sentinel.
It's in the Orlando Sentinel.
Yeah.
But you could, and there was a census.
There was a constantly updating census thing
of how many people lived in the country.
There was also, this looked really cool.
You could look into the behind the scenes room
with all the computers that controlled Epcot.
Ooh.
I think CommuniCorps was also where you had to go
to make lunch and dinner reservations.
You would pick up a phone there.
Wow.
I didn't know that.
I forget.
That's a whole thing.
I gotta look more into that.
When that was a novel,
I guess phone reservations weren't novel.
But there was something,
or was it like a computer touch screen or something?
I think it was kind of, yeah.
It was combining Future World and World Showcase.
Even though it is a dated concept now,
it would feel more futuristic
if you were told, proceed to the CommuniCorps
to book your dining reservation.
Even though you have to walk there,
it would feel more high tech.
Yeah.
And the aesthetic has aged a lot better.
The CommuniCorps aesthetic looks a lot better
than any of the Innoventions stuff.
Innoventions, I only got to go once
before they got rid of the rest of it.
It was already mostly gone.
But it looked very today.
I didn't even realize initially
that I was in Innoventions.
Oh.
You at Disneyland are speaking specifically?
No, at Epcot.
Oh, at Epcot.
Yeah, it was just a lot of modern stuff.
And I did experience two things that are now gone
also, so I'm glad I got to see
these Yesterworld attractions.
But I went on three things actually.
One of them was an experience
about how to tornado proof your home.
Yes, that was a weather simulator.
Yeah, but it was like a game show.
You would vote for which one you wanted to win
that you thought would withstand the storm.
Yeah.
We were only with two other families,
so we were trying to throw the vote
and make the house vulnerable.
And it worked.
We got to see the roof lift off, the simulation.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
And then we did something called Fitness Heroes
that I think was Marvel themed.
It might not have been.
And it was like a Kinect game.
And you had to do different exercise moves
to save a city from, I wanna save pollution.
Exercise moves?
And there was one other child in the room.
Just one very small child, their parents,
and me and my friend.
So that was good energy.
What did the competition consist of exactly?
You were just in place punching and raising your arms
and things or doing kicks.
And then it would detect that you were doing that
with PlayStation Connect type technology.
And then you would see a bar going, it's working.
And then you'd save the city.
And they would come in and they'd teach you some chants
about fitness and be like, no, you're all Fitness Heroes.
And the third thing was an actual good thing.
And it was called the Sum of All Thrills.
And it's where you programmed your own roller coaster.
And they would try to give you a physics lesson
about how not to build a dangerous roller coaster.
And we did the opposite of all their advice
because we wanted a thrilling simulation.
And it gives you a number score at the end
of how your simulation came out, a thrill level.
And I told it to the person that was putting our result
in the machine and they said, oh, that's 10 points away
from breaking the simulation.
We named it a wild snake and it was a masterpiece.
It was wild.
Was it fun to go on the simulation though?
It was.
And they would tell you as they're telling you
how to design your roller coaster,
they have a green zone of like,
don't make your hill steeper than this if you can.
And so we'd put it all the way up and they'd be like,
don't make your loop a perfect circle
because it's bad for the human body.
Like the inertia from it is dangerous.
So we just made it as round as possible.
It's good.
It's not a real coaster.
It's gonna be fine.
Yeah.
Okay, so this is very, that closed a few years ago.
And it was one of the newer things to open.
I have all the Sum of All Thrills stuff.
But I tried, okay.
So Sum of All Thrills, when I was there in 2014,
I tried to go on it.
I was very surprised.
I didn't really know it was there.
And I was like, this actually looks cool
because you've designed the coaster
and then you ride the coaster.
It was great.
The line was really long.
Yes, the line is really long
because there was only two capsules on
and they were on KUKA arms.
It takes forever to load you in
and strap you in and make it safe.
Yes.
Yeah.
And it's only like two people per vehicle.
So yeah, when it had a weight, it was very long weight.
So I watched a video of the ride through.
And so here's the thing I didn't know
about the Sum of All Thrills.
I knew it had a long weight
because it didn't have very high per hour capacity.
Very quickly, you learned that the sponsor
of this attraction is Raytheon, the weapons company.
The company who makes-
Are you serious?
Yes.
And they say it in, they say like, the line is,
this is part of Raytheon's commitment
to help inspire a new generation
of technologists and innovators.
Oh no.
So it's all about STEM and mathematics, but is,
and I've made this joke on the show before
and I've heard it on other, of like, yeah,
it's sponsored by like North Rep Gunnum or Raytheon,
these companies that make missiles.
But I didn't know this actually happened.
This was sponsored by Raytheon as a way to like, also like,
and it's about STEM.
I think, I'm sure they got a massive tax write-off
or something for it because it's about-
Because it's for teaching children.
Because it's about teaching children.
It's a service.
And like, you can do this too.
And maybe one day you can work for Raytheon,
the missile company.
And like, maybe this is naive,
but it can't have cost that much as an attraction.
It didn't take up a lot of space.
They had to buy the two KUKA arms, but that's it.
Which KUKA arms are not made by,
they're made by the KUKA company,
KUKA Rebatter GmbH of Germany.
But yeah, Raytheon also most recently mentioned
when Donald Trump launched a bunch of missiles
at an empty Syrian airfield,
those were shown to be Raytheon missiles.
They came out of the good press
of still having their ride-in interventions in that case.
It's a shame they closed it before that.
Yeah, if you could program the arm to swing you around
to set the exact trajectory of the missiles
on the bottom of the warehouse.
That should have been the third option,
because you could choose coaster or plane
before you designed your thing.
They should have had missiles as a third one.
Drone.
Is that the same,
was it different than the Disney Quest
build your own coaster?
Yes, so that was called Cyberspace Mountain,
and that was just a thing.
But CommuniCorps also had a design your own coaster.
So there was a history of design your own coaster
in this space, and that was very wire-framy.
That looked cool, you only had a few selections.
It kind of looked like,
have you ever played the Tron video game?
Or like the old, old arcade one,
or the Empire Strikes Back old arcade game
when it was very like, oh cool, it's in 3D,
but everything is wire-framed.
Sure, sort of the virtual boy a little bit too.
Oh yeah, yeah, wire-framing.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, some of all thrills lasted from 2009 to 2016.
Wow.
The entire Obama administration.
Pretty much.
You could go to Disney World
and watch a weapons company demonstration.
We have been sponsored in company.
Luckily there was no tie-in comic
like there was with Exxon,
where Mickey and Donald and Goofy were,
like Mickey was telling them about how good the company is.
This is the Patreon too,
it's much more tactically advanced than the Patreon,
not Patreon, Patriot.
Patriot missiles.
Jason is our Patreon always on the brain.
They make the Patriot missile system.
I see.
Gorsh, who makes the drones, Nick?
Yeah, so they were gone,
and the last two holding on clients,
Innovations West closed in 2015,
and is mostly the Epcot character spot now.
Oh, that's where you, yeah, my friends are just there
and they said that's where you meet Bigger Asick.
That's where I met Minnie.
I mean, ran into Minnie again.
Wow.
It was very fresh.
Minnie, yeah, well, every Minnie in Orlando kisses me.
And the performer inside the suit makes a mwah noise
when they press their big snout up
against the side of my face.
But what I, I think next time you get kissed by Minnie,
and it will be soon,
you need to survey the next 10 men in line
and ask if that happened to them too.
Okay.
Because if they didn't get a smooch,
then you know it's a thing.
Then I know it's a thing.
Yeah, it's a good point.
I did, we were at Disneyland like a week ago,
and Minnie walked by and she was on her way somewhere.
So she was busy, but she just waved at me, so she didn't.
I have like a couple pictures of it,
and they're great photos,
but she was clearly trying to get somewhere
and didn't need, she didn't have time to stop.
But you also, you have no idea,
you were far away from her,
not within the range where you could have heard
the smooch sound.
So you're very welcome to get one.
She blew me a kiss.
Oh, I see.
I was so impressed.
I met Goofy a couple weeks ago,
and I know they sometimes make kissing sounds,
they can't vocalize,
but this Goofy was making like guttural Goofy voice noises.
Like he would nod his head and go like,
ooh, ooh, ooh, like a Goofy voice.
And it sounded on the money,
and I was just like, this is incredible,
but it also was weird because they weren't words.
They were just like weird guttural vocalizations
that Goofy would make.
And you know that Goofy can speak.
Goofy is not a minion.
They don't like him to speak when he's in Disneyland.
Oh yes, sure, sure.
They don't know what he'll say.
Right.
He's not allowed to speak on behalf of the company.
It's a legality concern.
He'll talk about drones or something.
Yeah.
I think he might start expressing his political opinion.
Do like a Tim Allen or a James Wood.
They don't need that.
Yeah.
Don't drink the tap water.
There's fluoride in it, gush.
Yeah.
Where was Goofy talking?
Which part of the Disneyland?
It was Goofy's kitchen.
My family was visiting.
I had not visited Goofy's kitchen in probably like years.
In the Disneyland hotel?
Maybe they put their A Goofy at Goofy's kitchen.
Yeah, the one at the Disneyland hotel
in the little festival center.
That's a good question.
Convention center, I guess.
That's actually a good question
because you worked at Disneyland very famously.
Yes.
And I wanted to let people that knew that
feel like they knew it already,
but then let the new listeners know.
As if no one knows.
So famously seemed like it made the most sense to me.
Were there, was there a hierarchy of Disney performance?
Have we talked about this ever?
Was there an A Goofy, A Mickey,
and they would be brought out at the...
I feel like I didn't interact enough with characters.
There actually was kind of a rivalry
between guest relations and characters.
I think because they were the two departments
with the biggest egos.
So the characters want to be like,
everyone knows we have the coolest job
and then guest relations is the same way.
So if you would ever interact with characters department,
there would be kind of a tension there.
But I think with characters,
the main hierarchy was like face characters
versus fur characters.
So like the princesses versus Mickey and friends.
Faces be furs.
Yeah, so I think that's the main hierarchy.
But I do know that people would get scheduled more often
based on their performance.
Like there were princesses who were not there all the time.
And there were princesses who were always in the parades,
always doing everything.
Some would never get approved for parades.
So I would imagine there was some ego going on there.
But I don't know, with the fur characters,
I always felt like they were the chill ones.
Like I feel like the face characters are like the LA people
and the fur characters are the theater kids,
if that makes sense.
I get what you're saying.
Yeah, personality wise.
So I feel like maybe within the fur characters,
there's less rivalry.
They're all just there to have a good time.
Okay, interesting.
There's kind of a union.
They're more like good old boys.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They don't have the egos from like the improv skills.
Although there's physical improv skills, certainly.
There's been many great improv moments.
I feel like when Robin Hood,
I had his target on my shirt, remember that?
And Robin Hood like pointed right at it
and they did a whole bit.
He shot an arrow into your chest.
Yeah, that was the bit they were pretending to kill me.
Yeah, good.
It was great.
They loved that.
And when Minnie improvised reaching down your pants.
Sure.
Oh, nice.
In front of all those children, yes.
Inappropriate, Minnie.
I actually do wonder also like who,
when there's a high profile Mickey appearance,
like when here Mickey is gonna cut the ribbon
of Euro Disneyland or is gonna like.
Or the princesses who do the televised coronation events
and things, I think it goes by seniority.
And I think it definitely is something they think about
of like who they consider their best one.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, that's interesting, huh?
You see, you already.
Probably the ones that are signed off on the most areas.
Like for Mickey's and stuff,
you would want a Mickey that does phantasmic
because I feel like that's the hardest Mickey role.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cause you're like, I was watching a video
that phantasmic mishaps that explain all of the like.
Right. Stop gap.
Like if, and the Mickey has to know
if this thing didn't happen,
you have like a backup procedure and choreography.
Yeah, and he has a lot of precise marks.
There's a lot to remember.
Okay, so maybe a phantasmic Mickey is the one you want.
Or the one signed off in the most areas at least.
I see, okay, okay.
Cause every different show or location,
well not location for meet and greets,
but every different parade and show and everything
are different sign-offs.
And I think some people just know all of them.
Hmm, hmm, wow.
The Mickey that's gonna help open Galaxy's Edge,
they're going to let the ravenous first people in line
eat him.
Yeah.
Eat him to try and pacify.
So now I can send their top Mickey in that case.
That'll be the Mickey that started last weekend.
Right. Maybe, maybe.
Wow, what an honor, out of the gate.
They actually hold separate auditions
to see who the most vulnerable one is.
Right, the most expendable Mickey.
This is the way I want to go.
But the crowds might know, the crowds might know,
and get angrier.
They know it's a lesser Mickey.
That they're feasting on.
There's gonna be, yeah, they're gonna,
they'll find a lot of reasons, I think,
to be angry that day.
Sure.
This is close.
That's what people are saying.
That's the prediction I've heard.
But like, like a, almost like.
Like to get in, to the land.
Yeah, but like, they'll let you walk around,
like they'll give you a ticket or a,
I guess not a bus.
I don't know.
Will they?
I think that would make sense.
Who knows?
It would make sense.
I mean, that's what they've done with the Harry Potter's
on both coats, I think.
You essentially get a reservation ticket.
Will people then be scalping those,
and fighting for those?
They can't if it's attached to a ticket,
which is probably what they would do.
That's true.
Is they would attach it to the app,
or like a fast pass type thing.
So QRs will save this historic landmark.
QR codes will save this park from being destroyed.
I mean, my hot take, and I hate when people say
they should do this with every ride,
because with the infrastructure of the park,
it literally wouldn't work to have no one wait in any lines,
and everyone says, oh, they should make it all digital,
and not wait in any lines.
But I think with a newly built land,
it would be really good if they just had the lines be virtual,
and they can do that, because they can factor that
into capacity when they're building the land.
Oh, but you couldn't retroactively take Snow White.
Because Disneyland's fire code is set to assume
that a lot of the people in the park
are going to be standing in the queues,
and inside the buildings.
So if they're all suddenly on Main Street, it's chaos.
Oh, okay.
Interesting.
We're getting fire code info.
Yeah, this is the stuff.
That's why the listeners tune in.
This is why you're one of the most requested guests
to come back, is you would bring the fire code stuff.
But if Star Wars land is new, it's new land,
so if anything, the capacity will increase slightly,
but they could just keep that in mind
of people not in the lines.
We should get back to inventions, but real quick,
how long would you be willing to wait, like, first week?
I mean, how long am I willing to wait for anything?
Sure.
Two hours.
Two hours, okay.
Yeah, I don't like lines.
I'm just too keenly aware of wasting my time.
Yeah.
Because this will be the longest wait
probably anyone ever has to face in their life.
I just, I don't know, and it's too easy also
when you're local to just think that you can come back,
even if you really wanna do it,
you're like, I should just come back.
I could be in my home right now.
I mean, also, I think if I had a friend
who I knew was willing to do a really long wait with me,
I would be more willing to,
but most of my friends hate lines
and also don't like theme parks as much as me,
so I'm sure I could not convince them to wait
in even a three-hour line with me,
and I'm not doing it by myself, so.
Right.
Yeah, so that's usually the deal breaker.
Like, when I go to D23,
I never go in the store line and stuff
because I'm always with someone who's only kind of into it
and I don't wanna be like, hey,
wanna stand in this taped-out queue for three hours
for only me to buy stuff?
Mike, are your ears burning super hard right now?
Well, I understand that a lot of folks feel that way,
and that's okay, but I think that Jason and I
are prepared to wait upwards of six, seven, eight.
Are you guys gonna camp out?
Because even getting in is a great deal.
I won't camp out.
I would much rather get.
Would you wait like a full work shift
to meet Bruce Springsteen that one?
I mean, that's a different situation.
It's a different situation, but like.
This is, we're not like meeting
the real General Hux or something, you know?
No, but I.
Would you wait a long time for that?
Mm, no.
But think about it, if they transported a character
from the realm of fiction into our reality,
that'd be something to meet. But not Hux.
That'd be a better.
No, that's where you'd struggle a lot.
Constable Zuvio, perhaps?
Perhaps.
Max Rebo?
Oh, yeah.
Hell yeah.
Anytime.
You got me finally.
Oh yeah, I'll wait eight hours for Max Rebo.
I mean, meeting a robot I can haggle with
is kind of like a celebrity to me,
and I wanna do that before they turn it off.
You're haggled.
Oh, same, with all the droids that wander around
and the interactive ones and stuff.
Yeah, all that stuff that's gonna go away after two weeks.
That's the thing, that's the pressure to go right away.
That's why we're going.
Because you know they're gonna stop that,
and the improv training and stuff,
that's all gonna go away.
Yes, my feeling is that the situation should be
as soon as we hear when the dates are going,
we book the cheapest hotel and walking distance,
and then maybe the play is not wait overnight,
but the play is get there at four in the morning
from the hotel.
I don't wanna say this, I mean,
now I'm literally saying it on a podcast,
I was gonna say I don't wanna say this to too many people.
Oh, we can edit it out.
But.
What just happened was,
we just cracked how to do it.
Yeah, right.
And we did edit it out, and you haven't heard it,
and I'm sorry, we just can't.
Yeah, don't tell them.
Yeah, yeah.
Jenny honestly had the best,
because I've tried to crack this too,
but this is.
I have the best idea.
You have the best idea I've ever heard.
Okay, so.
Oh, all three of us are in, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's a clue a little.
Oh no, cut that out too.
Good, okay.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, cut that.
Or we bleep.
Just bleep, you'll be part of my, and then.
Yeah.
That's gonna set, like people will wonder,
what the fuck was that?
Yeah.
We cracked it.
We cracked it, we got it.
Yeah.
What's happening?
Wow, all right.
Okay, so back to intervention.
So let's jump back.
You must we.
In time to 1994.
Yeah.
So CommuniCorps is not cutting edge,
but in this opening special,
the pitch they're giving you is that,
this is Epcot 94, and like we need something new for Epcot 94,
but Disney's history is rooted in World's Fairs,
and they show all these footage of amazing inventions,
dynamic footage, first ever show,
World's Fairs from the Chicago World's Fair,
the Philadelphia World's Fair, the New York World's Fair,
of course they show the Carousel of Progress,
and they're like,
Innoventions is gonna be like a World's Fair,
right in Epcot, and it's always changing,
it's always updating.
It already was like a World's Fair.
It already was, Epcot itself is supposed to be a World's Fair,
so I don't, so.
And the Carousel of Progress wasn't like selling you
like humidifiers, like.
Yeah, they weren't selling you things
that were currently out, it was all speculative.
Yeah, you couldn't buy the VR machine,
but now we, so we need a place where we can actually
sell you the VR machine.
I think you could buy some of the GE products
you saw on stage. Yeah, they had at least one thing
that was current, I think they had the current
GE dishwasher or something.
Yeah.
Jason wanted to buy John's clothes.
I wanted to buy John's fashionable sweater.
But. Big roomy bathtub.
I think it was more subtle, and that's what I got
from the quick glimpse of trying to remember CommuniCorps
was like the corporate sponsorship was either
a little more subtle, of course if it's phones
it's gonna be Bell or AT&T.
It was either subtle or agnostic, there was no sponsor
for the virtual roller coaster, whatever, what have you.
But we're gonna change that.
We're gonna change that.
Use the negative money.
Also isn't part of the story maybe that Eisner
went to the consumer electronics fair or expo
or whatever, or CES is the thing.
CES is the one in Vegas.
And he thought, well this is so active and visual
and vibrant and you look out at, I mean it's like Comic Con,
like you look out at a room where it's a big mess,
there's 20 big signs and mismatchy displays,
but isn't it exciting and what if we could bring
that vibe to the parks.
And let me tell you this, I'm talking about this
sarcastically now, but when I was a kid,
because I think the second time I went to Disney World
was, yeah, Inventions was new, I bought it hook, line
and sinker, I thought Inventions was great
and I spent a lot of time in there.
Yeah, well I, whatever, however this was sold to me
as a kid, I was excited for our next trip to Florida.
And it is primarily the character that's on Jenny's socks.
Oh, oh.
Sonic the Hedgehog.
Wait, was he there?
He was featured prominently in the advertising.
Now I was a kid who only had Nintendo systems,
my friend down the street had Sonic, had Sega,
but I was obsessed with Sonic.
So what was his relation to the Inventions?
So there was a massive Sega area of free games.
So Sega Genesis, Sega 32X, Sega CD, Game Gear representative.
Sega Pico.
So you use the logo.
It's a little educational Sega for kids.
Oh yeah.
Oh, that was a thing?
Apparently.
Oh yeah.
It was at Inventions.
Wow.
I thought you wore those on purpose.
I was like, oh, what a great nod to Inventions.
I just have my Sonic socks.
That's pretty good.
So kids, me and my brother loved it
because it was a massive free arcade.
I mean, all the hotel arcades at the time were pretty big
and we spent a lot of time there,
but these games were pretty good.
It was pretty big and we spent a lot of time there,
but these games were all free to play.
And yeah, we were in Nintendo house too.
So Sonic, the X-Men game.
Was the X-Men game there?
That was one of the big Sega.
The two X-Men games were huge launches for them.
Was that the X-Men game where to beat it,
you would have had to hit the reset button at the end?
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Maybe.
Was that the Days of Future Past game?
Just a little X-Men humor.
Sure.
I mean, I got it.
I'm actually just trying to remember the storyline
if they actually borrowed from it.
I think it was something with Apocalypse though.
And I think at the very end of the game,
in order to win, you had to hit reset on the actual console.
That's insane.
Because people were so confused
because that doesn't make any sense to do that.
But that was the only way you could truly beat the game.
That might have been the second one.
Okay.
But the first one came pretty early in Sega.
Some listener will yell it at us on Twitter,
which I'm talking about.
The big deal was you could pick which X-Men you played as.
Right.
Out of how many?
Out of all of them?
Four or five.
Okay.
Because the other X-Men game that I played
at the Grand Floridian when I was a kid
was the side scrolling arcade version
where you could play Dazzler, Cyclops,
and they were all in their 80s outfits.
It was based off the pilot.
Based off the pilot that they released on VHS,
but they never made more than one of.
I think I have that one on my phone.
It's crazy now I used to spend so many quarters
and now I have it on my phone.
But I beat the game.
The machine was broken at the Grand Floridian.
And I beat it with six other kids.
And it's one of the most triumphant moments
of my young life.
Because the games would be like,
you have to die constantly.
It would be like the Simpsons arcade game or those other,
there's similar type games like that.
Where to ever get to the end,
you were having to just spend $10.
Just putting in quarter after quarter.
Right, unless you were incredible at it.
And then this one was just busted.
So like five allies and I one day
in the soda shop of the Grand Floridian,
whatever it was, beat it.
And that's another great theme park memory
that was just unearthed.
Okay, anyway.
Oh wow, you like that you buried that away?
I hadn't thought about it in a while,
but I was like, oh yeah, I played it at Disney World.
Also, now that I'm thinking about it,
a Ghostbusters arcade game that I never played
anywhere else other than the basement of the contemporary.
I never saw it in any Chuck E. Cheese
and any other place.
And we had a lot of arcades around where I grew up.
But there was a side scrolling Ghostbusters game
and I was my mind just, I lost my mind.
Like, cause I never.
I have a lot of time on these trips in arcades.
I guess, I guess now that I'm thinking about it.
Did you go to the Starcade too?
No, I've never been to the Disneyland Starcade
cause it was gone. I do remember the Starcade
and it was very lame.
Yeah, oh sure.
I think it may have had,
cause it used to be double deckered.
Yeah, it was two stories initially.
The area that they just turned into
the Space Mountain Line.
Yeah.
I think I have vague memories of that.
I do remember seeing the upstairs
and downstairs of the Starcade.
Uh huh. Yeah.
But never spending significant time there.
Sure, I mean it doesn't make sense to do that.
I mean, I guess these were all,
this was all after hours and I was little.
So we were in a hotel. Yeah, that's true.
It's like, what else are you going to do?
Right, cause we weren't there til midnight.
Most, only one park usually stays open late.
I don't even remember if they did that 25 years ago.
It depends on your parents willingness
to stay until closing too.
Yeah.
Like they tire out more.
Cause I feel like kids, they weigh a lot less
so their legs don't get as tired.
And they also get carried for a lot of the day.
Yes.
So usually it's the parents that need to call it.
Yeah, kids aren't waking up to golf at five a.m.
like my dad always was.
On the Disney World trips?
Yeah, yeah.
I don't think I ever would have been to Disney World
as a kid if there wasn't golf.
That was a sell-out.
I think it was a legitimately great golf resort.
Did you really shout it out the golf?
We gotta do an episode of the golf.
Yeah.
Would your dad do the episode on the golf?
I've, I have thought about proposing that.
It maybe is a can of worms, but,
and it may be as a ticket to now on the 14th,
you get kind of like, you know,
it kind of bends off to the right there.
Maybe a Patreon.
But that's, I have, this thought has occurred to me.
I've questioned, but now that we've said it out loud,
unless we edit this out too,
but I have thought about proposing that
and maybe now we have to do it.
Is that the Shades of Green resort now?
That was one of the golf things.
Shades of Green, yeah, that's,
I forget how that's affiliated with,
that was the Disney Inn before.
Oh, the Disney, Shades of Green is now exclusively
for military families.
And it's supposed to be very nice accommodations,
you know, lower prices for everyone.
And you're right next to the Magic Kingdom.
It is right next to the Polynesian.
Oh, right.
Well, and we can, and mainly,
if you don't know about the Disney World Golf,
there is a sand trap that is Mickey ears.
So, get ready to hear about that for an hour and a half.
Oh, oh, oh.
Hi folks, it's Jason.
And I just want to take a second to tell you about HelloFresh.
HelloFresh is a meal kit delivery service that shops,
plans, and delivers step-by-step recipes
and pre-measured ingredients so you can just cook,
eat, and enjoy.
Each box is made up of fresh, responsibly obtained
ingredients from carefully selected farms
and high-rated, trusted sources.
Feel confident when cooking HelloFresh
with the simple recipes outlined on pictured
step-by-step instruction cards.
And all the ingredients come pre-measured
in handy labeled meal kits,
so you know which ingredients go with which recipe.
Spend less time meal planning or grocery shopping each week
and get that time back to do more of what you love.
I recently cooked the Korean beef bimbab bowl
with zucchini, mushrooms, and carrots,
and it was really good.
And I was happy I did it.
So, for a total of $60 off, that's $20 off
your first three boxes, visit hellofresh.com
slash themepark60 and enter code themepark60.
That's hellofresh.com slash themepark60
and enter promo code themepark60.
It's like receiving six meals free
or up to 50% off three boxes.
Oh, oh, oh.
My dad did one, I think he golfed once.
But we were, did you golf with him or no?
No, no, no, that was his free time
where he didn't have to be at the theme parks.
My dad did the same thing, I think.
Once, I don't think it was every day.
I think he did it once on like one of our trips.
So maybe multiple trips.
A golf at Disney Paris also.
And I did take time while there
to go to the Disney Paris pro shop.
This was very locked in 1992
when I bought Disney Paris golf balls
that I proudly display at home.
And so yeah, all right, get ready.
Golf coming your way.
We were a miniature golf family.
Oh yeah, we played.
But not really in Florida.
We did enough of that at the Jersey Shore.
We didn't need to do that on vacation vacation.
Good mini golf courses down there though.
And also this Pirates mini golf
across the street from Disney World.
Oh right.
Whatever that center is, I forget.
With the Perkins diner.
Did you go there?
No, I've done gator golfing out on International Drive.
Oh.
Which is pretty special.
And then you get to see the man fight the alligators
after you golf.
What? Whoa.
It's a separate ticket.
He's like, if you want to see me wrestle the gators.
And it was like late at night
and there were maybe only like two other groups there.
And it was an elaborate show
that like culminated in him pretending
to fall into the water and be in danger.
And I was like, man, he got all his clothes wet just for us.
Like I felt bad about it.
Cause it was a really small audience.
And then- Oh like he didn't get to perform for 30 people.
Like was this really worth getting wet for?
And there was a bar across the parking lot.
My friend's dad, who's a local was visiting with us.
And he was inebriated enough by that point
that he's like, how much to let the girls in
and see the gators?
And the guy was like 10 bucks each.
So we walked across a shaky plank
and got to go near the gators and get pictures with them.
It felt very like under the table and not safe.
It seemed like that was negotiable, maybe the fee.
I think it might've been, he could've haggled it down.
It seemed like an attraction
that was not a real thing that was offered.
But just since the promise of more money was out there,
he let us do it.
It was like stripper tricks or whatever.
Like, yeah, this can be bought.
It's not written down on a menu anywhere.
And he had a lot of gators, I guess they were all rescues.
So he didn't have to feel guilty about it.
So it's a good time.
That's another, we haven't talked about golf
and we haven't talked about weird I drive attraction.
Yeah, I drive is depressing.
Okay, sure.
It's the Florida project.
But since my friend and her dad were like locals,
I think to them, it's like a nostalgic level of depressing.
So through their eyes, I was enjoying it.
But yeah, it's not,
you kind of just want to stay on Disney property
when you're in that area.
Jenny, you mentioned Saratoga Springs Resort.
Did you guys all know, I just learned this like last week,
the tree house suites are still there.
Yeah, I'd love to stay in those.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
The tree houses.
You can see them on the river at certain hotels.
You boat past them.
Yeah, you can see it like Key West.
We voted past them or something.
Oh, I know what you're saying.
But they were in all the promotional videos,
like in the early 90s and stuff.
They looked so cool.
And I guess now they are part of Saratoga Springs,
but it is like you are almost staying like off the,
as far off the grid within Disney property as you can get,
because like you have to drive.
There's a gate that closes
and you have to use your room key to get to drive it.
So you can't get like food delivered or anything.
Wow.
But like they restored them.
They look really nice.
But I just remember as a kid going like,
God, I want to stay in those tree houses for a day.
They're really cool.
I don't know.
I always feel like torn about the Disney hotels
because there are so many really cool ones,
but like for what they cost and how cool they are,
you feel like you should be getting your money's worth
by not leaving them.
But then you want to leave them all day to be at the park.
So it's like, how much is it worth it,
staying at the really cool ones?
Or should you just stay at a boring one that has more space?
Oh, to like encourage you to get up and out.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's what, yeah, like Disney Paris,
we maybe should have just sprung for one right there,
but we stayed at just a Radisson that was the dullest,
like let's get out of here ASAP.
And you're kind of like, I'm not going to be at the hotel.
And also my family's vacation club.
So a lot of the vacation club rooms
that are the actual like suites, like for more people,
are at the most boring resorts.
But usually the family vote outweighs the fact
that we should like be in the spacious one
instead of the cool one.
Can I ask what your home resort is?
Ah, it's a Lani, which I have no interest in going to.
Really?
Oh, interesting.
I can't swim and I don't like the sun.
So I don't see myself ever going to a Lani.
Very fair.
So we tried to ask if we could get a different home resort,
but we couldn't.
So we're thinking of trying to switch to a new one,
like the train one or something.
I think if you get more points,
you can get an additional home resort.
What is a home resort?
I don't know about this.
So that is where, like that is your base.
Like that is where you have to.
So the perk of it being your home resort
is if you ever need a room there,
they say that you can get a room there
no matter when you're booking it.
So like a Lani, if we wanted to try to book a room,
like Christmas Eve and it's like the week before,
I think in theory they have reserved rooms
for people that are their home resort.
And then they just, they give it to you?
Will you?
Or you choose it?
You buy.
No, it's just available for you to book.
Yeah, it's available for you to book.
And you have to like pick a home resort.
Like some cost more than others.
So your family picked it.
It's, you don't get to pick.
It's whenever you buy into the vacation club,
it's usually whichever one they just built.
And then they keep offering that one
until they've run out of rooms
for that to be someone's home resort.
Interesting.
And then they switched to whatever new,
new one they're building.
So I think in like next year,
it's gonna be the train one.
Yeah.
Where is the train one?
It's in Florida, but I kind of like it
because it's train themed, which I'm all about.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
I tried to ask if they were ever going to have any
for the Star Wars hotel and they were like,
I don't think so.
Yeah.
It's gonna be like a cruise ship type package.
So.
Yeah.
When we were in the nineties,
we were at Old Key West was our home one.
And that one's like, it's pretty good
because at least it's huge rooms.
Huge rooms.
But it's very boring.
That's the one my family usually likes to stay at.
It's also really spread out.
So it takes a while to like wait at a bus stop.
Until they get to the bus and stuff.
The next time I go, I'm just gonna Uber everywhere.
Yes.
I did it on my last trip and I was like,
oh my God, I saved like six hours a day in my life.
And now I can like park hop
and it doesn't seem like a hassle.
I was like, I'm never taking the buses again.
It sounds easy and it sounds like a game changer.
Yeah, and it's like $5 a ride
because everything's like not that far.
No.
Yeah, we did that and it's great.
And everyone's gonna catch on at a certain point.
Maybe we should edit this part out too.
Yeah, edit this.
We can't be giving these tips away for free.
No, I think some people are like,
they have that forced frugality where they're like,
you mean I can spend $5 or waste an hour?
Well, I'm gonna take the free bus.
And it's like, that's less than minimum wage
if you're thinking about like the value of your time.
I don't know, I don't get it.
But I think especially like dads get in that mode
where they're like, why would I pay extra
when it can be free?
Yeah, oh for sure.
But yeah, there are certain times when like,
you got two hours to get to Animal Kingdom
because they're open a little later for the Avatar rides.
Yeah, or you have like a food reservation
and you didn't plan ahead.
And especially if you're leaving a park
that's like emptying out.
Yeah.
It's like, you can end up waiting like two hours
to get a bus to your hotel.
And then they don't always stop at your hotel first.
It's a nightmare.
It all depends.
All right, interventions, right?
Interventions.
We gotta keep going back.
I couldn't think of a segue back to it,
but I forget that you could just say interventions.
Yeah, that's the segue.
Does anyone have fun anecdotes about interventions?
Either coast.
No.
Uh, I as a child, I remember,
so as a child I was like, oh yeah, this is Sonic's house.
Sega.
So I went in there.
I was like so excited because all I saw,
I didn't care about is new products.
Yeah, no, because it would be like, I can play Sonic.
And I think when I went, all the machines were taken.
And then at a certain point,
because this is also a phenomenon with arcades,
I think as a kid is like waiting for older kids
to stop playing the game.
Cause the older kids are also a little bossier.
And I was not very intimidating.
I was not, I was not an assertive young man.
So I think I just stood there for a while,
maybe played for five minutes.
And then my parents, I think were like,
we should go on a ride.
And that was it.
I don't think I've done any other interventions.
When I got to California, they had the house of tomorrow.
Of course.
And I was like, I'm not going to watch the presentation.
I can't remember.
I'm sure we bumped around there a little.
You and I, I'm sure for a little bit,
we played with the touch screens that were already
way more outdated than the phones we had.
Andurally weren't, maybe it was like first fourth
or fourth generation iPhones.
And you're like, our phones are way better
than these touch screens.
And that's it, I think.
I think we did a little presentation.
I think we saw some of a presentation,
but I cannot tell you what it is.
I think we did a real syndrome of this
in any Disney arcade and Disney Quest sort of thing,
which relates to something that I learned about also
from my friends Tyler and Kia who were just there.
They spent some time in something called Color-topia.
Brought to you by Gildan, Gildan Paint Company.
Or Glidden?
Oh, sorry.
What is Color-topia?
I don't know.
It sounds familiar.
That is one of two things hanging on in interventions.
Color-topia's still there?
Yes.
Color-topia's still there.
My friends did it last week.
Is it just surrounded by construction walls?
I think so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're trying to shout over people jackhammering and stuff.
So they were explaining it to me.
And yeah, so it's kind of this paint exhibit.
And it's hosted by Ty Burrell from Modern Family.
And they give you like a, ugh, what do you mean?
It's very exciting.
It's Mr. Dumpy.
I love Ty Burrell, but I wouldn't call him an A-lister,
is all.
Whenever any Modern Family cast member cameos in anything,
stop the presses.
It's a huge deal.
This never happens.
So my pet peeves coming out of the show.
So in this exhibit, Ty Burrell shows you how to take a fiber
optics brush, and you dip it into fiber optics paint cans.
This already sounds really fun, to be honest.
Well, so they're describing it to me at this dinner and say,
yeah, it's actually pretty neat.
And you dip the brush, and you can combine colors,
and you start with primary colors,
and then mix them, and that shows
you how to make secondary colors.
And my friend's explaining details of this.
And then all of a sudden, Tyler interrupts and says,
I don't know why you're talking about this so much.
This is the worst thing we did the entire vacation.
This was so boring.
He said that it reminded him of a flash experience
that you'd find on Newgrounds circa 1999.
But if you're physically walking around
with a magical paintbrush, it would feel futuristic.
It looks a little like the old image works.
That journey into imagination.
That's what it was reminding me of.
And it sounds like a successor to it, technology-wise.
Yeah, yeah.
A successor to the thing where you pointed
Fred Flintstone's head and turned him into Leopard Brent.
It sounds like the thing they had at the Warner Brothers
store in Woodfield Mall in Shawnee, Illinois.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yes.
Aaron mentioned that too when this came up.
Yeah, in the Warner Brothers stores,
you could touch the screen and paint the little dude's
character.
It's like blue and stuff.
And I loved it as a kid.
Taz with green eyes?
Yeah.
Crazy?
That's outrageous.
But I would do it.
I would be crazy and do that as a child.
That's as crazy as I got.
Saber stripes on foghorn leg horn?
You need to go to an institution.
You could spend at least a half hour doing that.
That would be great.
I love the Warner Brothers store.
We'll get to some Warner Brothers store stuff.
There's going to be a full episode on the Warner Brothers
store.
Might have a rocket you could climb in,
and you'd push buttons, and they'd make sounds.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's like a rocket tube.
Yeah, there's like a, what is that?
Was it Marvin the Martian?
Yes.
OK, yeah, yeah.
You know what killed the Warner Brothers store?
They never carried any Pokemon things at any point.
That store still existed at the height of Pokemon.
And they would play the trailer for the movie in the store.
And you'd walk in like, oh my god, Pokemon.
And they'd only have golf tees with Taz on them.
You'd be like, where's the Pokemon?
It essentially could have been the Sanrio store,
but for Pokemon.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Could have lost their lives.
Every other store and the malls I went to growing up
had Pokemon stuff.
And it was scarce.
Even a clothing store, they'd just
have a box of the beanbags by the register.
Yeah, there's a box of cars, there's a box of beanbags.
And just be like, oh, we're wiped out.
We don't have any.
That could have saved the Warner Brothers store.
It could have saved the Warner Brothers store.
This is a documentary waiting to happen.
Oh, yeah.
Who killed the electric car type.
Which, by the way, I swear that was not just
a ham-fisted segue.
There was stuff in Inventions about GM did
an exhibit about zero emissions electric vehicles.
And was it that it's impossible?
Yeah, yeah.
Like, university.
It'll never happen.
Garsh, that sounds too hard to even try.
Yeah, it's too hard.
They're never going to figure it out.
But won't we run out of these finite fossil fuels?
Yeah, but not for a really long time.
Hey, don't worry about it, man.
It's too complicated.
We shouldn't think about it right now.
The official mascot of Inventions was a gray sedan.
That is the thing I remember as a kid.
No, it was Tom Morrow.
Well, it was Tom Morrow.
But I also remember a lot of gray sedans.
But also, it's OK.
So it was Tom Morrow here on the West Coast.
Maybe we'll do a full shift over to the West Coast.
But on the East Coast, it was a different robot
who you could see all the insides of.
I saw you send me a video clip of him rapping.
You saw it.
OK, wonderful.
We're talking about Alec Tronic, who
was a clear robot.
And this was really cool to me as a kid,
because he looks totally crazy.
He just has a clear surface around him, and wires,
and pistons, and stuff inside, because he is just
an undressed animatronic.
If Lincoln didn't have any of his skin,
he would look like Alec Tronic.
If robot Lincoln didn't have his skin.
Not if the real human Abraham Lincoln.
Correct, thank you for clarifying.
Speaking for everyone knows.
This was kind of this centerpiece.
He was almost as close as there was
to a mascot of Innoventions, although not
to be confused with Sky Cyber Guy, who
was a Motorola animatronic who you could also
meet in Innoventions.
But he was only in the Motorola part.
Alec Tronic was a host to the whole thing.
Do you know the timeline on Alec Tronic?
Because when you sent me that video,
I was wondering if Tom Morrow was just him with another head
that they had hastily sent to the West Coast for Innoventions.
That sounds correct.
Because it didn't feel very planned.
And that looked like the same body, but don't they all?
Maybe it was a last minute.
Maybe they're like, we need an animatronic in this thing, too.
Yeah, because Tom Morrow felt like an afterthought,
and had such an incredible range of motion considering how
little he entertained people.
He has such people walk past him.
And I mean it in terms of time, but also in terms
of entertainment value.
This is the one voiced by Nathan Lane that sang an update.
And he had horrible hair.
Yeah, it looked like it was just magnetic tape.
Yeah, he sang It's a Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow.
But yeah, he had weird curly hair.
But like about products you could buy.
Yes, and I didn't realize until recently
that he had four different songs to preference,
four different pre-shows.
Oh my god.
I think they quickly stopped running most of them,
because I only ever saw The House of the Future,
to my knowledge.
But I guess there was a sports one.
There was like a communication one.
I don't know what the fourth one was.
Art, entertainment, or something.
There was also this little fellow in Florida.
Is this Tom Morrow 2.0?
Yes, yeah.
And I never saw him.
I saw him on eBay a little while ago.
Really?
Yeah, and I think it was the version of him
they used for promotional videos and not
the actual one from the park.
But yeah, he was in rough shape.
And he was on eBay.
How much was he?
A lot.
Like 10 grand?
Probably like two grand, but like a lot for what he is.
Yeah.
Sure.
He seemed much more endearing.
I think we could get him for it.
We should buy him if he's two grand.
Well, he's gone now.
Oh, somebody got him.
For like $600, you could get the Dance in Henry
from the dance machine that's now a Woody in the Connish shop.
Yeah.
Wait, what's Dance in Henry?
I don't know about this.
I forget what the bear was called,
but now it's called Woody's Roundup,
and you can have Woody dance by pressing buttons.
Oh.
And it's just a little coin operating machine.
It's in Frontierland.
It looks like an old Penny arcade.
There's like a Pinocchio version too somewhere, right?
Oh, yeah, there is.
Or there used to be.
I don't know if there still is.
Maybe it's on Main Street, the Pinocchio one.
I think that's in the confectionary on Main Street.
I think it is.
I think it's on the right wall where all the
little dancing guy.
So we can't move past electronic without talking about the rap.
So I don't know with the full range of what he did exactly,
his full show, but I found the one that is clearly the only one
to care about, which is and I don't know why,
why the robot host of a computer electronic show does this.
But there is a rap that he does about the recent presidents
of the United States.
Wasn't like Lyndon B. Johnson in the lineup?
He goes back that far.
Comedy gold.
He goes back to Kennedy.
He kind of closes.
Yeah, he makes fun of all of the stereotypes
that we know about LBJ.
Yeah, you can tell he's doing voice impressions.
And I was like, I don't know if this is what Lyndon B. Johnson
sounded like.
I have no idea.
I only know about Lyndon B. Johnson at all
because there's a robot of him at his own presidential library
in Austin, Texas.
That's pretty cool.
It's pretty crazy.
And you watch him tell folksy stories,
and then you hear disembodied applause.
Is it like a Carousel of Progress type experience?
You can walk right up to it.
Oh my god, can you touch it?
It's just like you round a corner, and then like, ah,
oh my god.
Can you lay your hands on it?
You're probably not supposed to.
You probably could.
You could maybe let him do his entire speech
while just holding his lower lip.
I just want to feel his cheek muscles move under my hand.
Is it still there?
Caress his face.
Yeah, I believe so.
You can look up videos of this really insane.
There'll be an episode about it.
I'm thinking if there's any part they don't want you to touch,
it would be the face.
Yeah.
The most precarious.
The droopy dog face.
I would like that robot to be programmed to play the audio tapes
of the phone call where he gives a tailor.
Oh my god.
Lyndon Johnson.
That's crazy.
He's talking to a tailor, I think, back in Texas.
So like, yeah, I just want you to take the crotch out a little
old pants.
Old pants were real good.
It's crazy.
I don't know why that exists.
I don't know why it is real, though.
Did the tailor record it for posterity?
I don't know.
I think it is from an official White House recording.
I guess either they did or LBJ did.
Yeah.
It's in the Library of Congress.
He just loved his pants, but he wanted a little more breathing
room in the crotch.
And also, it's a lot more vulgar than what I am saying.
Oh, yeah.
It's very, very coarse.
It was a coarse man.
Yeah, yeah.
He seems unpleasant.
But none of this is addressed in the rap.
Mike, what would you like to display to us
from the president's room?
I'm just going to play a second.
We're the whole thing will obviously post on Twitter.
But let's just so you guys can get a hint of what is going on
here.
I'm going to tell you to our president's.
Hit it, boys!
The name is Bill.
No doubt about it.
You're listening to the president's rap.
The name is Charlie, if you're watching.
I'm the guy with 1,000 points of luck.
The name is Ron and my friend's item is the only one
with a death belly page.
The name is Jimmy, I'm here from the country to help Billy
sell beer.
And help Billy sell beer.
A lot of like C grade impressions
of not relevant presidents.
No.
Yeah.
And he also, the Ford one, it's just a joke
that Chevy chased it.
He's like, I fall down a lot or something.
My name is Jerry.
I slip and fall.
Pillows and mattresses line my wall.
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Gerald Ford lines his home with soft things because he.
Yeah.
And also lining your wall ain't going to help you too much.
You want those mattresses on the floor.
He might also fall sideways into things
with a trajectory going.
That's true.
It makes sense.
So you need it all around.
Clearly you've never had his problem before.
Gerald Ford needs to live in Goofy's bounce house.
Yeah.
It is also the same.
I mean, this has been used many times,
but it's a Super Bowl shuffle, very familiar.
My name is blank.
Right.
We want to make sure you understand the impressions
because they can't trust you two without identifying
who they're doing an impression of, like any good comedy act.
Not that good.
Yes, every impressions should say, oh, I'm.
That's how a lot of people start impressions.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's my favorite thing when people start an impression
and have to say I'm and the name of the person
they're trying to do.
Well, we're describing the best content on YouTube,
which is I'm Stewie.
Oh, god.
Seven million views.
I shouldn't say it.
I won't.
It's an actual YouTuber.
How can you?
There's no way to know.
I'll tell you after.
There are 250 YouTubers who do Stewie Griffin impressions.
Look, I'm starting shit with Tom Morrow, who technically
was the mayor of Tomorrowland unofficially.
Oh, was he?
That's true.
He's kind of a mayor.
They still mention him on the People Mover.
Oh, that's right.
Paging Tom Morrow.
Tom Morrow.
So that's the question.
That's referencing the Tom Morrow in Epcot.
I believe it is.
Well, in general, I think he was a recurring character name.
Huh.
That's interesting.
I forget, did the episode come out where we sort of,
because you know C, the Society of Explorers and Adventures,
but we came up with another thing we think
we should pitch called space.
I would love that.
Tomorrowland Extended Universe.
Yes, because it does exist.
Yeah, there's a lot of aldermen in Tomorrowland 94.
There's a lot of bureaucratic positions.
With people like Sunny Eclipse.
When will we talk about Sunny Eclipse?
Boy, that would be a great topic to address.
I agree with you.
Or on that later.
Should we use the animatronics as the juncture point
to switch over to West Coast interventions?
We've already talked a little bit about.
My home in Oventus.
Would you know much more about, yes, you've
spent seemingly a lot of time in there, potentially.
Certainly enough.
Compared to other people, regular people.
So yeah, you're, all right.
This was part of New Tomorrowland 1998.
One of the major parts of it.
And I was such a weird, poisoned kid
that when I read that on Disneyland.com
in the computer lab in sixth grade, which
is where I spent lunch looking at Disneyland.com instead
of socializing.
And I have a very specific memory of going to the website
and saying, oh, Innoventions is coming out here.
Well, that's a smart idea.
And I probably went and told that
to another kid who just snarled at me and looked away.
Smacked a lunch bag out of my hand.
We went to the opening of Tomorrowland 1998.
Wow.
Really?
There was very little.
I barely remember it.
But I do remember the CEO came out and talked
and then flung a bunch of astronaut Mickey beanbags
into the crowd.
And we caught quite a few of them.
They tossed a lot.
My aunt found one recently and she sent it to me in the mail.
Just like, I thought you'd want this.
So I have a Mickey Mouse beanbag astronaut.
Wow, have you tweeted that?
I should.
I think it's literally in my apartment.
So I should.
Well, we tweeted.
The listeners want to see that beanbag.
They got to see that beanbag.
He even still has his tag on because it was just
one that my aunt had.
So it was never played with.
That's great.
How much things have changed.
You were just encouraged to play with that Mickey that
was thrown to you as opposed to eat that Mickey
at an opening attraction.
The thing is with the new Tomorrowland,
I believe other than cosmetic changes,
like moving the Astro Orbiter and things,
I think that the only new things were
Autopia and Innoventions.
And I might be wrong about that.
But I think otherwise it was just Rocket Rods.
Rocket Rods.
Can't forget Rocket Rods.
Which I wrote, I think, twice before it closed.
That's what I did too.
It's pretty good.
Twice is pretty good.
And I really liked Rocket Rods.
I actually remember that after the Mega Wait, that I sort of,
I enjoyed it more than I thought because it had been built so
down.
Yeah.
I remember both times we went really early.
So we didn't probably wait more than a half hour,
which is really nice.
Oh, really?
But the trick was being there when it didn't shut down.
I think there was at least one time we waited in line
and it closed.
A hard trick to pull off.
Which is pretty common.
So you're at the first day when Innoventions
sparkling new.
The only real thing I remember about opening day
was after getting beanbags thrown at us,
was walking in and being really impressed by the neon Mickey
that tumbles in his astronaut gear.
Do they still have that?
They sure do.
They do.
God bless it.
I love that.
I was so impressed by it.
I swear if it ever goes away, that's when I protest.
That's when I throw pipe bombs.
So yeah, I remember the gift shop had all these Tomorrowland
things in it and I remember the Mickey on the wall.
But I don't remember doing a lot else that day.
But yeah, I have vivid memories of Innoventions,
the new attraction and being excited to find out what it is
and queuing up to go into Innoventions
and watch the pre-show and everything.
And then, yeah, it's really just an ad for things.
I remember that right up until their closing,
they still had a large section where you would play PS1 games.
The PlayStation 1 Lilo and Stitch games.
Oh, yeah.
I remember that.
That was the closing day of Innoventions.
They still had that.
And I want to say that game is from 2006.
Sure.
Oh my god.
It was so old by that point.
They had some Disney Infinity stuff too toward the end,
right?
Yeah, toward the end they did, which
should have been an Omen.
And was it still called Innoventions
when they had the Marvel stuff open on the top?
No, then it was Star Wars Launch Bay and Marvel headquarters,
I think.
And that's what they renamed it the Tomorrowland Expo Center.
And they put up on the outside, cute,
retro-looking Stark Expo posters.
Oh, that's right.
OK.
Which I thought was an apt use of the space,
because it doesn't have that World's Fair vibe.
Sure.
But the contents were not interesting or good.
But visually, it was a nice concept.
I think there was one or two Marvel things when it was still
in Innoventions right at the end.
It was the Thor meet and greet and then Spider-Man meet
and greet.
Oh, I did the Thor meet and greet.
And maybe Captain America too.
Yeah, and the Iron Man suits where you could do, again,
Kinect technology.
Yes.
It would look like it put the suit on you.
I did the Thor.
And then I think send you a GIF of it or something.
And then the empty area where like,
Awesomo would come out.
Yes, I wanted to talk about Awesomo.
I love Home of the Future.
I love that in their version of the future,
they had what was basically Alexa technology.
But instead of it just being a box
that you set in your living room,
they thought that it would be a 500 pound, four foot tall boy
robot that walks around.
And it can only really do things like call people for you,
order a pizza, add something to your grocery list.
Literally nothing beyond what Alexa can do.
But it has to be a fully mobile 500 pound boy that shuffles
around your house ominously.
And he has to be next to four massive Microsoft Surface
tabletops that are pushed together.
And yeah, already out of date by the time they were.
And he knows your voice.
And they never made it clear from a cultural perspective
what Awesomo is doing when he's not doing tasks for you.
Like, do you think he goes on autopilot
in their imagining of it and just wanders your house?
Or do you think he stands in a corner unmoving
until you acknowledge him?
Put him in a closet.
I was going to say.
Yeah.
What is life with Awesomo?
Yeah, it depends how often you have to charge him, I feel like.
It feels like.
Probably really often.
So you probably.
I want to hope that he knows himself
how to navigate to a charger and plug himself in.
But I'm not confident that's the case.
I would like us taking a nap or going to sleep.
Yeah.
I would like to think that he knows, but he can't get there.
And he has to like hold up.
He has to come to you for help.
He holds up his plug and goes, please plug, please.
Mother.
Mommy.
I can feel the Windows 9 installing.
Edwin stands and clearly wants a walker food.
I remember for a time he ran.
But it happened frequently enough that he would fall over backwards,
that they discontinued his running because he was so heavy and fragile
that when he would fall over backwards, they were told not to move him.
So they would come out with like a portable curtain.
Yes, they just bring a wall out, which was the same thing
they would do with the meet and greet Wally when he broke down.
They would bring out a little curtain, like a changing screen
and just put it around him and have everyone leave.
That's why he's too heavy to move.
Yeah, that was the same with Wally.
I think Wally weights like 400 pounds or something.
I think if you're living with Osimo, like a dog who wants to play
catch or play frisbee, Osimo constantly wants to show you
that he can climb the stairs.
Yes. And he does it really slowly.
And he's wide enough that you can't go around him.
Is there something you need once he starts?
Can I go up the stairs for you?
Can I fetch you a glass of water, particularly one up the stairs?
He moves like half a mile an hour around the house.
His steps are so careful.
Osimo, it's really OK. I can run up.
No, no, let Osimo do it.
Osimo can climb stairs.
And if he's halfway up and you change your mind, he has to complete the ascent
because he can't turn around without falling.
That's too complicated. It's OK. You can stop.
No, I can't. Yeah, I will fall.
What are you? Do you have a curtain?
Otherwise, I must finish climbing the stairs.
What am I even doing anymore?
Fuck, man.
Who is Osimo?
If Osimo cannot climb stairs, is there Osimo?
I believe this was so it was called Dream Home, right?
I loved Dream Home. Dream Home. Yes.
That's what I was talking about with the screens.
Yeah, yeah. With the smart screens sponsored by H.P.
Microsoft and Taylor Morrison, a home building company.
Taylor Morrison. OK.
I remember one time I was there and they were doing their spiel about the TV
and it was like a smart TV.
This was like in the end times of interventions, like in the last five years.
So it was a smart TV, but it was connected to Wi-Fi.
And they were trying to show us the like beautiful picture quality,
like the high def picture.
But the Wi-Fi wasn't good.
So it was the worst image quality ever.
It was like 240p.
And there were only about like five people watching.
And my sister said much too loud.
It looks terrible.
And she said it to me, but everybody heard.
And the host had to awkwardly be like,
it's well, that's because of the Internet speed.
But the capabilities of the TV are much better.
So like they had to talk back to her saying that it looked really bad.
And I was mortified. Disneyland.
Not great Internet, not great Wi-Fi.
Still, still, the hotels have gotten a lot better.
But the walk around life is well, even for employees, the Wi-Fi is not good.
There are several like info kiosks they kept having to move
because you couldn't get Wi-Fi at them.
In fact, I think right now the one on the pier, like Pixar Pier, it's called now.
The kiosk used to be closer to the Incredicoaster line,
and they moved it across the way.
And now it just never has Wi-Fi.
And the Wi-Fi is slightly better, but now it's really loud
because you have to hear Dash screaming every day.
Oh, yeah.
So I think at the time that I left, everyone was begging them to move it.
And I don't think they have yet.
I did just go there for something, and it was something they couldn't do
because they weren't hooked up to something or other.
Set you up with like a if you're handicapped and you get the return times,
they can't do that without Wi-Fi and they can't give you fast passes.
They can't book anything.
Basically, every aspect of their job, except giving you buttons
or walking directions, can't be done without Wi-Fi.
It's one of the few things that Universal Hollywood outpaces,
probably because they are owned by Comcast and Information Services Company.
They aren't the good as opposed to being the company that tried to start Go.com.
Always a spotty history with Disney and the Internet.
He tried to start Go.com.
Wow. Yeah, that was their like competitor to Google or to ask.
Oh, my God. Yeah, that's why their site is still Disney.Go.
Disney. Oh, my. Is it really?
Yeah, if you like book a hotel or yeah,
I read times and stuff, it's Disney.Go.com.
Yikes. Oh, that's crazy. Yeah.
So in other words, in 2015,
Disney had a big display of poor Wi-Fi and video games from 2006.
Yeah. Here is a take from me of all the things.
I'll just do the I'll just do it.
How about in my lifetime since I've been going to Disneyland?
Inventions Disneyland, I think, is the worst thing passed off as an attraction.
And I count Superstar Lemmo.
I can't because that's a ride.
It is a stupid. Yes. But a rocket rods.
You did go really fast. Yeah.
What is the innovative that building is so big, a massive footprint.
They they dare call that an attraction.
Are you kidding me?
If it's a good if you if you listed under glorified shops,
if that's the heading on the map, then sure worse than like, I mean,
and I don't think these are bad.
The tortilla tour. Yeah.
At least I have fun for that.
Yes. I mean, I agree.
I'm just trying to throw things out.
Bread tour. You get a piece of bread. Sure.
The caterpillar. I agree.
The caterpillar is like Choo Choo train.
No, not like Choo Choo train.
The the farm equipment. Oh, right.
Bountiful Valley Farm Valley Farm.
Yeah, you might have me on.
You finally have one. Cornstalk characters,
which automatically makes it better than intervention.
Yeah. Yeah. Although does Osomo not.
Do you agree with my.
Oh, you're right. Osomo is pretty good.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe.
I didn't see the Osomo show, but he was not always running.
OK. Huh.
A single segue. I think too.
Yeah, not so like he's still on the he's on the utopia now.
Yeah. I've always wondered if those are actual Osomos who have just been disabled
or if they or if they're just I think they're Osomo shells.
But how scary to think that they have like a full brain and can like recognize
faces and are capable of walking, but not allowed to.
But I will never climb stairs again. Yeah.
It doesn't move, though, right?
On the utopia, isn't it? Or like a very little.
It moves. It's bird friend bird. Yeah.
Bird with a Y. OK.
The most famous moving robot is on the car ride and can't can't move.
I think one of them waves.
Yeah. The one that you can see from the train waves.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. OK.
He does like a Miss America wave.
That's something great.
Worth keeping that attraction.
Keep that forever.
Keep interventions and empty husk forever.
Yeah. What's going on?
Huge footprint that really be something better or at least electric.
Just going to put it out there.
Oh, sure. It's kind of embarrassing in Tomorrowland to have gas powered vehicle.
Well, doesn't Tokyo have electric ones?
I think they do.
But I think they cost a million dollars.
We didn't do it.
And I don't remember where it is, but I mean, I don't know if it was.
Can they get like Tesla to sponsor it or something?
Well, that's I mean, that that's my big because in Michael Iser's pitch
to to the viewing public about interventions, he said, like,
only the best of the in their fields are going to be here.
So I. Yeah.
Yeah. Honda, GM.
I mean, so when it first opened, it was GM and Sega.
And it was Chevron to initially of Autopia.
They had the Chevron car mascot.
Oh, that's when they had the faces.
Yeah. Right. That was cool.
But I always wondered why didn't they just turn interventions over to like Apple?
Turns out Apple was an original tenant of interventions, but it was 1994
Apple when they were selling the Newton, their version of the pilot.
Oh, no.
She's Newton.
It was the most awkward era of the most awkward between Steve's.
Right. The one that was the fewest, Steve's were pre.
Yeah. And pre next when Steve like sold that and then came back to Apple.
Yeah. So that that was very.
But like, yeah, you'd think like Apple and Tesla
like taking it over could do something.
Companies like that could do something, though.
Probably best that there's not a platform for Elon Musk.
Yeah, I don't know.
We need him and he's a rat.
He's a bum.
Maybe like five years ago, Elon Musk, before people like knew really what he was like.
Yeah. Yeah. Before we knew any facts.
Yeah. When he was just the guy that owned a company that was doing well.
And all I remember hearing like, you know, he's actually kind of like the real life
Iron Man. He's Tony Stark.
No, but he loves the idea that he's Iron Man.
I think there's an Iron Man statue inside of SpaceX.
There's also one of Rick from Rick and Morty.
So, you know, but so two statues, zero unions.
Yeah. I mean, we can't deny that both Tony Stark and Rick would be anti-union.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
That's why those are the statues.
Rick does not exactly think collectively.
No. The first episode of ours posted on Reddit with seven hundred ninety six comments.
Two thousand down votes.
No.
Stay away from Rick.
Oh, boy. Our first real death threat.
And they didn't tell us how they're getting into Galaxy's Edge.
That's true. This is why you withhold the information.
Yeah. Yeah. You have to earn that.
Now, you talk about leaders in your field.
There were, of course, there were leaders in their fields at interventions.
Ninety eight. And I'm talking about Kaiser Permanente.
Thrive. Thrive.
The second floor was health geared.
I also remember my first trip to Innoventions.
They had a tiny corral of segues.
And I found that really exciting.
It was the first time I had seen or heard of a segue.
But I was very young and you had to be 18 to try the segues.
So basically, anyone old enough to try them was too old to be interested in trying them.
All the children wanted to ride the segues, but it was not allowed.
It was a liability.
The same. You had to sign a waiver before getting on the set.
Oh, yeah. Innoventions, you can sign waivers.
You've never dreamed of was there wasn't a segue.
There was like a segue tour of California.
California just a few years ago.
We've talked about that before, I think.
I regret never doing that.
So that was all probably from the same batch of segues.
Yeah, the same sponsorship.
You're right. They would wrangle them from the corral and take them right.
To California Adventure.
The running of the segues. It was so cute.
It was like a segue petting farm.
Like it was maybe like a 10 foot diameter little thing.
And like everyone was just like having to go and then stop
because there were so many segues in this tiny little circle.
It really was like a segue corral.
Like they were going to round them up for branding or something.
But it was kind of eating time.
Yeah, they were milling around electricity, little pellets from a machine
and have them come up to you over the fence.
Bolts. I that's insane.
If I could talk about this Kaiser Permanente thing really fast, I sent you
I sent you guys a video.
I yourself would really think you least want to do it at theme park
in front of your weight.
And then it would give you like pointers on how to like lose weight.
God, what?
Your BMI for you and then went like you might want to eat less carbs.
After you just like ate a churro, it's like, cool, I love this.
I oh, yeah. Wait there.
Well, there's also confusingly, there was also a thing that was sponsored
by St. Joseph's Hospital.
What? Like the Children's Hospital?
Yeah, it's kind of a down.
This attraction was called Healthy University.
That's where you could calculate your BMI, play virtual sports games
and have a chance to see yourself 50 years in the future.
Oh, no. You're fat.
Here's what you're going to look like before you look what you look like.
When death looms before you.
50 years is like not fun for anyone, even if you're really young.
At least they said 10 years, maybe if you're 10, you want to see yourself
as like a hot 20 year old and be like, oh, good.
It's all going to work out.
Hey, get ready.
But yeah, no years.
There's no age at which 50 years you're going to be like
like you're looking forward to that.
But 50 years gives them a huge margin for error because like you
no one can look at it and go, that can't be right.
What if 50 years is so long?
What if you were 80?
Oh, no.
It shows you like a skeleton.
This is a you at a hundred and seventy.
The skeleton dance short that plays in the face.
So so also there also is a kind of because of permanent
thing, and I found a video about Kaiser Permanente's
it was from their YouTube channel that was from, you know,
Kaiser Permanente's video magazine Perspectives.
This is now posted to their YouTube channel where it has a solid seven
hundred and ninety one views.
Oh, my God. And I hope it.
Hey, listeners, get up there.
Let's get them to a thousand PTR Army.
Let's help Kaiser thrive.
And you'll also get to see Charlie McMillan, the president of the McMillan
group, which is something that has to do with what he's hanging out there
to give an awesome type show every hour.
Show us what you can do, Charlie.
You can run downstairs.
Let me just show it since you didn't see this video, Jenny,
let me just show you some stills of the boardroom where people wait.
Was that a physical thing inside?
Oh, that's a video.
No, this is this is people brainstorming at easels.
The you know what the attraction is going to be.
And this is a purple plastic wall that says magnetic madness,
magnetic resonance imaging.
And then here's the lady who's the host of perspectives in front of a light.
Literally just get an MRI at Disneyland.
Yeah. Why would you like, hey, think about MRIs?
Always a good sign when you're getting one of those MRIs.
You you not only that, but you could do
a practice ultrasound.
You could like rub the little arm onto something or other.
Some where little belly and in the frame that I have in front of me,
I sent you guys a video, but I don't know if you saw this detail.
Well, yeah, you're looking at sort of a simulation of a little baby
black and white in the womb.
Sounds like x-rays were like you're not supposed to get them for fun.
Like it's not great for you.
So you're supposed to do it sparingly.
It's better, I think, than an x-ray, but I don't know that it's not.
I think I remember some news story where like a rich celebrity
bought an ultrasound because his wife was pregnant and he just enjoyed using it.
Like recreationally, let me see the fucking good buy one.
We can use it all the time.
And I remember the news was very much like this is not a thing
you should have done because it's not like medically responsible
to do that all the time.
I don't editorialize very much, but I need to I need to say something here.
This Edward Armour moment.
Maybe it was a question of like, if you're not a licensed tech,
it can be dangerous.
But I don't know.
The impression I got was you're not supposed to just go,
let's look in your arm.
It's Disneyland.
Boy, well, I had a great day at Disneyland.
I did an MRI.
I did a false ultrasound and I went on seven roller coasters.
Anyway, can't wait to have that baby next month.
The very MRI like take a long time.
I want to imagine they like put you in the tube for like 45 minutes.
I think so.
It's very loud, right?
They're very loud.
Noises.
I don't know if there was a shout over it.
I'm not entirely sure that there was like a fake MRI,
but you could learn about MRI.
Maybe they had like a puppet MRI kind of like the House of the Future
demonstration where there wasn't really someone on the phone.
Right. So it's like the machine's not really on.
It just screams at you.
And it goes, look, that's their brain.
And it's like an actor.
They should have put awesome in the MRI.
Oh, God.
What are you? OK, you're in here with me.
You need a fork in a microwave.
I feel like something bad would happen.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah. I climbed in here with you so I could keep you company.
Ah, zap fire.
You burn up to they should have put the old John animatronic
from the carousel progress in the MRI machine.
Well, yeah, that would have been better.
Well, I can't.
I like a turtle. If I'm on my back, I can't get up.
So someone please help me.
The frame in the ultrasound point, they can't get up.
After he falls down.
Oh, tap.
So the frame in this Kaiser Permanente video
where they're showing you the fake ultrasound,
it has a big blue bar up at the top of it.
And children are looking at this.
The big blue bar says, current view, genitalia.
No.
This is what they showed in their YouTube video.
Computer, enhance.
No.
No, mom.
So that's what a baby's dick looks like.
Why are they doing that?
That's bizarre.
I don't know.
Innoventions where you can see unborn babies.
It feels like the Imagineers had nothing to do with this.
I hope not.
It just feels like this is a separate thing
from the rest of Disney.
I feel like they were involved as much as a teacher's involved
in a group project you might have,
where they check in on your idea and give you gentle guidance.
And the more lost you are, the more they step in.
Right.
It's a nurturing role.
Although maybe somebody's like, my proudest
accomplishments at Disney, California screaming,
and Tower of Terror, and got to go with the baby genitalia
machine.
My three proudest.
Put those on my tombstone.
I was the one who made the choice
that Innoventions in Epcot, the pathways through it,
would look like little roads.
So there was white lines with brakes that you could pass,
and yellow lines if you shouldn't
be walking on that side.
It added some whimsy.
Roads indoors, they said.
They left me out of the room, but I showed them.
Well, if you were on a Segway, that
would make a lot more sense.
Now it's a division of the traffic lines, right or left?
All the sidewalks are going to have that one.
Segways are the new thing.
It's coming up.
Any day now.
We're going to wake up, and it's going to just have happened.
We're in Segway worlds.
Tomorrowland 2020 will be the future that never was,
but it was the future predicted in 1999.
So a lot of Segways, a lot of in the promotional,
one of the Innoventions specials,
are like, in the future, your phone's just going to disappear.
You won't have a phone.
It'll be in your TV and your coffee maker.
And you have Osmo instead of a smartphone.
And you have Osmo.
And they were kind of right.
And also, they were horrifically wrong.
Now our phones are like drugs that we can never
be without them.
Well, maybe this was a juncture point in Britain.
Maybe we wouldn't be in all the messes that we're in if we
didn't have these things.
And we just had little eager Osmos want to climb stairs.
Eager Osmos, more curved metal, more curved plastics.
And we all go out and we're not connected to each other
because we're looking at our phones.
But if to be connected to the internet,
require you to carry around a 500 pound baby at all times.
Right?
Yeah, we need to go.
This is the almanac I want to go back and get.
And when you want a picture of something,
you say, Osmo, take a picture.
And he goes, well, what do you like me to take a picture of?
And you have to point your finger very precisely at what
he's going to take a picture of.
It's a three minute ordeal.
You have to kind of lean over his shoulder
to see what it'll look like from his perspective.
Or aperture.
And then he emails it to you and you can look at it at home.
Portrait or landscape.
Yeah.
It will be from a low POV.
I am very short.
Unless I climb stairs.
A lot of them flattering selfies.
Instagram would have never existed.
Sure.
Everyone from chin down.
Osmo is the solution to the selfie.
But if you were using a stranger's Osmo,
it would be constantly, sorry, I security lock.
How do I?
Yeah, and he wouldn't know how to recognize your face.
So he would not focus on you.
I was not told I can trust you.
You are not my owner.
I would also like it if he was just upset when you would check
and make sure he was doing something.
No, I'm OK.
I took a few.
Come on.
It's fine.
You don't need to check.
Who are you?
Mom?
Dad?
I am never shaky.
I'm very steady.
Get off my ass, everyone.
I'm tired of this.
So did you guys experience the show
that was in the smart home?
Not only the intro show with Osmo and the interactive stuff,
they had a tiny theater you could go into,
where you would go on a virtual vacation to one of three places.
Oh, yeah.
The walls were screens, and they would pump one smell per location.
So if it was like a camp, it would be like a woodsy smell.
Or if it was a jungle, it would be like some kind of tropical smell
or like beach smell.
And the seats didn't move.
And I think there were only like five seats.
It was like a single row of movie theater chairs.
And then you picked your destination
and they'd be like, OK, you're at a vineyard.
And they'd be like, ooh.
And then you'd leave.
So is that as if soon you will take vacations in chairs at home?
I guess they thought in the future you would have all your walls
be screens and buy scents.
And there will be just different vats of scents
that you will keep for different vacations you want to come and go.
Exactly.
Instead of just buying a candle, you're going to get a scent machine.
That's like vacations of Fahrenheit 451.
That sounds like a nightmare.
And I was always questioning how much of a return
you get for a room with walls that are screens over just looking
at a video of the same image.
How much more are you deceived by bigger screens than just like,
you still don't think you're there.
And the Wi-Fi keeps cutting out.
Yeah.
And it's all low res.
And it's not a VR.
Yeah, no, it's not.
We're adults, so it wouldn't trick us.
But if you had a child and raised it in a world where
they thought that was traveling.
So if you're constantly deceiving your own child
into thinking they're going on vacations, then you raise them that way.
You train them not to enjoy vacations, so they make no demands of you.
Don't ever get curious about the outside world.
See, look, we just stepped into another room,
which took us to Colonial Williamsburg, which smelled like tar.
So you never want you never want to go there again.
I hope you want to go back because we bought at least a liter of the tar smell
and it's super concentrated.
So we have to go at least 60 more times.
Unless any of you folks would like some tar scent.
Yeah. Your dad got upsold on tar smell at the vacation store.
Salesmen really talked it up.
Like if you get five at once, it's like four of them are free.
Yeah. Yeah.
You got to get the tar.
I don't.
Future Giants.
I went in and I think, but my memory of it is just so nothing.
Because I think every room, so they had like the kitchen,
which was the demo space. There was a piano in there, right?
Yeah, there was a smart piano.
But like people would play it as well. They would.
I think I tried playing it.
Smart was like the keys would light up to like a guitar hero of a piano.
Yes, that's right.
So if you didn't know how to play, in theory, it would teach you,
which I think is a tech people buy now.
Yeah, yeah, it is.
I think our pianos.
We had a keyboard that did that in like 1995.
But it was built into a real piano.
Oh, it's built in. Oh, OK.
Yeah, well, I think keyboards have done that for a long time.
Yeah, yeah.
I feel you and I were in that room and I think I sat down at the piano.
Maybe maybe I'm mixing up my time.
I definitely remember.
I remember going once in like 2012 and making the connection of like, oh,
dream home, like House of the like the old House of the Future.
How cool.
What an interesting throwback concept.
And they did not lean on the nostalgia.
They just leaned on the Microsoft. Yeah, not at all.
I remember being more entertained by like at some point you got
like one of the light bulbs that you can change the colors on from your phone.
Like, yeah, yeah.
Eleven or 2012.
And we were all kind of like, oh, shit, check this out.
And that entertained us for longer, I think, than the house.
The tree. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. 100 percent.
They had that was like a missing the mark kind of thing was
they did have app controlled light dimmers.
And I think in theory, like the temperature control, although obviously
you can actually control it in the demo. Yeah.
But instead of deciding it would be on your phone,
they believed that in the future, people would attach tablets to their walls
permanently and just go up to the tablet to control it instead of like
having a thing in your pocket to control it from.
So, you know, if you want to do the lights in every room,
you have to walk to the wall switch tablet.
So it's not any more convenient than having a dimmer switch.
I used to work at an office that had like some tablets framed outside of like
common you like conference rooms and stuff so that you could like
you could just slide over.
You could slide over just whether it was occupied or not,
which must have just been like the photos app on an iPad.
And those iPads were turned on for about two weeks, I think.
And then just I could see it having that instead of a switch,
if it fulfilled like many functions, like if it was temperature,
whether it's occupied, what's in it, and then maybe an app.
If you're lost in the building and need to know where to go.
But it seemed like it only ever replaced a thing a switch could do
and did the same thing a switch would do. Yeah.
I think they had that Neil Patrick Harris's character has that on an iPad
in Gone Girl, and it's meant to be like, look at this insane person.
It was gotten surveillance and can control everything in his home
from his iPad. Look at this weirdo.
A man of the future.
You want to be like Neil Patrick Harris in Gone Girl.
Spoiler alert, he does not get to see much of that future, folks.
But yeah, it doesn't work out so great for him.
You know, in keeping with
interventions being the home of characters no one is fond of,
there was also apparently something called Body Builder, a 3D game
allowing guests to build digital human body.
It featured the voice of Wallace Shawn as Dr. Bones. That's great.
I mean, I'm kind of into I wish I'd met Dr.
Bones. Yeah, but nobody ever told you it was good.
No, we character, I guess so.
And maybe just a voice. Yeah.
So if how good could it have been if nobody ever alerted you
that there was a wall of Shawn characters only in theme parks that you could go see?
Because there's no part scale for this.
There's no Park star Dr.
Bones that I have or anything.
These are think about this list.
Electronic Tom Morrow, Tom Morrow, 2.0.
None of them are Park stars.
They made six wave five waves of them.
Even Sunny Eclipse is a Park star.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah, of course.
I mean, there's much more obscure characters in Sunny Eclipse, too.
Who would you say is the most obscure Park star?
Oh, that's a good question that I now feel like.
You set it up. I set it up.
I got one. Yeah. Laguna Gator.
Yes, that's good.
The old mascot of Typhoon Lagoon.
Typhoon Lagoon. Yeah.
Yeah, not the brother of the ice skater.
Is he no longer the mascot?
I think he might still be.
He was never prominent like ice skater. Not obscure.
Not as obscure. Well, Wally Bogue is kind of obscure.
Wally Bogue, the human man, is a Park star.
Yes, I have him. Yeah.
Wally Bogue, Abraham Lincoln.
And I feel like there's one other real life person.
Yeah, I forget.
Abraham Lincoln is also an animatronic. Wally Bogue is not.
No, he's a man. He's definitely a man.
That's what makes that really weird.
Yeah. You know, you could get a Wally Bogue.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
But no Eisner. No Eisner.
We want more Eisner merch.
That's a big thing on this podcast.
Like for voodoo purposes?
No, we like. No, we like him.
We have a fondness for him.
We have the specials when he would introduce, you know, like.
Did he just spend an hour and a half complaining about an attraction
that he thought of? Yes, but.
Yeah, he tried to like make himself a character like a Walt Disney.
And he succeeded in our hearts.
And we want a hundred dollar deluxe toy of him.
We won't stop until we get it.
Oh, like one of those super realistic ones.
Yeah, like like Marvel characters like this Adam West.
Adam taught toys by Adam West.
And I have over here. Yes, that's what we want.
Yeah, Michael Eisner.
Are we are we anywhere near the hundredth episode of this show?
Did we close?
Oh, we were close. If we're OK.
Well, if we're 80, I have this is 80 in my weird numbering system.
They were just for me.
I'm going to tease a little something.
Oh, I have a Michael Eisner related surprise that I will be really
that I will be sharing with you guys and the audience for the 100th episode.
Whoa, 100th episode spectacular.
Let that be an exciting.
I'm excited about this.
Almost as exciting as my father being on a lot to look forward to.
And that one out, that's a surprise.
Yeah. Oh, shoot.
I'm glad it's in this one.
Well, what have we missed?
You know, I don't think we like I don't think we really acknowledge.
I didn't talk about bedroom of the future.
Oh, please. Yes, which was the final room of the House of the Future.
And it was like a girl's room.
And it also had a tablet control.
But it also had like a smart mirror where you could virtually try on outfits.
And clueless.
Yeah. And it was very dated tech.
So it did not work well.
It was just kind of a hovering image of a cartoon outfit in front of your body
that like kind of synced up to your movements.
And we went in there today.
It would be readily that.
Yeah, that was something that you could easily do.
Probably on your phone.
No, you could probably do an app where you take a picture of yourself
and upload it to a site or something. I would imagine.
But they also had like a computer that I think had its own game of some kind.
But my sister went over to it and immediately hit control.
I'll delete, I guess, just to see what it did.
And it just crashed everything in the room.
And like the mirror had like an error warning that popped up
like on the smart mirror, which was obviously just a screen
hooked up to a computer that was in the same system.
And she was like, oh, oh, no, something happened.
And I was just immediately like, we have to go.
And I just like physically dragged her out of the room.
I was like, I want to be out of this house of the future
before someone notices that you broke it.
But yeah, that's my strongest memory about the house of the future.
Were you worried that the control all delete would also turn the Osmos evil?
Yes. Everything's going south, which they couldn't.
They can really chase after you.
But if you were running outside and one of them was trying to start to jog
after us, but fall over back.
No gods, no masters, no god.
But it would remember my face after it looked at me.
So, yeah, you're never really clear.
If you went back four years later.
Yeah.
You might like lightly try to punch you start walking toward you and never tire.
Take this. It's like it follows.
But with Osmo,
yeah, that's a good idea.
He's slow, but he doesn't stop.
It might take it might be like 12 years, but he will track you down.
And he might need a stranger to like put him back on his feet.
Please help.
I don't think we acknowledged enough that they
suckered the Sherman Brothers into doing a new right.
But they really reassize it.
Yeah. And in this opening special that I found, they you can see them
singing the new song.
No. Yeah.
They're still alive.
Someone else read it. The lyrics.
No, they like we did it.
He had a song about sports.
He had a song about the house.
I think they did it.
I think they wrote that's devastating.
You can say I found the video.
I'll send it. I'll send around.
They you can see them go.
It's a great big world of in a bench.
It kind of crushes your spirit.
It's like, I don't know.
It has a vibe. It's it feels like I like watching the guy.
And this is when they were both still alive.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's even sadder.
What if it was the one guy's last work?
It could have been man.
Although he's the surviving one, the lyricist or the melody man.
I think the lyricist that's still alive.
Well, Robert is a or Richard is alive and he's the guy who played the piano.
Oh, OK.
The other one's just kind of sitting there.
He oh yeah, he would.
He is the one who clearly saw some stuff in the war.
Yeah, he was the one who came back from the war.
He was like injured and he had PTSD, right?
Something. Yeah.
I'm like probably undiagnosed because it was the olden days.
Right. They're just like, yeah, just get over it.
Yeah. Yeah. If you're a man, you'll be fine.
But then, yeah, stuff it down.
Yeah. But then he would come up with like some whimsical lyric about something.
He was lyricist guy. Yeah.
Oh, so like the weird like the the stuff that makes you cry,
like the feed the birds kind of stuff. Yeah.
Well, so the reason I asked is because that is sadder because the only one
that really had to redo anything for InnoVentions was the lyrics guy.
So it may well have been his last work.
Oh, my God, we have to look at it.
If it was the last work of the melody man, I'd be like, well, he already wrote the melody.
So that's not sad.
Right. They did that musical, right?
Didn't they? Wasn't there a Chitty Chitty Bang Bang musical that they did some new songs for?
Oh, yeah. Maybe that's right.
Like a stage. Yeah, yeah.
I ran in the West End. You're right. You're right.
I've run long at the West End.
Yeah. I forget. Yeah.
But they what a nice way to go out to like write, you know,
like there is a man named Dr.
Bones to find him just beyond the future home.
I don't think that I don't think they'll know.
Pretty good. That would have been pretty. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Your phones disappear into TV.
Now go try some virtual reality.
The example they showed in one of the specials of virtual reality was the magic carpet ride.
Oh, yeah, there was a real look at the Disney Disney Quest one.
Well, it looks like a primitive version of the Disney Quest one that goes.
And they had that in California.
I think it was in Orlando.
I also don't know how far.
But that sounds good.
The my other favorite thing of the opening
is when the the guy who was the representative for Sega
says the phrase in the most monotone voice,
the Sega experience is going to be overwhelming.
We might just have to do a commentary track for that special.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
You know, I wrote down who that guy is, Tom Kalinsky, who's a major figure in Sega history.
I didn't look into it too much.
But like if you're apparently the book, Console Wars, which now I do want to read.
Yeah, he's responsible for a lot of Sega innovation,
interventions, including the scream.
He like pushed the scream.
This is our Sega. Oh, really?
I don't know if he thought of it, but he's the guy who's like, that is our hook.
Sega. So that boring guy was the guy who thought it was memorable.
I know Sega. That's it's memorable.
That's a scream.
I don't know. Well, that's when that's when it's turned on.
That's when you turn it on.
OK, yeah, that's the Genesis startup sound.
I think they dropped it.
Well, I'm sure that you're discovering now that I didn't have a Genesis.
That's why I know none of us were Genesis kids.
I had a Genesis. I had a Genesis.
You said you were a Nintendo house. I was a Nintendo house. Hey, boy.
That was our six. We we so we got in.
I think when I was like in second grade, we got Nintendo.
See, all right. Lindsay was a Genesis kid and she is proud.
In fifth grade, I think we got a Genesis.
And then when I was in seventh grade, we've got an N64.
We always got the systems when it was a little into the like a couple
years into the life run when you would get like Disney to.
Well, sure.
Yeah, so we had and then eventually once my brother, my brother was very good
at saving his money to get new games and systems and stuff.
And that's when I sort of faded out from from video games.
Checked out a bit.
Did anyone have a dream cast? No, no, but I loved playing the demos and stores
like they were good about getting those demos and stores.
And I would love to play.
What was it? Knights Knights?
Yeah, Knights. The first Sonic Adventure had a great demo.
Yes. First level in the cool cut scene with like chaos breaking out of the building.
And you'd go, what's that? Oh, my God.
Good for Sonic.
Any any closing thoughts about interventions before we wrap it up?
I mean, what what can you say about an attraction like interventions?
I mean, what would we how would we plus it up?
I was going to be my question.
What would you guys do if you got if you were in charge of the new
interventions project?
You guys mean you don't like spectacular brought you by Marotta
electronic components?
The one thing to current clients is is the color topia and then spectacular.
Inventions West entirely closed in 2015,
and they claimed they were going to do something with it.
Nothing has really happened.
I believe that you some of it is still in there behind the scene.
I think you can see it on the YouTube channel for that back to our Disney
account, an account that seems to constantly be having a very normal one,
very regular.
Oh, just a balanced guy.
Just really.
Everything seems great over there.
He's definitely in like a great time in his life.
It's having a normal one all the time.
So yeah, a lot of the 90s kind of design stuff still hanging out in there.
So who knows what will happen?
Oh, interesting fact, I learned this is probably more for the communicator one.
Those buildings were built so high because they blew sky early on.
We're thinking about putting a people mover,
connecting them where you could look down.
Wow.
It's a breeze.
Oh, yeah, that would have taken it up a real.
So I think that like an actual like more science driven,
because I think like Cornell University did sponsor some exhibits at some point.
So a more science and academic and nonprofit driven one, I would be interested.
So is that what you would do if you could decide more science?
Yeah, more science stuff and a people mover to oversee it all.
More sonic is what I say.
Sonic the Hedgehog. Yeah.
Why can't they get sonic?
Make all of the things sonic.
So it's a health exhibit, but it's sonic and you're like running.
And then you could see Sonic and Tails or Amy.
Who was Amy a character?
Yes. Amy Rose. Amy Rose.
Right. Come on, Mike.
Well, I forget because I stopped playing.
I'm a big Sonic fan, but I can't could show up.
Those are the characters.
Big the Cat.
I'm only tangentially familiar with that when they introduce all those characters.
So I know. Look, I'm an old school
rotor guy from the Archie comics.
I read the walrus and Sally.
And what was it?
A little fox with the Colonel's outfit on Antoine.
I was waiting. Yes.
I was way into that.
I was a way into the ABC cartoon.
Antoine was definitely the weirdest concept.
Yeah, he wore like a little generals outfit.
He was a Frenchman and his character trait was that he was a coward.
Yes. He was a one joke character.
And they always had to like phonetically write out his French accent.
I'm sure they really just busted it.
So Vichy France exists in Sonic canon.
Funny Sonic cartoon or dark Sonic cartoon?
Oh, dark all the way. Yeah.
Funny. I didn't care for that much.
And there was a lot of like the Sonic Saturday morning one
where everyone's getting roboticized.
Yes. Maybe it was dark.
And I really liked it.
They were both your little white voiced.
But I think they put all the characters.
You can meet all the characters, theme, all these like loose
corporate things to whatever Sonic and his character.
Fantastic.
Now you got me in there.
Maybe it's a little chintzy, but it's tied to an IP that I love.
And it's done deal. I'm into it.
It's a go Sonic.
Oh, wait. Well, let me tie it to an IP I love.
You said Jaleel White.
This is one fact that I missed that interventions was the home
of the invention of the year contest in the Disney World episode of Family Matters.
This was the first public demonstration
of the transformation machine that turned Steve Urkel into Stefan or Kel.
Laura broke off a piece so that he would stay stuck.
Stefan or Kel.
But so, you know, this the machine had only been used in the Winslow's
basement or wherever Urkel lived.
This is the first public demonstration of it.
This is science history.
This is pop culture history.
Yep. The first place.
And he ended up David Lander from Laverne and Shirley challenged.
He had a suitcase car, which initially worked better.
People did not believe that the transformation machine was real and really worked.
In a really stirring emotional two parter, eventually
spoiler Urkel bests David Lander and wins the contest.
So if you'll carve out a little bit of Sega for me to constantly tribute.
Would it be an animatronics driven dark ride conveying the story you just told us?
Hell, yeah.
Yeah, it could be a full ride because it's again, the moral is it's better
to stay the way you are and never leave your home.
Hmm. Yeah.
Like you mean like so it's like a little like morality tale.
Yeah, but now Urkel singing at the end.
It's better to stay the way you are.
If and also like doing the snow white witch effect, but a fun version
where you're looking in a mirror and it's Urkel and then he turns and he turns
around and you see the back of normal Urkel and instead of, you know,
shoving an apple in your face, he's offering you a rose, a rose,
a rose for you, my lady.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
Stefano Urkel's famous catchphrase and of course, yeah.
So put that I want Stefano Urkel presence and if not burn it to the ground
for insurance money, except for the electric umbrella restaurant,
which I like because it looks like a 90s Edwards movie.
Oh, OK. It's sick.
Yeah, we can all agree on that.
I have two ideas for what to go for.
Yeah. OK. For California.
My first idea when I didn't know what I know now is I for a long time
wanted the interventions building to become the new Q building for something
utilizing the people mover track.
Yeah. Because it used to load from the building that's now Buzz Lightyear.
They couldn't use that anymore.
So I was like, that's plenty of space to put like a big wrap around Q
and loading bay on the upper deck.
And it's attached to the people mover track already.
Yeah. But then I found out that, A, the people mover track is no longer complete.
It has a big chunk out of it at the Buzz Lightyear building.
But they could rebuild that.
But the bigger issue is that it's no longer to code
and they'd have to totally redo all of it to ever use it again.
So if we're going with the actual budget that might be given to an
innoventions project, I would decide that in like Florida's
Tomorrowland, my favorite thing, which is now gone, is
all the set dressing things like the electric palm trees, the robot newsy.
The phone of the future.
So for me, I'm taking a page out of the Mickey Mouse house in Toontown
and doing the equivalent of that, but for like fun future ambiance.
And that would just be the interior of innoventions is different scenery
of fun, futuristic things that are also photo ops to appeal to the Instagram
generation, who likes to go to those pop up museums and take pictures with everything.
And if it's something more involved, like a ball pit or something,
there's like a line for it.
But otherwise, you just wander around and take pics.
I feel like this is probably a silly question to ask.
Would push the trash can be there?
Yes, of course. Great.
I'm on board.
And then, you know, one room can have like a single animatronic
of like sunny eclipse type that's maybe performing or something.
Sounds good to me.
And maybe this is a good time to say, Jenny, have two ideas.
Oh, yes. That was the second one.
That was the first one. OK, great.
And it's a perfect pop up. Perfect.
Yeah. Well, you maybe already we've I'm sure we already said this on Twitter
as you hear this, but if you want to hear more from Jenny,
we are doing our first ever park hopper.
If you want to hear more, you can.
You can hop over to the second gate, our Patreon,
where you will hear us talk about sunny eclipse along the way to top.
So we've wanted to talk to you about for a while.
And I always want to talk about it.
Yes, I think this will be this will be an easy breezy go
for us to talk about sunny eclipse, who if somehow you don't know the character,
the lounge singer alien in Tomorrowland in Disney World,
who plays in the hamburger restaurant.
Yes, in cosmic.
Two empty crowds.
Yes, often empty.
To talk about him for a while.
So that so that to say that if you head over to the Patreon,
then this is not the end of Jenny Nicholson this week.
But for this specific episode, Jenny Nicholson, you survived.
But that's the ride.
Thanks for being back.
Much appreciated.
Any any time, really?
What a fun topic as well.
Oh, thanks for bringing it to us.
I know. I was pulling for InnoVentions.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah, you got it.
Very on board. No complaints from us.
That was that was a blast.
Oh, wait a second.
And if you listen to the Patreon first and you're hearing this second.
Thank you. I don't have any.
Yep.
Just a reminder that InnoVentions is a portmanteau of invention and innovation.
Sure.
Jenny, do you want to exit through the gift shop real quick?
Plug, plug all your stuff.
Yes, let me exit through the gift shop.
I'm Jenny Nicholson on everything on Twitter, on YouTube.
That's it.
OK. Watch my stuff.
I do funny videos about sometimes theme parks, sometimes movies,
sometimes just miscellaneous things I want to talk about.
Sure. Yeah.
You do. Yeah, you do great stuff.
Yeah, my channel doesn't have a theme anymore.
It's just whatever I talk about.
That's great. Yeah.
Why? Yeah. Don't don't box yourself in.
Exactly. Yeah. Yeah, indeed.
So and for us, as we said, go to patreon.com slash.
Pug has the right, especially right now, because exciting stuff's happening right now.
And otherwise, check us out on Twitter or on Facebook or on Instagram
or there's a Reddit where things are happening.
And anything else?
No, I think that's it. We're good. Great.
Sounds good. All right.
Hey, we hope you hop parks.
We'll see you there at the second gate. Bye bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.