Five, four, three, two, one.
To RHCP at DLR on PTR 2G.
That's right, today you didn't ask for it.
Today we are talking about the red hot chili peppers
takeover of Disneyland.
You remember it in the spring of 2007, right?
For four months.
Well look, my name is Mike Carlson here.
Podcast right here.
Oh, I didn't introduce yourself.
Yeah, I'm big SG.
Yeah, and I'm a.
King of the space rockers.
Little, I'm a tall MC.
The other space rocker.
I'm Jason Sheridan, and I don't believe I asked
for this either.
Yeah, well, yeah, why this?
Why are we doing this?
Why are we talking about the red hot chili peppers
being the soundtrack of two rides at Disneyland?
Well, because I was at Disneyland a couple days ago,
and I was in a crowd, and somebody behind me
was talking about it, and I remembered,
because of that, that it happened and was funny,
and I texted you guys, and now we're doing it.
Wait, yeah, I think we were both immediately on board.
Thanks to that person for reminding me
of the Celestrius affair.
Yeah, this is very much in our wheelhouse.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, limited run option.
Limited run magic that's also a little odd.
A little confusing.
And pop culture mashing up with theme park culture
in a strange way, which this certainly is.
My first time going on Screamin' and Space Mountain
was soundtracked by the red hot chili peppers.
No kidding, wow.
Well, then I'm so glad we brought, wow, you'd never,
I mean, you've done it in Florida, obviously,
but not your first Disneyland taste.
Right, because I didn't go to Disneyland
until I moved out here in 2007.
No kidding, wow.
So yeah, it's wild.
So in your mind, the proper version.
Yeah, the real version of Space Mountain
is with the red hot chili peppers
playing on the space stage.
Playing on, they're setting up on the space stage.
This is one where the explanation of the topic
is pretty fast, as I said, in the spring of 2007,
a limited Disney promotion that was actually called
Rockin' Both Parks, that's the name.
Everything about this is so lazy.
And like a generic ass looking like billboard too.
That was like.
Mickey's ears, but they're like subwoofers.
Right, and it doesn't say what,
it does say, well, it says red hot chili peppers,
but it's in like the most boring font.
Well, and I found a map that also has the branding
for Year of a Million Dreams on it,
which was a thing they did, I think for longer than a year,
but like lots of different,
like maybe you'll get a free pair of,
I think I got a free pair of mouse ears one day
when I walked in the park,
and other people got to stay in the dream suites.
Like.
Maybe not as good.
Not as good.
This is like 2007 is like they're giving annual passes away.
Yeah, true.
Yeah, much cheaper.
I wonder how much cheaper if you go back.
Oh, you can find it online.
Yeah, I mean, I was shocked.
I think one of the things,
because I didn't know, I didn't even consider,
I've said this before on the show,
like I didn't consider the idea that you would have a pass
and you could go all the time.
It was like.
I didn't either.
I don't know that I really did it,
maybe until a couple years ago.
Yeah.
I did it in 2008.
I had been living out here about a year.
My dad and brother came out to visit
and stayed down at the Grand Californian,
and I think I had a three or four day park hopper,
and at the front desk, they're like, oh, you're local.
You can convert this to an annual pass when it's done.
And you credit to it, and I think at the time,
I did not have to give a lot of money
for a decent annual pass.
Lindsay says, and I don't know,
this seems like it's insane,
but you could get a free ticket on your birthday to go in
and then use the free ticket
to take a piece of the price out.
I think that's right.
For the annual pass.
Because we were gonna do that.
We were in an improv class together,
we were gonna go down after it once.
Yeah, because I think,
either the first or second time I went down,
it was just like, oh yeah, you can get this
and it's $200 and you can go 280 days out of the year,
and it's a lot of, maybe a few Saturdays in the summer,
I guess one of the tiers is now.
And yeah, it's $200, and I was like, what?
Like, whoa, whoa, whoa?
I can't believe that this is a thing.
So that's obviously, that really re-kickstarts
my obsession with all this stuff.
Yeah, this is after the 50th anniversary,
but before California Adventure getting redone.
Not good, yeah.
Right.
So it's like, it's kind of a,
I think it's a lull in park history.
It's a, I don't wanna say it's a,
like a mark on the.
Well, nothing great had been added for a while.
Like, especially to Disneyland proper.
So they're trying to find ways to.
How are we gonna make everyone come to the park?
What are we going to do?
You know, I remember coming the first time
in like the end of August, 2006,
I did a semester in LA for college.
The second or third day I was here,
like one of the guys who I was living with,
their girlfriend was visiting for a few days
before she started school back in Ithaca.
And she, he's like, well, we all wanna go to Disneyland.
I'm like, yeah, let's, yeah, let's do that.
And I had been in Orlando that summer
and the Magic Kingdom was in not great shape
in the summer of 2006 when I was there.
It was looking a little beat up.
The Disneyland park, summer of 2006,
still pretty fresh off that anniversary.
Everything had just been painted.
Everything looked really nice.
Everything was running really well.
So I was, I was very impressed.
Oh, and also the food, because the food,
maybe even still like Anaheim has better food.
Better, oh, certainly.
The quick service especially.
That specifically.
Especially in the recent past.
Yeah, they're stepping it up.
But yeah, oh, well, this pristine, beautiful park.
What better to do with it than to trash it
like a hotel room with the help of the ultimate
rap scallions.
Yeah, interestingly.
2007's most popular rock group.
Hell yeah.
2007. When was the last album?
When was the last Chili Peppers album?
In 2007 or recently, I mean.
One in like 2005 or 2006.
Before this, yeah, they had a Stadium Arcadium.
Right.
Which was a double album, which came out
when I was in my last year of college.
Or second to last year of college.
So yeah, like 2005, 2006.
Double the bass slap.
And the hit, they had a hit on that.
The hit on that is Danny, California.
Yeah.
Which sounds like Last Dance with Mary Jane by Tom Patty.
Oh yeah, so it does.
But it's in a very familiar chorus about California.
That's a theme they sing about a lot.
Californication was on an earlier album.
2009.
On the album entitled Californication.
Which I think, believe on the podcast,
one of my favorite moments is you realizing
what Californication meant.
Yes, that it has the word fornication in it.
Oh, because we talked about this for a sec.
This must have spurred that conversation.
So I think maybe I mentioned this then.
I think it's crystallized a little more for me now.
My relationship with Red Hot Chili Peppers
is they were just ubiquitous when I was a kid.
They were ubiquitous.
I have never paid any money for an album, a t-shirt,
anything, but I have somehow absorbed them,
but not processed them.
Because reading about these two songs,
reading the lyrics to these two songs,
the Red Hot Chili Peppers might be one of the main bands
where when I read the lyrics, I go,
that's what they were saying?
That's what that lyric was in that?
Because to us, it's just,
umbo-dee-ba-dum-ba-dub-busky-bo.
Pretty much, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, I don't really like them.
I don't dislike them.
They're one of those, hey, they're around,
you guys do your thing.
I have no objections to anything that they do or wanna do.
It's just not what I listen to.
I was way into Red Hot Chili Peppers.
I think that a lot of things, I came to them late.
I wasn't listening to popular music
until I was 16 or something.
Yeah, same, yeah.
I knew Sugar Sugar by the Archies.
I could sing Leaning on a Lamp Post by Herman's Hermits, sure,
but I didn't know the popular music of the day
until I started listening to Q101 in Chicago.
So I think the first album of theirs I liked
was Californication.
And then, very famously to tie it back to Disney,
I bought their classic Blood Sugar Sex Magic
at the Virgin Megastore in downtown Disney.
I see.
In a trip that happened very soon after that.
So I got way into the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
Their follow-up, By the Way, I was obsessed with.
I was listening to By the Way in preparation for this
and going, some of these songs are good.
I was like reliving my, whatever, 2003.
I like that, I like By the Way, I like Californication.
There's a couple songs on By the Way.
I was like, is By the Way the best album?
I feel like I'm gonna, after you guys leave,
I will make a Red Hot Chili Peppers playlist.
I will put all the hits in my mind
and I'll share it with the listeners.
Oh, maybe I can make it only Patreon exclusive.
You can, but it's next post in Patreon.
What's gonna happen is people are gonna be sharing the link
because people are gonna be so wanting to see
what I pick as some of my favorite Red Hot Chili Peppers songs.
They're gonna go re-viral with your curation.
It's gonna kick off, like when a band gets a song
in a big movie, it's gonna be a big deal for RHCP
to have the MC stamp.
So I was way into them.
I think I had the What Hits album as well,
which had some of the older songs,
some of the pre-Blood Sugar Sex Magic songs.
And I saw them a couple times in kind.
I saw them at Lollapalooza one year.
They were on the Simpsons episode, right?
Yeah, yeah.
No, they were there in Krusty's last episode.
Oh, oh, Dancer Under Underwear.
Yeah, they're with Johnny Carson and Bette Midler.
Yeah, yeah, and it's kind of a nod to the doors
where Krusty comes in and tries to get him
to change their lyrics to something nice
and they can see to it.
What you got, I gotta get him, put it in you,
change to what I want is I wanna love and hug
and kiss you or something, is that the one?
Yeah.
And then he goes, the other line that's really good
in that episode is when he goes,
look at him dancing around in underwear,
so demeaning or something, and they go,
Krusty, five minutes to your little stinker sketch.
And he goes, I want a bigger lolly.
And they give him a giant lollipop.
I love in that episode when they all come into Moe's naked
and all say hi to Moe and then there's the big, hey Moe!
That's a very funny animation, a funny performance.
I also remember the Californication music video,
was he jumping through a video game level?
Well, it looked like Crazy Taxi or something.
Yes.
That was the music video for that.
That was the third single, I believe,
on Californication after.
Which is interesting,
because Crazy Taxi was a lot of offspring.
Well, it was only offspring.
It was only offspring.
I believe that first Crazy Taxi just played that one,
ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, for many hours and levels.
I think there are other songs
and I think they put out a soundtrack for it.
I think it is largely offspring.
That's a good question.
All I watch is the name of it?
You can get it on your phone now for free.
So, I would, that was a thing I remember as a kid,
going to Sears' video game sections
when my mom was shopping and just playing
the Crazy Taxi demo again and again.
Yeah, so I was way into them.
In college, when I started getting into the cooler stuff,
I still got Stadium Arcadium.
And I was like, I like four or five of these songs,
but it was starting to wane a little bit.
And then I kind of fell off with them.
I've heard the singles,
and I was listening to some singles earlier.
I was like, no, okay.
But there's, I would argue that there's at least,
like Flea is such a good bassist.
And like, if you like music at all,
you'd be like, I can listen to this bass line
independent of any dumb sex lyric
that's in these songs and go,
well, that's a really cool bass line.
Like that's.
Yeah, I think they're all amazing musicians
and the various guitarists who've been part of it
are all fantastic.
And I love John Fuschanti,
who was the guitarist for many of these albums.
And he's got weird solo albums.
He's not in the band anymore.
He does a cover of How Deep Is Your Love,
that's on YouTube, that is so great.
Like he's got such a weird,
he has like the high parts on all the songs,
but he's a fascinating character
that I'm very intrigued by.
So anyway.
I've set my piece on the road.
That's a lot more than the two.
Mike has enough like of them for the two of us.
Yes.
That's true.
And then some.
But I think the main thing is what in 2007,
I don't know, I guess it wasn't that insane.
And you need like a name band.
Look, like giving a roller coaster to Aerosmith.
I think it's hard for Disney to have a relationship
with a rock band and to do something that's not,
to do something that's name, but actually current.
And I don't know.
For sure.
I think it's clearly doing the rock and roller coaster model.
Yeah.
Like it's, they're just trying to go,
all right, we'll just make it a radio station.
And like, that's sort of the lead up to the ride.
And what band like Aerosmith is there?
And I think I said this on the rock and roller coaster
episode that I feel like Aerosmith and the red
and chili peppers are very similar in some ways.
Like these bawdy, dirty lyrics,
like pseudo-rappy kind of vocals in a lot of songs.
I don't know.
They're both sleazy bands in a lot of ways.
So like, it feels right.
I feel like that's, even though it's like 10 years later.
Yeah, man, they'll wear like a top hat
and a feather boa and stick their tongue out.
These guys are fucking wild.
They're so crazy.
So yeah, it feels like somebody going,
well, let's just do the rock and roller coaster here.
And maybe it's a whole,
because they were talking about actually doing
a rock and roller coaster here and it got canned.
With no doubt.
Which is interesting then.
That's a great idea.
Why didn't they just do no doubt then?
Yeah, and you get a second roller coaster
in California Adventure.
I mean, money is the answer, probably.
But yeah, so this was this like temporary overlay
just to sort of a gimmick to get people in.
Did anyone specifically go for this only?
Oh, it's a good question, isn't it?
Did anyone not have an annual pass and I need to go?
Gotta be some chili pepper fans who went.
I texted before we started this,
I texted Doug Jones,
who is a big Red Hot Chili Peppers fan.
And I was just like, hey, we're doing this episode
about the Red Hot Chili Pepper overlay on these rides.
And Doug's obviously a huge Disneyland fan too.
I go, do you have any memories of that?
And like, Doug is very into the music scene and you know,
he knows stuff about all this.
Music scene.
I said it like an old man, like sure.
He's, he knows what the kids like.
And Doug said, I should just read what he said.
He, hold on one second.
Where do I have it?
It's, this is a podcasting.
Get all those phonographs out of the way, Mr. Music.
I said, Doug said, I was not aware of that
while it was going on.
I only learned about it afterwards
and I've only read what's online.
I don't really have any insight.
I'm a Red Hot Chili Peppers fan,
but it seems out of place to have their music at Disney.
So Doug didn't even know.
And didn't know and doesn't like the sound of it now.
Yeah, he's a hardcore Disney and Red Hot Chili Peppers fan.
Wasn't even on his radar.
Maybe the exact audience for this.
That's why I was like, oh, I'm gonna text Doug.
I know Doug will know something about this
or at least be like, yeah, I remember that.
And we went down and we were so excited.
No, he was there at the time.
Didn't even know what was happening.
I texted Nick Mundy about this,
not cause I just unrelatedly.
And together we came upon a Chili Peppers determination
that we wish we could have seen.
I wish I could go to a concert by the animated band
that they voice essentially in Beavis and Butthead
do America.
Cause they're these like lounge lizard sleaze bags,
these retro 70s men, but who sing like the Chili Peppers.
If I could put like Gorillaz style,
see the Beavis and Butthead version of them live.
If it was 10 years later,
you may have been able to do that
cause they did figure out like how do Gorillaz shows work.
And the answer early on was they play in silhouette
and there's a lot of original animation.
Nowadays, I don't know if they even bother
with the silhouettes.
They haven't done that in a while.
That's my plus up for the idea of the Gorillaz in general
is that the opening act should have always been.
Cartoon Chili Peppers.
Here's my plus up, just put blur back together
with the band I like.
Decent plus up.
You don't like Gorillaz?
No, I do like Gorillaz.
But I think Damon Albert usually tempered,
tempered by Graham, by his blur counterpart, Graham.
Oh, I see.
The thing about the music scene too,
don't sell yourself short on the music scene.
I like the music stuff.
I like the Brit Pop, 90s Brit Pop,
the less popular one of the two.
I think there's a couple of years
where you're like really into like new pornographers
and you're like, there's a college rock zone
where you live in.
You know what it was?
It was like the golden age of MP3 blogs.
When blogs would, every entry would be about a new MP3
and then at the bottom of the blog entry,
you could just steal the MP3.
You could just have the MP3.
You know, Gorilla versus Shark, Flux Blog,
like all of those things.
Yeah, me, I don't go for the SoundCloud rap.
I'm more of a LimeWire rap guy.
Oh sure.
I like Kazaa.
Yeah, they call me when it's Kazaa again.
I'll do an Audio Galaxy rap any day.
This was clearly we're veering from this being
a quick episode.
There's not a lot of records of this.
No, not really.
I was literally spent 10 minutes going like,
I know there's a Yesterland page about this
where I can at least start and there's not.
Even Yesterland is not really cataloged.
There's not a lot of info.
So here, I'm gonna go in reverse order
of how much there is to talk about
so here's what happened.
They put a song on the biggest roller coaster
in Disneyland and California Adventure.
In California Adventure, that is what is now
the Incredicoaster, the time was California Screaming
and that, wait, the song is Around the World.
Yes, correct.
Just kind of slapped on.
Yes.
Not really set up.
Well, no.
They did re-record, I mean, they recorded new stuff for it.
They remixed it.
Recorded new stuff?
Yes.
Yeah, hang on.
Hold on a second.
The lyrics, they kind of recut,
so it skips a couple lyrics for the length.
I cannot find good documentation of this.
There are guitar solos in this version
that do not appear on the album version.
There is a whole outro jam that appears
in the roller coaster that is not on the album.
Huh, well, that's interesting.
I know they remixed it and also,
there are, they change up verses.
First of all, there's some dirty lyrics on the song.
They cut and paste, the first verse on the roller coaster
is a combination of all three verses.
They have chopped up the lyrics.
Wow.
In different ways, just, I guess,
probably to get rid of anything that's suggestive.
So they took Krusty's advice.
So they did take Krusty's advice to the roller coaster,
but I think from the sound of it,
unless they had just leftover takes from,
maybe they tried stuff on, in the studio,
there's for sure new stuff in the version of
Around the World on California Screamin'.
No kidding, wow.
Well, I really like the idea of an alternate mix
of a song that I like that you can only experience
by going on a roller coaster.
That is a fantastic idea that more people should deploy.
In this case, I'm going in this order
because Space Mountain had,
the Space Mountain version had 10% more to talk about.
This essentially is the same ride,
but with a new soundtrack.
Some might say much like the Incredicoaster.
Yeah, fair enough.
It's so, that's not true.
I like all the tunnels and everything.
And obviously we figured out that a rock song
is not the optimal soundtrack to that ride.
It was always meant to be a woman searching for her infant.
There's no other way to experience those specific
dips and loops. Of course.
So, and unlike Space Mountain, there's just, there's no,
we'll get into Space Mountain,
and like just, you know, lighting effects or whatever.
And the kind of this intro as you go up the hill.
This is just sort of the song plays.
Fine, innocuous, whatever.
Cool, I don't know.
I don't know if I like the song so much.
I'll say that.
I don't know.
Doesn't this one feel to you?
Do you like the song or,
because to me it's like being just casually aware of them.
I'm like, it's kind of their tricks.
Dibba, dabba, da, dabba, dabba, da, da.
I cannot sing it in my head right now.
I'm staring at the lyrics.
I can't produce this.
We're talking about Around the World.
Yes. Yeah.
I can sing it.
Yeah, if you want me to.
I'm not going, I mean, all around the world
we can make time roughing and a-stomping
because I'm in my prime, born in the North,
just want to entertain ya,
cause I'm down for the state of Pennsylvania.
I try not to whine, but I must warn ya
about the motherfucking govern California.
Alabama baby say hallelujah.
Good God girl.
Wish I knew ya, I think is the first verse.
So I do know it pretty well.
It's not, it's not one of my favorites though.
I will say that.
I do think when you take off on the, in the launch,
I think that part is cool with the,
like that intro part is cool.
But then I don't think it makes any sense
for the roller coaster to have that boom, boom, boom, boom.
Like it loses its propulsion at that point.
Yeah. They're pretty unrelated.
It's a weird, it's a weird choice for that.
So I don't know.
Yes, Jason.
So I think one thing about the Chili Pepper,
I feel like I never know the names of their songs.
I think the songs are called whatever the chorus was.
So this song, I feel like I mentally refer to
as I know for sure.
Sure. Sure.
I know for sure.
This song also has one of the most problematic outros,
I think, and they don't have it on the ride,
is where Anthony Kiedis sings in fake Asian Chinese,
where he goes ding, dong, ding, dong, ding, dang,
dong, dong, ding, dang.
Oh yeah, he does.
Yeah, it's bizarre.
Certainly, I think that probably holds up less well
than almost any other terrible dirty thing in the songs.
That's probably not true.
We probably could comb through it
and find more problematic stuff.
Yeah, not one of my favorite songs,
but I do kind of like that intro part
where it's like fast up the launch.
Sure, that part seemed to pair decent.
But it's a bizarre choice.
I don't know why this is the choice.
They have faster songs.
This wasn't even that big of a hit, I don't think.
So I don't even see them justifying it going like,
well, Around the World was such a big hit.
People are gonna clearly wanna hear them do that song.
I don't know.
And in my head, I was like,
I didn't go on California Screamin',
but I was like, well, it must be,
they must, I assume they are using Love Roller Coaster.
And they were not.
It's wild.
Yeah, it's right there.
Someone has to explain why they didn't do
Love Roller Coaster.
Clearance, because it's a cover.
I guess, but who is it though?
Who does the real players?
The Ohio players have been holding out for more money.
I mean, or whatever.
Higher ground is Stevie Wonder.
Sure.
How did they clear that?
Well, he's always playing at their Christmas specials.
So they had a good relationship with Stevie.
That's a good point.
Ohio players.
Also, maybe some shyster stole the copyright
of the Ohio players.
That's possible.
It happens to a lot of those bands.
It is, unless, if I look at the lyrics
to Love Roller Coaster, it's just so filthy.
Yeah.
But Ohio players, they were writing dirty stuff, right?
Roller Coaster of Love, I guess is that-
You could have just essentially made it,
and maybe that maybe writing someone that you love
is too dicey for Disney.
Yeah, maybe.
It's just that notion.
Like, I have the lyrics to Roller Coaster.
Roller Coaster of Love, say what?
Roller Coaster.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, Roller Coaster.
Oh baby, you know what I'm talking about of love.
Roller Coaster, oh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Like, whatever, that's fine.
I don't know, your love is like a roller coaster baby.
I wanna ride.
I guess that's it.
Yeah.
I guess it's like-
Maybe it's a problem.
Ride, but then they like used loving
and loving a roller coaster for Aerosmith.
Well, that's ridiculous, that concept.
And they play pink outside.
We know what that means.
And Steven Tyler was doing sex gesture for many decades.
So I don't know, I guess they thought
around the world was less problematic.
I don't know, well, let's go across the esplanade.
Let's rock across the esplanade.
Let's rock our way.
Let's do a rockin' park hop and talk about Space Mountain.
Or as it became known, well, we should,
it was rockin' California Screamin', not California rockin'.
And then across the way was rockin' Space Mountain.
Lazy, so lazy.
Really lazy.
I'm glad we're covering this now
because we can take this out
of our eventual Space Mountain episode.
We've just freed up 20 minutes of Tangent.
So real estate cleared.
So this thing, this worked better, I think, right?
And over here you get the cover
of Stevie Wonder's Higher Ground, as he said.
I should say, with songs from like 89 or something,
Mother's Milk is the album.
It's one of the first recordings
with John Franchante and Chad Smith.
So this is early, the classic lineup of the band.
And I hope that made me sound like a musicologist
or something to have even looked that up.
And here you got a little more going on
because there is a premise here.
And the premise is that, well, what is it?
The Red Hot Chili Peppers are due to perform
on the space stage.
So lazy, it's bad, frankly.
Every now and then when I make my notes for these episodes,
I will get so mad, I'll just write the phrase,
oh, fuck off, next to a note.
And the space, I think the Red Hot Chili Peppers
are about in the space stage.
There is a come on, fuck you, next to that.
There's not much there.
I like imagining though what it is.
So I just, I just imagine a floating platform.
I imagine them having like 60s cartoon,
just sort of that like scoop, like deep sea diver,
yeah, fishbowl helmet on with like a little air tube
in a backpack and they have the instruments.
They're probably naked too.
They have socks on their dicks or whatever.
They have dick shaped helmets.
Dick shaped helmets as well.
But they're on just like a floating stage in space.
And I don't know.
Yeah, that sounds cool.
They don't have time to explain what it is though.
I don't know, it's a long lift till I think
they could have fit that.
And now the space stage, keep in mind is,
so they've got a helmet on there.
Remember, no ins and outs.
You know what, they do that on Rock and Roller Coaster
because they go, wow, check out Steven Tyler's new hat.
So like they could have been like, look at,
the Red Hot Chili Peppers have socks on their dicks.
Like they could have said that.
There's a precedent for rock themed roller coasters
pointing out the clothing of the band.
So no excuse.
Just a reminder, if you think you're coming backstage,
you need the wristband and the lamby.
Just one of those won't get you very far.
How bad do you wanna fuck flea?
Um.
You mostly know him from his acting work.
That's gonna be the weirdest one I've heard all day.
I don't buy that for a second.
So, and this is narrated by the way by Uncle Joe.
Uncle Joe.
Uncle Joe is a DJ for 95.5 KLOS here in Los Angeles,
apparently owned by Disney.
Yeah.
Oh.
Synergy.
Yep, Uncle Joe Benson, who's on Twitter.
We should say hi to him and say he did a great job
and see if he writes us back.
So, and if he has any fun memories of recording this
over the course of four minutes.
He knocked it out in a session.
Over a decade ago.
So, well the other important point is that on the space stage
you don't broadcast, you broad blast.
Oh yeah.
The chili peppers will be broad blasting live.
I like that more, less lazy than space stage.
I'll give them that.
Yeah, that's good.
And what now, what does that mean?
Is somehow the kinetic energy of you on the rocket
like kind of shoving the radio waves into lights.
Are you like on the rocket carrying the sound waves
faster than the speed of sound?
Yeah, I think that it has to indicate that it's faster
than a normal radio wave.
So, it would have to be.
Well yeah, but broad blasting.
It's so much faster.
I like that a lot, yeah.
And then you hear some tune up and you hear a guy go like,
how about some of that bass?
Boom, do, do, do, do, do, do.
I can't tell, I can't, I wonder if that's Flea
or that's like another guy.
That's generic.
It's probably generic.
I think their participation was as minimal
as humanly possible.
As evidenced by the fact that they didn't do a press event,
they didn't play a concert, they didn't broad blast live
from Disneyland.
There was no photo.
I was on the mice chat message boards from 2007
and there was a rumor.
Bound in a book, in a leather band.
There was a rumor that they were gonna play
because someone goes, did you hear the rumor
that the Red Hot Chili Peppers are gonna play Disneyland?
And people are like, I have not heard that.
So, they did not turn up.
Probably they were trying to set it up
and then literally anything else came up
and they did that instead.
Yes.
I will say as far as their involvement,
I forget the guy's name.
I did find the guy who remixed the song.
Oh.
Who was like a major music producer.
I should look it up.
It's not Rick Rubin, their long-time producer.
Okay, but like maybe the actual producer,
mixer of the thing.
I think Rick Rubin did Californication though initially.
I was, you know, to this, on this topic,
I was trying to find if there was any other association
between the Red Hot Chili Peppers and Disneyland.
In Googling this, I found several results.
Anthony Kiedis in describing his adolescent life
full of drug use as a teenager,
he said that he described his life back then
on the Sunset Strip as being like an adult Disneyland.
So, there's one.
It's a negative thing more than anything.
I love that you're reading this out like a 60 minutes anchor.
And he described it as an adult Disneyland.
Also just side note is describing,
elaborating on why it's an adult Disneyland.
At some point, a naked share crawled into bed with him
when he was in the eighth grade.
Oh yeah, I've heard that story.
Wow.
Yeah, that's inappropriate.
Yeah, not great.
I don't wanna say it, cause it's just too weird.
There's a lot of like very problematic stuff
in his autobiography.
Uh oh.
Oh no.
That's all I'll say.
All right, I'll stay away from that then.
He's a rock star, man.
That's all he knows.
They had trouble keeping his autobiography in bookstores,
right?
Because it's titled, Give it Away, Give it Away,
Give it Away Now.
Man.
I don't even know.
I don't even know how we can continue after that.
We set a price.
Why aren't people paying the price?
What's the title?
Why does everyone want some sort of deep discount?
I Googled some other members of the band
to see if they have any fond Disneyland memories.
And I did find that in 1955,
when the castle was first built,
that it ended up being infested by a number of feral cats.
And the feral cats were carrying on them many fleas.
Uh huh.
Sure.
Um.
Oh, okay.
So stretch but true.
I don't know how we can continue after that.
Also, Walt's solution side track
to finding a bunch of flea cats in the castle
was to be very kind and give them out to the employees.
And when somebody told him,
maybe you shouldn't give all your employees fleas,
he then, they decided, oh, let's keep them around
and have them be the natural scavengers and hunters
of the rats that might end up in Disneyland,
which they are still to this day.
So those cats showed up, apparently,
that tradition goes back to before the park even opened.
Wow.
So there's your flea fact.
And hey, one more thing.
The Anaheim pepper is a red chili pepper
that is grown in Anaheim.
But it is mild.
You wouldn't call it a red hot chili pepper.
Why, if you consult the Scoville scale,
which of course measures the pungency of spicy foods,
you'll find that the Anaheim pepper
is eight times milder than a jalapeno.
Wow. Okay.
And those are all my results
of Googling red hot chili peppers.
That was the most wholesome content of the show.
There's not even a picture of Anthony Kiedis on the,
like there's a famous picture of Billy Corgan
on Big Thunder Mountain Railroad
from a couple of years ago looking very unhappy,
which he looks in general all the time, but.
He ought to go to the,
he shouldn't go to Universal Studios
on the Despicable Me rag
because he'd get mistaken for Gru.
Well, that's his place of business.
You're joking, but he looks a lot like Gru now.
Yeah, and I was never heard of me before.
Wow, that's crazy.
Wasn't he working for Impact Wrestling for a while?
Did he own it?
Well, no, he's certainly, he bought NWA Wrestling now.
So that's his new, but he did work for Impact for a while,
but now he is a full on like owner of NWA Wrestling.
Oh, okay.
And the reason supposedly that Darcy claims
that the Pumpkins went back on tour
with at least two of the three originals
is because he lost so much money investing it in wrestling.
She has a smart business to get into.
So he's back with the Pumpkins because he needs that money
and he's playing the hits.
And keeping his right wing views quiet.
And kind of.
Yeah.
Right now that picture pops up on the internet.
It's like, is that Billy Corrigan next to Alex Jones?
Yeah, you know, the globalists.
Anyway, Ryan Hewitt is the record producer
who was the record producer on Stadium Arcadium.
I see.
So he was just around and they were like,
we need to do this fucking Disney thing.
Which maybe, yeah, maybe he just went through
like what they were demoing.
And then some alt takes or whatever.
So let's get back on the lift hill
where we're preparing for the broad blast.
The Wikipedia that I read had this great description.
Finally, once riders crest the lift, the sun explodes.
Which I kind of on the way up, there's sort of like,
you know, instead of the typical space mountain patterns,
it's kind of like psychedelic lava lamp patterns.
I think the videos are not so good on this.
So it's hard to say exactly.
So this song I thought was either called People
or Power, because I misheard for many years.
I thought that first line was power
is people keep on learning.
This song I'm a little more familiar with
because the Power Rangers skydive to it
in Power Rangers is the movie.
Yeah, that is a hundred percent a soundtrack I owned
on cassette and has a, they might be giant song
called Sense Around that I really like.
Well, I miss that train.
You know, I had every other day.
Yeah, weird.
I miss that.
Oh, I gotta play that for you after this.
Yeah, that Power Rangers album.
What was that other big song on that?
Well, it was Trouble, I believe is the name of it.
By like an Australian teen girl group or something.
Like it was like, uh-oh, we're in trouble.
Trouble, someones going around
and they burst our bubble, yeah, yeah.
That's right, I recall that.
I didn't like that.
I didn't not like it, but I, oh, you know what?
Also, that's the first time I ever heard
one of my favorite Van Halen songs, Dream, Dreams,
excuse me, of a Hagar song, which I really liked too.
It's been a lot of money on the music
for the Power Rangers really.
But that wasn't for the movie though,
but I bet they licensed it.
Yeah, I don't know, Dreams probably was not.
Not inspired specifically by the Power Rangers.
They didn't write it thinking about.
Like man, they're all separate beings
that all unite into a greater whole.
Just like us.
And their skydiving jumpsuits match which color Rangers are.
Damn, good point, Alex.
Yeah.
Van Halen.
I think Dreams has some of the dumbest lyrics in any song,
but I love it.
I was gonna say, oh, I didn't know,
I don't think I heard the Stevie Wonder version
of Higher Ground for years.
Yeah, yeah.
You were surprised. I'm sure I knew.
I was like, oh, huh, Stevie Wonder covered
the Red Chili Peppers song.
Huh, that's cool.
He must be into cool music like I am.
Well, I think that this song is a better,
I think it delivers on the promise of the Chili Peppers
being this mashup of 80s Grammy rock and funk.
P-funk, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It's pretty good.
This is about as quality of a rock track
as you're gonna hear it on a Disney ride.
Yeah, I think this is a good pick for this.
I mean, obviously not as good as Roller Coaster,
love Roller Coaster, but yeah, this is a high energy song.
It's fun probably to listen to while you're zooming around.
And the lighting, like they made it look like
there were spotlights and stuff, stadium lighting.
I will say I would not mind like after nine o'clock,
it's Rock and Space Mountain
and they cycle songs in and out.
I would not.
That was the plan.
Yes, you're right.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, sad.
Well, yeah, because the setup for this,
before they hatched the Chili Peppers plan,
they were set up to do all of this
and had put in screens and such
because they auditioned this idea at Grad Night 2006
in which they were kind of half-heartedly calling it
Rock It Mountain, like Rock It Mountain.
So the Giacchino song, pretty new.
And that was what I read was that there is a collection
of soundtrack of the park and it labels the Giacchino
Space Mountain song as like daytime theme.
Oh, oh, so they were gonna regularly maybe.
So they were gonna like at night,
it was gonna switch over.
This was on Disney.fandom.com, the entry for,
that actually did have an entry for Rock and Space Mountain.
I'll say though, the screen made my mouse
turn into a little Mickey hand,
specifically a little Mickey pointy finger.
Not wild about that, it's what he died to.
Calm down, disney.fandom.com.
Yeah, first time, not necessary anymore.
So, but they were gonna, yeah,
they were thinking at some point like,
all right, it'll be spacey in the day
and it'll be rock and roll at night.
Now, I know because Jason and I sidebarred,
I know that we know what was played
during Grad Night 2006.
Do you know this fact?
I don't.
This is what we were hoping for.
Hit me.
The first rock song ever played on Space Mountain.
Hit me, baby.
Play it and then announce it.
Without, oh, okay, all right.
Strap on the headphones.
I'm ready, I'm ready for this, I'm excited.
You'll know it right away because it's an iconic track.
And that's all I have.
What the hell is that?
Why, of course, Michael, that was everyone's favorite band of the 2000s.
Huba Stank.
Oh, wow, it's not even a hit.
Let it Out by Huba Stank.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know, sorry, Huba Stank.
According to something I saw, that was like a number two song.
Was?
But how? And that version I just played was from the live DVD Let It Out.
So they liked that song enough to name the DVD after it.
But why Huba Stank?
Not a pleasant performance to watch.
I was like, well, Huba Stank, their hit was...
What was I? Wrote it down.
The reason. Their hit was the reason.
Yeah, we all shed many tears to the reason.
The reason is you.
The music video for that.
Folks, go find it. It's bonkers.
It starts with a woman being hit by a car.
And then you think it's about a guy regretting what he has done with the car.
And it turns out that it is a setup for an elaborate jewelry heist.
And she is fine.
It is bizarre.
It is so strange.
So, yes, the first this was ever attempted.
Friggin Huba Stank, dude.
Wow.
And I am a little upset because I was at Grad Night 2005.
Because I made my little sister take me.
One year away.
I had a second Grad Night.
And yeah, if I was only one year off, I could have seen this pioneering rock moment.
It would haunt me.
Yeah. Yeah.
Also, this one, I had the idea of a DJ setting up the space stage.
Well, not the space stage, but it was introduced by a DJ who was referred to himself as Cosmic Ray.
Now, is this the same Cosmic Ray who runs the Starlight Cafe that Sonny Eclipse performs in?
I'll say yes.
I think so.
I think that establishes him as like a music fan.
And he likes everything from a lounge lizard like Sonny Eclipse all the way to the hardest rock like Huba Stank.
And is Sonny Eclipse and Cosmic Ray, are they in C?
The Society of Explorers and Adventurers.
They're probably in a more cosmic version of it.
Space.
What's their organization?
Society of...
Let's see.
Can we see?
There's a lot of letters.
Explorers and Xenomorphs?
Planetary, Astro...
Planetary, Astronomical.
I'm too exhausted.
All right, we'll figure that out.
Fill it in later.
But DJ Rex is in it and Halix is in it.
Oh yeah.
And Halix 2.0.
Man, we just created this.
This is real now.
This is a space drill building.
So we will declare the full space.
I like this so much more than C.
This is way up my alley.
Let's tie all the rock shit together.
When we get Rodeon, we gotta pitch him this.
Yeah, let's make this official.
They need their own oars put up in restaurants as well.
Space oars.
They're space oars.
And Huba Stank's into.
Huba Stank is the first band in space.
So you're in.
But the aesthetic has to be the 2000s curved metal aesthetic that I'm so fond of.
The...
Where everything had a lot of loose, like palm fronds.
Yeah, loose fronds.
Like a lot of inflatable neon furniture about.
Then repurposed for high art exhibits.
I was showing my co-hosts this.
My new favorite Twitter account is called the Y2K Aesthetics Institute.
And it catalogs a lot of this.
Weird Timex watches that had tie-ins with the Tomb Raider video.
You could buy this watch and Lara Croft, Polygon Lara Croft had the watch in the game.
Oh, wow.
Like the Tomb Raider.
No, I gotta get this.
I gotta subscribe to that Twitter.
I don't...
Jason, you were talking about inability to remember the song around the world.
That's how I couldn't remember the name.
The last couple of days, I'm like, what's this song called?
Like, Work Me Up?
Jam Me Off?
I could not remember.
And we just listened to it.
And in my head, like, give me a poison.
Marry me.
I've got tears for you to say.
I don't...
My brain cannot retain.
How did this band ever work?
That is not a band.
I liked a lot of mainstream stuff, but that is starting to get into the mainstream rock
where I was just like, what is this?
Well, Three Doors Down.
I guess I liked Superman okay when it came out.
But then once they started getting into the...
What's the one?
Being the only band going to play with Trump.
Oh, yeah.
Hold Me When I'm Going, like that stuff.
I was like, this is...
Oh, yeah.
That's an awesome song.
I can only assume...
I'm gone.
Any alien ant farm that is not the cover of a song you like already, it's probably pretty rough.
Yeah, I don't...
But I don't know.
Movies?
Maybe I would love Alien Ant Farm.
I feel like maybe I liked movies when it came out.
Which was not as big of a hit as Smooth Criminal was.
It was at all.
You don't know movies?
Movies is...
I'm not going to say it might be pretty good because I haven't heard it in a long time when
we play it and I'm like, oh, I'm embarrassed now.
Look, it was never used on a roller coaster.
That's kind of how I judge if a song is good or not.
They should have had it in Hollywoodland at California Adventure because it was about movies.
Missed opportunity.
So, Hoobastank.
But without Hoobastank, you don't get Rockin' Space Mountain.
Now, who cares about that?
I guess maybe you shouldn't.
But remember, without Rockin' Space Mountain, you don't get Space Mountain Ghost Galaxy.
Right.
Because all of the projection and the extra shit was put in before that.
So, Rockin' Space Mountain, a not beloved thing, led to another thing that is...
It's there.
I don't know.
People like it.
I think it could use an upgrade.
I think it takes more into people like it than don't.
Yes, I think so.
People love Star Wars too.
They like hyperspace.
A lot of people really into that.
Hyperspace Mountain.
So, Hyperspace Mountain...
The Admiral Ackbar doesn't join the Space Mountain Fund unless Admiral Hoobastank
Paves the way.
Sharts the spaceship first.
Sure.
So, this is a very important pioneering ride, obviously.
And it makes us think that they have missed a lot of opportunities to
continue to include the Red Hot Chili Peppers in the park.
Of course.
Why hasn't this been done more?
Everybody gets their lists.
So, pull out your pre-written material because we are going to discuss ways to inject the
Red Hot Chili Peppers into the park.
You bring it up and I don't want to be rude and try to jump the line, but I feel like
mine is the obvious one.
I'm worried it's going to get done.
I don't know.
Mine could be too.
Maybe we're all classics.
I told Mike's already.
I see.
Well, I told you the other day.
Yours isn't that obvious.
I bet Scott doesn't have it, but I could be wrong.
Let's hear it.
I'll just go.
I mean, we're saying it's right there.
It's crazy they didn't use the rollercoaster song on the rollercoaster song.
I think you have to use the Zephyr song on Golden Zephyr.
It's right.
It's like sitting there.
I mean, as the ride is starting up, you know, you're all buckled in and it starts to
slowly go around in a circle before it goes medium around in a circle.
Just hearing.
Can you imagine hearing?
Can I get your hand to write on just a piece of leg to bite on?
What a night to fly my kite on.
Do you want to flash your light on?
And then as you get to the highest point and you're in this retro throwback rocket
ship design like the pulps of the 1920s, which is how they justify the existence of this ride.
Just hearing as you're zooming around Paradise Gardens Park,
fly away on my Zephyr.
I feel it more than ever.
And in this perfect weather, we'll find a place together.
And then you come back down to Earth, man.
Right.
I and you know what?
That's actually I just went on the Golden Zephyr for the first time and it is oddly still.
It was kind of nice.
It's a fun to swing out over that.
Lake and I like the design.
And like I like I think it's a neat throwback thing.
It's it's so crazy.
It's still there.
Yeah, crazy.
Barely.
It's it's a sign of our crowd at the park is that they're operating it.
But I actually think genuinely I think I really do think put the song in.
Sure.
Put the song in.
Also, interesting fact about that ride.
If it's a little too windy, they can't operate it.
And certainly if the weather turns inclement, but like, yeah, winds.
It's kind of susceptible to winds.
Besides that stalwart ride.
Yeah.
All right.
Zephyr song on Golden Zephyr.
Mike, thoughts or I can.
Well, I mean, I got I got a couple things here.
I'll do one of my less interesting one.
I mean, I think they're red hot chili peppers, famous song, snow, hey, oh, you know that?
Of course.
Yes.
Let's put it on the Matterhorn.
OK.
Oh, yeah.
It's got snow all over.
I'm talking snow.
Listen when I say, oh, I mean, that's fun.
That's going to give it a different mood because really what you're trying to do
with these overlays is give it a different feel.
What is that song called?
Snow, hey, oh, I just always thought it was just called, hey, oh,
I think there's a parentheses in it.
Let me look at it.
Let me look it up for sure.
I don't want to be inaccurate here.
Snow, hey, oh, yes, snow parentheses, hey, oh, is what the name of the song is.
So I think, you know, that's on the Matterhorn.
I think now it's a fun experience.
And maybe you know, you're on a snowy mountain, right?
And an abominable snowman, maybe instead of he's reaching at you.
I think in the last time when we did Matterhorn, I said he's giving you an ice cream cone.
This time he's just giving you like the rock and roll symbol on your way up.
He's just rocking out.
Yeah, he loves snow parentheses.
Hey, oh, he says, hey, oh, hey, oh, that's great.
And then where there's that all the garbage and stuff, it's just a guitar.
There's a guitar there.
He stole a guitar.
It's a kind of a throwback to the laziness.
Yeah, I don't want any new robots.
Just a broken guitar now added to the Skyway cab.
Throw it on the pile.
Yep.
Great.
Love it.
Okay.
Well, I think that the Chili Peppers have been the soundtrack for some of the most
thrilling attractions on the property.
Yes.
And they, you know, they proved their metal with that.
But I think it's time for them to score the most thrilling attraction in the whole Anaheim
Resort, which is of course the Bodine Sourdough Bakery.
I think it's time for the Rockin' Bakery.
It's time for the Chili Peppers to set up shop in the home of the Motherdough and Papa Steve
and all the iconic parts of the attraction that we know.
You know, where there's rock lighting in the people making the bread have to do it under
flashing rock lights.
Also, they all take their clothes off and bake with just socks on.
And obviously there's gotta be Chili Peppers blasting loud.
Now for my full notion of it, they are going to have to do a custom song, but I was nice
enough to do the demo for them.
Oh, wow.
And so I'd like to do that.
All right, please.
Present it to them now.
Every piece of dough comes from the mama.
It's a process that was mastered by the papa.
Steve always uses the sourdough starter.
He takes a little flour and he mix it with water.
Colin Mockery wears an orange polo.
Colin Mockery mocking Rosie's info.
People ignore bakers in the window.
How come everybody just wanna get the sample?
Give it a bake, give it a bake, give it a bake now.
Boat Dean knows how to bake a solid bread bowl.
All right.
So that should save them some trouble.
They could just use that as the guide and lay it down.
And I think that's gonna,
I think that's a great idea.
Maybe increase traffic to the sourdough factory a little bit.
Rock, is there, what did you say a name already?
Is it Rockin' Sourdough?
Like, what is the ad?
What are the ads gonna look like?
Yeah, I guess Rockin' Dough.
Rockin' Dough?
Rockin' the Dough?
Rockin' the Dough, give it a bakery.
The Rockin' Dough, give it a bakery.
Right. Yeah, great.
I think, yeah, use that one,
or just like use Roller Coaster on that,
because you were subverting expectations.
Yeah, not on the roller coasters.
Use it in the bakery tour.
Just in every bathroom.
Either way.
That's part of the thing, every bathroom.
And obviously you're gonna have to, easy one,
bring back the Starcade and call it Stadium Starcadium.
Well, that's good, I mean, that's just good.
So there's a ton of ways to get it.
Well, my other ones, they're not gonna pale
in comparison to the original song.
I just feel like there's two classic songs
from Blood, Sugar, Sex, Magic
that could be applied to a couple dark rides.
I'm talking about the song Suck My Kiss
that should be placed on Little Mermaid.
Oh yeah, she kinda sucks, well, she sucks the voice.
Right, but she's looking for a kiss,
true love from the prince.
So Sebastian should be like, suck my kid,
like he should be doing that.
And it's just talking about kissing,
it's not anything else dirty.
And you could get like an aquatic animal,
I don't know what's, I guess they've already got a,
the base is like an octopus.
So you just make like a sea turtle that looks like Flea
with the head down kinda slapping that thing.
And the famous line,
come to me sweet sacred bliss,
your mouth was made to suck my kiss,
sung by some, please come to me.
It's somewhere like in a pizza man, but whatever.
I was gonna say it's like a vampire a little bit.
I can't hear these headphones, that's why.
That's it, but you could calibrate your Jamaican.
Yeah, and then the song from Blood, Sugar, Sex,
on the same album, a song called I Could Have Lied,
obviously on Pinocchio.
Sure.
That was my, the thought in general is that Pinocchio
as this sort of, Pleasure Island is this broken wasteland.
You could almost, hey, how about this?
Why don't we slow Pinocchio's Daring Journey down a lot.
Okay, yeah.
Like make it like 10 times as slow
and make it kind of this crawl through
where you like kind of address Ketis' past.
Oh, interesting.
And like show, and like instead of them
just turning into donkeys,
like they're strung out on heroin
lying around Pleasure Island.
Yeah.
It could be a perfect, like,
because the Chili Peppers deal with some themes too,
and it's, this is a theme park,
and I think it's time to, you know, why not?
That ride's kind of a guilt trip anyway,
so let's teach kids about the dangers of drug use
and of playing too much billiards.
Sure.
Then that's also, I think, if we're gonna go that route,
which I am all for, I think that there needs to be
one addition to the Pleasure Island section of the ride.
I think you need to build the bridge
from the song Under the Bridge.
So, which is the, you know what I'm talking about,
that's the famous song, Under the Bridge.
Take me to a place I love.
Jason knows it is take me to the place I love.
That's why I was trying to get to the chorus
and I couldn't think of it for a second.
So you build that bridge, you put it up in there,
and then when you go in and slowly through the vehicle,
you go under the bridge like in the song.
Hmm, yeah.
So. Yeah.
Pretty simple there.
Yeah, yeah.
And you move the hell section of Mr. Toad
to the end of that.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
It's a sad song, so you die in this one.
It's called Under the Bridge.
The song's called Under the Bridge, yeah.
I really didn't think it was called
Take me to the place I love.
Once again.
Sometimes I feel like I don't.
That's probably the biggest song they've had, actually.
So music recommendations for the end of this episode.
Take me to the place I love.
Power. Power.
Parentheses people, keep on learning.
And the Australian song about the Power Rangers.
Trouble. Trouble, yeah.
Well, we got a lot of great music picks.
And of course, and of course, Who Bustank?
The name of the song, which was called Live It On.
Let it out.
Okay, close enough.
I almost got there.
Parentheses, hey-o.
Live it out.
Prevent.
We're tired.
Check out the Reason music video.
Be sure to watch the Reason music video.
I'll post my, but I will make a Chili Peppers playlist
tonight, I promise.
But before I go to bed, I'll fall asleep doing it.
Even though the audience won't hear this right now.
No, they won't, but I want it ready now
before I lose the interest in it.
How could you?
Clearly what Disney's teaching us
is to keep the spirit of the Chili Peppers
in our lives 365, or at least for four months
until the licensing agreement ends.
Right, and let's get some retro Chili Peppers merch
in Disney.
Let's get a yesteryear shirt.
Jason's holding his head in his hands when I say that.
There was some debate real quick.
The last thing I have to say is that I was looking online,
there's a lot of debate of why Disney wasn't doing
a ton of marketing with the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
And there was a debate whether it was just something
that was kind of limited time,
or there was a possible dispute
with the Red Hot Chili Peppers
that they didn't want to actually be used in advertising.
And that they just licensed the music for the rides,
but not, they didn't want to appear in the ads.
Interesting.
Because the commercials that you find online
don't make any mention of the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
It just goes rockin', space mountain,
and it doesn't say what the song is,
it doesn't make a big deal out of it.
It doesn't even have rock music, I think,
in the commercial or anything that's actually that cool.
Rock music in general.
Yeah, so it's confusing.
There's debate about exactly what was going on.
And that's the last very interesting tidbit
I had in my head.
All right.
You know, I missed one quote,
and maybe we can end with this one as a final note,
and you survived podcast ride the second,
wait, you survived RHCP at DLR on PTR2G,
which I'd like to catch on in general,
that the second gate is PTR2G.
But in the immortal words of Uncle Joe,
no matter which planet you're from,
it doesn't work, it's at the end.
What I'm saying is you go out into that,
as you start your day or whatever you're heading off to do
as you finish this episode,
no matter what planet you're from,
we're about to rock your world.
This works great.
And it's all gonna happen in five, four, three, two,
rock and roll.
Bye.
Goodbye. Bye.