Forever.
Dog.
Warning. This episode contains claustrophobic cues,
dad embarrassment, and just when you feel deep in a film noir nightmare,
a tropical light at the end of the tunnel.
This is Roger Rabbit's Cartoon Spin on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast where, if you know exactly where to freeze frame it,
you can see us without underwear.
I'm Scott Geer, here.
That's my Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
You had to remember why that joke exists, because the topic is Roger Rabbit.
Also real creepy if you don't know. My name is Mike Carlson, by the way.
And impossible in a podcast.
I just wanted to talk about it.
You know, there's that freeze frame thing, and then I really like the other one,
the one in the short where there's the poster for rigid tools.
It's a Jessica Rabbit looking character straddling a chainsaw or something,
and it says rigid too. It's such a strange phrase.
Before everyone turns the podcast off, because they think we've turned into perverts,
we're talking about some of the classic weird pornographic Disney secrets, I guess.
Actually, if you listen to every episode of this podcast, at some point you can hear me whisper,
take off your clothes.
Like in Aladdin, the magic carpet.
It's an Easter egg. It's in every one of them.
Send us all the time codes and we'll give you a prize.
And like the Little Mermaid cover, our logos have the drawn boner.
Erin hides a boner in our artwork.
Look for the secret in our abstract Epcotty symbol. Yes, you'll see it.
I'm trying to think of all the different ones.
Okay, so there's that, but then there's also supposedly a secret boner in Little Mermaid itself.
The priest.
The priest, right? Yeah, we've talked about this many times.
I know this shit's like a side shot.
It's kind of a profile shot and this is where Little Mermaid like rise in his priest garment.
And that people say, maybe it's a knee or something, but it is a pretty like just thin, straightforward,
you know, the way boners go straight out.
They don't like rise up.
No character, no change at all.
Like Pinocchio's nose, I guess.
Just straight ahead.
Bloop, straight ahead.
Can I ask for context, not just for the audience, but also for myself?
What is the under, so Jess, there's a shot in Jessica.
When they're spinning out in the car, right?
There's supposedly that's what it is.
I think it's, I'm not sure the scene.
I just like, cause I thought I could only remember the rigid tools.
I actually forgot there was one in the movie and I think it was like corrected long ago.
I'm not sure.
And you have to like brighten it up to see that it's, I don't know if it's no underwear or if it's,
or it could have been a mistake too.
It's like you see up Jessica Reyes dress.
I feel like this is something like on E-bombs world that I watched 10 years ago or something.
They were like, here's the clip of it.
And I think I remember watching it and just like, okay, okay.
Well, that was it.
I don't know.
It's kind of, if it's just passing by, it's sort of a let down.
If you see it in some scandalous slideshow, it seems like a lot more risqué than it is.
Cause someone's like lightened the image and really made it a whole thing.
Presented it for you.
I see.
This is an interesting way into a thing I learned today.
Roger Rabbit is based on a fucking book.
Uh huh.
Who censored Roger Rabbit?
And a much grimier, like, like it's a parody of like Sam Spade, Philip Marlowe, kind of Noire detective stuff.
And like there is no judge doom.
Roger is a lot more conniving and addition to being mischievous and Jessica's a full on like retired adult film star.
Oh, really?
Oh, that's apparently I don't think, I don't know that it's in print.
And I think, but I think you can find on like eight books or like used book.
Websites.
And then there's two, two sequels to it too.
Who whacked Roger Rabbit and there's another one who discovered maybe that was that one of the unmade sequels was or prequels.
That might've been one of the seat.
But yeah, I had no idea there was a book involved and the off offer.
I think it's Gary K. Wolf has sued Disney before.
I think ended up winning a few hundred thousand dollars for like, he said he was owed for gross receipts and they said he was and they actually owed him.
And so eventually I think he was rewarded legal costs.
But oh, gotcha.
But it was, it's funny.
The Disneyfication of thing where this was like a, like a noir book playing within the world of forties cartoons and to see them take it all the way to Roger Rabbit's cartoon spin.
New Disney.
Yeah, Disney and Amblin.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Career co-production.
Is it so did they buy out the rights completely or did they just like option at like a movie?
I mean, obviously they own Roger Rabbit now, but was like his dispute was like he just was owed more because he created a character.
Yeah, I think he was claiming he was owed more because they've made so much off the character and DVD sales and stuff and everything else over the years.
Yeah.
And now Rod, now as you're saying the Disneyfication, but I think like now that wouldn't be made because Robert Zemeckis is saying that like Disney doesn't like Jessica Rabbit anymore.
Like the other very means the lack of use of the property on them not wanting such a sultry.
I don't know if it's completely that, but I think he's mentioned that he's done a lot of interviews with people ask him about it.
But I think he said something about like Disney is not a fan of Jessica Rabbit anymore.
It seems like it was a fallout to with Disney and Amblin couldn't come to terms for like a full theme theme park land, but did come to terms for one single ride.
And that is why this ride exists.
Oh, gotcha.
Like there was yes, because and we'll talk about it.
There were a number of alternate Roger Rabbit attractions.
Yeah, which could have happened.
It could have been like, I really wish it would have happened.
Yeah.
Sometimes you hear about rides that didn't get built and you go, well, how would that have worked?
These all sounded really cool.
Really cool.
And really in the spirit of the original MGM studios, the first decade of that.
Yeah. Yeah.
And would have been a killer expansion for that.
Yeah.
And I believe if I'm if I'm remembering correctly, Jim Hill was talking on one of his 25 different podcasts that I listened to about how they're going to reuse one of these ride systems for the Roger Rabbit ride.
On the Zootopia ride.
What?
Really?
The trolley.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
Yes.
Well, because we're you know, we can jump all around.
There was going to be a ride called the Toontown Trolley.
Yeah.
There was a little trolley that you might the Jolly Trolley that's still sort of around in Toontown and Disneyland, but not functional.
But it's a little trolley car that dipped, you know, kind of tipped back and forth.
But there was going to be a concerted ride that was a lot more of a Star Tours simulator that I don't really know the plot of it, but just, you know, you're you're in a trolley car.
Trolley, I'll get told, driven by Roger and wrapped around a little more screens.
Oh, like through the windows?
Yeah.
Oh, that's cool.
OK, OK.
So this was potentially Zootopia.
So that's yeah, that's what Jim Hill said.
I'm trying to think of which podcast it was.
I don't know if it was his one with Len or it was somebody different.
But yeah, he said that there it's going to be like a bus and you're going to be on like some police chase through Zootopia.
I mean, that makes a lot of sense.
The other thing was because there's there are wires on the Sunset Boulevard area of Hollywood Studios and those were going to be for red car trolleys.
An idea that they also have reused in DCA.
But you were going to take the red car trolley down Sunset Boulevard, you know, which ends with Tower of Terror.
And now Rock and Roller Coaster.
But the Rock and Roller Coaster plot was where they were going to put the Roger Rabbit stuff.
It was called either Roger Rabbit's Hollywood or Maroon Studios.
And there is still a Maroon Studios billboard and Hollywood.
Yeah, right. Oh, gotcha.
So it's always there's like little Easter eggs of what was potentially to come and kind of follows what is popular the last decade or so of a fully themed land.
So it's like multiple attractions, a bar, the terminal bar that like Bob Hoskins goes to like that would have been so great.
You hop off the trolley, go to the bar.
Well, and this all sounds because it all sounds cool because that Sunset Boulevard area of MGM Studios like pretty neat and a very like it just made so much sense as an expansion.
Like we've got you go you go down Hollywood Boulevard.
So a like attached Sunset Boulevard, but the things are a little like seedier, creepier down.
That's where the scary rides are.
Yeah. And that culminating in the world of Roger Rabbit, which is sort of seedy and creepy and sexy as we determined.
So I guess what I'm saying is that's a better end for that area than a warehouse with a guitar on the outside playing pink all day.
It feels very copacetic if it had been sitting next to the Hollywood Tower Hotel.
Yeah, like that. Right.
Roger Rabbit's Hollywood and the hotel like that makes sense.
But those obviously would have fit the best next to the Hotel Mel.
Oh, of course.
You know about the original Tower of Terror?
Oh, the Mel Brooks one.
Yes. When there was going for any listeners who don't know, there was the notion of a hotel drop ride before the Twilight Zone entered the picture.
But it was going to be a wacky madcap thing involving Mel Brooks.
Was it just like Mel? I forget it.
Was it original characters or was it like Mel's classic characters on the whole?
No, I think it was him.
Was he like, we'll look to more.
Was it him like showing up? Was that a robot Mel on the ride?
Or was it what if that was going to be a screen ride like it is now with Guardians?
But every floor there's a different he's a bellhop, but he's also like an overall wearing like repairman.
Or he's like both a man and a woman having an affair together.
Like one door opens and like like my word and they cover themselves with the sheets.
Him and Carl Reiner eating dinner out of their TV trays watching like Jeopardy or something.
I would love a writer cameo also back there was going to be I think it's still an unused expansion pad.
The David Copperfield restaurant.
Oh, yeah.
That never got built.
I want that's the thing.
I'd love to do an episode about and yet I don't think there's like any info about it to hang an episode on.
But it was like a outside of Disney and GM Studios.
There was a sign there was like Copperfield making a plate levitate or something.
They got that far into we're committed to building a Copperfield restaurant and then didn't didn't end up happening.
We need to get more like OG Hollywood Studios imagineers on here so they can give us the scoops.
We need to get more insiders.
I think to get scoops like that because there's a lot of stuff like that where it's fascinating, but there's not a ton of stuff online about it.
Yeah. So we got to dig them up ourselves.
And you're right to say MGM Studios, but like it does seem like it has the most weird and then what was going to happen and what was going to happen.
I think the nature of like odd briefly popular properties being able to slide in and out of there made it so a lot of really cockamamie ideas.
Ninja Turtles, Power Rangers, Dinosaurs, Ace Ventura.
That's still the weirdest one.
And the end as we talked about a little while ago, the many different Muppet attractions that didn't happen.
Yeah.
How do we get started looking at names?
Let's name names.
If you have a name at home of somebody to talk to about the Disney MGM Studios history.
We're starting to get emails of people like kind of giving us some little tidbits of information that might not be public.
So let's keep that going.
Let's get the stuff going.
How many characters was Mel Brooks going to play?
Was he going to be a dowdy woman offended that you caught him in his underwear?
Right.
Or underwear.
Like turns like rude or no look.
That was oh, look, a man was a genie does that or something.
I think like he's got in the shower.
Isn't Genie in the shower at one point?
Sounds right.
I don't know what I'm saying.
And does a like, oh man.
Yeah, yeah, something like that.
Like that old trope.
Yeah. So that would have been one of them.
Yeah, I guess so.
I'm stuck on this a man.
That's really in my head.
I know somebody says a man in a movie.
Maybe that's not the genie.
I don't think I kind of don't think it is.
What is it then?
So one of the listeners will tell me.
It's another trickster, shape shifting character.
Is it the mask?
Does the mask say a man?
Who says a man?
Is it a Joker?
Is there a Joker that ever says that?
Is it a Looney Tune?
Is it Bugs Bunny?
Which kooky character is it?
Yeah.
It's a kooky character.
Who's excited to see a man?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Somebody's script.
Like this is the kind of thing where there's those lapses in our knowledge where someone
has tweeted at us by the time we wake up on the day that the episode is released.
And this will certainly be one of those.
And they're mad at us.
Yeah.
How could you not remember?
As you have every right to be.
Look, I mean, they could be at a different time zone, but look, doing shift work sucks.
So it was drop dead Fred.
You're not remembering.
Doing that third shift is raw.
I've done that before.
That or swig shift.
You know, you start to crack a little.
Drop dead Fred.
Take your anger out on your favorite podcast.
We understand.
Well, you want to stay in the zone of Roger Rabbit.
We have some big news, but maybe we save some time at the end of the episode.
Oh, you want to do it at the end?
Why don't we tease our big news?
It's very big news.
It is very big.
You're right.
It's been, it's been, you know, let's talk about the ride.
Let's be selfless before we talk about our giant accomplishment.
But for now, Roger Rabbit's cartoon spin.
So a little bit of Roger Rabbit did make their way into, especially MGM studios.
And the big one that I believe is still there is the stunt car.
Like the car that was Benny the cab, the actual car that Bob Hoskins would ride in and a stunt driver would drive it like there was a seat for him behind it.
That is in the back lot express restaurant or at least used to.
I believe it is still there.
The restaurant is still operating at Hollywood studios.
Is that right?
Yeah. And that that you can see the pictures of him like riding down the bridge that connects the Atwater Village neighborhood to the Silver Lake or Los Feliz neighborhood.
Yeah.
Bridge. If yeah, that we're frequently on and that a lot of people we know live around there.
Sure.
You forget that you've probably driven on it a ton of times without realizing, oh yeah, this is where the Roger Rabbit car chase culminates.
Yeah, I know it almost to the Atwater Dunkin Donuts.
You do that weird U-turn before the Starbucks and you have a view of the Dunkin Donuts.
Yes.
You probably just go straight to it, but you crashed your car through the window.
And I'm on the lower street and then I the car goes up above the bridge to get onto it.
And then you eat as many like donuts as Homer did when he was in hell.
Yeah, every day.
That was the second Dunkin Donuts to come here, right?
There was one in Santa Monica.
And then I think that was like the second one.
Something like that.
Yeah, there's still building.
There's still not a ton.
There's one right here.
Obviously, no one say where.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't don't dox yourself.
Santa Clarita, California, where we record, go start marching on, go start knocking on every door in Santa Clarita.
You'll find that's where we record.
And then so that my faith, I was very happy to discover.
I did not imagine this as a child.
You either used to be a bunch of photo ops at the end of the the backlog tour at MGM Studios.
You would get off and there was the cars from Roger Rabbit and the dip machine and you could get your pictures taken.
With all of this stuff.
But I have a very clear memory of as a child going like I did not care for the dip.
I do not like I'm scared of the dip.
I am scared of the dip.
Yeah, the machine was like very well done because it scared me as a child.
Yeah. So you didn't take a photo.
Do you have a photo with you?
I'm sure I have photo.
Well, I think there was like a Benny the cab that you could get a photo into.
So I must have a photo in front of that stuff somewhere.
But I remember that it felt like and I don't know if they said there's Roger Rabbit stuff coming.
But like I feel like as a kid, I was like, well, I bet they'll make a Roger Rabbit ride at some point.
Like I just kind of was like, well, everyone knows Roger.
He's in the giant inflatable Mardi Gras parade.
It was really heavy presence at the parks around.
We've talked about how he was essentially like all like kind of the big six.
He was almost in there.
And yeah, they were the giant pres.
I strongly associate him with early Disney MGM studios, despite there being no attraction there.
I thought the backlot tour was so full of Roger Rabbit pushing.
He was like Stitch or Pooh Bear.
Like they recycle in and out of this like sixth character where you're like, why so much Stitch stuff around?
Although I think probably he was maybe I know people do like Stitch, but it does feel a little bit forced.
We've talked about that before, but I definitely.
Sure to be excellent live action version.
Yeah, when is that action film?
It's so fun to see these movies rendered and live action.
Is that real people and 3D joyless.
That's the thing I know from my memory, but now it's different now.
I don't think I can get into the head of the person who's excited about.
I don't know.
Some of I don't know.
I shouldn't be such a grump about some of these movies are better than others.
But man, like like Aladdin.
Dear God, what are we?
Yeah, I don't.
I like Jungle Book a lot.
I was I was expecting like it so much, but I really, really liked it.
And that's I haven't seen Cinderella, but that's the only one I've really been into.
But yeah, I don't know.
It's hard to take a movie that everyone loves and then put in a totally different media like in a different type of media.
That's not the word.
Another medium.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
And then make it as good.
It seems almost impossible.
It seems like especially with the Aladdin and Beauty and the Beast.
It would be one thing to do like Oliver and Company, which is not even though we all have fondness for it.
What you want with Oliver and Company may have it memorized.
I feel like lately we're in the territory now of films that we have committed absolutely to memory.
And in the case of Aladdin, it's like, you know, then the genie shifts shapes and there's a giant guy becomes a snake.
And you're like, how is this going to be more visually appealing?
Yeah, yeah.
With CGI, the musical, I believe, is very well reviewed, the Broadway musical.
But I don't that one.
I'm like, why don't you just make a live movie of the musical?
Because there are new there's additional songs, too.
OK, maybe that's obviously we would be on board if at every screening Will Smith or all right.
A Will Smith sound alike was broadcasting live in the theater, updated topical jokes.
Well, that's every script responding to short tweets as they occur.
If Trump tweeted something at five p.m., I want the seven thirty show to have a new genie joke about it.
That genie is going to dab, right?
The genie has to dab.
Has to dab because he can't really floss because he's got or no, he can floss.
He can make legs.
Yeah, he can make legs so he can floss.
The later genie, when he was like more, I mean, he has legs in the movie before he's freed, but I think he can make legs.
It's just like he's generally float when he's floating, he has no legs.
Will Smith will have legs and we'll walk around.
But I bet he'll float. Yeah.
So for sure, I think Genie flosses.
I think like what is this?
I mean, he has to because now it's built in that Genie makes topical jokes like as much as we were talking about how like, oh, yeah, this is weird that the California venture Genie is doing that.
That was Rob Williams did that.
There's tons of topical jokes.
Jack Nicholson impressions like stuff that should not have been in a movie that was set a couple hundred years ago.
So like it is built now into the Disney Genie.
So you're right.
He has to dab or do the floss or transform into Pete Davidson.
Sure. Or the Casio Cortez.
He has to reflect the culture.
Yeah, I think that that's right.
I think we're in for hopefully a very pop culture reference Genie.
This Genie will be doing the sarcastic clap.
I think Jafar is going to do something bad and then Genie is going to be like, and then like it'll pause on it.
And I think everyone will go nuts on the Internet.
And then people will like that in the theater.
Now they think about it.
Yeah.
If they really have to like get it exactly right for people to get the reference, although people have probably forgotten about it in three months.
So maybe.
So how would they?
I'm thinking about like making a Roger Rabbit, a live live, a more live action Roger Rabbit.
We have to see realistic hair audiences today want to see hair that gets wet.
They want to see every follicle with crystal clear clarity.
Yeah.
To correct myself from earlier, the photo op for the backlots where you could get a photo next to the Weasels car.
OK.
Or you could get like green screened with Benny or Jessica Rabbit.
But you could get a photo.
I forget what blog I pull this from under the under the wheel pose like you were getting rolled over like Judge Doom.
Like you were getting smashed.
Yes.
That was probably what I was like.
I don't know.
That was upsetting to me because I saw the movie not when in the theater, but I saw it on video and it disturbed a lot of things disturbed me about it.
And I think one of them for sure was him getting crushed by that at the end.
I think I would have been a much different person if I'd seen this when it came out in the theater, because at least on VHS I could like close my eyes or like sink into the couch.
I saw it like at a friend's house and I think I like ran in and out of the room because I was during a lot of the scenes because I was freaked out by a lot of the elements of it.
I do think Jessica Rabbit freaked me out as well.
I think keeping with my game on the show, I think Jessica Rabbit sexuality in real life.
I'm very comfortable with everything.
But in the show, my persona on the show is someone who's very repressed and is someone who's not comfortable with things like this.
But I do think I was like just too much.
I don't know what's going on here.
Well, it's more aggressive sexuality than probably any.
There's other sexy cartoon characters.
Yes, it's pretty cartoon.
As I said, sexy cartoon characters, I ended up looking right up at your the bear from Swing and Teddy Bear over here on my other sexy cartoon characters like swinging Teddy Bear.
Yeah, it was like a Maywest flustered to it threw me off.
I am purposely put in the seat where I can't see her because I would never get any episodes done.
Can I move my chair for future episodes?
Just kind of want to just different kind of fung shui.
It has nothing to do with not wanting to stare the sexiest bear in the face.
Swing and Teddy Bear.
I but yeah, more aggressive sexuality certainly.
Yeah, and I was not ready for that.
I'm trying to think is this the earliest like crime detective thing I would have seen?
And because I liked even as a kid, I liked all that.
I remember step by step doing like a detective parody episode.
Oh, God, I see a battery.
So a full they did a lot of like the genre.
It turns into a movie for the entire.
Yeah, that was like a go to genre parody for sitcoms, kids, cartoons, like anything and then eventually voice for actresses.
Is like, hello, Mr. Spade.
But like, that's a good.
That's a great part to give to like a person in a play without a lot of range.
That's a voice anybody can do with that.
And then the this is a classic.
This is a go to in improv.
This is one of my go tos.
And it probably is the heavy, the heavier, the like, hey, Mac, all right, get out of here.
Like I was in a sketch show where I played a bouncer at a jazz club, but I was like, well, there's no question in my mind that I am.
All right, you're out of here.
Come on, Bob.
And like a dozen characters do that voice in this movie.
It's nothing but yes, it's nothing.
There's a weasel.
Yeah.
And then one of the weasels is like, I'm going to ram him.
There's a very funny in the car chase scene.
I was laughing, listening at the driving weasel going like, I'm going to ram him.
There was I did.
I was UCB has things called spank shows, which is like you're putting up a show.
Oh, you don't need to explain this at all.
I know you guys know.
But that means that you're trying out a show to see if it gets a run.
And I was in a show that was written by a guy named Josh, a friend of ours, Josh Weiner, and it's called Retired Baby.
And I believe it was me and past guest Jack Allison and everyone was wearing diapers in the show.
And I believe I did the weasel.
I had like a sucker.
I said, I did that voice like this, like the high gangstery voice like that.
So it is so that movie and these types of characters are everywhere.
Yeah.
You're either high voiced, heavy or gravelly voiced heavy.
Yeah. This guy.
Oh, this guy.
I used to be a Golden Gloves champ.
And then they kicked me out because I didn't throw the fight.
This sounds like the cab to you're right.
Everyone in this movie is baby Herman.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's oh my God.
Baby Herman is a deep one.
Wow. There are 10 heavies in so many.
Have they?
I think I like I think I liked that as a kid.
It was more just like when they would go into Toon Town and like I think they do a great job in the movie and also in the attract in the ride we're talking about like of Toon Town is unnerving.
It's unnerving to be a person in in this world in the Roger Rabbit world.
I think you feel like an outsider.
There is a culture here.
Yes. They all adhere to and we and we're on the outside of it.
But the you know if we want to start getting into the ride the when you say unnerving maybe this this may be the reason why this is not a ride that I frequent and I'm going to toss this out.
And I'm curious how you guys feel but I think you might feel the same way.
There's something about that ride where it's all the way in the back of the park.
It's like the furthest away.
It's like it's if you were going to walk from this ride to Midway Mania.
It's like two miles.
Yeah.
But that feels like still part of this vibrant exciting area and Toon Town is kind of ducked ducked back there.
It's sort of an area that's mainly photo ops and for children.
So maybe it feels weird to go back there.
But once you're in this ride that line is so upsetting and claustrophobic.
Yeah.
It's like a ride that's so unneedlessly long seemingly and boring.
It's like being trapped in a sewer for 45 minutes.
Yeah.
The queue is very claustrophobic.
You're right.
Yeah.
And the rides fun the rides fun.
I do like the ride.
I feel like I don't.
Yeah.
I don't go back to Toon Town a lot.
For some reason we you and I were down there once Mike and I had gotten down there early and you were meeting me down there.
And then you came and met me.
I think I had a fast pass for Roger Rabbit and I just remember you getting a hot dog and like hosing a hot dog and two or three bites.
Hosing meaning eating fast.
Eating really fast outside of Toon Town.
I've eaten a very fast hot dog outside of Toon Town a few times I think.
But yeah that seems right.
Yeah.
Because you go up to the little window there.
There's a little there's a little spot.
It's yeah.
Did you have more to the store?
You just wanted to know.
I was just like I have a very specific memory of like by the trolley or by like.
That's fair.
I think that's I've done that a few times.
Did I miss hear a detail.
Was this in the morning.
Well I think it may be 11am or 11.30am.
I was there a little early and he was there around lunch.
Jason's more of a breakfast hot dog man.
I try to eat more hot dog around lunch and I generally only eat it when I'm out.
I don't have a pack of them.
Do you have by the way just an update for the hot dogs.
Do you have a fresh pack of hot dogs in the fridge right now at this moment.
No but I have a little salami I need to finish.
All right.
That's something Jason's to do list.
Yeah.
Salami.
Any other meats we should know about pizza rolls.
And that's not what I've looked for.
What it's not did not meet as liver sausage or something like that.
No.
OK.
Well anyway back to Ryder Rabbit.
Yeah.
The Roger.
So I think because of its proximity to nothing that like small world is right there back in the back area of Disneyland and Toontown is.
So there's nothing that would trick us to go back there regularly.
It's not on the way to anything.
It'll be less of a dead end soon with Star Wars.
Although that's not true.
That still won't connect.
Yeah that won't connect.
So that's well isn't there technically someday maybe some frozen thing bridges the gap and then it's not a dead end anymore.
Well there's a lot of rumors that are floating around.
The most recent rumor is that Mickey and Minnie's runaway railway will come to Toontown backstage.
So but yeah it'll go back.
So I'm not sure.
I forget where the frozen expansion.
I think the frozen expansion might have if they were because they were talking about frozen and they were talking about putting a be our guest back there.
Oh wow.
But I think there's like a plot in between sort of Toontown and Star Wars land but they could use that for Star Wars ride.
They could use that for the fantasy land expansion.
You can also bulldoze the fantasy land theater.
They've talked about that too.
I mean for a while Toontown was seemingly on the chopping block.
That was for a long time the rumor that that's where Star Wars was going to go.
Right.
Pretty amazing when they made that announcement and like oh we're not even lose that they're putting it where and we're not even losing Toontown.
And it's a best case scenario.
I'd be fine losing Toontown but I'm not a little child.
Sure.
Easy for me to say.
Now that is the big thing.
Little children and out of town visitors or people who don't go to the parks that often.
That is when I found myself back there because people want to get they want to go to Mickey Mouse's house and get their picture with him and meet the characters.
It's fun.
It is fun.
I like it.
But it's like it's never.
Yeah.
For us who go quite frequently.
It's not something you do every week.
Childless also.
Childless men in their 30s.
Sure.
But I do think Runaway Railway is a very good idea to drive traffic back there because that's supposedly a very impressive ride.
I'm sure it's family friendly and like we'll all go back there very regularly to do that.
So yeah.
That's kind of liven up the area big time.
If that indeed is truly because that's the most recent rumor I've read that's happening in that zone.
I feel like there's not been a ton of chatter about Frozen or whatever.
Not that it's not going to happen.
But sure.
Most recent stuff is about Runaway Railway just moving into one of those buildings essentially like they're going to gut the building.
But the building will still stand like a backstage building.
Yeah.
Which like it's the entertainment department.
So you know costumes parades all of that.
We'll lose a massive facility.
It's going to get worse and worse to work at Disneyland.
Pushing farther out on the outskirts of the land Disney owns to like different to the point probably where like Tony Baxter was saying on our episode that we don't know when even really knows exactly how much land there is still to expand Disneyland with.
Which is we were all blown away by that tease.
But in the in the months since I've done a lot and I think we all have looked at the Google Maps a lot to go like OK looks like.
Yeah.
You can get the you can get like this much land up until the freeway up until the five.
So I feel like they're just going to keep pushing buildings out in that backstage area to the point where like all of those buildings will be like across town.
And they'll all be bused in and it'll just be this giant disk because it doesn't seem like they're going to build a third park anytime soon.
If you're a Disney employee you're going to have to park at the Citadel Outlet Mall right up the five freeway half an hour away.
You know get a good hour and take a gun on your cost.
A gondola will take you down to Anaheim.
It's a fun hour and a half gondola.
Yeah that's what's going to end up happening for each ride on.
Yeah you have to pay for it.
The genie comes alive on a screen and says a dollar twenty five please.
At this point Disney and the Anaheim offices have more like city planners and crowd specialists than like costume character performers like just to figure out like how do we manage this theme park in the middle of an actual city.
Yeah.
But as it yes it keeps encroaching on the city limits.
It's an organism.
It's a living organism.
Talking about unused land.
I mean the Roger Rabbit stuff that was going to go in Disneyland was going to go behind Main Street in a new area called Hollywoodland.
And one of our favorite specials the Disneyland story with Harry Anderson.
He says coming in 1993 I think like baby Herman's.
Run away run away baby carrot bumper baby yeah bug no buggy run God baby buggy ride run away baby buggy ride to explain one of the many lies in that run of what's coming in the Disney decade this list where I don't think a single one of them happen which is heartbreaking to watch and I watched as a kid and like oh I can't wait for all of that and not a not a one of them happened.
Little mermaid ride eventually happened 20 years later.
What a yeah yeah yeah.
Which that ride.
In keeping with your sketch experience you would have all guests would have dressed up like a baby to go on the ride.
This is sort of a unique facet of it.
This is all Jim Hill info that you were the do you guys read this that what the plot of the baby Herman ride was a little of the broad.
Strokes yeah that it's not because it's Hollywoodland there has to be the you're on a set.
Oh yeah.
Little I really but it's sort of fun funny that in the line you pass by baby Herman's trailer and he's cantankerous and cigar chewing and he's refusing to come out of his trailer and to do the scene and he's saying it's too dangerous.
Get a stunt double and so when you get to the front of the line an employee says hey would you guys be willing to be the stunt double for the baby and then you are outfitted with baby bonnets.
Let's go in the written the perhaps the only is bizarre park use of the only theme park instance of clothing being shoved upon you that is not besides 3D glasses.
You are given a prop.
Which I guess maybe that's like paper so that's that's akin to like a paper hat or something so they can afford to print those cheap and give them out but maybe there was a cleaning station very cleaning station that would have had installed and you were there was just people back there cleaning bonnets all day.
Yet another measles outbreak as an unvaccinated child is sullied baby bonnets.
Soaked baby bonnet.
Measles soaked baby bonnet.
Measles soaked baby bonnets.
Not an actual baby a seven year old dressed as a baby.
There was an outbreak but that but so there would be your photo taken a la space man or splash man or whatever but everybody would everybody in the car would be wearing a ridiculous baby bonnet.
But you could see how does that like that's an interesting idea that they should deploy for something.
Everybody looks silly you would see those on social media.
That's true. Yeah I mean it is a good idea because like the joke of course would be everyone humiliating their father.
Yeah that's what they're looking for.
Is that everyone's father with a baby bonnet on would look absurd and then everyone would want to buy the photo because then it would be like how look at your asshole dad who's an asshole all the time.
So much stuff is just based on like dad's being cranky and assholes all the merch.
Yeah.
We know dad's not happy to be here.
Buy him a shirt to call him an asshole and then buy a picture where he looks like an asshole to stick it to him for not being happy to be here.
I can't tell if that's embracing toxic masculinity or really giving it to him.
I think it's straddling the line.
It's taking him down a peg. Remember you were just a baby once.
Yeah.
You think you're so big.
The.
Oh god what was I gonna say.
I lost it.
You're just imagining we're all imagining our dads.
We're all about to.
I think my dad gets worried about it when he's gotten pulled up to do.
I'm not sure I've seen my dad wear a costume.
This is a rare event in the world.
Like I've been watching King of the Hill lately and like my dad's not like Hank Hill but I think probably a lot of dads have shades of Hank Hill and I my dad's probably more the type like I don't know I look ridiculous.
Right.
I think my dad wore like a little costume once but it was not he would not dress up.
Yeah tiny was my dad did the did the ceremony where you had to worship the totem god at the adventurous club.
Oh right.
What did that make you wear.
You just had to like kneel on the ground and bow to the giant animatronic head.
No.
Because I was like I know they give out a pin that you can't buy in the store.
Can you.
Oh yeah.
I mean you made him go up and get it for you.
Would you volunteer.
Oh that's right.
He was a great sport of valid.
Yeah.
This is an interesting question for all our listeners to ponder.
Has your dad worn a costume.
And improve your life.
Did it like make you a more open free thinking person to have a costume wearing dad even just like one time.
Send us photos of your dad in costume I think.
Tweet us photos.
Oh I remember what I was going to say.
So that if if that if the Hollywood land stuff and the baby Herman ride had come to fruition in modern day they would have had to shut that ride down for a few weeks to take out all the cigars to take out all the like child smoking reference because like oh yeah.
Because like yes.
That's not OK.
Today.
Good point.
You can't smoke in like I don't think anyone smokes in any Disney stuff period like Wolverine I guess in the Fox movies Wolverine smoked but like Nick Fury usually chopping on a cigar in the comics.
Not so in the Avengers has Wolverine smoked lately in movies though.
I don't know.
Yeah I'm sure though I'm sure drinking and popping pills and Logan but that's our rated.
Right.
That's true.
So yet another if we were if Zemeckis is declaring that Disney's uncomfortable with Jessica Rabbit and clearly they would not want baby Herman around a baby smoking a cigar.
There's a lot maybe preventing Roger Abbott's presence from being bigger these days.
Yeah probably.
It's the most offensive film of all time.
Right.
That's what I'm determining.
What were the did you guys read about the the sequels or prequels.
A little bit I've read a little bit like I said I think I think I'm correct that it's who discovered Roger Abbott.
Yeah that was like the killed Roger Abbott.
That was the I'm trying to remember because there's been several different ideas.
There's been like recent ones.
I think there's been a recent script.
When I say recent I mean like in the last seven years and there was stuff that was like an immediately happened after it.
And I'm a little fuzzy on the chronology here which was going to make our listeners like yell at us.
It seems like well look it's about the we're talking about the ride.
We don't have to care about the movies but we that we can be mumbly and tangential in our vague knowledge of the films.
I mean clearly they wanted to do a lot with the movie does not land like who framed Roger Abbott and without making a big attempt at being a franchise.
Yeah.
And clearly they tried and they kept the characters alive with these shorts.
And I think there were it seems to me like there were still murmurs of a of a Roger Abbott sequel as late as the late 90s.
Yeah.
And then the towel was not thrown in till you know over a decade later.
I think they've still talked about a couple of years ago.
They were Zemeckis was talking about they had an idea where it would be like the Pixar characters too essentially like you would get all of it like so they're they've been floating stuff lately.
We've heard the rumor from years ago about the Hope and Crosby remake starring Mickey Mouse and Roger Abbott.
What they were going to remake do an old road comedy remake that would make Roger if that's what the kids want.
Well it's what this kid on the come pointing to Jason Sheridan once.
I love it.
If you did Roger Abbott now if you did a new Roger Abbott you have to have the minions right.
The minions have to show up.
I hear what you're saying.
I don't disagree.
Yeah.
Or Shrek.
I guess it could be Shrek.
I think that I would be fine with Shrek.
I think that's probably unlikely now because of the companies being at war kind of with each other.
Yeah.
The peace pipe that is the Mickey bugs scene I'm not sure occurs today.
Like our politics.
Yeah.
There was once a time when Democrats and Republicans could reach across the aisle.
Our and Disney and Warner Disney and the other any other company could get along.
Now things are awfully divisive.
The Roger Rabbit is an impressive creation of like looks kind of Disney but has like the Bugs Bunny sort of like mischievousness.
Yeah.
Because it's definitely a little bit more edgy too.
I think maybe there's probably a different set of characters like maybe the Hannah Barbera characters are more up for grabs right now than the Looney Tunes even though they're owned by the same company.
But you know who knows.
I maybe like if characters are sort of in flux are the characters that they would have like let license out to Disney to use.
So there's a whole set.
So Mickey and Top Cat could be.
Mickey and Top Cat.
Mickey and the Harvey comics characters.
Casper the ghost.
Hot Stuff the Little Devil.
Little Lada.
You know all the classic comics characters but just the TV series ones just like the Troll Hunters.
OK.
Yeah sure.
Mickey can meet a Troll Hunter.
Mickey can't meet the real Calvin from the comics but he can meet a ripoff Calvin peeing on a logo of a truck.
Right.
The bootleg Calvin.
Yeah.
That bootleg Calvin obviously Mickey can talk to any show.
So yeah there's ways around it.
But yeah who knows.
So yeah they've been talking.
There's many options on the table.
I still think every time they ask Robertson Mecha about it he doesn't like close the door completely.
It seems like he's wanted to do it forever.
And I also think he wants to do like motion capture.
I think he's you know we know he's high on that motion capture.
It's like a weird it's like like the relative you know is going to bring up that interest he has that you don't want like he's going to get into this again.
Yeah.
It's also weird with his motion capture because I feel like his specific motion capture has a thing to it that most people go oh yeah.
OK he's doing one of these movies again.
Whereas like say what you will about Avengers Infinity War like but Thanos is a motion capture character and I thought he looks great.
I like he's kind of seamless.
Yeah.
Seamless.
It's just Josh Brolin.
You get the performance from him.
People have you know like what's the planet of the apes.
Yeah there's great motion capture.
So it is weird.
Whatever the way.
Yeah I don't know what it is.
Marwin the fact that he stepped aside for a while and then did Welcome to Marwin and like right in the back exactly where we were before.
But it's like secret like the movie is a lot of just regular footage right.
Yeah.
It's a mocap.
They snuck me into a mocap.
But there's still something about it that feels like he's like it's like a Sega Dreamcast game.
Yeah.
That's how he likes it.
I think Zemeckis likes the uncanny valley.
Yeah he owns the property in the uncanny valley.
Uh huh.
The polar.
It's spacious.
There's no neighbors.
Nobody else wants to live here.
But it's not a throwback like I feel like and I'm sure like in the indie video game world that you I bet you're starting to see if not now I'm sure you will.
At some point like PlayStation one kind of poly gone sort of design like virtual fighter level design because you can do that on like a fucking laptop.
Now you can design that.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
It's interesting.
The Zemeckis one is not really referencing anything besides reality kind of.
It's referencing creepiness.
Yes.
It's referencing looking very strange.
Very strange.
I saw the film.
It's a very strange film.
But I'd rather talk about the fun spinning ride.
Yeah.
Talk about Zemeckis's own real life wife being naked in his film.
Oh wow.
Maybe we do want to talk about that.
No wait that's not.
That's Zemeckis.
We'll do that on the Welcome to Marwen cartoon spin episode.
And we spin out our Welcome to Marwen theme part.
Marwen land.
Welcome to Marwen land.
Dubai.
Marwen land Dubai.
That's what's moving into that Fox space.
Oh yeah yeah.
That's the only buy Zemeckis is going to buy it and make it a Marwen theme park.
You heard it here first.
Trestworthy rumors from podcast The Ride.
Let's talk about the fun spinning ride.
So the line is a bit claustrophobic.
Yeah.
I was just going to jump to back what you were saying about it.
It is sort of not a fun.
It's hot in there too.
I feel like.
Very warm.
And dark.
And then you'll look.
It's mainly you're just like looking at doors and trash cans.
But then you'll look in the little slat while open and the big scary gorilla eyes of the bouncer will be there.
And that's the most entertainment you have.
It's like being in jail.
You're in solitary confinement in this line.
There's something weird about this ride too that is not memorable.
Like the line isn't particularly memorable.
Whereas like Toad's line is so tiny.
And I guess maybe that's but I know the lines for all of those dark rides and fantasy land so well.
I guess it's just because I go on and more.
Especially there's that statue of Toad that everyone stops to take a picture with.
No one's ever.
That is one of the most oddly photographed locations in Disney.
You have to take a picture.
You can see the wear and tear.
It's like the wood is faded a little or whatever is faded where people put their hands.
I'll just say my plus up for this ride right now.
Take the line.
Just take the roof off.
Just remove the roof.
Make it like a nice little park.
We don't need to get into the story.
Just give me a garden to walk through because that I think is what's up with Mr. Toad.
You end up in his house.
But a lot of it.
Yeah, it's just like nice shrubs.
Hey, it's a nice day out.
It's a great line.
I don't need any more shrubs.
I'd rather have a couple of trees and some oxygen.
Yeah, I don't know what I'm trying to remember.
There's nothing like there's crates, right?
There are crates.
There's like crates.
I think you hear the weasels talking.
You hear people talking.
You hear creeps murmuring, talking about plans for what they're going to do to the character you like.
I feel so.
You hear the creeps murmuring.
Yeah.
So, uh, I think that's the thing.
I think the line is the problem.
The line is why I don't go back there.
If I can fast pass it.
Sure.
And it's a good way to fill a little gap in your in your Max Pass hopping around day.
Right.
But if you like, you literally can't do that line.
Like I don't like I'll never do it again.
I hate that line.
Yeah, I get it.
Huh?
Yeah, I get I would guess now that I'm thinking about it and I've been to Disneyland in over
I guess 12 for 12 years now and I've been over 100 times because the annual pass keeps
track and it was over 100 at one point and then it reset because I there was a couple
of times reset.
I don't know.
I've lost track.
I'm upset about that because I was like, oh cool.
It's really tracking it.
And then I let it lapse for a couple of months and now it's back to why you don't let it
lapse.
Don't ever take a break.
Yeah.
I'm like 20 or something.
So I bet I've only been on this ride five times.
I bet it's five in 12 years.
In 12 years.
I bet I've been on it five, six times.
I can't be much more.
It's about where I'm at.
Jason.
No, I'm trying to think like, yeah, it might be around there.
I've been on, you know, big thunder 50, I bet 50 or more times on a mansion, 50 or more
times.
All the big pirates, 50 or more times.
Roger Abbott's five to seven.
Yeah.
And think about where you are in those lines.
You're weaving in and out of a fun little mine town.
You're, you're, you're in a nicely manicured courtyard outside of a stately mansion.
Sure.
And you're in like a nice little fountain area in a new Orleans square.
I like, I think there's something about, I like, I like gardens.
I think I'm a garden guy.
The land opened in 93, the ride opened in 94.
They don't have an excuse.
They built it off from scratch.
They could have made the line big.
Yeah.
Like probably nobody's going to want to go on this.
I guess they were thinking, cause it is like, it is a little bit of a bigger and scope dark
ride, like the fantasy land rides.
So were they thinking like, we'll make the line as short as those lines?
Maybe they didn't have the room.
Like, maybe they, yeah, maybe that's it.
Still, you could have pushed back.
I don't know.
It seems weird.
It seems weird that the line isn't a little bit bigger.
Is there, is this the worst line?
Oh, that's good.
That's a good question.
Worst line.
I don't have any at my disposal.
Fun line.
Astro orbiter is bad.
Cause it's nothing.
It's really tight.
You're stuck.
But does that even count?
Cause it's nothing.
Does the Pixar, Pixar around account?
Cause that's nothing.
That's nothing as well.
You can't load a first wheel.
There's no way to load a Ferris wheel fast.
I think the question now should be changed to of all the lines that are something.
Is this the worst line?
Okay.
That's a good one.
Because the Astro Orbiter is nothing.
The fun wheel is going to call it.
Of course, that's not right.
It's the Pixar pal around.
That thing we do with our friends.
A normal phrase we all know and love.
I didn't even recognize it when you said it.
Oh, it's the Ferris wheel.
I'm the host of this.
You know, it's next to the years long broken fountain show.
It's next to the scrap yard that used to be a fun nighttime extravaganza.
I think you got to go to maybe to like Epcot.
I feel like there's bad Epcot lines.
Spatial birth is outside mostly.
You kind of get on right when you're inside the building.
I almost consider that almost nothing.
I'd almost consider that line.
Nothing.
Beautiful mural to the beautiful seventies kind of mural.
But it's a by the way, let's not to wrap it up.
Let's put it to listeners.
Yeah.
Worst line.
That is something that is something because like Buzz Lightyear, a lot of his outside,
but there is an inside line and I'm trying to think, do I, I like that line better.
It's still a little dated looking now, but you got that big Buzz Lightyear animatronic
there and that's still fun to see him.
There's no that Disney term with the weenie, the thing like, well, even this part's a slog,
but I'm going to get this.
You know, it's a bad line, not star tours, obviously, but the pre star tours, if you
end up in that other room, that's a dragon.
Yeah.
Once you're past, you know, Toy Story Midway Mania lures you in with Mr. Potato Head, which
is great.
Yes.
But once you're past that, that room is awful.
Yeah.
Just the back and forth with only four posters to look at.
Yeah, it's nothing.
That's a thing that makes you have to get a fast pass for the, like you can't get stuck
in there.
Right.
But he's still, that's, I'd rather.
It's not as bad though.
I'd rather be in there.
It's a brighter room at least.
Yeah.
I'm like, I'm getting ready for the carnival.
It's the most theming, it's the most theming worst line.
You know what I mean?
Like it's cause it is a, it is themed the whole way and it is a decent amount, but it
is, yeah.
Huh.
I think, I think it probably wins these parameters in my mind.
I think this is the answer.
I can't think of anything where a line was specifically made with decisions and it's
not good.
It does feel like every now and then you hear about like, well, this was a story decision
or an imagineering decision.
They really should have checked in with operations more because I feel like they're the department
to go like, Oh, that's actually unpleasant for a human to do that for more than five
minutes.
Can we plus it up though as it is, cause there's like certain parts of the Indiana Jones line,
which are claustrophobic, but you're constantly moving, especially now, which I think I've
never said that somebody corrected me.
I said this a while ago that there must be a fire issue with the line, how they move
us through.
That is not the case.
So somebody corrected me online.
I said, cause now there's no, you never really get backed up until you get to sort of the
end of the Indiana Jones line.
Cause you don't get to see all the great details in it because you zoom through it so fast,
but it's not because of some fire issue that's changed.
It's because the way they've had to do fast pass, cause it was not built for fast pass.
So they have to keep most of it clear in order to actually send you to the front for the
fast pass to skip anything.
Exactly.
So that's why it does that now, which is a bummer.
Now we know.
So yeah, somebody corrected me.
Well, it's good to skip parts of the line, but then you don't get to enjoy one of the
best lines and a good claustrophobic line.
In terms of how to plus it up, some lights, lamp.
Sure.
Okay.
Lights, lamp, ceiling off.
Fans.
Yeah.
Is there something you would want to see?
Do we want to see a character?
Oh, I mean, if there was an animatronic Roger talking to you.
So yeah, can we just put a very expensive talking Roger Rabbit, like the potato head,
and would that make us go in the line?
Be like, well, that robot is good.
We're hot as shit by the time we get on the line.
Baby Herman roasting you.
That would be good.
Borscht Belt jokes.
Cause then we would want to go into the line.
I feel like if there was a really good baby Herman.
Let's go see Herman.
Let's go see Herman, see what he's going to say.
Or Jessica Rabbit.
Well, that I wouldn't.
I could handle myself.
I couldn't do that.
I forgot there was a Jessica Rabbit animatronic in this ride.
So I might have to change my leota girlfriend choice.
Oh yeah.
Well, we all forgot.
To Jessica Rabbit.
Because we all forget about this.
And she's got a giant mallet.
So kill me queen.
Smash my head in like Gallagher's watermelon with that mallet.
Hashtag kill me queen.
By the way, is that a thing people say?
Or did you just compile things that people say into kill me queen?
Or have you seen that?
There is like a running joke on Twitter.
I feel like I've seen articles about it now of people saying like, yes, murder me.
Murder me, Ariana.
Murder me.
Oh, OK.
Hemsworth brothers.
It's a jokey way to say, I love you.
You're great.
Gotcha.
Murder me with a gun.
But in this case, she has the literal capacity.
Yeah, she does.
She can kill you.
But you know what?
Let me say this.
I feel like it's, hey, this has been like the line itself.
It's been a dark, dreary journey.
We're talking about how much we don't like this line.
And I think it had to be addressed.
We're talking about rides that never got built.
And you know, then scandalous pornography in these films.
For all that said, I do like the ride.
And I'll say another thing.
I'll amend that a little bit to say, I did really like the ride.
And in my memory, when this came out, so I don't know when you guys went on it
the first time, but I went when I went as a kid, when it opened closer to 94, 95,
it was great.
I might have listed this as in my top five.
Really?
Oh, sure.
And what I think is that the quality has dipped.
I think it like, maybe this is a case of my childhood memory being brighter
than what something is.
I had rose-colored glasses because I was a kid.
But in my memory, the spinning worked better.
It was just generally better kept up.
I feel like it came out of the gate, shiny and glossy and a lot of fun
and all the effects work.
And it was a new type of ride.
It was before there was Trackless, which is kind of the new dark ride innovation.
It was sort of the first new type of dark ride in a long time
to invent a ride vehicle, which is very fun.
And I think it worked better in the 90s.
I think maybe they've sort of just let it not.
I just feel like it's not at operating at peak quality.
But I think the people who made the ride did a great job.
I think it's a great notion of a ride and a ride vehicle.
Well, what if I told you that there's a place where you could go back
to where everything looks shiny and new?
And it is in the land of the rising sun.
Because the only other place this was ever cloned was Tokyo Disney.
And I watched back to back a couple of times the Anaheim version
and the Tokyo version.
And I'm like, are these different?
And they're kind of not.
All of the set pieces, all the show scenes are the same.
So I'm not spoiling anything for you.
But kind of a conclusion we hit on the Tokyo one,
and I forget whether you would scurried away or not,
is everything, everything seems the lighting seems better.
The paint seems better.
The effects seem everything seems to be working.
Shiny ride specifically on this ride from the video.
So I know there's going to be a lot of you got to cram a lot into your time
in Japan.
But if you are thinking, well, I did really like this,
you guys don't know how long I'm going for.
No, we don't.
Oh, I got to bring that.
We'll see.
I'm not even sure I know.
That's a good.
That's good.
That's a great.
I will say this.
We were there for three and a half days.
We did not do this ride.
OK, I think I got to do it.
I think for a second, you should try it.
I'm not going to tell you which language it's in.
I know it's a 50-50 chance.
It's in Spanish.
Didn't see that one coming.
You know, that thought across my mind, and I will definitely
make time to do it unless I can only wait in the line.
And maybe I'll do the line.
And like, the line was great.
The line's fine.
I don't know what the line is.
I might need to do it.
I might need to devote an hour and a half of my time to it.
It's probably that long, because everything's
such a long wait.
OK, there it is.
Well, so I'm hopeful about that.
Because I do, in my memory, this happens.
And I think Toontown in general came out of the gate so strong.
That's what I was going to ask.
It was a fantastic land.
What are your memories of Toontown?
Loved it.
Loved it so much.
I'm sure there's a full Toontown episode down the road.
So I don't want to get into it too much.
But I think you guys have all commented on,
it seems like the paint literally fades.
I feel like it opened, and it was so bright and vibrant.
And to see a land where every structure
is bending and twisting, it was super dynamic to walk around in.
And also keep in mind, Bounce House open.
The Chippendale ball pit and slide open.
You could actually do the things in the land.
I can't go in that ball pit, even if I wanted to.
If I wanted to go take a piss in that ball pit,
it couldn't be done.
Did you do all of that when you were little?
Yeah.
It was great.
It was all so great.
The Bounce House wore me out, I remember.
I remember getting exhausted.
You imagine that you're just like your tigger jumping around.
This will be super easy.
I'll be bounding across the room.
But in fact, it was a tremendous amount of physical exertion.
And other kids are mean, and you're getting stomped on.
But yeah, still, Toontown was fantastic when it opened.
That was, though, we've talked about this, I'm sure,
was when I saw pictures of it.
Because we didn't have it in Florida.
Oh, yeah.
We had Mickey's birthday land, and then that kind of evolved.
But it was not a true Toontown.
I can't wait to talk.
That's the topic I'm looking forward to very much.
Mickey's birthday land slash Mickey's Starland.
Obviously separate.
Two different episodes.
Two totally different than Starland.
Two and a half hour episodes on their own.
But I was so envious of it, because as a kid, especially,
it's living and seeing Mickey where Mickey lives.
And I don't know why it's hanging out in Mickey's house
is the thing I wanted to do.
But I did, I guess.
You gotta see the den.
Yeah.
We gotta try and get a call and response going the next time
we do a live show.
We say, if I want to make a call, you say, I use the den.
What do I use?
The den.
My dream.
That's my rock.
I'm like Mark Wahlberg in the movie Rockstar.
What if I was the leader of my favorite band in the world?
And then it came true.
Hey, everybody.
Where are my calls made?
I think we'll have this dream realized this year.
I think so.
Somewhere that'll happen.
We gotta do it.
Start practicing, everybody.
So just jealous, envious, so imagining
how amazing this must be.
I was very excited about seeing that Indiana Jones ride in,
but more for sure, more so about Toontown.
And of course, as I've said many times, I thought,
oh, man, that sucks.
I'll never, ever go there.
I will never go to California.
Why would I ever go?
I go to two places, Illinois and Florida.
That's it.
That will be it for the rest of my life.
Ricky and Lucy and Fred and Ethel drove to California,
but it was a whole ordeal.
Yeah, and I was on one airplane when I was 15,
and that was it.
Before that, I was like, I'm scared to fly.
You'll crash.
I don't want to do that.
If somebody came to you and said,
not only will you live in Los Angeles for many years,
but about a decade in, Dunkin' Donuts
will migrate to Los Angeles.
I would have been somewhat excited,
but I'm not the Dunkin' man that Jason is.
I go to Dunkin', but we had a donut place
called Family Donuts.
Family Donuts?
Am I losing my mind now?
Not family, that was a family video.
Country Donuts, thank you.
Country Donuts that we liked better.
We thought was a better quality than Dunkin',
and I think they probably were.
So my hypothetical figure from the future says,
what if I told you one day Dunkin' Donuts will be,
well, actually, well, that's all right,
but there's this one that's better.
And I would explain to him that it's not really
one of my favorites.
I would be real pithy about it.
All right, oh well, all right.
I'll go tell Jason about the,
I'll go tell your eventual friend Jason
about the Dunkin' Donuts instead.
He'll like it better.
So, yeah.
What I did, I made it.
I made it to California though.
You made it, and you did go on Roger Rabbit's cartoon spin.
You answered all of the trivia questions correctly
at Lucia Tribute, and you got to California.
Sure.
My future two and a half hour.
Oh, I'm ready for two and a half hours on the Lucy.
Oh, that's right.
We had the discussion in text about
what would be a C ticket, and there was the declaration,
no, no, no, Lucy, a tribute is a full episode.
Yeah, in case you don't.
If you don't know, yeah, there, where, Mike.
I was gonna say, on our Patreon,
which is our exclusive episodes for the subscribers,
like we have little shorter episodes for stuff that,
maybe that doesn't warrant a two hour discussion.
Only an hour. Not that much shorter.
Not that much shorter, yeah,
about a 45 minutes to an hour or something,
and I think, yeah, Scott was like,
you know, we could do Lucy, the Experience on the C ticket.
I think Jason and I were like, no, full episode.
Hang on a minute.
We've got Gail Gordon to get through.
Yeah, so there will be a full Lucy, the Experience episode.
Okay, let me talk about something big
so that I don't forget it.
As I said, a successful part of this ride,
and I think what is neat about this ride,
is that it is a spinning ride, like the teacups,
mixed with a dark ride.
Very cool idea.
I wish the spinning worked better.
It's pretty arduous to do it,
and I found there's something where,
if you're turning left, then if you spin left, it's great,
or vice versa, but if you're spinning against the grain,
the thing kinda struggles.
Which children love to do.
There's gotta be a new version of this.
I don't know if it exists yet,
but there's gotta be a new version of this
where you're just hitting buttons,
and you're not actually, with your strength,
spinning the ride, because that is what,
I think, is happening there.
You are literally using all of your might
to switch the ride to a different direction.
Like an actual old car, no power steering,
no power assisted steering.
Yes, exactly.
A kind of car will never have to drive.
Yeah, and it's not like Buzz Lightyear either,
which is just kind of a joystick.
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
Oh no, you're right, there it is.
That's exactly what I'm saying.
That's the way to do it.
But that's not really an out of control spin.
Right, but I'm sure there's a way to just do that
that's a little bit wilder,
because you don't wanna be wild
when you're trying to shoot at Emperor Zerg.
You want aim and precision.
Yeah, right, but that's exactly what you're saying.
I was like, I don't know if this exists.
So this ties exactly into what I wanted to talk about,
which is that they knew they wanted to do a spinning ride,
and there was the talk of what is our ride vehicle
going to be.
Maybe it is an OmniMover,
which is what the Haunted Mansion most famously is,
and also what Buzz Lightyear is,
where it's a track that is nothing but cars
that is always going
unless somebody needs assistance getting in the car.
And so there was discussion of, well, is it that?
Is it an OmniMover,
or is it something where you're launching individual cars
a la Pinocchio's Daring Journey,
or the other Disneyland, or the other Fantasyland dark rides?
And to solve this issue,
apparently Imagineers got to take a teacup
and put it on the Haunted Mansion and Pinocchio's Daring Journey.
This is a story that has resonated in my head since childhood.
I had to go back into my physical copy of Disney News
that I subscribed to from the 90s,
and I looked it up to make sure I wasn't crazy.
I couldn't find this online anywhere.
This is lost to the sands of time.
You just remembered this from 20 years ago.
And I think it factors into how much I liked the ride,
that I maybe liked the ride more than you guys.
It's possible that I've had this in my head for so long.
The idea that this fantasy
of taking a different ride vehicle,
like the power of these Disney people,
they took a teacup onto the Haunted Mansion
and they spun it around the entire ride.
That's interesting.
That you talk about Disneyland fantasies or whatever,
that is upon remembering it immediately on there.
Yeah, wow, that's like, I'm trying to think
what else you could fit onto the Haunted Mansion track.
Like, cause it's a perfect, I guess, like a toad vehicle.
You could pull like a toad motor car
on the Haunted Mansion track.
But I guess there's no other,
what you'd wanna do is drive a car yourself around.
Yes, that's true.
You wanna take an Autopia car through the Haunted Mansion
is what you wanna do.
Yes, but that's-
Crash into all the tombstones and the ghosts.
Right.
You may as well just take a golf cart though at that point.
Or like a- Yes, great.
Ford Focus or a smart car.
Or send the Haunted Mansion, or send,
sorry, send a Space Mountain bug going through there.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah, that would be good.
Or flood it with water.
And let me take a log through the Haunted Mansion.
Sure.
This is the Disneyland in the future.
What about the Cars ride from the Meteor Springs?
Absolutely.
Yeah, that'd be good too.
Maybe too wide.
I wanna take a Main Street Electrical Parade bug.
Oh, I mean, this is decadent.
Just imagining this.
You won't even allow yourself such a fantasy.
Yeah.
It's too good.
Wait, wait, wait.
Put the Star Speeder on the Haunted Mansion track
and ride Star Tours while you're going
through the Haunted Mansion.
So with like windows, you can also look into the cemetery?
No.
You just know you're there.
You just know.
If you're showing a security video,
you know you're taking a Star Tours
through the Haunted Mansion.
You'll just know it.
It'll be a thing, you'll a little secret.
And Mike, yours would be just a regular Doom buggy,
but Teddy Barrow would be a company.
You know, room for one more.
Like she's the animatronic, pats the seat.
If you could take an entire,
if you could do a swing ride all the way
through the Haunted Mansion,
and you're sitting on a swing with Teddy Barrow.
And Michael's just covered in flop sweat by the end of it.
What about Silly Symphony swings
and Teddy Barrow's in the swing next to you
at California Adventure?
Cause she swings, she's swinging Teddy Barrow.
Yeah, that's true.
So every other one, there's like a robot bear or something.
Like your childhood,
you are withholding your own satisfaction.
Put yourself in the swing.
No, I'm too uncomfortable.
I can't.
I can't have that much happiness.
I want her close, but not touching me.
I would prefer that.
You want her to be able to like,
cheekily wave from afar and wink.
This is what I wanted in junior high,
in high school.
And I want it when we're doing this weird bear fantasy.
The only thing that would be better
than taking a teacup through the haunted mansion.
So apparently this was done.
They did it.
Wow.
And they said, and Pinocchio, let's not discount that.
They took a teacup through Pinocchio.
That's so crazy.
How does this happen?
How does it, like mechanics have to like,
wheel a teacup around and they have to drop it onto a,
how does it even function on those other?
Tight clearances in Pinocchio too.
Yeah, can it even make it through?
It's so straight.
It almost makes me wonder if this is like a made up story.
Did you find the magazine?
Oh yeah, I read it.
Oh, okay, great.
Oh yes, with quotes.
I forgot, I didn't write down their names,
but Imagineers are quoted who say that they did this.
They said that the haunted mansion was cool,
especially because they got to go down the hill
into the cemetery, like, you know,
where you were down by the shaking leg guy.
They got to do that hill spinning the entire way.
And that was super cool.
However,
the public could not be trusted with that ability.
Once you fall out of the teacup
when you're going down to the cemetery.
It is kind of steep.
Or everybody would like spin down to the side.
You could never like stay up on top.
But I feel like you could fall out.
Yeah.
At the angle.
Absolutely, yeah.
Maybe they were like belted around like,
when you're sawing a tree down at the top.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Or they were strapped in like a rapid ride or something.
Jason gave me that.
When I said that Jason gave me the eyes like,
I know.
I know what that tree chopping down is.
Your log in days.
So they did this.
And then, but actually,
so it's something like, well, that was very cool.
Do we do an Omni-Mover?
Then they did Pinocchio.
What they found was, oh, this is so cool.
There's doors smashing open,
something that you couldn't do in the haunted mansion.
Like the haunted mansion, there's no obstacles
because there has to be constant cars going through.
But when you're crashing through doors,
and like, or if you, you know,
clearly there's a part in Roger Rabbit
that's very much like Mr. Toe,
kind of a tribute to Mr. Toe,
to like the explosion goes off and now like,
and it's, and you're spinning while doing it.
So you're disoriented and everything.
So you could do effects like that.
And the coolest thing they found was that
they're spinning towards Monstro at the end.
And they're approaching and Monstro is starting to rise.
Then they do a rotation.
And now Monstro's right in your face.
Right.
So it's as if he's, you know,
he's three times bigger in the space of a second.
So they said, that's what it has to be.
It has to be a fantasy land dark ride combined
with the teacups as opposed to the Omni-Mover.
Yeah.
And this experiment, that's the kind of thing
that makes you like, you'd go,
I'd kill to be an Imagineer.
That's so fun.
So, so neat.
So, it's interesting they went with the full,
like you can decide where you're turning though,
because that specific effect you're talking about
with like all of a sudden coming upon Monstro,
when the guest is doing that, it's like, that's random.
So it is weird that they didn't just make it a spinning ride
that was pre-programmed.
Sure.
Cause it does seem like that way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where they could like make things happen
to their liking.
But I guess, but hey, it's up to you.
It's up to the guest.
I think probably interactive rides are becoming in vogue
because that was in the biggest way gonna happen
with Indiana Jones very soon.
So they're probably thinking,
who guests wanna customize the experience?
And I think they also thought, maybe you don't wanna spin.
Maybe you're not-
Or you mean random ride, like randomized.
Yeah, what did I say?
Customized.
Oh yeah, it's not, yeah, it's not gonna make
your own experience, but like, yeah,
I guess rides that are different every time.
Yeah, that switch between things.
Yeah, yeah, that makes some sense.
But yeah, it does seem like that would be a cool,
cause it seems like with Humpoo's Honey Hunt,
which I apologies again to you for not being able
to do this when you're in Japan.
But like, there's a lot of, I don't know,
there's nothing as big as that reveal you're talking about,
but it is like spins and stuff and you can really
all of a sudden spring something on you
because the audience is not controlling it obviously.
So it does feel like it's a missed opportunity
to do some of that fun stuff.
Well, I get the idea.
I think in retrospect, I think this Roger Rabbit ride
is maybe like a step in the direction of stuff
like Pooh's Honey Hunt.
It's like even more dynamic and that's like
a Fantasyland Dark Ride, but five times longer
and crazier animatronics.
But I do, you know, I think it's a type of ride
that I like, that's all of those Fantasyland rides
are pretty claustrophobic.
They're done very quickly.
You don't cover a lot of space.
And I like that this Roger Rabbit ride is, you know,
two times bigger.
I kind of wish there were more of these.
It's like Little Mermaid, which I enjoy.
It's like Monster Zink, I don't go on a lot,
but I like that it's there, like kind of a two times,
three times bigger Dark Ride.
Yeah, I, Little Mermaid obviously is a good example
of what this kind of feels like.
I do think this one's better than Little Mermaid,
even though like the robots are better
and there's some like better show scenes.
And, but like we were talking like the,
there's a couple more memorable things to me,
like the buildings at the end is a very fun, cool effect.
Yes, great scene.
Yeah, absolutely.
But I do feel like the first half
is a little bit unmemorable to me.
Well, like I said, like it feels like
it's much more memorable in Pinocchio.
Some of the same kind of themes and tricks
and very similar settings kind of are like in Pinocchio
and Toad and they just stick out in my brain more.
And maybe this is my problem for just going on it five times
and not 20 times like, or 30 times,
like I've probably done Toad or Pinocchio.
But I do feel like it's, I don't know what it is.
I don't know if it's like, since it's got a bigger space
and it's not like knocking me out like Pooh's Honey Hunt,
like maybe, I don't know.
It doesn't resonate with me as much.
Doesn't feel iconic maybe?
Yeah, I guess it doesn't feel iconic.
It doesn't feel like it has like these big,
like the biggest, the best thing in the ride
is the buildings, right?
Yeah, you explode, you are exploded out of the building
and you fall from the sky essentially.
You're just going down a hallway,
but because of perspective,
it looks like you are falling.
A trick that I really only associate otherwise with,
I guess isn't too right,
but mostly the amazing adventures of Spider-Man
has a great, like when Dr. Doom is levitating you
and then unlevitates you and you fall
and there's falling buildings on the screen
and like sets around you
and then Spider-Man catches you in his web.
And I think they do it again in Transformers too
because it's got some similar beats.
It's very similar, yeah.
Yeah.
Sort of a visual drop.
Yeah, but I can't think of like a practical dark ride
that really does it,
and at least doesn't do it as effectively
as Roger Rabbit does.
Yeah, it's very clever
and to like shift your perspective on a ride
that is just going flat.
Now there was gonna be something
that would spice the thing up
and give it like a boost over other rides,
which is that in the original plans,
you were gonna go up to a second floor and go outside
and that the entire top level
of like the not the residential half of Toontown,
but the city half with the gag factory and the fire station,
that that second level was gonna have the kinetic energy
of the cabs spinning around up top.
Yeah, sure.
And if you were able to spin around outside
and get a different perspective on the land.
Like that would have done it for me.
Cause it's like most of those rides,
you can pick out three to five things.
That's usually what I say,
like three to five moves or big things where you go,
I love that, that, that.
And then that leads up to a ride.
But like this one, it's like, I like that building thing.
I like that end scene.
Portable hole.
The port, yeah, the portable hole.
The stretching arm is very, very neat.
But those are the two things I think I go,
those two things are great.
And Roger Rabbit, like kind of,
cause you fall through like the roof of the building.
And like, after you fall through the city,
you fall through a building, like with a staircase.
And Roger Rabbit is sort of like up in the one corner
going like, I'll help you, I'll get you down.
It doesn't really stick the landing and the transition
from the stairway to the other factory you go into
or the other warehouse.
Like that's kind of a weird in between hallway.
And like the Jessica, there's Jessica Rabbit,
but it's like, she's kind of an afterthought
in the scene in a way.
And not in the ride elsewhere, not teased.
You're gonna see Jessica Rabbit in this ride.
It's not like you go into a club and it's dark
and there's Jessica Rabbit and she's singing or something,
which seems like that would have been the time,
that would have been such a showcase kind of scene.
And like a concert is going haywire.
Sure.
Like she's being chased around
or the angels have taken it over.
It feels like it's missing stuff like that
or something like where you really kind of get.
Is baby Herman in the ride?
It's a good question.
I don't know the answer to it, right?
They said, what I read was that the Imagineers
were attempting to capture the essence of Roger Rabbit.
And I think that is a more interesting point of view
than Little Mermaid, which is like, I guess.
The telling the story.
The book report as Tony sometimes says,
the book report version of the story.
That's true, yeah.
But then you end up like missing big things
you like from the movie.
You misspeak them.
I mean, there's no mention of Bob Hoskins characters
or other humans and stuff.
Weird thing that always kind of rubbed me the wrong way
that bumped for me is like in the opening scene,
like the first time you spin,
it's because like they dumped the dip on the ground.
But like Roger and Benny are in the middle of the dip
and they're just kind of like, whoa.
And it's like, shouldn't Benny be dead?
Like shouldn't he be dead?
You are of course in Lenny the Cab.
That was the thing I learned about.
You ride in Lenny the Cab, his relative.
Why in the world are you not,
I guess it's because they wanted Benny to be,
you wanna be able to see Benny.
So you're in Lenny.
But who cares?
What do you mean?
I don't think I would care.
I think just, I'm in the,
why create an identical brother?
Yeah.
It's very confusing.
Prestige-esque.
The prestige really ripped off
the Roger Ebbett cartoon spin, right?
We didn't really talk about loading into the ride.
I didn't remember this is what the cars looked like.
That it's like two people to a car,
but each car, but there's two cars.
It's like a pair of cars every time.
So if you have a party of four,
you can all kind of ride together.
And I guess it's split up so if some people wanna spin
and some people don't, you can do that.
But it's a weird shrunk midi cars.
Okay, so what you just reminded me,
obviously you can't be in Benny.
You have to be in Lenny so you can see Benny.
But you're next to another Lenny.
So why are we okay with two Lenny's?
Why can't we just be,
if we're already breaking car math.
Are they all, like how did the taxi,
cause there are other cabs in Toontown, right?
It's not just Benny.
Clearly Lenny is also pulling some of the weight.
Lenny is not in the movie, right?
Lenny is totally ride specific.
So Lenny is like Botanicus.
Lenny is a created for, well no, no,
that's not different cause he was created in a book first.
So it's not Botanicus, but it's a,
who's a ride specific character.
Well we'd have to go to who censored Roger Rabbit
and figure out how many taxi cabs are in that.
Okay, but we haven't done that.
Oh yeah, so Lenny the cab could be in the book,
which is why Gary Wolf is owed money.
Right.
Maybe he is in canon.
He is like just out of the clink.
He was doing some time.
And then the ride is post movie.
So he is back on his feet, turned his life around.
Okay, yeah.
So there's multiple Lenny's.
There's multiple Lenny's.
But I guess in the narrative of most rides,
the other cars don't exist.
Even though some, a lot of rides,
car vehicles are different and named differently,
but I think you're not supposed to see the other people.
It's supposed to be just you're during this happening once.
In Alice in Wonderland, you're in the caterpillar
and then you see the caterpillar.
That's true.
Yeah, who gives a shit?
Why are we starting to break this apart now?
You know, it was the 60s man.
And suddenly in the 90s.
It was the 60s.
The 90s was just, everyone was having their lattes.
They were too logical in the 90s.
I guess probably it's like the Cars Ride 2
where it's like you're in very similar
to Lightning McQueen's, but they're not Lightning McQueen.
They're different colors.
They don't have names.
I think it's just naming it Lenny
is the thing that's throwing us off.
All of them are Lenny.
That is an issue for me.
You're inside a Lenny that's next to another Lenny.
Should have just not named it Lenny.
No.
It should just be Citizens.
That's a-
Lenny and Kenny, it's another one.
A thing that's always rubbed me the wrong way
about Toontown though is Mickey's Toontown.
It's Roger Rabbit's Toontown.
Mickey is a resident.
Roger's the king.
This is a different, I think it's a different Toontown.
I think it's like there's multiple Springfields
in the world.
But isn't that Toontown like the bad Toontown?
Mickey's Toontown is Disney Toontown.
It's a little wacky, but it's friendly.
But they're splitting the difference.
And they're just splitting.
But I'm saying once you go on the ride,
it's like the bad part of town or something.
Like that's the Roger Toontown.
But that's just Los Angeles.
Sure.
I'm just saying, I think that's probably the difference
they make in their heads.
Outside it's Mickey's Toontown, inside the Roger Rabbit.
Obviously it's Roger's.
But then wouldn't that just be downtown LA?
Because that's where all the warehouses and the judge
and stuff are, right?
But it's still a different, you have to take the tunnel
to get to Toontown.
It's still a separate place.
That's true.
It's sort of a north side, south side Chicago situation.
There's friendlier parts and there's less friendly parts.
Sure.
That's what's happening.
You don't really go through a tunnel
to get to this Toontown either.
I guess you de facto go under the Disneyland Railroad.
But they don't make it look like
like they're gonna make.
The graphic 110 exit that was used for.
They're gonna have the frightening tunnel.
Frightening tunnel, yeah.
For Nintendo Land you're gonna go through a pipe.
I mean that's great.
Which is very exciting, yes.
Oh man.
There's like a big start button outside supposedly
and then there's like a big green pipe you go through
to get into Nintendo Land.
And if the rides are broken they just blow on them.
Sure.
Hey.
Wish I could press that.
I knew I had to couch that in an annoying voice.
The cat scale comedian voice.
I knew it was a little bad.
Wish I could press that start button
to pause the people coming into the land.
Cause it would be so crowded.
It's gonna be so crowded.
It's starting to get scary.
All right.
Crowd control is not great, no.
We'll write all these jokes down and put it in a set.
A standup set.
Yeah, sure.
The most successful set of all time.
And then obviously close with,
what, where do I, here's the phone.
So, what, okay.
I mean you're right that scenes are not super memorable.
But fun.
I don't wanna be like a hater.
I don't hate this ride or anything.
I know, I feel like this episode's been more negative
than it needs to be.
I don't think so.
I like it, but I think we could like it more.
It could be bright.
I'm hoping that I find what I'm looking for
in the Tokyo version.
You know, there's some cynicism and some brightness
in the movie itself.
It feels like a fitting tribute to this world,
to the characters, to the late Bob Hoskins,
which so great.
Bob Hoskins is so great in that movie.
Well I don't think the ride's a fitting tribute
to the late Bob Hoskins.
No, I mean our episode is a fitting tribute.
It is?
Isn't it?
Why?
Well, a fitting tribute to the spirit of the movie.
You've talked about him for like two minutes.
And he's a part of the movie.
I don't, come on.
I like him, I just don't think we tributed him.
Yeah, I don't think we said barely anything about him.
I certainly have not said the name Bob Hoskins
the whole time. Okay.
I guess the movie in general.
His memory will always remain.
He's a great actor.
It's a wily, the spinning,
with hard to spin movie.
We were monitoring Nintendo Land.
Oh yeah.
Of course he was famously Mario after.
There'll be a start button and then there'll also be a sign
that says in memory of Bob Hoskins.
Yeah, like kind of like a little shrine,
like a Catholic shrine or something to Bob Hoskins outside.
He was very good.
He was, he like Christopher Lloyd also in this film,
so blew my mind as a child.
That's all the same guy.
Yeah.
Doc Brown and Judge Doom and Fester are all the same guy.
Eddie and Smee and Mario are all the same guy.
Crazy.
These guys were so goddamn good.
Yeah, Christopher Lloyd, Rick Moran,
it's like early comedy, comedy heroes.
Early comedy.
I really liked Camp Nowhere.
Like Christopher Lloyd's really funny.
It's like this like weirdo who helps these kids
have a camp with no other adult supervision.
Yeah.
This episode is a fitting tribute to Camp Nowhere.
Okay, all right.
That is just about enough.
It's really fed up.
Pumkin' holes.
Well, what else do we got?
Because we have a little bit of other stuff to talk about.
Our outro, our tribute to ourselves.
I mean, yeah, we like it.
Just like I wish there had been more Roger Rabbit,
I wish they had come to terms to make a full land
or continue making movies and stuff with the characters.
I wish they would like figure out solutions to like the line
or like gussy up the paint and the lights and stuff like that.
And I think if there had been more Roger Rabbit
in the parks, I think that might have encouraged
there to be more films.
It might have kept him alive a little more.
It's like, is there a bigger missed opportunity
franchise-wise than who friend Roger Rabbit?
But isn't Jessica Rabbit merch a thing that does sell?
Yeah, but there's not that much of it anymore.
Right.
There used to be a lot more, I think.
But now I don't even know if I can remember
seeing something recently.
Back to Betty Boop now.
If you're sexy and into the 40s, you
want to represent that with a purse, turn to Betty Boop.
I mean, one of the things that's stuck around
since opening of Islands of Adventure, no shortage
of Betty Boop merchandise.
Yeah, and then that Simon Cowell-produced Betty Boop
movie, which is true.
That's a real thing.
What?
Did that happen?
No, but I think like a year ago it was like Simon Cowell
to produce Betty Boop movie.
That's not made up.
That's real.
You want him to produce movies now?
I guess so.
Yeah, so maybe Betty Boop will.
Paula Abdul's family circus.
I could pick of no way to top that.
With that Roger Aveds cartoon spin,
and if we missed anything, please let us know,
because we jumped around a lot.
But we need to jump to something else, something else big.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I hope I didn't build it up too much.
And yet, there's no way to build it up too much,
because this is major news.
If you are an avid listener to the podcast,
then you know that we have been tracking for a long time
since before the podcast began the opening of Jimmy Buffett's
Margaritaville, the resort in Orlando,
which is not just a hotel, but also a timeshare situation,
like a condo.
But you can live in the Margaritaville Resort.
Yeah, it's a village, right?
Well, it's unclear exactly what the terminology is.
It was announced as Margaritaville Village,
which is good.
But then it became Margaritaville Village,
which is not good.
It was clunky.
On the website, it just says Margaritaville Resort now.
So I don't think the village is being used anymore.
Which is different than Latitude's Margaritaville,
which is like a 55 and older residential neighborhood.
It's not a retirement community.
It is a water park slash hotel slash place you can live slash,
I don't know.
Mud pits?
Have they fixed the mud pits?
I don't know about them.
They're just keeping the houses out of there.
Let nature solve the mud pits, and then we'll build a house.
Let the gas station deal with it, the adjacent gas station.
But what is clear is that we don't even know the name of it.
Let's you know that they have had some trouble
with the names in this place.
And in fact, they put it out to any potential condo buyers,
which we pretended to be, to say, please help us name
our streets.
This is a year and a half before we start doing this podcast,
I think.
And I think I got the email first,
and it was like, hey, Parrot Heads,
we're creating a Margarita Village in Orlando.
Send us some ideas for fun Jimmy Buffett inspired street names.
And they gave us all the different like,
avenue, street, circle.
You can do anything you want.
So we got on a text chain with, I
don't know if we were all in the same text chain,
but three of us and then Anthony Geo, past guest Anthony Geo.
We got to have him on.
I know, he has to have him on.
Yeah, we've only been on that singular episode.
It's kind of short changed him by only having him the once.
Right, he's certainly not been on a ton of times.
So yeah, the four of us just made up
a bunch of names for streets.
How many?
100.
100 in total.
We all separately.
And I remember, I was more unemployed at that moment
than I have been in a while.
And I was like, oh god, something to work on.
I treated it like an assignment.
I worked really hard on my names.
Something to do, purpose.
So I'm very fond of these street names for that reason.
My contribution is to the list of 100.
And we sent this list and we heard nothing.
They didn't even go, that's funny.
You sent 100 names.
I have the email here.
Hold on one second.
I just don't think it's weird that they didn't go.
They acknowledged it, but I think
they didn't go like, oh my god.
That's what I think I was expecting.
So yeah, so here, I won't say the name
of the person who sent it to me, but it was like, hi Mike.
It's time for us to begin submitting names
for the streets in Margaritaville Resort Orlando.
I would love to have your creative help in naming
our streets for the resort.
Feel free to use song lyrics, sea, sun, and ocean themes,
or anything that screams Margaritaville lifestyle.
Below are some street suffixes
to help you complete the names.
I really appreciate your participation and input
as we create a truly unique destination in Orlando.
Finn's Up, and this is from, this is Tuesday,
January 26, 2016.
This is three years ago.
Over three years ago.
Predating the podcast.
We came together cosmically with the magic of Buffett.
And when you say suffixes, it's just words like road,
way, lane, circle, alley.
Boulevard, circle, cove, drive, garden,
parentheses S, gardens, lane, loop, parkway,
path, place, road, street, trace, trail, and way.
Yeah.
Now we posted about this and we talked about it
in the Margaritaville sector of the City Walk Saga,
and we tweeted all of the names.
I just remembered that we did that.
So you may have read the names.
Perhaps we'll retweet them to remind you.
Sure.
We sent them 100 names.
And lo and behold, a video is released very recently
by the YouTube user, The Tim Tracker.
Clearly there are some people who follow us
who also follow him.
He goes and tours construction sites and theme parks
and makes these very exhaustive videos.
Somebody on our Facebook group found a screenshot.
Let me credit that person if I can find it in time.
Amanda Hasaka noticed a freeze frame in this video
saying with the address of the particular location,
the timeshare condo that this guy toured.
This condo is at 8029 Dreamsicle Drive.
Dreamsicle Drive.
Now I'm looking at the master list on the email.
Number three submitted is Dreamsicle Drive.
I mean.
Ladies and gentlemen, the quest to name a Margaritaville street.
You know, if you throw out a hundred darts,
one of them's gotta land.
A thousand monkeys at a thousand typewriters.
One of them will eventually type the words,
Dreamsicle Drive.
Ladies and gentlemen, you may now live on Dreamsicle Drive
thanks to your friends at Podcast The Ride.
Wow, I mean it is.
We did it.
I was gonna say, ladies and gentlemen, we got him.
Mission accomplished.
Yeah, so Dreamsicle is a song of Jimmy's.
Yes, no, tell me, cause I don't know this.
I don't know what Dreamsicle is.
I know with Saturday Night Live,
you're not supposed to take credit for yourself.
They do more now.
You take your credit for your sketches maybe.
But like in the old days, I think Dreamsicle Drive is mine.
I'm pretty sure.
That's a deeper level.
Mine was a lot of nonsense because I don't know
the actual songs as much.
But yeah, yours, this is right at the top of the list.
As far as they read, I think they saw this list and said,
we gotta throw one of these,
we gotta throw these guys a bone.
What's like, please, let's not have to read
this entire thing.
Third one's fine, great, let's go with it.
Yeah, you'd think it'd be mine
cause it's pretty close to Creamsicle.
Pretty close to the delicious orange flavored treat.
A Dreamsicle is a Creamsicle.
Oh yes.
It's a brand.
You're right, it's a different brand.
It's a brand name basically.
Dreamsicle is on the album Volcano,
which you may know that song.
It's like, do do do do do do.
I don't know where I'm gonna go when the volcano blows.
You know that one.
I don't know.
We know that one.
Usually at Margaritaville restaurants,
there's a volcano that erupts.
I don't know.
Green, like a margarito.
Yeah, anyway.
So the song Dreamsicle is on that album
and I won't read all the lyrics,
but I'll read the four lines
where the word Dreamsicle appears.
I shot myself in the foot by condemning myself
to have to hear lyrics.
You have to, although you know what,
I'm gonna go back now, four lines.
No, you're punishing me.
Okay, I got house pets, leer jets,
trying to learn about bassinets.
Oh, Miss Piggy, dance with me.
Let me take you to the sea.
And then that's the first floor.
And then he goes,
I'm no longer proud of this accomplishment.
Then he goes, Dreamsicle, Big Dill Pickle,
high school honeys sure were fickle.
I'll be damned, country ham,
take me back to Alabama.
So that's the-
It's okay.
Is Lindsay laughing upstairs
because she's hearing this?
She knows Dreamsicle.
Because Edwin is also running up and down the hallway.
Oh, okay.
She clarified she is not laughing at the song lyrics.
The dog is running up and down the stairs.
I for sure tortured her with Dreamsicle before.
Most days in this apartment,
Mike is reading the lyrics of Dreamsicle out loud.
Those lyrics are all over the place,
even for Jimmy Buffett.
Like Big Dill Pickle, I feel like is a reuse
from the Cheeseburger in Paradise universe
from like hamburger fixings details.
I don't want to pickle anywhere near a Dreamsicle.
Do you want to hear the rest of the lyrics?
Was he talking about bassinettes?
We'll make that a Patreon, that's the second game.
Did he just have a kid?
Is that why he was talking about bassinettes?
I don't actually know the history of Dreamsicle.
I should look into it.
All right, back to the lyrics.
And they're not as good as those eight lines,
but I mean, he goes, let me tell you now,
he sips, he quips, dreams a lot about sailing ships,
wants to throw it all away, wants to have it back someday,
loves fool, seers tool, wants to win that football pool,
span it on some real good grass,
disappear in oh so fast.
That's not as good as the other,
now sailing a ship is just him going back to the well,
or in the case of Jimmy, the bay.
Sure.
Going back to the bay.
Yeah, I think that's, yeah, he, he, look,
he writes a lot about boats, he writes a lot about,
he writes about food more than Weird Al.
That's a thing.
Weird Al doesn't make as many albums,
because Weird Al has quality control.
You take that back.
So yeah, so Dreamsicle Drive is real.
We don't, I was looking and trying to figure out
if this is on Google Maps yet, it is not.
No, none of the streets are, and it's only via this video,
so thank you Amanda for bringing this to our attention.
We wouldn't have known to take this victory lap,
if not for this screenshot, and also thank you
to the Tim Trekker for exploring an empty condo.
Which by the way, did you guys watch the video?
I did, I like Tim, Tim is not backpack man,
I will say this, Tim seems like a nice man.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, no, he seems good and thorough
and informative, this place looks like garbage.
The garbage patch.
I will say that Tim seemed very excited about it,
and I was like, this all looks like this is gonna fall apart
in six months, this doesn't look.
It looks like the town where the Cat in the Hat movie is set,
where the live action Cat in the Hat.
Well I didn't, I actually, Margaritaville Enterprises
didn't have much to do with it,
we teamed up with a Mercurial Casino owner,
and we're just kind of licensing partners.
These guys named Fuck Jerry built the houses.
You'll learn about it all soon in two documentaries.
We got three cardboard boxes stacked them on top
of each other, you can live there for 300 grand.
Luxury VIP villas.
I was ready to suck dick for Margarita.
Wait, what?
Maybe they didn't have one Firefest documentary
with the guys.
That is a very topical joke.
Hey, I haven't watched any of these documentaries,
I'm sorry.
You haven't caught the Dicksuck Man?
I haven't caught the Dicksuck Man.
Unfollow hashtag fuck fuck Jerry,
shout out to Make Records.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, sorry.
That was a good joke, I can tell now.
Yeah.
Unfollow Fuck Jerry, follow the Tim Tracker
and the official Margaritaville Resort Twitter.
Yeah.
My favorite thing about this video,
and we'll post this, is that Tim is so excited
about a strip mall that's being built nearby.
Well, to be fair, we talked about the strip mall
for about half an hour.
That's why Tim is one of us, is what I'm saying,
and he's very excited, he's like,
oh my God, there's gonna be so many stores here.
There's gonna be a restaurant.
Wow, a Lidz.
Wow.
You also keep multiple times,
the last few months have been like,
this place where I live, this town, Santa Clarita,
is really coming up.
Like the next five, 10 years,
it's really shaping up nicely here in Santa Clarita.
I'm not saying I'm not embarrassing, too,
I'm just saying I think it's so funny
because he's walking around empty buildings
and he's like, wow, there's gonna be restaurants.
Oh, sure.
He points out that, imagine that you could live
next to a spa, like a day spa.
That's your house, and then that's a day spa
right next to it.
I have the names.
And it's all on Creamsicle Drive.
Creamsicle, what's it?
There's a Creamsicle Drive.
I have some of them.
I don't even know.
Like Peter Parker, easy to remember.
So they didn't forget.
There's Parrot Perch, there's Surf's Up Fitness,
which looks like a pretty standard hotel gym.
Yeah, yes.
Which is on the site.
There's the Saint Somewhere Spa.
He's like, wow, can you believe it?
Like you go to a spa right here.
It's the Saint Somewhere Spa.
There's the Parakeet's Kids Club, not done yet.
It's just an empty room at this point.
Why don't they keep, why does this guy
run around filming videos?
I don't know.
Nobody should be allowed in here.
Did you catch, though, what will make this
a lot more attractive for Scott Garner to move in?
No, I don't know what you're,
I didn't watch all 18 minutes.
There is a winery across the street.
Well, well, well.
What would Jimmy Buffett name a winery?
Is there a-
It's not his, though.
It's just a cupcake.
It's the cupcake one.
Obviously, but obviously, no, it would be called,
it would be named after his song, The Why No I Know.
That's a real song.
I didn't make that up.
Which is how you describe me in conversation.
Yes, that is what I say.
The Why No I Know.
Who's Scott Garner?
I don't know him.
He's the Why No I Know.
Now, Lindsay's laughing at Jimmy Buffett content
from upstairs.
There is a Margaritaville wine subscription club, right?
Am I imagining-
Oh, is that right?
I think that's, is that true?
The brightest, bluest wine in town.
I don't know.
It tastes like salt.
It's a lost, hints of lost shaker.
Tastes of lost shaker.
Hints of pickle.
A lot of tannins and also pickle.
Do I detect Heinz 57?
On the back of the tug.
There's a little aftertaste.
Did you look into what was there before?
This like China?
Splendid China, which was like owned by China.
It was criticized-
It was a Chinese owned area in Orlando?
We have to do a lot more research into this,
but Splendid China was criticized for being owned
by the government of the People's Republic of China
and that officers of the corporation that owned,
controlled and operated Florida Splendid China
were appointed by the State Council
of the People's Republic of China.
The critics cited the following specific allegations
about the inclusion of minority exhibits.
They were protesting.
It's a lot to read, but it was Tibet stuff.
Oh my God.
Oh.
Yeah, it was, yeah.
So the People's Republic of China made a land deal
with Margaritaville holding CLC.
Right.
But like look at this.
It's a beautiful Chinese garden.
That is really insane.
And now it is a bunch of tin boxes.
Yeah.
Like they all look like 50s track homes,
but like three stacked on top of each other.
Yeah, you gotta have multiple stories.
This is like a demented Tim Burton town.
Margaritaville.
We have to do, I have an email address too
for if you wanted to audition to be a performer,
like their whatever, like their performance space.
And it was-
So acoustic guitar, steel drums,
a second set of steel drums.
Right.
Where'd it go?
I'll find it's for something.
Just a toucan sitting around.
So if you're a toucan, apply today.
You know, like that China story,
we got some flack recently
because we were revealed we are owned
by the Shen Yun people who put them on this billboard.
We're on the Shen Yun.
We're switching to the Shen Yun podcast network.
There's gonna be a lot more acrobatics on the show.
I know it's tough to do acrobatics audio-wise.
But it is thousands of years of history.
It's a proud tradition.
You'll hear the fabric flopping around.
It'll work as a podcast.
I do think before this place gets blown away by a hurricane,
we should try to do a live show in the town square maybe
with no amplification.
By the weakest hurricane Florida's seen in 20 years.
Just a strong wind might take these houses away
from the look of this video.
Yes, it turns out you cannot,
the parade floats cannot fit down the street
when people are on it and there are no emergency exits.
So again, that's what happens when you partner
with a mercurial casino owner.
I feel like Jimmy Buffett,
much like Lyle Landley on the Simpsons.
I got a suitcase full of money.
I'm outta here.
See you later Orlando.
Like, and this thing will just like fall apart
as fast as the Monterey.
I got a hiding hole in China.
Thanks to my thanks new Chinese friends.
I've bought all those little castles
in the mountains in Turkey that are uninhabited.
All of these buildings are all gonna get picked up
by the wind and carried over to the vacant pool
in the Queen of Versailles mansion.
That's gonna be a big stack of pink and teal,
cheap roofing.
Now I hear they have great views
of the Disney World fireworks at the Queen of Versailles
mansion so I guess we have to do a second episode
about the Queen of Versailles mansion.
And there's a Queen of Versailles themed casino wing.
That's what the part of the Star Trek experience became
because the Queen of Versailles company Westgate bought,
so it's very theme park tied in.
It absolutely is.
We do have to say though,
Westgate vacation time shares are a great value
because you're only on vacation a few weeks of the year
so why would you pay for the whole year?
People don't get to see their families.
Families being torn apart,
vacation's more important now in the recession than ever.
Yeah, we are partially owed Westgate vacations.
Yeah, we took the Westgate money and the Shen Yun money
and we're doing great.
We're joining Buffett in that hiding hole
and of course all the royalties that we're going to get
from having named Dreamsicle Drive.
Yeah, exactly.
We're in the money, gentlemen, for sure.
I have preemptively burned off my fingerprints
just to be safe.
Here's my final question.
Do we have a lawsuit on our hands?
Can we sue now for not being compensated
for naming this street?
No, we gave that on our own volition, I believe.
But maybe we didn't kind of know the scope
of what we were doing.
Maybe we just thought it was a fun thing
and now it is a real thing
and people are living on this street.
They actually are using our idea.
I think we may have a case.
Yeah, living in your ideas,
but our idea is what if you named this song
that is a trademark of a popsicle company.
That's true, but we have documented proof
that it was our idea.
We do, unfortunately, all of the cash reserves
for this company is Confederate money.
Sorry, it's half Confederate money
and half Iraqi dinar.
I use a shell company to build all this stuff.
Mr. Trump, I've been reading on Twitter,
Mr. Trump's gonna adjust the Iraqi dinar
and it's gonna be worth a lot of money.
Suddenly I'm pro-Trump.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Mr. Trump, fix the dinar.
It is possible that the people in this place
wake up one morning and they're just on land
and all the houses are gone
because they were picked up in the middle of the night
and they just move them to another country
and we're gonna pull the same grift
on another set of people.
He was like, what the hell?
It's a good way to dispose of dumb people from this.
Because the house is so thin,
the walls are so thick.
Like the sting, like a full fake business.
Yeah, it's a fake resort
and then he has like 30 helicopters come in
and pull the houses up and the people,
just they put them out
and they're just sleeping on the grass.
I'm taking these to Margaritaville, Abu Dhabi.
You guys didn't get the hint when we played the theme
from the sting on all our playlists, like a lot.
We tried to give you a warning.
One of my favorite things is that in all the houses
they have the concoction machine
and he's like a $30 margarita maker.
30, no, that's like $300.
Oh, is it that much?
Yeah.
Well, I apologize.
It cost 30 to make.
Oh yeah.
But if they, okay, if they gave us each a blender
and like filled it with dreamsicles,
would that shut you up?
Yes.
Now we don't, now we are in owed money.
That is what I want.
I think that they owe us something, I guess.
Maybe a lawsuit's not the situation,
but I think that they certainly owe us
at least one concoction maker to split
between the three of us, the four of us.
Sure, yeah.
And also we don't know if there are more streets.
Here's what I know.
I know there are more streets we've seen.
I've looked at the Airbnb listings
or one of the real estate.
I was like, let me see every street name.
You got your flip-flop way, sandbar drive,
shaker street, key lime loop.
None of these were on our list.
Now we did submit to them Seaplane Avenue,
one word, seaplane.
They have seaplane spaced out lane.
So does that count as one of ours?
Fuck yeah it does.
Pay up Margarita.
That is a better punch up, seaplane lane.
But the core of the idea was us.
I mean the real base of the con,
anybody can punch up a good idea
and put a little ribbon on it.
But we gave them the raw meat.
We need to look at like WGA bylaws
and use some of the legalese in there.
Yeah and we need to get Jack Allison
and Seth Simons involved.
We need to, we'll get a big Twitter rouse going on.
And this'll end up going our way.
All I'm saying is that maybe there are little like
sort of courts or cul-de-sacs or like utility entrance
for the hotels or something that's named after
one of our streets like Ribbs Lane or Dill Drive.
Or Lobster Lane.
Yes, so look like trucks need to get back and forth
and make deliveries and why can that not happen
on Pelicans Beak Bay?
Or my favorite, Shorts Street.
I believe that is yours Scott.
Hey all right.
Shorts Street.
Shorts Street can be a gutter.
That's fine.
As long as it's getting anybody,
anything from one place to another.
Be that dirty water or several rats or termites
as high as if it's being used to get from place to place,
it's a street, name it.
Shorts Street is deceptively simple
and that is such a hard thing to do in common.
Like everything where it's like, oh that was so funny.
It was so simple.
Has had so much work to it and I feel like
it's a gold standard like Shorts Street.
Well yeah, you know when I thought of Shorts Street,
I felt like in a pretty top creative time in my life,
I felt like all the gears were turning
and I was just open to,
but you always just gotta be open to divine intervention
because I don't have the ideas really it's from the Lord
and the Lord gifted me,
but I was open to receiving Shorts Street.
Mm-hmm.
I hear you.
That's gotta be the type of wisdom
on your vanity pseudo-religious website, GRIFT.
You start soon.
When I get to my.
Yeah, when you get to your level.
Learn the secrets of succinct funny street names
with Zen Master,
Scott Gardner School of Street Naming.
We're not gonna tell you what kind of God,
but like there's a spirituality aspect.
Whatever it is for you,
any spirit in this universe can bequeath to you
a funny street name.
And if you check out our videos or our articles,
click the store button while you're there.
This place don't run for free.
Yeah.
So we're feeling great.
And I think it'd be the ultimate trip if,
I mean we're gonna plug the regular stuff.
Check us out at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
Go to Twitter, Instagram and Facebook,
Facebook where you can get great info
like screenshots of Dreamsicle Drive.
Yeah.
But really the best thing you could do for us
would be to buy a condo on Dreamsicle Drive.
Yes.
The best way to honor this podcast.
I was gonna also say we did this on our Hanna Barbera episode
and I think this is a perfect time to do it again.
If you wouldn't mind rating and reviewing us on iTunes,
but when you're commenting,
you don't have to say like how great of a podcast.
Just name a fictional,
like name a Margaritaville Street for us.
What would you have named a Margaritaville Street?
So flood our Apple Podcasts.
So it's Hanna Barbera characters.
Well they're Thai.
Like what neck wear they would have.
Oh sorry, yeah what neck wear they would have.
And then now when you're-
Well for example, this podcast gave me so much joy
and relaxed me so I felt like I was driving down
gumbo gardens.
Yes, exactly.
Or like yeah, I was hanging out on Skippin' Work Circle.
You know, that's the type of thing.
So yeah, you would come up,
obviously read through our 100
and make sure you don't have any duplicates.
A flash flood washed away cars on gumbo gardens
after a faulty drainage,
poorly constructed, cheaply constructed drainage ditch
failed to work properly.
A tall man leaned on a building and knocked it over.
The Orlando Margarita Resort.
Exposing a woman taking a shower and she went,
oh a man.
A man.
And also in the reviews let us know what a man is from.
So unlike if you lived at Margaritaville for six months,
you survived podcast The Ride.
Appreciate it, we'll see you on Dreamsicle Drive.
Fins up.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen,
Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
Engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.