Forever.
Dog.
Warning. Today's episode includes everyone's least favorite Indiana Jones adventure.
Old oars with old men's names.
And the thrilling conclusion to a tale involving two pizzas.
Welcome to our Tropical Hideaway episode, you lucky people you.
It's Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, hosted by three grown men who can finally sleep at night, knowing
that Munch's Make Believe band is fully intact at several Chuck E. Cheese locations across
this great nation.
I'm Scott Garner, joined by Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
I'm Mike Carlson.
I saw a couple people tweeted us this, letting us know of certain locations where you have
the full Chuck E. Cheese band is still playing and rocking out at the restaurant.
Because we were worried because they're supposedly getting rid of the band.
This is Jason Sheridan by the way.
It may still happen.
And it's been in the process of happening for a long time.
This is following up on something we talked about in our episode about fellow beloved
food centric animatronic Sunny Eclipse with Jenny Nicholson.
We were expressed our concern that the band was starting to disappear.
And for a long time, there's been this version that's a bunch of screens and only one Chuck E. Cheese
who I don't like, who just has a big boring t-shirt with a C on it and gym shorts.
I don't like that Chuck.
He's got to have the bowler hat and he's got to be a wise guy in a tuxedo.
To clarify though, there are no bowler hat Chuck E. Cheese bands or are there?
I think there are.
That I'm not sure.
I'm forgetting at the moment what if you're seeing a full Munch's Make Believe band, I forget what Chuck is wearing.
I saw the...
It's not so 2002 skater punk.
But it's in that vein.
I saw a picture, somebody tweeted us a picture of the full band and Chuck E. is not wearing, he's wearing more of the shirt and shorts.
Skateboard guy.
Because he's kind of gone through a couple different looks after the bowler hat.
He has the skateboard look, but then he also is like, the newer one is like the shrunken mouse, rock and roller mouse, I think.
Who has like a guitar and I think is voiced by the lead singer of Bowling for Soup.
The band we all talk about at all times, Bowling for Soup.
They tapped into the coolest music to revamp Chuck.
Yeah, that's the strangest thing about all the Chuck E. Cheese is that you're looking at...
You can have in your view five different Chucks at any get.
Like the one on the video is a puppet and then there's a walk around that looks different than the animatronic.
Right.
It's all a big mess and it's been a big mess for a long time.
And depending on what restaurant, maybe they have different Chucks.
I'm hoping somewhere there's a bowler hat Chuck.
I think there might be.
Somewhere.
Does the walk around one...
Can the walk around one be out and about while the show is going on?
I feel like they don't have the discipline to factor a bad show.
I agree with you.
I agree with what you're saying because my memory as a kid was that he would just be roaming around while the robot was on stage.
Yeah.
And I'm a weird...
I was a weird enough little kid where I would have been like, well, this is impossible.
Like this is cognitive dissonance.
I mean, I wouldn't have been a little kid talking about cognitive dissonance, but I would have known something was up.
I had a weird feeling.
Yeah.
I like to kind of think of it maybe as like a Chuck multiverse or Chuck E. Cheese multiverse where there's different versions.
Earth two Chuck E or three Chuck E.
That I would have been...
That justification would have been OK with me as a little kid.
Right.
Because it's a nerdy DC comics thing.
Yeah.
Into the Chuckiverse.
The Chuckieverse.
I mean, if we're not hired to write that, I don't know who should be.
Well, if it's anything, if it's anywhere near the ilk of Chuck E. Cheese's previous film, which I believe is called Chuck E. Cheese in the Galaxy 5000, I could be getting the number wrong.
I think that's where Chuck E. meets Power Man 5000.
They hit all the biggest bands.
Yeah.
They all want to be part of the Chuck family.
It's a weird movie where Chuck takes some real human children to space to participate in some kind of like...
I mean, honestly, our recent topic, Alita Battle Angel, it really seems like a predecessor to Motorball.
I think Alita ripped it off from Chuck E. Cheese in the Galaxy 5000.
I think that's right.
We'll talk about the Galaxy 5000 more.
I'm not totally sure where it came out, but my thought and hope is that it was a tape that was almost a full length film, that was a prize that you got with tickets.
Oh, I have to imagine.
Which now is just on YouTube for free.
But anyway, I really love it.
But let me just say, let me call out the specific, because we put this out there, is the full Munch's Make Believe band there with Mr. Munch, Pasquale P. Pieplate, Helen Henney.
Jasper T. Giles.
Jasper T. Giles, great.
Are they still nodding and clicking around anywhere?
And all of the answers were from California, but they're spread across California.
Fernando Mendez wrote us that in Scripps Ranch in San Diego, there is a full band.
Josh Ship, or Shipy, or Ship, that's a person who comments on a lot of stuff and I know is a big fan of the show.
I'm sorry I don't know how to say your name, but thanks for listening.
But Josh told us that at least as of a year ago, they were still in Pasadena.
And Mike Olson tweeted at us that in Temecula, there is not only a full Munch's Make Believe band, but also a Rocky Mountain Chocolate Factory with my beloved Truffles, the big sad teddy bear that lives at the Rocky Mountain Chocolate Factory,
who people have been sending photos of, which makes me very happy, makes my wife very happy.
So I want to institute that same policy with this.
If you are, if your hometown or somewhere you're visiting has a full Munch's Make Believe band, tweet at us with a photo and I'll propose the hashtag full Munch.
Hashtag full Munch.
And also, especially if Chucky is in his classic outfit.
That's the holy grail.
Please, I'll give my cell phone out now if you want to text that photo to me.
Because I need to see that right away.
You can't have the barricade of potentially that you don't have Twitter.
Right, so at the end of the episode I'll give my phone number out and only in that instance that you see Chucky Cheese in his full classic red and yellow bowler hat outfit, please text me immediately.
A lot of power, don't abuse it.
Call, call, honestly, call. If it's the middle of the night I'll wake up and...
You know what's weird? I trust our fans. I think our fans would respect this because they seem proud of being good boys as well.
I mean, who knows? My fear is that the episode falls into the clutches of a non-fan and a non-good boy who does abuse the phone number privileges.
But hey, our phones are... are you guys just getting calls about discount leg braces all day like I am?
Like I get nothing but scam calls anyway.
The Subaru dealer nearby has been calling me. I don't know why. I haven't looked for a car in eight years.
You don't currently own a Subaru?
No, never owned a Subaru.
I just get the cloned phone numbers close to my own and if you answer it just says if you'd like to be put on the do not call list or Hilton Vacations would be interested in you.
But as we... we're Westgate people, okay?
That's what I tell them. I'm a Westgate man.
Westgate for life.
Westgate for life. Great timeshifters, good people who run.
So numbers similar to your own number. That's interesting. What would your phone number be? What's a similar number to your phone number?
I have it.
No, that's okay. That's alright.
I have faith in our fans but I do not have faith of 2019, one of the main things people being into, being restraint.
I feel like that's not really invoked right now.
There's been many good years for restraint of course but 2019 a bad year for restraint.
2004 is a real restraining year.
The first half of 2015.
In fact in preparing for this episode, met one of our very nice listeners at Tropical Hideaway who immediately posted that we were doing an episode about this.
Robert.
Jason, I think the three of us doesn't like spoilers about our future episodes.
Look, I like the element of surprise. I like to have fun. That's my little fun. It's the surprise. It's seeing people surprised.
Right. Because you like to wake up every Friday morning, it's like Christmas morning for the listeners.
And you like to be like a benevolent Santa Claus and look on Twitter and say, ah yes, look what I've done.
Look what gift I've given the listeners today.
Yeah, I like to. It makes me feel like God, honestly.
Oh, okay.
More powerful than Santa.
More powerful. Santa is kind of a deity figure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
For sure.
You know what, I'm with you. I like that. You write the little teases before the episodes come out.
Oh, I like to have a little fun with those.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I like when sometimes people know it right away and oh my God, it's this.
And sometimes it's a real hidden clue and you don't know.
And sometimes you say an old friend comes back and people always think it's Bugsy.
Yeah.
No matter who, it's never been him. Will it be him someday?
I would say never. He'll never be back.
Not on my watch.
That son of a bitch.
Certainly there will be no warning. Absolutely not.
Yeah. He could be around. Really, though we say we're not going to have him back on any podcast,
he could walk in the door at any minute. We won't know.
So listeners, beware.
Yeah, and if you're a listener and you see one of us out with an old time gangster who's a skeleton,
don't tell the other listeners that he's coming back.
Yeah.
If you're just, yeah, if you're sampling like the food at the Be Our Guest restaurant with Bugsy.
If there's a skeleton in a gangster hat with Jason.
You're Jason, right? From Podcasts Around. You're Bugsy, right?
The villain who haunts Podcasts Around and shoves jewels into their mouths.
Yeah. Good to meet you.
In all seriousness, it was very nice to meet Robert, who started our subreddit.
Meet him down there. I met a nice young couple on Main Street, too.
I did not catch their names.
I love you shaking hands.
An older, but fatherless relative who had no idea who I was.
But yes, nice to see you all.
Hey, fun. Hey, what a blast.
Well, so yeah, because you went down there to sample the eats and treats at today's topic, the Tropical Hideaway.
Yes, from one animatronic based restaurant to another.
Another food, but there's probably some like little code word we could like, like animatronics that live close to food and talk about food.
Like food centric. I think we could crack the little like, I'll have that in the back of my head for the episode.
But I'd like to officially coin the term there.
And if I were quicker, I'd do it right now.
But it's not coming to me.
But hey, we'll get a while thing.
Tropical Hideaway, if you are not, if you are a person who goes to the other parks, not Disneyland, Tropical Hideaway is the restaurant that recently opened that shares walls with the Enchanted Tiki Room.
It's right between the Enchanted Tiki Room and the Jungle Cruise right along the banks of the river.
And for a long time, this was a closed off dining area with even a big wall and a gate.
And now it's open concept and you can look into it as you finish your Jungle Cruise ride.
And I think it's been very well regarded and enjoyed by people.
But we haven't really talked about it here yet.
So let's do it.
Yeah.
Should we start a little history of the area, perhaps?
Like what was here before?
I'd love to.
Yeah.
Do you guys, little T, let's not say it yet.
Do you guys know what was there around like 2008?
Did you find this?
I believe so because I think I saw it.
Oh, OK.
Wonderful.
Not you, Mike?
It's not coming to me.
It's really good.
We'll see.
So we'll get there.
It's a tease.
I wonder if this history was thin and not with what I found.
So anyway, yeah, I think when the Tiki Room opened in the early 60s, if not right away,
then fairly soon after they opened this facility, the Tahitian Terrace, which is like a Polynesian
themed restaurant where they did luau kind of shows, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
They were like hula girl.
That's probably a very base description of whatever it is.
But like women in grass skirts shaking their hips, men with fire coming and doing crazy
little fire dances and stuff.
Presumably some Kahlua pork, fruit juices.
I have a menu.
I have a menu of the Tahitian Terrace.
Sort of smaller scale.
What would become, you know, a lot of the dining and entertainment at the Polynesian
down the line.
Right.
Of course, it's taking me a second to find the menu.
Here it is.
Tahitian Terrace.
They had a Polynesian combination platter, which was barbecue ribs, crisp fried shrimp,
tempura, chicken, almond with Polynesian vegetables, Cantonese rice, a dollar eighty,
eighty five.
Yeah, everything's cheap as hell.
Surf rider, tropical idol, oil choice, chop beef steak with pineapple spear vegetable
and Cantonese rice.
A dollar sixty five.
They had pineapple ribs.
Monte Cristo sandwich.
A dollar fifty.
I know this really sounds like we're a bunch of old men now.
Can you believe it?
How cheap it was and how expensive it is now used to be able to get a ham sandwich fried
wrapped in flour and fried for only two bucks.
They would pay you to cart it away.
Here's Jason.
Here's you're going to be interested.
The desserts, rum and raisin ice cream wafer.
Nice 40 cents.
Tahitian rainbow ice cream and a wafer.
40 cents.
Pineapple ice cream covered with crushed fresh strawberries.
Sixty five cents.
And Polynesian rum cake.
40 cents.
Can you believe it?
They were playing it less safe back then than I feel like Tropical is playing now.
You mean that you mean these are bold choices?
Yeah, I post what they have on the menu.
Yeah.
Oh, that's true.
The desserts are pretty basic.
Yeah.
It's not a big old variety.
It's kind of like soft serve at the end of the day.
It's variety for typical theme park cuisine.
I'll say that.
I'll give them that.
Sure.
Yeah.
There's there's one really odd thing that I saw in there that I guess this wasn't even
in the dessert portion.
I don't know what you would call this exactly.
What genre of food is this?
The Wahi Mahana who who a Salada, a bouquet of tropical fruit with lime sherbet on shredded
lettuce.
What?
World.
Yeah, I feel like that's a real throwbacky kind of like before food was good.
Yeah.
I feel like I've read articles of like before the 1970s or even the 1980s, food tasted bad
for the most part.
That's what I meant.
Whenever I see old menus, I've looked at like what they would have at the contemporary.
And there's a lot of like gelatin that are sort of it's a very that's a very like or
like ambrosia salad.
You know, canned canned stuff and marshmallows.
People got hooked on certain foods during the wars and it took a while for those to
get out of circulation.
Yeah.
I mean, Walt loved canned chili and diet custard.
It's like you can see his shopping list and his pantry like recreation at the Disney Family
Museum and diet custard is the funniest thing.
Have you, Jason Sheridan, ever had a diet custard?
I probably have.
But truthfully, I don't really like any like artificial sweetener kind of like.
I don't think I've ever had custard.
I've had got it somewhere.
I mean, lots of things are considered custard.
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
Some soft serve ice creams are.
Yeah, I know.
Depending on the milk, fat or eggs.
That Culver's in the Chicago area.
Now that I think about it, I think they call that custard.
Yeah. So I've had custard.
I don't know if I've had diet custard, though, like what is it?
Well, yeah. Does that mean it's artificial?
It's like NutraSweet type ingredients.
That's what I'm assuming like diet custard or light custard
would would be considered.
And over a bed of shredded lettuce over delicious, nutritious lettuce.
Yeah, the combo of dessert and gelatin and savory foods in general.
What were we doing? Why did this happen?
My grandmother always make a jello mold.
She was like, I'm making a jello mold.
And then like once in a while, I would have fruit in it.
And I would like wait for the pieces of fruit.
And the fruit was always like not in there.
Not not the sweet chair, the different cherries.
I'm trying to think what the different type of cherries are.
Not maraschino cherries, but like a different sweet cherry.
And it would be all like it would be like basically fruit cocktail fruit.
Did you have that as a child?
It would be a fruit cocktail, which is like coated in this like sugar syrup.
So every piece, like it was probably like peaches and cherries
and then a couple other fruits.
And but it was coated in a sugar syrup as if fruit isn't sweet enough.
And then you throw that in the jello mold and then we would eat it as as children.
Yeah. Making. Yeah. That fruit needs a lot of help.
Yeah, it's really weird.
Yeah. But you got to remember changing
refrigeration and stuff like it used to be a real treat
to bring a bag of oranges back from Florida.
Like they would sell like citrus crates and stuff at the Contemporary
or like an orange in your stocking.
Like that was a real treat because like, oh, citrus season is either
ending soon. It's going to be harder or at least expensive.
Yeah. Yeah.
You get this stuff.
And we're only like 30 years away from going back to this
where there'll be scarcity for fruits and it'll be, oh, what a treat.
I got an orange in my stocking.
I've had an orange for seven years.
Yeah. So that'll be good.
Yeesh. Anyway, sorry to bring everyone down.
Oh, that's all right.
Hey, shout out to the sponsors of the of the Tahitian Terrace, Stouffer's
and Hickamon.
When you when you think tropical food,
when you think Hawaiian food, you think Stouffer's.
Stouffer's.
They were the ones bringing it to you.
So that but I don't really know much about what that entertainment was
or if it was like particularly I don't know if there was a regular there
like Wally Bogue, the host of Golden Horseshoe.
I don't know what the I don't know what I don't know what happened.
I believe it was like, yeah, Lou out.
Let's say like flame fire twirling.
Have you seen the video of it?
No, there's a video of you just search Tahitian Terrace, Disneyland,
the first video that comes up and it's got a great line read from Walt.
I think it's probably from a wonderful world of Disney.
And he's signing autographs at Disneyland.
And then all of a sudden, you're kind of like drums in the background.
And he goes, Hark, the jungle drums are calling.
And then like they go to the Tahitian Terrace and it's like Lou out dancing.
And what's great about this video is that there's a lot like
I don't know how to put this without sounding like a pervert.
There's attractive women dancing and they make sure to show pictures of
or excuse me, clips of the old men watching them.
And maybe I'm reading into it, but it's definitely to me,
seems like they put it in there to be like, hey, this guy is really enjoying the show.
And then there's like because they'll be like guys like they're
I guess what I'm seeing is that they're like leering a little too much in the video.
Like the Andy Daly like some daddy.
Yeah. And like one guy's eating a rib and like they really like
focus on this guy eating a real boy is watching these like young women dance.
And we have their bare midriffs.
And I'm like, why do they put that like just put the crowd shot and everyone's having fun.
But at least I have to look up to see the rib man.
I could be not interested in the beautiful women.
I just want to see this weird old man eating a rib real for a long time.
Can somebody just cut that down and just send that to you?
I mean, you have to sit through that.
Edit, read.
I mean, this all makes the fifties, you know, 50s, 60s.
You see the rise of tiki culture and like Hawaii like, whoa, what an exotic vacation
that we have to go to Hawaii and Hawaii becoming all these big hotels and resorts
springing up and.
Yeah. Obviously, for whatever reason, that that part of the world and Samoa and Hawaii
and Tahiti like was very in because of the Polynesian.
And I think my mom like that.
That's why we wanted to stay at the Polynesian the most.
I think there was like that was a very interesting culture.
I think that's a holdover to so many servicemen served in the South Pacific
and absorbed it there and brought back stuff and, you know,
yeah, sort of new and fascinating in the 60s.
Yeah, much easier to get to.
Yeah. Air travel becoming more affordable.
And we did we when I was young, we did the full like luau at the Polynesian.
Sure. Did you ever do that?
No, I well, I don't think so.
I don't think we ever did.
I think it's it's a pretty similar show.
It's just a lot of like dancing girls and then fire and then you eat a bunch of meat.
It's funny. Everybody gets one rib and you know, on it sensually.
I think you get to I think we got up and they get out.
There's it's much more like interactive, like they get they get dad up to do a little dance.
Oh, yeah. The impartial put on a hula skirt. Right.
You look like a total fool.
Who embarrassed dad is usually the was the main thing.
Theme park people do are the imagineers are like, all right, this is a great Star Wars.
It's great. But how will we embarrass dad?
What what thing? What photo op will we have that will embarrass everyone's father?
They do need to figure that out for Star Wars land.
I don't know what the Star Wars centric way is to embarrass dad.
But this has got to be someone.
You got to have an alien yell at him. Right.
You got to have like a smuggler or own own doc goes like, what are you doing?
Like, you know, which character is that?
What is the den of antiquities? I I.
Oh, which one is that? That's not the.
Oh, is that the robot that you'll you'll haggle with?
Yeah. Well, now it seems like it's up in the air whether that haggle is.
They've already probably cut that.
Seems like a terrible idea for the most crowded place in the universe that you.
Yeah. You'd set your own prices.
Yeah, for sure. There's no way.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe in 10 years, they like quietly turn the haggle toggle on the robot.
And then somebody's like, oh, heck with the robot today.
But yeah, no, it's crazy. I have to look that name up.
I don't know that. I don't know his name off the top of my head.
Doc. Home, home doc.
So that's what it'll be known as.
You're acting like I'm like some sort of no.
Sorry, doc owned are. That's familiar.
OK, there you go. OK.
Oh, it's like, no, no, I'm just acting like a whole episode about this.
I know I just it didn't sound familiar.
That's why I was skeptical that that's what it was.
Katz and Naka, Rontos, Roaster, like all these fucking names.
All those names sounded familiar to me. OK.
I because I read all these articles and I commit once I hear a new Star Wars character,
it gets committed into my memory. Sure.
It gets burned into my brain.
I don't remember the names of the main ones from the original movie,
the original trilogy and my wife, like, like in the last five years said,
what's the name of the gold one?
Like she actually can you do your I think you're the least big Star Wars fan of the three of us.
Is that right? Yeah, certainly.
Can you do 20 characters off the top of your head?
Do I have to?
You don't have to. But now that I've set up the audience will be really upset.
Well, let me skip a case. You know, I can say OK, three PO and R2D2 and whatever.
Uh, uh, should I just? All right.
OK, so Luke and Leia and Darth Vader and Maz Kanata,
Finn, seven, Ray, eight, uh, Darth Maul, nine,
Ogre, ten. Of course, that counts.
Doc Unc. I'll allow it.
Well, Unkar plot.
Plot. That's close enough. Yeah.
Twelve, right? Java the Hutt.
Yep. Getting the irony ones out of the.
Yeah, there's plenty more.
Oh, yeah. What's the one that the one everybody made for Constable Zuvio?
Constable Zuvio. Yep. He's not in the movies, but he is a toy.
Uh huh. Uh, in the trailer.
You got six more. Rex.
Easy. Rex. That's good.
Yeah. Um, you're missing an embarrassing one.
Anakin. Skywalker.
Yep. You're almost there.
Uh, I'm missing an embarrassing one.
Padme. Padme.
You're missing like two big ones.
Well, but there's plenty of big ones.
Yeah. Uh, oh, Kylo Ren.
Kylo Ren. Right. You didn't say that before.
No. And, uh, uh, uh, cool guy.
What's, what's his name? Mr. Cole.
Come on.
I can't Lando Calrissian.
Oh, I feel the ones I thought you're missing were Han Solo, Obi-Wan Kenobi and Yoda.
He said Han.
You're right. I did not say any of those names.
I went to Unkar plot.
Yeah.
Cause that's like an almost ironic reference.
We did not get an IG 88, a Bosque.
None of the pod racers, not team Topagaly's, not Subulba, not, uh, uh, Juan Sandage.
I don't even like hearing these names.
Not Kira, that very dynamic character from Solo.
Oh yeah. Not any of the solo characters for some reason.
Kira?
It's Kira. We know Kira.
Just the regular name we have in our world.
Yeah.
But there's a Q and an apostrophe in there.
So all right.
All right.
We're heading to something with a Lucas character with a very normal name.
Matt.
Well, we'll hear. We'll go. We're one step away of history for, but anyway, thanks.
I think I deserve some applause for that.
I gave you the applause.
Yeah. I'm not, I'm not named. If you ask me to name 35, I'm in trouble.
I'll do my research.
Anyway, so Tish and Terrence runs for a while, seemingly well-regarded little restaurant
and dinner show. But around the nineties, they want to bring some more current IP into the park.
And we end up with Aladdin's Oasis.
And if you go in there, the main feature is that there is a big, very well done cave of wonders.
The big, uh, tiger head, the stone tiger head, uh, from Aladdin.
My memory was this opening, me seeing that get built, me loving Aladdin as a
kid, oh, the laden's going to have a place in the park. And I never, it felt like it was never
open or that, like as soon as it was built, I felt like it was two years, right. And it was gone.
Like the full show was, was two years and it was gone. Cause it was another dinner show.
Okay. Um, and I probably didn't want, I bet I refused to go in retrospect because I didn't
like like weird food, like, like rice. I think that is how it was as a child.
My mom was very, like, very skeptical of like, oh, Jason and Brian won't eat that. Like they're
not adventurous eaters. And I think what she was really saying was I am not an adventurous eater.
And I think my children will be the same. And as we got older, much more adventurous.
You excelled past your mom. Yeah. I think all our parents also were raised in a very dull
more in the era of the gelatin lettuce.
Jason needs fruit cocktail and diet custard. And that's it.
Well, I actually, I remember my, that I, I didn't like, I didn't want to go anywhere with rice
peel off and I still don't like rice. Oh, I love rice. Really? Yeah. What is, wait,
what is rice peel off? I'm not even sure. But let me tell you, I eat a lot of things with rice,
big rice guy here. Uh, something about peel off does not appeal to me. And maybe that's just my,
it's still my childhood. Uh, like bad for it can be boring. Like it's, I think it's really cheap
to make in large quantities. So it's often just tossed off. It's like the stuffing or something.
Yeah. I've eaten it before. I'll get a big bowl of rice peel off. Okay.
This.
So Aladdin's Oasis, it's some like, yeah, it's a dinner show that kind of tells a compacted story
of Aladdin. Um, not to be confused with what they did at California adventure later with a topical
genie, no topical genie. Um, yeah, I don't know. Like it was always there taking up so much real
estate and that sign was there. And like, I felt like the vast majority of its lifespan was spent
closed. Yeah. And then in Florida, they have the flying carpets, which similarly just feels like
dropped in adventure land. Like it messes up the traffic flow. It's kind of like off game. Like
it's not a hundred percent right there. I think, yeah, they clearly the Disney parks thought
adventure land is our way to get Aladdin in. But the, uh, Disneyland Paris, which I've had a lot
of complaints about, I think one very well done aspect is that it feels, although I guess it
predates Aladdin coming out, but maybe they knew Aladdin was on the way. Aladdin feels like more
nicely organically embedded into adventure. I think adventure land is very well done in, uh,
in Paris and a lot more like probably how galaxy's edge is going to be with little like,
you know, corridors and this marketplace feel and this odd little tight space where somebody pops
out and there's a little show. Um, but yeah, I totally agree. This thing steps six out,
like a sort of the adventure land vibe is clearly jungle tropics. It's not. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So
it's never really sat there perfectly well, I guess, cause they think like the thing across,
like the gift shops are like bizarre, like a little bit across the way from it, but that doesn't
feed it with the architecture a little like a, with the place making a little, um, kind of merging
those two things. But I think like, if you go too far in, in, in that direction, it is clumsy,
like Aladdin's Oasis was. Yeah. Yeah. That's fine. Carpets. Yeah. It just feels like here. Plop
unrelated. Um, yeah, I'm calling you out flying carpets a little bit. So, but you guys never saw
any Aladdin thing there. Did you ever go into that space? We would just cause cause when I went
in, whatever the first time 2007 or whatever, we would just be like, what is that? And it's closed
and you'd like peer in and you'd be like, just like tables in there and then when you go back there,
I feel like sometimes they would, sometimes they wouldn't. Yes. It was used as distribution for
like that, like pay $40, get a fast pass for paint the night, paint the night or fantastic.
And here's a box lunch. Yeah. They would give you a little box. That's where they would
distribute it or something. And then you'd get a fast pass, but that's the last. Yeah. So I,
we would walk in there, but there was never anything interesting happening. Nothing was
happening at all. So an enclosed courtyard full of boxes of chicken. Yeah. Yeah. That was the most
exciting time there as far as my memory in chicken hour, except what you were going to reveal, I
believe, which is, uh, I guess in 2008 around the era of crystal skull, there were the Indiana,
there was a event at Disneyland, uh, called the Indiana Jones summer of hidden mysteries.
Oh, I don't know anything about this. I never experienced it. This, this could be a whole,
I think we had talked about doing like Indiana Jones in the parks, park two, Indiana Jones stuff,
because I don't think we really touched on the Paris kind of roller coaster or this. And we
certainly haven't done the stunt show yet. Yeah. Yeah. That's a good idea. Yeah. But I, I can't not
talk about this a little bit because it's insane. So they did a little show in the Aladdin's Oasis
space, uh, which as I've said, was dominated by the cave of wonders. How do you get around that?
Well, you fold it into the Indiana Jones mythology and you create a live
pseudo stunt spectacular called Indiana Jones and the secret of the stone tiger. Oh my God, really?
He's just running around the clearly Aladdin cave of wonders much more cartoony than anything in
Indiana Jones. Yeah. Yeah. Save for those squirrels that watch the cargo pie or whatever. And not
gophers. Yeah. A ton of room to do very elaborate fighting, but there was fighting. And do you have
the, the, the thing that makes this show stick out as like, Oh, that's weird. Yep. Uh, in this show,
probably the main, uh, thing to speak about of it is that, uh, Indiana Jones punches a woman in the
face. What? Yeah. The woman's name is Rachel. As I said, it's not some exotic, she's like a British
woman in Rachel. Well, she gets possessed, I believe is what I remember from the story. So they were
during the day, I think they were, they were doing not this Aladdin dinner show, but like more
storytelling shows where kids are involved and they need, they have some invented need for the kid
to come up and participate. And that's essentially what this was. It had some mild stunts, but it was
more like, uh, this, the majority of the show is Rachel, the, uh, uh, archeologist who, uh, I, I
didn't watch the whole thing, but you know, she seems to have a little tasks that kids come up and
help with. And then Indiana Jones shows up, bursts out of the cave of wonders and side issue. He's a
very OC Indiana Jones. He's a very like Orange County, San Diego, Kyle Mooney character, Indiana
Jones, who there is a part where, uh, okay. Okay. So, so Rachel is after, uh, a golden tiger,
like, uh, very, as we just talked about legend, the hidden temple temple, she's going to like put
it on a staff. It's this like coveted archeological thing that she's chasing. And, uh, um, so
she's after that. The kids are helping. Um, but once she gets it and it puts it on the staff,
she goes mad with power. It's too much power. And she turns evil at the drop of a hat.
So there is a moment where Indiana Jones, she, Rachel needs to get the jump on Indy. So Indy
goes, Indy's talking to the kids and I'll post this video somewhere, but let me do an impression of
his dialogue. Uh, uh, Hey, sorry about the snakes. You guys had to deal with snakes, huh?
Who's stuck their hand in the basket? Oh, is it you? Is you? Oh, wow. You're really, you're really
brave. Yeah. See, I heard the tiger roar. I knew you guys were solving the clues.
That's a little exaggerated, but that's essentially, this is what Indiana Jones sounds
like in the show. And then all of a sudden, uh, Rachel smacks him with the stick and they get
into a big, she, you know, he kind of like pushes her and she falls to the side of the stage. But
then they get into more hand to hand combat and just like pure punch in the face of this woman.
2008, huh? 2008, but only for like a couple of weeks because one of these, yet another
almost identically named website to the ones we go to mouse info.com, somebody complained about,
so this is, this is where we're at. We've made Indiana Jones into a character who shows up,
punches women in the face and then gets out of there. And also due to the contracts they had
with Indy at the time, he couldn't do like a meet and greet. So the kids didn't all get to meet
him. So at the end of the show, he just like runs up to the top of the jungle cruise line and you
don't, you never see him again. Well, see ya. But he stays up there and just kind of watches you
leave, but you don't get to like, get a picture with him. Uh, one thing that sticks out, uh, uh,
of this, like I think I was there a couple of times that summer, every now and then throughout
the day on one of the roof of the buildings in adventure land, Indy would show up and some bad
guys would show up and it would just beat them up. Well, that's, that's similar. There was an event
in 2014 that we went to that was the anniversary of the ride of the Indiana Jones ride. And they
had a show, they put a little show together. So like if you were by, um, the ride at a certain
point, like whatever, once an hour in the Tarzan tree house, you would see Indy fighting with some
goons. And they did a whole fun show like once an hour, just for like two days, two nights of this
celebration. Or maybe it was one night. There's a binder on a shelf somewhere or like a PDF in a
drop box that it's like, okay, here's the Indy, uh, fighting people on top of things, choreography.
And let's dust this off. Like foot charts, like old ballroom dancing diagrams. So yeah, maybe five
years from now, there'll be yet another Indy events and we'll get to see him fighting with people.
The smoking rubble that once people have destroyed it because they can't get into Star Wars land.
Disneyland. Yeah. This is where the ride used to be. Real people will be punching real women
in the face to just to get into the, uh, uh, not just, not just fake Indies.
What a buy a $200 lightsaber.
God, it'd be chaos. Uh, so there were, yeah, bizarre Indiana Jones show. Uh, and he, he,
he ends up pushing Rachel into the tiger's mouth and she dies. She dies. Yeah. Yeah. She eats.
Wait a minute. He doesn't even save her. Nope. He says like, Rachel, it doesn't have to end this way.
And then pushes her into it. I feel like you could at least like justify, well, you know,
she was attacking him, but he saves her at the end. So everything's fine. She just does. She's a
good guy, right? Who gets possessed. Well, I think they had the working, um, closing mouth, right?
Because it was the cave of wonders. No, no, it just fogs up and that's the end of it.
Okay. Well, they had the fog juice, so you gotta, stuff goes bad.
What a cold end of the show. I think it's, it's one of those scenarios. I think
to give them a little credit where, uh, she, if she were to like let go of the staff,
she could maybe save herself, but she's determined. She's like, you know, she chooses the treasure.
Gollum sorta rules. Yeah. I don't, I don't care for that. Yeah. Give the folks home happy for
God's sake. You don't need to end on a downer. The kids all cheer. They're glad Rachel is dead.
Even though they weren't helping Rachel like sort through fake snakes like 10 minutes prior. Now
they're like, Hey, fucker. Go to hell. You're dead to us. See you in hell, Rachel. He showed me
that you're true way. I'm glad he punched you. I'll punch you when I get to hell.
By the way, we're doing, these voices we're doing, we're very solid candidates to replace
Bob Saget as the voice of many, many pets on America's funniest known videos. Oh yeah. I'll
just drop out of this. I think it's bullshit about the new. Who is the current hook? I saw
Alfonso Riviera, Tom Bergeron before that Alfonso Riviera. I saw it like, yeah, cause it's still on
like Saturdays at eight or seven or something. It's still like a prime time. It's still like
one of the top shows on television. We forget that, but the thing that it's missing is Bob Saget
doing his one voice. Yeah. Classic Disney synergy where he was on dancing with the stars
and hosting America's funniest known videos. Just as Bob Saget was full house. And then Kool-Aid,
funniest America's funniest people. America's funniest filmed at. With, oh, what was it?
Universal Florida. Yeah. With Tawny Catane, of course. Really? Yeah. Dave Kool-Aid and Tawny
Catane. Wow. Here's a little funnier die inside story. She came in, they made a sketch with her.
She was a person, a celebrity who took a meeting and they want to end her when they're like,
Oh, so any ideas you've had? And she's like, well, I'd love to go on between two ferns
and the silence and the eye darting in this room as no one wanted to address the fact that Tawny
Catane would never be on. Poor Tawny Catane. Which at that point, you know, because now between two
ferns is the home to guests like Barack Obama and Sean Penn and like, no offense to Tawny. It's
just purely structurally, they were right. It's a plus list. I am the star meter has to be, you have
to be in the top 10. One of the biggest living stars. And Tawny Catane's more like number 11.
Right. Well, we'll have her on the show. Yeah. So that'll be your runner up for consolation prize.
Anyway, so that takes us through the history of it. Mostly unused venue and was kind of just
waiting for something cool to happen. And I think they did a nice little thing with the Tropical
Hideaway, which opened a couple of months ago. Yeah, there were rumors. I remember, I'm sure we
were texting about it, but it's like, Oh, they're doing something with the space because we follow
Twitter accounts that will follow different like permits filed for construction. Yeah.
Speak for yourself. All right. Two of the three of us will follow Twitter accounts that regularly
will say, well, a permit has been filed for construction. Or trademarks and copywriting.
And it's like, it's the Aladdin Oasis, the Aladdin Oasis space is going to have some construction.
So a lot of people are like, Oh, Tahitian Terrace coming back. So we were very, very excited because
like that, that would have been cool too. Also patents, patents are a big interesting look in
what theme parks technology will be in a few years. That's how we can guess what maybe some
Marvel attractions or Nintendo attractions are going to be. Any good patents lately?
I haven't seen patents in a couple of weeks. I feel like there's been a lot of,
I'm trying to think, universal things. Or like there was a boat that could like move, like an
omnimover boat, even though they kind of have that. Oh yeah. That's the wrong term. With no track,
but like using water jets to look at shows. And I'm trying to think of how it's different than
the one in pirates in Shanghai, but I don't. So I'll get back. We'll do an episode on the permits,
the new permits. They haven't filed a permit to make the globe come to life and talk. No, not yet.
Say hi to you. You will love dark universe. We'll get it right. You'll get it right.
Double or not then. We'll get it right. Give it to the Blumhouse boy.
That's what's happening. On our episode, Griffin Newman like threw that out. And then days later
it was announced that that is what's happening. That Blumhouse will start getting like monster
movies, like make monster movies, classic universal monsters. Smart. Yeah. Very smart.
So yeah, so it was very exciting. And then it was like, I remember the art got posted on the
blog a few months ago, what six months ago. Tropical hideaway, of course, a reference to
the song. Welcome to the tropical hideaway. That was the saddest. Very tentative. We like this too.
We like this attraction. I think we were all just a little shy. Yeah. And I was worried about like,
I don't like hitting notes, you know, recording this early in the not really early.
My pipes don't open up till like 8 PM. You got to warm up. I couldn't remember what like a cartoonish
accents of members of the current at the time, UN security council, the victors, the UN security
council. Welcome to the Dickie room. And I guess one loser of world war II. Yeah. Cause there is a
German bird. They said when there was a treaty signed for equal country representation. Yeah.
When there is a animatronic Tiki bird show, part of the world war II agreement. Yeah. So they're,
well, the one thing that's weird about this, I remember reading blogs that they're saying,
or it's the tropical highway. It's kind of a connected to the Tiki room, new place to get
the dole whips and Rosita is going to be there. It is going to be there. And I read that and was
like, what's that? I don't know what I feel like every single thing I read acted as if I was deeply
familiar with Rosita already. I knew Rosita cause there's a cause especially cause a couple of years
ago, I real cause they've already done references to Rosita in trader Sam's drink. Is that right?
I think that's right. And there's also tons of bootleg. I know where Rosita went or like,
where did Rosita go shirts for sale online? There are. So you should have Scott known
there have to be people out there. Someone back me up. If this'll be, I mean, it is a non-secular
must've not known what, and I didn't have that show memorized. I guess what it, what is it a
really a reference to it's in the Tiki room. There's the mobile of the, like the chandelier
with all the singing birds comes down and they're all like bathing beauties, like from a 20s movie.
Uh, and they named them all. And then somebody says, what happened to Rosita? Whatever happened
to Rosita? I didn't know any of that sold a month ago. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, obviously yeah,
it's a non-sense. It's a throwaway line, but I think that it loomed large in the nerds at
Imagineering's head because it has popped up here and there. And then it's, yeah, it's on
several, whatever T public shirts probably that say, yeah, where did Rosita go? Am I crazy to
have missed this though? I feel like I had trouble finding any, an explanation. I kept looking. So
what is Rose and nowhere explained it from scratch. That's what I'm trying to do for anybody.
You, it is not you. You are a star tourist guy. Like that is you have combed every inch of it
and every history of it. I'm not a big Tiki room guy. You're not a big Tiki, but there are Tiki
room people, especially again, with the crossover of like Tiki bar culture and stuff, there's a lot
of Tiki group people. So I can see, like I can see, you know, different elements of fandom,
like missing other parts of the larger. Sure. And I think it's possible you could, if you
aren't super versed in haunted mansion, you might've missed hat box ghost where it, which was
presented in a way of like, it's, I feel like even that was announced to be part of a movie that
hasn't happened. And I wasn't totally clear on that box. Certainly the whole like blood story
that was like, Oh, maybe we'll do that. Or like all the potential backstories for haunted mansion
and stuff. And also we asked the question we had on our Patreon episode about Sonny Eclipse. I said,
well, if you're subscribed, you probably knew who he was before, but somebody did a poll and it was
like, there was a decent amount of folks who didn't know Sonny before listening to that episode. So
yeah, even nerds, even nerds have blind spots. Let's, you know, uh, we all, we all try our best.
We didn't know team Topagaly is either it was a pod racer. So there's no Duke of Unc.
Just going to keep like Xerox copying that name until I like Duke of Unc. That's my,
my original Star Wars character. Um, so Rosita this referred to, but not seen character in the
Tiki room. I texted my mom. I remember I texted my mom, the art of the, or the blog post announcing
this. And I think she texted back Rosita three exclamation points. Now I'm not sure if she,
I think she knew right off the top of her head and she's, she loves the Tiki room. That's like
one of her favorites. So I think she, yeah, I think she got that reference, but she probably
doesn't know who Sonny Eclipse is. He might look familiar to her, but she doesn't know the space
angels. So I guess since it's come up, how do we all feel about the execution of Rosita?
How it was done. They do not execute her. That is not the show. I think it's terrible. And I think
if you're in support of it, you're a monster. Uh, no, I think, I think her, uh, the little spade,
that little nook is really nice. I think it's really nicely art directed, her little like
umbrella thing that she's on. And I think it's clever the way they keep it a little bit into the,
into the jungle cruise river. So you can't like touch her, throw food at it or execute it. Um,
she's sitting on, she's sitting on like boxes of bird seed and then she has luggage and her little
hat. That's really, and she's waiting for her skip. She's waiting for a specific jungle cruise
boat to come, I believe. Right. She's waiting for a skipper to come. Um, because she keeps mentioning,
I watched a mega cut of all the pieces of dialogue she has. Somebody just stood there and
recorded the whole thing. So she's constantly like, when is my skipper coming and blah, blah,
blah. Well, when you, okay, you know what? I like the art direction of it, but I watched some of
that video that you're talking about and I, I got bored pretty fast. I was not like dying to hear a
bunch more of this dialogue. I will admit. Well, there's a lot. Sorry. I was going to say,
I think the like kind of a borscht belt or corny jokes, I think the jokes themselves are good.
I just think the delivery is a little modern. Well, this is, I've talked a little bit about
this with some people. Uh, this character and the red head, uh, red, the new pirate red, uh,
enunciate a little too much for my liking. There's a very like modern sort of VO style. It's what
you're saying where very much I am going to pronounce like, and make sure that everyone
can understand. And I feel the same way with red where it's like, Hey, come on boys. They want the
rum. Like as opposed to the old Disney where it would be just these drunken character actors who
it gives the voices and the character a little bit more personality or character.
There is an, um, I don't think it's like one of the greatest
performances or animatronics ever in the part. It is a little that she, I have to say the way it's
set up, I was sitting there and I was a little far away. I was kind of in one of the tables in the
center and I watched it for a few minutes and I was like, you know, because she's kind of just
doing these jokes out into the ether, it almost feels a little like she's bombing.
But I guess the only other option is you either have it off to the side and people can enjoy it
if they want, or you have it like the Tiki room pre-show where it's like stopping everyone. Look
at this now. That's a little harder when people are eating and trying to get through lines and
stuff you would have had to like put her above things and had a big sound effects.
So they also probably want to move people in and out of that space. We're saying that about
sunny clips too. If it was like a more, if you were more directed to that show, um, you maybe
you don't want, you don't want people planting there for a super long time. Oh, also you were
right by the end of the jungle cruise. So if it was like a huge booming show and stuff, there would
be like weird sound bleed between attractions. I guess I think there's enough. I think there's
probably some math problem. They did some equation that there's enough spaces in between
every time she talks to make most people go, well, we can't sit here and wait for her to say
everything she says. So we got to get out of here because it's enough. If it was like every five
seconds she talks, I think you might, there might be people that go, oh, let's see everything she
says. Let's, let's maybe see the loop, but there's a big significant space between every time she
talks. So it's like, all right, well, I like this bird, but we can't sit here and watch this whole
thing. Yeah. Yeah. Designed to bore you a little. Yeah. Cause it can't, yeah, it can't be super
engaging or else. Yeah. The problem that's a limited seating situation there. This place is
pretty popular right out of the gate and, you know, deservedly so I've been there twice now. And
I've got, I think it's, I think it's a really nice space, aesthetically and the little like,
I think the signs nice and the little waterfall. And I like that it's this open air cascading
thing instead of the Indiana Jones's famous stone tiger block in the view. So I think just like
placemaking, I think they did a good job, but let's talk about the food. Can I actually,
sorry to go back real quick. A couple of the Rosita things I just wanted to say. Oh yes.
Okay. So yeah, as far as Rosita, a couple, so I went through all the dialogue. First of all,
Rosita must be a big fan of Billy Crystal because she says one of his big famous catchphrases,
you look marvelous. Really? Yep. She says it. I don't know if that's why she says it. I mean,
that's, I guess a phrase people say, but I don't, I don't, I don't know why I only think of Billy
Crystal. What's the character's name? Fernando. Fernando. Uh huh. This character that I never
cared for, but I think he never got it. I don't know what it was referring to. What is it? I think
he was just that guy. He's a, you look marvelous or whatever. And he would do it, I think every week
on Saturday Night Live for a year. In the one season he was on, I think they, yeah, they feel
like they did it in every episode. That I feel like is, is like, like when Looney Tunes would
reference Humphrey Bogart and the Marx Brothers, it's like going a little before. I can't, but what is?
Like a lounge lizard or like a weird entertainer or something. I don't know. She didn't do Billy
Crystal's other catchphrases. Sammy Davis Jr's catchphrases. He had two blackface characters.
And they play, there's a thing that I remember being funny where he and Christopher Guest are
like old timey baseball play like, you know, like old 1800s, but that, but also blackface.
Wow. Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, not go. Sorry. I led you right into the pool there. But I mean,
well, no, but I said, I think I remember the sketch being funny, but probably not okay.
We'll revisit that. She, the Rosita makes a reference that she looks like a pineapple
princess also, which I like because that's an old song, a Sherman Brothers song from, what is it?
It's from an Annette thing. Yeah. Is it a movie though? I can play pineapple princess on ukulele.
I won't do it right now though. Yeah. You know, I don't know on the ukulele. Yeah. You've never
heard pineapple princess. No. Oh my God. We got to pull all these missing areas. Is it better than
monkeys? Uncle? Uh, hell no. The beach boys are on that one. Well, it's sure as shit. That song
slaps. So all right. All right. I'm a big pineapple princess fan. There's also a remix of pineapple
princess on that, that, that album deconstructed an electronic version.
It's the remix. This is original.
That's a little bit of it before we. I am a big fan of Annette's output as far as a recording
artist. And there's like, she has a, she has an album called Italianette and they're all Italian
songs. And then there's a Hawaiianette, which is what this is from. And they're all Hawaiian.
I like that naming structure. Uh, and there's some really great Annette's though. You know what?
Patriot episode about Annette's singing career is for sure. Oh boy. Yeah, I'm way into that. I'm
way into that. So as long as we hit monkey's uncle. Now this is the remix of pineapple princess.
By what artist? Uh, it's on deconstructed.
I think a pineapple. If you're the DJ who did this, let us know. Kinsey,
Kinsey more remix.
Disney needs to learn not to match up old timey and electro.
No, this isn't suitcase in a dream territory. I say no, it's not. It's not great. I mean,
that's now play the little Xan feed the birds. Be the burst up as a bag.
But now subscribe to the Patreon for a future in that episode. Um, so yeah, pineapple prints.
She makes a reference to that. And then she also makes a reference to Tahitian terrorists
and Aladdin's Oasis. Really? Yeah. She says like this place used to be a real dump.
People are here for the first time in 20 years. Uh, yeah. So, uh, I like that. That's all I wanted
to say. They're always giving me grief in the Tiki room. I'm taking a bigger beating than Rachel.
I mean, if she made a Rachel reference, that would be pretty insane.
Rachel and her staff. Um, well, so food to the real reason that you're there, the food, uh,
what do we think? What have you guys had there? And Jason, I just feel like you've got some,
some hot, some takes hotter than the food. I had a bit of a journey.
Okay. So I was the last one to go to this place and I went a couple of days ago. Uh, uh,
I just hadn't gotten around to going down and trying it. So, uh, I had something to come back
for in the afternoon on a Friday. Uh, so I was at seven 11. Yeah. Uh, I thought you said potluck
dinner at seven 11. You were the corner of the store. So, uh, I was also, I was like, I'm going
to be down there for three hours. Um, and I was like, I, I, to preface, I was like, you know what?
I haven't been to in a while is downtown Disney, uh, you know, for an extensive visit.
I wonder what the parking situation currently is. Here's the current parking situation at
downtown Disney. Uh, no free time. You don't use to get free time. This ain't news to me. I know,
I know all about it. So here's the deal. Uh, if you spend $20 in downtown Disney, you get,
you get three hours validation. If you spend, I guess the same amount at any table service
restaurant, you get five hours. So, uh, my debate was, do I spend $20 for Mickey and friends, like a
schmuck or do I buy $20 of pizza? And that's what I did for three hours of parking. Um, $20 of pizza,
saving you the five extra dollars to park in the Mickey and friends parking. No, the Mickey and
friends up to $20, 25 or it's up to 25. Yes. So you spent $20 at food. Oh yes. So saving me. Yep.
Yeah. $5. And it also gave me a chance. I had not been down to see, uh,
Napolini the quick service, uh, pizza had been reconfigured from slices to personal pan pizzas.
So I bought two 10 inch pizzas. Uh, this is after, why would you, you're going to eat, huh?
You were going for a food place and you still bought two pizzas.
Yeah. I don't see the issue. Cause then I got a couple of meals out of this, uh, trip too.
I had a, like a slice of each pizza to try, uh, after tropical hideaway. And then I ate the rest
for dinner. So you brought two personal pizzas into Disneyland with you? No, no, I did it the last
thing. Okay. So I went in and I tried tropical hideaway. I got there at about 11 30 ish. So
shortly after it opened and it was already packed, like all the tables were full. There was a line.
I got to say the crowd flow could be better going to like, I was confused if I would have
it at the one station, if I would have that boat and, and they sort of like, I was just following,
there was people, like a line of people and strollers going into it. So I just followed them
and immediately they went the wrong way. Cause you can kind of go around the coolers they have set up
and they, they need more signage to say like, order a cold stuff here, order hot stuff here because
other people made the same mistake. So we, I was confused too. I agree. Yeah. That's a good point.
So I got, I knew what you had, you had gotten the big like kind of Sunday thing. So I tried the
other side, tried the pineapple raspberry squirrel, and then I got an order of the
pineapple Lu Pia, Limpia. I forget how it's an M in there. Yeah. Yeah. Lumpia, which is basically
like a, it's kind of like the Dell taco cream cheese, caramel egg roll things, but it's pineapple
and cream cheese, and then it's covered in cinnamon sugar and then served with a side of what is
essentially sweet and sour sauce. Could have done without the sweet and sour sauce. The Limpia was
pretty tasty, a little small, the portion size. And then I had the, the pineapple raspberry
squirrel, Dole whip pretty good. My thing with Dole whip, I get sick of, I get a little tired
of it about halfway through where you're saying, yeah, I don't really finish. Yeah. It's an
overwhelming, I think all three of those flavors you get a little, it's overwhelming. And like,
it's a lot of citrus too. It'll be a little irritating. Yeah. I think you get tired of that
fat or I get tired of that faster than a chocolate dessert, which you can go and go forever.
That is my, my, one of my big complaints, I was like, you know, what would make this all perfect
is chocolate shell. I wish I could get chocolate shell topping on this, the hardened chocolate
shell, because I love citrus and chocolate as a combination. And I think having the dip
would, would be great. That would, that would sell it for me. The whip, I will say I had the,
they call it a loaded whip. That's what we have. I split it with Lindsay, which also maybe that's
since we split it, I wasn't having too much of it. They have exotic fruit in it, which also means
just like oranges, oranges, pineapple and coconut. Right. It's very exotic. Fuck you. Exotic. I'm no
fool. And crystallized hibiscus, hibiscus, which is like little sticks. And so like, yeah, you get a
little like, this, you know, sweet, but then there's a little savory in there. So you can like kind of
you cleanse the palette a bit. So I did feel like it was a nice mix of things. And I could have
eaten one alone. I didn't, I didn't need to split it. Texture to me with ice, like I like something
else in there, like even as simple as sprinkles or like cookies and like something else besides
the creaminess. I like the texture. I'm sure we've talked about it on the show. What is your normal
ice cream purchase? Oh gosh. Well, I don't know. I mean at Disney or anywhere, I just like all of it.
Oh, at home, I switch it up. I'm all, I like to surprise myself. I really like a cherry,
a cherry chocolate chip. I like just regular chocolate chip ice cream because you get a
creaminess and then you get a lot of like chocolate chocolate. Right. But usually you're,
it'll have something in it, something in it. Yeah. Chunks, chunks, chunks or like a, like a caramel
ribbon or a marshmallow ribbon or something. So you're not, you're not doing just a straight up
chocolate ice cream. You want some, some texture beyond the cream. I want some. Yeah. I agree with
that. I like, if I like a strawberry ice cream, I like chunks of strawberry in there. Absolutely.
Yeah. I guess I like, I guess I agree with that. I like a cookie dough. I like, I like the Ben and
Jerry, there's cookie dough and chocolate or no, what's there's a half baked. What's that one?
That's like chocolate chip cookies, isn't it? No, it's got two things. It's got cookie dough in it.
And it always got brownie and brownie. Yeah. That's what it is. That's like extra. Yeah.
So fish food, I think is one of the tops because you get everything at that. You get little
chocolate fish, you get caramel, you get marshmallows and chocolate ice cream. Yeah. So
I feel like the loaded whip, honestly, like for, for maybe those who, and I don't actually have
the problem that you have. I don't always get to live. It's not my number one. It may not even be
top three snack at Disney for me, but I don't have the problem where I get tired of it. I do like it.
What are the, what are the sticks sticking out of it? Is that the hip crystalized? Oh wait, no,
you're right. That's like, isn't it? It's 10 cents worth of chocolate covered coffee.
This is that little, the drizzle of little like crystals. Yes. But I'm, yeah, you're right. What
is that called? Yeah. I think you're right that it's, it's Pocky. I was getting confused that that
was the hibiscus, but yeah, Pocky is the thing. There's like four little posts of like a salty,
like kind of pretzely kind of a thing. And that's what you can really cleanse the palette with.
So that, I mean, it does look good. And I thought it would be a little overwhelming
to eat with one person because I wanted to try the limpia and I also wanted to get $20
worth of pizza. So I knew you had had that. I also like, I'm like, I mean that does look good,
but like you're not full of me. I know wholesale, like that's cheap fruit to buy. That's cheap.
That's five cents worth of five. You're doing the profit-esque math in your brain,
outsmarting this place. Okay. But here's, you're not at the point yet though, like,
like some old men where you like kind of tell all the employees that you know,
no, because I've seen this crap and we're like here at the grocery store and they're like, you
know, you can get this for cheaper at this other, like, uh-huh. Okay. Here, 20, $25 your total.
That's a few years away, I think, from you explaining to the, to Rosita, you know,
this is all whole set Pocky or 10 cents a pop. So well, but just thinking about that, I mean,
the Dole Whip, the Dole Whip swirl was five 69, the Limpia was six 99.
The profit episode. I'm picturing little infographics while you talk.
So, and then it's also, so no annual past discount. Yeah. No, any barbecue, which is a similar
stand with seats does give an annual past discount. So kind of confusing in that sense. Now,
side note, if you're comparing those two things, uh, my wife, a vegetarian
didn't really like veggie bow, uh, and has become a big fan of veggie, uh, like chish kebab or the
skewers. Uh, so better veggie option, cheaper with an annual pass. So, uh, Bengal barbecue is winning
points right now. What else, what did you guys have when you went besides the veggie bow? Um,
I had done the chicken bow and I'm actually like, I really want to do the beef one because that one
almost looks the best and looks like it fits with the sauce the best. Uh, I need to, but I like,
I like the chicken well enough. Uh, and I went on a very rainy, the cold day. So the steam coming
out of that thing was great. It was just what I needed. If I had it on a regular day, what I like
as much, I don't know. We just had regular sort of soft serve swirls, uh, not really like loaded or
whippified. Uh, Erin had one with raspberry and she found that to be kind of like medicine. She,
uh, she thought that was like a, that tasted like NyQuil or something. I liked mine more, which was
orange, uh, pineapple swirl. Um, I thought in a good way, it reminded me of a Flintstones push
pop. Oh, wow. That's a great, yeah. That orange flavor. They're kind of fakey orange flavor,
but I like it. So I was happier all told, uh, than, than my wife. So, but I, so I veer more
positive, um, so far, but I hear all the, I hear the negative points. I think my, I think I was
okay with it because I got the same swirl. I think the sweetness of the raspberry balanced out that
like, you know, more tartness of the pineapple, but raspberry, it can be, it's a hard flavor
sometimes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think she felt the artificiality of it. Uh, yeah, I would like to try
that raspberry. Um, and she, and she tried my orange, uh, pineapple and found it superior.
Yeah. Uh, the, the load of whip has the pineapple and orange swirl together. Okay. I wasn't putting
it together that it's tastes like Flintstones, but I think that makes sense to me now. Yeah.
Well, nice little flavor flesh. Well, you had a fruit cocktail dumped on top.
Coated in sugar. Yeah. Uh, we had the bowie, the vegetable bowel and the beef bow. Um, both good.
I liked both of them. Um, I wasn't blown away. I think we're getting to the point where if it was
$3 and not $6, perhaps that would be a different thing because once we paid for everything,
I was like, Holy crap. Holy crap. So you get one bow for $6, right? Yes. That's one bow for $6.
Yes. Small. And we, I'm sure if you look at bowel prices on the streets where the real bow,
it's probably the cheapest thing possible in Glendale, like Din Tai Fung, uh, which is like
a real bow, but like bow and bun and soup dumplings and, uh, uh, from Asia, there's a location in
Glendale, California. It's a may, it's great. But nothing is like super expensive. And like,
for like one order, you get at least like six of each item. But how has anybody surprised,
you surprised at the Disney pricing? So I am not, I'm just surprised that it's like $6 for one.
I thought it would at least be like two in a pairing or stuff. When, when those,
the Bengal prices are great, the Bengal prices are good. I guess that's sort of what I was
comparing it to where I was like, oh yeah, I don't ever feel like so ripped off at Bengal
barbecue. Obviously there's plenty of overpriced things at Disney, but it did feel, it's so funny
because it's such a small difference. It does feel like it's a dollar more than it should be.
$5. I probably wouldn't be as like, yeah, you're like Disney, like overcharged radar. It like goes
up a little bit here where it's like, it's just because you're used to a certain amount of being
overcharged. And then this one feels like it's a dollar more than that. And that's why we're like,
Hey, they're taking advantage of us. Well, and the lack of annual pass discount in like an identical
survey. I get that. Cause like, but the, but you don't get an annual pass discount on ice cream
and you don't get it on Dole whip. So I get that there's some thing there and then like certain
carts and food carts, you don't get an annual pass discount as well. So, you know, they could do it.
That'd be nice, but there is some precedent for it at least. Yeah. Um, I just, yeah, I was like
comparing the two receipts of like, I don't know who pizza things. Uh, I don't know, but see,
cause I had the outside the gate, it is outside the gate, but I had the opposite reaction of like,
I was surprised that the prices were still low at this pizza takeaway thing. Now I think that's
also a trick because Napolini that you used to get like a $4 pizza slice. Now you're getting a
7 95 whole pizza. So they're getting you to buy more, but I was surprised that it's still only
7 95 and the annual pass works there. They may also just be trying to, uh, siphon off people who
might just walk to the other side of the Esplanade. Cause there's a pizza press at that first hotel
across the street. So it is comparable to walk though. It's a long walk, but it is,
the prices are comparable to blaze pizza, rev pizza, these fast fire pizza places.
And the crust was better. Like I did. I like Napolini a lot. I think it is a great food option
and easily the best pizza on Disney property. Um, yeah. And cheaper than the sit down restaurant
pizza port. I know. Can you believe that we're talking about values is like a single slice.
It was like a slice of sub Chuck E cheese pizza at pizza port is like, is up to like six bucks.
Like that much horrible. So go to downtown Disney and go to Napolini. Yeah. Yeah. There's your tip.
Do you feel good? Do you feel like, uh, you ended the day achieving value or not? I got out of there
with like 10 minutes left and then I think there is a 15 minute grace period. So I think I could
have stuck around for 25 more minutes in the park, but man, uh, noon on a Friday, it was already
getting crowded. I had time for one ride. What did you guys think I rode Casey jr. No, the boat.
Yeah. The boat. I rode the Mark Twain around cause the train, like I was like, oh, maybe I'll just
take the train back to main street. Two trains filled up and I was still like in line like there
was that crowded. How long did the pizzas last? You went down Friday. How long did you stretch
out dinner Saturday night? You had both pizzas? Uh, no, I had like two slices at downtown Disney,
two slices Friday night and then the rest Saturday night. Yeah. I was just wondering if you were
rationing it out still to like right now, like Homer with the sandwich. You made a pizza broth.
Yeah. Yeah. Some cups of pizza soup. It's better aged. Um, all right. So yeah, uh, let's talk a
little bit about all those numbers. We'll do the diagram. We'll animate diagrams of all of the
pricing, right? Sure. Post that our graphics team will, I mean, so that's my main thing. I like the,
of course we haven't talked about the oars. Uh, yeah, we're going to talk about a little bit of
the scenery. I was going to say as far as food, I was looking around for this because this does
feel like once alcohol comes into the park and star wars land, this feels like one of the prime
spots for a Tiki drink. So I was looking around and like, do they have anything that would like
a hint of like a hookup for a bar of any kind? I didn't see anything, but this is pert like
nothing would be better than sitting here at eight or nine o'clock at night with a Tiki drink.
And watching the jungle cruise boats go by in the afternoon, my man. Why are you waiting that long?
How about nine in the morning? Yeah. But like they only have pineapple juice. Like they need,
there's not even like passion fruit or guava or something. I would assume they would expand it
at a certain point, but I wonder if there is like a, in like a secret case somewhere with a lock.
And it's like, as soon as we are like, we're going liquor at Disneyland, they open it up and like a
couple different places you can do it. And this has to be one of them. I don't know. It just seems
like it's the perfect place. That's already. What does anyone think is going to happen? If we put
one ounce of alcohol into our Tiki desserts, that like shit is going to hit the fan. People
are going to be barfing into the jungle cruise river. Like I don't know. People are going to be
knocking Rosita off or perch into the deep. Have you spent time in Orange County? But you can drink
everywhere else on that property. And do you like, where is it chaos anywhere? This argument that
like Walt would be, I mean, we've said it a number of times, but mad. What are we? I can't believe
that Disney has stuck with it. That for somewhere trying to soak you for as much money as possible.
How isn't it crazy that in 2019 Disney is still like has a morality claw, like a fake morality
clause. You walk a hundred feet and get as hammered as you want in so many places. Sure.
Also, my favorite, one of my favorite things probably Bob Iger has ever done is that crack
about Walt taking slugs or having a drink in his office and stuff. And then he had to apologize
because the CEO was not supposed to say that. Facts about the founder of the company about,
and also, Hey, as I'm advocating for on this show all the time, the idea of somebody who likes to
have a drink, this being like a dirty sin. What are we talking about? The Walt Disney in the 50s
liked to have a drink in his office. Oh, what a pervert. Like, what are we mad about? The,
Iger had to apologize for that art like, and on the spectrum of 50s businessmen, he was like,
probably one of the most sparkling, clean functioning alcoholics. Yeah. There's so many
other things I should have positive for. Number one solo as I've said on recent episodes, I had
only just seen solo and I am still upset. Oh, you do really very recently did. Yeah. I had not seen
it. Uh huh. Name your least favorite character. Oh, least fit. Well, it would your 20 least
favorite character. I mean, I think Lisa moment is having to watch Lando more like boy having to
watch Lando process death. That's a weird moment in the movie, but one of the better moments in
my mind, a spoiler alert Lando has like a female robot that he fucks, right? Well, they imply that
they've had sex, but they don't do it or they don't show it. Like we make it work. Like there's an
implication that the role, the robot and Lando are romantic. Um, but then the robot has a brutal
death, brutal death. And then Lando is like very sad and it goes through multiple stages of grief.
Yeah. Um, and I will say one of the better parts of the movie in my mind. I guess. Yikes. What a blast.
That certainly seems like more fun than, uh, hundreds of Lord Miller jokes. Why would we want
that in our movie? No, no. People I would have thought should have been fired because of that.
I mean, recent Academy award winners. Yes. Recent when the movies were, when the nominations were
said, the applause for Spider-Man was deafening in the theater. Like incredible too. Yay.
We have to keep the U S the USC professor and his little boy on. We have to keep them.
My God, super villain delivery. I would like to flesh out and show, uh, explain a picture of how
Jason delivered that he had his arms crossed. And then as he said that, well, his right arm kind of
like fluttered it away, like flipped it away, like this very dismissive. Um, and it was, yeah,
as you said, it was a very super villain, the 20th most successful Kennedy. Uh, it's an evil
gesture you could have done while holding a cat. Right. Yeah. Sure. Yeah. Still more clear evil
motivation than any villain in solo. What's Woody Harrelson's character's name? I was just,
I was honestly, that's, I was trying to make a joke about it. Her producer of red.
I was trying to make a joke about it and I could not for the life of me remember what
he else's character in solo has the most screen time, maybe the most dialogue of all the characters
for some weird reason. Uh, and I cannot remember his name. Hmm. Um, well look, there's more
important names that we have to get to and that's the names on the oars. Yeah. Members of sea
members of sea. Just briefly, you explained seed from the ground up again. Okay. See stands for
society of explorers and adventurers. And it is a fictional group, uh, made up by, we don't know
if it's like Joe roadie, but it seems to come about in pleasure Island, uh, time, which is what? 25
fish more than that years ago. These things factor into his ride, seemingly the most. Yes.
And other stuff has been grandfathered in sort of the, the big thunder mountain lineage, uh,
Jason Chandler and Barnabas T Bullion. It ties basically ties multiple rides and multiple Disney
parks across the world together by saying all of the people that maybe owned the ride or were in
charge of the rider at something to do with the ride all belong to the secret society of like rich
maniacs. So yeah, as you were saying, Barnabas T Bullion owns big or owned big thunder mountain
railroad Harrison high tower at the tower of terror in Tokyo. He owns that hotel. So all these
characters are in one little special club and they're not all from the same era necessarily,
but they're, they've all belonged to this club at various points in time. Um, correct. Like some
would be from like the isn't Schweitzer of Schweitzer falls. One of the oars. Yeah. He's a
character from the jungle cruise mythology. Dr. Albert falls. Dr. Al. Oh, oh, right.
Schweitzer is a real person. Okay. Yeah. Um, uh, Carmelia, I, I, where's my Carmelia Falco, uh,
one of the, the worst pot, the earliest member of this, of C and recently announced as the,
the character in a Soren fantastic flight, which is coming to Tokyo Disney say,
but this was her first mention was in this. And then they announced her for that.
Well, so the, all right. So the thing, if you haven't been, the thing is that all of these
characters are tributed with oars hanging right next to where you pay for your bow.
Not a convenient place to dilly dally, much like where Rosita is not a good place to hang out and
take pictures of dorky shit. Um, and yet that's where they put them. But I, but I think this is a
fun, uh, you know, that's a, it's a fun little Easter egg. And if they're starting to tie all
of this mythology together, that they can do something like this. It makes it, I think it
elevates the, what could just be kind of a really just a quick service restaurant into, oh, it's
like it's placemaking and it ties together something from Tokyo or Hong Kong. Yeah. I mean,
it's, I think that's what was kind of exciting about seeing Rosita there, like in the art was
it was like, oh, this is not just going to be, this is obviously going to be touched by some
nerdy imagineering people. Obviously we didn't know that there would be like sea paddles,
but just Rosita itself is such an inside reference. You knew that there's going to be some aspect of
that and there's going to be some history, there's already history happening here. And then the sea
paddles were just an extra little cherry on the top of like, oh yeah, okay. This isn't just some,
like the corporate people didn't just go, add a sir, serve them some different colored dole whips
or whatever that they were like, they got approved little references. And then a tease
to the character that would be coming to Tokyo Disney sea. But then there were three, like I
looked at the full list again on, on the Disney Wiki and all of the characters had their own pages,
except three S Shio, Dr. J L Battarista and chef Tanja Tan Daji. Those did not have any answers.
So those might be teases too, upcoming attractions. And an imagined year was quoted as saying like,
there is hints of upcoming attractions in tropical highway. I mean, that's fantastic.
That's interesting. Yeah. Uh, I don't know what's coming that involves like adventurers.
Yeah, that's the problem because everything is coming is IP. So it is like where, yeah,
where are you going to put stuff like that? I've, I'm trying to think like,
yeah, Soren in Japan is, is like an original Disney ride. The chef makes me think restaurants
that could be coming. I mean, there's lots of hotel work being done in Florida.
Well, they just did the, uh, um, what Mary, what's her name? Uh, they just did some stuff with her.
And, um, she's on the cruise ship and on pleasure Island. Yeah. So I feel like maybe now
for a little while, the society of explorers and adventures are going to be like, uh, regulate,
relegated to, uh, non rides. Oh yeah. Well, and I mean, I have to, I would bet money on it,
like something in the jungle cruise movie. I mean, it's been pushed for a while.
Well, also the, there's a little clues in the places because, uh, chef Tandaji works on the
Irrawaddy river, a real river in Myanmar. Um, so, okay. Well that's not it. So that's Burma.
Is like, is that possible? I don't know where the jungle cruise takes place. Is that India?
Um, I don't know. We have to look it up. I'm glad you said, I only know geography and not real ones.
So we're not taking sides in the, there's a conflict. Yeah. Conflicts in Myanmar slash Burma.
Well, this, the only side I take is the side of Trevor Noah being our greatest.
Oh, it's a great time to be in the Trevor Noah business. Early March.
He heals us with laughter. Um, anyway, uh, uh, hey, you know what else? I think the oars themselves
are neat. They didn't just like stack up 10 oars. There's cool textures on these things.
There are various levels of aging. One has an arrow in the side. One had some bites taken out of it.
One has a crocodile skull attached to it. Is that merry weather pleasures?
I think so. Yeah. From, yes. He, I guess being the founder of pleasure islands, right? Which crazy
that like this old, this defuncts attraction that was essentially like a nightclub place where we
went to see some disco is attached now to this same mythology that links up the tower of terror
in Japan. Well, sure. And Jason Chandler was one of, going to be one of the like main like story
points of discovery Bay. And then they, he was a young inventor. And so then they kind of factored
him in into the big thunder mythos that he made the drilling machine that Barnabas T Bullion bought
to drill into the mountain. And then he was like, Barnabas, I don't know if you want to,
there's a lot of spooky stuff happening. Maybe you should dial back, but his Barnabas is thirst for
gold drove him further. Oh, wow. The thing I missed, which is embarrassing to say is that we
didn't go in Tokyo and you're going to go to Tokyo soon. There's a restaurant in Disney called
Magellan's and just like, you know, you can't hit everything. So I was just like, oh yeah,
we didn't get to Magellan's. I think it's a little more expensive, but whatever. But Magellan's is
the headquarters of C. Oh, so you have to go to Magellan's for the report. Yes. And anything I
I'll take pictures of anything on the wall, even if I don't understand it, I will copiously. Yeah.
Get ready for Magellan's. Yeah. That's where they all hang out. Cool. Okay. Neat. Neat. So they all
got a flight to Japan and they're like balloons and dergables. Well, but it's not technically Japan.
Oh, you know what I mean? It's like what part of Disney sees it in what's the error, the theme
volcano and stuff. So what part is that around mysterious Island? Yeah. Yeah. So it's not really
Japan in the fiction. I see. It was Verney. Good point. I gotta get my head. I didn't think I
realized one of the things that like kind of tanked Discovery Bay was the sort of lackluster
results of Island at the top of the world. Oh, okay. The movie. Uh huh. Gotcha. Yeah. I had
never known that. Do you think somebody on one of these oars is a character from the
Dwayne Johnson Jungle Cruise movie? Yes. Oh, yeah. That could be it. That seems right. Yeah. I
would assume because there's a lot of been a lot of talk for years now because they've been
they just pushed this movie back another year for some weird reason from scheduling, but they've
been talking about this right. That's this movie for so long. They've been talking about ride
upgrades for so long as well. So it would seem like this is something they're expecting to be
a giant hit and expecting that they'll get money now to redo Jungle Cruises across the world. So
it wouldn't surprise me if they were. This was a real like synergy relationship from the start,
but potentially, I mean, I was just listening to an older Disney dish on the drive over about how
like imaginary has been told to pump the brakes on the, uh, the Mary Poppins. Sure. That's true.
Sort of attractions for the UK Pavilion. That's Jim Hill, right? Yeah. You cite your sources.
I said Disney dish. Yeah. Sorry, sorry, sorry. Yeah. You're right. I missed it.
Now I feel like this happens a lot because that happened with gigantic for the, yeah,
they have a lot of grand plans and then the movie doesn't, but like, when does a movie go according
to play? Like when has a movie besides like infinity war? Well, every Marvel Awakens been
like the openings they expect. Only Marvel movies can you at this, at this moment in time count on,
I think. Cause yeah, I don't think, I think Mary Poppins is just according to Jim,
just broke even across the world and now is making money. So it was not a runaway success.
And they were talking SQL, but who knows? Yeah. So what you're saying is we will see a Captain
Marvel Air Force recruiting center. It's like a, just, yeah, it's just an angry person going like
you, you got what it takes kid. And then you sign up and then yeah, you're in the military
or in the air force. I've been over your fantasizing about if, if in fact this is a reference to the
jungle cruise movie, I would like to see a new mythology society set up, which is I'm calling
SOAR, S O R society of rocks. And this is the mythology that ties together all of the identical
jungle running around rocks of which there are now three, I believe. I have the IMDb up in
jungle cruise. His name is Frank in a rampage. His name is Davis Okoye and in Jumanji, he's Spencer.
So let's start tying to get, they all wear sorta like, just like Explorer hats or like open shirts,
mainly open shirts. So if they like have, if they like took all of those busted open broad chest
shirts and hung them up on a wall somewhere. Yeah, that's great. Yeah. And then so they have SOAR,
we have source C and space. Space is the one we're inventing. Right. But a lot of people have
the cosmic ones. People had some great acronyms, but we're not for that. Those are great, but
we're still working on them. Yeah. And this is, and maybe I could also propose a society of
food centric animatronics. Oh yeah, that's good too. That's good. Yeah.
Food animatronics, digestimatronics, what about Dinamatronics? Ooh, I like that. That's clean.
So SOAR, the society for Dinamatronics. Are there enough? Oh, you know what problem though?
It sounds a little like dinosaur. Confusing potentially if you were a Dinomatronic.
Interesting. You just gotta put that E in there. Are there enough characters in the park that drink,
like I can think of a pirate or two with a bottle of wine to make a club for like winos.
Hmm. The society, the SFA, the society of functioning. Wait, no, I guess, well, it's,
it's a, what AA is, uh, uh, alcoholics. Yeah. Audio animatronic alcoholics anonymous.
Oh, that's good. Yeah. Who else drinks? Um, I mean the pirates, mainly pirates.
Right. But there's gotta be a, uh, at the table in the Haunted Mansion, someone's drinking
because you see it go into them. The old Humphrey Bogart watches the old
Ingrid Bergman animatronic get on that plane. He takes a swig from a flask in his coat.
The most advanced audio animatronic sequence ever made that they demolished. Yeah. He's in, uh,
and uh, who goes canteen. Okay. Yeah. Oh, I have to sing it in the rain. Uh,
Gene Kelly animatronic was a little tipsy in that scene. Right. Fine. He's in. Yeah. All right.
Mary Poppins has all that. She's drinking all that medicine. There's gotta be some alcohol in
there. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So she had Mary Poppins. She's in awe. She's in awe.
Like we're forgetting a big one. Who else got to be, who else drink, but are they secret alcoholics,
which they very well might be. Right. Um, yeah. Rocket raccoon drinks. Oh yeah. Yeah.
First guardians. He gets real hammered. Oh, that's right. So he's in a,
this is my kind of crew. I like all these. This is, these are a lot of my favorite characters.
You and Poppins and rocket. Oh yeah. Oh, and you know, Rex gets down to he's, he's at that
bar every day. He's getting free. Probably it's probably how they pay him is in drinks. He is.
Yeah. You definitely get some drink tickets. Uh, he, but I feel like he is constantly pouring
liquid into his, what would be his mouth and it's sparking and he goes, Oh no, I forgot.
That's right. Wait, I can't drink. Oh no, I'm still getting used to my
digestive programming. Um, and you know what, to tie it back together, Chuck E. Cheese gets down to
bowler hat. Chuckie. Yeah. Yeah. I think that's why I like that guy. He's I I'm imagining like a,
uh, who's the, who's the drummer, uh, uh, as buddy rich, like a buddy rich tape of, uh, Chuck
scolding the munches make believe band. I'm just like, you gotta stay on rhythm munch.
You're fucking flat every time. I mean, are you going to make that video now? Aren't you?
I guess. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, uh, like, yeah. Yeah. Like, like Pasquale, I took a risk on you,
taking you out of the kitchen. Maybe I should put you back in there. Maybe I put you on toilet
duty is because you're, because you're drumming is shit. Hey, uh, can, uh, can security come over
here? There's a guy who's been sitting right by the stage for an hour, just videotaping.
He's not bothering anyone, but I feel bothered and murmuring lines to himself in a quiet chuck.
Chuck was talking about alts. He keeps writing down like notes on one pad and then like all
something called alts on index cards. And he's, and he's up to his third glass of white wine,
which is served to Chuckie cheese. I'll head there after this. Um, we should walk over there.
Do we not do the, uh, uh, uh, I'm, I can go either way. How long, how long are we doing?
55. 42 minutes. So, uh, we're almost at, we're almost at 40, one hour 40. Hmm. That's plenty.
I was saying I wanted to do it, but, um, yeah, I would like to do it, but for the sake of time.
Yeah. Yeah. That's why we call it for another. Yeah. Then maybe we could, we did it before.
Mine also, I would like to have more time to research it. Cause I just went down a real,
I found something new this morning that ties into like KTLA TV history. And I'm fascinated
with why it is associated, why this character is associated with Disneyland. Well, um, huh.
We have an episode that could, I had an idea. I was gonna pitch you guys that it could tie into.
So that's like another thing we'll talk about. Okay. So, um, how do we get out of there?
Wrap up last thoughts. Yeah. I have one other little stupid thing I want to bring up.
Okay. Uh, uh, okay. Um, anyway, yeah, yeah. Straight, straight to Jackie cheese, straight to
the, uh, yeah, straight to the wine, uh, uh, the wine aisle. I'll bring up mobile order wine is good.
I'll bring up one thing I like, which is just a nerdy thing is that the original Tahitian Terrace,
Tahitian Terrace had a sign that said sun kissed, I presume, which is like a reference to, uh,
Dr. Livingston, I presume. Yeah. Uh, and now the new tropical hideaway has something that says
Dole whip, I presume. Oh, so another nerdy reference to a classic thing, which again,
you feel it. Nerds like us feel the detail, which is why you want to go back to a place like this.
Doing it. I discovered, uh, not, uh, not everything from Aladdin's Oasis, uh, terrible.
They preserved a lot of the beautiful metallic and glass lamps and stuff. And they're off in
the corner and it says like lamps for sale. That looks very, uh, pretty and a nice nod to the
history of the area. I like that too. Yeah. I like all, I like all the little like, uh, scenic things
and rugs and yeah, all that stuff's fun. Good lamps, good oars, great lamps. Okay.
Food mixed food, but I have a nice feeling about it anyway. I'll say this like, yeah, like Mike said,
it might just be like a dollar too much. So I'd say put that annual past discount in there,
but you know, they may not want people, they, they want people to come and they want people to spend.
But when I was there, I was like eating on a trash can for a while until a table opened up.
And even then I'm like looking around and it's like, Oh, people have posted up. And then I am,
and then I was looking around and like, Oh, families with kids are looking for a table.
So then I'm like, woofing it down. Cause I feel very guilty. Just make a single person taking
up a table for four. Yeah. Yeah. Um, and you're just in your cursing that without that annual
past discount, you, you blew 60 cents cursing up a storm yelling, you're lucky. I'm going to get
$20 worth of personal pizzas after this, uh, which I have to say one of the, uh, the pizzas,
again, I recommend more good except one said it came with pancetta on it, like pancetta onions
and cherry peppers. I thought that was going to be like the little crispy kind of fatty chunks
of bacon. And it was like shaved pork. It was more like, like Italian pork kind of, so which
was okay, but not what I was expecting. Anyway, definitely check out tribal hideaway and check
out Napolini too. If you need a quick bite in downtown Disney or to get your party validated.
What an ad. Something tells me we're even though we talked about it here, we're not done talking
about it in general. I think Napolini is, uh, maybe there's an appellate month, maybe four
episodes about Napolini. Uh, all right. Yeah. That's, I like it. Uh, all that would make it
better is plus it up is let's get just a couple of Tiki drinks in there. It doesn't have to be
a full bar. There's not a ton of room. Make them pre-made. I don't care. Put a jug under the
whatever counter, just pineapple juice and put some rum in there. Who gives a shit? Let, let us
have it. Let us have our medicine. We just want, we just want to sit and watch boats go by. Of
course, I understand, you know, capacity wise, but whatever, let us put, put those spots all over
the park so we can, you know, we don't have to all be in one centralized location. Oh, uh, cast
members were also all great there. Lots of people walking around, taking trays, uh, all the people
behind the counter. Very quick, very helpful. Uh, I know it probably sucks working at a new restaurant
the first six months as they're figuring stuff out. Everyone was really good. Hmm. That's great. Um,
well, I say, uh, yeah, give us our medicine, make this the first place you turn on when liquor goes
park wide, which will happen as soon as star wars is a hit. I would think. Yeah, it's got to. Uh,
and I say retroactively make things right every once in a while, do a show where you let a
woman punch Indiana Jones in the face over and over again. Great. Yeah. I think that's easy now
cause this is, this is still pretty general. So yeah, you can run shows in there once in a while.
Yeah, there's, yeah, it's crowded, but crowded, but I mean, I'm saying it's not tied to another IP.
So, you know, let Rosita attack him. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Peck his face. This is for crystal skull.
A fridge. Are you kidding me? Bring back Mutt Williams.
Justice for Mutt. Mike, Mike, by the way, gave me for my birthday what you're a Mutt Williams action.
That's true. Yeah, I did. I also maintain Mutt is a fine character. I, what is down the number 20
on the list of, of issues with that movie. That might be true. Yeah. Uh, I love that switch blade.
Yeah. Is it funny? Sure. That's hip stuff, Daddy. Oh, all right. You survived podcast, the ride.
Thanks so much for taking a trip to the tropical hideaway. If you want to hear more nonsense,
including an upcoming, a net episode naming structure, a Hawaiian at there's a Hawaiian
at album and Italian at, and then there's like a workout album and I forgot the name of it.
So how do you, Patriot at, uh, oh, Patriot. Oh, that's great. Yeah. I guess where I goes,
Patriot nets. And you'll be able to hear that at patreon.com slash podcast, the ride. Uh,
check us out on our, our Twitter, our Instagram, our Facebook and our sub Reddit program by the
nice guy who you met at the tropical hideaway. Yes. And then you yelled at no, you're doing a
heck of a job, Robert. I'm assuming ours is a lot less maintenance than the doughboys one,
which said you were also an admin on God's getting into suicide bomber territory over there.
It's chaos. Uh, and, uh, Hey, if you're out and about and you see our favorite band,
hashtag full munch. Um, and otherwise we'll, uh, to do a new episode next week. What a catchy
sign off. Jesus Christ. Hashtag full munch. Hashtag full munch. Bye bye.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts. Keep up with the latest
forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page
on Facebook.