Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains souvenir pricing estimates, operations questions that
Disney refuses to answer, construction speculation, and oh yeah, I guess some talk about, you know,
rides and stuff.
Our guest, Carly Weisel, has been to Galaxy's Edge and lived to share the tale on today's
podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men who'd rather have
an appetizer at the upcoming Epcot space restaurant than talk to a real astronaut.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I would agree with that.
Yep, Scott Gardner also here.
But I disagree because I would really like to talk to Buzz Aldrin, but not about going
to space, but rather about when he performed She Blinded Me with Science live with Thomas
Dolby and he was the old man doing science.
And there's one part where he gets it wrong.
He clearly has barely been coached in this and instead he says, silence.
And he does it like a beat late.
It's one of my, it's my favorite, one of my favorite videos that I, that is not viral
that I wish was viral.
Late Buzz Aldrin saying silence.
How old is it?
A couple of years ago.
And Thomas Dolby's playing a crazy like little like, you know, pack strapped over his chest.
He's like hitting the drum pads and it's a funky little version of it.
It's pretty good.
And Buzz Aldrin, clearly Buzz Aldrin not familiar with this pop hit of 1982.
So I would like to talk to Buzz about that.
I'll skip the space part though.
Okay, yeah.
Who gives a shit about space?
But those appetizers are going to be really good.
Yes, I've got space.
Still prioritizing those.
Absolutely.
We have a guest today.
Let's bring her in because we have a ton to talk about.
Folks, you know where she's a prominent theme park journalist.
Please welcome Carly Weisel.
Hi.
Hey, welcome to the show.
Thank you for being here.
I'm thrilled.
Yeah, we're very excited.
There's a lot of stuff you've done.
I will say you did just do something that's insanely exciting that we're very jealous
of.
We're of course talking about you being on the Disney Dish podcast with Jim Hill and
Lentesta.
I'm not gonna lie, career highlight.
I agree.
I'm very exciting.
Exclusive dream that not everybody...
I don't know, it was like the closest I'll ever come to sitting on the couch at Kimmel.
You know what I mean?
This was really my Hollywood moment to be in the middle of the internet.
Well, and it's funny that you bring up the talk show thing and I was thinking about that
because we reached out to you to talk about some other stuff besides all that.
And your response was, I would love to come on.
I should tell you that I am doing Jim and Len.
And I was like, huh, is this the beginning of a 90s Leno Letterman-esque guestbooking
war?
I'll be the first of two there, just wanted to let you know.
I just wondered, does it start to become that, you know, like, do they start now?
You chose them first and we respect that.
Well, they did ask first.
They did ask first.
They were on the ball.
But does it start becoming...
They get Jeff Garland and they get...
Yeah, Jim and Len poached Jeff Garland from us.
We have him scheduled, but obviously he's like, I can't do it!
Do it, Jim and Len!
He wouldn't disrupt everything to go to Celebration Florida?
Well, it depends.
There may be a whole thing, Len may have a private jet we don't know about.
He starts flying guests out.
Who knows how bad this war is going to get.
We don't have a jet.
And then suddenly we ask one of our significant others, Aaron or Lindsay, to be on and they're
like, oh, you know what?
I'm doing Disneyland.
Come on, no.
Aaron will only do Disney dish.
I just like their show better.
Jim and Len seem more pleasant than you guys do.
I know.
I'm so sorry.
It's just that's the way it is.
We understand.
How was...
How did you...
You went on to talk about the...
Some of the Star Wars rides that you may have heard about.
Yes, the hottest planet in the galaxy.
Is that right?
Yes.
How was your...
Tell us about...
Well, I do think that you guys are way more interested in hearing about going on the Disney
dish than...
When we're leading with it, just because we knew we wanted to give a lot of time to it.
And if we have overrun time, also address some of these Star Wars...
If we get there, yes.
We don't like...
We keep our own pace.
We don't like the machinations of giant hyper corporations to drive our content.
So, you know, when all this news came out, I think at least my reaction was, oh, god
damn it, we have to do an episode about this.
Geez.
We just did one about the entryway and the Today Show Cafe and all that.
Listen, you know, I have a gripe about that because I think I'm the only person in this
business who is psyched about the Today Show Cafe.
Oh, yeah.
We did just talk about a little...
I am.
It does seem like the food is a higher quality level than what Universal has been offering.
Before, I think it was that Beverly Hills Boulangerie or whatever.
Yes.
I'm pretty sure.
What's the place?
It's a place that I have never eaten food from.
I assumed it was just like the Tinseltown Cafe.
It was like a nothing.
Yes.
It was like an airport sandwich where everything's focaccia.
It was kind of like that.
All right.
And I don't know.
I like Al Roker.
I'm very curious about what food he will feed me.
I'm sure there's going to be some brown rice with an edamame.
It'll be something kind of healthy.
Did you get it on an email?
Did you get the press release?
You get all the press releases, right?
Yes.
You probably get more than we do.
Well, that's the thing.
They don't really email you lately.
They'll just throw it up.
I mean, at least for Disney, they'll throw it on the Parks blog and then you'll freak
out if you miss something.
Oh, really?
I'll definitely come to us.
Though I do get a lot of press releases about animals being born in Animal Kingdom.
Oh, really?
That is fun.
Yeah.
But I'm also like...
Any good ones lately?
I mean, I got a press release about a new giraffe and I got a press release about the
kid city at Epcot and that was basically it.
Interesting.
So far we've been shut out of any sort of Disney official press releases.
Universal, both coasts are very...
Oh, wow.
They send us a ton of press releases and stuff.
And Mike got an exclusive interview.
I got to interview the Grinch a few months ago.
Oh my God.
What a get.
Yep.
Yeah.
So Universal is...
They're very friendly to both.
So far Disney is not...
We would love those press releases about the animals being born because we would...
I'll see what I can do.
We could get two hours out of every one of those, certainly.
We do have so many questions for you about your general career covering the parks and
we were saying it does seem like you're always at one.
You're traveling around a ton.
Yeah.
I spend a lot of my free time in Florida alone, which for most people would be a red flag,
but for me is just another day at work.
Sure.
You did...
Because I was looking at your Instagram live videos and it was a week or two ago and you
were doing something that I was very on board with and I think Scott would be very stressed
out by.
You were there for a very limited amount of time and I'm not exactly...
You'll fill it in.
And you were just going somewhere so you could get to Epcot maybe for a few hours.
Do I have the story at all correct?
Yeah, you have it pretty correct.
So okay, a long story made probably very long by the end of it, but I had to be in Sarasota,
Florida on the 15th of February.
It takes a whole day to fly from LA to Florida, as you guys probably know, like west coast
east coast whole day.
So I had to fly out the day before so I could drive the next day, but it was Valentine's
Day and I thought it was very sad to spend Valentine's Day alone on a flight.
Keep in mind I am married, but that did not factor into my plans to go to Florida alone.
So I thought I will wake up at, I think I woke up at 5 a.m. to take a 710 flight to
Florida and then after I got a rental car, all said and done, I had four hours to cram
a solo Walt Disney World vacation in and I did it.
Yeah, I really did it.
I like this is the thing this gets like of the show.
I mean, Jason, I think there's a spectrum here of people that like to do something like
that. That's insane. I think I'm the one who likes to do something like that.
The most Jason next then Scott.
I think that stresses him out.
Oh, I don't wait.
I don't know what you're saying though, because me just just spending four hours in
Epcot or something that sounds I'm also the guy who likes to just pop in.
That's true too.
No, I crammed a whole vacation.
You crossed the border.
She did the full.
Oh, yeah.
You like, yeah, that would not be wild.
Would not be on my.
Well, what did you do?
How did that play out?
OK, so I got the car took way too long.
Very stressed about it.
I changed into Florida clothes in the driver's seat of the rental car, went straight to Epcot.
Clothes and shirts that said Florida.
Oh, no, like warm weather stuff.
OK.
No, I wish.
Sure.
I mean, like a casual Mickey Mouse sweatshirt.
You should have one in a go bag at all times anyway.
You never know when you'll suddenly end up.
I mean, I'd laugh to just put a Disney parks poncho in my trunk yesterday being like, who knows?
Yeah, because if you're anywhere nearby, you might as well pop down.
So I drove very fast to Epcot and then I sped walked to the Germany Pavilion of the World
Showcase to get caramel corn because that's stop one.
Oh, stop one.
And then I ran into a friend, which was great, but it cut about 45 minutes off of my time.
Oh, yeah.
Just very stressful.
Human contact.
I don't know about this.
No, it was it was fun.
It was worth it.
I was happy to see him.
And then I walked so quickly back to my car and then I was going to.
That was it at Epcot.
Oh, yeah.
Just caramel corn and that way.
Very efficient.
Wow.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I don't.
I really don't understand.
Well, keep in mind, I spend a lot of time in Florida.
Right.
I was there like three weeks before that.
Of course.
Oh, OK.
Yeah.
Well, there you go.
So then I was driving back.
I was driving in the Magic Kingdom and I was like, I can't do it.
And I just turned.
I just took a left and I went back and I went to Fort Wilderness because I wanted fried chicken.
Wow.
Yes.
And so there is a specific fried chicken in Fort Wilderness.
Yeah.
So the Hoop-Dee-Doo musical review.
I don't know if you guys are lucky enough to have experienced the weirdest show ever.
It's the longest running show at Disney World.
I almost did it.
I went with two friends last March and I was like, hey, would you guys want to go to the Hoop-Dee-Doo
music review?
When I was a child, I went.
I think it also holds in a record, at least in America.
I think the Agatha Christie play is at the Mouse Trap.
It's like still running in England for like 60 years straight.
Something crazy like that.
Is some sort of like the most consecutive performances record that Hoop-Dee-Doo has set.
Yes.
In America.
Simpsons of live entertainment.
Except a bit more dated.
Oh, so they saw the old show.
They haven't even updated the show at all.
Yeah.
Do you have an example of that?
What's the dated?
Well, they're all acting kind of like the show just rolled up through town and it's
very Western and they're wearing like period dress.
I like that.
Yeah, but I do not like the show, which you just lost all of your listeners.
I apologize, but I love the fried chicken.
So did you see the show or did you get to go at the Hoop-Dee-Doo?
There is next to there is Trails End, which is a buffet, but inside Trails End is a to-go
counter where you can get the chicken to go.
Got it.
So I sat outside of a playground like a female pedophile, just eating a ton of chicken and
macaroni and cheese all alone on Valentine's Day and honestly loving every second of it.
It's the opening of Little Children 2.
It's a deep cut for the Little Children fans out there.
What is that?
Kate Winslet.
Isn't that what that's called?
Oh yeah.
Kate Winslet, Jackie Earl Haley movie.
Okay.
Never mind.
You might be probably right.
You are married though.
Yes, I am.
Yeah, that's so.
Did you just repeat that to yourself like a mantra?
It kind of it made it a safe space.
You know, I had something to lean back on.
I didn't only have my sad cup of macaroni and cheese.
There are other things in your life than a cup of mac and cheese.
So was that the extent of the four hours or did you cram more in there?
No, no, no.
Okay.
So after that, the problem is that for I'm so this is so boring.
Four Wilderness has an internal bus system, which I am not a fan of internal bus systems
at Walt Disney World.
No, no, no.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
To get you to the specific lodging.
So then I had to wait for a bus to go back to the front of the campgrounds to get my car.
And then I was like, I got to catch Happily Ever After.
Right.
The Fireworks show.
The evening fireworks show.
So I foolishly goofed on what time it was at because it's usually at nine and I feel
like it was at 830, which was really upsetting.
And so I saw it from my car driving to the Magic Kingdom and it was great.
Oh.
It worked so thoroughly.
You have a little private shell for it, I guess.
That's kind of cool.
And I was in traffic, I think, because no one was driving because they were like,
look at the sky, it's exploding.
Right.
So I got to watch the show from my car and then I made it there and I sprinted to a fast
pass I had for Peter Pan.
And then I made it to Big Thunder, I think at like 850 and I had a fast pass set for that.
Then I just enjoy the rest of the night.
That's great.
I mean, I like it because I like the idea of that sounds like a mission, the whole thing.
It's not a pleasure, but it's a mission.
But I like a feeling of like time crunch.
I'm Ethan Hunt and then we have to get in and out and we have to do it.
Which I did the other day.
And listeners will hear on an upcoming episode in and out in three hours.
Maybe I don't want to spoil too much, but it involves two pizzas.
It involves $20.
Three hours.
Yeah, yeah, we can't spoil it.
It's a pretty big, it's a lot of, we make a lot of hay out of it, but Jason,
let's just say there's two pizzas involved.
That's we'll leave it at that.
Can I ask one question?
Yeah.
Do you really like pizza or was one very bad and you had to redo the experience?
Oh, it's a different angle than you're thinking.
But they were both pretty good.
But this is a killer tease for a future episode.
You know, people are going to be like, I know what the people want.
Yeah.
And I have a follow up question that I think people also want to hear.
Fried chicken at the trails end better than the Plaza chicken in Anaheim on Main Street.
Okay, so this is what I'm going to say.
The fried chicken at Hoop-Dee-Doo review is the superior chicken.
I think one, because it comes in a boneless bucket, which everything is that round of a bucket.
And two, I think because it's times for all that to be put on your table at the same time,
it's the perfect temperature.
Okay.
And sometimes with Plaza on a trails end, you get where there's just a few pieces left and it's kind
of sad. You get those like real like gross pieces of chicken.
Yeah.
So that's why I would say.
Oh, but it's made with like dinner theater precision.
If you see the show, it all comes out at the same time, like a,
like a high end multi-course meal where they put everything on the table together.
That's like what we experienced at the pirates dinner adventure in Buena Park,
with the difference being that it sucked.
Besides that similar idea.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That makes sense.
That is the most I ever feel like my mother and I don't do it off.
It is like, I, I see there's a fresh tray coming out. I'll wait a second.
Yes. Yeah.
My thoughts exactly.
But as I get older, I realized like, well, she is right. I mean, no skin off,
no skin off the workers. They're just going to dump the old ones and mix them up anyway.
Yeah. Why not?
I feel like we also have to, we have to ask you about this list that you just
posted where you have ranking.
Ranking the Disney world attractions.
Yes. I will mention that is an old list that got updated.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah. So I already kind of dealt with people sending me screenshots of cast members and
private discussions, making fun of me. And now it's all coming back again.
Oh no.
Interesting.
Oh, really are within the Facebook group for this show. I know this was posted and people had very
strong opinions. And this was sent to me by Mike, but by like, like, oh, this list, boy,
a lot of hot takes here. And I read it and I was like, yeah, sure. I don't know.
I wasn't too upset.
I got the list. I will say this. I got the list texted to me from a friend who lives in Illinois
that like knows I'm into this. And she was like, I think I'm trying to figure out exactly what was
the controversial order.
The only thing that I think everything for, depending on what person it is.
I guess that's the problem. The only thing I found offensive was country bears. So low,
but that's it. Other than that, I was like, okay, you really called me on here to answer for my sins.
This is where you're to get into the, uh, into the stuff.
I was wondering about the lit cause yeah, a lot of people were talking about it,
but like your top 10 very much made sense. And I,
like as I'm reading it, I mean, I think it's, uh, uh, working in media. I mean, we,
we try to be, I try to be self, uh, aware cognizant. You are writing for a large
general audience. Like travel and leisure is a general interest, like large audience magazine.
Yes. Full spectrum of fandom.
Also what's the, there is no list that makes everyone happy. Obviously.
No, there really isn't.
Cause like my list is country bears. Number one, but that's crazy.
Yeah. That is wildly inaccurate.
I'm searching my feelings and it's right. So how would that ever be a possible
in terms of, and that list is also not my personal list, right? Right. Right. Right.
Because personally, all I do is go on space mountain and I get a fast pass. This is a
Disney world and I go, Oh, no, no, no. I only write on the right-hand side. And then I make
them let me go to the right-hand side. And then I, depending on how I feel, I choose a certainty.
What's up with right-hand? What's right-hand side?
So I believe the right-hand side is the original track. And then they duplicated it on the left
and the left is generally where standby goes. But sometimes if the, cause they don't fill the whole
queue for the fast pass, they'll shove you to the left to go on the standby. And I don't stand for
them. Interesting. Do you think it's a better track or it's just more fun to go on the original?
I think that it's a better track. But also I know which way it leans. So it feels like home.
Oh, interesting. I got to do that.
Will it also beat you up?
Is bad.
Like, yeah.
It's a little like, they're both rough.
It is Space Mountain. Is there, is there a component, what, what have you found people
have like, have been upset about in that, in your rank?
Everyone just thinks I'm an idiot. It's just like the general consensus.
It's cause either it's, you know, a fan faction where they're like, you gotta,
you gotta lift up the old rides. Like the rides that people have a lot of nostalgia about.
And then I think everyone else just likes to hate, but I kind of tried to approach it as a,
you know, like what, like quintessential Disney attractions. Like, where is there a lot of story?
Where is there like a full range of experiences? Which is why I did one for Disneyland also.
And I put Splash Mountain one, even though I never go on Splash Mountain.
But I still think it's like, if you go to Disney and you ride one ride and you leave,
that'll give you the gist of what the park is.
Exactly. That's, I think I did Everest. Number one.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Yeah. Because if you, you know, if you show up to animal kingdom and you go on Everest,
I feel like you can figure out what Disney in 2019 is.
Right.
But people don't like that answer.
This is just like the one that Rolling Stone published, the top SNL cast members,
and everyone was upset. And obviously a list always is going to be controversial. So.
Big dis on Robert Downey Jr.
Robert Downey Jr. was like second to last or something?
Or the last.
He's like one of the country payers of the cast.
I guess. Pretty much the same thing.
Yeah.
I guess when you, when you talk about writing for a wider audience, yeah, I recognize it.
Wider, wider, not white.
Not white. No, no, no.
Yes, yes, let's just clarify that.
Oh, he's just a whites only. Oh my God. A wider audience. You, like,
I recognize that it requires levels to enjoy the carousel of progress. You have to be,
you have to have the disease where it's like, oh yeah, isn't it crazy and great that it's
VR that hasn't changed since 1994 for like a family from the Midwest visiting,
like that, like probably a seven year old child does not have the level of wait,
why is 1994 VR different than current VR? And why is that something I want to do whatsoever?
So I hear what you're.
I really have to code switch a bit, I guess, just kind of like,
cause I mean, you know, in the fan community, like I get everything that's going on,
but I can't really say that to someone who, you know, saves up for six years and goes to
Disney World. And they're like, I hear this carousel of progress is really tight.
And then they go in and are like, why are we trapped in this room for 45 minutes?
Yeah, it is crazy. Like, cause cause some of us are in our thirties. And we like,
imagine we weren't a nerd for theme parks. You just going into that right now today.
You didn't know much about Disney and you're in a theater and there's an old man talking about
an oven and that's the animatronic. He's talking about an old oven and what it was like to use an
old oven. And you're like, this is the thing everyone's been talking about.
Yeah. Then he shames his daughter in multiple ways through multiple decades. He mocks her
for costumes she's wearing and he explains the phenomenon of commuting.
And then they have like their uncles like drying out in a bath tub.
Uncle Larville, who gets no privacy for decades.
All this stuff that I've described, we love all the robot talking about an oven, but I guess a
roller coaster is roller coaster might be there. He has broader appeal. It is so funny. Any, anytime
any list is published, it's I don't, there's never been a list where everyone was like,
that's it. That's the perfect one. You guys should just make like a prank list where it's all of your
favorites and everyone will agree with you and the internet will love you. Yeah. I think we talked
about that. We talked about, we are like UCB performer people from the upper instance brigade
theater, comedy theater, and we would improv there for many years. And I just wanted to do an
unpublished, like an unauthored anonymous list of the top improvisers in Los Angeles.
Just a list of names and like just soft public publishing and like never say who did it. Wait,
I think someone did do that. I think someone did do a similar thing later, but there was some
UCB list where it was like every performer and it was just unranked. I think someone did a,
maybe a bit, there was, it was more of a bit about like, you know, how they have like the
up and coming comedians or whatever. And I think that I think that's what you're talking about.
Yeah. They're like the best thousand comedians. Oh, yes. Well, that's an annual, this guy does
this annual bit of the top 1000 comedians. And last year, like now they're starting to be like
every year there's a different twist on it. Like last year it was all women. This year it was the
top 2000 finalists. And at the live show they would reveal the top 1000. I was happy to say
I was in the top 2000. I don't know. Yes. My entire sketch team made it in the top 2000. I don't know
if I made it into the top 1000. I still have to find the video. That's the funny,
nice, fun bit version. Mine was just going to be this weird thing that was going to drive everyone
nuts by ranking them. But you were going to put like, like, like Ian Roberts was going to be low,
but then like some random student was going to be like, yeah, yeah. Or like, yeah, yeah.
Matt Besser would be number like 15. And then like some kid who had been doing it for a year was one
ahead of him. I love that. I love that so much. This is where people of theater gets burnt down.
Yes. This article. Yeah, we didn't have it. But it was such a fun fantasy too. To imagine.
Better than the current where it happens for the insurance money.
And there's some problems at the theater financially.
I'm sorry. Anyway. So let, hey, I'm safe. If it's a, if the list is a dark memory, I'm sorry.
I was not expecting it to be promoted on Facebook. That's what happened.
Is it recently got promoted on Facebook? So I keep getting screenshots. Listen,
it's great. Listen, like I, the company gets a ton of clicks. Everyone's discussing Disney.
What's better? Yeah. Yeah. I appreciate the debates out. No one has sent me. There are some
very mean comments about me on the internet. Oh no. No one has sent me anyone. Yeah. If you
guys want a good time, check out my eater video series. It is dark. Oh no. No. No. Sorry about
that. What about YouTube comments? Oh yeah. And I fully looked at them and it was the thing is
though, nobody made fun of my appearance. It was all the way. I held a fork and knife.
Really? Yes. Like Cotillion etiquette. Yes. People. It was very, and they were very upset about it.
That's not a salad fork. Like what were they? They were just, I can swear here, right? Yeah.
It was just like, bitch doesn't know how to hold a knife. Why is she hosting this? And it was like,
I'm just here to put cake in my face and get paid for it. Like, why are you giving me a hard time?
I mean, you didn't hold it with the blade in your hand, cutting your hand,
did you? Cause if so, I like to cut with a fork sometimes. It's just,
that was the problem. I don't know. I stopped looking. Yeah.
Yeah. You mean to tell me it's difficult to be a woman on the internet. Now I've heard everything.
You'd be shocked. Yeah. All right. Even in this joyful community.
It is a more, do you, do you find that though, that like with theme parks is your primary source
material? Is it like nicer? Do you think that writing about general whatever or broader pop
culture, whatever? Maybe not. I don't know. I don't know. Interesting. Because there I've never,
I mean, I've written about a lot of different things. I started writing about theme parks
about four years ago and I've never experienced a group of fans so passionate about everything
you do and everything you say. Like I'm currently filled with anxiety that I'm going to mispronounce
a star Wars reference and I will never live it down. Well, that's the perfect, you know,
Venn diagram, right? Theme park fans and star Wars fans. Like that's a lot.
Yeah. If there is a train shall meet. Blood will boil. Cities will be toppled.
I think every now and then like something will come up that is like, ah, like fandom behavior
happens, but like spending so much of my life reading comics and learning about the history
and the culture around it, like very little surprises me of like insane fan behavior,
wrestling too, getting to know more about wrestling. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. Nothing in theme
park has quite surprised me of like compared to comics and wrestling. Yeah. People have a lot of
time on their hands and a lot. Now they have a space to put their thoughts. That's really what's
going on. That's what it all was down to. That's really what's going to destroy all of our brains.
Well, let's open up, let's open up the floor to mispronunciations. Let's start talking about,
yeah. I'm so sorry in advance. I won't know. I won't be the one who knows. I don't know any
of this. The only way I'll correct you is if it's like one of my favorite pod racers.
So it's, you'll be fine. He's gotten years of comedy off of just knowing a dozen pop racer names,
like in multiple formats. Yeah, I'm laughing already. You're going to be very disappointed.
So funny. That's what I mean. My phone, when I was trying to type out the phrase Hondo Onaka,
my phone gave me the prompt. Did you mean condo non-com? Which is also kind of a good Star Wars.
I mean, imagine we were at this, we were at this three day Star Wars Galaxy's Edge press event.
Yeah. And we were not allowed to take any photos. And typically when you're reporting,
you take photos of, you know, like food signs. So you get the ingredients, take a photo, you type
it up later. No photos. So I was with my iPhone trying to write down all of these space food names
and it's just auto-correcting everything. And it was so stressful. Oh my God. You just got to shut
it off entirely. Well, so to, let's, let's explain the whole thing. Yeah. You have just, you've just
returned from this giant press tour. Wow. Wow. One of the first to go. You wrote an article,
or you've written about it in Travel and Leisure and for, yes, I wrote one story for Eater and I
wrote a set of six stories for Travel and Leisure that are, there's two more coming out this week.
Oh my God. Really? Okay. So if you're listening to this, you may have already heard some Carly's
work about this, but yeah, the main thing is you've been there. We have not been there.
And you got to walk through, through queues and through parts of rides and you've experienced
food months ahead of, well, I might, we might not be able to do it for a year and a half.
In my head, in my head, it does feel like I'm talking to someone who like touched heaven,
like went to the other side and now you're back. Cause I'm thinking like you have been in the ride
because we, do we go by and I always make my girlfriend, we, I stop on the top of the parking
garage and go, that's where the ride's going to be. And I like think about it. Same thing every time.
Sometimes we have a time. And does anyone think we're not all in on that, that we are not part of
the fandoms we have described? Yeah, yeah. Yeah. Oh my God. Yes. Yeah. When I, yeah,
I take the parking garage photos. Yeah. We're out of our minds. Yeah. I do hope that heaven
doesn't have a nine hour line, but if, but I would argue though, that if heaven is as good as people
say, worth it to get in for a nine hour line. So that's the same way in like, are there bathrooms
in the queue for heaven or no, okay. That a picture with Bruce Springsteen. Yeah. Jason,
eight hours to meet Bruce Springsteen once. Was it worth it? Yes. It was pretty satisfying.
Yeah. Anyway, so you did this incredible three day. So yeah, explain exactly a whole thing.
So it was, it was a three day press trip. It started in San Francisco at Lucasfilm. So we were
in a conference room there and they were kind of giving us general, general ideas. And at that
point, you know, them even saying the name of a character was news. So we were all like,
oh my God, we were like eating it up, not realizing how in like the next three days would go. Like it's
as though we've been to war and came back to tell about it. But we got like a little,
little quick trip through the office to look at it. It's beautiful. Those people are so blessed.
And then we went on a plane and flew to Glendale or flew to Burbank, stayed in Glendale, went to
Walt Disney Imagineering the next day, then drove to Disneyland that night, stayed at Disneyland and
then had some meetings, tasted the food and then went into galaxy's edge. Wow. How many folks are,
were invited? Like how big was the group? I want to say like about 15 journalists at the beginning.
I think at the beginning there were about 10 and then for the final day we had,
we might've been up to 20. Wow. This is an elite group of theme park journalists too.
Yeah. I mean, I've really never been in a situation where you're with like capital
R reporters. Right. So every question, every single person asked was beneficial. It was amazing.
Interesting. So yeah, that's great. Yeah. Because if we were there, it would have been a lot of like
me asking about, well, are there pod racers on this ride? Like, so these are people that like
they can format a question so fast in their head because they do this, you know, all the time.
It was like all of us learned so much more because a lot of it was asking and seeing if you could get
an answer. And we learned a lot of things just by, you know, tossing something out there and seeing
if we can get a response. Right. And because everyone was so much better at their jobs than I am,
I got a lot of info. Sure. Yeah. I read the, I think I read the, I read the tech crunch coverage,
the entertainment weekly story is I can't understand 80% of what he ever writes. And I'm always like,
can you explain it to me? Like I'm an old person who's dumb and I still don't get it, but he knows
he got the most interesting details. Yeah. The technical side was very interesting. A friend of
the show, Todd Martins wrote about a free LA times, a kind of honed in on the play aspect,
entertainment weekly, a kind of like an overview. What are you? I'm laughing because the episode
right before all this came out, I trashed the play Disney app. Yeah. Well that and it's apparently
a big part of Star Wars. All the stuff they said sounds awesome and cool. So I was just specifically
saying the space mountain game left us very frustrated. Well, the amount the company has
used the word play recently is starting to get to me the way like 10 years ago, IP and content were
like, Oh, that's bumping me the wrong way. But then eventually I guess you just get used to it. Sure.
But everyone kind of have it. The entertainment weekly, similar to your article, is kind of an
overview of everything and split up into sections, which was helpful. What's really interesting is
that we all seem to have gotten like one tidbit other people didn't get. And like I know that like
me and a few other people have kind of been exchanging those little bites, but it was really
like there's little bits of information. Like I don't know if I got that you're going to carry
your droid around in a backpack, which I was not aware of. Yeah. We wouldn't carry your droid
around. Yeah. So when you go to the droid depot to make your own R or BB type droid, the droid
can physically move throughout the land, but for obvious reasons, it's not recommended,
which there's not a chance I'm not going to be using my droid in the land. But it's you put your
little droid in a little backpack and then it like beep boops when it goes near stuff. Oh, and wait,
so what does it do in the land? Am I getting ahead of myself? Do we want to go like top town?
Let's finish this part. But basically what you're saying is I think is that there'll be like in the
Harry Potter land or whatever, there's like certain spaces or certain spots where you use your wand
and it'll do something fun or it makes it rain or whatever. In this strip, there'll be like a bad,
not a stripper thing. There'll be like a bad guy or something. And then your little R2 unit
will notice that because there's some sort of signal it gets and it goes beep boop and like,
and maybe it alerts you to something or something like, oh, so it'll be like,
yeah, you're on a little adventure. So then because, you know, typically at Wizarding World,
you have a wand and you have to do a specific motion with the wand. Typically, it does not work.
Typically, everyone's children are confused and crying.
Yeah, it's very, it's a very specific like loop de loop up down.
It's like old we emotes on Nintendo.
But with the droids, supposedly, from what we understand, they will communicate to each other
and with droids in the land. So you won't have to do anything besides like hug it close.
Right.
And it will.
I laugh because the cast member picture that came out had someone carrying the droid in like a droid
carrier that looks like the Build-A-Bear. Oh, really? I haven't seen that.
Carrier thing. I forget where that was.
Yeah. So will everyone get a backpack?
Oh, no, I think I think it's probably a purchase item.
Oh, so you have to purchase a backpack also with the droid.
The backpack was like a sidebar that I got of like a side interview with Scott.
So it was just like a little like a little nugget of info.
Who's Scott?
Scott Trowbridge.
Okay. And I've heard that name.
Imagineer.
Who is he as part of this?
I would call the captain of the galaxies at a ship.
Oh, okay.
Interesting.
I believe their title is like portfolio lead creative, which none of those words make any
sense to me. But you're making all the cool stuff for the spaceships and the lasers.
That's complicated to put on a business card.
I'm sure there's like nerds screaming in their car right now about his full title and his
very brilliant outlook on everything that's being created. But he's yeah.
But you're following this guy around for three days.
Oh, he was. He gave like some lead presentations.
Okay.
Because the thing is at these events, we're like a ragtag group of journalists asking a
lot of questions that they're not allowed to tell us answers for.
You said on the Disney Dish podcast that you were kind of stonewalled about any operational stuff.
Yes.
Which is, I mean, very much our interest.
Of course. All of us. All anyone wants to know is how am I going to get in here?
How long am I going to wait? Am I going to get on a ride? What's it going to cost?
How do you think you're going to pull this off?
Yes. And we were given, I mean, the first day I was told like, no, no, no, no, no, this is
top level. Like we're telling you what animatronic you're going to see,
which is understandable because you know that they will release that closer to opening day,
but doesn't get not going to stop me from being curious.
I mean, hopefully it's that like, yeah, we're fine tuning everything. We don't want to say
anything until it's confirmed. Every now and then you hear horror stories about like,
oh, Imagineering doesn't communicate with operations that much.
Oh, no, there were multiple panels where they were like, this is the first time we've had
operations involved from the very beginning. Oh, great. Yeah. So it's definitely, they're not
not saying anything because they don't know. It's just that, you know, once Disney says anything on
the record, it is like God's word. Yeah. So I think they're just waiting until it's
right. Very, very specific and done. Interesting. Sure. Well, how do we tackle this?
Well, yeah. So yeah. Yeah. Okay. I guess we start a little bit. Do you want me to
visually walk you through the lens? That would be good. Sure. All right. Let's start. I guess.
So where did they put you up? What kind of per diem are we talking about?
I'm a freelance writer. I lost money on this. Okay. All right. We've all been there. Yeah.
They took us to the Lucasfilm gift shop. So I lost money. Sure. Yeah. So they have a, what are the,
what's the exclusive merch like at Lucasfilm? So basically they're like, if it says Lucasfilm,
it's exclusive. Okay. So I bought a very cute sweatshirt. Okay. And I bought a very cool water
bottle. That's it's like the opening credits. So it looks like a sky. It's like black with like
little white dots. I like that. Terrible water bottle, but it's very pretty. Oh, that's good.
I like that. When we got to go to Imagineering, I got an Imagineering mug and it sucks. I have
to reheat my coffee in like 10 minutes. So I feel you on merch that's still worth having, even though
it doesn't do its function. Definitely. I have a lot of promotional water bottles from events over
the years and it's all like a knockoff swell bottle. Yes. If you know what I mean, it's like
that aluminum with a twisty top, but it's not a swell bottle. So it, the top doesn't like fully
fit. Right. But I still paid $29.99 for it and was very happy. Yeah. We've all dropped some money
at Mickey of Glendale. Oh, did I need to buy an $18 goofy pin dressed in his outfit from the
current 90th birthday celebration? No. Did I? Yes. Does he have a similar Mickey outfit, the party
suit, or does he have a different? He has like a fun little hat and then he has a handmade confetti
vest. Okay. Yeah. So similar to Mickey minis. Yes. I'm into that. So, so when you get,
did you know, cause this, this, this is my experience with the day that you guys got to
all put these articles out. I was seeing a movie with my girlfriend and I got out and I said,
Oh my God, I have 30 texts from Jason and Scott. And I went like, did some, did something wrong?
Is something, did somebody die? Did somebody die? Like what's going on? Yeah. Did Walt Disney rise
from his grave and we have to do a quick episode to cover this. And I'm clicking through and I was
like, what? I couldn't even, there were so many articles. So, so did you know that this much info
was happening when this trip was proposed? Did it say we're going to do X and Y? So did you know,
I'm going to get to go to the land. I'm going to get to go to Lucasfilm. Did you know the extent
of the trip? Yes, because there was the most travel that's ever been involved in a work trip
before. Right. Okay. So you'd need it. We traveled every day and stayed at a new hotel every day.
Gotcha. But we knew there would be an embargo. I don't know if we knew at that point what day
we'd be able to publish. I think they just told us you'd have a few days. We'll let you know more
once you're there. But we knew we didn't know what we'd be doing. We didn't know what the panels
would be. We knew where we'd be. And I think I had to have known. Yeah. We knew we'd see the land,
but I kind of don't, I, until I'm physically there, I don't trust anything because anything can change.
Of course. Yeah. But I knew that we would be releasing information. I didn't know what would
be at midnight Eastern time. Oh, that's right. That's why it was. Yeah. Okay. It was at 1201 Eastern.
I'm still not really sure why, but anyone who went to bed early that night, it really lost out.
Yeah. Yeah. I was like on my way to an early, I was trying to keep it mellow and then the
news dump happened and I lost my shit. It feels like this is the only time it's happened after
office hours where they're like, Oh, were you going to go to bed? Never. Like just everything
came out. And I tweeted about this, that I did feel like the kid in the Disney world commercial.
I'm too excited to sleep. Which I don't, I, this is jumping around, but we did, let's just, the
thing that I found out via you and you, okay. You said, ask me, you said, ask me. Yeah, let's get this out of the way.
The speed of sound I typed is Paul Rubin's back as Rex. You did not know it was, that was like a little
dagger. Cause I was worried. Maybe I didn't know because I might've been clinically brained
at it this time. Cause I had been writing, I threw an Oscar's party. So I started writing two days
later than everyone else cranked out five stories in 24 hours. So I was, um, that's why I was like,
Oh no. Yeah, sure. Well, thank you for helping me anyway. Cause you refer me to your friend at
Nerdist. Is that correct? Amy Rockleff who knows everything about everything about star wars. She
is a brilliant genius and I knew she would know the answer and she did. And the answer was yes.
Paul Rubin's is back as Rex, as DJ Rex in the, in Oga's Cantina. Uh, I true, like you guys know,
I don't like, there's not a ton of IP that I am crazy for. I w I felt like such a little,
I had such a flurry, such a swell of a mode. I'm not kidding. I was too excited to go to sleep.
I could sense that from the, I think I said to once I go, I think this is the most excited
Scott has ever been. I could tell from the text messages that you were like on the highest of
highs, just of going on. I mean, it's as we've said, it's, it's become a joke, but I do think
it's true that Rex is my favorite character in fiction and knowing that he'll, he's back,
he's, he's back with his actual, because if it was not Paul Rubin's and also, I mean,
I love Paul Rubin's anyway, and this is, uh, you know, this is a great gifted comedian's second
most prominent character in the world. It goes, uh, Pee Wee Rex, Penguin's dad. Yeah. No, no,
side of that. Penguin's dad's really good. Like there's more mythology coming to my favorite
character and it's really him. This is, uh, God, I was at D 23 two years ago and I texted both of you
when they announced the Rex was going to be back in the land and it was like, uh, the Avengers
coming on stage. It was that the audience was that Jack. So it's, I'm, so I'm saying a lot of people
have this affection. So I get, I mean, I feel it too. I have more like feeling in my heart right
now than I ever have on the show. I can't believe what I can't believe is that you're, you're new to
all this. I love Rex so much. So people can't see your face right now, but I wish they could.
You're, you're elated. Yeah. Yeah. I'm a little like red in the face. I just felt relief. I was
like, Scott's going to be so worried until he gets a firm answer. And hopefully it's going to be the
right answer. And thankfully we got it really quickly. What would I do? I don't know. Rex is
played by Josh Gadd. Oh God, God, God. I'm in the casino. Trevor Noah's doing it.
Introducing Megan Treanor as Rex. Oh no, no, he can't do everything. Um, yeah, incredible new,
but what I, I was getting concerned because, um, you know, the announcement was made that Adam
Driver and the, you know, the, and, uh, the, you know, Daisy, really the cast of the current films
is going to be in it and not seeing a specific name confirmation for him really made me afraid.
Yeah. Cause they're all involved in the, and I will give a formal attraction name. So PR doesn't
send me an email in case they ever listen. Who knows, but it is star Wars rise of the resistance.
Okay. Right. The cast of the current sequel trilogy, as I've learned through writing many
stories last week, that's what it's called. Um, that they are there in the ride, but there,
I think they're only seen within the attraction. Right. Okay. Gotcha. But I told you, I, I saw
Rex, right? I wait. No, I'm not sure if you did. Maybe you didn't maybe I'm forgetting.
You did. Well tell me, tell me. They showed us. Oh my God. Do you see them in operation? Yeah.
Oh my God. All right. Take me through every step of that. And then I swear we'll talk about it.
You knew this was going to be the next hour though. I've got ribs. I need to cover. Okay.
Okay. No, hot dogs, space hot dogs. There are space hot dogs. Oh, yes, there are. Yes.
There are space hot dogs. But okay. So I'll try to, uh, uh, but I kind of want to drag it out
because I want you to be as happy for as long as possible. You could do, we could tease it.
You could, you could get to it because if it's part of the bigger story, well, it's just that we,
so they, on the day we went to imagineering, um, they took us to the animation building where we
saw Honda Anaka and we saw doc on dark and we saw the most important, of course, and they,
I got caught for recording sound cause I didn't know you weren't supposed to. So, um, I didn't
have, but I didn't start that until after, um, we've heard him bop around and play music and
give DJ commentary. You heard him talk. You heard new dialogue. Like wail his little arms. Can you
say anything you heard? Maybe not. Um, well, you know, so he, he said something during that,
but then he also, this is just going to be a big old jumble, but there's also, as you know,
as we've talked about, they're selling a small toy shaped racks that can just like
scoot around your apartment and play music. He moves. Oh, he moves. Oh yeah. God damn.
Big news. I didn't read that. Like boogies around on the floor, like a Roomba, but he can also
attach to your smartphone so you can play music through him. Don't get too excited yet because
you can also have him do commentary over it. And he will make like noises.
Cause he's a big fan of air horn. Bullshit. Oh my God. It was like peak toy execution.
Wow. Who's around? You can play any music you want through recs. Oh my fucking Lord.
So Gang of stuff. Whoa. Make a drink. Gasolina, Despacita. Weezer's Africa. All my favorite songs.
All of our, yeah. I mean, God willing, if you're able to get one, you can have. What do you mean
God willing, if you're able to get one? People are going to be, yeah, it's going to be as many
as possible. What do you mean? I just, I don't know. It's going to be really hard to get.
Okay. All right. Now you have to stand in line with us. Yeah. That's the wrong one.
You have to go first day. It's good. It's like a, it's, they did a very good job. You saw the toy.
Yeah, we saw it. Like so here, larger question then how tall are these droids available for
purchase? Okay. So the droids are like a foot. I would say maybe the, the height of a character
popcorn bucket, a little taller than that. Okay. So they're not, they're not miniature,
no, but they're big enough where like an adult can carry it under one arm.
Okay. Like a baby. Like my child. Like very much like baby training to carry one around.
My God. They are, they are very cool. So, all right. Dialogue. How's he sound? How does he do?
How's he doing? How's he been since his flight disaster? The way that they kind of explained
it to us was that he had like pivoted jobs. I think there's a whole backstory. I think as he
ended up on planet Batu at black spare outpost, which is the like marketplace center,
Cantina, et cetera, area of planet Batu. But he ended up there. He, Oga supposedly gave him a job,
I think is the backstory. And then he's there just playing like an hour. I tried to fact check it
the other day. I was like, now is it a three hour show or one hour repeats, or is it three hours of
original music? And I think it's, I didn't hear back in time. I apologize. Okay. I think it's at
least minimum an hour of original music with him in like interstitials. And you said the music,
it's bangers. So good. What's described. I mean, what I read was synthy poppy eighties,
which drives me absolutely insane. This is the most made for me. I almost want to say it's a
little worldly, which is very general because it has like alien languages in it. I think. And it's
very neck. My favorite thing in the star wars franchise, the song in return of the Jedi.
Oh boy. So real quick in case the listener, uh, there were two versions of, uh, with many
versions of star wars, uh, not unless should I return to Jedi? The original had this like very
princy sounding song. That's a cool ass song done by John Williams, son, a long time member of Toto.
Yes. Um, yeah, yeah. Current singer of Toto. Uh, and then it was replaced by in the special
editions, Jedi rocks. The worst thing I've ever seen. Yes. The thing, what's the piece of your
throat? The dangles. Yeah. You see the aliens, uvula. They go so close on this fake looking.
I hate that they replaced a cool ladies jam with that. Oh no, this is, this is a fuck ton of fun.
Oh, man. Oh man. Oh man. Okay. Can you, and then I'm sorry to keep our fingers. Yeah, we will,
we will get there. This is a special seven hour. I can relax if we clear all this. Can you remember
anything that he said or are you allowed to even say that? Um, I can't remember, but I could listen
to my audio from the toy presentation and figure out what he said and then text you later. Okay. I
will accept that. Uh, sorry audience, but you know, I hope you're all on my side. You're all here
rooting for me. I think it's some like radio puns. Okay. Okay. That's neat. As long as he's trying
his best. That's all we care about. He's doing a great job. That's what it is. I was connecting,
like I went on star tours last night and I was, and I was the spy for the second time, by the way.
Wow. The tips that I know how to play out now. Yeah. The audience with Kyle's there's Kyle had
a tip and it works. I think he said, yeah, he said it's just something about like it's, it's like
looking bored, but in a way that reads, it's like playing out. It's like finding your light
or finding the camera. It's like, yeah, it's sort of like you never look too much down. I think you
just put your belt on, but always look kind of straight ahead, but kind of like have just like
bemused or whatever, like a non plus look on your face. You can't act it up too much. Right. You
got to still play it down. But yeah, you know, it's like a sort of like a photo bomb. Like you have
to still like, you know, why you have to be like a figure that reads. Right. And as my wife pointed
out, you know, you can do that all day. However, if, if there's somebody with Mickey ears or wearing
something silly, it's going to be them. But if you're in a cabin without silly hats, you're in
the clear and you could potentially be the rebel spy. But I'm just so impressed that we learned that
tip and I've actually made it happen twice. Yeah. Yeah. I feel like I got an act for it now, but
anyway, start tours. I was just reminiscing about Rex and I was thinking it's what you were saying
about Buzzy. He's like, you know, he's a little guy trying his best and there's some, maybe I
didn't connect to star wars as much as a lot of kids because I, you know, I, everybody seems so
official and they know the universe and they know what they're doing and they speak in all this
jargon. I get on star tours and Rex is just like a regular bumbling guy. He fit. I just like,
he was your every man. Yeah, absolutely. I guess more, I guess for some reason, more so than Luke
to me. So yeah, if star wars has started Rex and not Luke, you would have loved my favorite movie.
You know, it actually, I seriously do equate it to Marty McFly because I love back to the future
a lot more than I love star wars. And I think it being like just a regular nervous, geez, I don't
know. I just connect to it more than like somebody would the rebel Alliance will be like,
well, they're going to have to, they're going to have to physically remove you from the cantina.
That's what I don't, I don't know how I'm going to stay there. You love so much. I've really made it
clear. I think like, if we have to call his mouth is a gape, I just, I mean, I feel, honestly,
I feel guilty that I've seen him and you have it. I did not cherish it this much, but you answered
my question. You passed, you, you didn't have an answer to my question, but you passed it along
immediately to somebody who did. And so I, I owe you very much for that. And you came here with very
little notice, like, like very little lead time to tell us about all this. So I'm indebted to you on
that love. You're it's, it's, it's great. Exactly what he said. I promise. Sure. You're a journalist
too. Like Scott, if you were in there, it would have been embarrassed. He would have been, we've
been trying to hug him and yeah, like, and yeah, and they would have to like be, sorry, excuse me.
We have to revoke your press clearances and credentials. Like, so sorry. Like my feelings
about Adam West and it's like, like there's very few things that occupy this or Prince or like,
there's very few pieces of pop culture. Adam West, Prince and Rex. All right. Let's start.
You guys take it from here. I'm spent that that sort of reaction the other night is like,
if we have to divide our efforts to, to experience this, I know Scott is just going to post up in
August canteen. I sure am for other reasons. I'll get, yes. Or other reasons. I, I think my big
pick would be a rise of the resistance. I think you're correct. Are you crazy? The main attraction,
Mike, you're doing the Falcon then. So, uh, just by possible limitation, sorry to saddle you with
the pod. I'm going to just hug that giant, a pod racing engine in Rondo to Rondo. That's fine.
Space hot dog. All right. Back to the start. Let's go. All right. So let's talk rise of the
resistance, which is sort of like, I would call it the Star Wars colon rise of the resistance.
Okay. I'm totally kidding. I'm totally kidding. Please. We love punctuation. We have a colon in
our title. So yeah, you're calling, um, yeah, Star Wars colon rise of the resistance. Uh, let's see,
what is everyone actually going to call this ride? The resistance ride or the, the big ride.
Yeah. What's the like, like just in the way that regular people are going to call it Star Wars land.
You mean like how I don't, I'm not going to call it Michigan. I don't call it the other one. I think
just the other one, probably the other one. Yeah. Right. Cause they're going to call it Millennium
Falcon. The big one or something. Yeah. The big, Hey, you want to go to the big one? Yeah. So you
have been to the big one. You've been inside the big one. Um, it's, so they showed us a portion of
the attraction. They did not show us the whole thing. We sadly did not get to go in that little
eight seat droid powered track with vehicle, but I did see a lot of artists renderings of it. So
I feel like if I convinced myself, I've been in it, it could, I didn't even, uh, it wasn't even
like to sit in there in the ride. There was no sign of those vehicles. No. So this is what I didn't,
cause, um, as I think you guys have talked about before, the description of the ride has been
utterly vague. They're just like, you're going to maybe see somebody bad. Like there's nothing
about it. Um, but I didn't realize that it's so the second day of the trip, they told us that it's
essentially four attractions in one, which we were like, go on. Um, and they showed us what we
think is one and a half out of the four. Okay. So there's still mystery as to what the four are.
Yes. Oh, because you, the coverage, the verdict seemed to be you all got to see one third of this
ride. So I, um, yeah, I asked the guy after I was like, so how much did we see? And he's like,
you saw about 30%. Yeah. Really? Just started screaming. And he's like, he looked, the quote
he gave me was like, yeah, it's a monster. People are going to freak out. Yeah. Did you see that
number that was floating around 28 minutes? Yes. They commented on it and said it was inaccurate,
but it is, um, one of the longest attractions they have. Interesting. What is, do we know the
longest attraction? Pirates. So the thing is though, that it's not all sweet, completely upends any,
any idea, like basically what you think is an attraction. This thing will explode because it's
part of it is walking something like something that would generally be a Q situation. Whereas
like you walk, you turn a corner, you walk is part of the attraction. Right. So, so like, yeah,
like two different ride systems bridged by walking that all counts in the time for the attraction.
Basically. Yes. So you're not sitting in a little vehicle for 20 something minutes, but you are
part of it's the attraction or universe of energy. It's probably the,
yeah.
This is kind of like the new universe of energy.
There was a thing I'm always, I read a lot of the message boards for rumors and like two years ago,
there was a rumor that it was a ride you would get to get off in the middle of.
Yes. I mean, so I think it's hard to tell because so the part that I experienced was we walked the
entire queue, which it's big. I'm just going to leave it as that. And you said, I think on the
other Disney, Disney dish, it's like probably as long as the avatar queue. That's what it felt like
to me. But unlike the avatar queue, I don't know if you guys have had the pleasure of really walking
that entire length. It's not, it's not kind of like there's small spaces, then big spaces like
the lab and then small spaces. It's really all themed similarly. So it's all kind of small
corridors through laser knife cut openings.
Oh, yeah. So you're like in this cavernous expanse for TBD amount of time. And then you get into a,
I believe it's like a communications merge room. And then that's kind of where the ride starts.
So you merge like the standby fast pass, and then you see BB eight and raise there. And she's like,
come help us. And then you go out, then you go outside. Right. So like this door opens,
you know, like a star Wars. Is there a technical name for like a fancy star Wars door?
I don't think so. So you go and then you board this
outside. Yeah. Wait, I didn't know this. Yes. Okay. So it's like you're in a merge point.
And then from there you enter the first room. I guess I'll just give you the whole spiel.
Okay. So then BB eight's like, what's up? And then they're in a group of, I think it's like 48 to
55 people. Okay. So imagine like you, once you enter the haunted mansion, you're waiting to go
into the stretching room. Cool. Yeah. Yeah. There's quote unquote stretching room is Ray via
hologram BB eight explaining to you the mission that they need you to go on with the resistance.
So from there a door opens and instead of going down a terrifyingly cramped dark hallway,
you are outside and pose X swing. Is that yep. He has an X wing. Yeah. Okay. I'm scared. There's
like some secret official name for it besides like generic X-Wing. I only know about Rex. So you're
fine with that. I don't know. I live true. I don't know about anything else. You're all set. I just
can't mess up in front of the other two. So that new fun, new Han Solo's there. Uh,
Han Solo, but different is there. Uh, so a couple of questions. Uh, so there are bench,
bench like seating carved into the walls in that queue area. Of the queue.
You're asking a lot of benches. Operational questions. Uh, single rider line. So I could
not confirm. I, I, I listened back to my recordings and it's just me, pathetically asking
multiple men being like, hi, I saw four doorways leading into the merge room. Does that confirm or
deny that there's a single rider? And they're like, you need to walk away. But I did physically see
the single rider sign in the Millennium Falcon opening. So I, so I saw the sign literally
that is happening, but they have not said in this very long, uh, uh, rise at star wars, calling rise
the resistance, right? You didn't see a sign of any bathrooms halfway through the queue. There are
not. Okay. I mean, I definitely asked them and I think it's, um, the type of thing where I don't
know if you guys have seen the way that they load in flight of passage and animal kingdom at Disney
world, but they hold the line and the walkway to Africa. Okay. So they hold the line for the most
part outdoors now, instead of in the actual indoor queue, I think so you can like get out to get
coffee or get out to get a snack and they have little snack truck there so you can get food. So
you don't just like wait hours and hours before eating. So I think it'll probably be something
like that because the ride is separate from the rest of the land. Okay. Yeah. It's down a pathway
to the left. So I think there is room just in that general space to hold an outdoor queue. If you like,
I assume that's what they'll do. But that's just an assumption. Yeah. They were kind of doing that
opening summer of green guts. They had a lot of snack stands in line and like a return system.
If you want to use the bathroom, it was, yeah, worked pretty well. I think it'll be like that,
but I don't think there will be a single rider line because you do move in this massive group.
Sure. Oh, right. Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah. So we're outside.
Fine. Listen, when I saw, I saw the seat, the bench seat in the queue and I pointed it and was
like, what is that? Yeah. It was thrilling. No, that is a need that they give you.
It's not the whole queue. Don't get too excited. It's only a portion. Okay. Sure. So then the door
opens and you're outside on a loading dock. And what we're told is that there'll be sounds of like
ships taking off and a lot of things happening. And then you and your, your crew of a zillion people,
you enter the first quote unquote ride vehicle, which is a ship. I don't know the name of it.
They didn't know the name of it. I think it's just a general transport ship. Right. Sure.
Oh, I, yeah, I don't know. I don't know. I know. I think I know who pilots it though. I think I read.
Yes. Should we all say it? That's the way I say it once. Nine. It's nine. And I realized for years,
I was mispronouncing my name. I thought it was neon, but his real name is nine. And he is,
are you talking about in the Falcon, the smushy face in return of the Jedi. I stopped paying
attention after the Toto song. I don't know. He shows up in force awakens to apparently I thought
he dies in last Jedi. No, only Akbar dies silently. Yeah. I agree. I was telling them
before you got here. I only just a couple of days ago saw solo for the first time. So before all
this dads, all this star stuff was coming out, I was like, I, this is getting me interested because
after solo my star was interested is at an all time low. Do not enjoy that movie. I am
enjoying all of this. All this stuff that's come out about the land though. So yeah,
the land is the best movie already. I have a number one. Yeah. It's for sure the best movie.
There's no way. So yeah. So, so you're in there with an interesting thing is that I,
as far as I can remember, they said during this, this ship, they said there's two pilots.
I feel like they said, oh no, no, they said there's two animatronics up there.
The only one they named is nine and no, nine and no, so they are not ready to reveal
the other animatronic or it's like a small nothing. That's not even worth thinking.
Like it's the back of someone's head that you don't even see. Yeah. So not sure. But I know that
Finn, yeah. Finn patches in, no, Pope patches in while you're on the ride because he's your escort.
He's no, he's like, he's coming with you, but he's on his own ship. Right. Yeah. So he, I know that
he then like, you know, there's something happens as something always does and then they fight.
And then I know that Poe leaves. Yeah. He escapes and then you get sucked into a star destroyer.
Right. Are you looking up nine numb? Yeah, I do know nine numb. You see, you know,
it's like if you put a pancake on your face, he's like, he's a little mole guy. All right.
Yeah. So you're in this, this ship and the thing moves, which I'm really curious about because it
moves, but you're not, you're not holding onto anything. You're not seated. You're just standing.
Oh, that's interesting. Yeah. Which is a ride system that I don't think they've used before,
unless you've been on the Armageddon attraction at Walt Disney Studios in Paris. Yeah. The world's
worst ride. Yeah. My wife glared at me. Like the, maybe the low point of our honeymoon was like,
why did you make me go? Oh, that is the first attraction I went on when I got to the park
and my husband's like, we're going home. We both lost our spouses essentially. Wow. It's a marriage
ruining ride. Wait, wait, how is it? But that's like a thing you like sit on that or you're like,
it shakes. It's like, it's not dissimilar to like the parts of back draft and twister ride it out,
have little like plat for your standing, but it shakes around. Yes. Okay. There's a void.
When we did the void, you are in a transport ship and you're standing and you feel the room.
Oh, right. Yeah. Is that at the end or is that the one where you're over all the fire?
Early on. Oh, it's, it's what's taking you down into the law of the world. But this,
it does like physically move through space a bit and it moves like by itself. Oh, okay. Okay.
There's an effect on journey to the center of the earth in Tokyo that feels like that. It's,
yeah, Scott's going. He doesn't want spoilers. Let's know. We made it this far.
All right. I guess I can't say. Do you know nothing about the attraction? I don't. This is
my first chance to have a couple rides where I don't. Yeah. Thank you. Thank you. He left.
So we did an episode. He left in the middle of it when we were reviewing it. Yeah. I don't know
what happened in that episode. I'm excited to check it out. We'll give a spoiler warning for the whole
thing before this too, because these are some spoilers. Yeah. No kidding. Yeah. Well, I'm going
to tell you as much as I know. Of course. Sure. Yeah. All right. So this platform. You didn't go
in the ship. You just. No, I went in the ship. Oh, you did. Okay. Yeah. It just wasn't zooming
around. Yeah. I mean, the experience I'd relate it to is probably a stretching room in that sense.
Then, you know, you're with a group of people, you cram in, there's stuff happening in the room. It's
moving, but who knows how much I mean, moving at least on this coast, but yeah. So, and then you
get off, it's like something happens. Then you get sucked in and the door. So you basically, you board
and you're looking at outside, looking at the landing deck. You're looking at post stuff. The
door closes. Then the other door opens later on and you're inside the star destroyer. Oh,
it's so amazing. It's like a big reveal of what they called one of many reveals. Okay. It's a
massive room. I cannot, I cannot underst like it. This is the biggest room. Like I walked in and
was like, how do you have space for this? How is there a ride after this? This is the biggest room
I've ever been in my life. Yeah. It's a hundred foot screen, which is very big. Yeah. And it's
just, it is all consuming. Yeah. I mean, yeah. I, I'm now getting very excited. I've been excited
the whole time, but I mean, my recs, heart swelling, I've had like physical palpitations.
I'm nervous in this. I'm like, I've, I don't know. I like my, my body is experiencing weird,
weird feelings. Right. Yeah. I get the vibe that everyone who works on this attraction is like,
oh, you guys think the Falcon's going to be good. And they're like, just wait for it. Okay. Okay.
All right. So the, when you're on it, obviously everything's not worth it. They don't have all
the sound effects. So when it opens, I'm assuming there would be music. Did you get a full soundtrack
thing? No, no, no. I mean, okay. To set the scene, I am walking through a dusty construction zone
with like full cranes, like potholes. I'm wearing a pair of men's boots loan to me, safety goggles,
a helmet and a vest. Sure. So I'm like just like flopping around and it's, everyone's just working
on the attraction. So they're just walking us through and being like, here is room scribbled
down as many notes as you can before we move on. Right. So, so you were, we'll open it up and
there'll be like a big score and lights and you open it up and there were like 50 men in hard hats.
Yeah. It was just people being like, why are you in my workspace? Right. But there will be,
they say 50 AA or no, not 50 stormtroopers, some of which are AA's. So some of them will be
animated and kind of like scare you. Oh, some of them wouldn't be humans. Well, no, I think some
of them are just statues. I see. But if there's enough, you wouldn't necessarily notice that the
one in the back is just static. Yeah. And then I think there's the cast members who are just as
first order officers are yelling at you or escorting you into a hallway to go to a detention cell.
Oh God. Fantastic. Scary. And did you go in the detention cell? And is that where your tour kind
of stopped? Like that's it. Yeah. And that's where they said will be the first time we see Kylo Ren
and it'll be, he'll be up top as he like came in on a balcony and you're just locked in a detention
cell. You have to figure out how to get out. Is that an animatronic or is it? That's what I asked.
They wouldn't confirm. They said it's one of the many forms you will see him in. So I think there
got to be an animatronic of him, but I don't know if that's the one. Wow. I've never been so scared
in an episode. I'm so freaked out. I'm scared for you having been there. It seems like it might have
been like a, was it all sort of like a freaky place to see, especially in its weird nascent form?
I think the weirdest part is that it's like seeing a 90 minute movie and then being like,
you need to absorb every single thing you're viewing because you're going to need to talk
about it for the next three months and just being like, I can't remember. Yeah. Yeah.
Cause you know, you can't take any photos, but it, it, it looks like it looks exactly like the
movies. Like it feels like, I think what you're saying, and maybe I'm wrong is that I think,
you know, certain theme park fans like us might have like a lot of dream literal dreams and
nightmares involving theme parks. And I do think I've had dreams where like I'm walking through an
attraction and it's like half built and the lights are on. Like it does seem creepy what
you're describing in a way too. And maybe that's just my own. Is that what you're thinking?
Well, I mean a little bit that, but more just, this sounds like a scary ride. Like the first
time we all do this, not knowing what's coming. Cause you don't even know to take it all the way.
You don't, you've done some of this. You don't know what happens at the end of this ride. It
doesn't seem like, okay, okay. Oof boy. So it's going to be scary, but I'm thinking of it in the
half as much as I, if they invited me to go to this, I would of course do it. But part of me
thinks like, cause we've all had nightmare. Like we've all thought about how scary it would be like
the post-apocalyptic theme park. That's like by half built and there's like people working in,
like it just seems like that to me. I'm someone who can't look at the thing Banksy did.
That like makes me actually ill. No, this is just more like, like, Ooh, like they're making a cake.
Sure. That's a good way to think of it. It does sound like they're getting people out of their
comfort zone in terms of expectations for theme park. I think it's, there never has been an
attraction like this. I think that any, any way you view a ride will be upended by what you go on.
Sure. That's what a lofty statement. Holy shit. Well, I mean, when else are you, is the part of
the attraction like walking into a ship and then walking off a vehicle and then walking to something
else? Yeah. And with the haunted mansion is an analog that that's the way more way beyond that
certainly. But like I, what a cool, what a type of move Disney's really only done once or maybe
twice. Like it's very, it's really different. Yeah. And it does like it definitely like, this is
sounding like what they're talking about with the hotel and with every, like this feels very much
more like there's a full narrative and you are really in it. Whereas most rides it's a very,
you're still, even though you're in the car and you're supposed to be going through the thing,
it's a much more passive kind of experience. You're much more of a specter. This really feels like,
yeah, both of them are right. Yeah. Literally on the other one. Is there more, is there more to say
about rise of the resistance or should we move on to? So I mean, that's kind of where we, where
we were ushered out and kind of thrown back to the rest of the land, but it is very interesting that
kind of their top level viewpoint of galaxy's edge is that they want you to feel like you're,
you're in your own star Wars story, which is the exact PR messaging. But like the way they set up
the ride is that it's cinematic. So you feel like you're in a scene, like you feel like you're in
scenes in the movie throughout. And I think a lot of that is the scale. Like the, the art we've all
seen is that you're in that little vehicle and like the ad-hats are like very tall and you're very
small under them. And I think a lot of that will be feeling like you're in scenes and like things
are scary and large and intense. Yeah. I do think that will the size of the AT-ATs will scare me.
Yeah. I think I feel it's big things in a small room. Scott has a fear of big things in a small
room. Is there anything in a ride specifically that, you know, thankfully I don't get it in rides a
lot, but I get it from just 16 bit super Mario worlds where if you're in a small space with that
big ghost, big boo, big boo. It's all fake and like the most like many generations ago graphics,
but the idea of you open a door and then a ghost that big. Yeah. I can tell you're like really
working through some stuff with this ride. You're like how scared should they be? Yeah,
I know. You've kind of gotten me to this vulnerable place in general. There's a, I think, yeah, well,
I think the level of detail extending to of like your, your eyesight of like your eyes almost as
the camera of like all the coverage years included talking about walking into the land and like
everything slowly revealing itself. Yeah. Yeah. Like, um, yeah. What do you know about like when,
when a guest just enters galaxy's edge, what's the deal? So we, the one thing we didn't do is
actually physically enter through either, either the three entrances. Those are walled up, I guess.
And then the entrance that's by like back by critter country where you'll enter through the
resistance forest is that area. So that you don't really get as, as much of the whole like,
cause the whole area that unfolds is black spiral outpost, which is the main section.
So that's the frontier land and the fantasy land entrances at Disneyland TBD at Disney worlds,
because we don't really know the orientation.
You'll pass to pizza riso, I think. God bless pizza riso.
The pizza is garbage, but it is run by a rat. All right. That seems like in the middle.
I love the theming. Okay. Okay. All right. All right. That's a notch in Doug's belt.
Well, do you guys know about the, the, what happens to the sign at night? No. So at night they have
this big neon sign outside. It says like pizza riso and there's some slogan under and like about
every 15 seconds, the lights flicker and some of the letters blackout. And then it says it's rat pizza.
Brilliant. This is the most embattled thing in a theme park. People have been hard one way,
hard the other. That's an interesting, I mean, I'm not liking the food I can get,
but not liking the theming. What's wrong with you? Wow. Well, the guests have said that I
feel like you were not, but you missed some stuff. I missed the upstairs room, which was the,
like the disco room, which I, it sounds really great, but as far as just like kind of walking
in and out, you really have to look hard for a lot of the detail. Cause like when you think
Muppet restaurant, I think my, my expectations were pretty high. Yes. So it's just sort of like,
well, there's a sign that has a reference to the Muppets, which is nice, but I was thinking,
I was hoping like there'd be a rat with a chef's hat on. Oh yeah. I would love a Muppet character
dining. I think that's my dying wish. Yeah. So I think that's really where it's coming from,
but yeah, I had a, there's a feud with friend of the show, Doug Jones, who started texting me
angrily from Orlando that pizza risotto was good. And then apparently I, I told the story of him
texting me on the show and he said that I trashed him and then we hashed it out on another episode.
So there's a whole long, and then when I go back to Orlando, I will reassess pizza risotto.
I'm not trying to be just a hater, but we can't, we can't, we're getting too much.
We're talking about that. I'm still stuck on the fact that you will transition from, I love that.
I love that a lot. I'm stuck. I'm hung up on the fact that you will transition from critter country
into resistance forest. That is what crazy neighbors. Yes. But it, I think it'll work.
Yeah, I think so too. Cause I was on the Mark Twain the other day and I was like, oh, the rock
work. Yeah. No, yeah, I'm always on the Mark Twain. But the eyes, the, the eyelines, the rock work
around the train tracks and the rock work slash petrified trees of black fire outposts did look
right together. There is one opening of trees where you can see a clearly star wars turret.
So hopefully they'll put some more trees right there. They just started putting in trees. Oh,
okay. Cause I was asking them very specific tree questions and they're like, uh, I have no idea.
Can you tell me the name of this tree? And they were like, I worked on the ride. Like, no.
So they're putting, cause also when you, um, so when you're on, I guess rise, I guess that's what
we'll call it. Sure. When in that area where you go outside to get on the cargo ship thing,
currently you can see the whole land from there, but they will be filling it with trees so that
nobody from outside in the land can see that portion of the attraction. So there's a lot of
landscaping to be, cause that'd be like the, the allies and the access were like looking right at
each other. Cause the resistance is set up in the woods. The first order is set up in black fire.
I'm Sarah Palin seeing Russia Russia from Falcon. We talk. Okay. So, um, I guess to go back to the
entrances. So it's the thing that I can, we've compared it to this on Len and Jim's podcast,
but it's like coming under the railroad when you enter magic kingdom or Disneyland, where you
enter, where you can't see anything from the gate and you get like a little more and then they
shrink you down and then they expand it back open. And that's what it's like. But once you enter,
you can't see the Falcon. You have to go kind of into black square outpost in the middle of the
town. And then it appears. What do you see in first? You see kind of the buildings, the different
structures, depending on which one you walk in. If you walk in fantasy land, there will be, um,
a first order ship on your right. Yes. Or left your right. Cause that's like the first order side.
Basically is the entrance through fantasy land. And then if you enter through frontier land,
you'll be kind of in the center. And then there's, if you look at the model or photos of that,
there's that stairway. There's like a little stairway and then a walkway and you can go up
that. And then it would be Falcon time. Okay. Okay. Falcon time. Well, if it's Falcon time,
uh, what can you tell us about that? You've been inside, you've been, you've been in a cabin. Yes.
I've pushed all the buttons. I've pulled the levers. Wow. There's a lot of them. I guess.
There's so many buttons. Do they really all, and they all do something. Do you have to?
That's the thing is that I, you guys have been on mission space, I assume. Yeah. Yes. Where it's
like push the, and then if you don't push it, it's just like, it doesn't override and it does it.
And I can't really get an answer on if that will something like that will happen or not. Yeah. But
there are a lot of buttons and I don't know how many will be lit for you to push it once, but it,
I mean, it feels like the real thing. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Like even the chairs, I was looking at
photos, like the chairs look exactly the same. And I, from the description, I forget which
article said that it was a religious experience being in the Falcon, but one of them did.
And I think I was like, they were like, yeah, everything feels like it's not a chintzy
like little button. It's like, these are like, it feels like a real machinery. Yeah. It's not pretend.
Right. But I guess we should, so we should talk about the fact that, so you wait in the queue to
get in there and the queue is two levels and it takes you past the whole outside of the ship.
So you get to see the ship from the level of the top of the ship, which is very cool,
which is not an angle. I thought that would be worthwhile, but it's like to your left and
it's just there and it's very neat. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Cool. This is cause you are loading into
the Bay of, I believe it's Onaka transport solutions. Don't quote me on that. That is,
no, that you can quote them. Is that right? Yes. Got it. So Hondo Onaka, a character only seen in
the cartoons has started a transport company and she has loaned him the Falcon. I love
bureaucratic solutions to ride. Probably love like fake companies and rides and stuff. Yeah.
They like plot this character from cartoons and made him the second most advanced audio animatronic
they've ever built. Yeah. Shaman. Yeah. Shaman of song, but also not from a film. It's weird that
the two most original. Yeah. Kind of neat. Which I have two, one that it's always easier to make
an alien creature look more realistic than try to get into uncanny Valley territory. That must be
why. The other thing is, and this is probably too cynical of me, but I'm like, if that was a chewy
animatronic, everyone will want to stand and watch it. But if it's a character they care less about,
they'll be impressed and move on. Maybe. Maybe that's my personal theory. The great Jim
Cummings doing the voice. Yeah. He does it in the cartoon in star wars rebels. Yeah. Yeah. He,
I mean, what do you know him? He's, I mean, he's always dark winged dog. Of course I weirdly go,
but he's been winning the poo for a long time. I weirdly go back to Pete as much as Pete is not a
major. I just, when I hear, when I hear his voice, especially being, being mean and gruff, I think of
the big fat cat Pete from goof troop and goofy movie. This is going to sound stupid, but I didn't
realize Pete wasn't a dog until about three weeks ago. Whoa. What is he? Pizza cat. Oh,
that's why he's after Mickey and steamboat Willie. Okay. Anyway, that's fine. With everyone. I mean,
they're very complex creatures, cats. So, uh, yeah, but I think how do I mean, he looks great. Like
the, what they believe in action. He was good. He kind of like swirls on his base. He swirls like
back and forth, but he has full hand motion. They like went into a lot of detail about how
they like specifically did everything to make him look real, but also to fit in extra.
I mean, read Matt's story. He knows all the, yeah, it's like electric transistors in the heads.
Yes. It's easier to make fluid movements then, and you don't have to have hydraulic lines running
into the animatronics. So like you have more space for other components. I only kind of understand.
We have a lot of panels on those type of details and I was like, TNL really doesn't cover the
science of your audience. Yeah. You saw that in imagineering. Yes. Right. I think we saw him in
the ride also, but I can't remember if he was animated or not at the time. Oh, so there was
probably an animatronic. So the animatronics we saw at WDI were the ones that are being shipped
to Florida. Oh, okay. So it's, you know, it's the exact same one, but just those are being finalized
to be shipped. Oh, cause they don't need them there yet. Cause that one's a few months like
further on the schedule of this one. Wow. When you're in imagineering, do you like
look over and like is Bell's animatronic from the Japan, uh, you saw that? Oh, yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Cause I was sort of thinking it would be like, well, they only let you see this one thing
in the specific place for star wars. They do tend to like push some things away. Like there's this
one hallway that's sort of a conference room at WDI that every event like this is held in.
And then next to conference room is a workshop where they work on a lot of stuff that is usually
newsworthy. And I found it very interesting that this time when I had to go to the bathroom, I took
the long way. Oh, wow. Like we will assure you to take three right turns so that you don't take a
left. Oh, interesting. So they definitely hid that from us this trip, but, um, no, like, uh,
we saw the beast and we saw bell, but what were, I think there were two A's. Yeah. We saw them
working on it. There's that. I saw that in that video was the horse bell. Oh, I don't think I saw
that. I mean, it was a little like, I was trying so hard to write stuff down and I didn't pay
attention, but it was there. They're working on it. Was there any Spiderman anywhere? No. Oh,
no, no, no. They, we did see the thing that actually Matthew covered at tech crunch.
The, I forget the name of it. The, um, the AA that they fling in the air. Oh, yes. Yes. I
forget the name of that project. Yeah. It's a stunt. Yeah. The robot stunt. Yes. Whatever
the specific name of that is, we saw where that was filmed. Oh, it's like right behind the animation
building. Right. Yeah. Wow. Really? Yeah. Awesome. But yeah, we did see that.
She's building and out. You're seeing Florida, Honda, Honda and Florida. Rex.
Oh, and Honda also has a Droid with him, but I don't know if it's, I don't know what Droid.
Right. Okay. I don't know. I don't know who Honda's Droid is, if that exists.
Anyway, you gotta learn about, we all have to immediately love Honda.
I love him already. And I love his Droid, but I don't know what it looks like or what his name is.
It'll be a good time. So you're in that room with him and TBD Droid, and then you go down
a hallway, et cetera, et cetera. And then you are in what I believe is called the guest quarters
of the Millennium Falcon, the main area with like the holo chest thing. Yeah. And they change the
way that they queue the rides that you get to hang out in there. How many of those do you think
there are? There's one. There's just one of those. How many cockpits of the Millennium Falcon are
there? So, okay. I've asked some follow-up questions and they kind of were like, whatever are you
talking about? But the way they designed it so that it feels like there's six people that load
onto one and it feels like you're the only person that's in it. Sure. But I'm very curious to know
the mechanism by which that works. There might be multiple Millennium Falcon ones. I don't know.
The thing is they took us down very specific hallways. So I don't know if there were other
hallways or if it was the only hallway, but regardless, everyone will feel like they're the
only person who's piloting or gunning or engineering the ship. Right. It's a very neat trick and a
much different from like say the Back to the Future or Simpsons ride where you can see
all of the doors. All of them pulling at once. Chewy, we're home. Chewy, we're home. Chewy,
we're just down the line. That's what the cast members will say when they take your picture with
your eye. All right. Everyone say Chewy, we're home. Well, actually, I don't know if there are
multiple because it must hold like 60 people. Okay. You mean multiple areas before the cockpit.
Guest quarters of the Millennium Falcon. That's a good question. Because you hang out in there for
a bit. So I don't know if it's just like a queue where they would just hold the next 60 in line in
one place. Yeah. We're in general finding ways to have areas that are you're still in line and
you're still waiting. This is going to sound like a stupid comparison, but it's almost it seems like
what they've started to do over at the Race Through New York attraction. That's exactly what I compare
it to. Okay. Okay. Huh? Interesting. Because it is the type of thing where you wait until
your group is called. Okay. Well, that's cool. That's a better way to give you this stuff up.
I mean, I don't know if they'll have like tabletop games. Why is the holo chest?
Well, yeah. But if there's only one of those tables, that's going to be a fight. Yeah.
People will die. Yeah. What else on Falcon? You went inside, you touched buttons. Any
weird factoids about that? No, I mean, the screens weren't up and running. So it was just kind of,
we only got to experience sitting there. But I mean, I don't know how operationally they're
going to decide who gets to sit in the first two seats. Yeah. I know I would murder someone
to be able to sit there. Yeah. That's, that feels like a big problem coming, right? Cause like,
who, it's like, doesn't come down for their like, especially for less weird people, like unlike us,
who we're going to go a lot or try to go a lot of people for their one vacation and they want to
sit in that front seat. So here's what's interesting is that I know that there's
not a lot of information out about how play Disney parks factors in or how your reputation
follows you throughout the land. That whole thing that none of us have any clear details on.
I think that I don't know if it's part of that, that you have to do different positions that that,
cause I know it's like a group score. I don't know if sitting not in the front two seats is
beneficial for you. Who knows? Interesting. But I mean, in every Disney ride, you can always request
where you want to sit. Right. Yeah. And I can't see it being different for this, but they're going
to need like a two hour line for all the people that request. Maybe they have that. Maybe they
have it. Cause I always request where to sit on flight of passage. Oh, what is the secret for that?
What is the, I think it's seat eight. Cause you know, it's two rows of, it's 16 seats. I believe
first date and then second eight. No, I request seat nine because it, it, that means you're in the
middle of the screen. I wrote a whole story about this once. And then I request like what level is,
yeah, I like to be in the middle one, but it really doesn't make as big of a difference as long as
you're in the middle of your interesting 16 seat thing. A question about both rides that I'm not
sure I saw gift shops after exit. We were not, we were not taken through, but there are, who knows?
I don't know because they did. So they, all of the stores they referenced, there's like a resistance
posts where you can buy a resistance gear and then there's like a first order or something.
We were first order stuff and those aren't at the ride exits. Right. So maybe not. Maybe not.
You're going to have plenty of ways to spend your money. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You have doc,
owned ours den of antiquities shop. Yes. You do have doc, hundreds of antiquities,
which I forget what I tried to say his name earlier. Oh, what? Uh, the other episode we were
recording later, but yeah, you Jason called them like doc on or don't go. Yeah. I think it was
confusing him and Hondo Onaka. Uh, how could you? So now he is the animat, he's the animatronic,
right? He's like the gruff shop owner, but he's a big animatronic and, but you do not actually
haggle with him. That's been, that's the rumor, but it seems like it's kind of been debunked
because that's, that would be where I would be immediately. I think it's not imperative to the
checkout process, but I think that the cast member in the store haggles with him. I did clarify,
which I thought was maybe the smartest question I've ever asked is does he speak English? And
the answer was no. Whoa. Which means that I think that you never get to converse with him. Sure.
Cause he doesn't speak English. I believe they call that standard. The language is called standard
in star wars language is what English is called. Oh, okay. I didn't know that.
So like depending on what the line is like, the human performer could like decide how much business
they'll have with the robot and the customer. Maybe. Well, also the other thing is that I think a lot,
I think this is like a high end store. So I think maybe if you're buying like a fancy collectible,
then the interaction would happen. Is this the store that sells, I saw a picture, there were
gold busts of Jedis, including Yoda, Mace, window, and my favorite Jedi council member, Plo Koon.
Is this that place probably? So, yes, I think they also said a lot of Sith related goods.
Why would it in the same store? I'm pretty sure that's where those are being sold.
Interesting. So this is like not the jewels of Biff. I cannot confirm or deny where the jewels
of Biff will be. So Galactic Basic is what English is called. Oh, that is such a good insult.
Yeah. Standard. And then our Bush is the language is sort of the sea on a lot of stuff. Yeah,
which will be throughout the land. I know that, but I'm definitely going to call somebody a
Galactic Basic if they're being annoying in star wars land. You're going to be calling 200,000
people that phrase. So they, did they tell you like, this is more of an upscale store? Like
it feels like this. And then the lightsaber thing also is upscale, at least price-wise.
No, because I fact-checked that and it, I'm still, I sent a follow-up email. I'm still trying to
find out, but I know that one publication ran with pricing, which was, I believe like, I want to say
like a hundred dollars for a hilt and then like $49 for a blade. So it put the price of a lightsaber
around 160. But from what I understand, that's not the main one at the shop that you would make.
Oh, okay. So that's maybe a special one. So they said this thing called a legacy lightsaber. This
is so detailed. I'm very sorry. No, no, that's what we want. So in one meeting they said
legacy lightsaber, which was like a fancy lightsaber of a character. So like a Kylo Ren
lightsaber. And then when we toured Doc Ondar's, they said like, this is where those legacy
lightsabers we sold under glass and under glass means expensive. Right. Yeah. But I can't get a
final word on if that 160 is for the legacy lightsabers or for something else. Interesting
because there's a lightsaber show at the like salvage or place where you design one. Yeah.
In experience. Yes. In experience. What are the sabers? How are they doing the sabers?
Okay. So when you go to Savi, wait a minute, Savi's lightsabers. I know there's a dash in there.
I'm seeing Savi's workshop. So I know that that, I mean, if you had to relate it to something,
it would be going to Wizarding World and getting like the show with the wand, except that this is
more handmade. I know that you have a say in what Kyber crystal and what kind of basic saber you
want, but there's a lot of show elements they didn't tell us about, but I know it is a show
attractiony experience. Wow. That's also merchandise. But then when you get it, what is it?
It's like two pieces, right? Like it doesn't extend. It's a good, it's not like a cheapy.
No, it is not cheap. I was like, Oh, it's heavy. Like pretty significant. Sure. And then it, you
know, when you push the on button, like it makes the noise, it lights up, whatever color crystal
you have. And the crystals are interchangeable with a Holocron. Holocron. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Wow.
And they're going to sell like a whole, like a sling for you to carry this around the land.
So you're not just carrying a weapon, whacking people. Okay. Very interesting. You bring this
up because I did mention that and they were like, it's no different from the sabers we sell in the
park. So we don't foresee any issues. So I know that operationally they're already on top of that.
But when I interviewed Scott, he did mention that they, there will be a sling because I,
I was like, Oh, so I'm just going to be carrying like a bag of a drawing, like should be care,
all this stuff. And he's like, yeah, interesting. Take a giant pole on a 20 minute ride.
That's the thing is that you can't, I don't think you can bring it on the ride. Yes.
I don't know if they hold it for the end of the day after you make it. I don't know if you,
they send it back to your hotel. The process is a little, um, yeah, yeah, they got to work something
out there. It seems like they know what they're doing, but they haven't told me. Right. Uh, uh,
colors. How many colors do we know? Purple, red, green, green and blue. Okay. I was wondering
five different, or no, four, four or five different like genres. One's like power and light. And one
is like evil. Sure. Uh, okay. Uh, my story comes out this week by the way. I don't remember.
Okay. I was just wondering if there would be like a rainbow lightsaber, which is what I would watch.
Maybe for gay days. That'd be cool. Oh my God. That would be my choice of color for it. Either
a purple, I guess, like mace windows or rainbow as a kid. Those were my two favorite colors.
Yeah. Uh, so we'll get back to the droid depot. Let's, let's talk a little toy,
dairy and toy shop or whatever it is. A toy shop or toy fair. There we go. Is that in the
marketplace? Yes. Okay. So everything we've just discussed is okay. Black Spire outpost is part
sook. You know, like probably an old timey marketplace with stalls. And then there are
individual standalone shops and buildings. So everything doc on DARS, Savi's workshop,
Droid Depot, all that stuff, like the, the dining, the Cantina, that's a buildings. And then
Ronto roasters is the entrance to this marketplace that leads you towards resistance forest. Yeah.
And Ronto roasters is like meat stuff, including a space hot dog in a pita.
And that is the official space hot dog. Yeah. It is a, I believe a Portuguese hot dog inside of a
pita with slices of pork topped with a slaw and a clutch sauce, which has says one peppercorn in it.
I just want to say this whole episode has been frigging clutch sauce.
So yeah. So what is it? What is a Portuguese hot dog? What is the difference?
It's kind of spicier Portuguese sauce. I didn't, I found it to taste much like a generic American
hot dog. But perfect. They said it, but I was told it was Portuguese. I didn't find the hot
dog to have any spice in it. It was mostly the clutch sauce. I will be filling a droid backpack
with them to wait, to wait in line for rise of the resistance. It'll probably get me to at least the
whole thing. So I start bartering with first water troops. You don't even go on the ride
because you just exchange hot dogs for your escape. I am making my own Disney play app,
which is all hot dog bartering based. So yeah. So a toy, a toy dairy toy maker is one of the stalls
in this marketplace. So we only went in one of the stalls. We went in the creature stall, which is
small. I mean, this isn't like, this is not a shop. This is just a little, a nook. I mean, like a,
like a shop size nook inside of the marketplace, but it's fully, Oh my God, it's fully propped out.
So I think it's going to be a very, very themed smaller environment. Having seen the creature one,
I assume it's going to be a lot of like references to characters via toys, like soft plushes,
little squeezy things. Is there any sort of, cause a toy Darien, for those of you who don't know,
is the Wado's alien race. Is there a Wado around? We have asked that and we have not gotten the
straight answer. But I know there is like a few toy Darien toys. I saw a picture of a toy Darien
toy, but I would like a robot Wado to be flying around in there. But the plush Wado is really
cute. It's going to be strange if they're big, this black eye, like the button eyes that I look
the plushes are really cute. But like, give me some real life aliens selling me some merch.
Yeah. So that's what I saw. I, that's my biggest question I think for the land right now, not the
rest of the 70% of the ride, but will I get to talk to a toy Darien?
So the way that it's been conveyed to me is that there is an opening day plan and then there was
a further rollout from there. Oh, interesting. So I don't, I cannot tell if that means that
the answer is yes, but not yet. Cause I forget if you were talking about this on Disney dish, but
because at first they were talking about droids roaming the land sort of autonomous,
autonomous, but every piece of artwork, but there's no way for the first so many months
that's possible, right? Cause there'd be too many people and kids pushing them over.
And I think it depends on what the actual ops are once it opens. But I, I mean, from what I've
been told that is intended to be part of the land. I don't think they've been like, let's just
forget it. But also like, I want to see a droid, but I mean, there's going to be stationary things
like outside of Droid Depot, there's going to be a lineup of droids like in the fourth movie where
like, you know, they beep boop at you and stuff. It's funny. You said earlier, like, you know,
stuff Disney saying publicly and press releases and stuff, like they're very careful because it
like, Oh, then that becomes rule of law, word of law, whatever. But in the early stuff they have,
there was going to be like a table service dinner club. And that is seems to be off the table now.
Um, yeah. And they did not publicly mention that it was not happening until we were like,
is this the only dining option? Because you definitely mentioned a very dope supper club.
Yeah. And no, um, I can't tell if there's room for that on the backside, like past the cantina
and they just haven't, that's maybe a phase two thing, but that is definitely not happening
right now. Cause Ronto Roasters is like quick service meant to be kind of more like a kiosk.
Yeah. More like a kiosk. There's the popcorn at that's got a Cotzakas kettle. Yes. Cotzakas kettle.
Docking Bay seven is the big quick service table, like sitting down at a table,
quick service restaurant. Yeah. Interesting. Uh, like it does feel like with that restaurant,
it's like, I'm sure they would make a ton of money. So I wonder what the reasoning
for getting into that is. I mean, this is me just speculating. I have to assume it was just
something that they could be like, we don't have time. Let's do this later. Um, but I mean,
that would be a huge upsell. Yeah. That's what I mean. I would be, I would not be surprised if they
announced that in like two years. Right. Yeah. What's, um, okay. So I have some of these food
items in front of me and we're like the, you know, if I refer to the, no, not literally, but, uh,
you know, what is this? Correct me. Put me in the right place. Uh, but where, which, where's
the place where I get the, uh, smoked cadu ribs? That is a docking bay seven food and cargo.
Okay. Great. Which are ribs served with blueberry cord bread. Yes. Well, here's what's interesting
is that they sliced the ribs in half the other way instead of going down the line, they slice it
and then in half the other direction. So they have a kind of like alien shape to them, which I guess
is, um, like a butcher cut that they had to specifically order and get.
Which is pretty cool. They reimagined cutting meat. Oh, and then the, um, what is the chicken called?
The, the fried endorian tip. Yes. That is also, they said that they sourced in all white breast
meat that comes naturally compressed in a rectangular cubic shape that they then, um, they coat in a,
house made, this is how much work I've done, a house made flour breading. And then they deep fry
it. Yeah. So it's this like, like unique alien chicken nugget. Uh, I, it's, I cannot wait to watch
heat stroke dads go like, all right, I need three, uh, fried yip tips. A couple of the
can candy, where it can be a job. Shrimp noodle salad. Yeah. Uh, uh, just trying to,
it's not the pollution garden spread or not blue milk or green. I don't know. Just a milk. There's
two milks. Oh boy. Milk in the milk. What are you talking about? Milk in the milk. There is no milk
in the milk. Yeah. Yeah. That is no milk in the milk. Yeah. Yeah. Did you get to try the alcoholic
drinks? We tried one. Okay. Um, the food and beverage program I would say is, you know, it's,
it's a bit alien in look and in style, but it's not drastically different from a Disney bar. I
think that it's, um, it still feels very Disney in terms of the beverage program. It feel all of it
feels like familiar things presented in a unique way. Like it's not flavors that conflict. It's
like, Oh, it's ribs and cornbread, but maybe you don't have blueberries and every kind of cornbread
you eat, but it's like a complimentary side dish. I mean, they, I think what they've done is they've
snuck some flavors in that the general audience will be shocked by because that blueberry cornbread
has a little cayenne in it. Oh, that's really fun. So it's kind of stuff where like they've,
they've taken these spices from around the world and like shove them into these foods that look a
little alien, but are a little normal and to make kind of please everyone. And I think they did a
good job of that. And a lot of vegetarian and vegan friendly stuff, which is future rate, like
gets more and more future. All the time. I thought I was going to be eating like a ham hock. I don't
know if there's meaning a ton of meat and the last, no, we're going to eat rath char or, um, uh,
the thing that almost ate Luke and Jedi. Oh, um, not a taunt. A tauntaun is what he rides.
That's possible. And that, that plush tauntaun very cute. Oh my God. And when you pet it,
like not squeeze it. When you pet it, it goes like, Oh, it makes a little noise. Okay. All
the creatures in the creature stall are like these future pets where it's, I mean, the poor,
the party is very fun, but it's a puppet. So you have to put your hand in it. But the other stuff,
like, um, the rath stars, the thing with the teeth, they have one of those that's plastic.
It's not as soft, but when you activate it, it just like freaks out and shakes and jumps around.
Wow. That's wild. What drink did you have? I want to say a tatami and sunset. That's probably
inaccurate. Did you have the milks? No, we did not have the milks. I know. I want to have those
milks real bad. I was mad when they did like the, um, whatever they called it in 2015, when they,
they did hyperspace mountain and they did all this star Wars food. I think they actually did
themselves a favor by setting the bar so low on this, that stuff. Then this stuff seems extra
impressive now. Yeah. I mean, it's going to be served at the milk stand frozen, like a smoothie.
So, um, it sounds much more appetizing than a lukewarm glass of milk. Yeah. Jason's going to be
disappointed though. I think he was looking forward to a lukewarm glass of milk. Well,
in, in Ogas, it's milk milk. Someone has close read some articles. I have read an obscene amount
of articles. It is served chilled at Ogas Candida with a rice crispy cookie on top. Oh, really? Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, now I'm into this milk with a little like bantha horn fondant thing.
Wow. Well, let me move things to, to what perks me up beer and wine. Yeah. Cause there obviously,
yes. Not only Rex is playing synth music in the place where Rex is playing synth music. It's also
the place you can get alcohol. I was, I was starting to wonder, well, is it all star Warsy
drinks, which all sound like fun, but also like, you know, I read the fuzzy tauntaun. It's like a
fuzzy navel. I don't think I'm drinking a fuzzy navel probably. Uh, there's a rum punch and a
bloody Mary. I would, I don't like bloody Mary's, uh, bloody rancor, which comes with a meringue
bone you can put in your mouth. What? It's very, okay. So there's, I don't know how much time you
guys spend at Disney world, but there's this place, Amorettes Patisserie in Disney Springs,
which is like Dean and DeLuca pastries. It's so fancy and it's so beautiful and nice.
You buy like a petite cake and you eat it, maybe share it with people or eat it alone. If you're
me, but it's so good. And that dude made the meringue bone. Wow. And he also made the desserts
at docking Bay seven, which were very good. Right. Yes. One was an orb. And then one was this like,
I want to say it's buttermilk, but it was like this crusted green thing that I,
I think it was maybe Jim or Len who mentioned like, or no, no, it was my, it was my editor
eater was like, is this supposed to be a reference to that bread that Ray makes? Like that portion
that kind of grows very fast. And I think it might be because they haven't told us the name
of it yet. Interesting. So it's this green thing and then you burst it like burst open with like
purple colored raspberry filling. So good. It's like high end pastry. Good. She is in a more
reputable Baker made a meringue bone just for a type of Bloody Mary. They have the level of
detail they're going to get that bone for the Bloody Mary, which you're only going to drink
like the first three hours of the day. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Presumably. So I think there's a lot
of like, I think the drinks look like Disney drinks, like you were saying, like they look
like things that a Disney audience will be safe with, but they're filled with ingredients. You
would not expect, right? Yeah. They sneak them in there. And yet on top of it, custom beer and wine,
because I thought it was all going to be weirdo cocktails, but in fact, beer and wine, you can
only get there. Uh, well with weird, you know, white Wampa, a whole imperial red cabs have, uh,
will you do the Imperial red? You think Scott, Scott, like,
a tone array from Alderaan. Yeah, that's a, that's very rare. Cause that planet doesn't exist
anymore. You gotta get that cast. If it's, if it's aged enough that the planet it's from isn't
around. So you gotta go with that. Um, we tried the IPA. Okay. Um, and I'm not a beer person,
so I, unfortunately my notes were like hops. Okay. Okay. Um, it was palatable, I guess. Okay.
Okay. But I just can't believe that like on top of that, like that it is a full menu with this bar.
Yeah. And, and let me, uh, Mike, your favorite detail that you've pointed out in text, uh,
that they are, they have done so much research and done so much backstory that they know what Padme
ordered at the bar. Yeah. So I forget who said it and what article was set in, but they said that
in their story and their backstory for the land and for this Cantina,
Darth Vader has been here. Padme has eaten here and they've gotten so detailed with it. They know
what she ordered there. They didn't say what it was. I have what she, oh, you do. Oh, from the book.
Yeah. All right. Cause it's in the book. Oh, this is big news. That's of course where they
brought Timothy's on back to write a new extended universe. Oh yeah. Well, I knew that obviously.
Uh, I, uh, this was in the gizmo gizmo, the article. So then Padme ordered white wine,
motherfucker. I, I guess she joined the dark side and doing white wine. So I think that's what I
might have to go with. You are wine buddies. Yeah. I'm joining a wine club with Padme. It's kind of
crazy how like this detail will, some people won't even notice it, but like the people who
are looking for it will find so much joy. I am going to get Padme's beverage of choice.
And everyone else will just be like, give me a white wine. I don't care. Sure. Yeah. It's cool.
It's way, it appeals to any kind of a white wine drinker. I think they knew they were,
they were going to be getting an aggressive type fan and they really catered to them. Yeah. Yeah.
Without sacrificing the main audience, which I assume is maybe impossible to do. Yeah. And in
this they've crafted the only thing that I could be an aggressive fan of a place where I can
experience both Rex and white wine. It's really insane. I don't like, I'm really worried. I'm
not going to be able to be there for a long time. I don't know if I'll be able to make it in here.
You haven't experienced it. What do you like? Do you think it's going to be possible to breach
the wall or people going to be able to get into this place? So, okay. This is what's interesting
is that at Disneyland, they came out and said that you have to consume your beverage within the
Cantina, which means that people at Disney world might be filing in and out more quickly
because that's an alcohol friendly park. Oh, okay. Oh, right. Right. So specifically the line at
Disneyland might be longer because you have to complete your drink in there. Jeez. But we know,
it sounds tough. I mean, we still don't know. I know they've had to do this with the Harry Potter
lands before, like you get a reservation just to come into the land. Now I would hope they would do
that with Galaxy's Edge as opposed to just insane lines snaking through the entire park. That said,
you see pictures of opening day star tours or Indiana Jones and there are insane lines
snaking through the park. I think that they are so prepared and they're just not telling us anything.
I hope so. Okay. Because they know, like the thing is the only question that people keep asking me
is related to like, how do I get in? So they're feeling that times like a hundred thousand.
Yeah. So they're, I mean, they, I know you can't, you can't have the whole place just be lines.
No, no. But I'm curious to see how they do it. I'm curious to see how they do it. And the other thing
is, and this, I think the major thing we haven't really talked about is how the Disney play app
integrates with a lot of the land. When I was there the other day, I could not get a consistent
wifi signal between frontier land and main street. And that is like a smaller than a one mile radius.
They only have hotspots set up around fast pass kiosks. I think. Is that what it is? It's
the words like near right. They're not, it is not full coverage. Yeah. And they said that they would
be working to update that before the opening. Okay. But yeah, it's, it's like a broken wifi system.
But within the land, if they're building it from scratch, I'm assuming the whole thing will be
blank. I think it has to be built the land with the app in mind. Yeah. And some of it I think is
like, it's more Bluetooth. There's like, I think it's possible you don't have to have wifi. That's
true. Yeah. But I think for the app you do. Really? Okay. I read something. I'm not sure.
I think a lot of stuff is Bluetooth powered, but I think the, I think for the app you might have to.
Well, especially if, did they say anything about like, because the rumor is that fast passes will,
it will only be fast pass plus in galaxy's edge as opposed to paper ones. Is that really? I don't
know. I think that's all, I don't know. I've seen every version of speculation. So I don't know what
that is. Like, yeah, I don't know. I don't think there's also a lot of things I've read that's
been like, it's just going to be sort of, they're not going to do a ton of that for a while. Like
they're just going to sort of. It's all just standby. It's all just one line. So I don't know. I
don't know. I don't have any information. I mean, for years, Universal did not have any of the Harry
Potter attractions on the express pass until they added them. Yeah. I don't know. Who knows?
I think, well, yeah, it's, it's like the big question that won't be answered. What's your
galaxy's edge plan when it opens? We don't have a, cause it's the second one. That's an
unfree question to ask. Were you able to get a fast pass while you were there for June? I was not.
That would have been dope. That was like the handout. No, I got a baseball cap. That's cool.
Pretty good. Yeah. That's cool. I wanted to draw it, but I'll ask. I don't know, but I can
tell you, I'm going to be writing a lot about it once I do know, cause there's going to be a strategy.
I just had to figure it out. It's also depends on like, they might literally only have one area
for an entrance. They might like have time tickets. They might have something you buy for the first
month. It could be anything. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Not announced. I don't know. I don't, and we,
you know, we talked about this a little in an episode recently and we came up with a plan. We
think could be a plan. And then we bleeped the plan and people were mad. And I do
issue an apology, but we also aren't sure that the plan works. I guess Jenny Nicholson had the idea
and then she was like, didn't want to reveal it. And then we bleeped it out. And I have had,
I just had a listener come up to me a couple of days ago and he goes, what was the plan?
Yeah, I've, I'm getting a lot of, we're getting a lot of like DMS. It can't be a secret if nobody
knows. If you go to our Facebook group, people kind of people pretty much figured out what it is.
It's not an impossible thing. But I don't know if it, I don't know if we'll talk about it.
We don't know if it'll work. It's Jenny's idea. So I don't want to reveal. It's hers to reveal.
So we can tell you off the podcast. That's her content. Let's let her do with that content.
See, I'm mostly a Disney world person. So for me, like in Disney world, there's a,
you're used to booking things 180 days in advance. Oh, right. That's true. So it's only like the
Disneyland people who are losing their minds. Like we're used to planning things freakishly long
ahead. That's me. I hate all this. My, when I, I've had friends who just went and I didn't know what a
like hellscape it had become in terms of the, the mega booking. It drove me crazy. It makes me
furious. I mean, I guess it's, it's what it has to be. You like that. I love it. God, I like it too.
They have a way spreadsheets out and shit to have a go on a fun ride.
They've already got me out of the land in Florida by distracting me with a new transportation
system. I'm excited for those guys. Skyliners, yes. They're on the track. They're testing them out.
Still have not used the phrase air conditioning when discussing it, but I think they have that.
They, they seem like they figured something out for it. It's gotta be breezy. I think it's breezy.
Yeah. The roof fed a kind of a fast race. Yeah. It's mostly Disneyland people that are
is there anything I'm exhausted now? I'm mentally and physically,
and we recorded another episode too. So I'm just like, I'm so sorry. No, no, no. I, are you kidding?
You have at least to apologize for any guests. I really am. But everything else too, that you've
like, you've given us info. I didn't know. I mean, is there any random question you have that I might
for listeners, the plague app integration, the Carly wrote about it in the LA times and the tech
crunch articles. They go into a lot of detail. Yeah. But read mine. Screw you, Todd. Yeah.
We love you, Todd. But also read my story. He wrote a wonderful piece. Yeah. I do have a small
piece coming out about it, but basically you're, they didn't give us, they told us what you could
do in the app, but they didn't really tell us how it would actually work. Like when you're in the
land, when you ride the Falcon, when, you know, what the actual operations of it would be.
Yeah. And it will be interesting. The operational differences between the two coasts, because we
don't have magic bands out here and they have that in Florida. And also points of purchase.
It's much smoother in Florida and here. How are you, how do you keep a credit card in story?
Yeah. Right. Oh yeah. I think you mentioned cause yeah, it's easier if you're in magic band,
you can scan it or they doesn't even matter. Your movement and it makes more sense. Right. Yeah.
Yeah. But here. So they didn't even mention anything about, cause there's a whole talk of,
if you do badly on the Millennium Falcon ride, is there any talk about how that works out here?
No. And your credit doesn't work in the score. They reject your cards if you do badly on the
Falcon. But I do know that it's not your individual performance. It's your groups. Right. Right. Right.
So it's how all six of you work together. But is it potentially that you scan something on your play
or your Disneyland app before you do Millennium Falcon ride? And that's maybe how it works. Who
knows? And then no hotel talk yet. Of course out here. The hotel is so, so far away. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. I know there's a whole issue they have to work out with other things. That was a very
early announcement. Right. Oh, this isn't a question, but a thing to talk about.
Apparently Star Tours not going anywhere. Apparently. Yeah. Happy to hear it. Very
relieved as you know. Or are they just saying that so we get comfortable? Yeah, maybe. I don't know.
But I, you know, to me you take that out in the first year of galaxy's edge or gutting tomorrow
land. You're like, there's nothing there. That's a people eating attraction that, uh, you know,
why not? And people are going to want to go on. It's going to spread crowds around. I'd say it's
like, depending on what the system is, like if it is a time dentry or something like that, being able
to like pregame with Star Tours is great. Cause then you land on Batuu and then you're like,
I'm ready. Oh yeah. That kind of looks like a little preview. It's getting you into it a little
bit. I think it'll actually be probably have longer lines for the next two years. Yeah.
People getting amped just cause they're in the Star Wars mood. Right. Yeah. Yeah. Um, yeah. And
they do have the problem with it where it's like not there's the Star Wars area, but then Star
Tours is far away from it and they're split up and then where does it land on the timeline?
My response to that is who the fuck cares? Leave the fun ride open. But they will be most likely,
I mean, if history repeats itself, when the new movie comes out in December, they'll add new scenes
to Star Tours. Okay. For the past few years. Interesting. Let's get Greg Grunberg,
snap one friend. That's his character name. See him in there. Uh, was there any talk on the two rides
of, um, I assume there's like variations on things, but there's no talk of like, you get a totally
different scenario on the Falcon or you could get, there's different paths to go on on the ride. Like
I asked them about the spectrum of opportunities, like, because it's not that you can just crash
in the right ends in three seconds. You will have the same length. It's just how well you perform.
But I couldn't figure out if it was like, you do great. You do medium. You do okay. I can't figure
out how many variations there are. Right. But there are supposedly many, any chance of Will Smith
rating your performance, all of the men in black alien attack. Right. God, I wish. Y'all did okay.
It's the worst locker area in the entire park. Is that right? Oh God. Oh really? What's the,
what's the problem? Oh, it's just, you're always, you're always on the ride in that queue for too
long. And then you're like, I was once a child, like that I, nothing makes me feel old and sad
more than going on that attraction. But it's got so many, it's just a wealth of standard definition
screens and rap songs from over 20 years ago. Being in an empty office, you know, the portion
of the queue where it's like people do work at this desk. Oh yeah. It makes me very sad. You can
get a, apparently if you just, it used to be like an exclusive thing. But now if you just ask a cast
member, can I go down, walk around the floor? They're like, yeah, come on. Not a highlight.
I want to meet the twins. Prices. How much will the Rex toy cost? Do we know? We don't know, but
I'm going to say 64 99 and see in a few months if I'm correct. That's just like your guess. Yeah,
it's my guess. It's like a high end toy. And you can't, I would pay $1,000. Yes, he knows.
Scott does not have Amazon dots or anything, but he will get a Rex for the living room,
one for the bedroom, one for the office. I'll introduce them to each other. They'll all have
parties. On Twitter. I said, I'm going to go in for every room because of the music. Yeah. What
are the, oh wait, also, so there's also like BB date style. Yeah. Well you can build your own BB or
our style droids. Yeah. But you can add like different colors and different panels. And one
had a little pop out camera and then you can put different chips in them to make them make different
noises and have different personalities. You can't build your own Rex. Rex is a standard.
Rex is one you just buy. Right. And there's a, why would you change something that is perfect?
There's a C three PO one as well. That's the same size. It's like, I'd say it's more like an
action figure doll. Okay. But cause it's a little taller. Okay. And then if you pop his head off,
he, they only showed us them popping his head off, but every time you like pops out or put it on
backwards or put it back in, he says different stuff. So he knows what's happening. Like if you
put the head backwards, he's like, I can't see. Right. And then if you put them back the right way,
he's like, oh good. What else? Expansion pad next to Star Wars land. They tell you the third ride
or something. I also have heard that gossip and I don't know where that would go.
Well, we've looked at Google maps a lot of the area and there is space there, but it's unclear.
Like it's cause yeah, it's unclear. Exactly. It's on the, like if you're looking overhead,
it's like, uh, east, like Northeast a little bit this way, like Hagrid's magical rollercoaster
ride, whatever it's called. Like that took eight years, nine years for it to open. Yeah.
And they had to demolish a roller coaster to build a roller coaster. So, well, I mean,
it's gotta be better than dragon challenge, but they're not going to build a third attraction
for at least not a main amount of time. Yeah, I would think so. That's tape. Take her easy guys.
You've done a lot. This is if they've created an attraction that is mind bend, that changes your
idea. I'm also like, what is it going to be? There's gotta be imagineers though in Glendale,
like every week going like, I can't believe the fantasy land theater has not had a wrecking ball
taken to it. It's so big. It's so you can do so much with that plot of land. Well, what I want
them to do is to like merge worlds and make kind of a, like a star wars a fide new videopolis
where you can see a hologram concert by Jefferson starship, a la the star wars holiday special.
Now that might be just me, but I think they got room in tomorrowland. Yeah, make it out. Yeah.
You got the space. Just put up a hologram driven. So we would, I know Mike and I have joked about
like a holiday overlay of life day. The wookie holiday celebrated in the holidays, but they need
to own life day. They don't know what they're sitting on. Life day. Life day rules. Oh my God.
All right. I mean, I'm sure I have a hundred more questions, but are we in longest episode
territory right now? I don't think so. I don't think so. Okay. Should we keep it rolling?
Let's see if we can get there. Let's just stall. I think we get like a tight 20 out of you about
Rex for sure. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I did already. I'll do it again. It's not tight. It's tight in that
Rex is tight. Well, if you guys or anyone else has questions, they can annoy me on social media and
I will let you know, or just give you PR speak that says they didn't tell us. Sure. Well, I guess
with that being said, Carly Wisell, you survived podcast, the ride. Let's exit through the gift
shop. Anything you would like to plug in. Where can people find you? Oh, so I mostly write for
travel and leisure and I write occasionally for eater, but you can find me on Instagram because
I'm a freelance writer. So I got a lot of free time. And my Instagram is Carly Wisell spelled
C A R L Y E W I S E L. I spell it because there's too many letters and you almost wouldn't believe
how many there are. And then I'm on Twitter sometimes, but mostly Instagram or Twitter. I
will lead and I will just post a bunch of links to random T and L stories that I write. Right.
Well, and your dot com is nice and tidy. There's all your, like a lot of your best articles.
On a vacation to Walt Disney World and you need help visit Carly Wisell dot com. Have you been
to every park? Yeah. Wow. Jeez. Yeah. Pretty good. Do you have a crazy trip coming up?
Um, I'm trying to do, I tried to call this 2019 year of the regional theme park. So I'm trying to
hit like every East coast park I haven't been to. Cool. I haven't been to Dollywood, which is crazy.
Well, Wildwood Grove is coming. I know. I want to see all those butterflies in real life.
So I'm trying to do that. I'm trying to hit like everything this year so that
I just covered it. I just went to Bush gardens in Tampa, which I'd never been to.
Yeah. I fed a giraffe. Wow. Cool. It was thrilling. I bet. I mean, animals. Yeah. They're crazy.
There's a lot of great theme parks out there and it's a shame that they have to wheel that we've
we probably haven't done our due with regional theme parks.
Well, there's so much going on right now. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The big dogs are really owning it.
We still want, we want Dollywood to fly us out and cover and, you know, we'll do a whole thing.
They don't have a good budget for something like this for a really niche theme park like us.
Things are very different between the people who are owned by gigantic media corporations.
Okay. Interesting. People in a theme park that has a bunch of butterflies in a dry county.
That's true. That's my sister-in-law. I was like, looked that up and was like, nope, not going.
In Pigeon Forge is a dry county? I don't know that every
single part of it. I think it might be like restrictions on when you buy from stores.
Oh, I see. I see. Margaritaville Hotel. There is a Margaritaville Hotel.
There is one there. They just opened a huge Margaritaville Resort near Universal Orlando.
Well, yes. There'll be a future episode. You'd be amazed how much of our podcast
has been about that. Really? Yeah. Yeah. We've, I'm glad we finally given Galaxy's Edge its fair
shake because we've been very Margaritaville Resort heavy. We will tease in a few, a couple of weeks,
there's a big reveal about us and Margaritaville Resort that again, we only can tease on this
episode, but we'll tell you once we're done recording, it's pretty incredible.
Oh my goodness. I didn't realize you were such like Margaritaville heads.
I'm the big one and there, yeah, we've been- Is this something that CityWalk spurred in you or?
No, no, no. City, we liked, we had an affection for CityWalk before Margaritaville, but then when
it moved into our, it was already at CityWalk, obviously in Orlando, but no, that's just a
perfect marriage. Margaritaville, Jimmy Buffett in general, I got kind of fascinated with like
five years ago when I was going through his music on Spotify and I came across a song called Math
Sucks and it was S-U-K-S and it's just a song about how he doesn't like to do math and from
then on I was hooked. I was like, this man is so fascinating to me. And then ironic fixation became
as genuine as Rex is. Yes. And then that extends to all of his lifestyle brand and his resorts and
his hotels and et cetera, et cetera. And yeah, so- So look up at Margaritaville on Instagram,
check him out on Facebook, Twitter. Please, they need it. They need your support.
Listen, a math sucks on Spotify and get the numbers up because I don't think that's one of
the top, let's get that in top five. I don't want to listen to a rich man complain about counting
his money, honestly. My theory was- It's so hard to get those dividends.
I don't know what, hey. My theory was that he had done, he was having a hard time tipping at a
restaurant and then he was like, this math sucks. And then that was it. And then he wrote a song
about it and he wrote it in five minutes. He just laid down a $500 bill and was done with it.
Whatever. And then he- I like to imagine Jimmy still doing his own taxes with the paper forms
and the calculator that spits out the paper roll. And all the papers are flying away because
he's at a desk on the beach. Yeah. I do this happens every year. Why do I keep doing this?
If you have time to do anything else after with all of this extra homework,
check us out on Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and check out the second gate, patreon.com
podcast, the ride. This has been something else, exhausted, more exhausted than any other episode.
Wait till we actually go. But exhausted in a good way. I mean,
I mean that listener also like high, like adrenaline surging the whole time. Exhausted,
not exhausted in the sense that we're like fatigued by the too much information.
Really brought the whole crew down, huh? No, no, no. No, no. I mean, yeah.
Satisfying. Up and all around.
It's just so, it's too much information. It was.
It's you, I shouldn't. Yeah. If you feel euphoria for two hours, your brain is going to crash.
There's just no way around it. I do think I'm going to go home and then,
and just like sit silently for a while. Just take it all in, just try to just kind of like
meditate. It does kind of feel like I've been there too. I know.
Yeah. You did a great job. Thank you.
Yeah. Definitely starting to feel more real. Do you think there's another media
day like this weekend, like this coming up? I heard that no one's going in the park till
like it opens. Wow. Wow. Interesting.
Either till, like, I don't know what the format will be, but like this was the only hard hat
walking tour. Interesting. You were in rarefied air and thanks for.
Yeah. It was wild. Thanks for bringing some of that air into
this apartment. I'm glad I could like use my tiny P brain to remember details.
You didn't need that camera. I didn't need this.
Yeah. I just soaked it all up.
Come back any time. Talk. We can have. Yeah. You do your other adventures.
Yeah. Any other adventures.
If you have any more controversial lists that coming out.
Or if you just want, we'll do a two and a half hour episode on the Hoopty Doo review.
Please. No. Okay. Fine. Fair. Fine.
No. Fine. There's only so many washboards you can spray.
All right. I don't know about. Yeah.
This episode's going long enough, but I'm feeling like between the country bears and the Hoopty
Doo review, maybe you have a bias against old time. And Dollywood.
And banjo music. I come here with little to no nostalgia.
Okay. All right.
Not pining for the good old, those good old jingle jingle days.
No, definitely. You don't like a man playing a jug, I guess.
I don't think I do, but I love the food that is offered at.
Fair enough. The jug celebration.
Well, we'll find a different ride then. Hey, the dog's whining because he's
really upset how long we've been recording. Yeah. Well, I'm with him.
Let's wrap it up. Thanks for listening to Podcasts The Ride. See you next time.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to
our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.