Five, four, three, two, one.
Podcast the Ride, the second gate.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined today as always by Scott Gardner.
That's me.
And my Carlson.
Hello, I'm here.
As long as they have joined, we all do it,
and we usually say today, join today by.
Oh yeah, like as if.
They would never not be the case, though you never know.
So if some illness falls one of us.
Sure.
We all try to be there for all of them
as much as we can.
Edwin's here as well.
The show dog.
He's got his collar on, which is a mistake.
I should take it off.
One good Patreon piece of content
would be an all Edwin episode.
Let Edwin talk for a while.
And then we just posted silent audio file
and that gets us out of it.
That's funny.
It's got free.
That's good stuff.
So there's that's coming out.
All right, the Edwin episode coming down.
Edwin episode, yeah.
But today the podcast, the Ride post office is open.
Is open.
Welcome everyone.
Welcome to the post office.
Ding a ling.
Very exciting.
Oh, it looks like we have some letters today.
Jason, would you like to.
Sure.
All right.
I've got a few letters picked out.
Scott and Mike don't know what ones I have.
So let's just get into it though.
This one I think this is good,
but I think it's a nice one to start off with.
Sean Jennings writes,
are there any good books about theme park history
you'd recommend?
Especially around non Disney parks,
which are a bit harder to find.
So I think let's start.
Well, let's start with Disney ones
cause there's a lot of them.
Disney has a publishing arm.
And ads for a long time.
Yeah, but my fear is that I'm gonna like start saying them
and then not know the exact names.
I might have my phone out while we do this.
I remember a really good one
that is out of date at this point,
but there was one at the library
that was like the best one available to me
when I was a kid called,
I believe called Disneyland Inside Story
that I liked a lot.
And even if it's an out of date book,
there's always nice pictures and such.
Yes, Disneyland Inside Story by Randy Bright.
And I remember another one,
I believe called Disney World the first 25 years.
Does anyone recall that book?
I have not read it.
I recall it though.
Yeah, I think we probably had it floating around.
I'll say I did write some down
knowing that I was picking this question.
Secret.
Thank God.
There's one Scott and I,
we both have at least one of these.
Oh yeah, that's great.
There's these coffee table books
just called Disney Imagineering.
There's two volumes.
One was made in 1996.
One was made in 2010.
So you get one has a Michael Iser intro.
One has a Bob Iger intro,
which is funny to look at
and funny to see what they're hyping in both.
There's some great stuff in that first one.
There's a full body sunny eclipse drawing.
Oh yeah, you get concept art.
And you get, we were just texting this around
because there's concept art for Captain EO
of Fuzzball and one of the other characters, maybe Hooter.
And the concept art was done by Joe Roady.
Now, maybe the most prominent current Imagineer
behind Avatar and Guardians and Animal Kingdom.
Yeah, and there is also concept art in it too
for the never completed the Downtown Burbank.
Project where Disney was gonna build.
So we gotta do, oh my God.
That looks crazy.
I don't, look, this might not be as interesting to people
who don't live around here,
but the fact that the Burbank Mall,
really close to where we record,
though could have been, it's now a mall in an Ikea,
but the Ikea moved,
but that this zone was almost essentially
a mini Disney MGM studios
with like Pleasure Island components.
What is that insane?
And now it's like a Fuddruckers.
Yeah, which is good, don't get us wrong.
Fuddruckers is good,
but not quite as good as having a mini theme park.
And also we would not be recording here.
The value would be skyrocket in the area or the opposite.
Yeah, because there's so many apartment buildings
and single family homes.
Burbank High School would have been next door.
Like Burbank High School was just there.
Maybe that was not gonna be sustainable.
Maybe it would just be like wastelands
of a park at this point.
It might've been taken over by gangs,
but at this point, yeah.
High school gangs.
Stay out of there.
But by gangs, I mean just like guys on hoverboards
who I see as a gang,
because I'm afraid of teenagers.
The newest thing I was reading
was that Haunted Mansion Imagineering,
a Disney classic book, which is like a paperback,
that they're like, they sell the parks,
but you can get it on any Amazon and everything.
It's pretty awesome.
It's very in-depth, but it's just about one ride.
There's a couple of those books
that are just about all ride,
but this question is about other parts.
I mean, I don't even have.
Oh no, no.
I think Disney ones are good.
Marty Sklar's book is good.
I've read a little bit of Marty Sklar's book.
Oh yeah, absolutely.
Included, which I think is called Dream It, Do It,
and includes an insane chapter
where he was doing a lot of PR.
He was doing a lot of,
he was writing scripts for the TV show
and he was doing a lot of communications work
that someone will read this or this is a press release,
including him getting called into
whatever higher-ups office was,
like the day after Walt died and them saying essentially,
Walt's dead, we need you to write our public statements.
Oh my God, whoa.
What a tease for a book.
Yeah. That's great.
Unofficial book, not Disney sanctioned,
it's called Mouse Tales by David Koenig.
Is that how you say it?
Koenig, yeah.
Yeah, that's a great, like, you know,
that tells the weird stories about the deaths
and people sneaking in and all the stuff
they don't want you to know.
But yeah, that's a very good one.
I don't have this book,
but I like their blog and their Twitter account.
The book is called Progress City Primer.
I think the Twitter account is just called Progress City,
but they post a lot of cool concept art.
When it comes to non-Disney stuff,
I wrote down a couple that see,
I haven't, I can't vouch for either of these,
but the one we've talked about before,
J Bangs, Hal J Stein, MCA,
and Universal invented the Modern Theme Park
and beat Disney on its own game.
That is written by a guy named Sam Genoway,
who's also, he wrote the Universal versus Disney book
that I quoted from a lot in the Jaws episode.
And then another book that really interests me
that I cannot vouch for the quality of is called Grandstand.
That is the novel based on the story about Hard Rock Park.
Oh, that's the fictionalized version?
The fictionalized version.
Oh yeah, right.
The summary, quote,
regional media conglomerate Caitlin Tufts
and her managing editor Jack O'Banion
have set out to discover the real story
behind Rock Time Amusement Park
and Myrtle Beach South Carolina.
Rock Time.
Oh man, Rock Time, love that.
And then could you count the literary adaption
of Escape from Tomorrow?
The novelization.
The novelization, excuse me.
Yeah, that's what I meant to say.
Which was written secretly inside a theme park.
Don't get caught.
We had to disguise our laptop as a fanny pack.
Yeah, I don't know.
I can't think of anything else off the top of my head.
I've heard that the, I cannot vouch for it,
but I've heard that the new book from Tashin
called Walt Disney is Disneyland.
Yes, I gotta get that.
That's what people have been saying as well.
Yes, I've sent them emails asking for a review copy
and I've not heard back.
Review means free.
Yes.
Also the Disney Imagineering Field Guide.
So these little pocket-sized books
with lots of behind the scenes stuff.
The idea being you can take them to the park
and look at the attractions
and then look at the little stuff in it.
Disney put those out.
They're pretty neat.
You know what I would like to look at?
I was so obsessed with just the Burn Bombs guide
to Disney World.
Those are on eBay.
Just like those.
I read this on the flight to Disney World.
I read this thing cover to cover, the Burn Bombs guide, 1992,
so that I knew every single thing, exactly what it was,
every detail as soon as we walked up to it.
I bet it'd be charming to look at those old ones
that you might have highlighted stuff you saw as a kid.
That's fun.
Yeah, this is a nice question
that we have a nice real answer to.
Yeah.
What do we got in the mail bag,
unless we have more books?
Are we done with the mail bag?
No, no, I've got more.
No books in the mail, but we didn't get any books today.
That's good, it would've been heavier.
But it would've been good
if we got a review copy in the mail bag.
It would've been nice to get a Tash and a Bean copy.
No Tash and Book in the mail bag,
but there's more of your letters.
John Rhodes writes,
Dear Podcast The Ride,
as someone who has been to Walt Disney World
on numerous occasions, but never been to Disneyland,
I was shocked when I watched a ride through
of Guardians of the Galaxy Mission Breakout,
only to discover that the ride leaves out
all of the excellent pre-drop aspects
of the Orlando version of Tower of Terror, he means.
Thankfully, you mentioned on a later episode
that this was always the case
and not something the IP-based reworking extracted.
Either way, it got me thinking, for better or worse,
what are the biggest differences between rides
that exist in multiple Disney or Universal parks?
I mean, the Tower of Terror, Anaheim, Orlando one,
that was a big thing for me.
It's always there, and when people get mad
about the removal of Tower of Terror in California,
I think it's weird because it was always a cheaper version
that was missing big, expensive elements.
And cheap, expensive, cheap elements too.
The end of the ride in Florida,
you end up in a spot with the dummy and other fun.
And the eyes, yeah.
Well, but at the end of the ride
is fun, Twilight Zone stuff.
There's memorabilia as you land,
and the dummy and chairs, and there's this whole little scene
that happens sort of at the end, and nothing plays out.
It's just you land in a different spot
than you started on the end of the ride.
Just that is different, because you start from the same place
and you land in the same place in California,
so they can't do something fun like that.
And the Paris one is also a minimized version, I believe.
Yeah, and the one in Tokyo is the same.
The one in Tokyo is a whole other story
because the theming is so excellent,
but there's no fourth dimension room there either.
It's the same one.
Oh, okay, so only the Disney World one.
Yeah.
So it's all been sort of like,
you don't even want to say lesser towers in all these cases,
but they are missing that.
They're missing that, which I mean.
A big one that sticks out for me,
and the comfort of my spine is Space Mountain in Orlando
versus Space Mountain in Anaheim.
Totally different tracks, totally different.
Well, there's two, yeah, and there's two tracks in Florida.
Oh, yeah.
And it's rough as shit.
It's closer to the Matterhorn
in that it'll just fuck your body up.
Yeah, it's real rough.
I feel like it's not as bad almost as the Matterhorn,
but it's still pretty bad,
and it also makes you really feel
like you're gonna fly out of the car
because it feels more like a toboggan,
whereas Disneyland feels like
you're in a full roller coaster vehicle.
Yeah, that thing's pretty hefty at this point.
Yeah.
It feels safe in there.
What's the big, I mean, the Space Mountain,
that might be the biggest feeling of a change
to go from one to the other.
Pirates, obviously,
because there's no waterfall,
there's no drop in Florida.
There's no drop?
Yeah, it just sort of starts.
Oh, really, and you don't come back up out the waterfall.
And that whole fun, maybe that's the biggest
drastic change is because you miss this whole fun,
all the ambiance, the restaurant is gone,
and you just- The bayou is gone.
The bayou is gone, you don't have that minute
of just crickets and banjo man on the porch
that's obviously like something's wrong with him,
but it's nice to see him.
Yeah.
We had to do a whole episode about the banjo man.
Yeah, oh, the banjo, that'd be great.
So that, I feel like that is missing
such a crucial element to the ride.
It almost feels maybe more important to me.
Well, then, Tower does, but maybe not.
And that's maybe a change here and there
is the lack of space that doesn't give you as much time
to settle you into the story or what have you.
The rides are the same, but the Little Mermaid
is different in land and world in terms of setting.
And world is maybe superior in that you're actually
in the Little Mermaid facade rather than the-
Whoopi Goldberg movie.
Yeah, the San Francisco palace that is left over
from the golden dreams.
There's the sea cabs.
It's the same Nemo experience in the submarines
as in the path to the Living Seas.
Oh, the Living Seas, yeah.
Yeah, it's the characters in these bubbles
that are projected.
So that's the same stuff, but one is submarines
and one is the Living Seas sea cabs,
which that feels more functional.
It's more of like, let's get you down here
rather than a ride in and of itself.
You used to just take this big elevator.
The Hydra later.
Not to be-
Is that a Cyber later?
It's not a Cyber.
Oh, it's not a Cyber.
I always fuck that up.
No, no, no, it's powered by Hydral.
It's powered by water rather than powered by
the digital Infoscape.
The, what else?
Very minor differences in the Haunted Mansions
between Orlando and Anaheim.
Certainly the building designs are different.
There's like an extra room.
There's like an MC Escher room in Florida,
which is kind of cool.
That's kind of cool.
I like that.
Railroads, there's no Medieval or Primeval worlds
in Disney worlds.
Is there any, the train in Disney world
doesn't take you through anything special in particular?
Oh no, not really.
In Orlando, it's much more functional
because that park is so more-
It's a bigger place.
Yeah, it's so spread out.
I mean, I would say just the Tomorrowland out here
doesn't have Sunny Eclipse.
That maybe is the biggest one.
That would shut me up about a lot of this stuff
if they'd throw a Sunny over around somewhere.
Yeah, Tomorrowland can rot like it's rotting now
as long as there's a robot in there rotting with it.
As long as he's doing songs and he's rotting, that's fine.
Yeah. Absolutely.
Oh, you know what's another one?
In Paris, Big Thunder is Tom Sawyer Island.
It replaces Tom Sawyer Island.
So the mountain is in the middle of the rivers of America,
which makes it a longer ride.
I love the Big Thunder in France.
It takes you underneath the rivers.
That's really cool.
Yeah, it adds a lot of time and added a lot more time
the other way because that was the place
where I got stuck on the third lift hill,
which is probably the furthest point.
It gave me like the most distance to have to walk through
to get back to where we came from.
And we were walking under the river.
So super cool.
That was like such an ideal breakdown experience.
And the ride up until that point was great.
Although I heard, I think Tony Baxter said
that the finale of Thunder Mountain Paris
is superior to the other ones
because they had more space.
And I don't really know why or what happens
because it stopped.
So I'm missing out on potentially something.
I don't know, there's no like big effect I'm missing.
I think it just like is a more superior.
Because you know what's a bummer about Disneyland
is that the most thrilling zone probably
is between lift hills one and two.
And then it kind of just sputters out.
You get that splash down,
but that's not particularly an exciting drop or anything.
So Big Thunder Disneyland does kind of like,
it's a little bit of an unsatisfying end.
Yeah, I think now that I'm thinking about it,
what is my definitive answer for this question?
I believe I have the answer.
It is Pooh's Honey Hunt from Tokyo to California.
Well, but that's not called,
this is a different attraction I would say.
I don't think you would quite.
It's not, we're talking many adventures versus Pooh's.
But it's so, but there's so many of the scenes are the same.
Michael, you're out of your fucking mind.
I am not out of my fucking mind.
You're losing it, dude.
Not true, the narrative of the ride is the same.
But the ride system is.
But the ride system is so much different.
Well, but that holds true for the people movers
in Florida versus the late one in Anaheim.
Yeah, but I don't think you can,
because there's no, well, there's a few little scenes
for people movers, but I'm saying as far as a ride,
this is the same narrative.
And then you go through the same.
So there's a Heffalub and Woozle scene here.
There's a Heffalub and Woozle scene there.
And the one there is so much better.
Mm-hmm.
I think this counts.
I would quantify these as different experiences.
I know.
The names are different.
But the names are different
because they didn't want to invite comparison
is my feeling about it.
One is so vastly superior.
Yeah, I know that.
I know that's why I would call them different things.
This is a splitting of hairs.
I think we're splitting hairs here because.
But like just even there's effects from the one
in California and effects there and just robot wise,
the poo is so cute and furry in Tokyo
and he's just not quite there.
He's cute, don't get me wrong, but he's not the Tokyo poo.
You mean to tell me that the Japanese
got something cute, correct?
Like they made a very cute thing.
I am saying that.
I don't believe that.
So I believe that my answer stands
and I believe I am the most correct.
Now.
Well, now we're taking it too far.
I believe I am.
I am most thing.
The most correct.
That's the stubbornness I would expect from an Eeyore,
not a poo.
Is he?
I think rabbit is more stubborn maybe than Eeyore.
Yeah, fuck I think you're right.
Yeah, Eeyore is.
Eeyore is too.
Stubborn in terms of like wanting to stay sad
and not wanting to get help.
Yes.
He doesn't want out of his funk.
Right.
Because it kind of defines him.
It's like people who own and nurse their own depression.
Exactly.
And they use it as an identity.
Eeyore, all your friends care about you.
They want to help you
and they're going to like you even if you cheer up.
Anyway.
So if Eeyore is listening.
Most correct.
Oh boy.
I'll let it slide for now.
What else we got?
All right.
Shake another one loose.
This is where the, I think the mailbag episode,
the post office episodes are where we're,
we've like diverged from being a comedy podcast.
This is where this like.
For sure.
These first two have just been like,
we're being tested.
Yeah.
These first two questions are like test questions.
And we're all kind of eyeing each other.
Like, do you know it?
I think I know the answer.
Is this next mailbag question,
answer 10 questions about the history of Disney?
No.
We should do a quiz.
Yeah.
Maybe that's a fun,
but like if we somehow like,
I don't know who could be impartial enough to give us
questions, but a little competition.
That's a fun episode.
I don't have, I don't know the mechanics of that.
Like trivia stuff though.
Yeah.
But it would have to be a variety of topics.
Who would call that though?
Yeah.
I mean, there might be some.
Oh, that's interesting.
Quiz master Jones.
He might be into that.
Yeah.
I wonder if there's some book that exists that we could
like pull from or somebody could kind of randomly select.
But Doug is the quiz master.
That would be different.
Cause I feel like we're not tight to like,
if we have it written down, we'll go like,
actually that opened in like,
that didn't open that year.
I might eat shit if it's a lot of dates.
I forget dates a lot.
We would all discover our own areas of weakness.
And yeah.
We'll come, that sounds like fun.
The great trivia challenge.
That's fun.
All right.
Or maybe, or with quiz master Bugsy.
That's a very different kind of thing.
And if you lose, you gotta suck my jewels.
All right.
Amanda Hasaka writes, first off, love the podcast.
Thank you, Amanda.
But now that Netflix has passed over Disney
in terms of being the biggest media company,
do you think they'd get into the theme park game?
If so, what are some properties that would make the cut?
The only thing I could think of is a stranger things
upside down situation.
Or maybe they can take all the Netflix Marvel properties
and do something with those.
Would love to hear your ideas.
They can't do that because it's Marvel.
Thanks.
And congrats to Scott for being a launch queen.
Okay, first off.
Wow.
All right.
Hold on, I gotta say,
one launch does not a launch queen make.
Oh, really?
That doesn't count.
Let's not go crazy.
Where do you draw the line?
What do I have to do to earn your respect?
You know, well, first off, you have my respect.
Oh, that's good.
I know.
But I think like, let's not go overboard.
Let's not, you already said you love the podcast.
Let's not hype ourselves up too much now.
I say let's not contradict
this person who said nice things about the show.
Well, I think if, I think let's let the fans decide
what constitutes a launch queen.
You tell me what kind of queen I am.
For the listeners, you should know
we are both squeezing apples as we say this.
So they explode to get our anger out.
No, I think that is a very funny question.
What do you guys think?
What is Netflix?
I'm scrolling through here.
What could we do?
So yeah, Marvel has to be out because that's Disney.
And even though Netflix is showing them, that doesn't work.
I want to be legal here, too.
I don't want to do something.
We can't use a property that wouldn't be able to.
So it has to be like a Netflix property that they own.
We take a tried and true lesson from a playbook.
I think you want big letters spelling out Netflix
in front of the whole California adventure.
But we have new technologies now.
So I think you get some really high def OLED screens
on those letters so that it looks like they disappear
and then they reappear and that Netflix pop
and they constantly playing the boom.
Well, I think when you check in, when you scan your ticket,
boom boom.
Oh, for sure.
That's good.
Every time you hit in the door.
How about this?
So there has to be different lands.
And look, it's a trope maybe at this point,
but there has to be some sort of Western theme land.
Yeah. Okay.
But it can't just be, you know, frontier land.
It can't just be old West town.
I would like to theme this to the Netflix original movie,
Adam Sandler's The Ridiculous Six.
Oh yeah.
Photo ops with all six.
All six. So not godless.
No, not godless.
You can make it Westy.
Is that what you thought I was going?
A restaurant based on it or a store,
but let's keep it minimal.
Let's keep it to properties
that are like the most popular properties
because I want to make money off of this thing too.
Yeah.
And Ridiculous Six, the Adam Sandler movies
do very well for Netflix.
They've re-upped with him.
So this is going to be a big draw
and you're going to meet all of the characters
from the movie, characters like Tommy,
characters like Chico and Herm and little Pete
and Ramon and Danny and Will Patch.
And one of those I can only assume is vanilla ice.
So definitely we want a vanilla ice walk around.
So that's for sure going to be the fun to your land area.
I think that there's got to be a mini land next to it
of like the Ridiculous Six land felt, you know, guilty
of like, well, we got to do something for this guy.
And so there's going to be a real Rob land, right?
Rob Schneider's the real Rob.
Based off Adam Sandler's relationship with.
Oh, I think like if you're going to build an Adam Sandler land.
There's kind of a real Rob land.
Yeah, you got to throw Rob a bone.
Like, yeah, the Rob zone.
And it doesn't have to be a lot of room.
And then all of the buildings in the real Rob zone
are all colored oddly orange,
like all of the actors in the real Rob.
Watch the trailer, you'll see what I'm talking about.
I know what you're talking about.
There could be a world showcase vibe
because Netflix films take you all over the world.
So for sure, you'd want to land after Ibiza
or as it's now known, Ibiza love drunk.
We got to go to Ibiza with our favorite ravers,
Gillian Jacobs and the others.
And you can buy their unicorn onesies.
How many people now that you're like,
we've heard of Ridiculous Six.
They know Ibiza love drunk.
I feel like maybe at this point we've lost everyone.
When you say Ibiza.
Well, I'm going to bring them back.
Hit them with a hit, hit them with a hit.
Hit them with a hit, yeah.
Licensing, big parks do have to license stuff
from other things.
And this is like, license.
This is a big Netflix crowd blazer.
I'm talking the Great British Bake Off.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think.
That's just a good idea.
I was going to say this is actually good.
I mean, signature dining, just to me.
I mean, you're going to get some great sweets and stuff.
And I think that can be,
I similarly, there is other great food stuff on Netflix.
Well, here's how the great,
you go to the Great British Bake Off Cafe
and you order, you know, like beignets
or profiteroles or whatever.
And then like, and then Eager Baker is like, okay.
And then goes off and sweats it out
and makes it up from scratch for four hours.
And you, while you sit and wait,
and then you, you can't leave.
You can't go on other rides.
You can't leave, you have to watch
from like beautifully shot, like Mind of a Chef or
Yes, absolutely.
Chef's Table.
And you have to like pay compliments.
You can't get impatient because it's a very nice show.
So you have to like, say they're doing a good job,
encourage them if something goes wrong
and it melts before it gets in the oven or it doesn't hold.
You have to like be encouraging and pat them on the back.
But it's, yeah, it's the world's only
four hour dining experience in a theme park.
Who needs quick service when you could
have a cake baked from scratch?
Yeah.
I have another restaurant idea for the Ridiculous Sixland.
I think this fits.
It's not, it's gonna loosely, it's on Netflix.
So it's not Adam Sandler, but you're gonna have to go eat
at a little place called The Ranch.
Yeah.
All right.
So The Ranch is gonna be a different,
like a different restaurant, highly themed restaurant.
There's a college student dressed as the Sam Elliott
character from The Ranch.
The character.
The character we all know the name of.
Do we all wanna say it?
Yeah.
Hold on, I'm looking at the...
Billy?
Is it Billy?
Billy Hannigan.
Robert Hendrix.
All right, my guess is that his name is Louie.
That's our, Bo is his name.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's perfect.
Bo is great.
Bo Bennett.
Bit, we were messing with you.
So there's that, I mean, for sure,
there's gotta be a fuller house.
House.
You wanna see the, you wanna walk through
the famous red door.
Of course, who do they live next door?
Uh-oh.
The brownstone that just Claire Underwood lives in.
Yes.
From House of Cards.
Just Claire Underwood.
There will be no representation of Frank Underwood.
No Frank Underwood in the park.
Frank Underwood was, there were plans for,
I mean, there could still be a White House
because Claire's president now,
but Frank Underwood been scrubbed from the park, thank God.
It's nice, you know, Disneyland has nostalgia,
but I like it, and even in the new parks
that Disney still honors classic properties that they have.
So they're still, you know,
they're gonna build a new Peter Pan land over in Tokyo.
And like, that's great,
because obviously that movie is very old,
but they're still honoring the classics.
And I think that obviously a Netflix theme park
has to honor their heritage.
And they have to go, and they have to remember,
it all started with a gangster in Norway, right?
What kind of gangster?
What was the tagline?
A New York gangster?
A New York gangster in Norway.
I'm talking about Lillehammer.
There has to be a Lillehammer dark ride.
Yeah, absolutely.
Okay, and it takes you through Norway,
and it takes you to meeting all of his paisanos.
But then how's this New York guy gonna navigate in Norway?
How is it gonna work?
And like, you're gonna have to navigate the streets of Norway,
just like our famous Lillehammer.
Is that his name?
Or is that, no, that's- Yeah, Lillehammer is his last name.
Yeah.
It's not the place in Norway he's going?
Wait, is it a place in Norway?
I don't know.
I always thought it was his last name.
I also, you know, I don't-
No, it's not his last name.
Lillehammer is the place, I think.
Rural, Lille, yeah, Lillehammer is in Norway.
His name is Frank Tagliano.
Oh.
I love a good Tagliano-Bullionese.
I know it's not, I don't know that this is on Netflix,
but if it is or ever will be,
and you can, I think other properties can be roped in.
I think in Lillehammer hand, you wanna meet the snowman.
You gotta meet the snowman.
Yeah, if we're going, you gotta meet the snowman's friend.
Oh, what was his name?
With Harry Holley Walker.
Harry Holley, yes.
This feels like we should have had a little notice
that we were doing this,
because we could have gotten some more specifics.
No, no, no, I like that we gotta throw it out
off the top of the dome or off of shows up on our phones.
I have the snowman, I have the book at home,
and I have read another Harry Holley thing.
They are very dark and sad.
Oh, okay.
Well, you know, you got live glow wrestling
five times a day. Yeah, hell yeah.
Whenever you go into a store to buy shirts or memorabilia,
you can see if it fits, but it's not with any,
just any mirror, with a black mirror.
You gotta go visit the penitentiary,
where all our, where the crazy kooks over
in the women's prison live.
Sure.
And there can be, and there's like, you know,
maybe there's different rides based on every season,
one through five or six, but everybody,
most people stop doing the rides after season three.
I think the glow entrance needs like a carnival barker,
like a Mr. Potato Head style carnival barker
of Mark Maron's character.
And he's in character, you know, hyping you,
you gotta get in the ring, like, you gotta do this.
But then pretty quickly at the end of his loop,
he like devolves into regular Maron
and starts talking about like,
ah, what is your Lorne story?
Well, at the end of the day,
when they have to close up the ride,
he has to say, lock the gates.
Lock the gates.
They play that announcement,
they play that like the recording.
Yeah.
I would like to just add another detail to the ride
because there's gonna be highly detailed animatronics
in that Lillehammer dark ride.
Of course.
And the big iconic scene is when you meet
the famous character from Lillehammer,
Giuseppe, Joey the Undertaker, Tagliano,
of course the character played by Bruce Springsteen
on one episode of Lillehammer.
Hell yeah.
Once, really?
Yep, that's gonna be your like, kind of,
he's gonna be like the Yeti on the Matterhorn.
You're gonna like get glimpses of him
and then it's gonna be like, wow, there he is.
There's Giuseppe, Joey the Undertaker, Tagliano.
I think phase two of the park, I mean.
Oh, we're cutting it off here for budget reasons?
We can't do more than a phase.
I mean, it's better to
You gotta get something up.
under-promise and over-deliver, you know.
You know, people like colors
and they like shows that are a little off.
You gotta get that maniac ride in there, right?
We're all going god-awful for maniac.
Yeah, but I think you gotta allow a little time
for it to sink in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, let it grow.
The tough thing about kind of budgeting
the future of Netflix land is that
it's hard to do the math on it because when you
like, so what were the attendance figures for this year?
We cannot say, we will never say our attendance figures.
How dare you ask for our attendance figures?
So that does like prohibit the growth.
That being said, Netflix land is on track
to produce 5,000 original rides every single year.
And then also like there's like certain deals
like they're gonna give Bob Gurr $200 million
to design a new Skyway.
They're just throwing so much money at Imagineers
and you're like, this doesn't seem sustainable.
His best work is clearly behind him.
Why are they even doing this?
But yet Bob is gonna make a lot of money
and we're happy about that.
The Ryan Murphy land is just insanely expensive
but no one has any idea what it's gonna be.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They give $2 billion to Barack Obama
and it might just be him sitting in a chair.
Who could forget the beloved walk around the character
for this park?
People dressed like our dear friend of the show,
Mike Mitchell.
For love.
Oh wow, yeah.
His character for love.
The most beloved character on Netflix.
Yes, of course.
Yeah, so you can, and also Joey Tagliano
is a walk around character from Little Camer.
Oh sure, yeah.
Oh man, and if they see each other,
they're gonna do a little interact.
Yeah, they're gonna do a little bit of.
There's so much street-mosphere going on.
Just from the Lillehammer characters.
And when you, and as you exit each ride,
you get to rate it and based on your ratings,
you might see different rides than the other people
you came into the park with.
It's really, it's very metaphysically confusing in that way.
The review feature, your ability to review the movies,
that went to yesterland a long time ago.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And on the app, the Netflix theme park app,
you get to say what theme park rides
you're thinking about going on,
but it's weird because even a couple years later,
you haven't gone on any of the rides
and you're not sure why, but they're just sitting in there
and then you're like, well maybe they didn't ever
really wanna do any of these anyway.
Yes, this will be the first theme park in the world
where people spend a lot of time looking at the map.
A lot more than actually enjoying the experience.
Although that might actually, depending on a busy day,
that might be more of a theme perfect
Disney theme park experience.
Well that is true.
Going on five rides and looking at a map most of the day.
Yeah, some people just go on the first 90 seconds of a ride
and then bail, you just jump out of the vehicle.
A lot of people buy tickets to this theme park
and forget about it.
And they just never.
Yeah, they just rely on kind of.
There's like a million, a couple million people
that totally forgot they bought tickets and never used them.
And that's just how this works.
Any ideas for hotels?
Hotel, full house hotel.
Oh maybe that's it, maybe it's an immersive
and you get like the Knott's Hotel
where Snoopy tucks you in.
You get tucked in by a.
An orc from the movie Bright.
Do you think that'd be a good eat?
Nah, let's do it as a hotel.
No, no, Bright is a hotel.
Meanwhile, unfortunately after the 39 days in operation,
Cecil land burnt to the ground.
RIP Cecil land.
Poor Cecil land.
Well, look.
It sounds great.
Yeah.
It sounds really good.
So we're gonna need.
Oh, you know, and you know what?
We haven't talked about where to build it.
We're gonna need a lot of land.
We're gonna need so sprawling acres.
And obviously it should be built on the former site
of Rajneesh Puram, the cults community in Wild Wild Country.
We will go to the actual former spot of the town.
Cause it gets enough to contain all the dreams
that Netflix land could possibly have.
Of course.
I'm really though not looking forward
to the American Vandal themed bathrooms.
Will there be a statue out front
of Ted Sarandos and Bojack Horseman?
Oh yeah.
Walk partners.
Pointing, walking, whatever.
And then there's a whole like show
where Bojack comes to Hollywood.
It's like a suitcase in a dream,
a California adventure with Mickey coming out to Hollywood.
And don't forget in the air, he arrives in an Uber
a la 2016.
Yes, right, right, right.
Bojack gets out of an Uber.
Right.
And performs a little music number.
Sure.
Yeah.
This is good.
I mean, this is all pretty good.
Yeah.
Hey look, I sprung it on you without any,
we had some real prep time, you know.
Oh yeah, this would be 10 times better if we had prep.
Yeah.
But also, we would have done this for hour.
We would have lost days.
Yes, that's true.
Basically to arrive at almost the same points.
Exactly the same jokes.
You would have laughed about the same.
It just might have been.
There's mild laughter.
No laughter at all.
It might have been about the same.
Less hesitation and at less time
that we spent pulling out our phones
and looking at what the hell is on Netflix.
Steven Van Zandt's character name.
Well, I'm all for it.
Let's get up to rural Oregon and get this thing,
kick out that kids camp that's now where the cult used to be.
Yeah.
I mean, they're gonna need a lot of land
because Hulu land will be coming, you know, a while after.
Like a while, while after.
Yeah.
But Hulu land is mainly,
there's just a TV playing old Seinfeld.
That's really what sustains Hulu land.
Yeah.
So there'll be a whole Seinfeld land then.
That's most of it.
Oh yeah, well, I mean, if you start thinking about Hulu land,
you had to include most of filmed entertainment.
Well, let's get breaking ground.
That was an excellent question.
And legitimately, like,
if they are the biggest media company in the world.
Why not?
Yeah.
Sure.
That's what all the other biggest ones have done.
Warner Brothers was opening,
it was putting like scare mazes on the lot,
on their lot in Burbank.
Yeah, that's crazy.
Like full Arkham Asylum, full It-Hat.
So like, let's do it.
Wait, really?
Yeah, there's a full Arkham Asylum,
which this will come out after Halloween,
but there's a full Arkham Asylum
that you can go to the Warner Brothers and do.
I didn't know about this.
There's like, they're turning Warner Brothers lot
into like Halloween horror nights.
Wow.
Yeah, that's really cool.
And the walkthrough,
the walkthrough is fun.
Like there's actors playing all the Batman villains.
What's funny is the Batman villains all have to act
sort of as the line keepers too.
So like Joker's like, hello there,
but whoa, hold on a second.
Just let these people go by first and then you stay here.
And then, but you're like, oh,
but Joker seems really concerned with the flow of the crowd.
How many in your party?
A devious amount, four.
But that's, yeah, let's do it.
Everybody should do it.
Yeah.
Open up that fucking Netflix building.
Let's have some scare mazes in there at least.
They just, well, they just bought the rest of the building.
It's a 10 story building and only some of it was Netflix
and now it's all of them.
And I want the rest of it to be an indoor themed experience.
Like Sid and Marty Croft.
Yeah, all of us in Marty Croft or Disney Quest.
That Netflix building that you can see in Hollywood now
on Sunset Boulevard is built on studio land
that has been there for decades.
So there is probably real ghosts.
So you're halfway there.
You think there's ghosts?
You think there's ghost Hollywood ghosts?
It's adjacent to Sunset Gower, isn't it?
And a lot of people have died at Sunset Gower.
I mean, I think.
Where was William Frawley's apartment?
William Frawley's from I Love Lucy.
Ted Sarandos' office.
Oh, God, I was just reading about that hotel.
I would love to do a highly themed William Frawley's ghost maze
in the Netflix building.
What was that hotel called?
That's Fred Merch from I Love Lucy, Kids.
It was a show from 70 years ago.
Hey, get out of my apartment.
Telly wasn't esoteric enough.
We had to get into Frawley.
People know Fred Merch.
Yeah, more than Telly Savalas.
But people might not know that his name is William Frawley.
But I'm sure Fred from I Love Lucy is still sort of known to people over
28. He's known to people because he's haunting them.
Yeah. Yeah.
Get out of my place, you ragamuffin.
He died in his studio apartment.
I know he died in the street.
He died outside.
But he wasn't in the street, right?
Sorry. It was like a hotel.
It was a hotel a lot of people would stay at.
I thought it was more of a flop house, but it was a place people would live.
I hear his ghost and Vivian Vance's ghost do not get along.
Absolutely not. Don't put them in the same.
They go to opposite sides of heaven.
Well, great question. Great questions.
And with that podcast, the podcast is closed.
Get out of here.
You're not willing for all these ghosts chasing you out of the post office.
He's the postmaster, the ghost postmaster.
A ghost master needs to sleep.
The ghost master.
So be aware if you send a question to us at podcasttherideatgmail.com
and we don't answer it, it could be because the ghost postmaster,
William Frawley, didn't deliver the letter to us.
Yeah. And blame him.
Blame him. It's his fault.
He's a grouch.
Yeah. But keep those letters coming.
That's a lot of fun.
Yeah. And we'll do we'll do more of this soon.
Later. Goodbye. Bye.