Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain four grown men hashing out a longstanding
Michael Eisner related beef.
The shocking truth of why Phil Collins didn't perform at the Oscars 34 years ago.
And khakis, khakis, khakis.
It's the ultimate theme park media snarkster crossover as we welcome Kevin Perjurer, creator
of Defunctland to funk it up with Tarzan, Jane, Old Turk and Podcast the Ride.
And a podcast the ride hosted by three guys who are friggin pumped to spend a few hours
talking about rockers in dockers.
I'm Scott Yerner joined by Jason Sheridan and Mike Carlson.
Hey guys.
Hey, yeah, they're the dress, the musician style dress is amazing in this.
Not to tip too much too early.
No.
But I was also.
It paints the era.
I think the only thing that could pin this more into 1999 is if the performers yelled,
let's hear it for the NATO forces, victorious and Kosovo.
Just watching it, it evokes such an era with so little.
And if only Disney really does need to acknowledge specific military campaigns more often than
their dance shows.
Like Tarzan would have announced the killing of Osama bin Laden.
Yes.
We got him.
Jane, we got him.
Hey, so yes, as we're alluding to today, we are talking about Tarzan rocks, which if you
don't know it, and there's a little bit of likelihood you might not know it.
This was a live show that started in 1999 and ended at some point in the mid 2000s that
was celebrate a live spectacular celebrating the music of the eternal Phil Collins Tarzan
score in a much more rockin manner than Disney is usually willing to do.
But if you don't know this attraction, then you probably do know our guest.
I'm sure you're familiar with his work if you are a theme park nerd or regular listener
to this podcast.
Over the last couple of years, he's made a series of extremely popular history videos
about defunct theme parks.
He's often cited as a source from us.
He does probably significant more amount of research than we do.
And we're happy to have the to hear some stuff straight from the horse's mouth today.
Joining us for the first time on podcast, the ride from defunct land, Kevin Perjurer.
Welcome, sir.
It's about time.
I am angry.
And I can only get into Tarzan rocks.
It was my Trojan horse.
And I'm so glad that it finally worked.
Weakness, which is, you know, weird music, weird rock music.
Two worlds, one family, podcasting and videos coming together.
At last.
I remember the first time I listened to the podcast.
I mean, you were in my ears as I run.
Oh, yes.
Oh, I love I love the podcast.
You know, I thought I thought, wow, these these guys are really funny.
I mean, I was because I assumed it was like a research based like podcast.
I'm like, these guys are hilarious.
And then I looked all three of you up and they're like, oh, they're comedians.
And they don't always do their research as much as as I do.
At least this was in this was in the earlier episodes.
So you were like quoting like my videopolis video from the second episode.
You're plenty of us.
Most most of the time, our sources are you and Jim Hill and Len Testa.
So congratulations. You beat them.
First of all, you made it here first.
Yes. And you should be proud.
But thank you for letting us siphon off of your info.
Say it a little less carefully and pass it off as our own.
No. Well, we've we've been such a fan of your videos for for a long time.
And I think I had a similar reaction in that, you know,
I probably saw a thumbnail of one of them and I pulled it up
fully expecting to be immediately greeted by a guy saying, hey, guys,
so today we're talking like who's in like a friggin Tiki
shirt and like, you know, like a hovel of an apartment with
too many too much bullshit around him.
Scott just trashed half of theme park media.
Apologies. Like everybody's all my friends.
That's good luck luck luck.
I have no I have no problem with having a bunch of crap in your apartment.
It makes it. But you know what I mean, there's like a type of video
that I've come to expect from theme park media online.
And to watch your videos and find that they're like they're very clean.
They're very well produced.
They're they're they're funny.
When you go for jokes, they are funny.
Like it was all like your stuff is a real breath of fresh air.
And yeah, hey, I'm glad we're all we're all here complimenting each other.
Sure. Well, thank you.
I'm glad I am the the the the again.
I got I got into it.
I think the first episode I listened to was Universe of Energy.
And I was the point that I remember the first time that I was like,
this is hilarious. I was jogging because I listen to podcasts
only when I'm working out.
And I was I was jogging.
And you made the universe of energy joke where you say, like,
it's like the guy that wants to have sex with energy as one of the theme songs.
And I like I like people like we're like I was running around a track at a gym
and I like started laughing so hard, I had to stop running.
So it just looked like my heart had given out.
And it was like holding onto the wall.
And people were like, what the hell?
I'm like, no, no.
And I mean, too long to explain to these people.
But I mean, great, great, great content.
There's a comic book where Mickey explains Valdez and I don't know.
I mean, the whole thing, that was so great.
And then I saw the Videopolis episode and my ego was like, you're mentioned.
And I'm like, what? And I was so I was like, I was just like 15 seconds,
15 seconds, 15 seconds. And then I was like, I was mentioned.
Oh, fantastic. I mean, great stuff.
Hey, thank you.
I think if you had played that clip over, if you'd asked them to put it on the gym
loudspeaker, I think it would have played.
I think everybody lifts and weights would have understood
the deep yet at University of Energy comedy.
So next time that next time we I think we often provoke
the fits of laughter so intense that
hospitalization is a lot of times.
Bodybuilders come up to me and they say they'll be benching and listening to us
and that they drop the bar right on their chest very often.
So I would advise people not to bench press and listen to podcasts to ride
caved in picks.
Kevin, you were also nice enough to ask all of us to do
voices for the your Disney's America video,
which I wanted to let you know I sent to my mother.
And I said, keep an eye out for a familiar voice.
And she's like, that video is very good, very interesting.
I really don't remember much of that park.
What voice was I looking for?
And I was like, mind your son's.
My dad got it immediately.
Like, I think my dad was like, oh, is that Mike's like the first thing?
But yeah, my mom did not recognize me as disgraced, pervert
Senator Larry Cricket.
That also started you.
At you basically, we had a competition between Scott and I for Michael Eisner.
And I don't know, we were we got in the zone.
I still think mine wasn't it was OK.
I got a little gravelly, but we started like I was at a bus stop
waiting to get on like to get to the airport.
And I was just like, hello, hello, hello, hello.
Like, is that right? No, it's not.
I'm like trying to listen to it.
I'm like walking away from the other people waiting for the bus
because I'm trying to figure out Michael Eisner's tone.
And like so so thank you for casting me as Michael Eisner.
If it ever happens again, I've spent more time on it.
It's not good yet, but it will be good.
Yeah, well, I'm so happy that you guys came on.
He also came for charity land.
And and those are just those are great.
Both of those were great experiences having having you all on.
But I agree that Michael Eisner ended up being really good.
I love to use it again.
That was, of course, I brought you on because it was a Ken Burns style
documentary on Disney's America.
So I guess I need to find my which was a Ken Burns Civil War parody.
So I guess I need to find my Michael Eisner Vietnam story
so I can bring you on again to do that one.
Well, I was, you know, like we've talked about and we and we brought this up
a little when we did your charity live stream
that I think maybe one thing where we disagree with you on a little bit.
I think you're a little hard on old Eisner.
And and I was trying to remember like where
where I started feeling that, where I was like, oh, the like the Eisner hate
is is strong. And I think it was I realized it was at the end of Disney Quest.
And I rewatched the end of your Disney Quest episode.
And speaking of documentaries, I was like, this is like this is turning
into Fahrenheit 911 about Michael Eisner.
This is like painting a picture of a warmonger.
Where? Yeah, it's I don't know.
I I'm curious.
I think Mike's played well because you did such a villainous
take, which is probably what you were after.
A little bit. I had ulterior motives to my casting.
Yes, perhaps. Yeah. The the the darker, the darker.
It's like takes on battle.
You know, do we do fun?
Do we do fun, Batman?
Like Adam West or do we do?
Do we do a scarier Frank Miller one?
And clearly you were that you're the scary.
You're the scary Frank Miller.
I swear to me.
But but I'm guns, Carrie.
The weapon of the coward.
Here's what I will in that one.
You described him as an unfocused, fickle, often angry CEO.
I don't doubt that.
Did you not remember it?
Because like we don't I don't remember like some things I say.
I mean, I've never had them like I never had that read to me
out of context and just that before in an interrogation six months ago.
You referred to Mr.
Eisner.
No, I think, you know, I see where you're coming from with it,
because clearly there was like a good Eisner era and a bad Eisner.
I think he I think he turned.
And this will all I better shut up now or we'll never get him on the show.
We want him on the show.
He's made it sort of a declaration.
The party line Eisner was perfect.
He was always perfect.
And that's the that's the way I feel.
No, no, no. I think like,
yeah, clearly there was I mean, because he got ousted from the company and everything.
Roy Disney sort of pushed him out.
But I think we're I don't know, I feel like we I feel like we forgive him.
I feel like, you know, we talk about music a lot.
It's like the good the good stuff was so, you know,
oh, you know, the first five albums were so great.
I'll forgive the shitty last 17.
It's like Weezer.
Well, I don't know what we're doing on that one.
It's the two first albums are so good.
I'm ready to forget anything.
Forgive anything.
You're going to forgive any amount of Weezer of Rivers solo rap.
Yeah. Anyway, Eisner, though.
Eisner. Well, like the the argument between a good Eisner and a bad Eisner is kind of
it's basically is that the case?
Is there a good Eisner and a bad Eisner or was there a Frank Wells and a not Frank Wells?
Yeah. Because if you
I mean, like the in the story I'm telling in season two of Defunct Land is
starts with Euro Disneyland and that failure.
And that was the start to his downfall.
So I'm telling his downfall.
I'm not talking about his from 1984 to 1992 ish.
I mean, then not that there was anything extraordinary happening there besides the
the seeds that were planted to make these incredible renaissance movies.
And also that time that the rescuers down under like inexplicably did well.
And like they like someone burst and they're like, we're winning.
And they're like, that's not that can't be right.
Would the rescuers down under is really performing on the box office.
But but the but, you know, Eisner is is is is kind of like an antihero
in that he is the most human character in any of the Defunct
Land episodes because he is and, you know, I do treat the subjects as characters
to a certain extent because you have to, you know, tell stories.
And when you're telling multiple stories throughout multiple episodes,
you see my guys has turned to the dark side at the end of Disney quests,
which is why that that that quote you mentioned was there.
Well, you know, the Philadelphia location, as you point out, is still a parking lot.
But in their defense, the Market East neighborhood is not exactly flush
with parking options. So good for our fair city. Yeah.
Yeah, it's well, like, well, I think the Philadelphia parking lot takes the place
of like the returning to Flint, Michigan and all of the Michael Moore.
It's the heat that we lay waste to, you know, all these big decisions of laid waste
to this poor town. Yeah, they're they're they're they're exactly parallel, I think.
Yeah. Well, the but with the series, you know, I try to find out where Michael Eisner
turned, because I think no matter who you ask, there is a there was the turning point.
And so everyone kind of says it was Euro Disneyland.
And my argument was it was more of a result of Euro Disneyland,
Disney's America, Club Disney, Disney Regional Entertainment as a whole.
And that's when he turned. And that's what brought us Superstar Limo.
And then what's coming up is Hong Kong Disneyland, which is the finale.
Oh, interesting. I don't know when this airs.
So no one's doing my ideas if this is an hour already.
At least it'll be in February or March.
Do you know when when that's when you're heading for the finale?
February.
Gotcha.
No, no, no. I meant as in we are in February.
Oh, yes. Currently in this time that we're recording.
Yes, yes, yes.
Gotcha. Yeah.
But OK, so you're building up to Hong Kong Disneyland, which we haven't really talked
about a lot on this show.
I don't like.
I mean, don't give away your video.
Don't give away the things that happened.
Yeah. The things that happened.
I can reveal my past is the take on it.
I mean, it does seem like it's probably the chinsiest of the Magic Kingdoms.
That's fair to say, correct?
It was a it was a horrible, horrible mistake.
It was it was a terrible idea from the start.
And I'll go into it, but it's worse than Paris.
It's it's such an interesting story of like of the magic of the magic of the magic of
the magic of the magic of the magic of the magic of the magic of the magic of the magic
of magic for the magic of the magic of the magic.
So like, the magic of the magic of the magic of the magic of팩 Ranger has destroyed
imprisoned to the point where ityelling and screaming at each other and all and collect
all the migrants, all of them, soldiers.
So I mean, the message of magic.
OK, so from the beginning I went with the idea that there was, you know,
but the but yeah, I mean, I don't know.
I find it I find it very funny because it was like, yeah, we're going to go classic.
We're going to build the Disneyland Castle.
And yeah, yeah, we need to save a lot of money.
We're going to build the smallest castle we can.
Yeah, they didn't decide that super well.
That seemed pretty evident what they were.
And now they are replacing the castle, correct?
They're doing just why I'm doing the episode, right?
Yeah, sure. That's my defunct of the defunct.
I mean, Hong Kong is still around.
So that's it. It's the castle.
But it's the first walk in a way.
The first castle ever to be torn down again with parallels to, you know, Iraq War era.
It's sort of like the tearing down of the Saddam statue.
There's a lot of significance to this.
I hope we get to see footage of the castle being turned in.
If we're talking if we're talking CEOs, though, like if you were to write, let's say one to
10 Eisner overall and then Iger overall, do you have a number that pops in your head
for both of them just to weigh out all the stuff they've done?
Well, it's it's hard to say.
The and so if you read my book plug for book, the there's a great the ending.
Not that there's a there's kind of a I come to come to this this head of the Michael Eisner
hate and like the book is kind of about the Eisner hate towards the end and like how how
to handle it and different things.
And it culminates into a lightsaber fight between Bob Iger and Michael Eisner and which is
which is a wonderful ending to that to that classic book.
But the the I'm trying to think Bob Iger is a so Bob Iger came from capital city, right?
He was ABC guy. He was brought into the company.
And I think I was reading somewhere Michael Eisner was worried from the start that he
wasn't creative enough for Disney, like he was too much of a numbers guy.
And he's like, yeah, Bob Iger, I don't know.
He has his potential, but he's just, you know, he's too much of a numbers.
He doesn't he isn't thinking about the product.
So so Eisner thought of himself as like an avant garde artist.
And Bob Iger was this uptight guy who only knew how to do math.
No, I mean, like I wish because that would make a great like 90s drama blockbuster movie.
Sure. But but no, that's not really quite that.
I think it's more of Bob Iger is is so obsessed with the stocks and getting and getting the
board on his side. And Eisner was so obsessed with becoming Walt Disney and like being that
guy. And no, there's just it's multilayered.
I don't I don't know how to answer that. I feel very I do feel like this is an interrogation
of sorts. I was giving you a very, very broad question that I expect you to give a perfect
number response to the CEO's performance.
The polygraph is just going crazy right now.
I just imagine like Bob Iger holding a lightsaber and going like, I love this classic lightsaber
like like with Simpsons characters talking about like this lightsaber is my favorite
of all the sabers.
Hamburgers are more of a weekend food like George Bush on The Simpsons.
I think in the book I gave Michael Eisner the Disneyland Star Tours opening ribbon
cutting saber. If you remember that one.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, that severed the ribbon at the beginning.
OK. Oh, wow. You gave him a specific one that he had held in real life.
Yeah, I know. I know that was just like a throwaway joke, but that's actually something I
did. And then Bob Iger, I think, had Kylo Ren saber, if I remember correctly, maybe
just a red lightsaber. I don't know.
That makes sense. He's shepherded the Kylo Ren films.
So, yeah, yeah.
Makes sense to me.
Spoilers, I guess.
He also started the last shareholder phone call by proclaiming destroy the past, kill
it like Kylo Ren.
So and that's how we got Will Smith as the genie.
Oh, boy. I think that's going to be good.
I think we're all going to be surprised.
No, they keep doing this thing and they keep getting surprised when it doesn't work or
they they I guarantee Disney has this one VFX studio made of like 15 people that they
only use for trailers because they did the same thing with the Avengers trailer where
Hulk was running at the end of Infinity War.
But really, it was just Mark Ruffalo in the mech suit.
And so they have these these people that are doing visual effects just to throw people
off in the trailers. And they keep getting surprised with the Latin trailer because he's
like, yeah, just just make something real quick.
And they got this blue monstrosity.
And it's just for the trailer.
I'm sure the real one looks way better than that.
Isn't the rumor that they did that real quick because they released that photo of him
without the blue. Like, there's multiple photos of him, not blue.
And then everyone was like, why isn't he blue?
And they were like, no, no, he's going to be blue.
He's yes, for sure going to be blue.
Don't worry. He's going to be blue.
And then they turned around and were like, oh, my God, make him blue right now.
He has to go. Like, like, that's what I heard happened, which makes a lot of sense with
how weird some of those shots are, too, that they were just like, oh, shit, we got to
make him blue. People can be mad.
Make it the stinger at the end.
Let's reveal a major character is the state.
I mean, yeah, I don't know.
It's the the the the this is Eisner's fault again, because he made one hundred and one
Dalmatians. That's true.
He did. And the book.
Yeah, I was thinking about that the other day.
Like, that was the first live action remake.
But like, we don't really think about I mean, how often do you find yourself thinking
about the live every day?
I mean, I do like it.
Yeah. And you, Larry, a young you, Larry.
That is a movie, I think, that delivers on the promise.
Not that I'm not planning on watching one hundred and two Dalmatians anytime soon,
but I feel like it did basically deliver on the promise of the casting, like good
casting for a, you know, a significant character.
Will Will Smith as the genie go over the same way?
Well, I'll say this, it's not going to be the same because it's not going to give
the the now defunct MGM studios a wealth of behind the scenes.
Here's how Dalmatian animatronics work.
Like they went all in on showing those on monitors and stuff at the backlot tour
and like little displays and all when those movies were coming out in the 90s.
So like, here's how we made one hundred and one dogs without having to have
one hundred and one dogs on set.
And a lot of creepy animatronic puppies.
Yeah. Yeah.
Like we're like writhing around and sort of like the bend in their
bend in their lip flaps and then in a bizarre way.
Yes. Yeah. I remember being freaked out by that.
That's my Disney experience.
Your ultimate Disney attraction.
That's my version of the that's not my president meme.
That's that's my Disney experience.
Yeah. Feel free to implement that as much as you can.
You aren't seeing creepy animatronic puppies.
Just for my last question about pertaining to Michael Eisner, at least for this, is
would you purchase a like a deluxe
hundred dollar to one hundred and fifty dollar doll or figure of Michael Eisner?
Would that be something you would be interested in displaying in your home
for the purpose of the bit or in like my actual I have to actually
think about this as a purchase in my life?
Yeah. And let's put the caveat in that like it's not you can't like even get
ironic Instagram likes.
It's just for you. It's just for you and the doll to look at each other.
No, because my answer for me is yes, I would buy it one hundred one hundred fifty
bucks if it looked really good. He's got the suit on.
I would love it if it came with his desk from those opening of the
and then like Walt's desk.
But yes, it's Walt's desk.
It's exactly how he had it.
But Michael Eisner standing over it, feeling very cocky.
But yes, I would own that doll.
I think Scott agreed with me.
He would also be interested.
And he's not a big guy.
One one caveat is there a change of ties?
Yes. Oh, yeah.
These high format figures like this Batman I have here, you got different faces,
you got different outfits, you got different.
Yes. I want a big wide tie with like a Donald pattern on it
and then a big white tie with Glenn Close from Under One Dalmatians on it.
As long as I can change that those ties, I mean, three minimum, but optimally seven.
So a different tie for every day of the week.
And it's littered with accessory.
I mean, you got the it definitely comes with a beaches and cream kitchen sink.
Sunday, it comes with carpet.
Why did it come with that?
Because he loved he loved the Yacht and Beach Club.
OK, he loved the the New England sounds like the thing for your toy.
What I want.
I will buy it if it comes with all of these ties.
Yeah. OK.
Carpet samples for the Grand California Hotel.
Extra Deluxe figure comes with Breck, a child Breck.
Thank you for Star Tours, Breck.
Thank you. I just want to.
He's given like the thumbs up and there'll be like little pictures of the rides
and like Breck, you can display it.
So Breck is thumbs up being like classic rides.
Michael has a notebook in front of him with ideas and then
Splash Mountain with Darrell Hanna animatronic question mark is written on the front.
With all of these, I think the accessorizing has won Kevin over.
All right. So you're in, Kevin, is what I'm asking.
Yes. One more thing on Michael Iser, though, that I should say that he exists
within the Defunct Land series.
And if I knew if I guess if anyone's listening that hasn't watched the series,
I should you don't have to.
But this would make a lot more sense why the Eisner hate
the and it's not that I don't like Eisner.
I think the company was much more fascinating when ran by him.
I think he is a he's one of the best programmers to ever live.
Like as far as deciding what content should be created and, you know,
cultivating and pushing that content to be its best.
He was one of the worst CEOs because he didn't understand business.
He doesn't. And when he focused on it, I still don't think he really understood it
in that in that time period, or he was just too unfocused.
But in all seriousness, I do prefer the company under Michael Eisner.
I'm a big Don Tatum guy, though.
So I would say Eisner over Eiger, but I'm Tatum all the way.
So when was the Tatum one?
What years was that?
Oh, my gosh, I just had to look it up because I said it out loud.
I was like, you stumped me with Don Tatum.
It sort of rings a bell.
Oh, my gosh.
See, he was
CEO until 1976.
He was right after Roy.
So because Walt Disney was never the CEO of Walt Disney.
So from 1971 to 1976, he was the head of the company.
OK, what is so? Yeah.
Wait, where was the Don Tatum guy right here?
Where was E.
Card Walker during that time period?
Wasn't he the head after that?
After that. OK.
OK. So I'm trying to make a run.
Like, what are some films in the Don Tatum era?
I mean, like, he probably probably a couple of love bugs.
Did Herbie go bananas in the Tatum era?
Well, let's see.
I'm sure her herbie did go bananas in the Tatum era.
He did not.
Unfortunately, that was that was all herbie went bananas for Walker.
I believe herbie will only go bananas for Walker.
I'll tell you this right now.
Well, I got a list in front of me now.
The barefoot executive, maybe based on his own experience, if he was such a cool guy.
Was he like a Jimmy Buffett type?
Might have been the type.
I've been to this is the early 70s.
Oh, yeah. Even such a thing as a Buffett type.
Yeah. The million dollar duck.
Of course, the biscuit eater, you know, like Jason's favorites.
Oh, the biscuit eater is about it.
It is about a dog. That explains it.
I pull up the poster and it's about a dog.
World's greatest athlete, super herbie road again during his era.
The hell is the Bears and I, the Bears and I, starring Chief Dan George.
Most movies don't start chief.
So like that, I'll be honest, I have I have never heard of most of these.
Yeah, which that's something.
Oh, but here we go.
Apple. Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Now, that's what I like.
Yeah. Apple dumpling game.
So just for having given us Apple dumpling gang.
And what's going on in the parks in the Tatum era?
Well, Walt Disney World's coming out.
Oh, yeah. That's one. Yes. Good point.
So this is actually where Tatum does come in is Epcot is heavily developed.
Or this is the time where so and I'm going to explore this in season three.
But I always consider Epcot Walt Disney's Rosebud.
He just like shouted it before he died.
And everyone was like, what the hell does that mean?
And so for like, you know, the next 10 years, people were like,
did he mean like a real city or was this like a scale model of a city?
And I don't know.
And so that he spent a lot of that time, like, you know, talking to the state
of Florida and the state of Florida being like, please don't build a city.
And he's like, I don't want to build a city
for that whole thing.
So that was a really that was a really interesting time for the parks.
Hmm. And clearly they finally correct what Walt wanted.
When it became a display of upcoming Sega games
that finally crystallized his vision.
Walt Disney envisioned Sega the entire thing in the moments before he died.
And they finally got it.
Mickey and Sonic together.
OK, so season three, we got Tatum, we got we got the death of Disney.
Anything anything else you can tease or that you're starting to think about?
So I separated into seasons and people were like, this is why are you doing this?
This means nothing.
And it means something to me.
And that's all that matters.
Season two is very much about season two is like headline.
Attraction would be journey into imagination.
It's all about creativity and the what the creative process can yield
and what obstacles can get in the way of the creative process
and the results of the creative process.
And, you know, in the in the medium of theme parks, theme entertainment and whatnot.
And it's also a look into what businesses have the ability to do
two things such as creativity and all that jazz.
And so season three would be more about the future and the views of the future.
And and so that's more of the Epcot kind of idea.
So I guess the headline would be Horizons.
I'm not sure if I'm going to do it for that season, but Horizons would be that
attraction where we're all we're talking about, you know, we're going to World's Fair.
I don't want to spoil too much because I know everyone's on the edge of their seat.
But yeah, so that would be my explanation of that.
And season one was a mistake.
I mean, do you have do you have like a multi like season arc?
Like, do you have like a series finale in mind?
Like what the last season of Defunct Land?
How far in advance do you think about this type of thing?
I think season to season and I do have a series finale in mind.
And it might be at the end of season three.
We will see. Oh, really?
I might be wrapping it up. Wow.
Well, is it just so I can reboot it, just so I can be like the new class and it'll be
all right. Right. Yeah, I see.
With a different person.
Yeah, reboots are in vogue. That's a smart move.
That's good. And Screech will be involved.
The whole thing. Yeah.
Well, you that you have the that you are thinking in a bigger way and do have a season
finale in mind that puts you a notch ahead of Vince Gilligan.
He just figured it out as he went.
So you're I'll declare it here.
Kevin Perger, superior to Vince Gilligan.
Yeah, better showrunner.
I appreciate that and agree with it more more so.
Yeah. Happily take that and just own it.
You know, it's a question I had for you also is, you know, because we're both in us, us
with our theme park podcast and you with your theme park video series.
We all we all have to we all have to think about topics and figure out, you know, how
much how much meat is on the bone.
And is that just a thing that's part of an episode or does that sustain a couple of
episodes? Is there anything about your process that you can tell us?
And specifically, have you ever like started a video and gone, there's not enough there.
That was a trip to nowhere.
Yes, I have started videos and I talk I talked about this in a recent one of my podcasts
where I I you know, that becomes a challenge for me where I say, well, I'm going to I can
make it interesting because, you know, I can make anything interesting.
And then you realize that I would know you can't that you're not that talented.
No, sometimes no one's that talented to make certain things interesting.
And what I've come to is in some situations and I should pull up just my
I keep it all on Google Docs, which is a great business suite.
But I can I can scroll and see if I have any that I just haven't done.
But what it comes down to for me is if the people that are supposed to be interested
are not involved or not, you know, if they're if if they as people do not have their
mind focused on this park or ride, there's probably not a story there because you don't
have any characters. So for for instance, I gave so Wonderland Sydney,
is an episode on an Australian theme park that closed down.
It was it was absorbed by a company for business purposes and then abandoned for business
purposes. They didn't care about it at all.
Purely a business transaction. It's like the bakery didn't make it.
There's no story there. Like, that's all it is.
But there was a huge fan base that was just like crying on the last day.
And that was like, OK, that's a story.
You know, people are involved. People care.
This was this affected people. But if I know and it's and usually in the theme park sphere,
people really care. So it's really great.
But sometimes they don't.
OK, here's actually an example. Wow.
Never mind. So the arcade is something I've always wanted to do.
The arcade, if you can guess, is was the arcade on the Disney cruise line ship Disney
Dream and it was removed and replaced with Vanellope's Sweet Shop themed to Wreck-It-Ralph,
which is ironic. And that irony, because it was an arcade and Wreck-It-Ralph is.
Yeah. But the but that irony was not enough, believe it or not, to drive a 12 to 24 minute
episode unless I gave the entire history of the Disney Cruise Line, which was actually the
purpose for the episode to begin with, because I love the Disney Cruise Line.
But yeah, did you experience the arcade yourself?
Oh, I mean, it was it was an experience.
You know, it had the sign outside that had a little parrot sitting on it and said arcade
with like three or four hours. And I was like, whoa.
And I go inside and it's this it's a small arcade.
And then I played a game or two.
And then I left. I was like, wow, that was the arcade.
You're saying that wasn't enough for 20 minutes.
Yeah, that was not enough for 20 minutes.
I couldn't find the imagine here behind the arcade, which was another thing.
I'm sure there was there was a lot of drama at the time of how are we going to how are
we going to accomplish the arcade?
Although, you know, I do want to do an episode now that I'm just on this for some reason.
I do want to do an episode on all the arcade puns.
I don't know if I've mentioned this before at all to anyone or maybe even you.
But for some reason, this sounds familiar.
But I want to do the starcade, the arcade.
Oh, I'm sure there's more.
What was the arcade in the contemporary called?
Or is it still there? It is still there.
Most of the hotel ones are still there.
They don't have fun names, I feel like.
Maybe they do. Maybe you can set it all to music from the red hot chili peppers
stadium, Arcadian.
That's that's my note for you.
Yeah, I'd like to see 20 minutes just
determining how many hours there were in the pirate themed.
No, I mean, what?
That's not the point of it.
That was the yeah, it's on a boat.
It's got a lot of hours. There's a parrot like.
I mean, that was it. That was the whole thing.
It was the the parrot had an eye patch.
I think. But when you get.
Sorry, I was going to say, it does sound like it's enough for us to do an hour
second gate episode on it, though, if it just has a parrot with an eye patch.
Like that's enough for us to think in the world of comedy podcasting.
You just go. You don't think about it.
Too hard. Wow.
You should. We yes.
Yeah, we yes. And that's why they're all so good.
Do you know? I mean, I that's how my my good friend, Disney Dan, makes videos.
He brags about it all the time.
Sometimes he just did a video.
He does the costume character revolutions, if you've ever seen those. Oh, yeah.
And he's like, I didn't even write a script for that one.
I just started talking.
And I was like, that's that. OK.
That's like Ken Burns being like, I didn't even research the similar.
I just started talking.
Then here we are on episode eight.
I feel like I've heard like Jay-Z or something like I don't write the rap
they just come out of my head.
Yeah. So Jay-Z and Disney Dan are very similar.
Yeah. Kevin has been skill again.
And Jay-Z, Disney Dan is Jay-Z.
Yeah, I would say that.
I think it's the analogy falls apart when you realize that, you know,
you can just make up raps like it doesn't.
Have to be based in fact.
And Dan was supposed to be making a history video, whatever.
But no, yeah, I agree.
I'll yeah, I'll give him the Jay-Z title for today.
You don't think you can successfully freestyle a history of Pluto
costumes from 1955 to today?
I mean, we're about to freestyle a history of Tarzan rocks.
So, I mean, I guess we'll find out.
I didn't do extensive research recently.
I've always been fascinated with Tarzan rocks, but I can start making up facts.
Well, well, Disney Dan it.
Well, it's just a seed of our fuck it.
Well, Disney Dan, I fuck it.
Disney D or Jay-Z.
Yeah. Well, let's let's let's start getting into it.
Let's let's start rocking, gentlemen. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm really excited.
And you you came to us with this topic and I'm.
Well, that's a question.
You talk about meat on the bone and stuff.
Do you think do you think?
Well, we can determine after this episode, perhaps.
Do you think that there is a defunct land video in Tarzan rocks?
Or is it or is it a mere podcast?
The right episode?
This this will serve as the video, most likely.
I will say there is enough because you have Tarzan and you have Animal Kingdom
and you also have the right.
So essentially, at this point in my videos, you pick a topic
that's going to be the meat and then you season it with all these other things.
So there wasn't a ton of information that I could go off of for the
I don't know if you saw the haunted castle mystery tour video
from Tokyo Disneyland for Halloween.
I did that. So, yeah, I was that was a great.
I was shocked, by the way, of then during that one.
I had no idea what that was.
Yeah, that was a super interesting.
But there wasn't a ton of the meat just explaining the right itself
on information of that.
But you can talk about the Black Cauldron and that history.
Super interesting.
And then, you know, Tokyo Disneyland a bit and its opening.
And so you can season it.
I think this is one of those things.
It was early in the park parks development.
You have the history of Tarzan as the last movie in the Disney Renaissance.
And, you know, there is a video here.
The reason I'm considering, you know, transitioning from defunct land
eventually, maybe season three, four or five and not doing this like indefinitely
is because, you know, I would start to get into like Tarzan rocks.
I could do an entire season of just like Tarzan rocks and Spider-Man rocks
and all those.
You are familiar with Spider-Man rocks.
Did you do an episode on that?
We touched on it in a stunt show episode that was one of our first four
episodes, I believe.
So we hit we have a new theme park podcast.
We got to hit Spider-Man rocks ASAP as quick as we can.
So, yeah, we know all about it.
Yeah, you do the rock season like, hey, we're helping.
We're part of it. We're doing all the voices you need.
We're making up songs for you. We're scoring.
That's that's our wheelhouse.
You're fighting over who gets to be Hard Rock Park CEO John Benkowski.
Like, no, I'm going to do Benkowski.
Oh, yeah, that's that's what ends us.
The fight to be Benkowski friendships over.
I think you get Benkowski to do his own voice.
Yeah, he could do it.
This is actually a great idea.
Now that I think about it, I'll do rock season defunct land rocks, defunct
land rocks, defunct land rocks.
Please make it happen.
I will be Winston the punk rock dog, though.
That famous character, you know, the famous character from the Hard Rock Park,
Winston, the punk rock dog.
Come on, Kevin.
No, he's a famous character.
I looked in these episodes, need characters.
And with that park, you have Winston.
So it writes itself.
You have Winston and you have the amazing bare metal family.
They were like the country bears, but they rocked and the acrobatic roadies.
That's true, too. Yeah.
Which, yeah, that's fitting.
This show is very acrobatic.
It sure is.
I would say the I would like to just to butt in and say that the country bears do rock.
And that that was a offensive comparison to put down the bears like that.
If you see the movie, the country bears.
That's right. I think, Kevin, you and I share the same love of country bears.
When it's so good.
When that evil Zack Ryder was trashing Disney World Rides, I was OK.
Carousel Progress, I really like a lot.
But then when he said the country bears was kind of boring or the robots world,
I did share your anger.
And he did. He was a real heel when he said that.
And I you and I, we're going to do multiple country bears episodes.
My co-hosts aren't even prepared for what I will eventually propose to them
in regards to length and amount.
The question is, do we even have to be here or can you just talk for four hours
straight without assistance?
Do you already have the audio?
He's just been recording it.
I feel every night.
What I do is I put a little candle by the bed and I bring the recorder
in the bed with me and I just talk about one of the characters for two hours
and I go to sleep during that.
Like I I drift off to sleep at that point.
And that's where you wear, sir.
He wears three petticoats and each more lovely than the last.
Good night, Trixie.
This is why this is why Lindsay sleeps in a separate bedroom.
Like you are some rich old money weirdos.
Liver lips, mackerel.
Ah, I do down out there.
So I do have a quick country bear story that also involves Disney, DJ, Disney, Dan.
We were at the parks in the other during Christmas.
So like during like, you know, the time you're not supposed to go.
And it was crazy.
And the country bears was packed because the park was packed.
It was it was it was amazing.
And Dan, we get in there.
We are in the back row of the theater and everyone's quiet.
You know, they're getting ready for the the the cast member to start the like
the puns before we get started.
And we're standing up as we're walking in with the last ones to sit down.
Dan still standing, starts clapping and he says, we're about to give these bears.
He does not speak like this normally.
He just did this for this this part.
He said, we're about to give these bears the best costume performance
I've ever seen. They've been practicing all week.
Let's give it up for these bears.
And the amount of confused Brazilians in that room was more than usual
for Orlando at the time.
But we did get a large portion of the crowd to start cheering for the bears
as if they like it, get them to come on stage.
It was a fantastic moment.
So definitely next time you're at the Jamboree,
try to get the crowd a little riled up beforehand.
The bears love it. They've been practicing for a while.
I think that's great.
Orlando, some of the crowds are a little lackluster.
Not the case in Tokyo, though.
They were to see those robots.
Yeah. Standing out.
Not a standing out, but they were definitely like clapped
and they were they were hungry for those bears.
Thank God. Beautiful.
Well, but let's talk about some some different
rock and animals here a little bit.
Tarzan Rocks. So so Animal Kingdom opens a couple of live shows when it began.
There was a Jungle Book live show, I believe, initially.
And a couple of years into the run, they traded out
in ninety nine to promote the
then new Disney animated film Tarzan,
with, of course, the Phil Collins score.
Did you guys get a chance to see this?
Who saw it in person? I never saw it in person.
I have no idea if I saw it in person or not.
I cannot remember.
I would have been I would.
You know what? I don't think I'm saying this.
I don't know if I would.
Maybe we saw it. I have no memory of it whatsoever.
Watching it. And I also watched a a pretty good quality video of it.
And I have to give the person credit because they cut together two performances
for this video.
And but the only difference is the main narrator has
one of them as bright blonde hair and one of them is very bald.
So it very much gave the feeling of like in The Shining,
when the shots go back and forth and furniture has moved like that unease
Kubrick was trying to create kind of happened when I watched the video
of Disney Rocks. But the The Shining reference is interesting
because I was actually thinking The Shining because the Jungle Book
show that came before this,
Baloo looks like Blo Bear from The Shining,
the bear performing oral sex on a man in a hotel room.
You mean? Yes.
I mean, have you seen have any of you looked up the Jungle Book,
the one that came before this? No, no, no, I haven't.
Do you have a computer? Google it. It's amazing.
They didn't. It's not full body costumes.
It's full body minus just the face.
You what? What?
Weird. I was thrown in.
I mean, in the Tarzan one, because Turk is an actual like,
you know, character like a walk around character.
Oh, my God. By the way, audience, you all know Turk.
You know, Turk, right?
Rosie O'Donnell's beloved, beloved scene stealing.
Every Disney animal steals all the scenes, steals all the scenes,
especially terms it up when Turk trashes the camp.
Also, Kevin, very bold of you to declare this the end of the Disney
Renaissance, like that this is what I what was to that was 2000 dinosaur.
Was that what was that the next big release?
Sorry, I'm trying to play this jungle book so we can get a picture of the horror.
I see. So there were there were there was a version of the Jungle Book
where they they had a face, I guess.
But the there was an earlier version where there was no face and it was creepy.
But but yeah, this would be the end of the Disney Renaissance, I believe,
because this is Disney post Renaissance starts in 2000
with I know I just know Tarzan is the is the end.
You consider it and that it's it's hand drawn.
It's still like it's not it's it's Tarzan well regarded.
Where do we where does it really land on?
Well, it's not I don't even think it's like a consideration.
I thought that this was just the way they were deemed.
Like I thought that was just the errors.
I didn't know. Yeah.
Is it up for debate? Well, I'm talking personal.
Yeah, how does everybody feel about the film Tarzan?
I remember I saw I've seen it once.
I we don't we did not own it on VHS.
I saw it. I remember liking it, but I remember it was what?
Ninety seven, ninety eight, ninety nine.
Ninety nine. Is it ninety nine?
Geez. I remember thinking I didn't need those animals talking.
I remember, but I remember thinking it was kind of a decent, like almost
adultish cartoon, like a more of a, you know, a little bit more of a mature
kind of a story. There's a hanging in it for God's sake.
Was there? Yeah.
The bad guy gets hanged at the end, I believe.
Oh, is that right? Kevin, can you confirm?
How many? This is going to be my role.
I was just someone did.
Someone was killed.
Yeah, no, I can't confirm that that happened.
There they also it also starts with a double murder.
And then it's not just like by the tiger, I believe.
And then the tiger chases after Tarzan.
So it wasn't just like an off screen like and then the ship didn't make it.
It was like, oh, no, this tiger murdered your parents.
And then the tiger is going to chase you for the rest of the like.
I liked it. I remember liking it, but I didn't.
It didn't make such a crazy impression on me.
I thought the Phil Collins song was fine.
I like the Phil Collins song now, but it was not such a big moment in my life.
Yes. So this is multiple songs.
My friend. Excuse me.
I'm just saying the big one.
The the major. Yes.
I refuse. I refuse to acknowledge one as better than the others.
I'm so sorry. They're all equally amazing.
They're one distinct musical piece like Queen's Night at the Opera.
It's a sweet. It's all one thing. Yeah.
So You'll Be in My Heart is a this one.
The Academy Award for Best Original Song that year, as well as the Golden Globe,
beating out South Park's Blame Canada and Amy Mann's Save Me.
Is this was this a correct decision?
That's a good question.
Now, I will say, since watching this, I have had these songs
stuck in my head for a few days, but say beating out Save Me is
Save Me is a really great song.
It's such a great song. Not in consideration, although the General Tarzan
soundtrack did win a Best Original Soundtrack Grammy.
So in that regard, the entire suite was represented.
So Phil Collins raking in awards from the score.
How many times can I burst into one of the Phil Collins?
How many times can I do a terrible Phil Collins impression before people will stop
listening and unsubscribe from my videos?
I was I was threatening the same thing in the episode
to my wife, who encouraged me to not.
But I kept thinking if somebody if one of you presented a factoid
of something interesting, I wanted to I wanted to always go, I want to know
and show me I want to know about the Tarzan Rock show.
So my personal thing with Tarzan, I what is it?
I want to know.
There we go. I'm glad I could say you're already old.
Much like I cannot remember if I saw this show,
I cannot remember if I saw the movie in theaters.
I believe we had the soundtrack because I mean, the soundtrack sold a lot of copies
on vinyl. Yeah, probably on vinyl.
That's the best way to hear a son of man's song.
Trash in the camp really pops.
Neil Young was really mad about Son of Man's audio quality when it was on MP3.
Yeah. That's why you had to get Pono for.
We were a cassette family for too long.
My mother would not fudge from the cassettes.
What year did you get a CD player?
When I was in eighth grade, so like probably 98, 99.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Wow. And I had to argue for it.
Like I had to to fight for it.
So, yeah, I but my my childhood association with Tarzan was the Johnny Weiss
Mueller animatronic in the great movie ride.
But those were not the movies I saw.
I saw it out, you know, singing in the rain.
I did not seek out the Johnny Weiss Mueller Tarzan.
But so I really didn't get a craving for it.
You didn't leave Disney World going more Weiss Mueller, Mother Miller, more Jane.
No, not really.
And I think even as like a kid, because what I would have been just starting high
school, I think I would have been coherent and not to go like this.
This Tarzan have dreadlocks.
Is this a white guy with dreadlocks?
Because you knew this was cultural appropriation even in even at 13 or whatever.
Well, I don't think we use that term, but I think I just knew like, oh, this is weird
that this is going to be a one of the biggest movies of the year.
And sure.
Yeah, it's Tarzan.
Why the marriage of Phil Collins and Tarzan?
Like musically, these things don't really overlap.
I don't. I think he did.
I think he made an admirable attempt at being the omniscient musical narrator
of the tale. If you haven't seen Tarzan, the characters don't sing.
He just sings for them.
I don't know.
I think it's an interesting choice.
All I said was an admirable attempt.
I'm not saying it was good, although the Academy said as much.
Can I say this little bit of Phil Collins Oscar trivia that it was interesting to me?
He was nominated for Against All Odds in 1985 in a stacked year.
Other nominees. Let's hear it for the boy Footloose.
I just called to say I love you.
And there's another really good one that's Ghostbusters.
That's got to be one of the best five ever in that category.
And the Academy looked at who was nominated and they said this Phil Collins.
Now, who is this?
Oh, he's one of the most popular musicians of the time.
Well, look, we're really more of a movie award show.
And I don't know if we want this music guy.
We have a big presence on our show.
Meanwhile, Phil Collins had rerouted his tour to like
I'm going to cancel some dates so that I can be at the Oscars.
He's there. Can't wait to perform.
The Academy says, no, you can't.
And they got some friggin choreographer to sing Against All Odds instead of him.
And he's just sitting in the audience watching a performance at which,
if you watch it, is terrible.
It's an awful performance in the same year that Ray Parker Jr.,
who for some reason was allowed to perform.
Well, yeah, like, what is that logic?
And Denise Williams performed.
So they count as movie people, but the Academy is like,
can't wrap their heads around getting Phil Collins to actually play.
So he's sitting there.
He's watching this.
Meanwhile, Ray Parker Jr.
does this really bizarre Ghostbusters performance that's interrupted by like
Borsch Belt, Three Stooges Ghostbusters, who are dressed, of course,
in the iconic bright blue, shiny uniforms.
So with giant silver shoulder pads.
Yeah. Why? Ray Parker at one point shoots magic out of his finger like Mickey
and blows up a ghost.
So Oscars are over.
Phil Collins loses to I just called to say I love you.
He they ask him, what do you think of the performance of your song?
He said it was shit.
But I'm kind of glad I didn't have to perform after what they made Ray Parker do.
So they just totally pissed all over.
If like if you're watching the current Academy Awards debacle and thinking
that's the worst thing the Academy's ever done.
Yeah, yeah. I don't like the the Academy Awards have always been
really wrongheaded and stupid.
But could you imagine them now so desperate for ratings going like Lady Gaga?
You are not singing shallow. Absolutely not.
Yeah. Well, I don't know.
Their decisions have been so inexplicable and shitty lately. Yeah.
No. Yeah. I think today they would just give like 30 minutes
of the broadcast to Phil Collins.
I do come whatever you want, please.
It'll be after our tribute to the Lifetime Achievement Award for Brian Singer.
I'm Kevin. You were saying a quick thing on Ray Parker Junior before this.
This goes away forever.
Is the I I share revenue.
So whenever someone copyright claims a video for music or video,
you know, they have options. They can either take all my money.
They can or they can put a copyright strike strike on me.
They can do nothing or they can share revenue.
So we both receive revenue.
I've only been I've had none of those things happen, maybe ignoring,
but only one time have I shared revenue with anything.
And that person is Ray Parker Junior for the Ghostbusters
spectacular episode of Defunctland.
What's interesting is it's not a company.
So it's not like Universal Media Corp.
It is Ray Parker Junior.
So if you click on that video, what comes up is says you're sharing revenue
with Ray Parker Junior, and it's the funniest just image.
Oh, so you just got an email one day saying there's been a copyright claim.
Oh, what? By BMI? No, by Ray Parker, by Ray Parker Junior.
Not a company at all.
And he didn't he didn't want all the money.
He just wanted to share some of it.
Just a little bit.
I mean, I mean, great.
I was strange. Wow.
So but on the Tarzan thing, before I forget this, too, I.
So it's interesting.
We have a running theme of improving
the of improving like episodes through this podcast for some reason.
I was looking up and so I was going to make a joke.
I was like, you know, it sounds like Phil Collins is improving these lines
in the like in the songs because he because some of them don't make sense.
He's like, in learning, you will teach
and teaching you will learn.
Like, you know, it's like the Dana Carvey
Chopin Broccoli, where he's making up the song on the spot
with executives over his shoulder.
But that is how he came up with some of these.
So it is. It is.
Yeah, I just read that it came from improv sessions
and his reactions while reading the treatment.
So he literally got up there and he's like, so man, I'm going to sky.
And then he's like, I'm going to sky in the next one.
Or I'm assuming it's British or something.
And anyways, I mean, this whole thing.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, it's you know, it's strange to tie back in the copyright claim thing.
I have some experience with specifically the song two worlds
and the performance of it in this video for any any listeners
who are the rare, beautiful bird of who is a fan of both podcasts, right?
And the clip cup franchise.
There is a video that I did
the full title clip cup four point live campus, Columbus,
a live edition of a video that a video series I was part of in which we
it was a live show, so we needed to finish it with, you know, a big, glorious,
you know, you know, just just a big spectacular finale.
And this was shot where I went to college, Loyola Marymount.
We finished this thing with a huge performance of two worlds by Phil Collins,
which we wanted to do a sound like, you know, just like something
with the two worlds vibe, just make this out of nowhere.
This thing feels like Tarzan rocks.
All of a sudden we realized what sound alike is ever going to give you
the pure raw magic of two worlds, one family with what that did result in
is the video being pulled from Funny or Dice YouTube channel
due to a copyright claim by by Phil Collins, maybe not Phil Collins himself,
but by whatever whatever owns the Walt Disney, I would imagine.
Anyway, if now you want to see an even more stirring performance of two worlds,
then the Tarzan rocks version, it's exclusively available on view.
Bu dot com vi o bu dot com two worlds, one family.
Anyways, litigiousness runs rampant and many pieces of work.
So but because of that, I do have this fondness, particularly for for two worlds.
There's something sort of like, I don't know, which one.
What song do we like the most out of these?
If you had to declare one, you'll be I think I like the you'll be in my heart.
So still you'll be in my heart.
My toughest time with that one's kind of like a little like,
I don't know, that's that's like a sleepy ballad to me.
I think I discovered I think I actually ended up over researching this dig.
And I want to know, can you show me?
That's not the name I know.
I like that, too, though. I don't want to put it.
I don't it's not like by heads and shoulders like in my mind.
Sure. All the same zone of, you know, Kevin, I feel like you're not a fan
of any of this from. No, no, no. I love them all.
That's the thing is the only the saving grace of this film,
because I remember seeing it and being like, why is this?
Why do they make a sad version of George of the Jungle?
I mean, which I think came out before, right?
Is that right? In the same time, right around the same time.
And apparently Brendan Fraser did read for Tarzan.
Who the hell is Tarzan?
Doing you know who it is?
It's the actor who plays the president on Scandal. Oh, yeah.
Strange. Forget his name.
But I thought that was just such an odd thing.
Yeah. Also, if you go to the Wikipedia page,
the story by credit is given to
nine, 12, 15, 18, 21.
People have story by credits on Tarzan.
Wow. Wow. 21.
Like this being, you know, an old book.
Like how many people needed to crack the story of a preexisting old book?
Right. Yeah. Well, I mean, I guess back in the day, what they I mean,
my Michael Isers wanted to get rid of this when he came into the company.
But, you know, when they were making really great movies in the dark age
after Disney's death, I mean, they were doing it the way they always had,
which is they didn't.
They just had the halls lined with with paper and just like that.
Every every single frame or every storyboard of the animatics they created.
They didn't write scripts.
And if they need to change something in the story,
they just walk down the hall and change that part of the story
and put up a new piece of paper with what's happening on screen.
Oh, gosh. So it might be a situation like that.
But sorry, back to the soundtrack.
OK, I don't want to keep derailing because I'm just reading this fascinating
Wikipedia page.
Well, I yeah, that Wikipedia page, I the filmmakers talk
so much about two worlds, one family is really the core idea of the movie.
And it just gets repeated.
So every all the writing about the movie, it's like you have to understand
the hands, the symbol, the symbol is the hands.
Two worlds, one family.
It's just like, Jesus Christ, you're really hitting the nail on the head.
And then in the show, of course.
By the way, I don't know how much we've said this is like not so much.
This is if you've seen like the Beauty and the Beast musical at Disney,
where it's not like that.
It's not like that.
No, no, no. That's what I'm saying is there's, you know, it's not like a
a series of scenes from the film condensed into a live show.
This is a rock concert. All right.
There's a band visible on stage.
And when they in about a couple of songs in, they introduce themselves
and they say that this is the two worlds concert tour
where we all come together for this journey to begin.
What can I can I can I describe the first like five minutes of this performance?
Because I've watched it like 20 times and I'm like, please do.
Yeah. On the soundtrack, I do love the soundtrack.
I cannot I can only remember the song I've heard last
because they all sound the same to me until I hear them.
And then like, oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's just like, yeah, it's just a heart, a heartwarming Belton.
And if anything I've learned from Tarzan Rocks,
it's that these songs are only good if Phil Collins is singing them.
Yeah, it's the only thing that works about that soundtrack.
And when it's kind of like three barely harmonize and,
you know, Florida performers.
Yeah, it's rougher.
Phil Collins has figured out the encryption of music
and that no cover will even be possible if it's not sung by him.
He's created a musical style that only works with his voice.
But the I guess the first five minutes, the it starts with saying like,
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Tarzan Rocks.
And it's in the theater in the wild, which is currently
we're finding Nemo the musical is just at the stage.
This is pre Everest or I think that's where.
Yeah. Which it's like, oh, yeah, this is this is Animal Kingdom.
And it's not a zoo still.
And so you you have the guy come on.
You have Tarzan Rocks and big letters.
Also, this is not enclosed.
I should mention that because there's, you know, back in the day,
this thing was not finding Nemo the musical.
It wasn't all enclosed.
So you are outside technically.
It's an open air amphitheater like the Hollywood Bowl.
You see a concert.
Yeah, I mean, it's a concert.
It's a concert for this.
The two worlds tour.
I mean, this is Leeds.
Am I at live at Leeds with the who?
Is this the Isle of Rite?
This place looks rockin.
You're at Bonnaroo, man.
And it's it starts similar to how Mickey's film our magic starts
in that there's like there's characters off screen.
So if Mickey's farm magic starts with, you know, goofy being like,
and he like, you know, walks up the stairs and does all that, it's cool.
This one does not start like that.
This one starts with audio clips from the movie.
Nothing has indicated that the show is starting.
These people might as well be saying, like, put on your 3D glasses or watch out.
But it's like literally just clips of being like Tarzan.
He's he's he's a man.
And it's like it's like unrelated.
And then the the characters like come through the aisles like the.
And I guess this is when we can we can someone else can describe,
because I'm not going to do it justice.
What these these animals, I guess,
the trapeze artists or the roller skaters, I don't know.
Someone please help me to describe.
OK, so they're kind of like they kind of look like
the more locks in any production of the time machine,
be it stage or screen, like they're kind of ape like,
but they're also kind of like just generic, like there's I mean,
they're supposed to look like great apes, but they are on roller blades.
They they kind of look like the shrub people who hide in yards and
like like as part of a SWAT team and attack people.
But if they shaved just like 70 percent of their on body shrubbery.
Yeah, like a ghillie suit.
Yeah, there's felt ghillie suits mixed with rollerblades.
I just immediately was like, oh, Starlight Express.
Yeah, oh, putties like some of the pariaginic putties.
They kind of reset the Power Rangers had.
Yeah, in case you don't know, goons that were called putties, like the
turtles had foot soldiers and they were just people that were going to get
the shit kicked out of them. But yeah, they were.
Yeah, very scary. They looked a little better.
They that's a little darker, a little better.
That that's kind of what these guys look like. Yeah. Mm hmm.
So they're they're running around and the stage just gets populated.
Yeah, just it's already full and the curtains haven't even opened yet.
Immediately full.
Uh huh. Just just so we're clear,
Tarzan does not show up until 14 minutes.
No, we're on minute three of my explanation.
Minute three. The lead.
And he any like any leaves about three minutes later.
Yes, Tarzan barely present in Tarzan Rocks.
It's really weird.
But who is present is like a guy who I I describe as a glam Ryan Styles.
That's the singer of the band.
My description would be Craig Kilburn,
just regular with no regular Craig Kilburn.
Regular Craig Kilburn.
While people are doing Cirque du Soleil
s acrobatics everywhere on stage like this is also not to jump around too much
because Kevin, I think you were building to the moment where, yeah, there's acrobat,
there's ropes and skaters like what's going on?
We walked into a Cirque du Soleil franchise, what's happening?
And then a big guitar hit.
A second curtain opens behind the first curtain.
Or it's more of a tarp drops
revealing scaffolding with a multi-layer scaffolding with a bunch of musicians on it.
And it's very much in that Jesus Christ superstar.
Yes. Mold or the musicians are on stage.
This isn't some Rodgers and Hammerstein.
There is rock on stage with you.
And scaffolding also of the time, rent, I believe rent uses scaffolding.
That's a very 90s thing.
But it's very renty.
And I imagined somebody in the Disney organization having to pitch like
there's something there is a movement happening in New York theater right now.
I don't know if you know about it.
There's this little play called Rent, and it is revolutionized the way people
are having to bring the bringing the culture of rent to the family friendly
organization of Disney.
There's like a model and they like pull it, pull it off like multi-tiered staging.
But wait a minute, that's just scaffolding.
Why haven't you dressed it yet?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Also, that this is a musical.
Yeah, like I don't know if we fully explain the Beauty and the Beast
like show that used to be at MGM Studio.
Is it still there at Hollywood Studios?
Probably.
I mean, that's that's the that's Tony Baxter, the book report kind of version
like the abridged version.
You get the story, you get the songs with the show, though it is a book report.
Yeah, I but this is more like a jukebox music like like the leader of the pack
or like whatever that Billy Joel one moving out like this Jersey boys, the
spirit, the spirit of it.
And it's it's a menagerie of songs.
There I was a young ape man with my whole life ahead of me.
Little Johnny Tarzan.
Yeah. And I have to give credit like you pay for Phil Collins.
You want to get your money's worth, you know, you want to get those songs in there.
You want to get your use of them.
So we kick immediately into two worlds.
But as Kevin said, a little a little it's not the vocal force of.
We've got Craig Kilmore and he's backed up by like the choice of their style.
I wrote down they're kind of like Meredith Brooks, the singer of the song,
Bitch. Yeah, yeah, there's two Meredith brothers in there in like leather trench
coats and bustiers.
It yeah, I don't know how the stage is full.
And that's the thing that I can't get over is how full the stage is.
Very busy. Yeah, very busy.
I mean, this is a great encapsulation of a thing I think I brought up before,
which is like the the theme park idea of rock and roll.
Like it's where it's very it's it's inoffensive.
It's got the tenets of rock and roll, but there's nothing really.
It just kind of is.
It works with the basics, such as coming out, asking how people are doing,
receiving a response, saying, I think you can do better than that.
Asking again and the response being higher.
To answer your question, the backup singer is like kind of pirate ask
like a lot of lacy, long, slipping sleeves.
You know, in general, this video reminded me of the thing that we experienced
in Buena Park, California, the Pirates Dinner Adventure.
And that it has people on ropes and acrobatics.
And it made me wonder why we as a society don't value acrobatics more.
Why are we not impressed by acrobatics?
I know it's really hard to do.
It's it's so impressive.
The the the full all around body strength of these people.
And yet a theme park show with a ton of acrobatics you leave going is OK.
Well, I would argue that perhaps this is not on the artistic level of a Cirque
de Soleil. That would be my argument.
This might not be a show as well thought out as something
that Tarzan and Jane stuff with the the silk where I forget what that term
exactly is, but they're using the sheet there.
They are like just holding themselves up and soaring around the stage
with these sheets and they're just wrapped around their arms.
That was a there was a very similar part.
Exactly the same, I guess, in the Pirates.
Pirates. And it was impressive there.
It was. It's a very impressive thing.
It's used to convey, I think, lovemaking.
I think it's a sex like it's a stand in for that.
But it is a very physically impressive feat.
Those of us who've had sex know that when you have it,
it feels exactly like soaring through the clouds while gripping onto a fabric.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Your massive forearm strength is required.
It is interesting.
It's all in the forearms.
The dulcet tones of a khaki wearing open shirted man.
Khaki. Yeah.
Semi-formal like this is this is me going out to a semi-formal dance.
I really did not want to be at in high school.
Why do you think there was a version of Tarzan rocks on the
in the blue sky period where this man had a Tarzan outfit on,
at least like a loincloth type thing?
I would imagine that would have to have been like a certain point.
They're like, well, let's make it a kind of a jungle band
as opposed to dress like Mark McGrath.
Yes, you're right. He's a very McGrath as well.
Well, the same guy who passionately pitched rent also said,
there's a movement happening in music right now.
Let me two words, sugar ray.
If we don't capital, if we don't incorporate sugar
ray into the parks, the teens are going to have our asses.
It's I also it's a rare opportunity in a Disney show
to see a performer wearing a big watch.
Mostly doesn't happen.
Mostly they got to leave their watches backstage.
Yeah. And he's really like showcasing the watch
with a big fist and like pulling it down, like, look at the watch.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
It's it's it's really bizarre.
Kevin, we're watching this right now.
Also, just on mute,
which is perhaps the way you should watch Tarzan rocks is on mute.
But just, you know, we're commenting on things sort of as we see them,
such as the two two identically dressed
khaki guys like sort of like standing side by side, one with a guitar,
one with a bass, but like that lame bass, like the six string bit,
like the sting bass, you know what I mean?
And it's like you got to wear it way high up.
And that's not a cool look with for rock and roll for most part, I think.
And there are multiple guitar and bass solos in this.
And at one point, I believe the rate rollerbladers jump over the guy
doing a guitar solo.
And I think in the version I watched that the audience went nuts.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, that's yeah, that is something happened. Yeah.
Because the thing that still I mean, if this was a comedy sketch,
if this was maybe something more free loose than SNL,
but if this was like an actual comedy sketch, there would be like the
the monkey man doing roller skating would be how it starts.
And then the tarp reveal for the Phil Collins would be a good
lead into the next one.
And then it would keep escalating with like, you know, there would be people
dressed in giant gorilla costumes wearing like sunglasses,
like shooting guns into the air.
And then the audience would just be camels.
I mean, it would just I mean, it just it would keep escalating.
If it was like cartoon, like, you know, adult swim, like this is something,
you know, I'm just it's and it almost is there.
It almost gets there.
And the thing is that every time they bring a new elements into the show,
they like half it like these roller skating moves aren't that impressive
other than the one where they jump over.
But like they're really just like going up the ramp
and then they're going down the ramp.
Like, OK, I just watched one that was pretty impressive.
But they're doing they're doing what you expect out of a roller blader
and not above and beyond.
Sure. I would like to pitch you if you're talking about
like plusing it and adding it.
I want poachers on unicycles.
This is a component here.
See, yeah, stuff like that would totally totally fit with this.
If this was made up, like if this was made for the purpose
of being ridiculous and humor.
I think, yeah, sorry, keep going.
No, go ahead. I'm I was just going to say, I think like the movie,
this show should start with two murders.
I think that that would be a really exciting way to get it started.
And it can be it can be, you know, shown through acrobatics.
It doesn't have to be a graphic thing.
OK, somehow we have not discussed Tarzan, Tarzan, like Edgar Rice Burroughs.
It is so weird, Disney and like the mid to late 90s.
Like we got to make Tarzan this thing originally published in the 19 teens.
And everyone is obsessed with everyone.
Tarzan a few years ago.
Yeah, there was. Yeah.
With Kristoff Waltz was the bad guy.
I forget which hunk was Tarzan.
But like Tarzan occupies a very weird space where the the novels themselves,
along with the early John Carter novels, also written by Edgar Rice Burroughs,
are in the public domain, but the characters are trademarked.
So it gets so like if you want to make a Tarzan movie or spin or something,
you may still have to pay the Burroughs estate some money.
And the other thing about Tarzan and this is one of my favorite Wikipedia
isms where they just kind of drop in phrases like this.
And this was about in the Tarzan movie page.
Another issue with Tarzan was the inherent and overt racism
in the original Edgar Rice Burroughs Tarzan.
The writers consciously chose to not include any African characters
in order to avoid this topic, which, yeah, that brings up a point.
It's all white people in this Tarzan movie, in the Disney Tarzan movie.
Not in the band, though.
Yeah, no, not in the band.
It's very diverse. Yes.
Are the singers white khaki guys? Sure.
But, you know, if you want to channel Mark McGrath, that's what you got to do.
I think they were taking some of the problems from the movie
and they were improving upon it here at the Tarzan Rocks.
So you could say it's sort of the perfect version of Tarzan.
They spent three minutes of this thing just undressing Jane.
Just like, oh, yeah, I mean, very impressive.
She does do like two costume changes, like behind like the big sheets with that.
That always makes me nervous in shows like, oh, God, you have to change.
Like you have to do a quick change on stage and it's part of it with multiple cues.
Like, that's impressive.
Yeah. And it kind of as terrible as this is,
you know, that point where she takes off the final layer
and she then like was looking around and has that weird clipboard
that she's running around with to like it's supposed to look like a book.
But it's definitely just like a folder
is that she keeps like running in the monkey man on stage,
like kind of get in her way and they like corner her and circle her.
And Tarzan comes and saves her.
And if you remember back to Spider-Man Rocks, there is a very problematic
scene that is very similar with Mary Jane and the alleyway.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah, I guess it's a little bit.
Yeah, those are kind of those are sort of like street rapists.
I don't I don't quite recall.
Oh, no, you don't.
OK, well, go back.
And I think I read somewhere was like a huge issue,
like behind the scenes of the show.
If not that, it's just like like today, it's totally crazy.
It's like it's very cartoony and odd and weird anyways.
But the but yeah, no, I'm just like probably you are.
I don't know what point you are.
I'm just I'm watching this this mess.
Yeah, we're out of sync here.
We're watching. We're watching flips.
We're watching.
Yeah, we're getting so well, this I don't know.
Tarzan Rocks 2005, this is 1210 into the video.
What's the time code?
Can you show me?
This is in the same year.
Well, not 2005, but in 99 when this opened just up I four.
There was I believe.
Oh, no, that came later in the early to there was a like skateboard
rollerblade show at Islands of Adventure in their massive amphitheater
that is mostly used for special events now.
The state of rollerblading in theme parks is dire today.
And we need to keep this tradition.
Another proposal of a season for you, Kevin, is rollerblading in the theme park world.
All of season six is about to land skates.
Yeah, it's going to be great to funk land skates.
Yes, you had now you have your arc with like a backwards D
and like a slash through the E.
Yeah.
Can I get that timecode?
Oh, it's 13 or eight right now.
Of course, you know, we're going to.
Hey, Tarzan just showed up.
He just showed up.
Tarzan looks just like Trevor Moore.
Every version of him in the show, it looks just like Trevor Moore
because you expect because in the cartoon, it's like a very it's a very cartoonish,
chiseled jaw, wide jawed kind of character.
And this one is just like a white guy with long hair.
And all I think about is Trevor Moore and how much it looks like
the this one that I'm watching looks like Trevor Moore.
White kids, you know, Trevor, Trevor Moore.
Yeah, that was why is Trevor Moore for sure.
But I will say this guy is jacked.
This Tarzan is Jack.
So they got, you know, they got a hunk from Florida.
So finally something for the moms. Yeah.
And now Jane here for the dads.
Well, well, no parasol holding lady.
My ultimate fantasy office Max binder that they have like a dozen of backstage.
So in case it gets misplaced, they have identical ones.
This strikes the whole thing strikes me as and I don't have any information
to back this up, but wanting to appeal more to mom and dad,
maybe especially dad, because like with kids, if I was a kid and I like Tarzan,
I just want to see Tarzan.
I just want to see the characters.
I don't give a shit about a band.
I don't care about the singer that isn't in the movie.
But they must have been like, well, you know, this is a more engaging thing
because Animal Kingdom is a little more adult park.
They must have like kind of trying to been catered to like a more adult audience.
I'm guessing that's a guess.
Dads like 90s Phil Collins.
I don't. Some dads, some dads do.
I'm just saying that was probably their thought process,
because you would just go with a pretty straight ahead Tarzan show.
I would think I understand they don't have the problem that the characters don't sing.
I think, yeah, I want to see the car.
If I was kid, I want to see the characters.
If it's going to be mostly music, I want to be encouraged to sing along.
Oh, OK. Not me, Jase, but like as I feel like there's a lot of sing along stuff
in the park. Am I wrong? Am I crazy?
Because if we jump around a little bit, the audience, of course,
gets a big chance to get involved with the performance of Trash in the Camp,
which is when the our beloved
our beloved Turk comes out who has a headset mic on who has.
Yes, that's the best part. Yes. Yes.
The Rosie O'Donnell monkey in a headset mic, similar to today's
hit TV series, The Masked Singer, in which the microphones are useless
because the people have to be miked on the inside.
In this case, Turk is probably re-recorded by a Rosie O'Donnell soundalike.
And she gets this great intro of you seen her in the film.
Now see her like you've never seen her before.
Give it up for Turk.
Comes out with a headset mic.
The audience is divided into into sections.
And, you know, one half does baby, Bob, Bob, Bob, Bob,
and the other half does about that data over it.
And this proceeds for in my in my memory,
75 minutes.
I I I truly hate that in any live performance
where it's like, all right, like how long it takes to go like, OK,
so this half of the audience is going to say,
Waboo, and this half is going to say, Waba.
And I hate doing it at UCB.
Like sometimes like hosts do that to pump up.
Like it's like those are hosting to promote a show in a few days.
And they're like, pop up the crowd.
And it takes so long.
And it kind of works.
When Turk hosts UCB shows, that's how she plays it.
Well, Turks always a hit.
I like Turks. Did you never go to a oh, sorry, I cut you.
No, go ahead.
I was going to say, did you ever go to a Ben Folds show with just him
on the piano or he'd make you do the horn part to army?
Yeah, that's the best version of the army.
And what's the other one? Not the same. Not the same. Yeah.
That's the best version of it, because he's actually teaching you octaves.
That's a little more going on than just bibbidi, bop, bop, skibbidi.
I'd also like to point out that the did you guys know about the recorded version
of Trash in the Camp, the Phil Collins version of Trash in the Camp,
as opposed to the film one?
No, I don't.
Why he couldn't do that alone to tear apart a whole jungle campsite.
He needed help from his boys in in sync.
Yes. Yeah, I knew this.
Yeah. Yeah.
And everybody seems Phil seems very like gunpoint about it.
He's like they wanted to do a pop version.
And I, you know, I thought I had to, you know, do something different.
And he never goes on to say, and the in sync boys are brilliant.
And I had a great time. That does not happen.
It is more reciprocal of the other way where J.C.
Chazee says something about, you know, when you get a call
to be part of a Phil Collins song, you're like, yeah, I think so.
Big J.C. really selling it.
Also in the video, super like bad era of timber, like bleach blonde.
Oh, yeah. It was his Stan era.
It's that's that's a that's a rough vid.
But I guess I'd rather watch Phil and in sync scat
than how this plays out in the Orlando show.
Yeah.
Are you synced up with us now, Kevin?
They're in the rope.
They're they're making love, I think, at this point.
No, what's this?
There's a big there's a big circular sheet that dancers are spinning around.
It's like a kindergarten game.
Yeah, that's the whole thing.
Can I get a time code like 18 or 1847 right now?
1847, I'm trying.
I'm so that was like they were swinging around on those ropes.
They didn't have any harnesses on there.
It's solely holding themselves like it is like.
So do you know about the accident?
Oh, oh, God.
No, I want to know, can you show me?
Yeah, there was an accident and I found it because all I all I could find
it was on a message board
because somebody yes.
So this is on mouse pad dot mouse planet dot com.
Even even better yesterday.
My oh, sorry.
In-laws and my cheese trap slash ear holes.
Tale of space in the part of the scene of Tarzan meeting Jane.
He prepares to swing on a vinyl.
This is before this on a hydraulic lift wire and soar above the stage
and crowd before picking up Jane and doing the same.
At this showing, Tarzan was lifted about 20 feet in full swing
when the wire gave way and dropped him to the stage risers
where he crashed into the legs of the musicians.
He stood up and exited stage right Jane after witnessing this ran off stage left
and the curtain immediately closed a voice stated, Dear guest,
due to unforeseen circumstances, this showing of Tarzan rocks
is immediately canceled.
And there were this was not the only message board post about this incident.
There were other messages.
I found another post from a different.
I think it was, let's see, the dis boards dot com.
I found and I'm not making that up.
That's not that that that they also somebody was like, is that guy OK?
Is anybody know?
And like no one had any information.
I think they were saying it was OK.
Walked off on his own will.
Well, but sometimes you stand up and you pass out dead.
I mean, a few minutes later, so.
Niche. Was there any was there a was there a third account on mouse snout dot com?
Mouse snout did not have I didn't go back in the archives on mouse.
That's a premium site, Scott.
Mouse, you got to pay.
I mean, I've been paying 15 a month ever since.
Yeah, I'm going broke because of mouse snout.
You could have bought three seesaws for that.
About like, you know, I they were running this show
multiple times a day for seven years.
So I guess that is like accidents are going to happen.
Just statistically, you don't have to be PR for something here.
No, but I mean, I don't I don't know.
Well, people I feel like when there's accident, people in the past
have been like, why didn't you talk about this accident on this ride?
Or worst case like, why didn't you talk about this death?
And it's like, well, it's a little ghoulish to jump right to that
and then jump back into jokes.
But this sounds like an accident.
It sounds like people were OK.
I haven't funny accidents.
That's why I read it. Yeah.
Well, yes. Immediately saying immediately canceled.
Yeah, sort of. Yeah.
That tips it into funny.
I wish they'd kept going and just.
All right. So exit to the back of the theater.
Remember, trust your heart.
Let fate decide. And two worlds.
I kind of wish they went up to the guy with this open shirt, the lead singer.
I mean, like, you're going to have to fill in, buddy.
You're going to have to do the swinging with Jane in the
whatever the material on the ceiling.
Grab hold of this fabric and we're going to pull you up.
I don't know. Yeah, come on.
You've seen the show a bunch of times.
And then he grabs like his pants, the knees, and he goes,
I knew I wore these for a reason to say and unzips his full length khakis
to reveal khaki shorts.
Unzips.
Yeah. Remember those were big for a while.
The khakis that it zippers like at the knees.
And then you can make them short.
You would zip off the legs and they would be shorts.
I sure do, Jason.
I think I may have been to Disney World circa 2000 and worn pants very much like that.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I don't think I ever owned any, but I remember admiring like that's very utilitarian.
Very smart.
Very cool.
And you would beg your mom for 10 years before you finally got some.
But grudgingly buying them at Old Navy, the cheapest store available.
Sure. Oh, we had a lot of Old Navy.
Any fond pants memories, Kevin?
That's my in this conversation.
I can't talk about anything else.
It's my only segue.
Unless it's about khakis.
I have no khakis information that is relevant to the discussion.
I did find a...
I forgot to go through my proper channels of research for this episode.
So sorry to me.
Sorry from me.
But I did do it just now and I have found the press release.
I don't know if you already found this from May of 2000 for the show.
Oh, please.
Yeah. So I read through it.
It's very short.
And here's a few of my favorite quotes.
This is the writer and director of the show.
He said, if I had only one word to describe the show, it would be fun.
There's so much going on up on stage and depending on where you sit,
you will see a different show, which is so true because at times I feel like two different people
wrote two different shows and they just did both of them because it feels like there is a rock show,
just a classic rock and roll.
We don't need acrobats.
We got our guitars, man.
We don't need to.
We can shred.
We don't need shred on skates.
We can shred on this guitar right here.
Like classic guy.
And there's another person saying, no, we got monkey acrobats.
We got roller skates.
We got people swinging on vines.
We got Tarzan.
We got Turk.
He has she has a microphone.
And then you know what?
We'll do both.
And let's just put them everywhere because it's the funniest thing is in the first video I watched
where they have two different angles.
They keep cutting back and forth, which doesn't work because there's two different shows and two
different casts.
But it was funny is they keep cutting to different areas of things that are happening at the same
time.
So it'll cut to like Tarzan and he lands and in the back, Phil Collins is still going.
And then it'll cut to like a person that he's like, he flies up and you realize after like the
first 20 minutes of the 30 minute show, you're like, this is all happening at the same time.
This isn't just like a highlight reel.
Like this is just chaos on stage.
Josh Birkbeck Yeah, to direct a video of this, you know, the guy who put this on YouTube did
an admirable job because I think if you had 12 cameras to cover this, could you really do it
justice?
How could you possibly cover everything?
It's two shows, one family.
Josh Birkbeck The second interesting thing about this article is they say that the reason they
had skaters is because the skaters were the animation reference for Tarzan sliding on the
tree trunks in the movie.
Oh, interesting.
Josh Birkbeck So that's just a fun fact.
And then this is fun.
Josh Birkbeck Yeah, that's just that's actually like a solid fact, like a fun fact.
Josh Birkbeck That reminds me of one that I love, which is that the how the inspiration for
Aladdin was Hammer with his big pants and shuffle around and he's faster than lightning.
And that's how a little that's how a little street rat could hop around of evading evading
police and stealing bread, which Hammer also had to when his finances at the fan.
Josh Birkbeck Once his cartoon went off the air.
Hammer also the inspiration for Hammer Man.
Little known facts.
Josh Birkbeck And then the final interesting tidbit of this is that Tarzan.
This is the last line.
Tarzan rocks is expected to stay at the animal kingdom for about three years.
It doubled its expected life expectancy, which is amazing because I've never
seen this before where they say like, yeah, it's only going to be here for a few years.
Like as like why they put an expiration date on the press release.
I guess.
Josh Birkbeck Yeah, doesn't indicate confidence, does it?
And the other but the what they were confident in the beginning because this opened like
less than a month after the movie, I think.
Yeah, you're right.
June this opened in July, like so they had to prep this like simultaneously with the movie release.
Well, it's not nearly as impressive as the legend of the Lion King, which came out months
before the Lion King came out, which showed at the Fantasyland Theater where Phil our magic
currently is.
They had a Lion King show and that it was puppets and clips from the movie and that
came out before the release of the Lion King.
Wow.
And they like did they had all the songs in it and stuff too?
Yeah, the whole thing.
You saw the whole movie before the Lion King was released.
That's a while.
I didn't know that.
Well, we talked about on the animal king animal kingdom, like kind of overview episode.
It's tough to be a bug opened months and months before a bug's life hit theaters at like Black
Friday.
So dinosaur, right?
Yeah.
You would see were spoiled at the Lion King show.
So, you know, you knew everything that happened on like a big spoiler of a puppet show.
Yes.
Yeah.
Big spoiler puppet show.
I would never do that now.
No, no, they just they just had that that that 20 VFX guys losing their minds, creating red
herrings and trailers and then getting the entire internet to attack them for it.
Who did they cut out of Pride Rock?
Who is he holding up?
I mean, like what do those people go home like?
What do you do for a living?
I create red herrings and movie trailers to throw off audiences and tick off fan bases.
What would be very funny if when the Aladdin movie comes out and he isn't blue at all and
he's just a man, he is just like, hey, what's up?
And then people like, what the hell?
I would love it if he just if Aladdin rubs the lamp and then a Toyota Corolla just pulls
in to create like a genie gets out of it or a stagecoach.
Like if Genie just drove a car.
Yeah.
To Wild Wild West.
Sure.
Oh, I mean, if Jim West, if they can tie together the Jim West mythology.
Well, they can because the genie is supposed to be self-referential.
I hope all of his pop culture references are just Will Smith movies.
Oh, yeah.
Hope this goes better than after Earth.
Wild Wild West.
When I roll it to the wild, wow.
Oh my gosh.
What part are you at?
This went back.
It was over.
I was just jumping around.
32.
They're looking at the no.
Jane is explaining how binders work.
She's got a trapper keeper.
I think.
Please go to 2715 and just press play.
2715.
All right.
Here we are.
You get a great wide shot of the stage and all the crap that's going on.
And then there's something happens.
It's amazing.
Church just walks in front of the camera.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we saw that.
And two of the performers, two of the performers did that to in another
part of the video where it's like if they saw a video camera, they would kind of play to it.
We're going to have to post multiple versions.
This one that we're watching and then the other one with the unnerving,
like two different hosts simultaneously.
And one of them kind of looks like Phil Collins and the other looks nothing like Phil Collins.
Yeah, because he's got the shaved head.
Yeah.
And every time I watch, no matter what performance I watch, it always feels like
an improv group that you're watching to where like it's fine.
But if you really look into the people on stage, you can tell that they don't like each other.
Plus that they're ready to attack one another for things they're doing during the performance.
Like right after this, they're like, what the hell was that?
And they're just going to throw their skates down.
It's like, we'll get out there every night.
Too real.
No, sorry.
Acquiree on improv groups, gentlemen.
Jason and I improvised together for many, many years and it's a hundred percent true.
Whoops, sorry, I can't forget about that.
You have so much contempt for each other by the end of the run.
Do you think Turk was stronger with like initiations or third beats?
Turk was not very good, but had a lot of ideas about theory.
He was great with support moves.
Yeah, it was good.
He would say, we're in a diner or we cut to a diner.
He would do any of those type of moves.
Can someone-
We're in a camp and we're trashing it.
Turk, you've given a suggestion in the last 12 shows.
Okay, can someone clarify, is Turk Tarzan's mother or friend?
Turk is friend.
It's friend.
Okay.
Glenn Close is Tarzan's mother.
Bring it back around.
I know, maybe Driver was the voice of Jane.
That's good casting.
Yeah.
Turk is not to be confused with the characters from Disney's Dinosaur.
Yar, Kron, or Plio.
Turk is not Kron.
I don't want to say this again.
I confuse Turk with Plio a lot.
I can use Turk and Plio a lot.
Very easy to confuse.
By the way, I also just did not shoot past the fact that there was a
Phil Collins, Rosie O'Donnell collab.
Let's not miss that fact in this world.
On the same track.
Yes.
Finally, they all met.
A bunch of cutie patooties, if there ever were.
Do you think I would bet money that someone involved in this movie at some point
said the phrase of, as we are about to enter the millennium,
we need to remember two worlds, one family.
Now more than ever.
You know they must have laid it all out.
Why 2K?
Well, let's not forget.
I was also recalling this on my Instagram recently with the Super Bowl having just passed.
There was a stirring performance of two worlds on the Super Bowl halftime show
for the millennium celebration, which was interspersed with very...
What you just said, Jason, essentially is said by a very sedate Edward James Olmos,
filmed in the closest shot in Super Bowl history.
And what is Phil Collins wearing for his Super Bowl halftime platform?
Khakis.
You know it.
And I think he might have those zippers that we were talking about too.
I think the ball that dropped on midnight, January 1st, 2000, was wearing a pair of khakis.
They changed it.
The ball unzipped his two khaki legs, revealing fresh hip khaki shorts for this
hip new millennium.
So much of this is...
I'm glad we picked this topic.
It's very ripe for this conversation for this platform.
Another thing I have to say about the Phil Collins stand in this is you don't realize
it until they start doing it and it takes you a bit.
They all have choreographed beats to hit, to where they're doing these very simple rock
and roll dance moves.
So they'll do like, you know, point over your shoulder, point over your shoulder,
now clap in the air.
And they have to do that move at a very specific time in every show.
What happens in between is up to them.
So what happens is he's like, you know, this is my moment.
I'm rocking out.
This crowd's really pumped.
This is almost the end of the Best of Two Worlds tour.
Not the Best of Two Worlds, the...
Whatever, the Two Worlds tour.
I really got to do this.
And so he's out there.
He's like way out there.
He's all the way at the front.
He's on the edge of the stage.
He's ready to take his shirt off.
He's like, son of a...
I got to go back there and do the over the shoulder, over the shoulder, clap in the air.
And then he runs back and he's like over the shoulder, over the shoulder, clap in the air.
And then he's free to come back and get in the way of the acrobats.
It's so funny because he only goes back to do those few choreographed dance moves.
Pump to the right, pump to the left, step, step, step, okay, back on stage.
It must be a union thing.
So have fun with it, but not too much fun with it.
Those were his instructions.
Because you probably would have gotten yelled at if he didn't.
Because like, we choreographed this and like, I'm always interested because I don't know the
answer to this.
How much the director watches these shows?
Because somebody is a director for them, but they run them five times a day.
How often are they getting reprimanded for doing something bad?
Like that Disney's California Adventure Aladdin show, they ran five times a day.
Was the director just would show up once a week to check in to make sure that they were doing
the right hand gestures and the right part?
Like how often are these people getting checked out?
So like, yeah, did he get reprimanded?
I don't know the answer.
I'm just asking this question.
I'm sure an expert would know.
I actually wanted to do the Aladdin show, but I stopped myself.
I want, I don't know if you've done it already.
We're bracing ourselves.
That show is incredible and I loved it.
I'm still sad it's gone and that's why I didn't want to do it because I just couldn't bring
myself to make jokes about it because I think it's perfect.
That's why I did not want you to talk about Tomorrowland 94.
Because I'm so attached to it.
The futures that never were, I mean.
So that's a joke-free episode you're dictating now.
No humor will be allowed.
Bring me back.
I have some notes.
How do you want to do this?
Do you want to like, you go first and then I go?
Or just like hold a very, very strict and corporate about our very detailed opinions.
No, but like Aladdin's great.
It's still on the Disney fantasy.
You can still see the show, which is awesome.
I don't know where you're scathing in from right now.
Are you on the Disney fantasy right now?
Does my audio quality sound like that?
I just imagine that's where you're making all of these videos.
You just like booked a suite on one of the Disney boats.
He's in like the captain's quarters.
Maritime taxes are actually quite manageable.
So tax breaks for making YouTube videos at sea.
Right. Exactly.
There is.
Okay. So I'm sorry.
The tangents, who cares, right?
Okay. So the, I have taken Disney cruises and they're amazing.
They have this morning show they do and you can look it up on YouTube.
It is the least produced Disney thing you will ever see.
And it is hilarious.
Every time the cruise directors will do one every morning.
So it seems, or pretty much like every other morning, they will record.
Like a today show style morning show.
A today show morning show of what's going on around the ship.
Like let's go check out the bippity boppity boutique every morning.
And I don't know if they reuse certain parts, but you know, they film these things in one take.
If the camera moves, if it gets stepped on, it's okay.
And they show them on your stateroom TV.
It's incredible.
Watch it.
Whoa.
We got a book.
This is your return.
Scott, Scott, her video content.
Like poorly made video content.
For a micro specific location use.
Yes. This is, this is certainly my wheelhouse.
Oh my God.
Second Trojan horse.
Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's your, that's your Trojan horse into the second gate.
I think it was for you.
You needed one for both.
So all right.
Well, let's start wrapping it up.
The final thoughts.
Do you have any final thoughts?
I want to know.
Can you show me?
I'm not gonna let this go.
My fine.
I, this is this well, how many years was it?
Seven.
Seven years after people stopped thinking about Tarzan.
Yeah. I mean, I like that.
I wouldn't mind if it still existed.
Honestly, this is a, this is a fun thing.
I would annoy people with taking them to for sure.
So like I would, I would like it if it was still there.
So I can't as much as we can goof on it, like I can't put it down
cause this is like something I would go, Hey, we could go to Tarzan rocks.
And I would be like, Oh my God.
Cause that's what happened with the Aladdin show a lot where I go, we only
Google see Aladdin again.
And people would be like, no.
And I'm about to be like this with Mickey's mixed magic, which I saw for the first time last week.
I just want to warn everyone.
Like, you know, we should go over and see Mickey's mixed magic.
So this is right up my alley.
I can't, I've, I've goofed on it enough.
I wish it still exists.
I have, I have a little plus set up something that was just sitting there waiting to happen.
With this, with a merger of Tarzan and Phil Collins, I want a big gorilla
playing the, in the air tonight, drum fill like that commercial that's sitting there
waiting to happen.
They don't even have to do the whole song if they want to avoid some, some copyrights.
If they don't want the legal arm of Phil Collins coming after him, like,
like they did me like having to me.
So that's, that's sitting there a 20 piece drum set gorilla playing it otherwise perfect.
I would have liked a little more lip service to me.
So I wanted like twice as many Tarzan yells.
And I wanted the singing narrator guy to go like, Hey, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be at MGM studios.
You know, like a little, a little bit of that 90s self-aware humor.
Like a Johnny Weiss Mueller.
That's a reference to like the animatronic.
It's like, Hey, you're supposed to be in the great movie ride.
Right.
Oh, I didn't see.
You got to fill it in a little bit.
Yeah.
I got to fill it in a little more.
All right.
That's thematically inconsistent.
The, that's good.
That's fair.
Yeah.
I mean, 90s bringing them back.
No, I think it's funny though.
The yells that they do is completely pre-recorded and plays on tape, which is hilarious because
the Tarzan is more concerned about not dying than he is about making sure that his lip
syncing works.
So if you go back and watch it, it's just like, Oh, okay.
I got to get this thing off.
They just gives up and the track keeps playing.
But like, should it still be around?
Given what replaced it?
I wouldn't mind this still being around because at least it's crazy
and fun and there's acrobats and things to watch because finding Nemo the musical.
Have you all seen finding Nemo the musical?
I don't think I have.
I have not.
Have you seen finding Nemo the movie?
Yes.
Sure.
Take out all of the pauses, add 12 songs and condense it to 40 minutes.
It is, it is the fastest paced thing.
They're like, we'll be damned if we don't get every single plot point in this 35,
40 minute show.
But we are going to also add 12 songs.
It is the most fast paced, like the mom dies.
And then all of a sudden it's like, it's time for school.
And then it's like, it's so quick and fun and terrible.
But I mean, the puppetry is really cool, but I don't know theater in the wild,
Tarzan rocks.
I say stick with it.
I think it would still work.
I like the idea of it.
So well, why can't the two worlds tour be a real tour?
Why can't they send this on the road?
Right.
Yeah.
Bring it to where we are in LA and bring it to you on the boat.
Bring it to the boat, baby.
As the helicopter lands and Tarzan swings down.
They did Devo 2.0 with those kids.
I see no reason why they shouldn't do Collins Squared.
Phil Collins tour, fronted by children singing the Tarzan songs.
Collins Squared.
So Collins, the one man, Phil Collins is replaced by two young children who meet
the new Phil Collins and it's two little girls.
Yeah.
In learning, you know, I mean, the way everything's going with Disney,
obviously, is that they're just they're just pillaging their own history and
they're making new live action versions.
So what are the chances that we get a new live action Tarzan in the next few years?
Pretty high.
So I don't think it would be out of the realm of possibility that a version of this could come back
or this maybe, you know what, a version this exact show exact show comes back.
Same performers.
Make it as a movie.
Make this as a movie as well.
There's a mocap person playing the Docker singer.
Yes.
For some reason, a like they need an old man mocaps themselves into a 32 year old Florida singer.
We get some Maccas on board.
We get the Polar Express technology and I think that would be yeah, I think it would be perfect.
And plus you can pull from the direct to video sequels Tarzan and Jane and Tarzan 2,
which was a prequel of Child Tarzan.
What?
Yeah.
This was the era of direct to DVD sequels.
I think they should put all that stuff back into continuity, honestly.
Yeah, I hope it's all on Disney and stuff.
Yeah.
Return of Jafar.
Aladdin 3.
I love Return of Jafar.
Return of Jafar is not bad.
I remember like, oh yeah, and his dad was like hot.
Yeah.
Yeah, you got a hot dad.
And Gilbert Godfrey has two songs in it.
As a kid, I loved that Yago had two songs.
Yeah, that is fun.
Jafar had a hot dad?
No, Aladdin had a hot dad.
Yeah.
All right, well then that's my request.
My plus up to Tarzan Rocks is-
I also think Jafar probably had a hot dad.
I want Jafar to have a hot dad.
Yeah.
Jafar is a hot dad.
I mean-
Yeah, that's true.
Yep.
I guess he's creepy.
He's creepy.
He's evil, never mind.
Please cut this up.
All right, so yeah, videos are back in continuity.
I want to see Jafar's hot dad and the Tarzan feature film is Tarzan Rocks.
Yes.
We've all agreed on many points and I feel good about what we figured out.
I think with that, Kevin Perjury Survive Podcast The Ride.
Thank you so much for being here.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Yeah, go to youtube.com slash defunctland, twitter.com slash defunctland.
Go check out the series if you haven't already.
I'd really appreciate it.
And if you are already watching, keep watching for that Ken Burns Vietnam where Michael Eisner
returns and all of the- and hopefully I can work in disgraced pervert Senator Larry Craig.
I'll pitch you one might be easier because Ken Burns did that incredibly- very good but very
long baseball documentary, Wide World of Sports.
Think about it.
Okay.
I don't know much about it.
Yeah, I want to- yeah, let's have an eight part series about a defunct gymnasium.
Yeah.
This is Atlanta Breeze spring training there for a year.
This is the last season, I believe.
Okay, we had defunctland rocks, defunctland skates, and defunctland-
Plays ball.
So we had defunctland plays ball.
Baseball.
Play ball.
Defunctland at the bat.
I'm here with my friend Senator Larry Craig.
It's not bad.
It's really good.
I think defunctland rocks should be called defunct band while we're still out there.
I mean, that should definitely-
Oh, defunct band?
Yeah, that's good.
Uh-huh.
I think you just start fictionalizing them.
At some point, you've proven your storytelling capabilities.
Just start making shit up.
Just make shit up, yeah.
Fan fiction about Eisner and Larry Craig going on a road trip.
You're going to approve Disney's America.
I can't.
We're going to build it ourselves illegally.
Buy some lumber, we're doing it.
You're going to go into that room and you're going to approve Disney's America.
How are you going to make me do that?
Anyway, there you go.
Eisner pulls a gun on-
I have a gun.
Hello?
I'm not afraid to use it.
Fickle, often angry, murderers.
Yeah, well, brings us back around to your quote, doesn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
Unfocused fickle, often angry, often carrying a gun.
I do like to think that Michael Eisner watched a version of Tarzan Rocks the year before
all the crap went down and he was just like, this isn't going to play well.
I think he watched it and rocked out, made devil horns and banged his head.
The guy's going to have a rocking good time.
I'm Michael Eisner.
This rocks.
Hello, I'm Michael Eisner.
I'm ready to rock.
I love to rock.
If you're ready to rock with Patreon exclusive bonus content, head to patreon.com slash podcast
The Ride. Check us out on Twitter, Facebook, Reddit, Instagram, and probably other things.
And we've got shirts on T-Pollack.
Podcast the ride at gmail.com if you want to email us.
Yep. And look forward to our upcoming episode.
He worms his way back in already.
Kevin will be talking to us about the boat exclusive morning shows.
These are on YouTube.
Yeah. Is this real?
I'm going to be very sad if this isn't a thing.
If you don't bring me back.
No, I don't know.
I think we're all sold.
I don't think we will.
Fantastic.
Yes, these are on YouTube.
It's a real thing.
I'm super happy about this.
Oh, yeah.
We're all going to have to get we're all going to have to go on the boat.
Yeah, to go on the boat.
All right.
We're hitting the open seas.
Kevin, thanks for being here.
Audience, thanks for being here.
We'll talk to you next time.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen, Joe Sillio and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.