Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain zero big eyes, a dispute over the meaning
of field day, a hexagon themed restaurant, and hot dogs, hot dogs, hot dogs.
We catch you up on the latest news out of Epcot Center and give you a passport to Iron City,
the world of the Leda battle angel with an interview with IM8Bits John Gibson.
Be careful, the factory is watching.
This is Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the show hosted by three men who are jacked by today's big
theme park news.
And I am of course talking about the announcement of the Today Cafe, the Today show themed
restaurant at the entrance of Universal Studios.
I'm joined as always by Scott Gardner.
I got it up on my phone.
I was ready for this.
I was ready to do the real news and then, but you know what?
The big one, we were thinking the same thing.
Yeah.
And of course, Mike Carlson.
I'm here too.
Yes.
A very excitedly Jason this morning when I saw him, he goes, did you see the press release
we got? That's Jason Sheridan, by the way, his WordPress.
Now, yes, we're inside info.
We do. And it's six in the morning, which of course would be nine a.m.
Eastern. Yeah, that makes sense.
Because you are on the radio.
You all are on KROC 106.7.
And I didn't go because there weren't enough microphones.
That is a true fact.
And also, you are making a television show.
Well, not at seven in the morning.
No, we don't know.
Yeah, we're no, we don't keep radio hours.
No, not like you nuts.
There were there were not no microphones.
Well, we we asked we got to be on KROC on the Kevin and Bean show today.
And yeah, the first thing Jason said to me when I picked him up was,
did you see the press release we got?
And it was for the Today Cafe, the Today Show themed restaurant
at Universal Orlando, replacing what again?
Whatever that generic restaurant at the entrance was called.
The Hollywood restaurant, probably whites camera restaurant.
Today Cafe will soon make its way to Universal Orlando Resorts.
Neck of the Woods is how the press release starts.
People get that off the bat.
Do we know neck of the woods without stopping and thinking about it?
I think Al Roker has been saying it for like 20 plus years.
He does that on the time that's embedded in my head.
Yes, of the tram tour, because he did the weather section,
which spoiler culminates in a flash flood.
And it would always be so the line was
what's going on in your neck of the lot?
I said he would always say what's going on in your neck of the lot,
because it was always the same video I play.
Like, why am I saying he would always say this?
What a repetitive guy. Right.
In the clip that we had to play over and over again.
It was video. He didn't have the chance.
There was no option for him to say something else.
Anyway, neck of the it's coming to the universals,
neck of the woods, which is universal.
Yeah. So this is this is more synergy from Comcast Universal.
Obviously, this is they did.
That's a night show ride.
So I think they're starting to make all their TV shows, I guess.
And the last call with Carson Daly dumpster in the back of the park.
And that's being that's over, though.
The dumpster is done.
The show was canceled.
The dumpster canceled it. Yeah. So
Drew Tarver had the martini shot
Oh, yeah, I heard this.
He was on like one of the last episodes.
Yes. Oh, my God.
It is it does seem like this is whoever.
Whichever theme park owns like the CBS catalog, this does seem like
like 60 Minutes, the cafe or something like what a weird choice.
I mean, I guess today's show makes a little more sense than 60 Minutes, though.
Jason has an Andy Rooney walk around character at the 60 Minutes Cafe.
It would be a wonderful, wonderful treat.
Can you believe the prices at this restaurant?
And also maybe not a walk around character.
You would just be sitting in a booth in the corner with a big newspaper
and you'd like go over and you'd like hassle you and complain
about vertical blinds or something.
I bought one small coffee early in the morning.
I bought nothing else, but I'm posting up.
I clearly brought my own snacks, not paying for their overpriced.
This is all like bit stuff, but not also bit stuff.
Just stuff you would do in general.
Yeah. For those of you don't know, Jason has done Andy Rooney
a long time out in Los Angeles at a bit show called Term of Nerds.
So it's a lot of sense.
Probably most people know what I think a lot of people have done a lot of research
and what characters Jason's played on a stage isolated to Los Angeles.
And the Sandi Rooney impression.
The impression has gotten worse and worse over the years
and the jokes have just gotten meaner.
I think it's really that you're morphing into him, though, completely.
Yeah, that's probably right.
So every year that goes by, you're turning more into an old war veteran
that's upset with everything.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah.
So today showed that what were the other details?
Were there any other? Oh, yeah.
I was saying this is the benefit of being podcast the ride today in 2019
that we get access to universal Orlando's share file dot com
portfolio with files posted by Haley Fitch.
It says the name of the person who posted it.
And we get high res imagery of the meals that will be available.
I didn't look at the pictures yet.
I didn't see this. Oh, God.
Let's let's see. She's a platter.
Is it themed to a person on the show?
Oh, yes, Mike. In fact,
yeah. Additionally, in a tribute to long running tradition
in Kathy Lee and Hoda's hour of today, guests can enjoy wine and beer on tap
with a delicious cheese platter for two. OK.
But doesn't have a name.
It isn't the Hoda and Kathy cheese platter.
OK, OK. Do we?
They currently are just named generic things such as vegan sandwich.
OK, this is I'm just, you know, if you've been with us for a long time,
you knew you know that we've always wanted to be insiders.
And now we're getting official universal emails
with three megabyte crystal clear quality photos of vegan sandwiches.
We can see every little seed on the strawberries
that adorn the vegan sandwich platter.
Well, of course, my favorite thing is and most theme park websites
had this in their their roundup announcements about this opening
is the the like CAD concept art
JPEG featuring like what it will look like in 3D rendering,
which features one of my favorite things.
The humans that aren't quite 3D aren't quite 2D,
but I think feel pain because they look like little monsters.
They exist in some horrible world now by virtue of them being created
in this 3D simulation.
They're like that Black Mirror Star Trek episode.
And they're walking around this awful digital trapped space
where they will live for 1000 years unless they can somehow
like zap themselves into suicide.
This poor this like mother who is not
keeping a correct eye line with her little son.
We'll have to post this.
Yes, yeah.
And like real like the most like boxy, polygony hair.
They all look like original Toy Story characters.
They're pre they wish they were Toy Story 3s.
They are distinctly Toy Story 1s.
So like pre are they like pre
just we didn't rewrite Toy Story characters before
just for the on to it.
Yeah, or not. Not at that level of rendering
with like a oh, boy,
it's like a big TV playing the Today Show and then a smaller TV
also playing the Today Show and people like cheers and coffee.
This is something we were we were joking on.
And we were joking on that one.
I think it was a void episode a while ago about all the different
like NBC universal experiences.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. You could do which like this is getting closer to that.
It's getting closer to that.
At that point, had Matt Lauer been shown the door?
We had a bunch of Lauer jokes.
Oh, yeah. But we didn't have
Megyn Kelly had not like tacitly gone like, what's wrong with Blackface yet?
Today's show stock is not super high right now.
Yeah. How would they would like the bathroom stalls
locked from the inside with a button?
Is that how they would honor Matt Lauer and his legacy in the Today Show?
Yeah, probably.
And if you're and while you were in the while you're in the stalls,
is the TV showing you photos of potentially racist Halloween costumes
and just just to let you ponder it and just a little like title underneath.
It's a what? We're just asking the question. Right.
Is this race? It's not racist to ask if it's racist.
Right. This is a dialogue.
We're opening a dialogue
and shutting the door so you can't get out.
Will there be a Jenna Bush Hager face character?
Jenna Bush Hager famously joining the fourth hour of the Today Show.
Because Kathy Lee is, of course, leaving.
Hoda is staying.
Is Jenna Bush Hager replacing is replacing Kathy Lee.
So in case again, in case you don't know, the fourth hour
of the Today Show is like a drinky like, I don't know if you want to say
like fluffy, not that the whole show is boozy. Yeah.
Yeah. But Kathy Lee is leaving.
And Jenna Bush Hager, George W.
Bush's daughter is joining permanently.
I actually didn't know that.
I am a big fan of her work in the annual
Barney Christmas videos.
I was just posting some of these on Instagram.
Every year, the Bush White House made videos
with some bad little plot with their little dog.
Oh, right. Right. Right.
Haring the White House for Christmas.
And Jenna acts in the final one.
And like what, Barney, that is a fantastic idea
to spend our final White House holidays together.
Like, I don't know what the eye line is.
Yeah, it's as if like, no, remember, when it's your line,
exclaim out as if there's a giant theater in front of you.
Don't look at the human beings, you know, in front of your face.
She admittedly is a child.
She's not well known.
All right. Fine. No, not even.
This was the last year. This is the last year.
So but she is a lot more polished as a host.
I doubt they would give a full hour of a show to somebody who exclaims
with no eye line like that.
However, they gave Megyn Kelly time.
Sure. It's dollars.
Was that what it was?
And we're really in that we're in the age of the pay the walk away.
We are cutting ties and she will only be left with what's in the 68 million dollars.
The payout was like 69.
Oh, my God. Million dollars.
I was lowballing. Mm hmm.
Well, wasn't there also a thing a few years ago where
Chelsea Clinton was given a ton of money to do correspondent stuff
for NBC News and did like two segments and then almost with the money.
She's really I think so. Oh, we got to look into that.
Yikes. If we get into some trouble and are forced to exit forever,
dog will make sure that we get all one hundred and eighty dollars of our
fellow fresh money.
There is no way I'm walking without the payout.
Yeah, you hear me forever, dog.
We'll get the big bonus. Don't worry.
So we have covered it.
The big theme park news.
Well, and let's end with one last thing, though.
One standout features of the take today.
Cafe menu will be seasonal dishes inspired by co-anchor Al Roker's favorite recipes.
I mean, that's all we're looking for.
Yeah, I mean, I like Al Roker.
I think Al Roker just fine. Yeah.
I you know what? I'll say I'm happy for Al Roker because that might have been fun.
He might have came and be like, hey, there's a today show cafe.
We're going to use some of your recipes.
And he was like, that's nice.
So you know what? Great.
And that was the end of his interaction.
Yes. You describe the proper amount of time.
Yeah. And he's never going to think about it again.
I would like the idea because Jim Hill brought this up on one of his pie.
I think you called Jim Jim out for this.
The idea or no, it was a different thing.
You called him out for it was the twister.
But Jimmy Fallon was going to live inside the twister ride.
Basically, live from it.
Yes. Yes. Night. Yes.
It seemed a little inexplicable to me.
That's but you listened to one of Jim's
15 other podcasts and have come away for with something else.
Well, anyway, he was said there was an idea, I think, for the tonight show ride
to have a live feed to the studio up in 30 Rock.
So if they were taping a show at the time
that an audience or a bunch of tourists went through,
Jimmy could interact live with the people getting on the ride.
That did not happen.
I think they felt like, well, that's not going to happen that much during the day.
What's the point? But maybe for this, you know, you can have Roker chime in
like it is comments on what you're eating or something.
Like if you got the tray, you're going through the line.
And he goes, oh, I see you got my mashed potatoes there.
And then you go, oh, wow, it's Al Roker.
He's talking to me or something like that would be fun.
I feel like I hope that I hope it has a successful passage
to your neck of the digestive tract.
That's great. Right.
Itself. Yeah, it's perfect.
All right. Well, that was sort of the above the fold news of the day.
So I guess we have a lot of news to dig into the.
Yes. Well, yeah, we well, news and then we're also talking about this
interesting experience that we had in getting a passport to Iron City.
Yes. Of course, the the
setting of the I can do the word setting.
I struggled there.
He the film Alita Battle Angel, we went to this like very odd
but but cool interactive experience.
We're going to talk about that.
But before that, there has some theme park news has dropped.
And we're getting this one out quick so we could talk about it.
Yeah. Staying in Universal opening June 13th, Hagrid's magical creatures
motorbike adventure, continuing the recent trend of new attractions,
having very long names.
How many words in that nine?
One, two, three, four, five, five.
Five. It's only five, but only one.
It feels like nine.
It feel it does feel like nine long.
A lot of syllables in there.
Well, because it's Hagrid, Hagrid is the owner of all of it.
The magical creatures are not the owners of the ride like Hagrid is.
So I guess they don't need an apostrophe.
They're like, I might like I,
I got to go back to an English class and figure out
grammatically and punctuationally how this works.
But there's no possessive qualities of the magical creatures.
They're just on it, I guess.
Yeah, they're just on it.
I guess. Yeah. So what I know about the right, what we know about the ride
is it's like a giant cool roller coaster with a lot of launches
and there's a lot of robots of creatures.
So that's fun. Now back to the title.
Now let's talk about the title.
Not enough punctuation.
I already joked on Twitter.
We got to have we got to feel superior to this cool ride somehow.
And it is through the amount of words that they chose.
It's a little nuts.
And this is in the wake of what these Star Wars rides call again
Star Wars, Falcon, Millennium,
Spalm, Smuggler's Run, Smuggler's Run,
which sounds like the reminds me of the Glenn Fry, Miami Vice song.
Smuggler's Blues.
It's not so much as Millennium, Falcon, Smuggler's Blues.
It was soundtracked by that song.
Yeah. Is that is there a button I can hit in the ride to make Smuggler's Blues play?
Oh, wow. I'm on board.
I think maybe there'll be a phenomenon where we could bring in a little boombox
and set it on the console of the Millennium Falcon.
If it's about making it your own and making it and it's an interactive experience,
I should be able to do that.
I agree. I think and you know, what's going to happen, too,
is that when we all go together for the first time, I'm going to hang my trusty dice
on the rear view mirror.
So that's I'm going to make that my own that way.
And also blast some red hot chili peppers music
to tie in with our.
Yeah, that's sweet.
Patreon knows, but I bet one of those buttons has to be
one of them has to turn on the world famous one of six point seven K.
Rock Rock. Am I getting that right?
Do you do you know?
Yeah, one of six seven K.
Rock and then Sublime plays. Yeah.
So that's that's my Millennium Falcon.
Right. What the hell is the other one called?
Rises and resistance.
All right. I guess that's fairly that one's shorter.
But that one still feels a little vague.
It doesn't sound like the name of a ride. Right.
Because I think the like
what would be written on a lot of websites before that was revealed
was battle escape attraction, which is cooler like battle and escape.
That sounds fun. There's going to be fighting.
There's going to be some sort of an escape.
This one is rise of the resistance, which is a very general like
this could just be like a PowerPoint presentation on the resistance.
So we've been in the middle of a rise of a resistance
in the nation for the last two years, and it's about the boring as thing
you could ever because there's never been like a cool moment of it.
You don't think like, you know, a bunch of Georgetown graduates
are the same as like storming the Bastille and the second actively miss
as exciting as exciting.
Nancy Pelosi clapping.
A bunch of yeah.
Yeah, that's like fire in a cannonball.
Ivy League people going, sir.
Excuse me.
Exciting. I call him 45.
I don't even say his name.
You shall not be named.
I think, yeah, I think that there might be some more thrills
and chills on this ride than the clapping, but maybe now we'll see.
We'll see. Yeah.
Kylo Ren, the robot clapping at you. Maybe.
Like, like it could be.
Look, it could be all Imperial Senate.
We don't know. It could be the first order exclamation point.
That could escape. The first order is good.
Yeah, that's more exciting.
Yeah, that's more. That's more dynamic.
And I like the I do like the rides.
How it gives you a little command like Twister, right?
It out to bring it up for the second time.
I mean, I think from the rumors we've heard, too, there's a little bit of like
there's a couple. There's like a narrative and then a fake out.
So I do appreciate maybe it just keeping it general to like
hide the surprises, perhaps.
But does it really mean that they kind of revealed something this week?
I don't know. If you look, you can find like what's going to happen.
Did you see this?
You might be concerned.
There's a ride. There's a height requirement.
Oh, on Rise of the Resistance.
Spoiler alert. Spoiler.
That ends with a drop. A drop.
I did read that and go, oh, no.
But at least now I'm prepared.
But it's only a two.
It is two stories.
But I feel like the most to could drop you is one story.
Yeah. Unless they dug into the ground.
Oh, potentially.
Or they shoot you up real high out of the building.
Oh, it's not part of the deal.
It's going to be crowded enough as it is.
I don't want my rides having drops and launches.
There's just the Wi-Fi vehicle drives its way onto a giant trampoline.
You bounce out of those building itself.
I think it's possible.
I mean, they're doing crazy stuff with this technology. Yeah.
Anyway, Hagrid's coaster.
Yeah, what is Hagrid's coaster?
You know, a lot of rumors about this Orlando Park stop.
You know, they were the ones who had the video going around,
like showing the expected track layout, what the encounters with creatures
are going to be.
So it's rumored there's going to be multiple launches on this ride.
Like five to seven. Yeah.
But like probably another problem, probably more like it.
But still, that's a lot of launches.
It's a lot of launches.
Even for even if you are a launch queen.
Yeah. How much are can you really?
How much can you?
I mean, it is a family coaster.
So I'm assuming more like the way that Slinky Dog Dash has starts with a launch.
It better be. It's all backwards sections.
Also, potentially a drop on this at one at towards the end.
On a roller coaster. I'm not having it.
There are launches and drops.
Scott's worst nightmare on one ride.
So unless I can listen to this ride as a part where you pull up to a tavern,
get out, have a beer for a little bit and then get back on.
No, that's no dice. Yeah.
That should be part of that Star Wars.
The rise of the resistance, though, because it's a 28 minute experience.
So you should be able to stop off and have a drink in the middle of it.
Well, spoiler, the thing that the main topic of today's show, this experience
we got to do, I think the main way they got me on board is drinking was involved.
Started a bar. Yeah, that's true.
They were after they were after my heart.
But we'll we'll get to that later.
Two hours thing. You need you need drinks.
Yeah, sure.
Hagrid's like you don't imagine is two hours.
But I think the wait will be long.
But I think if this were any other year, if the Star Wars stuff wasn't opening,
this would probably be the new attraction of the year.
Hands down, it might still be because it'll have less intense waits.
I mean, I waited four hours, three and a half hours for Gringotts, the opening summer.
But it is interesting.
I mean, I hope we're about that.
We're at the start of this.
I think we've said this before, like a theme park or a Renaissance
where it's like this is just one of the crazy rides opening.
Yes. Yeah. In another year, you'd be like this thing like a different
like years past, you'd be like, this is the craziest new ride ever.
It's amazing.
Whereas like this could be the third best ride that opens this year.
I hope so. I don't want it to be the nightmare scenario is
what happened in all of our childhoods where the Indiana Jones adventure
was the part of this climb of great attractions.
And then it sort of stopped.
There was not really great new rides after that.
I don't want a peak to happen.
And then we plummet down the peak.
I don't want drops in general. Sure.
Metaphorically or on my actual rights.
I agree. I think I think there probably nothing can beat this.
Nothing will beat this year.
Next year, like nothing.
There's not enough rides next year that are coming out.
But I hope like it's an overall trend and then Nintendo and Nintendo.
Well, Nintendo is the rumors.
I believe it's next year for Japan out here.
I think it's twenty twenty one.
And then they don't seem that close yet.
It's still I feel like they're still like in ground clearing mode.
Yeah. Well, yeah. If you drive by the lot over here, they're still doing
like site prep or maybe there's a big tall crane.
Though we have passed by that a lot.
I like seeing that crane. I know good stuff's coming.
Yeah, because what's also weird is I keep forgetting
Jurassic World opens this year, too, out here, which is obviously a reskin.
But still, like this is that's way down the list.
And they did it looks to be a ton of work.
Yeah, I don't think it's an insignificant.
I think it's a little more than a paint job.
Since we're talking Jurassic stuff, we're just starting to hear the rumblings
about a potential Jurassic Park coaster in Island of Adventure.
I was all right. Yeah. Yeah.
It's unclear like where because there's rumors of Jurassic
World going in that third park in Orlando.
And it's very it's it's I think there's a lot of stuff moving around there.
Yeah. So who knows what's going to land where and we're in a theme park arms race.
Yeah. Yeah. The the rumor is that
Disney knew that some long awaited details about this Hagrid
ride were going to come out and they had to strike back,
which is why on the same day they announced day with
they their their press armada launched quite emissive, which is an attraction,
an unnamed attraction about the general notion of play.
Come in that car.
So, yeah, so they did a big press release.
They announced a while ago, they announced, I know, big changes.
Epcot, they've announced that Guardians coaster and then they had two is coming.
I haven't talked about that a ton, but that's going to the France.
Is that this year?
I don't know what year that is.
That's part of the general.
I don't think so.
There's also a Beauty and the Beast sing along that will alternate
with impressions to France.
Did you guys know? I don't even know.
That's still going to do.
They're still going to do impressions.
But then sometimes in the day, they're going to do like a Beauty and the Beast
sing along.
No child will have a bigger tantrum than if their parents got
took them into the wrong screening.
I have to say, the last time I was in Florida, that one, the very end of one night,
I was like, OK, according to the map and the app,
I this should be open.
And I got there and I forget what the they're like, oh, no, it's he's close.
Like I was and I was very specific.
Void.
So mournful. So sad.
Ratatouille, the rumor, I think, is May 2020.
Wow. Yeah.
So that's a big step.
Until 2021.
Yeah, that's right.
On the way or as part of this rejuvenation of Epcot.
Yeah, we're getting a new.
What do you call it?
What the pavilion?
No. Yeah, but the entrance way.
Sorry. The entrance way.
Yeah, you're getting a new entry way.
Right. Which I don't know.
What else to call it?
New entry way.
Guess what? Universal eat it.
New Epcot entry way.
This actually probably will be very nice.
Yes, it looks nice. It looks beautiful.
Taboo, your trees.
Someone was speculating that's what the pink trees are called.
What taboo, your trees taboo.
Yeah, I was trying to find a pronunciation of it online.
And I could only find those YouTube robot pronunciations where it's like
eight seconds long and it goes like taboo.
Why in those videos?
I've had to use these multiple times.
Why does it take so long before the word is said?
And you don't know what volume to set it at.
So you might like, am I just not hearing it?
And then you turn your computer up all the way.
Awful.
Whoever whatever bots are making these pronunciation videos,
get your acts together.
Stick to Johnny Johnny.
Glad we're addressing this.
Finally, I could see a robot in the play pavilion pronounce words for you,
like that's the job.
That's the whole thing is you would type a word and then it would say it.
Like that's I think that might be what they're going for.
So you think it's pronunciation robots?
I kind of do.
I kind of think that maybe that's sort of what it is.
Well, I have a question.
Which one or which one do you want to discuss?
I am the answer.
Or the play? Yeah, it's like we don't know whether to go into interventions,
West or East. Which way do we go?
I don't have much to say about the fountains or about the new entrance.
But I have a couple of quick things.
Well, let's here's their press release that it will be.
So as you're entering Epcot Center on your way to the glorious golf ball,
a lush you'll see a lush area with sweeping green spaces, new pathways
and a reimagined fountain.
Take that potter that will pay homage to the original park entrance
with fresh takes on classic elements.
I'll probably like that because I love the architecture of Epcot Center so much.
So maybe this will be good.
But one thing that I want to talk about a little is that they are moving
the leave a legacy pillars.
If if you don't know about the leave a legacy pillar, congrats,
you're not a dork.
But the leave a legacy pillar, if you don't know, are
around the millennium.
They put up these big gray
tilty boxes. Monoliths.
Yeah, yes.
2001 ask Monoliths, but not as aesthetically pleasing as the 2001 monolith.
No, no one ever gathered around one like those apes.
Nobody was ever intrigued by these.
Everybody marched past him as quickly as possible.
So big monoliths, that sounds scary and unfriendly with lacking a personal touch.
Right. No, no, no.
This is the millennium.
You need to leave your mark on this era as mankind crosses into a new century.
You you could make a way they'd take a picture of you
and then they'd make a weird etching on this monolith.
So and there's like hundreds of thousands of these things all lining
these bizarre, not too detailed black and white etchings of visitors
to Epcot Center.
And they promised these would not get moved for at least a decade.
I think they made it almost two.
And now they're getting moved somewhere outside the park to a garbage can.
I don't know. But apparently.
But I you guys ever looked into the leave a legacy pillars for any reason?
I'm shocked. I'd be very curious.
I should ask my parents.
Like, did you ever get a brochure about this?
And did you ever consider this?
Did you ever consider naming a star?
Did you ever consider having your name on one of the spaceships on the Mars Rover?
I haven't looked into the details.
How much was it to leave your legacy?
Thirty five dollars a face.
There'd be a two for deal.
You get a little maybe maybe if you're doing two faces, you maybe get that for 60.
So they got you some millennium slack very kindly.
Well, now I'm mad that we didn't because that is a lot less money
than I thought it would be. Really?
To me, like if you look at the quality, I don't know that it's thirty five dollar
quality. I you might be right.
How much were the cobblestones in the Esplanade?
Do you remember that?
I don't know.
Outside Disneyland, between the two parks, you notice all the names
and the stones as you're passing back and forth.
And I don't recall.
I'm sure I must have been tempted to ask my parents to do one.
But those I feel like were probably more expensive because those at least look.
I would think a little nicer.
It's a little classier and more prime real estate, less likely to go away.
But you know who you know who popped out
at least five sets of thirty five dollars.
I never knew this in sync.
If you know where to look somewhere,
there's like one hundred and fifty thousand faces.
But all in a row, five in a row is 1990, 1999 era in sync.
Wow. Yeah, weird, right?
That's interesting. I wonder how many like famous people are on there.
I is somewhere in there, they say, in the last Zodiac killer letter.
He says, I bought it.
My face is in here. Find it if you dare.
The solution to the solution to the crime.
Everyone is like, that's too boring.
I don't know why they didn't.
Yeah, it was too boring.
And it's also they should have just looked because he was wearing the burlap sack.
So it would have been a dead giveaway.
There we go. Yeah, it's like he has something to hide.
There are some creepily, some people without faces in those,
because apparently you can find where people, you know, commemorated them
and their wife or girlfriend or vice versa, and then went back
after the relationship ended and scratched their face up.
That's bleak. Yeah, that's really bleak.
That's a fairly common syndrome there.
Yeah, yeah, pretty dark. So, yeah.
So the shards of lost relationships can no longer be viewed outside of Epcot.
We get some dumb booyah trees instead.
But I do a full leave a legacy episode.
I think I was hoping we could skip it by doing it now.
That was just a little teaser to a 20, a 20, 23 episode about the leave a legacy.
But I guess the right preview center.
We could do that when you're in Japan, but I think you're going to sleep on it
and get too excited and change your mind.
I mean, I did happily, willingly share information about the leave a legacy pillars.
Are they filled?
Filled? Is there any room left to leave a legacy?
There's got to be, right?
I don't know.
I don't know if it's still a deal.
They shut it down.
They shut down the center where you buy them.
But if we wanted to go crudely etch our own faces in there,
without their permission, it'd be easier to do, especially because they're moving them
to bumfuck outside the park.
So they're putting them where river country is right now.
They're just going to slowly sink into the seven seas.
They're going to try and fill the various sinkholes
scattered throughout the property.
They're going to solve a lot of problems.
Crush a lot of potentially
child eating alligators by dropping them into the lake.
Yeah. All right.
Twenty alligators underneath.
I have to say, I'm excited for this new entryway because it seems like they are going to
restore or do, as they say, in tribute to the original entrance.
It looks like the fountain, the clear glass fountain that used to be there.
That's what they mean. Well, now I think in the picture it looks like that.
And I also just think greener like if you just fill Epcot
with beautiful lush green trees like that does feel optimistic about the future.
And it will help cut down on the amount of brown,
the brown stone, brown metal just everywhere.
Oh, no, I love my brown metal.
Yeah, that's that's part of it. Or at least like, I mean,
I don't think they'll ever fully get rid of it, but just some touches of green.
Because the other thing about all the brown is it can get hot.
It does make it feel a little hotter than usually it is.
So it is a hot area that is grass.
Yes. It is like a big skillet, honestly.
If you look at the map, yeah, like a foreman grill, potentially
like our very own future.
Yeah, potentially.
I don't think it's potentially for sure.
Oh, God. Cook alive.
Well, there's more things to dread in the future because, you know,
we just did this interventions episode and I did not put it together
that based on our work, they just put up.
It seems like they're tearing those buildings down.
I think we got no interventions.
Yeah. I'll becoming gardens.
It looks like I heard this sort of stuff on the one that they
Disney, when they do concept art, they use
like greenery or like trees in like the distance or the middle distance
of just like, yeah, ignore this and look here like they they.
Oh, that's why it may like it may to touch.
Don't to not distract the eyes in the way that the go away.
Green paint is like, don't look at this.
This isn't important. Look over here.
I see. So the buildings might still be there and we still might be able
to use our fiber optic brushes, see Tybrell and
I guess no longer hear the electronics president's rap.
Sadly, though, if the garden.
So there's a rumor that the guardians queue is going to be filled with retro
Epcot stuff, which fingers crossed, electronic should for sure be in that line.
Yeah. With like the buzzy and whatever, like figment and stuff.
So I think maybe there's a chance, fingers crossed, we could get electronic.
And I'd like it.
I'd like them to update it so he would do raps about the president since.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Maybe there's some just off the top of my head, maybe Barack rhymes with like
I did the stilted way that I talk.
Just I'm throwing that out.
That's good for a future president's rep.
I think that's I think that's good.
You could start there.
I did. I'm sorry. I didn't freestyle the entire thing.
I'm no Eminem.
I I call we should.
We call for like scoops a lot.
And if you are an imaginary who listens to us and you are currently
working on the guardians queue and you want some more jokes for electronic
to say a rap, please contact us.
We will do this for free, much like we did the street naming at Margaritaville.
Yeah. Which now they think about it.
I don't know if that has come out yet.
The episode we did.
No, it is not perhaps not.
I well, preview of things to come.
And we understand the voice that we're writing for.
We're not going to write mean raps about Trump or George W.
Bush. They're going to be the most both sides material.
Are you allowed to if can you do satire about Trump's hair?
If he like he makes fun of his hair.
So you could maybe do a rap or would he like tweet angry things about electronic
and how he's electronic has been rigged?
I think he would mean tweet about electronic.
The robot is biased because then he would compare it to the other raps
about the other presidents.
Now, I guess if electronic is still doing his rap
about how Gerald Ford falls down a lot, then you could say, OK, well, he's roasting,
gently roasting a lot of the presidents.
I feel like he still might say no president has ever been
wrapped about so unfairly as sloppy electronic
rapping about the your president, glitchy electronic.
Low talent, low talent, least skin of any Disney animatronic.
If you're so if you're so cool, get some skin.
Medium medium talent is so much more devastating, right?
I think medium Trump has definitely gotten under some skins
by calling people medium talent.
I couldn't deal with it.
I feel like Alec would just electronic would just do like a joke about
you're fired or something like, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I would just be like, I'm very famous for saying you're fired.
Right. It would be very benign and like also be like celebrating his famous
catchphrase, I guess, because he didn't want to get too political
because you don't want to you don't want riots in the line for Guardians of the Galaxy.
Yeah, I am so upset about what this defunct
animatronic brought back to rap about a current president said
that I'm going to burn the roller coaster. Yeah, we don't want that.
Maybe we'll know more because they're turning in the Odyssey,
the Odyssey restaurant
in the sort of on the border of World Showcase and Future World
into like a preview center.
They sure are. And I'm psyched about that.
Because you talk about your browns.
I love that Odyssey restaurant.
I'm really glad that it's getting used.
I work we're going long on all this, but I would just like to point out.
I learned a little bit about the Odyssey restaurant.
It's on kind of it's between Future World and World Showcase.
And it's this boring building.
And I would describe the theme of this place as hexagons.
It is a hexagon themed
building that is a restaurant for like three weeks out of the year.
I think at one point it was a full restaurant, the Odyssey restaurant,
in which you could buy these three items.
Odyssey Burger Voyager Hot Dog Discovery Salad.
God damn it.
So when you were bringing it away for putting a preview center in there pay,
you know, so much Epcot retro love is coming back.
It's time to start selling the Discovery Salad again,
which I imagine was lettuce with maybe three cucumbers.
Right. And ranch dressing.
Well, they got a they got to put a nod to that on that space
restaurant they're building. Oh, yeah.
Those items, you've already trademarked these names.
Voyager Hot Dog is the perfect hot dog space name.
I I always thought this is the deal with Odyssey.
And I guess it's probably just a conclusion I drew was that they thought,
well, we need to have good.
We need to have good food options is a more adult theme park in all areas.
But then World Showcase restaurants were such a big hit
and so quickly that they're like, oh, this place isn't really doing that well,
because I feel like there are people like who like the restaurants in the land,
the quick service and then the character,
sometimes character buffets, sometimes a garden grill,
whatever it's it's currently serving.
And we're just going to land boat ride and just kind of reach off
when no one's looking and grab food.
A little bell pepper.
Yep. That's your Epcot hack for eating for free.
I got an alligator.
Bring a little like a shepherd's crook and like, yes, there we go.
Pull it or a little like robot claw like you get a dollar store.
My grandmother had one to like get something off a high shelf,
which still doesn't really make sense.
And maybe not the most practical thing.
But that was a fun gimmick to have.
If you're already a shepherd or the sandman from Showtime at the Apollo,
take that hook into the park, sneak it in in your clothes, like condense it.
Yeah. Take it on the boat ride and nip yourself a tomato.
If it's like a selfie stick, but a shepherd's crook where it could extend.
Well, you can't take the selfie sticks and you can probably get a shepherd's crook.
You could buy an extend extendable shepherd's crook.
In Orlando, here's the secret.
Bring in a sheep, but say that it's a therapy sheep.
Oh, yeah. The crook to,
you know, lead it around. Right.
Like a leash. This is a quick side note, but I think I saw on an airplane,
like because we were traveling with a dog and I think you could bring a therapy
like horse on a plane or something.
Not a full size like like a dog sized horse, like a dog sized horse.
I'm pretty sure it sounds crazy.
I'll double check that. But it was an animal that you're like, no,
that's a joke. Right.
But it was on the Alaska Airlines approved therapy animals.
I thought you were going to bring up the more insane shepherd's crook story
recently, which is in the connect, which connects to Disney. Yeah.
Which is that PETA? I think it was PETA.
So Toy Story 4. Right.
That's a perfect segue that I didn't mean to make.
Bo is back and she's kind of like she's got pants now or pantaloon.
She's got a new outfit, but she's still got the shepherd's crook.
And PETA is like, how could you bring back this character
with that barbaric shepherd's hook?
We're of all the things to be mad about now.
I don't locate. I get it. I understand.
I see what they're saying.
And we don't condone cruelty to animals, but of all the things
to be upset about in twenty nineteen, one is that a fictional
doll who her sheep are porcelain, as is she.
She is not using the crook to ensnare real sheep
and grind them up into some machine.
These are toys. She is a toy.
She is a toy.
And also, aren't we all happy that she's not gone forever?
I thought I thought it was alluded to that she was just gone forever.
And now she's OK.
She disappeared forever, seemingly never to be heard from again.
Now she is like the basis of Toy Story 4 and is probably going to be
a strong female character that is a good new way to bring back
Annie Potts, who's a very good actress.
But we still found a way to be upset.
Yeah, it's a little weird.
But now I sound like my dad or something.
My my feeling is like if I thought that like I sometimes there's stuff
where you go like a Wolverine can't smoke a cigar anymore.
And it's like, yeah, or Nick Fury.
He's a big he's like a gruff, dirty man.
It's like, I guess he should be.
But I get it for hire.
But to be fair, I guess I also understand that like a ton of kids see this.
And OK, fine.
Wolverine looks badass smoking a cigar.
We don't want to promote that.
I don't think there's a chance that a ton of little kids
come out of Toy Story 4 and go, Mommy, Mommy, we have to go get me a shepherd's
crook because I want to use it on a sheep at a farm.
Like, I don't think that's going to happen.
So I could see where you would advocate it if it was like possible.
The kids are now going to start just crooking sheep left and right.
But I don't see that happening.
They start with other animals at home.
Yeah, I want to croak the dog.
And he croaked the cat.
Crooking is that a verb?
Is that the crooking?
I hear all the kids are crooking now.
I saw this thing on Fox News.
It's called crooking.
And your children may be doing it behind your back.
They're probably doing it right now.
Turn and look at them.
They presumably just hid their crook in the time it took you to turn.
We would, of course, if we were if the crooking was around
when we were kids, we would have not done it because we were too good.
Yeah, boys. No crooks for us.
Anyway, let's get back to the play.
We still haven't talked about the play pavilion.
OK, we what it's OK.
So in where the Wonders of Life pavilion once was, you've heard about Buzzy
and Cranium Command is also where the body wars attraction was.
It's this dome that's been mostly empty at Epcot Center.
And now they're going to turn it into a new space devoted to playful fun
with an innovative city that will come to life with your favorite characters.
OK. OK.
So, yeah, I I'm hoping so that kind of doesn't mean anything in plain English.
Not yet. I am hoping people are speculating this kind of looks like the portals
and Ralph breaks the Internet, which I have not yet seen.
I'm hoping that's not the case.
I feel like that would age really poorly.
A tribute to the 2019 Internet.
Yeah, because it kind of looks like a city.
I mean, I'm hoping it is this color scheme.
The interesting theory, and I'm going to shout out theme park insider.
Their theory is that this is a Disney Imagineering pavilion
where they will show off new technology, show off like smaller scale attractions
that they don't have to scale to huge things.
I think that's a really cool idea.
I think it's very wishful thinking.
I hope that's right.
I mean, I would like it to be that.
What I'm afraid of is that it's going to be a lot of shit
that you do with the Disney Play app on your phone.
And they pass off as interactive because I think the Imagineering pavilion,
they would have to be really on the ball with updating it and rotating in new exhibits.
There's a lot of OK.
First of all, that's we haven't talked much about Disney Play, the app,
which basically and I don't know how it's been working.
It's been out for a few months now.
It's basically a line like time killer.
Yeah. And they had a version of it a couple of years ago
where you would answer trivia in line.
And that was kind of funny.
You just answer. It was multiple choice.
You'd answer, I think, out of four or whatever.
And then, oh, you get your score at the end.
And now we killed some time in the line.
Now there's a thing and I've only tried it with Space Mountain called Disney Play.
And it is an insane pain in the ass.
There's no other way to put it.
There are just like tasks where you have to like put little puzzles together.
And if you have to do it with another person and you're just it's like stressful
and you're doing it while you're walking in line.
But it doesn't make noise that would distract people around you.
What it absolutely makes noise that are distracting.
And you look over and you go, what are those people doing?
And then there's like a race every 15 minutes that you've.
So basically, like the idea for the Space Mountain one is you have a ship
and it levels up after you do tasks correctly.
And the tasks are hard.
But then you're playing against the other people in line.
And if you win, you get to like a fast pass to go to the front of the line.
And the race is hard and confusing.
And it doesn't like you can't even control it, really.
You're just like hitting a button.
And it's like and by the end.
So we did this. It took the whole line.
And we just got to the front of Space Mountain finally.
And we were just like exhausted.
And we were like, what?
Because the idea of, oh, fun game when a fast pass is cool.
I like the idea of it.
This was insane.
I don't know if it's still like this.
But the concept of this, I hope that this is not tied into like
a long, frustrating, complicated game system that you play.
I mean, it's the same Disney play.
And this is called this is like a salute to play or whatever they say.
It doesn't have an official name yet.
That's true. That's true.
That's how people are framing it.
Like if there's the imagination pavilion, then there's the play pavilion.
The power of play is what I think the press really says.
It's like something like more play modern theme park names.
The power play place sound like like
John Kerry or Tim Kaine describing fun.
Well, yeah, the power of play.
Yeah, the power of play.
So as a child, what would that mean to you?
Nothing is a child.
Show me a ball pit, at least if you want to talk play.
Get me in some tubes in a ball pit and show me a robot band.
We're a massive room full of free Sega Genesis.
Sure. I mean, that is what that's what this looks like to me.
It looks first of all, it looks neon. It looks cool.
This is no offense to any imagineers.
I hope I love this thing.
And I love to celebrate the power of play.
But what this looks like to me is like, oh, this is a new intervention.
This is a new end of Spaceship Earth, where there's a bunch of like computers
and kiosks that will age very rapidly after a year or two.
Like Spaceship Earth, where it's like, put your heads on the future family.
And you're like, oh, that must have been cute for a few months.
And then now you're doing it.
And it's just like designed to keep you inside for a few minutes longer.
So you don't go back out into the park and like fill up the frozen queue.
I'm awfully worried.
I think it I agree. It could be great.
I am the Disney precedent of interactive exhibits and stuff.
It's a pretty messy history.
It just never it's just yeah, there might be a couple of things in there,
but it's all it feels like all the things we're talking about.
Like the the stuff in the queue on Haunted Mansion, where it was like,
play a game in the Haunted Mansion queue at Disney World.
And then it's like, that's gone. No one wants to do that.
Just enjoy the real line.
Whatever happened to the old way of passing time?
The art of polite conversation?
Yeah, good point.
These kids are the game where they flip their name up on their forehead.
And that drives me crazy when people do that in line.
It is so. But, you know, I actually did it
one time with people and I did enjoy it.
It's not bad. It's a fun game.
Maybe I should try judging it. But I did have fun.
I assume the pavilion is just like a lot of phones with the names.
I think I may have been in a queue that is enjoyable,
like the Guardians queue or something,
where I was trying to like figure out what the songs were.
And then people are like, yeah, yeah.
President Clinton.
I think there's fun.
There's fun, probably applications with a phone
and like like queues where it was like you would discover things
or you're going through big thunder and you discover like
some piece of sea history on the phone and you answer a trivia question.
And then like there's got to be something cool.
Well, you're saying you want sea trivia.
You want children to have to learn about the inside
Disney mythology of the explorers who all own nice buildings in the past.
Yes, I guess that's true. Yes.
I do think kids should learn about sea.
What's the right age for a child to learn about sea?
Yeah, I mean, that's between the parents and the child.
But my I would think eight, seven or eight.
Then when you explore, introduce the the
Congress in Hightower, that's Harrison.
This is Barnabas T.
Bullion. He created the train.
We're going to go on, son. Oh, wow.
Here's something else you should learn, son.
You will have no friends as an adult.
Now that you know this much about Harrison Hightower,
you got a rough road ahead of you.
No friends.
Well, you will, but you'll be in your 30s and it'll just take you a minute.
Yeah, it'll take you a minute.
Maybe you can start a podcast.
Yeah, it's all different worlds.
Podcast. You will have anxiety.
There's a lot of talk in the press like about characters, so it feels like
like we're going to do all the character greeting stuff here.
It'll be a catch all for that.
So they're going to move wherever the character spots are now here.
People were kind of where's wallowing the concept art on this.
And you can see, I mean, Mickey came in with a family.
Mickey gave him a family holding their hands.
Yeah. You see here he's holding his young
the young child's hand and then kind of on the buildings.
There's sort of kawaii cutesy versions of like Edna mode.
Somewhere in here is joy from inside out.
She's on the right by the hotel. It says Hotel.
Oh, yeah. To say Hotel.
Is that a cat?
I think that's Marie from the Aristocat.
I mean, I like that. That's cool.
You want your theme park destination to hang with Marie
done in pretty explicitly Hello Kitty style.
Yeah. If you want to help Disney cut into the Sanrio market shares,
this is your place to do it.
I mean, the building that interests us has like the Wedway logo on the top
and then the sort of bottom kind of has a monorail sort of
pattern to it. Kind of.
How much do you mean the word interest?
We like that. You're figuring it out.
There's there's like a kind of a Rubik's cube type building
on the top left here that I might be interested in.
I could be see being interested in it.
I don't know what's inside.
Maybe puzzles, perhaps. I love the colors.
I love the blue and purple.
I mean, yeah, I'm hoping it looks like this.
And then there's like it looks like you sit down and perhaps
there's a show in the middle of you. Did you see that?
Sort of an amphitheater look. But it's like a small area.
So this this feels look, this is much better than
what they have now, I think.
Empty drop ceilings and empty rooms with naked robots.
Roddy easily stolen.
Yeah. So I think this will look cool.
Like, look at Epcot. It's got a look cool at night.
And I think that's what this is going to do.
Love the colors. This concept art.
Yeah. Sick colors.
That has a lot to do with my complaints.
And it's all in a dome.
I like that, too. Cool colors and domes.
Neon pinks. Scott's in. Fantastic.
So, yeah, who knows?
We shall see.
But, you know, maybe there's a reason to be optimistic about this
because we have recently had an experience where we've
that was sort of an immersive world of interactive elements and games
that transported you into into another dimension of fun.
And we did find this to be a surprisingly satisfying experience.
And I am referring to Passport to Iron City,
the pseudo main topic after a lot of today's talk of today's episode.
This is this interactive experience that is based on the film
Alita Battle Angel.
And this is something that's been set up in Los Angeles, in New York
and in Austin.
And it is a very theme parky thing that I guess, Mike,
you got curious about and you poked around if we could go visit it.
And we got the opportunity to visit it.
Yes. This is this like there's a lot of like movie
promotion stuff that pops up.
But this one was particularly intriguing because it's like kind of downtown.
It's in a weird spot.
And it felt like it was there was much more to it than like
I saw there was like a Lego movie, too, thing
that was in like a tent on Hollywood Boulevard.
So it felt like getting pissed on every day.
Yeah, this felt like, OK, this seems like they're going a little more.
They're going a little the extra mile, I guess you would say.
Yeah. So it was like, let's see.
Yeah, let's poke around.
And also here, you know, let me just not to make people just listen to a video.
But, you know, it is hard to explain what this thing is.
And I discovered that there is a video you can watch where James Cameron
explains what this thing is for the fact that James Cameron is involved
and does a sort of Michael Eisnery presentation about it.
That sure legitimizes it, doesn't it?
Of course, it clears a quick little moment of James Cameron's
part to Iron City is a truly first of its kind immersive experience.
It fully transports you to the world of Alita Battle Angel.
After you enter, have a drink at the Hunter Warrior Hangout,
the Kansas Bar, don't mind if I do, or Iron City
from the marketplace to the Motorball Stadium.
You can even dig through cyborg parts in the scrap yard.
We brought Iron City to life as a 12,000 square foot
high tech living board game.
Where you are one of the game pieces.
Where you're one of the game pieces, a living.
That's a lot of square feet.
There's a bar you can even scrap for parts.
Weird. James Cameron is telling me about something that I hate.
I don't think I would have like naturally been aware of this.
If you hadn't poked around or are from our friend Charles
texted me about it, he came along with us.
But so we were like getting curious and circling around this thing.
And then and then we got to do it.
Yeah, we got to be game pieces.
What a weird sell, right?
That is. Oh, yeah, that is a funny way to be like, you're a game piece.
So if you ever wanted to be one of the blank color pegs in, sorry.
Yeah, if you want to be a pawn in my game, like that is sort of what he's saying.
You want a burger?
You can experience what it's like for like a rich man to buy you and
right when we show on his island to be hunted.
Right. I guess that's just sort of how he thinks.
Because he could do is very rich.
Anybody could hunt humans.
James Cameron would be the guy.
Sure. He obviously he hunts underwater things.
He doesn't hunt. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He hunts species that have only been discovered by him. Right.
That's how he goes.
Yeah. So no one misses them.
Except the ecosystem.
The ecosystem is.
We'll find various way, various butterfly effect ways that James Cameron is
destroying the ocean species elimination.
Yeah. So I I didn't know a ton about it.
I just knew there was a lot like seeming seemingly a lot more to it
than a normal kind of walkthrough or whatever.
And you get a T-shirt or something.
It seemed to like a lot more than than a pop up experience
that sort of themed after a thing.
And yeah, were you like maybe you go get some lightly themed
refreshments or whatever.
And it also you go, well, is it sort of like an escape room?
And it's not quite that either.
Though it has components of that, it becomes a teamwork scenario.
I mean, my favorite description that I found was that this is a dystopian
cyberpunk playground.
Accurate. It's very much like
interactive or immersive theater elements,
because there are a number of actors walking around in character like.
I I well, you'll hear
I said that I met this as a compliment, but like not breaking character,
like they are fully in character once you get into the main
like room this take place.
And I met that as a compliment when we talked to the guy.
But I realized it sounded very.
You know, we laughed at your the actors did not break.
But I was admiring their commitment like there is this taxi driver guy
who I just thought he was delightful.
I would have I would have just talked to him for half an hour.
Well, and there's things like
it seems like that would have been possible.
You could have like broken like you could do whatever you want
when you're in this room.
You could. Yeah, you could have broken rank and just talk to this guy for a while.
There's things like there's people who have to do functional things
such as check you in to an iPad, check in the procedure
and a guy who has to give you beer.
And he stays in character like functional.
Things are all done by people who have to like speak the language of Iron City.
And I think it's like it's done pretty well.
Yeah, it's like because those jobs, especially the checking you in job
is so hard to do in general because you're a bunch of people going to a new place
and there's a lot of people with them and they have to access things
on their phone and get a QR code or whatever.
But you have to like stay it.
But you have to like, like, hey, listen up, all you people.
You come in here and you check the QR code and then you get on your phone
and the six of you and you have to scan in and then you go over here
and you get a lanyard and it's like you have to do all of that.
Then you have to troubleshoot people's, oh, the iPad ain't working for you
or whatever. And Mike spent about three minutes
tapping a laptop screen before realizing it was not a touch screen.
It was just a regular old laptop with a mouse.
Hey, you tall idiot.
It's not an iPad screen. It's a computer.
We don't got this kind of technology here in Iron City.
What do you think this is? Zalem?
Yeah. Keep it moving, screen junkies.
Screen junk.
I, I, when I say Zalem,
I'm referring to some mythology from the movie.
And by the way, so Elite of Battle Angel is a film in theaters now
that is surprisingly well regarded.
And I have to admit, I have not gone to see this film yet,
but it seems like people who have have liked it.
It's in that 4DX format that we had so much fun. Oh, yeah.
And it's doing, you know, OK in America.
Because it's weird, new mythology and people distrust it
like they do a Valerian or a speed racer or such things.
I equate it sort of in that genre a little bit,
but where it's like neat and original.
And if you get in, you're really in not doing OK in America.
Seemingly gangbusters in China.
So Elite of Battle Angel 2, I imagine, is around the corner.
Have you guys seen this film? No, we have.
All right. So I kind of like browsed
when we were there at the end.
Of course, there is a gift shop, but they they reissued the original manga.
It's been out of print in America for a long time.
They put out some nice volumes, full collections of that.
I think you can now get they put out a video to they got
Kishiro, the writer, artist, the manga, Ka, who made it
to come to the events and like sat.
They talked to him in the Kansas bar.
So I can only imagine for him that was a unique experience.
Well, and OK, so what's cool about this is that this is a
this is this experience that's a very committed to trip
into a very specific mythology that is not
super established here in America yet.
And it's like you feel like it'd be a tough sell
to get something like this made like a multi-city immersive experience.
It'd be tough to do it for the Star Wars, probably.
Let alone this sort of like not tested property.
And we and we got to talk to one of the people
primarily responsible for putting it together.
And it seemed like they really had their their their run of the property
to like to do like they they got to do whatever they wanted.
It's the it's people involved in Avatar.
John Landau, a longtime producer of for James Cameron.
He sort of oversaw it as he did the Avatar stuff in in Florida to some extent.
And I don't know, it seemed like it's an interesting mix of,
well, why not try something and why not promote a movie in a in a in a different way
and in a more full way?
I don't know. It was cool.
Well, how do we begin to explain this thing?
Like we said, it's like it's it's got escape room components.
It's like you you break off into teams of six and we assemble.
It was the three of us.
We you pick colors and we were the purple team because the logo was purple.
Had to get purple.
And our friends, Andrew and Charles and and Lindsay.
And you break off into into groups of six
and you enter a bar and you get drinks, which are apparently custom
made for this thing.
There are it's a custom Alita beer.
We're Battle Angel beer
that was brewed, yeah, brewed for this event.
Yeah. And you're in the Kansas bar, which I'm told if you see the film
has some very exciting events happening in it.
Of course, none of us would know.
Now, OK, have we dropped the ball by none of us seeing this film?
Perhaps. Maybe. However, one thing that I think is cool about this experience
is that I was I was hoping that I could I would go in
and there'd be this really specific mythology that was so odd
and confusing to me and I could sort of make fun of it.
And like, what is going on? I'm so confused.
In fact, they have created an experience that does not rely on you
knowing the world of Alita and in fact, just serves to make you curious about it.
Yeah. I guess not curious.
We were each given each team was given a table on that table
was a tablet with different pages.
And that kind of gave you the whole background, everything you need.
And later on, you would get it behooved you to spend five minutes
reading this information because there was like basic trivia stuff,
because the whole thing of this, you're trying to be the team
with the most credits at the end of it. Yes.
And this is where I feel I let you guys down, because as I said,
like, there's a theme bar. Great.
I'm just going to chill out and have a beer.
Then I was, I believe, the second person to buy beer.
I got right to it to my chagrin.
The bartender says, hey, you know, that little icon on your badge
is somebody else in this very bar who has the same thing.
If you find them, you're a match.
It can help you get credits in Iron City.
And I'm like, ah, damn it.
I wanted to just wanted to sit and have this beer and talk to the people I came with.
But you are thrust out of your comfort zone with stuff like that.
It's it's you should go interact with other people and get out of your
get out of your comfort zone.
But in addition, I'm just sipping on a beer, not retaining any information.
You get into Iron City and immediately realize,
oh, I should have been listening to all that stuff
because it would it would have helped us play the game.
Well, I think all of us caught little bits and pieces.
And that added up, especially in the trivia.
We got all of that pretty well.
And there's an introductory speech from,
I believe the young lady's name was Cobra
introduced kind of gave us the rundown of, you know, you're in Iron City.
This is the year it is.
This is what the deal is.
Everyone wants to get the Salem, the city in the sky, literally a heaven kind of
a very anime city in the sky.
Yeah, yeah.
Which is the funnest thing to talk about, like that's where
it was a lot of fun to go and not knowing the specifics of this world
and to just talking about Zalem and like,
oh, one of these days, man, I'm going to get there.
I've been dreaming of Zalem every night.
I've what does Zalem smell like?
And it was kind of more fun in a way to not know about Zalem
and to read the bizarre little text like you may even earn enough credits
to earn passage to Zalem.
Now, spoiler, you get to the end of it.
I don't know that the winning team, right, which could could have been us
could have been a different team.
But the winning team did not enter some beam and then ascend to some sky city.
No, that did not occur.
It is a cool reward for you.
It would it would be cool if it's like there's a version of Zalem
was a different, cooler bar.
Hell, yeah. Yeah.
Where the drinks are free, the drinks are free.
And so that was my one complaint.
I do think
that I do think everyone should got one drink ticket with your admission.
I think that would have been because the breweries involved
and the wineries involved in this are getting some free promotion.
I wonder I wonder if there's some weird thing like with a liquor license there.
I mean, that should be a pop up event.
And we should have we should have asked you should have asked that question
in our interview. Yeah.
All right. First thing.
Yeah. First things first.
Oh, I thought you meant asking character to the bartender.
It's like, oh, Mac, can press.
Does it press badge mean anything in this goddamn city?
I don't know what we don't have the press here.
Oh, just the factory, huh?
Just another factory stooge.
The factory doesn't represent podcasts with a, you know, mid to growing fan base.
Is that how it is? Is that how it is?
We should say the factory runs everything in Iron City.
That's true. Yeah. Yes.
And that'll help you in the trivia round.
All of this will help you in the trivia round.
Yeah. And what I you know, what I'd like to drive to and encourage people to do
is to perform better in the Iron City experience than we did.
At the end, we'll give you our stats.
And if you're encouraged and are in Los Angeles, New York or Austin,
I want to see if you can beat podcasts, the ride
will give you some tips on how to do it.
Yeah. So we were all like everybody in there is like seemed like they were game.
But I was thinking like for a second, I was like, oh, are we all going to have to be
characters? Are we all going to have to be like
and like, I don't know, because I don't know, I was going to make up an alien name,
but it was going to sound stupid like M.E.M.
Carl or something like cars, like whatever our friend Andrew did.
You have the option to put whatever you want on your name badge.
I didn't I stayed Scott, but I amended it to be iron.
Scott, our friend Andrew made himself for the evening into Amdo.
That's good. I was a big fan of Amdo.
I think we made us do that.
Alita.
Should have just gone with that.
Then we would have been the hero automatically.
Yeah. But I was like thinking for a second, oh, are we going to have to act?
And now part of me thinking if we go back and do it, maybe we should.
Well, we did kind of because we started getting mad at the taxi driver
when he like did a bit where he was like pickpocket Lindsay.
But I mean, we started yelling at him.
But I mean, like I'm going to go there with an eye patch or something.
I'm going to go there with like a little bit of flair, a little clothing.
And maybe I'll work on a character beforehand.
I think a little bit goes a long way of this thing, because again,
the actors are really good, really into it.
Kudos to the designers for not giving anyone the big eyes
that unnerve me for the promotional material from this that only one character has.
I don't know how it would be possible to get the big eyes in real life.
Or some like there's LED screens in front of all the actors eyes.
Yeah, yeah. And what their real pupils are doing now.
That's how it would have been an escape room.
If you entered the main room of this thing and everybody had giant eyes,
we would have all been like, get me out of here.
Yeah. Yeah. And on every door, one of these has to be an emergency exit
poorly labeled in some made up language. Yeah.
So yeah, it was so it was pleasant and funny.
What it ends up being is that although, you know, feel free to just go do it
and not listen to us explain it and find out for yourself.
Skip ahead. But you're you're chilling out in the bar.
You're learning some stuff.
It's sort of like it's you're getting accustomed to this world.
But then you enter this big
marketplace slash arena where there's all these different stations
and little rooms that can help you earn credits and that reward teamwork,
but also reward being bold and strategizing and splitting apart
and maximizing your time.
And some games are fun and some are sort of like tedious and time
wasting and probably like eat up time.
You could have been more easily accruing credits.
And it's interesting to get in there
to have had no opportunity to form a battle plan and to just like,
oh, God, we have to like learn the system of this and
work together and figure it out.
It reminded me of not and this is not quite the same thing,
but it reminded me I had a similar feeling that I would have
when I would do field day in elementary school.
Did you guys have field days?
Oh, yeah. Familiar. Yeah.
You did the days I looked forward to the most because it was in school.
Sure. It was just fun. Field day.
Yeah. You would get a little team together.
And then at our school, at least you would have like stations basically.
And you a lot of a more physical channel.
You're saying, oh, no, ours was just like it be like, you know,
movie in the morning, lunch from McDonald's.
That's not a field day.
Our long recess.
Did you say 50 minutes field day?
Just outside activities.
Having a field day.
If ours was having a field day, it was like stuff kids like.
So it was like because our field day was like
you would run a mile or run half a mile.
There would be relay races.
There would be like yours is like color wars at like a summer camp
or something. Almost it sounds like I get I've never heard that.
Color wars, I guess.
Maybe they were colors where the teams.
Yeah, the colors were the teams.
So like so we so basically like you would split up at our elementary school.
Like all the one through six would have like you'd be split up.
So you've been teams with sixth graders, first graders
on the uneasy alliances from the different grades.
And then it would be a lot of like physical challenges, throwing a ball far,
like sprinting and stuff.
And you'd all I forget exactly how it would work.
But it was like the most exciting day of the year because it was a big thing.
You do it with a group of people.
And then you would get points at the end.
So doing this, I would describe it as like the feeling I had with field day
where you would be like, oh, cool group, we're trying to figure this out.
We're going to beat this other team.
And it's like a very fun, like kind of big, like multi-challenge.
But pro, it doesn't involve strenuous physical activity.
And another pro, it does involve beer.
So it notches up in a couple of ways.
Yeah, it's all adults and everyone's a little buzzed, a little.
Yeah, a little buzzed, even on just like I just had a Mexican Coke.
But like those bottles so big, I had the caffeine.
You were you were buzzed.
I mean, I was when we were going down, I was like, I know this is crazy,
but I would kill if I could get a cup of coffee here.
Like I said that to one of you.
And then we did go into a bar and I was like, hey, Coca Cola, next best thing.
Huh? Yep. Yep. Close.
Yeah. Y'all got coffee in Iron City?
No. Coffee was outlawed in 2472.
Yeah. We all know there's no coffee in the world of Alita.
That's why everyone's so stressed out. We drink Gojuice.
Like they always have something though, right?
That was like death sticks.
Smoked Gojuice, one go away from GoGojuice.
The drink Honey Boo Boo had on. Well,
toddlers and tiaras.
GoGojuice. It's a dystopian world where Honey Boo Boo reigns supreme.
We almost play games to win her favor and she rewards us with GoGojuice.
The juice is a mix of Mountain Dew and Country Time Lemonade.
Is that what GoGojuice is?
I think it was like you had a real big Honey Boo Boo kick there for a while.
Yeah, you watched the show.
Yeah, you were really into the show. Yeah.
Yeah. And then there's some disturbing things came up.
Anyway, most popular reality shows.
I didn't forget about that. Anyway.
That's when you moved on to Duck Dynasty.
Yeah, there was something problematic there.
Yeah. Let's talk about some of the things that challenges.
I think we all enjoyed the music audition.
Yes, the music audition.
I was looking forward to part of me thought you were actually going to be able
to play the piano and I would get to show off my lazy piano skills.
And maybe even lazier.
I thought it was going to be karaoke.
I thought you were just going to do karaoke or something.
Sing the Iron City National Anthem.
No words. Go.
That would be great.
Yeah, it was basically just they had they had like rigged up a bunch of keyboard,
like MIDI keyboards, and then they kind of played the music ish thing,
an approximation of whatever music and people would listen to in the past.
Or Iron City, excuse me.
And then you just like hit a set of keys when they would light up.
So it was basically like I kind of felt like it was a like my hand was like
a cat's paw trying to get it like a toy.
So I just like kind of claw at the keys.
One of the would light up for a brief second and I just kind of hit it.
And like it was very stilted.
And I'm like, I was trying to do two at once because they're like,
do as many as you can.
So I had two keyboards in front of me and I was just trying to hit it.
And it's it was quick.
Like it was really quick.
It was like maybe less than a second.
But your chance to pretend that your keyboard cat.
That's a good point. Very exciting.
Yeah, just cans.
You know what a lot of these things felt like was it's almost like it
because there's also then like you put a puzzle together.
They frame it as like it's a propaganda poster.
Right. You got to form the pieces and you together as a team put up a magnetic
poster. It all feels a little bit like legends of the hidden temple.
I was just going to say that. Yeah.
But without the horrible men that grab you and without the monkey,
that seems so easy, but that everyone messed up so badly.
Everyone is fine. Can we?
No one scared us. No one scared us in this.
No, I was scared.
I was concerned. Will there be scary stuff?
And then we walked in this beautiful, brightly lit marketplace.
I was let down.
I was hoping there would be a few scares.
I won't say why, but I was hoping that someone would jump out at us
and that we would that all five of us would leap into your arms at the same time.
Like Scooby Doo. Yeah.
Yeah, I was.
I was hoping there might be a little bit of a scary element, but no, nothing was scary.
Yeah. So but how legend of hidden temple also.
Yeah. Can we say real quick on legends?
Those men in the temple at the end as a kid,
because as a kid watching those shows, you'd fantasize about doing it.
And that's I was scared of those men for sure.
I would like to sit closer to my parents of like, I know the men are coming.
I don't want to watch them.
And now as an adult, I'm more like, I know that was a non-union gig.
I know they were getting screwed in addition to the real horrors.
Real horrors.
Their faces weren't on camera.
Yeah. Didn't have to be Taft Hartley.
Yeah. So which, by the way, a good idea in general is Legends of the Hidden Temple
for adults. Oh, 100 percent.
What a good idea. They own this property via comms.
Failing. That's a good way to make money.
There's a five and like and they do a double their tour.
Yeah. Yeah.
Imagine little pop up legends in the temples.
At Comic Con.
It's funny to watch the Nickelodeon booth evolve from like shows
current children enjoy to like remember the go go 90s.
Remember, I have a photo with monsters.
I have an old Mac photo, me and Olmec from like two years ago at Comic Con.
And I don't think they brought the show back.
I think they just brought it there to make idiots like me
try to relive their childhood. And I did. Was he cool?
Yeah, he was cool.
So down to Earth, I bet.
Yeah, he's really he's chills.
Well, no, they did bring the show back.
Now I think about it was a different.
There was a film.
It was not a game show.
They made a weird Jumanji light.
OK, I don't know anything about that.
That the host Kirk Fogg did appear in
acting.
It's yeah, it's odd.
And they were like, so it was like a game show,
so nobody gets to play it.
It was like a narrative film of legend.
All right, you're all getting out near.
I ain't going near that temple.
Had enough of it that he drives off, drives his off road vehicle,
like set up a flare.
Something goes wrong.
It's like they're like Dan Aykroyd leaving the scary house in Casper.
Yeah. Are you going to call someone else?
Someone else?
The problem is they need waivers.
But the idea that you would go into the legends of the hidden temple bar,
drink two beers and then get thrown into a temple.
Monkey beer, silver, silver monkey.
I get a victory brewing golden golden monkey.
I believe it's one of their most popular.
It's a silver monkey, right on the show.
Or green monkeys.
What's the what's the color in the don't know offhand purple parrots?
I know. OK, I always wanted to be a purple parrot.
Purple parrot pilsners.
OK, great.
At the very least, you could do it because you'd have to have people sign waivers
if it was an actual physical thing where they have to climb.
But you could just do a haunt.
You can do a legend of the hidden temple haunt.
You're you're only taking out the worst part of it.
You can't like haunts that much that you want the horrible
temple men to jump out at you.
I kind of want.
Well, I'm just trying to think of a way for them to do it,
because it would be hard to get a bunch of drunken adults
in and out signing waivers.
People would be hurting themselves left and right,
crawling like on their hands and knees through like that section.
You know what I'm talking about?
There's a section where you crawl sections where you climb.
It'd be too much for for men and women.
There's like jump zones in every abandoned mall across this nation.
I think maybe you take alcohol out of the equation.
You got to pregame it.
They aren't going to officially.
You have to get a flask in the parking lot and get hammered
before you do your adult legends of the temple.
Hot boxing before going through.
These competitors are moving very slowly today.
It's funny, there's so many of these game shows now, like the Titan.
Have you seen any of the Titan games?
Oh, no. Oh, yeah.
These giant elaborate sets, which is just like a less.
I mean, they're very they're crazy themed and their scope of them are amazing.
But it does feel it's just a different version of legends of the temple
with strong people.
What's the Ellen's game show at night now to?
I don't know. Game of games.
Here's my question.
Do any of those shows end with a final trivia question of how much money is enough?
Either of those people like when is it?
No. When do you when is it enough?
What more do you need?
But the thing that's invaluable is having cameras pointed at you
and being able to tell people what to do and fetch you coffee.
Well, wait a minute. They point the cameras at you.
Now you have a.
OK, I think I understand.
The last thing I'll say is that the new
let or not let's make a deal.
The case, what's the stupid case?
You know, the dealer No Deal now shooting live from Orlando,
Florida, Universal Studios. Oh, boy.
So there's got to be.
You got to try to get on it.
Some one of the three of us should get on it.
But they're doing a lot of like public human interest stuff
where they tug at the heartstrings on the episodes.
So we have to find an angle for one of us that makes us look like a sad sack.
So we'll we'll figure that out and get we'll get on it right now.
If we frame Jason's frequent hot dog eating as poverty,
we just have to tilt the.
Look, just because when I was driving here today, I had the thought,
do I have enough time to stop for a hot dog?
And the answer was no.
At Costco?
No. Well, Mike got me on the 7-Eleven app
and I was trying to see if I had enough points.
But you were going to get a 7-Eleven hot dog.
Yeah. Where else would you stop for a quick?
I guess it could have been a wiener schnitzel.
That is still like that's gross.
Joe, the famous Simpsons, right?
Got booed.
Given Homer, our all day or like weeks at a time.
Never done me dirty. OK.
Never done me wrong.
7-Eleven. You're wrong.
Not only 7-Eleven hot dogs.
Just not often. How many a year?
One, maybe two a year.
I think that's low.
Oh, shoot.
I think I forgot about the cost.
Costco, you're going into a battle in the parking lot.
I guess I guess wiener schnitzel has a drive through.
I mean, I don't even think about that.
Ultimately, I understand the hot dogs are barely edible and it does not matter.
But there is a weird thing in my head about 7-Eleven food in general,
which you don't share, I guess.
No, I'm very curious about the pizzas.
I heard someone saying the pizza, if you get a whole pie, is pretty good.
You said before we started, before Scott said you heard.
I heard the pizza is better than Little Caesar's.
People online arguing and I like Little Caesar's.
I saw people online arguing saying like 7-Eleven is actually better.
If you're talking a five dollar, six dollar pie.
So I don't know.
Can I? On the six dollar pie.
We're talking price points.
Message board.
But now it's pizza, pizza and Domino's are trying to compete with also
like deals where the pies are hit five or six dollars.
It's a lot, a lot of exciting stuff going on in there.
We have formed that now Jason can go on Deal or No Deal.
Yeah. Forced to subsist on 7-Eleven hot dogs.
I'll go to pocket this discussion for doughboys.
Just copy and paste it.
Well, they'll go over our lines and that saves them some recording time.
Yeah. The thing on Deal or No Deal that they're doing now is that
there was like a guy who worked at the Ford plant his whole life
and didn't get like, oh, well, it might not have been a Ford.
It might have been different car company.
But then like the president of Ford came out and was like, for your service,
here's a plaque and you'll get to sit with us at the executive box
in Detroit at the next baseball game.
And it's like, oh, like they're delaying that on thick.
So for the Jason episode, the CEO of 7-Eleven will come out
and gift you with a year supply of free 7-Eleven hot dogs.
Seven hundred and eleven hot dogs.
All at once, all at once.
Almost to a day, but not quite.
7-Eleven truck pulls up in front.
But a voucher for if you want that second one,
when it's getting into the dregs in December and then for efforts.
And then you will swim in them like Scrooge swims in money.
You will swim in 711 hot dogs
in an old time bathing, a one piece bathing suit.
And say to say that for your for everything is terrible.
That's not where they're.
All right. Fine. All right.
You got to be careful in that hot dog pit that you can
very easily suffocate. Yeah.
Scrooge goes Scrooge like swallows the coins and spits them out.
If you go in for a mouthful of 10 hot dogs.
Yeah. You might not be coming out of the tank.
Jason knows what he's doing.
I know what I'm a man of the people. OK.
I'll brave 7-Eleven food.
So I think I do every week or even certainly not every day.
Acknowledge that I eat McDonald's a good amount and Taco Bell.
And God knows those probably are not dissimilar in their quality.
But for whatever reason, 7-Eleven, I do feel like the food is sitting there.
So I'm saying I'm saying, yeah, there's a stigma and I'm probably incorrect
about it. And you're more progressive than I am.
All right. And is that good?
It feels like the the morsels of food that they have to scrounge for
in the poor pockets of Iron City. Yeah, that's right.
We're doing a podcast.
Let's not gag up on Jason Marathado.
Well, you always say the same thing.
Something new comes out about your hot dog eating every week,
and it's hard to not examine it.
You offered information. We can't go here.
We're going to name this episode more about Jason's hot dog eating habits.
Epcot, slash hot dog, slash Aleta Battle Angel
passport to Iron City, the experience. Yeah.
OK, one thing that we have not gotten to in this episode yet
is that we talked to the people, the person, one of the one of the people
who are responsible for this thing, because this was done by I am eight bit,
which is a very respected art collective.
But they see he was talking the philosophy of making stuff.
They do releases of video game soundtracks on vinyl and they
and you know, and like video game re releases.
And and they've they've got an art gallery here in L.A.
And they've also like, I guess what happened was they made a
a Resident Evil escape experience that toured the country.
Sounds pretty cool. You love scares.
Yeah, sure. They give you some scares.
This was apparently this apparently caught the attention of the people
producing Aleta and seeking to promote Aleta.
They reached out way in advance, gave him like a big jump to do something
really cool with the property.
And that's what made this this thing happen.
And we got to go talk to to this guy, John Gibson, the co-owner of I am
eight bit really cool guy, passionate about themed experiences,
as are we and seemingly a big deal in in L.A.
Art world. We got to come to his place and bug him a little bit.
And you're going to hear some of that right now.
All right. We're here with John Gibson, I guess, to start,
just tell us a little about I am eight bit, the company behind Aleta
passport to Iron City, which we all did and enjoyed.
Sure. Well, thank you. Also, that's that's you had fun.
That's that's the operative word we've been tossing around.
So when that is achieved, we are quite happy.
My name is John Gibson, as you said, I'm the co-owner of I am eight bit.
We've been around for about 14 years and we for all intents and purposes
call ourselves a creative production company.
But that's kind of a bit misleading because everything we do is predicated
on experience in some way. And that's not necessarily traditional experiences.
That's anything from our perspective that you can
tangibly interact with.
So that could be an event that could be a stunt or activation
or anything that really brings something alive in the real world.
And we we really appreciate analog experiences and things.
You know, we come from the era of VHS and laser disks and cassette tapes.
And so we like to combine technologies and analog things
and make experiences that are cool and most of all, fun.
And we we appreciate that because we're, you know, as theme park aficionados,
we're always excited about real tangible experiences
and the anything that's not not a screen ride.
That's one of the big things.
That's one of the big complaints in our world, which you see a lot of these.
Which can also be, look, if you're on a ride, it's still a ride.
Soren is a really fun ride.
Like there's it's a screen ride, but it's you know, you're you're up there.
You're hanging. Your feet are dangling. Right. It's it's fun.
I'm afraid of heights, so also it's exhilarating for that reason.
It's the only way for you to get that experience.
Fake height.
I guess if you could tell us a little bit about how you guys got involved
with with the Alito project and how like how far into them
making the film did you guys come on board?
Because it certainly can't have been an afterthought.
It can't have been like, well, we got to do something to promote it
because this is it's so like it's it's so realistic in the production design
is is is next level.
So you must have been working with the filmmakers in some regard.
Well, thank you once again.
Absolutely. You've noticed all the things we were hoping people would notice.
OK, yeah, we started
working on this a good 18 months before we went live,
which is super duper rare in the film space.
If you're to approach it from traditional marketing channels,
which we did not like, this was not a venture that Fox Marketing
had anything to do with.
It was produced and financed by our partners at the CELU group.
They came to us one day and said they wanted to change live entertainment
and do something different in the space, but also do something
that didn't cater to typical marketing habits, bad habits, if you will,
where you get called up by a studio two months before a film comes out.
And they say, hey, let's do something cool.
And if you can imagine, two months is not a lot of time
to achieve much of anything,
let alone something of the caliber of passport to Iron City.
Did they have any ideas for you?
Did they just go hit us with your best stuff?
Do they do you guys present basically to them and then they approve?
Is that sort of how it works?
They were really integral in providing a thing that also isn't very standard
in the film world, which is the reason why we don't usually work in film.
We work in video games, primarily, or TV.
They provided us access and trust in a way that studios
typically would never really allow to happen.
As you can imagine, certain things are under lock and key in the film world.
Alita, when we first read the script, we had to sit in a room
and Amanda and I both gave up our laptops and cell phones
and everything was watermarked on the page.
And we sat in a conference room for two hours and read the script
18 months ago.
That wouldn't have happened in a traditional environment in the film space.
But it happened because the fine folks at TSG and Lightstorm were buddies.
And Lightstorm trusted us and TSG trusted us.
And they said, hey, read this, watch the movie.
It's in a very infantile, early state at this point,
because there's a lot of CG involved that's not finished or polished yet.
But after that, let's discuss what you guys think would be cool
and different and unique in this space.
So you're saying you saw the movie with normal sized eyes.
I think we actually saw the film before and after the first trailer came out.
And so they actually enlarged the pupils since the first trailer
when complaints came in. Really?
Yeah. You can look it up.
It's kind of amazing.
Like you compared side by side.
James Cameron and Rob Rodriguez got in a conversation and, you know,
they took note that people were complaining,
but they also are visionaries in their own respect.
And they're like, you know, we should we should enlarge the pupils
to make them more expressive.
Because when you see the film within a minute, that does not bother you anymore.
You are fully invested in this universe.
And like you realize in the context of a trailer, it might be odd.
But it doesn't matter because, you know, films are not trailers.
Films are films. Sure.
Were you guys familiar at all with the original manga that inspired the movie?
Because it was out of print in America for many years.
And Kodansha just put out like new collections of it,
which you can buy at the end of the experience.
Looks very nice.
But there are 2000 pages of material of like the full run of Alita.
And I read them all as an adolescent when I was a young boy in middle school.
Yeah, yeah. I grew up in Detroit and I used to go to the I think it was
Walden Books or like one of those mall bookstores.
And I would special order the the Viz editions, the trades.
And it would take like a month to get each one.
Oh, sure. I fell in love with the anime and then then realized it was based on a manga.
So I just started special ordering those with allowance money
and eventually got through them all.
And I still have all the original manga.
And I got to meet Kishiro, the creator of Battle Angel.
And he signed my first edition copy a couple of weeks ago.
And that was like kind of a little boy, you know, like if I don't know what
my might faint, not sure.
He barely speaks English.
But like all I all I want to do is like like hang out with this guy
who like really influenced me.
So this comes full circle for me personally, too.
Wow, that's great. Did he do Iron City?
Did he do passport or you just met him?
Oh, yeah, no, he like we met him at passport times.
Wow, really? He went through and, you know, that was the most terrifying part,
I think, is is to like, you know, in Japanese culture,
you know, perhaps it's different than American culture, where it's
it's harder to discern expression sometimes.
And it's like, are they having fun?
Like, are they are they nervous?
Like, I don't know what's going on.
Like, I hope he likes this. I hope he's smart.
And then they had a blast.
They got into the Turing's lab and started doing those activities
and got on the running pad.
And like and they loved the Kansas Musicians area with the keyboards.
Like the words were the minute they got in.
I asked them what they wanted to drink and they asked for waters.
And then I said, well, we have this beer that we made for the experience.
They're like, oh, we don't want to drink.
Like, we just got off our plane.
And I'm like, but and it's Panzer Kunst.
The fighting technique in the manga and the film.
And once they saw that it was like a little beer, they're like six.
And they like down them.
And that was the moment where I knew that these guys are having fun.
And a thing I really like to have to give them a lot of credit.
The actors were all really great.
Like no one broke character.
Like everyone was so committed.
I did. Well, not that I thought they would.
Like the base level.
Yeah, I know. All right.
We'll send you a secret shoppers next time.
Yeah, yeah. That's good to know.
I mean, the taxi like we spent, we probably could have gotten more credit.
We probably could have gotten one more game in if we hadn't spent like five
minutes arguing with the taxi driver.
But I was like, no, I want to keep arguing with this guy.
He's really funny.
And you touch on something really integral to the experience
and something that early on in play tests.
I don't know if you guys are familiar with play tests.
It's akin to a prototype.
You have something that you think works pretty well,
but you just don't know until people get on it and experience it and go through it.
And her play tests are really interesting because a lot of people
criticized initially the fact that you as a player have agency over this experience.
Like it is your choice.
You are a tourist in Iron City and we've created a bustling metropolis
that allows you to do whatever you want to do.
You can't do everything.
And on some of the forums before like, oh man, like you, I just need someone to tell me what to do.
You have domain over this environment that is not your house.
You get to walk around and touch things and experiment and engage in a way that
like a theme park doesn't necessarily provide you when you're waiting in line for something.
Like it's not as linear.
The thing that we kind of knew all along was the magic in a lot of ways,
because you come out of it having made every decision.
And every decision either got you credits or it didn't.
But you spent time with that taxi driver arguing with him and he was wasting your time,
but you were also wasting your own time having fun talking to him.
So maybe you could earn as many credits as you initially maybe went in wanting to earn,
but it didn't matter.
We talk a lot about specifically the E.T. ride on the show at Universal Studios
because it adds so much to the mythology.
When you're doing something like this that has like new characters or new stuff,
like how much is that you guys?
How much is that?
It's just a collaboration.
Like, do you have to get a new character?
Do you have to get each character that we interacted with approved as part of the mythology?
Does James Cameron now acknowledge all those characters are canon?
An actor might just say something that just becomes gospel.
If you're an actor and you're working on a show,
gospel, if you're an actor and you're working one of these experiences,
you know, 40 hours a week, like you're going to know a lot more than us after a week
or even a couple of days because you're just playing that kid.
Like you're specialized in that role.
And it's like we want to hear your feedback and we want you to have enough room to wiggle
and grow as long as you're keeping to the vocabulary and the fiction and the lore.
And you don't break character.
Don't talk about modern technology or like don't talk about the latest Ariana Grande song you heard.
There's like simple rules of the fiction because you're 600 years in the future.
Or if you said that Ariana Grande song from 500 years ago.
Exactly.
Just commit to it if you're going to do it.
The one thing we didn't really want to do, nor anyone else, was retell the story of the movie.
Because like, who cares?
Like, why would you want to do that?
And it's like the whole idea was how do we expand the universe?
Like, how do we make this something that if you saw the film,
it kind of opens your eyes and lets you explore this universe more thoroughly.
Or if you haven't, you know, it introduces you to this like cool, new, rad, futuristic world
that's just transportive and neat.
You know, you don't have to ever have seen Mr. Toads or Wind of the Willows, right?
But you can go on Mr. Toads wild ride and still have a blast.
You know, like I think that half the rides at Disneyland, like that stuff is so old
that kids don't even know what it is anymore.
They probably prefer people to not have seen Song of the South,
just go straight to Splash Mountain.
That's where, you know, as we record this, I still have.
I have not seen Alita yet, so I'll be going in reverse order.
Like when I say and it did make me want to see it much more.
But like in the same way, I'm a weirdo who saw who went on Star Tours
before seeing Star Wars.
So to me, it'll always be those movies in the world of that ride.
But I guess this will be to me as well.
Well, is a movie of in Iron City?
That's crazy. Like Star Tours before Star Wars.
Yeah, it's just how it worked out.
I don't know. But it makes you appreciate the strength of the world, too.
Like Alita is a brand new IP for 99.9% of people.
Like you don't see a lot. It's exciting in that regard.
The manga existed, but like not really in America,
like not really stateside at all.
And it was like out of print everywhere for a long time.
Like even in Japan, it was kind of invisible for a bit.
I guess here's a here's a question.
Can you often think of like the ultimate,
the mythology you would most want to tap into or explore or a
mythology or a property that would be like a dream to set up something in?
I just get lost and immediately always thinking of Home Alone.
Is that right?
Like, not that that's realistic or makes any sense.
Well, I'm on board right away.
But any thoughts as to what that is?
I just feel like it would be hilarious to like go through a booby
trapped house.
Do you think how you would do it without killing your guests?
But, you know, it sounds fun.
It seems like more of like a Halloween horror night.
Smey's maybe. Can you imagine?
I can imagine it.
Paint cans like flying just above your head.
I mean, there's so many complications to what that experience would be.
Like, you know, it's half half choking.
But if it became a reality, I'm sure we'd figure it out.
It'd be complicated to figure out how to give gifts the experience of stepping on a nail
into their bare foot.
It would have to be like a rubber nail.
And like they'd have to have like reinforced shoes that we give them a check in.
And it's, you know, legal.
Legal to shut so many things down.
Technology has made great leaps and bounds.
If it could trick me into thinking I was stepping on a nail, I'd be very impressed.
Do you see the house on like I feel like I do you feel like you
you've watched a movie enough to like know your way around the house.
Like the house is so iconic.
And he made the map.
I could probably draw the house.
Yeah, I feel like I know it.
But but you know, fake nails are like sensations, like technology that would simulate that.
You know, one of the things that we try to deploy in Passport, Iron City, too,
was things that were high tech, but things that were also super lo fi and like just
tangible, tactile things.
So it's like the marketplace
relies on that like old Halloween game of like reaching the bag and tell us what you feel.
Yeah. And it uses your senses.
And it like everything is designed very deliberately across the whole experience
to make everyone feel empowered and cool.
Like they've accomplished something and they're valuable in that universe.
Because one thing that not that this is an escape room, but clearly there's escape room
elements, escape rooms can make you feel really crappy.
If you're not really good at very claustrophobic,
very insane when you're trying to figure out puzzles and stuff.
If you're not a very specific kind of person that has a particular kind of brain
that really enjoys that kind of simulation, you can be really polarized by that kind of thing.
I'm not saying all escape rooms are the same, but it's a very particular thing.
I find them very nerve wracking personally.
And so it's like, yeah, we have a countdown clock in Passport, Iron City.
We have a dynamic credit system where teams are competing against each other, earning credits.
There's a leaderboard that refreshes like Grand Central Station flipping all the time.
There's elements that would stress you out in theory, but they don't because you're
having fun and you're distracted by the fun you're having.
So the leaderboard is there and yes, it's competitive and yes, there's a winner.
But that's not the point at the end of the day, because like you realize it's not about winning.
It's about like creating memories.
Yeah, which I before this, I did not have a memory of arguing with a shifty taxi driver
and half of my friends thinking that he was not to be trusted.
And we were like literally torn back and forth.
Like some of us were starting to go one way and like, no, you're coming this way.
You're with me or you're against me. No, hang on.
I think there's something here like how weird we're around each other all the time.
Now we're in like a weird like marketplace fight together.
Yes, what a strange way to like hang out with friends you see all the time.
We've gotten some hilarious feedback, too, where some people are like,
hey, one of the actors told me to bet on this this one racer in Motorball and we lost.
I'm like, well, why did you listen to them?
Like, well, do you just immediately trust anyone on the street that you're talking to?
Like their job isn't to give you the answers.
It's not that easy in the real world, nor is it that easy in Iron City.
There's a rhyme or reason to everything that happens.
Like everything has a solution.
There's a bunch of puzzles throughout.
Motorball is also a puzzle.
You know, you just got to look at the clues and it's like you can discern
for the most part who is going to win the race and the races rotate.
Like you're never going to see the same one twice.
But you know, you're still gambling.
You know, like Vegas doesn't guarantee you winnings, but like you can discern
and deduce pretty logically like who's going to win if you pay attention.
Much like anything.
And we forgot Slots rules for Vegas, where it's like if you can max
bet every time because that increases your chances.
That is the one thing that our cast members in Iron City will encourage
everyone to do, because what started happening early on
in play test was some people would go crazy.
Like they're just like gamblers of heart and they would just bet the max.
But so many other teams would just bet like a thousand credits
and you can bet up to 50,000 credits.
So like you got to think about it like a weird mix of jeopardy.
Yeah. Jeopardy and slot machines.
It's like the whole point is that like this is like the group activity
where you can you can rise up to number one, but you do have to risk something.
But you also have to pay attention to what you got on the leaderboard.
And a thousand credits isn't going to get you anywhere.
Yeah. This is how neurotic I am.
I guess that I'm not even willing to risk fake money.
Like I didn't I wouldn't even bet like non-existent
but like money that I've had fake money that I've only had for 20 minutes.
I'm like, yeah, but I earned that. I fought for that.
I pressed a keyboard.
It's real money in Iron City, Scott.
Yeah. Well, if it's any if it's any consolation and you may like
sink into like a giant, you know,
pool of just self-doubt now and depression.
But these credit coins, the actual if you if you're the winning team,
you get like a full on thousand credit coin that were screen used and minted
by like like a really awesome old machine in Colorado.
Whoa. Wild. They're like super.
I don't know if you guys have held these.
They're like they're really substantial because we lost.
So they're really substantial coins.
Yeah, that's it's it's a prize that is neat and cool.
And it's like a little piece of movie proptim, if you will.
This is very heavy, very detailed, like the etchings on the side.
This is cooler than I thought the coin was.
I was a little relieved when I saw people win the coins like,
just some plastic coin. Now it's a cool coin.
It's a very real coin.
But now they're selling on eBay.
We saw this thing for like seventy two dollars a couple of days ago.
Maybe it's gone up. But I'm like, well, I don't think now you can translate
into real money or bitcoins if you're crazy.
Sure. I got some.
It's down right now. But, you know, so I guess does anybody sort of
have like a wrap up question, you guys, because we talk about how it feels
like the world is becoming more theme park, like experiences like this
are popping up more and movies especially are doing promotional things
where there'll be like a crazy pop up for something.
But like, where do you see the future of this type of entertainment?
Like, do you have a vision for it in a way?
We hate that word pop up.
OK, some people have paraphrased us as pop up, but we're not.
What do you think about activation?
Because it sounds a little Manchurian candidate to me.
Activations is a very like insider baseball term for like agency talk.
Right. It's an act.
It's like everywhere a comic.
I mean, I introduced what I made, but was at the beginning of this.
Like I said, the word activation and stunt.
Stunt is another marketing word.
But this is not an activation or a stunt.
This is like a thing that will exist as long as people want it to.
Like it is something we have, you know, will run for many months.
We're not going away just because the movie opened already
and we'll keep extending our lease.
We have lease extensions for as long as people want us to be in these cities.
Yeah, so it's its own standalone business
and experience, you know, it's just about fulfilling the destiny
of expanding the universal lore of this place called Iron City
and it'll be a battle angel because you bet your butt
they want to make sequels to this thing.
Terrible. Absolutely.
Well, yeah, it's very cool.
Congrats on it.
And thanks for giving us a passport to Iron City.
John Gibson, you survived podcast, the right.
But where else? Where can people find find out about you or I am a bit?
You can you can check out the the URL.
I am eight bit dot com.
It's I am the number eight bit dot com.
And if you're interested in passport to Iron City and experiencing
what everyone on this podcast have so far, it's just a leader experience dot com.
And tickets are up until the end of March so far.
And we'll keep on going if people want us.
Cool. Great. That gives us more time to finish the episode.
It's good.
OK, we can drag our feet.
Awesome. Cool. Thanks so much for being here.
Thank you for having us. Great.
OK, John Gibson, co-owner of I am eight bits.
Cool guy. Fun to talk to him.
And he told you a little more about the what this experience was
and the ultimate goal of getting this this very cool coin,
which we were disappointed to learn was cool,
especially because, well, we should talk about our results.
OK, yeah, a little bit.
So we were doing so the multiple challenges.
So basically, I think we kind of said it.
But like how it works is there's multiple things to do
and you kind of run from station to station and you try to do your challenges.
Like we were saying puzzle or the keyboard thing.
Dr. Chiren's enhancement assessment.
That's what I meant to say.
I don't know what that was because we didn't have time to do that.
We didn't know it's a mystery to me.
Don't know who Dr. Chiren is.
They tell you you're not going to be able to do everything.
And that turned out to be true.
Yep. And then there's what's the smell one?
What was that one?
Marketplace one.
So like there's one more like a very mysterious person.
I will give you some smells and you'll say what it is.
You'll have 30 seconds.
And like I was so proud of myself, they waved it under my nose and I said chocolate.
And I gave me a good sense of self satisfaction.
I think we all did pretty well.
No, I was the first one up.
And only in a technicality was somebody nice and threw me bell pepper.
Oh, right, right.
Because that was the first challenge and I was the first person to do anything.
And I fucked it up and I felt stupid.
Well, but that's you know, that's it's a teamwork thing because I had it later
when there's a challenge where you put your hand in a bag and see what's in there.
And I was like, it's that thing.
It's like it's like a branch that's in a cocktail.
And someone was like, not Meg.
Yeah. So like I was describing it, but somebody it was an assist, you know,
so you shouldn't have felt so bad about that.
Teamwork was part of it. Yeah.
I just didn't like the starting at that point.
Right. So we were so long story short, we were kicking ass.
Yeah, we were number.
There's a leaderboard. So you get that we were running around.
We were in triple digits, I think, before everyone else was.
They were still in double digits.
We all, I think, felt like the smarty pants kids.
And we were like, we're going to do like that's another thing.
I was flashing back to like an elementary school feeling of like,
we are the smartest kids here. I cannot believe it.
We're going to beat everybody.
And so we were doing really well.
And then there's a final challenge, basically, which is a guess.
Essentially, you're placing a bet on what's the name of the sport?
Motorball. It's gambling.
Motorball. It's got the risk challenge type.
Right. It's like horse racing or something, but it's like robots, essentially.
So they kind of they help you along on all the challenges.
And the helpful man was like, you know, I would say go with
the two that have been upgraded recently.
Some pick between those two.
So you see that there's two characters that have been upgraded.
And I don't have anything in front of me.
What are the names of the crimson wind and junger not jungler not
jugger not.
I told you it was dry. What did you see through it?
And in there, yeah, we're not crazy.
You said junger not right.
It was junger not and who could to pep.
OK, I think I just got much better.
OK, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Juggernaut. Great. That's what I thought.
All right. So juggernaut and crimson wind.
And we were looking through.
And then on the iPad or whatever, you could look at like stats
and crimson wind looked like she had better stats than juggernaut.
And juggernaut looked like a bad guy.
And juggernaut also looked like a bad guy.
I didn't care so much about that.
But I because it's iron city, baby, I can I can support my.
I want to support the winner. I don't care.
My only allegiance is to money in iron city.
Sweet, sweet credits, sweet, sweet credits.
So I was like, I think crimson wind.
So this is I don't think we would have won
because we were still, I think, right at the end,
we were not in smarty pants first place.
I don't think we might have been second or third.
But the whole thing is that you bet credits, you can bet up to 50.
So it's like Jeopardy.
You're sacrificing like you could potentially be sacrificing
your credits if you lose.
So we all had like it happened too fast.
We should have done this earlier, I think.
We weren't all together.
We weren't making the decision as a group. Right.
Should have been.
So there was a debate of how many credits to bet.
Is it like Vegas rules where it's like, OK, double or nothing?
You know, right.
Which we probably should have leaned more toward
because I like afterwards when we were talking about, we're like, well,
this is a silly nonsense thing.
And we weren't going to get to keep this fake money.
And the hints were strong of who you should pick.
So a lot of people were going to pick the winner and potentially bet more.
So what do we bet? Ten out of 50? 20.
20. We bet 20 out of 50. Yeah.
And Crimson Wind beat Juggernaut at the very end.
Everyone cheered because everyone had picked Crimson Wind, I felt.
And we should say this is not the winner every time.
Stuff with all of these games change on a regular basis.
There's multiple variations.
Yes, I don't think you got their goat by knowing it's Crimson Wind.
Right. Yeah. Sometimes it's Crimson Wind.
Sometimes it's Juggernaut. Sometimes it's Junkernot.
It could be any of the three of the robots.
OK, well, that's an extra hot dogs to make up for this inadequacy later.
I told you about the app, though.
So it's kind of like I treated you to the hot dog.
Well, we've discussed the hot app.
This freebies on the app do not include hot dogs.
And you're right. You got to get more points.
So we got like second to last place, I think.
Third to last. Third to last.
OK. But it was very disappointing.
So now we know we can pass that along to anybody.
And after being first for almost the whole time, we were like the thing you want to have
when you're down in the gutter in sixth place, you think, well, if I bet it all,
maybe I could bring down that cocky guy at the top.
And we were the cocky guys at the top.
Yes. And thus we ended up with a final credit score of not it,
not like in terms of bank credit score, but just within this.
We'll give you our credit score later in the in Iron City.
Our credit score was one hundred and fifty one thousand five hundred.
So if you get a group of six to go do this thing, try to beat one hundred
and fifty one thousand and you will have beaten the Iron City masters here on podcast.
Honestly, it should be easy. We did so poorly.
Would you guys like to talk about your assessment results?
Yes.
I the factory evaluated my performance and determined I will serve as a factory clerk.
There's little stats that you get based on your performance in the various games.
And I was on the scale of safe to adventurous all the way down at safe.
I am I slightly notched barely towards rebellious
and and I'm way down towards passive.
This is an accurate reflection of life.
I feel I'm right.
Sixtieth percentile rebellious, not close to under.
Yeah. So basically on the chart of like interest risk alignment, compassion,
it's like there's one, two, there's there's eight different boxes.
So you can go through the spectrum.
So if you're like so.
So what were you on passive of which box did you check?
I'm closer to passive.
Was it three away? Three away.
I am also three away.
I was passive and we all have the same.
I don't know my risk. My I'm safe.
I'm two away from safe, which just means very safe.
I'm right on safe. I'm right on safe.
Oh, so I'm a little less safe than you.
Well, because they because they were scanning
this is because they know this is because they know I like.
Yeah, they were scanning.
They heard the podcast.
So they know I've done like three more hunts and you guys have.
So I'm a little less safe.
I'm cold.
I'm three away from being most cold.
I am also that I'm also that.
All right. We're all safe.
But what were your guys?
What's your job in the factory?
I man.
What is it?
Deck man. One word.
Is that a boat? Do they know about your boat stuff?
All they say is it's Fleet Week and the ships just stopped sailor.
You would be a good deck man.
Well, all aboard. Wow.
Mine is not as good as yours.
Deckman mine is factory farmer, which is like a bad job.
That's not a thing or thing we like in this world.
Yeah. Yeah.
So the factory is it how does the fact is that what is the factory make?
What do you farm in the factory?
Do we know credits credits?
I'm a credit from like a Bitcoin.
You're you're a credit crooker.
You take a big shepherd's crook
and you scrape all the credits around and
polish them up and get them back onto the street.
I don't like the sound of that.
Yeah, sorry. So yes, your life now.
And the main thing is none of us are on Zalem.
We didn't descend.
I did notice a green team on here has sixty three thousand, which is so much less.
So yeah, really bad.
We can feel superior to somebody.
Hey, green team at the four o'clock showing several Sundays ago.
You know who you are. Yeah.
You fucked up.
You know, too much in the Kansas bar.
Yeah, I saw.
Oh, yeah. Those are those guys who were like, who were tipping over and shouting
and punching each other.
Hiccup never wiping their eyes like they couldn't believe anything they were seeing.
You're never going to catch a liter that rate.
Catch.
A real quick thing I'll say before
before we're done with this is that Jason loved this one performer there.
And you said he was like an older gentleman and he was the one giving the trivia out.
And he reminded me of I'm trying to think like
a little bit less of a character, Richard Jenkins, maybe.
Yes, I would say that.
And you said something like he was he was good.
Everyone was good.
But you said, I want to be in something with him and I want him to play my dad.
Yeah. You never think about that.
Like who would play your family members and movies and like not a biopic movie,
but like, oh, if I wrote a script, who would you cast as the father?
Karen, whatever.
I mean, I guess if we if we're thinking about it, I want Star Trek
The Next Generation's Jonathan Frakes to play my father in something.
So I can see what you're saying just off the top of your head.
Yeah. Jonathan Frakes.
What about you, Scott? Oh, man.
I love I.
Yes. All right. Thanks for giving it to me.
May sunny boy.
A special hat for your 30 seconds.
32 years of good vibration.
In addition to this man I met once, Richard Jenkins would be like high upon my list.
Sure. Who but that's the listeners.
Who would you want to play your dad of all the actors you know?
Hashtag who's your daddy?
Maybe who's your hashtag?
Who's your daddy actor?
I feel like that was never been used for anything before.
Yeah, that'll be a clean hashtag for us.
Yep. We laid claim to that first.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, I'm looking forward to that.
But let me say one thing.
We as we've said, our Iron City stats, not so good.
Our risk was low.
We are somewhat cold.
Yeah. But and we did not walk out of Iron City with the precious metals,
with the beautiful coin. Right.
But we did go to IMAPIT and we interviewed John Gibson and he gave us the coins.
He gave us the coins.
We won anyway.
Podcasting. Yeah, we cheated our way.
We outsmarted everybody in that dumb city.
Because you don't have to follow the rules in Iron City.
Yeah. Yes, we understood it more than anybody.
We played the 13th round where you go interview the guy for a podcast later.
Yes. No, the secret round.
They didn't know existed. Yeah.
Yeah. We outsmarted everyone.
He we were interviewing him and he pulled out what I only can describe as a POG
holder from over by like where he was sitting.
And he opened it up and I went, oh, my God, is he of all those coins?
And there's a little elite of coins.
And like he kind of pulled him out.
I was like, oh, my God, is he going to give us a coin?
And he did. He put three to he did like a real cool move.
Did you see that? Almost like a like a dealer in Vegas.
He kind of put the three coins out and I was like, oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
You never like that magician, like familiarity and slickness to it.
I wonder if he does magic. We should have asked him.
Oh, maybe so.
I was swept up, though, and like, oh, my God, we can get the coin that I was.
I was starting to wonder.
I wasn't like banking on it.
But sure enough, right after we finished recording, he gave us the coins.
Well, prove it. We'll post a picture so you know that we got the coins.
We're not faking it. But this is I'm realizing that this is the second coin
that has been important to us over the course of doing this podcast.
The first one, of course, being the famous
city walk sector 19 sector 19
coffee coin, which was the key to the whole thing.
That was unlocking a key at the end of a long journey.
And now we have a thousand Zalem bucks.
I think I like this being we got.
I think whenever a coin is in play, we got to pursue it to the end of the earth.
I don't know if there's other good coins around theme park world.
I mean, I guess you can get a crushed penny at many theme park locations.
Yeah, we should.
Maybe we should start our podcast, the ride coin book.
And then that should like it should be some sort of like the Simpsons
and the paintings where like the last one of us alive gets the fortune at the end.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure. Which I'm sure is based on a real thing in literature.
But I can only think of the Simpsons one because I'm done.
And we'll try to kill each other when we're a little older to get it.
Like three years older. Yeah.
Global warming.
It starts hitting the fan and we maybe we can like
Zola like you're like Iron City, sell some of this like scrap metal
and try to get robot hands because our hands broke off long ago.
And we're all like knocking down Jason's door
because he is the only supply of hot dogs left on the earth.
What's it worth to you?
Now you're all with hot dogs.
I seem to recall you mocked me on a weekly basis.
And look at you now.
These will never go bad.
And they're all for me.
711.
I've gone down to one a day.
It's been tough, but if it's how I survived, then it is what it is.
You know what they say.
The one who lives the longest wins.
And that is hot dog throne.
Um, well, well,
we we survived podcast, the ride, Iron City experience.
But will we survive this new real world?
Who will survive the podcast, the ride coin hunt
that will go for the rest of our lives? Yeah.
Our gentlemen, the race is on.
And who will survive the hot dog wars?
I have one guess.
Yeah, yeah. Jason shared.
I have a hot dog warrior.
Something good personas for you.
They were warrior killers in the were they hunter kill?
I forget.
Killers, hunter killers, warriors.
Enter this.
Enter the eater killer hot dog area where moeur experience begins.
Hot dog ball.
You bet on hot dog.
When the ships going down, you will have.
Here's what you do in the apocalyptic future.
You use all the coins to pay your way into the.
You've heard there's like a secret vessel where you can survive
and you're taken all the way down under the sea with only hot dog
says you're offering.
And you get to a little sub a little submarine vessel.
And inside is James Cameron, who is it turns out as a big hot dog fan.
And it's his submarine is an underwater Oscar
Meyer Wiener Mobile.
It's just no wheels, no wheels on the Wiener Mobile aerodynamically,
actually the perfect submarine vessel.
And you live in the Oscar Meyer submarine with James Cameron
showing down on hot dogs while the shit hits the fan up on the surface.
I would love to be in the Marianas Trench in James Cameron's sub
toasting toasting hot dogs and laughing knowingly like
we really got them, didn't we?
James, we really pulled a fast one.
Then you hook your arms, you eat each other's dogs.
Like if you were drinking champagne with your new wife,
you guys eat each other's hot dogs like we did it.
And little do they know that unobtainium is real
and it actually keeps you alive for a thousand years.
Here's another shot of unobtainium, brother.
And then you somehow end up on Pandora.
Yeah, yeah, because it is also real.
Yep. Flying, flying mighty acrons and turning, turning other acrons.
Into hot dogs. Sure. Sure.
Well, who's laughing now?
Jason Jason and James Cameron.
And hopefully you hopefully had a good time listening to this episode.
If you want to hear more podcasts, right, fun, go to patreon.com
slash podcast, right where you'll you'll find the second gate,
a whole new world of fun and adventure.
And check us out on Twitter, Instagram, Facebook, Reddit.
Do I forget one in that list?
I don't public public assurance.
We have shirts. Yeah.
Public. We want we're not going to have coins.
That's for damn sure.
Those are for us. Although we should make coins.
Oh, yeah. Now that we're famously coin coin boys.
It's time to acknowledge any anything could put out pins.
We're going to have coins. Hashtag coin boys.
Each one will cost us.
Hashtag is your daddy. Hashtag coin coin boys.
Each one will cost us five hundred dollars to mint. Yes.
Limited run, though, of 10.
And you got to get them.
You'll have to find us and kill us.
Good luck. The chase is on.
Thanks for listening. Bye bye. Bye.
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.