Five, four, three, two, one.
All right, second gate, nobody asked for it,
and you got it.
We're finally doing it.
That could be most of the second gate, honestly.
The podcast in general, that is correct.
Today we are covering who wants to be a millionaire?
Play it.
Play it, exclamation point.
Play it, beginning the trend of weird punctuation
in theme park attractions.
Seems like it was written, when you would write it out,
it was who wants to be a millionaire,
dash play it, exclamation point.
So two punctuations in there.
Is it that long dash like guardians has?
It's like a longer, it's not just a minus sign,
it's kind of a long dash.
I always just kind of use those interchangeably
because I think a middle school English teacher
at a certain point got fed up after colons and semicolons
and went, you know what, we're moving on to Charles Dickens.
It was like, enough of this.
Hard, hard fight against colons.
You know what, let's just stick to literature.
Hmm, hmm.
And that affected the theme park naming structures
as we know them today.
And we're gonna get into all of that.
I'm Scott Garner, joined by Jason Sheridan
and Mike Carlson.
Hey, yeah.
Yeah, who wants to be a millionaire?
Play it.
Very possible that people don't know about this,
but they're for a brief time, I believe from 2001 to 2004
in Disney's California Adventure
and then in Disney's Hollywood Studios from 2001 to 2006.
There was a live experience themed after the ABC
game show mega hit, Who Wants to Be a Millionaire.
They perfectly recreated the set
and you could sit and watch.
Imagine that being on the set of a game show,
being in a theme park where you can go into magical forests
and the future and space and you get to sit
on a game show set.
This ride made, this attraction made it possible
and you got to play it.
This, for our younger listeners,
Who Wants to Be a Millionaire of its time
was the most popular show on TV.
Drawing something like 25 to 28 million viewings
in the early days and episode, it was an event.
It was so big in the summer of 1999
and I think it came out in nowhere.
I think it was primed to be a decent little summer hit,
summer where you don't have the sitcom season
so they can't rely on new Sabrina the Teenage Witch
or what the hell else was on step by step.
Yeah.
I guess not by that point,
but two guys, a girl and a pizza place.
So they have to invent some stuff for the summer
and I remember how thoroughly this blew up
and I think it seemed to come out of nowhere.
Regis Philbin, he's on TV all the time.
Why would a Regis Philbin thing be such a phenomenon?
But oh my God, it was, this format imported from England
and so much so that it started airing four nights a week
at its peak.
It was on TV so much.
Yeah, and it was an event.
I remember being down the beach in summertime,
like, okay, we ate dinner,
time to gather around the TV to watch
who wants to be a millionaire
and I remember seeing live the episode
because it went away and came back that November
and that's when the first guy won the million.
I just rewatched this, John Carpenter, was his name?
And he was so, he was cool as a cucumber.
That last question, he had not used a lifeline yet,
used a lifeline to call his dad to say,
dad, I'm just calling to tell you
I'm about to win the million dollars.
I know the answer to the question.
What a showboat, what a fuck you.
And he was right, he didn't know it.
Audience goes ape shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, I recall from the time that he then,
like two nights later, said live from New York,
it's Saturday night.
On Saturday night live.
100%.
There's this odd stray episode
in the history of who got to say that.
And this was- John Carpenter,
game show winner.
When like, start of 1999,
I remember being a kid feeling on top of the world
because I was like, I'm in eighth grade,
we're the oldest kids in the school, doing the play,
Islands of Adventure opening.
I was like a pig in shit.
And then fall 1999, I started high school
and reality hit me like a cement truck.
And yeah, freshman year was not easy.
Oh man, I can kind of relate to you
except for the part where I was on top of the world.
My middle school and high school were just the same,
there's just one continuity of like, ugh.
Oh, okay.
But I don't know, I think I felt some optimism
in the summer of, I know exactly what you're saying.
I think I was also going from middle school to high school
and Regis does make me think of like a summer vacation
where we all watched it and maybe I would achieve
some fortune with the reset that would come from high school
and this did not necessarily occur.
I also, this is a personal anecdote,
I got an accolade on the way out of middle school.
Like I, so there was like, you know, best whatever,
best chorus member, best yearbook editor, best all of this.
And there was best actors for the middle school.
And for one, it went to one guy and one girl
and two girls had tied in the past,
but two guys had never tied.
And me and another guy tied.
And I was like, yeah, we did it.
Look at us, we're good.
Huh.
Yeah.
And that was you and Mike Carlson.
And Mike Carlson, that's how we met.
We've known each other for 30 years.
I don't think that's.
That doesn't work out?
No, you're not 43 years old, are you?
Sometimes it feels like it.
The memory of it, I feel like we did watch it.
I don't know that we all gathered around the TV
to watch the show, but I do,
I was fascinated by it.
There was something about it where it was Regis,
it was a combination of Regis and like,
it was the start of these big,
like not that this is that high concept,
but this is, what's it called?
Deal or no deal doesn't happen without millionaire.
Like the back, the prime time game show is back.
And it's. Darkly lit.
They have more of a late night show vibe.
It's glowing floors.
It's glass and pillars.
And more quips. One versus 100 also.
I liked one versus a hundred.
I liked Wicked Link.
I thought she was very funny.
Yeah, they got a good, mean host.
Yeah, she was mean and Regis, you know, I like to read this,
but she was mean and that was different for a game show.
Yeah, that was.
You still got this trend today, essentially.
Yes, it's like almost back in crazier than ever now.
I'm excited for this Rob Lowe thing
where you're on an arm and it's swings you around.
Oh, yeah.
What color is the Smurfs green?
I saw that.
Sorry, it's blue.
Whoa.
That's a. Mechanical arm swings you around the room.
Is that a Cucar?
Yeah, they had to recheck that Cucar technology.
Mental Samurai.
We're talking about the new show Mental Samurai.
Are you a mental samurai?
It's like a high. Excited for him.
High budget Nickelodeon show.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because it does, it's like a crazy, like a,
you think of like Japanese game shows,
like doing more like that, stuff like that.
But no, prime time, baby.
Trivia cages in prime time.
And it wouldn't have happened without Regis.
That's true.
And I was just gonna mention the Titan games,
which I brought up before, the Rock's crazy.
Like it is an insane budget
and these are big stars hosting these shows.
And yeah, Regis did it.
It's Regis's fault.
Millionaire's been on ever since.
It never went away.
Right, it's just in syndication now.
Still in syndication?
I didn't even know, like, do you know Terry Crews
was the host of Who Wants to Be?
I did not know that.
I knew Meredith Vieira was the host.
And then who is it now?
If we worked in a hospital, we'd know this, but.
That's right.
Who is it now?
I think it's Chris Harrison from The Bachelor.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Yeah, but there's been more too.
I can't begin to name them all.
If I told you Jason hosted from 2009 to 2011,
would you believe it?
Kill for that.
I liked Meredith Vieira.
Sure?
His old job used to have the Today show on.
And I was like, yeah, I like when Meredith is on.
I think she was shit canned at some point.
Is that right?
I think so.
Is that a lower request?
She was on The View.
Maybe.
You're out.
Yeah.
She always seemed like a confident voice of reason.
I'm not recalling anything extremely dark with her,
which is a rarity for an NBC news personality.
I was thinking about that.
Like, oh, does she have skeletons?
We all went silent for a second.
I think we all went, is she scanning, scanning?
Is there a problem with Meredith Vieira?
We might discover there is one later.
Yeah, we'll do a follow up episode.
Apologizing for saying that she was okay.
That she fired a gun in the air,
like a state fair or something.
My favorite millionaire thing,
and I wanna say I did watch it live,
but I've seen the YouTube clip
as Norm MacDonald on Millionaire.
Where Norm breezes through the whole game
and then Regis convinces him not to risk it at the end.
Cause he's gonna, he's like kinda not confident
about the last question, do we get the million dollars?
And Regis is like, don't do it if you don't know.
Just take the 500,000.
And Norm's like, yeah, all right, fine.
So I think he took it.
And I think he would have won it,
but Regis talked him out of it.
It's a pretty crazy clip. Was it for charity?
Yeah. Oh, okay.
What if it wasn't?
In real life, whenever putting all your money on the line
was a possibility, Norm did it.
He took it. Yep.
And that brings him where he is today.
Yep.
But fake money.
At least he didn't risk charity money.
So this thing was a phenomenon in 1999.
Keep in mind what I said earlier.
This attraction opened in 2001.
By 2001, they were feeling the effects
of putting something on TV four nights a week.
The effect being that you get sick of it
and nothing, no star can burn that bright for that long.
And while Millionaire never went away,
it certainly stopped being a 25 million viewer a week
enterprise.
And another struggling enterprise
was Disney's California Adventure.
Yeah.
This was like the first band-aid put on the wound, wasn't it?
Like the first, like we gotta get something in there.
Yeah. That was, yeah, sort of the quickest possible,
you know, it went up in the Hollywood area
and building a fake soundstage building
is relatively easy.
They could build a box easier than they can build
a new roller coaster or tower of terror.
So in it went.
If you're in California Adventure today
and you imagine that the Muppets are on the left
and the Monsters Inc ride is straight ahead of you,
then kind of also straight ahead of you,
but also off to the left, kind of buried in a corner
is the building where Millionaire was.
And that is used, I remember there was some weird
like Frozen Village in there.
It's still sort of set up there
because there was a Pixar Pier event a couple months ago
that I signed up for on the blog
and the Frozen Village stuff's still in there.
Oh, they just know you like saw an open door in it.
It was just in there.
It was just like some of the stuff,
like set, like place making stuff were still up.
So this is still the area where the temporary crap goes.
California Adventure.
And so they, yeah, immediate problems.
We're thinking about this timeline.
This is February 2001.
They have immediately determined things are not working out.
What properties do we possibly have?
Let's jam this into the park.
They do it, they get it open, it is sparkling and ready
and we're almost ready to open it in September 2001.
Then some things happen and the ride,
the attraction opens on September 14th, 2001.
What a day to work that, like to work that first day
of operation, can you imagine?
Everybody's in a mood for trivia.
Everybody's, you know, everybody's in a great mood
for the quips of a game show host.
And in it went.
So several curses here.
The property has been diminished
in an immediately diminished park,
immediately after a tragedy.
But how do they counteract it?
What is the show that,
how is the show able to rise above all of these challenges?
Do you know?
Well, I gotta say, the set does look like the TV show set.
I do have to get them that.
Accuracy.
And I believe the prizes
can fetch a pretty penny on eBay, the pin sets and stuff.
Okay, well, let's talk about that.
The game is called Who Wants to Be a Millionaire.
The theme park attraction does not give you
the possibility of being a millionaire.
Well, you can get a million points, right?
You get a million points.
Yeah.
Could you wait, I'm getting confused now.
The one in Florida you could get on the real show, maybe.
Is that right?
That was, so if you got to a million points
for a short period of time in the early run
of the Florida show, you may win a chance
to go see a taping in New York
of Who Wants to Be a Millionaire.
And then eventually you would win a Disney Cruise vacation.
Oh, cause I'm confused.
Cause I was, I feel like they made it unclear
cause I played this in Florida.
And I was under the impression that
I was gonna be able to get on the show
if I won out of the whole room.
Wait, now played it?
Were you in the hot seat?
No.
Oh.
You played it in the audience.
Yes.
Oh, okay.
Every audience member had a chance to buzz in,
which could get you down to the 10 rows of chairs
where you could get a chance to get to the hot seat.
Yeah, you had to come to get a ticket
to get a passport that would give you entry
to sit in a chair.
Yeah, so if I had won that,
then they would have invited me the next round
to sit in the closer seats.
Or is that right?
Something like that.
I think they did two or three rounds per each session.
I remember being so confused cause for a couple rounds,
much like when we did a lead of Battle Angel,
a couple rounds, I was doing very well.
So much so that in the big room,
I was up top five or 10 or something.
And they kept showing,
did they show stats and say like,
here's who's well. They did.
They did on the big leader board.
Oh, interesting.
Now, did you guys both do this then?
Cause I never did it.
No, never.
I never remember watching it. I did it in Florida.
You did.
But not out here.
Okay.
So what, when am I?
How did I lose?
I'm not that smart.
Oh.
I mean, I'm not smart as some 10 people or whatever
that were in the room at the time.
I mean, the on deck chairs were a staple of the TV show
and they would have to put stuff in the correct order.
And the one who did it fastest,
like which of these battles in World War II came first?
That's probably a little too heady.
But whoever did it fastest got into the hot seat
and got to play with the host.
Okay.
The host who is,
it was those ever emulating Regis in any way,
or was it like just to, you know,
bring your own personality to it?
I think you had to make it your own.
I think, yeah.
As many casting directors will tell you.
I think some people early on were encouraged
to imitate Regis, but.
My memory was a generic host.
Yeah.
So yeah, I don't think there would like trying to,
they weren't doing Dana Carvey's Regis.
Like they weren't.
Well, that would have been fun.
Now that I think about it,
they should have all tried to do their Regis.
Yeah.
That would actually have been a better choice.
That's a lot of like women,
like Florida actresses doing.
Great.
Out of control.
I did say on Wikipedia that the various hosts
tried to emulate the US prime time host Regis Philips.
Really?
Hosting style, including his mannerisms.
But I watched the very last taping
and it was just a charismatic camera ready kind of guy.
So you are competing not to be a millionaire.
You're competing to maybe go on a cruise
or maybe go to a taping.
Along the way, there's like pins, you said?
So similar to millionaire, similar to the TV show,
like every five questions,
you would like lock in your winning level.
So if you got to a thousand points,
that was question five.
You got five questions right.
You got to play at lanyard,
100 through 1000 level pins, that's a pin set,
and a 1000 point baseball cap.
If you got to 10 questions right, that was 32,000 points.
You got the lanyard, 100 through 32,000 point pins,
a thousand level baseball cap,
and a 32,000 point embroidered shirt.
Getting pretty good.
If you get to a million,
that means you answered 15 questions right.
You get the lanyard, 100 to 1 million point pins.
So 15 fucking pins with numbers on them.
A 1000 point baseball cap, 32,000 point embroidered shirt,
1 million point leather jacket.
Whoa.
A 1 million point medallion.
You know how, you know we're all coin boys here.
And a Disney Cruise Line vacation for four.
Damn, all right.
That's sizable.
That is good.
Do we have any sense of how people did?
Were they giving these prizes away a lot?
Or was Disney trying to be stingy?
It seemed like people did all right.
I know enough that if you won,
if you were in the hot seat and won
like you had a six month ban from coming back,
and I think if you got the million,
you had a one year ban from coming back.
I think you'd still enjoy it, but you could not play it.
So that I said play it with a period at the end of that time.
All right, I found a new, who wants to be,
it says it's new, which it's Glatton new,
but apparently maybe it's never worn.
Maybe it's still in the bag.
Disney, who wants to be a millionaire
souvenir embroidered cat hat?
Cat, I got a weird dyslexic thing there.
Hat cap, I guess is what it is.
It's $11.
Okay.
Should I buy it?
That's up to you.
That's your call.
That feel, I mean, like it's,
you know, everyone takes pictures of their fit, right?
That's what the young people say.
They're fit.
You can be a hype beast.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
New slang from Jason.
Isn't that an outfit?
Like you're fit, you take fit pics.
Oh, I've never heard that.
Do you know what that is?
No.
Isn't that, am I crazy on this one?
You know, I'm sure you know what you're talking about.
I just never heard it before.
Huh.
Well, I'm going to think about buying this hat
because I'm a hat guy.
I mean, you are, as usual, when we record,
you're wearing mostly Supreme branded clothing.
As if you were waiting for a, you know,
a new sneaker release down on Fairfax.
And I think this, who wants to be a millionaire,
thousand point hat will go nicely with it.
Is it flat, is it flat for him or is it bent a little?
It's bent.
Okay.
All right, well, that'll be a cliffhanger.
Will I buy the hat?
Will you buy this hat?
Does Mike buy the hat?
Is that your birthday present to yourself?
Maybe.
Oh, there's multiple hats.
There's multiple Disney who wants to be a millionaire.
Look for the pins.
I think the pins.
Oh, I found the pins, yeah.
Yeah.
So these are all great ways to convince people
that you want on the show.
To, you know, pop up yourself in a catch me if you can way.
Yeah.
The logo, I mean, the logo for this attraction.
I mean, it's the logo for the TV show,
but to play it under, like this is a 2001 ass logo.
Yeah. Right?
Oh yeah. Very much so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I had a problem, I think in general,
with ABC being a big property in the parks.
I just never sat well with me.
And I feel like California Adventure opened
and there was a ton of it.
The soap opera, Bistro.
I hated seeing those posters around.
It's just not, I don't know, it's not right.
I think if there was like a giant,
if there was like a Game of Thrones level immersive show
on ABC and you made a ride out of it
or did something about it, fine.
But like, don't give me a private practice replica coffee
shop, it's weird.
It's just, it just feels chintzy.
Even though a TV show is a big expensive thing,
it's just a TV show in a theme park,
I think is really weird.
Yeah, I wonder, I should ask my parents
or my mom specifically.
I mean, she liked that soap opera.
That was a better show, obviously, in Hollywood studios
because she was in it, that show where they,
or not just specifically so far.
Superstar television?
Superstar television, yes.
Yeah.
But still, I do know what you're talking about
because like TV, even at the time,
it would be like TV shows, I don't know.
Are they cartoons or like, it doesn't really,
doesn't seem to work for me.
Yeah.
Like, yeah, it felt different, felt weird.
I think this has come up where like,
there's films after they come out kind of enter the canon
or disappear, but like TV shows age a lot quicker.
Sure.
Like how many TV shows from the last 10 years
are we really gonna be watching?
You know, we, the collective we,
of like, I guess Game of Thrones, Mad Men, Breaking Bad.
Mm-hmm.
Well, and you know, CSI is something
that'll never go away, which is why there is a CSI experience
in the MGM Grand in Las Vegas.
But that's, but CSI has sort of stood the test of time.
Yeah, that is like, yeah.
So that one, but you gotta be sure,
this is like, like minimum, it's gotta be a 15 season,
or perhaps multi-series TV franchise,
and that's the only way.
Walking Dead, I guess.
I don't, I feel like Walking Dead's
in that sort of perma place at Universal Hollywood.
Yeah, I mean, I'm sure I have, actually, you know what?
I have not been there yet, even though I like haunts,
but I saw, I should go into the Walking Dead.
Yeah, a new thing for me.
I should go through there, but I wonder if you,
I wonder if it's probably pretty easily,
like if they need to change the theme.
I bet it's not so crazy.
Did I say the word perma?
Like, I meant, it feels very like temp.
Oh, that's what you meant.
I see. Yeah, yeah, yes, yes.
Like it's, you know, it's where the house of horrors,
like stuff that they've switched in and out.
It feels like they could swap in if they,
cause they've done those Blumhouse houses
at two or three years now at Halloween Horror Nights.
If they lost the license from Walking Dead
or the show ended, they could easily,
like Blumhouse is at Universal,
so they could make it half Happy Death Day
and half The Purge or something.
Yeah.
The, they also had the weirdness where at some point
they had to also advertise
the Meredith Vieira syndicated version.
So you've got just a poster for a syndicated TV show
up really big in your theme park, which is already,
and Hollywood continues to be one of the chinsiest areas
of California Adventure or of any theme park.
It's just not good.
None of this is good.
No.
But one thing I do kind of like about it is the lifelines.
Couple of the lifelines could be the same.
50-50 is the same.
Ask the audience.
There's a big audience there.
That can be the same.
Phone a friend is a tough one
cause you don't want to wait around
in this uneditable live experience
for somebody to call a friend.
So they had to set up a phone just out in the park
and they labeled it phone a complete stranger.
Phone a complete stranger is such a funny phrasing
of what you would call that.
Yeah, I do like it.
Yeah.
And I like that you could have,
I wish I'd been there to pick up the phone.
Oh yeah.
And I wonder if they ever had a problem with somebody,
saying a curse or saying ba-ba-booey and hanging up.
How could they, they must've had to keep an eye on that.
Where was the phone?
Was it by the queue though?
Was it by like?
So like the people in line knew sort of already?
In line maybe.
Oh, maybe.
And cast members would be there around anyway.
Explaining, maybe ushering people to the phone
is sort of under lock and key.
Could you imagine talking to a stranger
and you ask them the question
and when they say the answer is ba-ba-booey,
ba-ba-booey Howard Stern's fetus?
Maybe that was the answer.
Oh, maybe it was.
It could have been depending on the question.
What have you been encouraged to yell into a church
by a national media figure?
What is the current preferred prank phone call saying?
Jerky boys.
Stern rules.
We need to get somebody who did this.
We have to find the host.
We have to find a host.
Yeah, those people have to be floating around for sure.
Because there have to be funny stories
where people didn't know or said something weird or cursed.
I would think it would make the most sense
to the people in line
because they're in the millionaire mode already.
They know the show, they know the rules
and they don't want to foul up the experience.
They have respect for it.
It would be great if the phone was in the middle of the raft
on the Grizzly River Rapids ride
and in the middle of getting soaked,
your dad has to answer a trivia question.
It's like, oh, I don't think, ah, what the hell?
Hang on.
She got soaked.
Put my wife on, hang on.
Or they just took a raft ride and they're bone dry
and have to take a phone call,
which occasionally you do come out of Grizzly River Rapids
very dry, like not a good.
If you're lucky.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's true, but usually you're a little wet.
Yeah, but it's not designed in the way that like the rapids,
Popeye and Pluto's bilge rat barges are designed.
Oh my God, I could not answer a trivia question on that thing.
No, absolutely not.
They soaked, you get buckets of water dumped on you.
Almost knocked my glasses into the rapids.
It's insane.
It is a real test for how thrilling is a raft ride.
Could you acceptably take a phone call on it?
Could you call it a trivia question?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, and so yeah, Popeye, no.
Grizzly River Rapids, it depends, is the answer.
That's very damning against Grizzly River Rapids.
Which of these actors have played Spider-Man,
Tobey Maguire, Tom Holland, Andrew Garfield,
or Robert Blake?
What'd you say?
I don't know, D.
I'm pretty sure it's D.
D. Robert Blake.
Beretta himself.
Well, while we don't have anybody with us who was the host
or who got into the hot seat, guess what?
You guys are about to have an opportunity
to go into the hot seat yourselves.
As we've established on the Sea Ticket episodes,
there are games.
Oh my God.
And as this is a game show themed episode,
we've got to do it now.
And that's why I'd like to invite one of you
to play Who Wants to Waste Time on a Second Gate episode.
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da.
How are we going to decide?
How do we decide?
We decide with the fastest finger question.
Uh-oh.
And I should make you aware that all of the,
as I slip into this voice, that all of the trivia items
in this game are Regis related.
So start thinking through your Regis knowledge
as I ask this fastest finger question to determine
who will play.
So do I say buzz or do I say buzz or something?
I think you should say buzz buzz.
Buzz buzz.
OK.
If you have it, say buzz buzz and then give me the answer.
I like the past Sea Ticket games.
Well, of course, now, as we know with comedy,
first time something happens, it's a phenomenon.
Second time, it's coincidence.
Third time, it's pattern.
And so now this establishes a pattern.
But like the previous games, you seemed like you were
doing this begrudgingly.
That's been consistent the entire time.
But a great Regis impression.
So I'm excited.
Oh, thank you.
I'm feeling pretty good about it.
We'll see if it can maintain for the entire length of the game.
Let's play it.
OK.
Get your buzz buzzes ready.
In the Disney Christmas parades, Regis Philbin
wanted a kiss from what character?
I feel free to attempt a false one,
even I'll give you more than one chance.
Okay.
Wait, this isn't multiple choice?
No, not this, no,
because I couldn't figure out how to do that
because you don't have fingers.
I don't have anything to hope yet.
Oh, we had a good point.
One of you just has to win.
Cinderella?
Well, you didn't say Buzz Buzz, but okay.
Was it Cinderella?
I'll still count it.
You said Cinderella.
I could have gotten you on a technicality,
but I'm feeling generous today.
All right.
Mike Carlson from Schomburg, Illinois.
Yes.
You're in the hot seat.
Thank you Regis.
We waited 45, Edwin, we waited 45 fucking minutes
for this ride.
Pipe down in the back.
We need to focus on Mike Carlson.
He's been a friend of 40 years.
Any funny stories from growing up you'd like to share?
Any of anything fun about yourself?
Oh, yeah.
I, as a,
I like Minnie Mouse.
All right, well it's time to play it.
Okay, here we go.
Well, I need to lay out the rules.
I will be asking one question,
and if you get the answer correct,
you stand to receive a prize that is a real prize
that was given out in Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?
Play it.
Oh, wow.
So the stakes are high.
Oh my gosh.
And in keeping with the game, you do have three lifelines.
They are 50-50, I eliminate two of the incorrect choices.
Ask someone else in the room,
which brings your choices.
I'll take myself out of it, but that would be Jason.
That would be Lindsay,
who has been eating cereal in the corner.
I'm dragging her into this,
but it's her, she doesn't have to participate
if she doesn't want to. Of course, yeah.
And it's your choice who you pick, or Edwin the dog.
Sure.
Or phone a friend, and you can phone anyone that you like,
but I should let you know that just in case
our mutual friend Andrew Grissom
is casually standing by and may slip into a corner
at the place where he's working
to try to answer this question.
Of course, he's not qualified to do so.
I just wanted there to be a friend element.
Okay, so, but you can only use one.
But maybe you don't need it.
Let's go.
For the one prize,
in April, 2009, Regis Philbin appeared on The Late Show
with David Letterman dressed as who?
A, Harry Potter.
B, Shrek.
C, Dr. Phil.
D, Jack Sparrow.
The answer, Regis, is B, Shrek.
Final answer.
Yes.
All right, without a lifeline, a risky move.
I guess it's a good point I should have just done the lifeline.
I mean that's a look Grissom seemed to be busy.
He'd slipped into a conference room 15 minutes ago and said, hey, I'm in here in case you
need me.
But now he went back to his desk.
So his availability is in question.
Feel free to throw it to anyone else in the room if you'd like to waste more time on a
second gate episode.
I think it's Shrek.
But let me throw it to Jason.
Do you know? Do you think it's Shrek?
Well, what do you think Regis Philman's threshold of looking foolish is?
Oh, Regis would embarrass himself.
He didn't care. He was very much up for anything.
I feel like Dr. Phil is the more grounded answer though.
I'm pretty positive in my head that Regis is Shrek.
But I maybe it's not.
I don't think it's Dr. Phil, although it's possible he was Dr. Phil once and Shrek another
time.
But keep in mind, it is a specific.
I don't think he appeared more than once.
It is April 2009.
Oh, I'm just saying there's a chance that he appeared as a different character once as
well.
Possibly.
That's possible.
We have to think about April 2009.
April 2009.
Is that when the Shrek musical was out?
Jason, what do you think?
Might have been running or in previews.
I know at that live Human Giant, a 24 hour, 48 hour takeover on MTV, Tim and Eric
kept showing up as Shrek.
That would have been 2007.
So that would have been Shrek 2 likely.
So 2009 had digital animation progressed enough to turn around a Shrek in two years.
Well, I think it was live show Shrek, the live musical maybe where he was farting.
Oh, sure.
There was a song about farting in the live.
We'll do a second episode about that one day, I'm sure.
There's a farting episode.
It was what?
Captain Jack, Dr. Phil, Shrek.
Harry Potter, Shrek, Dr. Phil, Dr. Shakespeare.
Harry Potter.
When did the last Harry Potter book come out?
Oh, after 2007.
Well, this is 2009 we're talking about.
Oh, 2009.
I'm losing my mind.
We're overthinking this so much.
I think the answer is Shrek.
That feels right to me.
I have a thing in my head that is a picture of Regis sitting on the chair with Dave and
he's got the Shrek outfit on.
I can't think of him dressed as any of those other characters.
Well, there's no stakes.
So why don't you do your 50-50 too?
Okay.
No, I know one.
We can only do one.
You can only do one?
Yeah, that was it.
That discussion you guys had was the lifeline.
Text.
Can I text Grissom?
Nope.
You can't make up a different type of lifeline.
I mean, Shrek's the funniest answer to give.
I think it's Shrek.
Final answer.
This is a video reveal which I will now play.
I'm stressed out.
Can I help you?
Guess who I am.
Oh my god.
Of course, I've seen this.
It's Regis Philbin.
It's not Regis.
Dressed like a Shrek.
How you doing, buddy?
Yeah, that's right.
My memory's right.
You look like Buddy Hackett after a bad clam.
That's a solid joke.
That's a great joke.
Yep, I edited the video to fit.
I'll ease out of Regis.
I don't need to be doing it.
Although I, well, no, no, I hate to hang on because I do need to give you the prize.
Because you have successfully wasted time on a second gate episode and you have won the
prize, a real prize, that was given out during the live show, during Play It.
One sec.
Is it the hat I wanted to buy?
Oh, well, wouldn't that be a wonderful gift to the Magi, wouldn't it be?
No, no, no, what I have for you is a seedy rom of Who Wants to Be a Millionaire Sports
Edition.
We had the regular one.
Wow.
Well, I'm glad I didn't get the sports one.
I'm glad I didn't get the regular one because now you have a second.
I have a second one.
I don't have anything to put it in.
This was also a prize in the early days.
No CDs, no computers don't have CD ports anymore.
Don't have a Windows PC lying around.
Well, yes, I should say you do need a four time speed CD-ROM drive and you are going
to need 32 megabytes of RAM.
So if you think that's the final test.
Well, it should come with a CD drive, an external CD drive that I could plug into the Mac.
You're going to have to buy that separately on eBay.
There's been a lot of Mike Carlson related eBaying going on in Scott Gardner's house.
I don't know when this one comes out as opposed to the other one.
I'll leave that a clue.
I'd also just like to say that separately on the back, this says a slam dunk gift for
millionaire and sports fan and then a grand slam for sports trivia fans.
So it's a slam dunk if you're a sports fan, but if you're a sports trivia fan, it is a
grand slam.
It is not a slam dunk gift for a sports trivia fan.
It's a home run for podcast transitions because this attraction sometimes had special event
versions.
Oh, oh, I know where you're going with this.
During ESPN, the weekend play, it consisted of sports trivia questions and you got to
team up with ESPN personalities and figures.
And the phone, a complete stranger lifeline was replaced with a chance to ask an ESPN
expert, which was either Howie Schwab or the Sklar brothers.
What?
Yeah, they just there for it's a weekend.
Yeah, I think they flew in like for events because the other special event weekend was
Star Wars weekends.
And this is I got to read the first two games of the day featured questions based on the
Star Wars films and universe and began with Greedo in the hot seat answering questions
in the alien language, Rodanese.
The lifelines worked exactly like the regular game, but were named 50 50.
Ask the Jedi Council and phone a stormtrooper.
So they were trying to keep it up, trying to keep it relevant.
Form a phone, a phone, a stormtrooper.
Did it actually just phone a friend?
Do we know?
Or was it actually like a preset like stormtrooper?
I guess there's a stormtrooper by the phone and they would answer in the stormtrooper
voice.
So somebody that was somebody's job basically all day is just to sit around.
Well, just the first two shows of the day.
Oh, right.
This was an interesting run, one to run operationally because it seemed like to be the first contestant
in the hot seat.
Sometimes you would just get it automatically at the fast pass distribution or sometimes
you could just ask towards the end and you could be in it.
Oh, so it's like any ride vehicle where if you asked to be in the front seat.
Kind of.
Maybe that would work.
It seems like it started to get less serious as time went on.
Or at least get to the first 10 people.
Huh, that's interesting.
Yeah, I really was for a second there.
I really thought I was going to be in that hot seat soon because I was doing so well.
So it was disappointing because it did seem like it, but I would have cracked, I think.
But you got to do it today.
You know what, I got to do it today.
I should hand this over, but congratulations.
I'm very impressed you didn't even need one.
Just like John Carpenter, you didn't need a lifeline.
And in fact, I told Andrew Grissom that we didn't need him and he was sad.
But I'm going to see if he gets the answer right.
We'll try to get a risk.
So let's see if he would have even been a bad choice as a Kona friend.
Who wants to be a millionaire sports addition now in your position?
CD-ROM, congrats.
How much, could I ask how much this was?
Well, a million points, which roughly translates to $3.33.
Still in the wrapper though.
Yes, yeah.
So there's tremendous resale value.
So that it was a stocking stuffer someone really was annoyed about.
Unless you were a Grand Slam Dunk Sports Trivia master.
Buena Vista Interactive, which I'm not sure what, like in the chronology of like games,
Disney games, because Disney now very famously is like, they're not making video games anymore.
You know, the job I have been working recently has a bunch of lamps that all on the bottom
of them have, there's a label on the lamp that says property of Disney Interactive.
I think I'm working in an office that inherited a bunch of the office furniture of Disney
Interactive.
When they dumped it.
That's how dead they are.
Famously, yeah, downsized a bunch, Disney Interactive.
But they're not making like original games.
They're just licensing it.
I think something like that.
Mostly for big video games.
So you got to, this is a passport into a brighter time for Disney's CD-ROM enterprises.
Yeah.
So to clarify, yeah, sometimes to get into that row of 10 seats, pre-hot seat, you would
get occasionally a Magic Moment coupon dispensed instead of a fast pass.
There were several tickets, basically.
There were several times where just asking before the show began would grant access to
one of the seats.
And there was still some open before the show.
And I think it's interesting.
Was there a timer on who wants to be a millionaire of how long people had questions to take?
I feel like people would really milk it sometimes.
Yeah, that's how they were able to spread it out into four nights.
Deal or no deal, also a real time waster.
A lot of reaction shots, a lot of milling around.
Yeah.
But there was a timer on this.
First five questions, you had 30 seconds.
First five questions, yeah, 30 seconds per question.
Next five, 45.
And the final four questions, 55 seconds.
So you were on a clock.
And the show was kind of dependent of like, the next show starts at this time or whenever
the last show gets out.
They wouldn't cut people off.
They would let the games continue.
It wouldn't be like, all right, get out of here.
We got a two 30 to get ready for.
I mean, I'm sure some people were knocked out within the first five questions and that
was quick and they could squeeze more in.
Yeah.
So the game didn't have a it wasn't like a like the Little Mermaid show at Hollywood
Studios where it would be every 45 minutes or something.
I think it had a in theory set thing, but there was a little bit of wiggle room, which
sounds like a nightmare for the operation.
I was going to say like that's that is a no no.
They want to know exactly when things are in and out and how many people and consistency
of a robot show.
Len Testa must have been losing his mind when they were he was counting people calling,
calling out to try to figure out an algorithm for how many people this attraction could
eat up all day.
So and then the band.
So if you won 100 to 500,000 points, you had a 30 day blackout.
And if you won the million, you had a 30 day blackout and you were not permitted to win
the million again for 365 days.
Did anybody try to get it or did anybody successfully get it?
I mean, sometimes did someone have a calendar where they would mark off each day and as
soon as this calendar is over, I'm back.
I can't wait to be back on the Disney dream.
It's like Cape Fear.
It's marking them on his back.
It's how he marks.
I guess somebody I mean, I wonder.
Well, there is an interesting one that the GSC, the trivia about who got the hot seat.
Oh, yeah.
No, I didn't see this.
The man who won five hundred thousand dollars on the syndicated version.
He became an expert when they started doing something called Ask the Expert.
And he bid on eBay for the seat.
And he saw my God.
Wait, what? Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. How much did he bid on it for?
How much did he get it for?
Four hundred dollars.
Four hundred dollars on this piece of theme park memorabilia.
What? That's it.
That seems low. This was put.
Somebody took the time to put this into a Wikipedia.
Yeah. Huh.
It's very low.
And and, you know, it's look, it's not Richard Kraft stats.
No, no.
The stuff going for a few hundred dollars was like paper products, brochures, press
kits, like that sort of thing.
I know, because I looked because I looked.
How much is the cheapest thing available right now?
Disneyland toilet knob would go for four hundred fifty.
I don't know. Yeah, I'm surprised that's from Disneyland.
Didn't have a section of just exclusively who wants to be a millionaire.
Remember, Bill? Yeah.
The exclamation point from the play it sign.
Box of hats, box of old hats, alternate Regis jackets,
like a like a XXXL Regis jacket like is is signature just like sure.
Chrome black, but they never got a host of that size needed.
I have to say, like, I don't think it's the wrong impulse of like this show is a phenomenon.
What if we got in the parks?
But I think they also should have copied like a limited run like that.
It was like two weeks at a time.
Like, I know you have to build a whole set that's complicated.
But ironically, playing this version of the game is closer to what you would see on TV.
Because we go to a real game show taping.
They're always stopping and starting and reset it like TV show tapings are kind of miserable to go to.
So you're saying that you would want it to be more you wouldn't want it to be a continuous attraction.
Yeah, I mean, I guess that would be the thing to do it.
Like, I think there is like a fun live element of like an interactive audience game show kind of thing.
People do get invested in that competitive in that.
But like, I don't know, five or six years is actually a pretty good run.
It's like, wow, I'm surprised it lasted as long as it did.
That's how long it made it in Florida.
Yeah, nearly as long in California.
No, no. You know, as I said, that space is now like temporary events in California Adventure.
In Florida, it was replaced by Midway Mania.
So a bit of a step up.
Yeah, fair enough.
The amount of plus up there is the did you see that Captain Marvel photo up they just started with like a big is it inflatable plane behind it?
It's a weird looking plane behind her.
I am impressed that they went out of their way to do it.
But is it in this building?
It it might be.
It just started, I think.
And that looks good.
She looks the walk around.
Cat Marvel looks pretty good.
I was impressed with the photo.
But it might be this building that they're using.
Or it could be the old Finns Arcade, the other sound.
Oh, yeah. Good point.
There's a lot of ugly sound stages that I guess are good for backstage stuff and staging and everything.
But that is a huge plot of land that like in the next 20 years, something's got to go over that.
It's probably it's either this or it's that what you're talking about.
It's one of those two, I would assume.
Yeah, they made a big like air.
Did you see it?
No, there's a big like fighter jet sticking out of the like hangar, essentially, which is just one of these sound stages.
That's cool.
So they did something with one of these buildings.
So maybe the where this thing was has something cool now.
Maybe maybe maybe a happy ending.
You know what? I think the idea of a game show, the live game show in a theme park is a little fun and it kind of hey,
it harkens back to Nickelodeon studios at Universal Studios.
It's not the worst idea.
I think tying it to sort of a of its time, like they missed it by like a year.
But but so this was a little off.
But, you know, a game show in a theme park, not not so crazy.
Right. You guys have favorite game shows that you'd like to see represented in a theme park in some way.
They might be more successful.
It's hard because you would these mega crazy shows like one versus a hundred would be great,
which was not as popular as these other ones.
But I liked it. It was one.
It was a hundred people all answering the question.
So it was not dissimilar to this situation because then you would have to like bet.
I forget you bet like with the hundred or against the hundred.
And then a hundred would get like eliminated.
Apparently, this is too complicated, which is why people why people didn't watch it as much.
But you would get all of a sudden, like 50 of the hundred would get the question wrong and then all their lights would go out.
But it was it was kind of a cool visual.
So it would make sense that you would load in a hundred people for a theme park.
And then you're in it. Now you're in the show.
You're in the actual show.
But there's not a lot of these that lend themselves to a giant group other than if like you played.
Jeopardy or something, then you have appeared in Ellen's energy.
Right. I mean, you could.
Then you'd have to type in your answer.
It wouldn't be multiple choice.
I mean, you could add multiple choice to it, but Jeopardy doesn't have multiple choice.
I think Jeopardy works just fine sitting and watching it at home.
I don't think I need to be part of the tremendous energy of Jeopardy Live.
Fair enough. But one just occurred to me that I think would be fun.
And you know what? You'll like this because this is, I guess, maybe an idea for a for a haunt.
What if you were inside the game board of Press Your Luck?
Oh, wow.
And you're gathering money along the way.
But around any corner, there could be a whammy.
And he jumps out at you, maybe spooks you, maybe you make him scarier than he is just in cartoon form.
Or he just jumps out and like does La Cucaracha and, you know, like has like little like Carmen Miranda clam shells.
Yeah.
Like they bite your money up.
Hey, I love that's a great idea.
It's not going to be like the game show, but I think as a haunt, it's a pretty good idea.
If you actually are, this is maybe a good haunt hybrid idea that you are getting money through the haunt
and your ability to keep the money depends on your ability to not get scared or to jump or.
That's great.
I do like, yeah, haunted house based on a game show, like like a whole game show set.
That's kind of spooky.
Let's expand the idea.
And it's just like Merv Griffin land.
And it's just a theme park that a game show rides and experiences.
Drunk pervert.
Griff, just assume he was an old drunk pervert.
I mean, you don't want to go spreading rumors about her.
I think if you were just an old in front of like camera host that far back, right?
Then he's got to be.
He might have been the kind of pervert that didn't hurt anybody.
It could be.
Is this a regular everyday pervert?
I think you're thinking of Richard Dawson.
Oh, maybe.
Who's a little more pervert.
Although who knows?
I don't know what Merv Griffin was up to.
We should generally stay away from the family feud hosts in building this park.
Fair enough.
Except for Richard Karn.
He's fine.
I have some information.
I was trying to think of an Air Force way to say it.
Captain Marvel is meeting in Hangar 12, recruits, cadets.
Hangar 12.
You've been working on the Captain Marvel joke the whole time?
No, I was looking up which soundstage it was in.
Oh, this was in soundstage 10?
No, it was 12 Flynn's.
I think 12 is the other one.
So that's where the Flynn's arcade was.
This one's weird and in the corner.
It's a terrible location.
Also keep in mind this was next door to Superstar Limo when it opened.
Yeah, I know where it is.
September 11th has just occurred and you are in the worst theme park in the world
where you go one way and it's a fake Regis and you go another way
and it's a horrifying mannequin portraying Melanie Griffith.
Uh, it felt like it was manifested by the times that it was existing in.
In some ways, this pocket of the park, it encapsulates 2001 in a horrible way.
Yeah, so it makes sense that the photo op is over there,
although they were doing other photo ops over in this soundstage.
Yeah, it's the old Finn's.
Yeah, which is also kind of out of the woods by the bathroom.
Flynn? Flynn? Flynn? Flynn's.
Tron? Tron is Flynn.
Finn is Star Wars. Flynn is Tron.
Finn is also Breaking Bad, what the sun started calling himself.
Oh, yeah, his full nickname.
Yes, that's right.
And that's everything that Finn is.
My pitch was going to be some sort of a supermarket sweep dark ride.
Hell yeah.
Oh, Aaron's been all about supermarket sweep.
Do you guys, it's not 100 percent, but Guy's Grocery Games on the Food Network.
I haven't seen it.
It's not a bad...
Is it like supermarket sweep?
You have to run around and find ingredients to then make a delicious dish for the judges.
I like that, but it almost seems more...
And there's some requirements.
It seems more sophisticated, though, than the dumbness of supermarket sweep that I liked.
It is.
Where were you going?
You get nice sweaters.
Are you given matching sweaters to get on this ride?
Oh, yeah, of course.
And I'm in, but what else were you?
Well, it's the problem is they generally don't want you to touch stuff when you're on a dark
ride because they want people to lose an arm or get caught on something.
But this will have to go so slow.
Well, that's the problem.
OK, here's what it is.
I figured it out.
It'll be a ride vehicle and it'll shoot you into the aisle.
It gets you in that aisle real fast.
Then it slows down so slow and maybe like sort of the Star Wars rumors.
You get out, you run up and down the aisle, you grab as much stuff, put it in the back
of your vehicle, you get back in and then it shoots you back to the front.
You're like in a big shopping cart, essentially.
OK, that's good, too.
Let's make the ride vehicle like a big shopping cart and there's a section for humans and
then there's a section.
It'll be like your babies and you'll be in like the front.
It'll be like a baby seat.
It's because it's that big.
Yeah. So you'll have to get out.
You'll you'll shop, you'll throw it in and then there'll be many hams as you can.
Yeah, just many of all turkeys.
It is weird that that's what everyone because I was also just now thinking I loved it when
they would grab a butterball turkey.
I don't know what's so satisfying about that.
Really odd. It's odd with like that there is like music with a lot of momentum and a
announcer like a sporting event.
But you are watching a woman gather up giant turkeys from close to the floor.
It's a really I think the mix is what makes it so funny.
Yeah. And I think it feels like it's some sort of fantasy because I think in our human
brains, there's all these like instinct like we've talked on the show before about like
doing something bad.
Like I would think during a band like band recital, I could just play the trumpet right
now and ruin this whole thing.
There's like we get bad thoughts.
Yeah. So I think that like you see order and you see a store, there's always like a
feeling of like you want to trash it maybe.
And then this is the ultimate fantasy for people because what is about it?
You're given permission.
Stealing. I guess when we were kids, they had those those prize, those sweepstakes
prizes where you'd run into KB Toys and just unload stuff into the cart.
Do you remember that? Obviously, it's a dream to do.
Yes. Obviously, that's toys.
So that makes sense. But supermarkets, we've almost just as satisfying to watch.
Were you a fan of Finders Keepers?
Oh, yeah, I love finding the board game.
Finders Keepers.
I should get the board game.
Yeah.
I don't think I still have it.
That's a you went on a room to room romp.
And I don't want to sidetrack, but I love the host of Finders Keepers, Wesley Youre,
who was like a man who is just generally uncomfortable around children and should not
have been talking to them and and like would like sometimes get a little weird and like
yell at him. And there's this one where he was not happy with the the level to which
they were tearing the room apart.
And he says, come on, you got to go for it.
Spiders Keepers.
He's mad that they didn't go for it.
So then there the kids just stare like, why are you Nickelodeon?
You're a grown up yelling at us.
That's not how Nickelodeon works.
Someone wrote an article as Toys R Us was closing, interviewing kids who had won
the Toys R Us contest where you would go through and take all the Toys R Us stuff.
And they said whoever hosted that was like the coolest dude.
And he's like, hey, I'm going to walk you through so you know where everything is.
Here's the thing. You're going to start at the bikes.
Just grab all the bike tags, like just grab a ball.
Oh, he gave him tips.
He gave tips. And then they like toured the whole store together, made sure everyone
was comfortable. Like, oh, is there some stuff you know you're going to go for?
OK, you better hit this then.
And like and they just said they had a room filled with toys until they were like 18.
There was still stuff they hadn't opened.
That's a dream. I get so excited you telling that story.
It is exciting.
Visualizing even living vicariously.
I have toys everywhere in here and I'm like, not enough.
Mm hmm. I certainly wouldn't like run around and in 30 seconds take them all off the
shelves. No, it'd be a nightmare for your toys.
Yeah, a nightmare.
It's funny. All these old game shows talk makes me think and even Millionaire 2, like,
man, isn't it wild to think about like cultural commentary at the time, either in like
editorial pages or like dystopian movies of like, can you imagine these game shows
and stuff or like, can you?
We're like it was like greed and commercialism.
Yeah, I grew up just like this is where the culture is now.
Like even Millionaire, like back when people didn't be we're reading newspapers a lot
more in 2000 and 2001, it was just going like this is what passes for TV nowadays.
These these cultural commentators could not even have predicted like Instagram
influencers or Twitch streamers like, oh, it's actually the the future is even more
dystopian.
No, the problem it peaked.
It got the worst with game shows and rap lyrics.
Yeah. And things are actually things are better and actually we're getting a little more
moral because we can put Santa on the Christmas Cup again.
Yeah, we put Santa on the Christmas Cup.
And does all the other stuff.
May I interest you in SoundCloud dot com?
What's wrong with SoundCloud?
I don't know. SoundCloud, Raffer, I don't.
They're mumbling too much.
That's what it is.
They just enunciated.
I'm with you there. I like I like enunciation.
Sure. That's why I like game shows and Regis.
I like Regis.
Yeah. Well, hey, that was a blast.
I think we covered all there is to cover.
Correct me if I'm wrong, except for one final cliffhanger.
Had you used the lifeline?
I did. I while we were talking, I texted the question to Andrew Grissom and he guessed
Harry Potter. So he would have led you astray.
Yeah. Good thing you didn't listen, Andrew Grissom.
He also said, my friend is trying to pass off two tickets to Stomp in Thousand Oaks
tonight. Any interest?
So your lifeline is giving me the opportunity to drive many, many miles away to Stomp.
I'm not taking it. He's a very generous.
He's a very generous man.
Did he send that second text from the year 2001?
Two tickets. Hey, two tickets to Stomp.
I can't use.
2001 Millionaire and Stomp are both going strong.
Yeah. Yeah. Hey, we still we still going to see Moulin Rouge this week.
All right. We survived.
But I guess the ride the second gate.
Thanks for helping us and wasting some time with that game show.
If you'd like to play Who Wants to Be a Millionaire Sports Edition CD-ROM, it's
available for very reasonable prices on eBay or come to Mike's place.
Come see the cover where Regis has a he's just putting his hands out, but he has a
basketball and a football and they are not in his hands.
They're just kind of hovering above his hands.
And they look like CGI hands.
They look like they were painted like that.
It doesn't look like a human.
No, that doesn't look like some Photoshop stuff.
Yeah, there is.
I tease the Twitch streamers, but there is some interesting articles started to come
out about like video game archiving is just now they're starting to figure out how
to play old video. Like, what do we do?
Like you have to find the old system and does the old system still work?
Like, how do you preserve it the way you preserve books or film and stuff?
Oh, man. Well, in in music, you should be able to you have to you should have to
like the old museum of TV and radio.
Oh, like talk to a woman behind a counter and one kinescope, please.
One one Sega Saturn, please.
And you got to blow on it.
Do you guys remember blowing on the video games?
Does anyone remember that I was back in the eighties or nineties?
If a kid saw that today, like what do you say?
If you're a fancy writer's room?
Yeah, we're working on a great job.
Yeah, I'm writing a show all about blowing on video games.
It's going to be and whether or not you remember it, it's just random.
How you came up with that?
It's pretty weird.
Remember Pogs?
All right. You survived by as a second game.
Thanks for subscribing. Keep subscribing for our regular stuff.
Go to Twitter or Instagram or YouTube page.
I've been trying to talk about. Yeah.
And a lot of fun awaits.
All right. Thanks for listening.