Five, four, three, two, one.
Happy Easter, everyone.
The most joyous day has arrived.
I'm Scott Gardner, for this magical Easter celebration,
Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan joining me as well.
Yes, ho ho.
He has risen.
The Easter bunny, that is.
Easter bunny. Does Easter bunny have like a catchphrase?
Hippity hop.
Hippity hoppity. Easter's on its way.
It is. For God so loved the world, he gave his only son.
The bunny says that.
Hippity hop hop. Is that how the song goes?
Hippity hoppity. Easter's on its way.
Hippity hoppity.
We were talking about that, how there's only like two Easters.
There's that and there's Easter Parade.
Which I think we'll hear both in what we're about to watch.
That's the Easter bonnet song.
Yeah, put on your Easter bonnet with all its frills upon it.
That kind of thing is why I don't like Easter.
It's all about pinafores and frills.
And as a Catholic child, Easter was exceedingly irritating to me.
Did you wear like Little Lord Fauntleroy outfits?
I kind of did. I sort of had to wear like little vests and stuff.
Like what Jason's wearing now?
Lacy sleeves and a tiny timepiece and all.
No, I feel like my parents made a huge deal out of Easter wear.
Which probably is why I don't think I liked dressing up for my whole life.
Until my wedding did I not have a nice suit and they turned me off.
It's all Easter's fault.
Well, on the East Coast, I mean, Easter fluctuates depending on the calendar.
But sometimes on the East Coast, that meant it was either cold and rainy
or it was like the start of humidity.
And in the 90s, children's, what I remember is like children's formal wear
was largely polyester.
So not super breathable.
Or potentially an Easter corduroy.
Oh yeah.
Oh right.
Corduroy vests.
I think I had a blue sport jacket one year.
Maybe two years.
And that was maybe the craziest it got.
My sister would always have an Easter dress and a bonnet.
But I don't think I did it.
In the 90s, madness what girls had to wear.
Yes, like American Girl dolls.
Like little dolls.
Little horror movie dolls.
And they had like full tablecloths on there as a collar.
Like a giant doily.
We're going to see some of that fashion in this because this parade is from 1990.
So it's probably going to get pretty hideous.
I've only like skimmed this thing and I don't have it.
We want to be fresh.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't want it to be overly rehearsed.
We don't have like the Mystery Science Theater Rift Track binders.
I saw them live once and they all had like stage reading style binders with jokes.
This won't be nearly as funny as one of those because we haven't prepared.
We promise.
I have, I don't know if it's this one.
I should have like looked through them more.
And it also might be like childhood memories mushing together.
But I have a very specific memory of like a flood of frilly Easter dresses and white suits and that Easter parade song walking down Main Street.
Filling up the entirety of Main Street.
Yes.
A grid of like seven frillies wide and 19 frillies long.
Yeah.
Graff, you multiply that.
So many frillies.
160.
And I was into that because I loved old timey shit.
But I have childhood memories of Easter being an exhausting holiday because you got to get up.
You got to find the baskets.
Then you got to go to church.
Then you got to go to a relatives for Easter Ham.
And then you come home and what's on Monday?
School.
We didn't get like Easter Monday off until I was like a senior in high school.
You got Easter Monday.
Monday.
Sometimes.
Depending on snow days.
Depending on how many snow days we had to account for.
No, but saying if we didn't have like if we hadn't burned through snow days, they would give Easter Monday off sometime.
Easter Monday.
I never even heard the term Easter Monday.
It's the day after Easter.
I get what it is.
Jesus.
I guess I'm saying I've never heard it as a thing.
It's not a thing is what I'm saying.
The day everyone rested from the excitement of Christ being born.
All the apostles had to chill out a little.
That was an exhausting day.
You think it was an exhausting day having to go to relatives and eat ham.
Imagine if your buddy, the savior of mankind, was alive again.
After you watched him take the most deadly walk in human history.
Yeah, he has to.
Bro, I needed Easter Monday off, bro.
But it's like Christmas.
You don't go back to school the day after Christmas.
No, probably not.
I'm just saying all I'm saying is I've never heard Easter Monday as a term.
I haven't really either.
All right.
I get what you mean.
I'm just saying that that's interesting to me because I've never heard that you get the Easter after or Monday after Easter.
But you've heard.
Have you heard of Maude Thursday?
Well, that's the day before Good Friday.
Maude Thursday.
And you're like, at least in Protestantism.
Yeah, if I had to be, I don't know what it means exactly.
How do you spell Maude?
Hold on.
I'm going to look at Noddy Thursdays.
Nod teams are on Mondays.
Yeah, it's on.
Are they?
Wednesdays, obviously.
Sorry, it's Maude Thursday.
It's a holy day.
Maude Thursday.
It's not Wednesday.
Okay.
That's what I, the week leading up to Easter, of course, is Holy Week, begins on Palm Sunday.
In the Bible, this is when the Last Supper took place, is Maude Thursday.
Okay.
And then Friday is the crucifixion.
Would you have Maude Thursday off as well?
Well, our spring break was usually Holy Week.
Covered Maude Thursday.
So that was the other thing.
Like Easter, like the end of spring break was Easter.
So you're back to school after a while.
So you're back to school after a week.
Would Maude Thursday still be a thirsty Thursday?
Well, for just one drink though, the blood of Christ.
All right, fair enough.
You know, we're recording this on Good Friday.
And actually, and it's three o'clock, it just passed three o'clock, so that makes this okay.
But when I was a, in my Catholic youth, I was made to be sad from 12 to three, which is supposedly when Christ was doing the walk.
When it went down.
So I had to like, we had to go to church for some of that, not necessarily the full three hours, though sometimes the full three hours in a darkened room.
And sometimes church at least has a guitar or something.
This was sad, dark church for three straight hours.
And I started protesting by just like hurling myself around the pews, like trying to like self-immolate essentially.
Like maybe if I bruise my own face really hard, I don't have to be here.
So I think my protests worked.
But with this, what we did settle on is that from 12 to three, I have to be sad.
And 12 to three on a Friday was when my Entertainment Weekly subscription would show up.
So I was always really upset.
I could not, I did not have access to hear like seeing a preview of The Matrix or whatever.
We were all such beautiful little weirdos in different ways.
I had that.
I haven't said a lot about mine, but that's for sure the worst part is about my, me having to behave and thinking, well, if I just like go outside and climb the fence and snatch the mail ahead of time.
But then go put the Entertainment Weekly back so I could get a half hour of reading time before my mom goes and gets the mail.
Madness is how I was raised.
How would it be enforced?
How would you have to be sad?
The garage door, well, the Entertainment Weekly thing, the garage door is very loud.
So if they heard it opening, they'd know I was going to get that Entertainment Weekly and learn all about Spy Who Shagged Me instead of sitting in my room and reflecting on the crucifixion.
So you just had to sit in your room and you couldn't watch TV for three hours essentially?
At that time I didn't have a TV in my room.
Right. So I'm just saying, so it was just no fun.
You had to sit and contemplate.
If there was music, I had to have it.
It had to be headphones and I had to be ready to hurl those off in case they came and did a prayer check.
And they did?
I can, I have to imagine.
Did you not eat meat on Good Friday?
No, all of lent.
All of lent.
But you could eat fish.
So we had fish sticks.
Fish and cheese pizza.
That's a weird cheat.
My family only didn't do meat on Good Friday, which I still don't do because now I'm not so much religious as superstitious now.
Like one year when I skipped going to church on Easter, I lost like a $60 camera battery at college and I'm like, well, can't do that again.
So you're still going?
I go on Easter Sunday and Christmas Eve.
Yeah.
I don't think I knew that.
Oh yeah.
Interesting.
Yeah.
It makes my mother happy.
Even though you don't go with her.
On Christmas Eve.
Yeah.
Usually I go with my family.
I'm down to just Christmas.
It was there was Easter in there and now it's just Christmas.
Yeah.
So Easter I will, you know, in lack of church, I will get to spend watching every Disney Easter parade in a row for, I don't know when they started doing it, probably like 86, 87, up to this day.
So as with every year, I will watch a full entire day's worth at least 12 in a row.
Do they still do it?
Do they still broadcast it?
I'm not entirely sure.
Yeah.
The people listening might know you might have already seen this year's and you can compare contrast to the year that we chose, which is the 1990 Disney World Happy Easter Parade.
So if you're, if you want to sync up with us.
There's a link in the description.
Okay.
And to make sure that you have the right one.
It is the 1990 Walt Disney World Happy Easter Parade.
The user is Sam's Disney Diary.
If you were to pull it up on YouTube, it would have a bright pink thumbnail, pinker and brighter than the pinafores that you will be seeing.
And what's a pinafore?
Is that the umbrella?
Or is that that's a parasol?
Good question.
Jason pinafore.
You're wearing one I assume.
I think it's the frills.
I think I'm going to look it up.
I just know HMS Pinafore from Studio 60 and The Simpsons.
Yeah.
The Gilbert and Sullivan play.
Who is wearing the Mondiest Pinafore at this year's Easter Parade?
Well, like I can tell you, I'll give you these previews about it, though you're soon to see an opening sequence.
But if you need encouragement to sync it up with us.
This year's the 1990 Easter Parade is the All-Star lineup.
Joan London, Regis Philbin and the begotten son Alan Thicke.
You stopped being asked to be around, perhaps due to general unpleasantness, perhaps drunkenness that you will see in this very parade.
I mean, not in this one so much.
Once I did watch a pageant that he was hosting where he for sure was tipsy.
But that just might be the way he spoke a little bit.
This year also features special guests Buster Poindexter and Howie Mandel among many of your many of your favorite members of the Disney gang.
So if you're ready.
I have a quick Easter question.
One last question.
Did you guys ever were you ever in like a crucifixion like little play at church or anything?
I don't think I had to be, but I had to do some like exhaustive altar boy because you had a lot more work to do.
You're like going around the stations and swing in a big thing of oil and that kind of.
OK, no plays, though.
I don't think I feel like I know the answer for you, Jason.
Yes, I absolutely was.
I was the thief who did not repent.
I was the because there were three people crucified and there's the one that asked Jesus for forgiveness and the other who's like an asshole about it.
And I was the one who said asshole about it, which just mean I had to go lower at the audience.
Sorry, the guy, I guess the congregation is what you say with church.
Glower at them and glower at Christ.
And they like had like homemade, not like like crosses made out of branches and stuff.
It wasn't my finest performance.
But at the time, is there a video of it?
I don't think we monetize it.
My family would have been like, yeah, that seems gauche to have, like because we would have a giant VHS camera.
But when you have a podcast years later, I know they weren't forward thinking that way.
I also can't talk about Easter services and little ceremonies without saying my favorite thing.
The only thing that gave me joy during three hour marathon churches on Good Friday, which is there's it kind of is a little Easter play and the priest plays Jesus.
He does Jesus's lines.
Obviously, he is the most holy and then other like cantors or whatever do the other parts like punches pilot.
But you get to participate, the congregation, and you participate by being the crowd that chooses to crucify Christ instead of the vill, the criminal that they're going to release instead.
So you get to make the choice and it is still I bring this up to Aaron all the time.
The funniest memory hearing three hundred dower people in a church all together like who do you wish to release Christ or Barabbas?
Are you sure? Christ, this man, Jesus, has done nothing where Barabbas has murdered and thiefed and such.
Are you really sure? Let me ask you once again, Christ or Barabbas?
Here a wave of barely enunciated we're acting in a play, but we're supposed to be sad.
It is the strangest thing and I can't find video of three hundred people all saying Barabbas.
Maybe this was unique to my church.
But boy, the only joy I should have gone to one today.
Well, they're tired.
I know the Protestant church is pretty chill that I went to growing up in and out 40 minutes an hour.
Like, wow, really? The hits may be a little longer on Easter if there was more music or stuff.
I do laugh because every now and then they would do communion on Easter to but not a guarantee.
And my mom would always be like, oh, jeez, they're doing communion because that's another like 15, 20 minutes just doing the traffic flow.
Just doing the trees and we didn't do the going up to the front.
The trees came to you, but that takes a while.
Oh, the bringing the baskets around.
Yeah, that's a big slow one.
Just to Pinafore, a sleeveless, usually low necked garment fastened in the back and worn as an apron or a dress.
So the HMS Pinafore back in the day was a very funny joke.
Oh, interesting.
Because it's it's a ship.
That's like, isn't it funny to call that ship a dress instead of something that dress?
I'm just not like it wasn't like Pinafore and that's a different thing.
I don't think so.
All right. Well, as funny then as it was on Studio 60 many years later, the modern model of a modern network TV show.
OK, well, I think with all that, we are now ready to begin.
I'll read it once again.
The 1990 Walt Disney World Happy Easter Parade posted by Sam's Disney Diary.
Thank you, Sam.
It runs about an hour and seven minutes and we're excited to watch it.
OK, and all right.
So you're ready?
We got your three to one.
Yeah, three to one.
And then on go, you will hit play.
Play, but make sure to watch any ads or any thing.
We're not counting.
We get your ads done now.
Yeah, it's zero zero zero time code.
So one more time.
Three, two, one, go is when I will say it.
I will play it.
And I think we filled at least 15 seconds past any.
So on your own, we hit play.
Go three, two, one, go.
Sam's Disney actually worked on.
All right.
I like the little head movements.
Regis Philbin at this point, still a street reporter, not invited up to sit with the gang.
Right. Regis and Joe and a lot of Disney afternoon, DuckTales and Rescue Rangers and the rabbit.
And the rabbit and the duck sits there.
Time to shine.
Mike, can you crank it?
Just a little says Easter.
Join Buster Poindexter.
That's that great Mickey balloon on all those ads.
Yeah, the big inflatable.
Well, there's like a beach party dance off.
They're sure.
This is 90s Mickey Mouse Club.
Pretty new.
Buckle up for the performance.
The Fred Astaire.
Oh my gosh.
That dancing guy.
Dapper Dan's.
It's a big time for them.
Thumper.
All these characters who just rot in the back most of the year.
They're front and center this year.
Cats don't count.
Figaro.
Sit in the back.
This is a marching band.
Which I've said before.
I did not get to do this, but I was in the marching band.
We marched in Disney World when I was 18.
Oh yeah.
So you know the holding area that these very people were in.
You were 18 years old when you were sneaking Sprite.
Hell yeah, my man.
You were a legal adult who could vote.
And you're like, this is mischief.
You were like getting all the Sprite you could.
God, I thought you were like 15.
I was under lock and key until I was 20 years old or so.
I did not.
There was not a lot of rebellion going on.
Not like me, man.
I thought of all the potential routes to go get that entertainment weekly during Christ's death.
Did I do it?
No, but I schemed.
I had unholy scheming thoughts.
I had scheming thoughts too, but very rarely did I actually scheme.
But I was, this was me.
I was in the front row.
Walt Disney World honor band.
The scheme still isn't the bad thing.
The scheme is.
I would make kids in band do stuff that was a little bit mischievous.
Like I said before, to this day, which is still.
Yeah.
Well, I don't control bug though.
There's other people.
So, yeah, I was in the front row like this band walking down Main Street at night at like dusk.
And I always be honest, I felt real cool.
That is cool.
Walking down Main Street.
What were you wearing?
Front.
One of these.
Feather in your cap?
But it was this, you know, this marching band outfit.
Did you have a business casual band outfit?
No, but I.
Because my school always had black t-shirts and khakis.
Alan is like walking funny like a marching band.
The hijinks begin now.
And we're happy.
Paving the way for his son Robin to unveil Masked Singers week after.
Oh, yeah.
The biggest.
That Alan Thicke slur, which the kid has a little.
You know, I've watched clips of him on the mass and going, you know, I remember what a pioneer Ricky Lake was week after week on television.
Really one of the great pioneers of women on TV.
And without it, without her, you know, you wouldn't have Amy Schumer's today.
So thank you.
It's got to be Ricky Lake.
The Penguin is Ricky Lake.
Cassimi St. Cloud.
What a logo.
And premier cruise lines, pre-Disney cruise lines.
The version we're watching has no commercials, you should be aware.
So if you're watching one with commercials, spin it around and watch something else.
Watch. Watch this correct copy.
So why did Alan have to wear a suit?
It's Easter.
It's a pastoral time.
Yeah.
Who doesn't love wearing a thick sweater in May in Orlando?
His hair is kind of like my dad's hair was your.
Do you guys have like permy dad?
No, not not so much.
Not so much perm.
Mine is a little slick.
He kind of he reminded me of Patrick Duffy a little bit.
Yeah, he used to wear it.
As established, my father looks like John Hammond from Jurassic Park and went white pretty early.
I'm hoping.
Oh, yes.
Well, I'm saying I'm hoping.
Unfortunately, I think the hair you get the mother's hair,
which my mother's father and siblings all went bald in the worst possible way,
whereas my father has like aged much more gracefully with hair.
So best of luck to you.
I think it all depends.
Do you have a can you compare your dad to any?
That's a good question.
I mean, he was dead.
Man, that's a good question.
I can't think of any sitcom stars of stage or screen immediately that he looks.
I wouldn't know.
He looks like Robbins for a long time.
He was a Tim Robbins.
But I feel like older Tim Robbins, not what Tim Robbins looked like when he was younger.
OK, that's so what?
Two thousands like the cradle will rock.
Yeah.
Then like, yeah, yeah, that's the closest I can think.
Look at this.
Reed is pretty outer blue, pretty tame by Reedus levels, a little more juiced at Christmas.
Well, wouldn't you be Easter is not as exciting.
Well, he's relaxed.
He's been saved.
I was said.
OK, the hippos, they count as Easter animals.
Yeah, they are pink.
Oh, this is the third song.
Hippity hoppy Easter.
You were counting.
Was I OK?
It was that an Easter bonnet.
Peter Cunton.
I realized I was thinking about the Santa Claus.
Thump, thump, thump, thumpity thump.
That was what I was thinking of.
You're thinking of look at Frosty Go over the hills of snow.
Yep.
Hmm.
Eighty five degrees.
Eighty five.
OK, so there's Robin Hood characters with Jiminy Cricket, which is, of course, inconsistent
universe wise.
Nokia.
Also a second ago.
And a lot of villains holding out their hands.
Who is that?
Oh, that's a that's from Pinocchio.
That's the evil man.
What's his name?
I can't think of his child kidnapper.
Yeah, the child's a good number.
You're probably obvious.
It's the right.
Why can't I think of his strong bully?
Right.
Yeah, I think so.
Wait, but then there's also that other guy.
Who's the guy without the beard?
Yeah, he puts him in the show.
But who's the guy without the beard?
Yeah, I think so.
I think so.
Yeah, he puts him in the show.
But who's the guy?
I don't know.
The more the gambling guy.
We don't know the movies.
We know the part where the parks fans, the movies.
Yeah, my father in law looks a lot like Geppetto.
All right.
If the audience needs to know.
Here's the right now.
Look like Robin Hood.
I'm wearing a green long green shirt with no pants.
Little boots.
And you're a big balloon and doing some like real like.
Yeah.
unrehearsed choreography.
You're watching along corny alert.
The Fox Robin Hood is on screen.
Oh, they got the boom.
I mean, so that's so like girls have crushes on that Robin Hood is what I'm told.
Everyone apparently does.
Everyone did.
And all the boys liked Roxanne or Lola Bunny.
Roxanne from the Goofy movie.
Yeah.
As I said in our last commentary, Gadget.
Gadget too.
Seems to I think will feature in this.
My mother had a crush on one of the Aristocats when she was.
Not the Aristocats.
No, no, no, no.
The Top Cats guys.
One of the Top Cats friends.
Buddies.
Yeah.
I'm trying to remember if I actually had a crush on anthropomorphic animal as a youngster.
Here's let's go to the hop from that era.
Pre-Beatles era when rock and roll was bad.
What?
Yeah.
What's the first song you like?
What's the earliest song?
You know, I was in that era.
I think I like Yakety Yak.
That's the first song.
I mean, I like like Rocker on the clock or some of the Brill buildings.
I was in Leader of the Pack, the Ellie Greenwich musical.
And some of that stuff's good.
Do you have a video of that?
No, because they were weird.
In high school, we did like the Broadway musicals and they're a lot weirder about videotaping that.
Now you can find a million high school productions of musicals on YouTube because no one gives a shit and you can just shoot it on your phone.
Were people worried about getting sued?
Yeah.
Well, I think when you the middle school ones, I think you came with a license agreement that you could videotape one night professionally.
Just one.
Yeah.
That's what I did in high school was I taped the play.
I led a crew that filmed all of the plays.
So we filmed them all very professionally.
Sure.
I don't know where the tapes ever went.
So if you are listening to this and you went to Shamanah and you were in a play and I can think of one person listening who made that may be the case.
I'm sorry.
I can't speak for the distribution end of things.
Your play is lost forever.
Jimmy.
Alan Thicke is touching her and she does not like it, I think.
Now this is Scott's favorite song.
Minnie she has a crush on you.
I would buy dolls with Mickey and Minnie with the neon green like that.
Got a crush on you.
What you gonna do?
That's the outfit I wore in high school band.
Now she's Teddy Bear right here.
Oh yeah.
She's swinging.
Look at that.
In the middle of the park.
Adorning a picture of.
Oh my god.
But imagining wearing different clothes.
I want Mickey with that outfit too.
Sometimes I'll just show Lindsey pictures of Mickey in different outfits on Instagram and I'll be like hey look at this.
And just gesture like hmmm see.
And she'll be like oh that's yeah that's cute.
God it's been decades.
We're in the middle of an accounting meeting but okay.
It's been decades of these two and it's still like Minnie's got a crush on you Mickey.
Yeah they are married.
Yeah the depression happened.
No they're married.
No they're by canon they're not married.
Yeah.
They have to keep the spark alive.
It can't be you know you can't.
Oh my god he's a mountain.
Oh mountain Mickey.
But she's not Canadian she's regular.
Oh my gosh there's Mickey with a jumpsuit.
This is archive footage I think.
I think they didn't film enough.
You're right.
What is this?
This is.
I'll make a call like you stuck in.
This is definitely the den voice.
Yeah.
In the specials did not use the agreed upon Mickey voice.
Sure.
I've heard before that like they have like a list of ten people.
Have you heard this where it's like they go down the list of who will work for cheapest.
A good enough list.
Yeah.
Succession.
Right so like if the number one Mickey doesn't want to do it for the rate they go to number two or something.
It's a real shitty sounding thing.
We read about Muppets that the to make Muppet Vision 3D.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It was like I want my guys and Disney said wait you just have the same person do Gonzo.
We just go down the list.
If they say no we go down the list.
Maybe that is where we knew that for the first time.
That song Mickey she's got a crush on you on the splash dance album one of my favorite Disney pieces of Disney music.
Also featuring the spark song Minnie Mouse that I love very much and they oddly moving song about gyro gear loose.
It's like I do.
Oh yeah.
I'm second gate.
It's like I kind of well up at this gyro gear loose song.
I couldn't even do a drawing of gyro gear loose.
I don't even know what he looks like but it's really moving little song.
Sunday strollers.
That way Mrs.
Mrs.
Strollers.
On the old time bikes.
Were the old time bikes part of the regular parade because don't you have to.
Those are special.
That's a skill to be able to ride on the old time bike.
Well that's true.
They probably need special permits or training.
Because you can't end up kicking a kid in the head.
You're right.
So Donald and Daisy also not married in canon.
No.
I like Donald's outfit here.
I think I would wear that legit.
Here we go.
Oh my God.
Jason there he is.
I'm having Vietnam style.
Jason and Scott.
Both dressed like that.
Little hats.
Did you guys have little hats like that.
No thank God.
I'm sure that would have been my mother's dream though if I voluntarily put one on.
Oh mother I found this on the sidewalk.
Don't you think it makes me look dashing.
I look like the happiest millionaire.
I did as a kid wear a little bowler hat like the character the happiest millionaire.
And I sang the song Fortuosity and my mom loved it so.
Wow.
This is put on your Sunday clothes from the Hello Dolly.
It plays a big part in Wally.
Yeah.
And now you hear it in the parks.
Which I like.
It feels like I'm going to go Wally nod.
I like how you called it Wally.
Wally.
Isn't that what you're supposed to call it?
I don't think so.
Wally.
That's Wally.
It's written out.
Isn't it.
Wally.
That's what I said.
You said Wally.
You like you kind of like edit a little thing.
God.
How much of this fucking podcast is how I pronounce this.
It does happen in almost every episode.
There's one in episode.
Here's Goofy as Sweetie Todd the demon barber of Fleet Street.
He looks real boring.
Were you in that?
No I wasn't.
He looks real like bored.
Goofy usually looks a lot more energetic.
This guy's not synced up left to right.
Oh my God.
All of these old men barbers.
I would kill for a barber parade.
Oh.
Revealing false hair.
Yep.
That's a toupee.
I the oldest man I've ever had cut my hair, cut my hair two weeks ago.
He had to have been 80.
Wow.
Oh right.
You were saying.
Is that a new barber?
I don't know.
Oh right.
You were saying.
Is that a new barber?
I went to a new place and the woman.
Oh my God.
Pluto has a mustache.
Whoa.
That doesn't seem happy with it.
That's what I want a doll of.
Pluto with a mustache.
And an old man giving him a trim.
Oh he hit his head on the pole.
He's stuck.
Oh no.
This is that unpolished parade.
Yeah.
That the Meghan Trainor era does not give you.
Also Disney would never allow old people on camera nowadays.
Yeah.
These are all old people.
Julie Andrews or Dick Van Dyke.
That's it.
It has to be a nostalgia old person.
Yeah.
A franchise old person.
Oh here we go.
Alan Thicken is propped.
I was thinking this was going to close the whole show but we're getting it now so it
must be like dynamite by the end.
There must be a big number to close.
They're like let's get it over with.
This is the.
I haven't.
Oh look at this.
This is why he was not asked back.
He definitely.
He drinks like this hand nodding.
He might be a little loaded.
He also though.
The white is special guests on these.
Well it was the 80s.
He also.
By the time Samuel Wright the voice of Sebastian started showing up finally there was one black
person in the business fold.
Yeah.
There might have been a Nell Carter or two in the 70s.
Alan Thicke definitely is like I remember like dads who really thought they were funny.
Yeah.
Oh man they do a whole thing.
And.
And a title card.
Wow.
And this is actually good.
Never mind.
I like the only part.
I watched the Brown Derby.
It's frustrating.
I'll tell you that.
No way.
I don't believe it.
I'm.
Yeah.
I'll host if you give me a number.
He appears to be said to every production.
Yes.
He's wearing evening wear at like 6 a.m.
Clearly shut for the park open.
We're losing daylight.
Hurry get the car out of there.
Is wave wave harder.
Did he ever do this.
Like was he on Broadway ever or is this just sort of like a whim.
He had music was always part of the Alan Thicke lore.
He of course wrote facts of life.
Right.
Their songs he wrote his own theme song for his show.
I'm a big fan of the Alan Thicke.
This is my least favorite Alan Thicke musical number far behind the immortal sweaty and
hot from the 1987 aerobics championships.
Sweaty and hot like the McGruff songs we've covered before it.
A jam.
Look up sweaty and hot and get.
Don't ever watch this again.
Watch sweaty and hot two times instead.
I. Baby I got some muscle for you.
There's another Alan Thicke musical number that I mean he like sang and played guitar
on the show all the time.
Yeah yeah.
Constantly.
Why am I freezing.
I won't dance.
Don't ask me.
OK.
Wow.
Kristen Wiig.
Don't make me sing.
It's like a 20 tap dancing Maryland's.
This is this is to use in a comedy turn.
This bumps for me a little because it was it was people in Easter where but now it's
Maryland but then all the guys are in white.
You would have been into this as a kid I think right.
Yeah.
Maybe not because of the.
Well it was in factually incorrect.
Oh.
They're crossing eras mother.
Because I like all this old time crap now but as a kid this would have just I would
have zoned right out of this time.
Now this.
Well I think it's I think fun weird stuff is fun and I appreciate the kitchiness of
it and obviously I know this is not like a great Busby Berkeley musical number.
I like.
Well this I like putting on the red.
I love it.
Putting on the thick.
I like this shit more than like let's go to the sock hop with a milkshake.
There's more like in terms of standards.
I think I think going to John Brian made me start to enjoy your you know your group porters
and your Gershwin's and your stuff.
Scott Joplin.
Yeah.
Rags.
I like rags.
I take a rag over this or over a bebop any day.
Yeah.
But like I want to do a rag.
I like I can breeze through a little Richard greatest hits.
That's pretty fun and that's all pretty simple.
I would rather it's.
Yeah.
This is so expensive.
I will never work on a production as expensive as what we just watched.
Yeah right.
Doesn't exist anymore.
Also what did that have to do with Easter.
Well I think was because it was an older song but then it had a resurgence in the 80s with
that.
Frankenstein.
No.
Taco.
Yeah.
Oh.
So that was a crossover.
That was something for everyone.
I talk about is I think that I like that taco putting on the ritz from the 80s until it
gets to God a dance.
God dance.
Well that's like a during Broadway melody from singing singing in the rain.
Oh so that's like.
Oh yeah.
That's the big musical number that they used to show in the queue for great movie ride
when you see Gene Kelly singing God a dance God a dance and everyone running around him.
That's a sequence from singing in the rain that day within podcasts the right you do
a personal podcast of explaining thing anything before 1950 to both of us.
Sure.
Yeah.
Because it's all a mush.
I mean and streaming doesn't really help whether you got to go to criteria channel or can't
appear something to find the any old stuff.
Well view boo's got some some 50s.
Well view boo's got some great stuff.
They are the libraries.
We are here detective from 1949 only on magic drum.
What do you do for realistic bunny.
I had a not cute bunny in the graphic.
I had a roommate in college who was in I forget the name of the it was a drum in bugle corps
and it's like what you have to audition into and there's only like I don't know 12 or 20
somebody will correct me.
A small amount in the country and it's insane.
They're insane.
They're like insane like I don't think they get paid a little bit but it's also like musical
theater nerds extreme like ride or die drum and bugle corps.
Once you're in you're always in forever and you go back and do after college.
What do you do.
You get a job teaching band in high school.
OK.
Even as a high school I was like what's what about there's like three sports you can play
professionally or like you then you teach your coach and Jim I guess so high school
or junior high.
I would like to see the don't think twice type movie about the drum and bugle corps
in their 30s wondering like what are we doing.
I mean what even is after this right.
You know I hadn't thought of don't think twice and at least one fiscal quarter and now I
am mad.
I'm sorry.
But now you're flashing back to all your favorite memories touching the rock for good luck before
going out and doing the show.
What is it called.
Weekend Live.
Yeah.
Which was we can tell from the photos on the wall was hosted by Daniel Radcliffe.
I think Paul Rudd hosted Weekend Live.
Sure.
We're in the movie we're watching Lena Dunham hosting Weekend Live.
She's pretty big.
Fuck mythology.
OK. So that was a good.
That was a perfect moment to do that because literally on screen was just women waving
slowly on screen.
It looked like a still photograph.
They were moving so slowly.
She would rather watch women waving slowly than don't think twice.
Yeah absolutely.
I would.
Just that is what movies were like in the 30s.
Right. Just one shot of a woman waving for.
Yeah.
Or if it was an exciting one people were coming in and out of rooms and mixing drinks.
If they could handle the frame rate of it.
Yeah.
It might blow out the camera to open a door.
Sure.
That woman almost tripped I think the pink flower.
Accidents would happen.
These things are great.
That Mickey special which we ended up liking a lot even though we thought we might hate
it.
Yeah.
It's still edited to the point of it feels gross.
It's not gross but it feels weird because they've cut around any little hiccup in the
production and they hate it.
And they like sweeten everything with fake applause and fake cheering.
Yeah.
That's that polish I was talking about where it's like this isn't the stuff we like.
We like it but it's a little messy.
You want Mickey to trip a little bit.
Speaking of messy I have watched this performance by the Mickey Mouse Club.
This is the 90s Mickey Mouse Club.
This is a level of precision that wouldn't be accepted by the the Lou Pearlman.
Oh my god.
Lou is later.
Like look how not synced up they are.
They're all wearing like five layers of unbreathable fabric and 85 degree weather.
And they're like lip lip syncing.
Wade Robson would not be pleased with this level of non-synchronicity.
Kenny Ortega.
Oh yeah.
He would be upset.
They're all fired.
Like truly it's not good.
Yeah it's like.
This is the first segment for anyone who is a child in 1990.
This is the first segment that would.
Well for you you liked putting on the ritz but.
Yes I was a weirdo.
I liked 90s Mickey Mouse Club.
I wouldn't see this is also with me as well.
I wouldn't have been into this.
Because I know if I was that when I was like what six years old when this era.
Disney because it wasn't a Disney song I think I wouldn't have been because my mom
wouldn't let me listen to like new music.
So I knew if I kind of had that too.
But what have how did it how did it break that play out.
Well it just that at a certain at a certain point my sister started listening to the radio
in like 95 or 96 and 97.
So then we started my mom started to get into like Matchbox 20 and Love Fool by the Cardigans.
It's a good gateway.
So yeah so then she would sort of back and so she knows like she has now a five year
period in the later 90s that she does know also.
So she goes from the 60s and 70s right to the late 90s and a little into the 2000s and
then she's done she's got no context.
You know how my dad and Nick Mundy's dad both like Maroon 5.
I know the only band post 2000 acceptable to.
I think I did that but I think I was combining those in my head.
That's what it's it's the early Maroon 5 it's not like moves like Jagger.
Well yeah my dad like last year said you know that band does that you know this love is
taken and I'm like yeah that's an old song.
Yeah it's like 2003 I think at this point.
Enough time is like dad the beginning of the Beatles to the end of the Beatles could have
fit in that run twice.
That's how old this love is.
Mike Schaumburg is the town that they based Footloose on right.
Yeah.
They wouldn't want you dancing.
Well if you look at the Facebook group the Schaumburg Facebook group it's mostly alt
right so.
Not everyone.
The Concerned Citizens Council of Schaumburg.
I'm glad you don't defend your town like Mitch and Quincy.
Oh yeah like Mitch he's always up against the ropes.
Yeah.
Fighting in vain.
You know look when you grow up in a safe suburb you got to invent your own.
A town of bold terror the whole Bolger clan.
That being said I should probably edit this out because I need to get those little Caesars
playland pictures from these people.
That's why I joined the Facebook group so I'm going to.
How much could that crossover be.
Yeah that's true.
I just want to get some good pics before we do that episode about Little Caesars.
You could just bleep the original the what your original source is.
This is Patreon it's fine.
Look at that the Mickey.
Hell yeah.
I always liked pointing this out to anyone within earshot that there is a giant hit the
biggest hidden Mickey of all at Disney MGM studios.
One is one ear is a lake and one is painted arbitrarily in a circle.
I like that.
I know we've talked about how we're not like so into these hidden Mickey's but that's fun.
When I realized it on the map.
Scott you would point that out and then the Monsignor would be like no it's not three
o'clock yet.
We're still solid.
Still quiet time.
I notice you are not weeping my son.
He's not all the way up the hill yet.
I think if I remember correctly he was by two o'clock and then the last hour was it
was just dying with modern technology.
You know how like hours the saddest of all where they have like Santa tracker now sort
of like online or like Jesus.
All right.
I'll stop talking.
Oh the Spears coming up the spirit in the ribs.
This is like niche enough behind the paywall enough that people are OK with our sacrilegiousness
and are just goofing around.
Are sat talking about the racism profile of Schomburg.
I mean a lot about this is making me happy too because I'm flashing down six music.
I should just I really need to make the best of thick playlist because they're sweaty and
hot. I will begrudgingly put putting on the ritz on it.
But he also sings his own theme song of thick of the night which is neck and neck with
Oh yeah yeah.
Oddly good corporate 80s theme song.
Better better.
OK better lead singing theme song thick of Alan Thicke singing thick of the night or
Kelsey Grammer singing tossing salad and scrambled eggs for my taste thick of the night.
OK I think Alan thinks of more.
It's like a joke that Kelsey Grammer saying Alan Thicke is a passable 80s more palatable.
Yeah yeah yeah I think so.
Why is that mama don't turn the light on.
I'm out of control tonight.
Why is he's looking up.
Why is the bunny behind them so dirty.
No I think that's the color it's supposed to be and said he looks like truffles.
He does look like he's great.
You're probably right. But to me he looks dirty.
He looks like a dirty bunny.
OK so we're going to Disneyland.
Oh my gosh.
I like this actually.
Jason before we started recording you asked one of us to explain Buster Point Dexter and
I was like I bet I could do that.
I know he was in the New York Dolls.
You said that and then I was like I'm out of facts.
I'd have no more one or two hits.
He had one or two solo hits but I don't think I get him.
This poor girl by the way who had to be in front of him on the single log.
It's so funny how like Tuxedo at a certain point became like that means you're an entertainer.
Like that's like it's a rat pack hold over it because like it is like evening wear or formal
occasion wedding wear.
You know what would be scary is going down Splash Mountain in like a big character suit.
Yeah and a lot of them had to do it.
Yeah.
To promote.
Like every week they were sending characters down.
But I would just be like so disoriented in there.
Oh my gosh.
It's Easter time.
Another thing I know about Buster Point Dexter is that for when the Dana Carvey Phil Hartman
era of SNL began he was in the band every week.
He was.
They said the G.G. Smith and the Saturday Night Live band with Buster Point Dexter.
Wow.
He was in it like for like a whole half a season.
You had to like and you probably to sit through a Buster Point Dexter song.
I think maybe he and Sigourney Weaver sing like baby it's cold outside in the beginning
of that era in the first episode.
I don't know anything about that.
It's a really I only know from Comedy Central reruns.
So he was so like inflatable.
It was cool in some throwback way I guess.
He was the Sean Arnav his time like Brian Setzer like yeah.
Big pompadour but it's from like the 50s but it's the 80s.
But then why.
Walk Ogins biopic walk Ogins in Buster Point Dexter biopic going because I feel like he
would do that.
Justice.
Yeah this is Marty grab floats party.
Yeah these wonderful.
Are these balloons just gone or do they exist somewhere.
Do balloons like this last.
They just dissolve at a certain point or are they just like they're in like a lake somewhere.
That feels like Mickey shirt.
Not a thing you see in parades anymore at the parks is inflatable floats.
Yeah.
Like I loved how tall they were.
Yeah I like that.
There was that the patent for drones that could carry like big puppets down Main Street.
Remember a year or two ago there were like drones could like essentially puppet a giant
puppet down Main Street.
They're having a lot of issues trying to figure out how to use drones without putting them
directly over people's heads.
Yeah it's illegal to do that I think.
And they just debuted those drones at Universal.
Yeah those looked great.
Point Dexter truly is one of the great filmographies.
I mean legitimately with Scrooge.
Right.
It's Scrooge.
Then you got Mr. Nanny.
Car 54 Where Are You.
The movie.
And Free Jack.
Wow.
I feel like I know more about Free Jack than a lot of people and I don't remember him at
all.
And of course when he was David Johansson Johansson's legs appeared in John Lennon and
Yoko Ono's 1971 film Up Your Legs Forever.
Have you heard of that.
Never.
No.
The fuck.
I don't know what that is.
Forever.
Oh they're singing hot hot hot and he's got a frilly carnival kind of outfit on.
Isn't.
Now this.
Hot hot hot.
What does this have to do with Easter.
I think this was just a popular song at the time.
Yeah how many was this.
Goofy sang hot hot hot on one of when we were looking through the Blizzard Beach.
Me soul on fire.
Who sang that originally.
Does Disney own the publishing to hot hot hot.
Maybe they bought it in a merger somewhere and like we got to use the hell out of this.
I do remember it being around party grow a lot.
1982.
Recorded by Arrow.
Is that the right.
I don't know.
Song an instant dance floor hit.
A leader covered in 87 by Buster Poindexter.
So this was one of his.
He had a hit with this.
Yeah.
That's what I know.
I didn't know that.
But why I didn't realize this was Buster.
Sound is like a late 80s early 90s reference that's funny to like Yahoo serious.
Like I really don't know much about Yahoo serious besides that Simpsons joke.
Yeah.
And unlike some things have become too kitschy and obvious to make a joke about.
But no hipster has resurrected Buster Poindexter for any.
Yeah.
But it's not true Jim Carrey and the way he currently lives his life seems a lot
like this insane.
Have you seen these paintings.
He's demolishing Trump with his water.
I feel like Buster Poindexter is acting like mid 90s Jim Carrey or something like a character.
Your mouth is too big sir.
Close that mouth a few notches.
He has a bigger mouth than those balloons.
If I remember correctly this goes they do another hot hot hot after.
There's another hot hot hot on this.
Or maybe I'm thinking that they did the party grass song twice.
Did you see party grow listen.
More like an instrumental version.
No it's no.
Back to what just play the party ground or wait is this in the party girl party.
They were saying I'm sure because they were singing party grow at the start.
Scott did you see in Japan the party grow show that's party grow show.
No.
Okay because I think they do I think they do hot hot hot in that as well.
I'm glad they kept the party name alive in that's where Donald and Jose were
fluffing each other's butts before they went out.
Oh right.
And I have pictures of it.
Like like in all that jazz when he says each showtime folks before every day.
Mm hmm.
They were just touching each other's butts.
This is this song is like I'm a really big fan of Todd Rundgren but he did the song
bang the drum all day that just sucks but to me and I don't like I don't I can't imagine
listening to bang the drum all day or hot hot hot willingly and like love shack lives to me as a
more that's a song you might listen to more of a song there but these are just pure novelties.
Sound like a it's coming from a guy who wants to work I would rather bang on the drum all day.
I just can't relate to the song.
Right.
You just love working.
I do I don't want to play I want to bang on a typewriter all day.
You do exhaustingly write your scripts with a typewriter and it's incredibly inconvenient.
One mistake I gotta throw it all out.
Like Quentin Tarantino does that.
He refuses to use white alda.
I think he does do that.
That's probably right.
An assistant then type it into a final draft.
It tells a lot of VHS right.
There's that dirty rabbit again.
I can't have a blotch okay.
If there's a blotch then it might be a blotch when I'm making the film okay.
I'll be a blotch my brain.
I'll be a brain around.
Try fade in if you don't like final draft.
Like try there's lots of options.
Writer duet.
They got a lot more on brand with these aerials later.
Yeah this doesn't the hair might not be the right color.
No I feel like today they have got it.
Yeah.
On there's style guidelines.
That also just looks like a bra they spray paint in.
Not real shell like.
Here we go.
Why focus why have so much hot hot hot when you've made up your own better hot hot hot
with under the sea that you own.
Right between the two no question there's similar songs calypso light.
For sure I mean I assume they were pushing Buster Poindexter hard.
He probably was in the family whatever label they owned.
So maybe that was something.
Don't forget they owned Queen at the time.
Yeah right right.
I would it would be interesting to know what was slowly walking.
Yeah.
Flounder has legs.
Oh my god.
Flounder should not have.
Later in Sebastian definitely seen like feeling the effects of 85 degree weather.
Flounder has evolved to the point of having legs so he can be on land.
Oh my god Ursula here.
Why is she even like this thing.
She's in the she behind.
She's the best in like she's like keeping an eye on.
Learning their weaknesses.
It is always interesting like sometimes I feel like they're do they're using the
characters after the movie like yeah and sometimes obviously these have to be before
this is before all this stuff went down in Little Mermaid but then other characters it
feels like well they're in their like final form.
Well remember the Little Mermaid TV series where like she's back a mermaid again she's
got a dipshit friend or brother no Prince Eric right but that's like a prequel.
Wasn't it sucks.
Is it a prequel.
I don't know.
It's like Lion King one and a half where it exists between.
Oh yeah.
Of events of.
Nice you want to.
Is blue.
He's just a real shirtless boy.
Is he barefoot.
Did he do a flip concrete.
He just he might have done like a cool.
Oh he's got shoes.
Disney rescued this kid from the Manudo factory.
They they adopted him.
Yeah he's fake shirtless never mind.
Oh yeah yeah yeah sure he's also 50.
He's a stunt performer come here.
Oh oh.
The big.
Oh King.
Whoa.
Holy crap.
Killing it.
Damn.
Wow.
Oh my gosh look he's getting down.
Off the float had to somersault while staying ahead of it.
On hot concrete.
Snow White is her favorite.
Yeah I was I was obsessed with the dwarves.
I'm sure I've said this before.
Obsessed with them.
How did that manifest.
Well I wanted their figure I've told this story I think before where my dad I asked.
For him when I was sick wants to get.
Oh.
So that's funny he's high as crap.
I asked him to go and get me figure seven dwarves figures when I was sick once and my mom was like
they don't make those.
We've looked and my dad found seven little ninjas and he goes these are the ninja dwarves here you go.
That's an upgrade.
And I bought it too I was like cool.
Good idea.
And then eventually they were making like high quality figures and by the time my sister
was born and she got these awesome plastic seven dwarves I was obsessed with the colors.
Where your sister's younger.
She was listening to rock music before you.
Yeah a little bit earlier yeah.
She got she was younger.
Yeah.
That's true.
I was just picturing an older sibling.
Oh yeah.
And you on to rock music the way it works.
Would make a lot of sense.
But it's your little sister telling you about TLC.
Yeah basically I mean it's a little after TLC.
It's like it's right around the time of like Lilith Sonny Came Home Lilith Fair.
It's kind of when I started poking my head out into like do I like popular music and I'm like
trying to find an end to Paula Cole.
Yeah where have all the cowboys gone.
My dad got Ace of Base the sign when you were as a stocking stuffer and I do we duplicated that
because I really like that album.
After that it was like a one two punch of musicals and they might be giants.
So the my life path was just kind of laid out in front of me.
Like all right you're a nerd and you're gonna be an actor.
You like a band that's popular but only with weirdos.
Good luck finding them.
Godspeed to you.
You know them from the Tiny Tunes music video.
What is on Howie's belt.
Malcolm in the Middle.
Malcolm in the Middle theme.
What is that hanging off of his belt.
It's a fanny pack.
Is it.
I think so.
Once Aaron was on an elevator at the MGM Grand and Howie Mandel was playing there and she was
making fun of Howie Mandel out loud the idea of him and then the elevator stopped and he got on
the elevator right at that second.
But he didn't hear.
I don't believe so.
Well that's good.
Or he's held a grudge.
My lack of progress in the entertainment industry is due to arm of the silent angry arm of Mandel.
Oh man.
Blocking me.
There was soundstage with Steven Weber.
Oh yeah.
Did you say cut real quick.
He's running a muck in this place.
Yeah.
They don't know what hit him.
This is honestly this makes the most sense.
Like this is just showing off of.
The new part.
Yeah right.
Like I get this.
I get why this is happening.
I don't understand why hot hot hot went out for 12 minutes.
All right I guess if Easter is just Easter equals fancy clothes I guess that's the justification
of that dancing guy.
What did he say.
Oh bungalows.
That actually was my reaction to seeing production facilities on this tour in the early 90s.
Yeah I was lit up.
I did this tram so many times.
Yeah sure.
Saw the van from honey I blew up the kid.
I was very into this.
Yeah.
Interior of the.
What.
I was like.
Interior of the.
What.
That's not.
That's a good guy.
He's on the tram and then he's on the tree.
That's a great.
That will be the funniest moment of this special.
Was this do you think this was written at all or it was just like how let how we go.
Let's just see what.
That guy had to be planned unless they went back and did it.
Yeah.
Whether the.
Unhonored.
Fake rocks of catastrophe canyon.
They're just look.
If cars is.
There's the same type of rocks as cars and cars are better.
Yeah.
I just have like.
Nostalgia.
It was also one of the ones we were talking about it's like oh most of these are still around.
This is gone.
Gone fake rocks could be an.
Still there.
Oh no I guess they're done with the backstage tour in Paris but there was a catastrophe canyon in Paris.
I didn't do it.
Because apparently the tram tour there you go see the sets of the movie rain of fire.
A Christian Bale.
Oh right.
They.
Is this unfamiliar to me.
John Lennon leg movie Jim and Len talked about that movie the whole studios park is
catastrophe canyon right.
It's just a big catastrophe.
Just like that movie I think that movie they were banking on being a big hit and it.
Only made millions of dollars.
So this is how we at what is is he off the show what show was he on again the hospital show.
St.
Elsewhere.
Is that over at this point.
Maybe.
He was probably doing the tonight show a lot.
Yeah.
On his way to Bobby's world.
He also has obsessive compulsive disorder like Mark Summers.
Yeah.
That always bugged me out as a kid when I learned that I was like where did these guys go.
I don't know if that's why they I don't know if that's why how he was missing for a while.
Mark Summers.
Mark Summers it kind of hurt his career because people assumed he was difficult.
Yeah.
Like people talk like oh I hear that guy's something's like he feels like he got a bad
reputation because of what is ultimately a pretty minor thing.
I.
Got a couple there and I've seen that.
Yeah.
We have to get him on the show.
I would love to.
That's a dream.
Okay more ads for the title is so pretty.
Oh is there a hot hot hot here too.
God willing.
But you consider you think like the Mickey Mouse Club doing escapade was too like grown up
for you.
Well I'm not I'm just saying for I know what I was like as a little kid.
But you wouldn't have I did like all of I liked MMC a lot by nine and there were I
I think I thought all their songs were original.
So when I realized wait another band does runaway train.
Right.
Yeah I wasn't like I didn't think it was like I'm trying to think if there's any
contradiction to this is that Mickey's birthday land.
Oh boy.
Oh we were big for sure.
Birthday land fans.
I yeah I have very strong memories.
One step away from the den.
You're a star you're a fucking star.
And he stands up.
Yeah.
Zips in his big mouth hog.
The gummy bears.
Whoa.
Why these guys.
Shit.
The scary way guys.
I will say there's a great theme song.
All those all those shows have such great theme songs.
Ducktales is obviously the best.
Ducktales and Westview Rangers would stress me out sometimes because I was like they're
going into these adventures without weapons because I was such an action figure kid that
came in action figures came with so many weapons and I was like well they're prepared.
So this is just yeah this is just promoting the Disney afternoon block.
Launchpad dancing.
I don't know why it's like Easter.
Yeah they tried to meld a couple ideas here.
Let's like have launchpad and then one of the.
These are kind of like cheeky versions of Easter dresses.
These are.
Yes.
A little sexier for daddy.
Right.
For screw for uncle screwed.
The men look like newsies the men look like.
Yeah.
This feels a little more rehearsed than most of the other stuff.
This feels like the higher quality dancers.
These are the triple threats.
Right.
Are you reading the lyrics to the Ducktales theme.
Now I'm looking I'm trying to remember this the guy who wrote the.
Ducktales theme.
Mark Mark.
Muller actually.
I'm reading my own Muller report right now.
None of these are that famous of songs though I'm realizing he wrote for all these big artists
like a heart and Amy Grant and in sync and to barge and.
But the biggest hit of his was the song called crush by Jennifer page.
Do you remember that song.
I don't think so.
When you were poking your head into music.
Just a little crash.
Oh yes yes.
That's the Ducktales guy.
Yeah apparently.
Interesting.
This is the poo where it looks like he kind of has a five o'clock shadow on his nose.
There's a Christopher Robin face.
Oh yeah you're right.
Walking around.
Holy crap it's just a boy.
It's just a boy in a yellow shirt.
Where is it.
Wait.
But you know I'm saying that poo that coloring on poo snoot is weird.
They were just talking about snoot.
So disturbed by snoot.
Yeah it's all I say about Edwin about the dog is I call him is now to snoot.
It's it's look it up it's right.
What's Edwin doing right let's do an Edwin check in.
He's over somewhere else somewhere else.
I was trying to get him up on the couch but he's.
Aghunt to aghunt today.
What is that joke.
Does he misspell things.
But he's like a professor he's like wearing his cap.
It doesn't really look like that owl.
That doesn't look like poo owl.
No that looks like the Tootsie Bro pop owl.
Yeah tootoo.
Who sounds like Tigger actually now that I think about it.
Gadget Dale.
Have I said on the show before.
Gadget always had to save their asses.
Confirmed or not but somebody said that Chip is dressed like Indiana Jones and Dale is dressed like Magnum P.I.
Yeah that's a hundred percent.
That's got to be right.
Yeah I was kind of making that observation in Japan because they're pushing these guys in Japan right now.
Yeah.
The two adventurers of TV at the time.
Yes.
And Gadget was supposed to look like the girl in the movie Real Genius.
The Val Kilmer movie.
Oh.
Kind of a crushable dork character.
That's like a wrestling move.
It all makes sense.
I know my type.
You just steal what's popular.
The wrestler Sting is just the crow basically.
Yeah.
I mean all that you know that Fred Flintstone is.
Ralph Cramden.
Jackie Gleason.
Yeah it's a tradition.
That's a big family.
I like those shirts.
There's a guy with a turtleneck in the back.
Family shirts are really good.
That's much better than like hashtag Disney dab or whatever people's shirts say now.
And I'd like to dress like exactly as Regis is dressed in this.
Yeah that's fun.
I would wear that.
I would wear that too.
Oh but it's love.
His love is really peeking out.
He's really close to Mayor from Jaws.
No anchors on that jacket but very close.
You're right.
I believe Paula Tompkins has that suit.
Not the exact suit but got that suit made.
He has every suit in this special.
This is not a song I like.
Jackamo.
What is this song?
It's familiar.
This was another like late 80s early 90s kind of hit.
Jackamo.
Oh yeah.
I'm anxious to do more MMC and I'm not sure how to do it.
Is it commentaries?
Is it an episode?
It looms large when I went to Disney MGM studios.
God this is where the guys are.
I'm not sure.
God this is where the guys work.
Where all my boys, Dale Godboldo and Ryan Gosling, that cool looking Canadian kid.
Paula the swimwear has come back around and is fashionable again.
Yeah I guess that's true.
Wave pool.
Oh my gosh too fast.
Too fast cuts.
Catch a kitty.
Great.
Green screen.
Wow into the water.
Ooh lady it's a classic take off the sunglasses because you cannot believe.
Yep.
Anything where that happens edited back and forth.
It would be interesting.
What's the first time that's ever happened in a piece of filmed entertainment?
We discovered that trick.
I mean I'm sure it's like a net movie or something.
It's like beach party.
Yeah I guess all the.
80s cool sunglasses guys sort of emanate from.
Yeah I'm sure there was.
Whoa check it out.
That's an interesting historical the popularity of Ray Bam sunglasses.
Like there was a point in time where they were not as ubiquitous.
And then I think it's risky business brought them back into the popular consciousness.
But that company has been bought and sold a few times.
Right.
Why is Goofy with Pinocchio here?
And why does Goofy have beach wear out and Pinocchio is just wearing his regular.
I think he's wearing slightly shorter shorts.
Pinocchio.
I rolled those up.
And then Tigger has beach wear and Chip and Dale have beach wear.
Better than 40s uniform.
But there's no way you put Pinocchio in the water.
Hell no.
Why?
It would float.
You put you give him a bath he warps.
Yeah he warps.
That's a literal joke.
Waterproofed.
You want to put a wooden pocket in the water.
You're out of your mind.
But that's not them.
Why did you use that title there?
The only place where it would have been appropriate.
I love that old man eating a hot dog.
Yeah.
Your future.
That's your favorite Disney character.
Yeah.
Papa Steve old man eating hot dog.
And Regis in that one shot.
Yeah.
Okay.
I mean that looked fun.
I would want to go there as a kid.
They did a good job of that.
My god they did a good job with me always.
Wooden puppet face down in the wave pool.
These specials ruined me.
Look at what I'm doing right now.
Doing a podcast about them.
I watched willingly watched 90 minute ads all the time.
They were my favorite shows.
I am broken.
You heard it here first.
Great place says Alan Thicke.
Scott would you rather be one of the beautiful people on their way to Coachella right now?
Where did that already happen?
Is it their honor in Christ the least?
I think it's going on right now still.
It's a two weekend last weekend one.
I believe so.
I cannot think of a place I'd less rather be.
Even if there's like that most I see five bands I'd like to see at Coachella and I'm like I'll
wait for them to come to me.
I think I could do it.
Hold on guys guys.
Now if they were at Coachella.
What song is this?
Oh, it's the annoying.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Those are their scarecrows, but they definitely look like they're on the crosses.
They're honoring.
I know that's how you hang a scarecrow, but it really looks like extremely.
You don't have to make it like that though.
No, that's insane.
Whoa.
Those are four crucified scarecrows.
If there was three, it'd be really spooky.
Shall I release Jesus of Nazareth or the scarecrows?
Is that Teddy bear up in the balcony there?
No, that might be the chicken.
It's claret.
Oh, it's a chicken.
Oh my God.
Those are scary strangers.
It's the strangers in an early role.
Christ's time on the cross was not filled with dance.
No, that's on that day.
That's fun.
Did you guys do square dancing in gym class?
Wait, we've talked about this before.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I guess it was Jim.
I believe that's a weird thing where they're like, we're going to just
wage you into the pool of touching each other.
Yeah, so rock and roll.
Red on those days.
We were in third or fourth grade was when we did it.
So I don't think anyone was really just kind of dip in their toe and even
thinking about that sort of thing.
Well, I'm just yeah, I'm not saying I'm like I was so
horny or something.
I was just it was uncomfortable.
Have I said on the podcast before how I knew that I was out of step with
people starting to boys and girls starting to like each other?
I don't know.
In fifth grade, I realized that a lot of the kids are like, where is everybody at lunch?
A lot of them were going and playing single out on the playground together.
Oh my gosh.
Christ.
They were coordinating.
That's insane.
An outdoor singled out.
I don't know what the prize ultimately was.
They were only 10.
Gee, what could it have been?
But that was a bunch of 10 year olds all emulating Chris Hardwick.
That's insane.
Truly.
Now, no one should emulate Chris Hardwick.
Jesus.
This is the best.
I love this.
Hey, how are you?
He didn't ask for the kiss like usual.
Yeah.
Muckracker Regis.
Cinderella mice.
I can't tell you.
Erin meeting Suzy and Perla was a precious moment.
I will cherish this for.
Is there a photo of it too?
I did.
I is a video.
I've videoed the whole thing.
That's good.
I've taken screenshots.
But yeah.
She said, you're my favorite in the most sincere way.
Oh my God.
As if she was six.
Then I met Captain Hook and I put up a hook next to him.
He kind of got a kick out of that.
But then he put my hook down dismissively and pointed at his own.
As if to say number one.
That's great.
Good character business.
Well, what is this?
What is going on?
Is that Tom Snyder?
Oh, give kids the world a wonderful charity.
That might be the founder, the guy who started it.
He looks like Tom Snyder to me.
So we're not allowed to make fun of anything.
No jokes.
All right.
I'm just going to be sad as in the hour of Christ's death.
I think, OK, so I can get I know for a fact they are updating their ice cream parlor
because I read some stories about it.
They are expanding their ice cream parlor.
Scoop Scoops dot com.
On the mouth, I guess.
Oh, all right.
I don't know.
What do we do?
Yeah, I know.
They're in a real tough spot here.
Oh, really tugging on the heartstrings.
They got some Louis Armstrong factoids to express.
He played on the Mark Twain at Disneyland.
Great charity.
Still going strong.
Check it out.
Look at Mickey.
It's the world.
There's Pinocchio.
There's a big edit in the song.
So we don't have as much of this to do as we thought.
Oh, but still a little bit of the song.
Still the bridge.
Right.
Is this the best song on the whole show?
I think it has to be right.
I like Descapade.
You think Escapade is better than this?
I think Escapade is a better song than What a Wonderful World.
Yes.
Well, again, that's interesting.
I mean, maybe not their version, the song itself.
We'll wait until the record scratch happens in this and they cut to another version of Hot, Hot, Hot.
Hey, kids, bet you never dreamed you'd meet Buster.
Let's go.
Din, din, din, din, din, din.
The first time Erin came to take the Universal tour, which began the relationship and marriage,
I said, if people came to take my tour, I was like, anything you want me to,
any factoids you want to request?
And she was like, oh, yeah, I loved when I was a kid.
And the tour guides would say this is in old Mexico is where they filmed the Escapade video.
So I made a point of it for her.
Wow.
That's if that's.
And that cemented the first date happening, I'm sure.
I think it did.
That showed that I was receptive to her demands.
Yeah.
And you wielded tremendous power.
Speaking of tremendous power, Reeds is still in the outfit.
Coachman.
Thick Furious.
Yeah.
What is that t-shirt the guy's wearing?
He agreed that that comedy would be entirely on me.
Who is that cat?
Yeah, I'm trying to figure, well, what is that shirt that gentleman is wearing?
It's like a no something.
I like it's like a Joe Cameli kind of character.
Shazam for shirts.
Oh, there's the Easter rabbit.
There he is.
Oh, Jones kids are in the parade.
Nowadays, it doesn't have to be pleasant.
Hop Dreamworks hop that rabbit who loves to play the drums.
Russell.
Jim is Russell Brand, isn't it?
Jim Hill said that Hop is going to replace half of Animal Kingdom.
Hop was going to be on all the rides.
Wait, these are all like Navy men, admirals.
Are those real Navy men?
Oh, the guy who came in here was 80 years old was in the Navy.
Oh, and he had a giant crazy toupee on his head and he was very shaky with this.
It was scary.
Thank you.
He still hasn't though.
Your hair is pretty shaggy.
You didn't like it was two weeks ago.
Hmm.
Did he not cut anything then?
He didn't do a thorough cut.
He may not have gotten all the nuances of what I was looking for.
I sort of wanted to get out of there quickly because I kind of wandered into the situation.
You went in with a picture of Henry from the country bears.
Give me one of these.
Once he started talking about the battleship that sank and how many men went in the water
and how many came out shark circling.
He did a thing where he started shit talking like
people who cut hair at a train station because he was like, you don't want to go.
He's like, how do you want to cut in the back?
And I was like, you can blend it.
And he's like, you're going to want a neck.
So if we blended, you're going to see your neck.
You should just do it like a square.
I go, oh, sure.
Okay.
And he goes, if you get your haircut at the train station, they'll just do whatever you say.
And they don't, they don't tell you what they think.
That's not a universal reference point anymore.
I go in about 40 years, I think.
I go, yeah.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks for the tip.
Whatever.
And he's like, they'll just do it.
They don't care what it looks like.
And I go, oh yeah.
The train station.
Don't trust the shoe shine.
Is that a train station?
Got to go to a real cobbler for that.
Mad at a trend from 1939.
I like that Mickey too.
That's great.
I would show Lindsay a picture.
Don't buy a pack of cigarettes without the tax sticker on it.
You don't know what they're sticking in there.
Soon Lindsay will be home and you can show her a picture of that.
She can say, hmm.
My sister had a daisy hat like that I think.
So they're just playing the instrumental Easter parade song and
it's just singing.
Easter parade.
Still in the.
Who's next?
Is Robin there?
I think, is that Mrs. London?
Is that Robin?
Or Mr. London?
Robin.
No, not Robin.
Oh.
Brendan.
Is Robin not born?
No, Robin's a little older than me so he has to, I think.
So he has to.
You didn't think him.
That one.
A little mad at Robin right now.
See like the kid not standing still.
That's great.
That's so funny and charming.
I think Robin's actually a little like more old.
I like the colors there.
That's a nice little shot.
They got that right.
Can we buy a shirt with the Kissimmee St. Cloud logo on it?
I mean there were so many.
Is there like a T-public?
Should we sell a shirt?
No, well we shouldn't do too many knockoff.
Can you, you can put a town's name on a shirt.
I guess that's true but I would want that logo.
Matt.
Like in a varsity kind of like college font, Kissimmee St. Cloud.
We should get Letterman jackets from like Kissimmee U or I mean Kissimmee High.
Oh they put everyone up at the Grand Floridian.
Nice.
Yeah, hell yeah.
Hell yeah.
Fancy.
Convenient and fancy.
That's the benefit of being Deborah Minchow.
Remember the stories of Eisner wanted all the housekeeping at the Grand Floridian to
carry the linens and towels and wicker baskets up to each room and they're like this will take
weeks to try and clean.
We need to use the carts.
Eisner you're mad.
He had some, he was blue sky-ing it.
He was a good blue sky and a good on game but it wasn't a boutique hotel where that's feasible.
Yeah.
Ray Lago.
There's no list of credits without at least one funny name.
It has to be.
It seems strange that you couldn't get, I feel like I could list 100 people I know.
And Dell Moody is kind of funny.
The set design just said quote Jimbo.
Yeah I saw that too.
Whoa.
That's going by real fast.
Alan picks wardrobe by Rick Pallick.
I remember Rick Pallick and Sherman Oaks and I remember all the late like Pat Riley and
the Lakers would have been dressed by Rick Pallick.
Oh wow.
Kurt Ramis's wardrobe provided by Rick Pallick.
Rick Pallick.
We should get Rick Pallick on the show.
Joe Rogan talks about DMT to a 10 year old boy.
If you like that.
If you like that you might also like Triumph of the Will.
No it was going to start playing the 1989 parade which we'll have to wait for another day.
At some point yes.
Well that was delightful.
That was a lot of fun.
1995, 97's still available to watch.
If you have requests of things you'd like commentaries on we've seen people call for
those and we're aware of them but we've only done the holiday tie ins.
Those have forced our hand but we hope you're having a happy Easter today.
I actually as a little like parting note I you know soon you'll hear my thoughts about
my trip to Japan but Easter big deal there.
I went to the Tip Top Easter show and I didn't write them all down.
Let me make sure I can remember them.
But here's my parting Easter thoughts.
From these are the lyrics of the Tip Top Easter show at Tokyo Disney Sea.
Honey bees begin to dance as the flowers grab their hands.
We cannot apologize.
Easter makes us come alive.
That is the most wholesome thing I've ever heard.
I love it.
I don't know why we cannot apologize.
I'm not sure what they're that lyric was said many times in a long show.
Very polite culture.
Maybe just giving a heads up.
And they should be able to apologize better than anybody.
You would think.
They can't apologize.
Well they're just doing their you know what they were put on earth to do.
Bloom and pollinate right.
It's kind of they're like keeping it 100.
Edwin did not care for that.
Edwin is a grumble real loud at that.
Did not like that wholesome observation.
He's right in front of the fireplace now too.
Like a real like if he had an Easter bow on it would be perfect.
In your Easter bonnet.
He's yawning now.
Now he's upset.
All right I guess let's get out of here.
I don't like when I sing in general as I've discovered.
I mean he's as unhappy with that as anything.
Yeah he's always unhappy honestly.
He's got to go outside and so do we.
Open the tomb for the children of the world.
Jesus.
Roll back the rock.
Climb off your cross for the Christians of the world.
And now I like Easter.
Happy Easter.
Thanks for subscribing.
Email us anything else you want us to do commentary on at podcastradar.gmail.com.
We'll hit you with more episodes soon.
Goodbye.
you