Forever.
Dog.
Theme Park fans are a passionate sort.
Check any of their favorite message boards like MouseWeb or ChurroChat and you'll see
they're always debating what's the best ride, what is the superior treat, which Theme Park's
corporation is best at lobbying the government.
But one topic is missing from these spirited debates.
A topic that this podcast takes very seriously.
A topic worthy of 150 minutes of discussion and a well thought out tournament style bracket.
The topic?
Fake Rocks.
On today's show, 16 fake rocks will compete in a knock down drag out fight to crown the
fake rocks champion.
Which fake rocks will reach the top of the mountain and which fake rocks will landslide
in an avalanche of humiliation?
It's the Fake Rock Final Four.
On Podcast The Ride.
Welcome ladies and gentlemen to a once in a lifetime historic Podcast The Ride gimmick.
Today's the day we've talked about fake rocks, our love of fake rocks in many an episode
for many a week and today once and for all we will determine which fake rock is the most
great fake rock in the Fake Rock Final Four.
I'm Scott Garner joined by Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
I'm here.
I'm nervous.
My name is Mike Carlson.
This is important is really what it is.
That's the word I would put.
I was in my car, pulled up out front, beating my chest, getting psyched up.
You were beating your chest?
Beating my chest raw and bloody.
As I was going through today, just revisiting all the pictures of all of these and I started
to get very worked up.
Like, oh well I know who's going to win this.
Were you psyching yourself up to argue with us or were you just sort of in general getting
your brain ready to like figure a question out?
I guess a little of both.
I took a steroid.
I took one steroid.
Single steroid?
Yep.
A couple hours ago.
So hopefully it'll time out and kick in and I will be at my peak of rage when we are determining
the last two or so.
But it was just like three months old and you had bronchitis.
It was that kind of steroid.
Yeah, yeah.
It's not really going to do anything.
No, it's not like I got one from some, you know, MMA guy or something.
No, it was doctor prescribed.
But still, you know, my body's not accustomed to it.
I'm hoping that I like rage out to where I look like a rock monster as we're doing this.
I should have been on HGH for this.
Human growth hormone.
You've talked about that for years.
I do want to go on HGH.
That's true.
We haven't talked about that on the show yet.
But I feel like that's good to go on.
You mean like the thing that people, it's like, you've talked about celebrities aging
weird and taking this crazy stuff.
Yes.
OK.
Like, like, look, maybe I'm going to get him mad at us.
He's never come on the show, but like Stallone probably does.
He's an older gentleman.
But look how damn it we blew it.
I mean, well, it's fine.
Perfect guest for Planet Hollywood.
I'm also not saying it's bad.
I'm saying it's good.
I think there's a lot of older guys specifically that take it.
And I think it's you admire.
You're not bad for taking it, but it doesn't always have good effects.
Sure.
I think it usually has good effect.
I think it usually makes you look cool and you're stronger and maybe your joints hurt
a little less as you go.
It makes you think it's a good thing.
Oh, I do.
I think I think I mean, I think you got to take it safely.
You know how to do it.
I don't know how to take it safely.
I wouldn't just go do it.
But I'm saying I think in the right safe way.
It's fine.
Yeah.
Like in the movies, superheroes get their powers through accidents.
But in real life, I mean, those superpowers, superheroes don't just spring up overnight.
You got to go to a superhero store, get some super items and like slowly adjust your body
to them.
Because I don't want to get too off track here.
But my also my thinking with this is like, I want to be able to go on these rides into
my seventies and eighties and God hope nineties.
You know, I'd like to go on the newest roller coaster in my nineties, my mid nineties.
And you know, your neck hurts, your back hurts, your knees hurt sitting in these cars, these
vehicles and I want to feel good.
So yeah, I think HGH or whatever is going to be around, you know, in 50 years.
That's what I'll be taking.
I want the same thing.
And I want the ability to get pregnant as well.
So I'm going to take whatever wide net of hormones I need to where I can be 90 and pregnant
and on all the rest.
My baby will be jacked.
Like they'll be like they'll be I've been ingesting nothing but HGH.
That's good.
So they'll be fine.
They'll be more equipped than me.
So whatever William Gibson, Warren Ellis, body hacking, cyber future shit.
Sure.
Yeah, let's let's go for it.
Yeah, we're talking the few our future, which involves like whatever is going to be done
to genetically modify meat and whatever, like any like any like DNA CRISPR, the gene editing
technology.
Right.
It'll be totally fair game for me to get pregnant in 10 years and go on all the roller coasters
I want.
Sure.
I think it's a good idea if you want your baby to have a six pack or an eight pack when
it comes out, which I think one on his front and one on his back.
Wow, that'd be great.
Very cool.
You could say like, yeah, you could literally like set on a computer how much you can bench.
You could have a baby that looks like that creature that that someone CG modeled like
this is what the human body would have to look like to survive a car wreck.
Have you ever seen that?
Oh, that's right.
Yes.
Yeah.
Really bizarre, exaggerated, just disproved.
Like you took a photo of a regular person and like did Photoshop like smudging all over.
Yeah, yeah.
Huh?
Yeah, I'm going to do that.
I'm going to have a baby that looks exactly like when they show what Homer would look
like if he was a real person.
You know, that's the real life Homer that 90 and take it on a roller coaster.
I think that that's that also gives me the idea that at a certain point, you know, because
you'll see those things where people get plastic surgery to look like famous people.
No, yeah.
So certain person would look want to look like Angelina Jolie and they would get the
same lips or whatever.
But I do think we're soon we're not far away from fictional character plastic surgery.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
Where you will get that terrifying real life Homer plastic surgery.
I don't know if it's Homer.
That's the one that will be the most sought after.
But then I'll get surgery to look like what's his name?
Hondo from from Star Wars Rise of the Resistance.
Yeah, sure.
Hondo Anaka.
Yeah, I'm going to look like Hondo Anaka at 90 years old.
I'm going to have face tentacles and stuff.
I will be I will ask for Davy Jones from the Pirates movies who also has tentacles on his
face. Oh, sweet. We'll get along great.
Yeah. So people are going to freak when they see us together.
Sure. Walking around.
But they'll have a lot of people have tentacles on their face in 50 years.
If you're also like if you're a big Futurama fan and you get Zoidberg surgery.
Of course. Oh, sure.
Futurama will be brought back 25 times in 50 years, I think, too.
So there'll be new versions of Futurama to keep it fresh.
The IP fresh in people's minds.
Yeah. So there's a big family members.
Are you going to look like a face tentacle?
Yes. Mine will, of course, be hot dogs.
My tentacles will be hot dogs.
Will they like grow and regenerate and be snacks for you?
Oh, sure. They can't always be like Nathan's all the time.
Sometimes I'm going to want to Polish.
Sometimes I'm going to want a little smoky like you have at the Christmas.
That is so disgusting.
Hey, I got those Trader Joe's pastry pups, the little mini ones in the fridge
right now, make my way through a package of those delightful.
How do you portion those out? How many serving size is four at a time?
I had five last night and four today with a side of baked beans.
I got some baked beans to have with them.
And yeah, maybe I'll have the rest tomorrow with some chips
or the rest of the baked beans like a hobo with a home. Yeah.
I mean, maybe that's the best description of Jason ever heard.
We correctly correct it.
Yeah. I mean, he goes on vacation. He takes a bimble.
Yeah. And the chalk so I can leave messages for the ones who come after
and to LAX friendly house.
Yeah. This security line is very good.
And an old beat up hat.
Well, back to fake rocks
in the sports of fake rocks that we're doing.
So we've talked about do it.
We had the idea to do a final four about something brackets for something.
And Mike, you came up with the fake rock notion.
And that's it's perfect because it's it's an extremely competitive category.
It's jammed.
I don't know how we're going to be able to narrow it down to just one.
And also, I don't think is did anybody Google.
I don't think anyone's because with theme park stuff,
we're not the first theme park podcast.
We're not the first person, the first group of people to do like a bracket
for rides or something.
But I think as far as fake rocks, this is the first in the world.
I think this is we've never there's never been a tournament
to determine the best fake rocks before.
There's maybe listicles of like ranking the Disney Mountains.
Sure. That's not exactly what this is.
And there's mountains that don't qualify in this.
Absolutely. And I want to say, just because you are a mountain,
don't think you're making it to the final rounds.
I want to say that right at the top.
That's an interesting point.
But, you know, I might have been a little mountain centric in my thinking so far.
So that's a good challenge already to make me question.
I have not really we're saying I haven't really picked these out of the 16
that we had narrowed down to 16.
And just that was very tough.
But I do not have my choices within this.
And you might have shifted my thinking already.
Yeah, because I mean, we're going to see.
I think it's going to become apparent as we start talking about it.
Now, I've got my favorites and I've got some dark horses.
But I don't, you know, who knows how it's going to shake out.
Like you might kind of like be pushing for one that is
maybe more of a personal preference than a like
board of directors would determine.
It's the best. Yeah, I think that should.
Yeah, I think some of these are going to be more personal than others.
Some of these none of us have ever seen in person.
Yeah, that's going to that's going to hurt it.
We can admit some bias there.
But I think including them shows that we have a good
vista of what's out there, fake rock wise. Right.
And we're representing the international parks.
Even if we haven't been there in person.
I want to say this is not about the rides.
Yeah, I want to be very clear.
This has nothing to do with the rides themselves.
This is all about the fake rocks that are outside of the ride, inside.
They're like part of the ride.
It depends depending on what attraction we're talking about.
But my liking of the rides has nothing to do with me choosing.
What's the better fake rocks? Yeah, absolutely.
It's possible that like a lesser ride, it's possible that a if
if you went into a crazy fake rock facade
and it was essentially it was like superstar limo in there
and the ride itself has some problems.
But if that outside is beautiful and the transition inside is beautiful,
there's no reason it shouldn't be able to compete against like a top tier ride.
Yes, exactly.
And I think that's a great example, because I think it universally agreed
upon the superstar limo exterior.
Beautiful.
Folks, look it up if you haven't seen it.
Oh, boy.
When any time when pop art was part of the parks, when it was just, you know,
when like the postcard come to life and.
Yeah, I it was a phenomenon.
I don't remember Disney and Universal quite doing this,
but I remember going to your your smaller, but you even Six Flags
or the Paramount Park stuff like that.
You would get your free maps.
But there was a fun souvenir map suitable for hanging or framing
that had some real kooky characters on it that you could buy for a.
That's sort of what Superstar limo is like. Yeah.
Yeah, it was like a weird.
It was like like lobby art come to life or something. Yeah.
We'll get to it. That's maybe a potential.
That's a future Final Four.
It could be worst facade. Right. Sure.
And Superstar limo obviously would be nowhere near it.
It's it's great. It's perfect.
It's kooky. It's the California spirit.
Yeah. I mean, best lighting, lighting or colored lighting setup.
That's a potential future Final Four, I think.
Oh, absolutely. Right.
Another point I had within this is like,
I mean, well, you know, I figure we should talk a little too about just like
why fake rock.
We've talked about fake rocks a lot and why we then that we love them.
I don't know if we've really said why we love them.
I don't know that I have a good answer for that.
But as you mentioned, Superstar limo, you know, think about early days
of California adventure.
There were some fake rocks, but not a ton, not as many as there are now.
Think about the cheapo era of Disney.
When California Adventure opened, then it was a little underwhelming.
Disney Studios Paris, the worst Disney theme park, probably still.
And and then compare those to Tokyo Disney
Sea, which opened around the same time, one full of fake rocks
flourishing with fake rocks.
The other is just sound stages and hangers and just flat walls.
I think those are some of the least fake rocks.
I don't think there was a single fake rock in Disney Studios Paris,
and I think they paid the price.
Yeah. So I think fake rocks are crucial to a theme park success out of the gate.
I agree. I know there's not.
I'm trying to think of like a good example of where you need it.
I mean, it's like it's essential. You're right.
It's it's something that I don't know what it does.
It just gives a texture.
It gives you a feeling of being somewhere that you're not,
which is just really just in a parking lot somewhere.
And people build a bunch of fake stuff.
But fake rocks transport you.
Yeah. In a way that a lot of things don't.
I wonder if even subconsciously, too, you go like, oh, they took the time.
This is a they had to make this.
It is a fake rock.
They didn't just buy a bunch of big rocks.
They constructed this.
They designed it. They constructed it and they painted it like there was some care.
There was some attention to detail from whole cloth.
And I bet we'll get into this that I think I would have to think
that some criteria would be the the depth of the painting work,
because there's like very slow,
deliberate gradients and like so much texture and variety within certain fake
rocks. And a fake rock that just has one color, the front to back,
is probably not as good of a fake rock. Right.
I you know, I actually I'll save this for one of the rounds.
One of them, I think my best argument for fake rocks is in a round,
but I won't do it here. Oh, OK.
Because I think I can make I can illustrate it better.
I have another little argument that I don't think applies to a specific thing,
but I think this might impact it as we go on.
I think there's some fake rocks that are very impressive to look at the entire
tableau. But I think some fake rocks have a brand to them.
And if you saw a close up of one of the rocks, you'd know exactly where that's from.
Now, does that matter?
I think there's excellent fake rocks where that test would not apply.
The forest for the trees test.
But I think something about, you know, that you could take the pattern of a fake
rock and use it as like a cell phone wallpaper or something that it's
instantaneous. The shade is iconic.
That's got to be. Yeah, I see what you're saying.
A big step for one of these rocks to be pulling in. Right.
I hear a guy. Yeah, I didn't even think about that.
There's a lot of things that we're going to explore.
We're going to discover, I think, too.
I think that really what this is about is discovering more about
why we love them and what makes one great.
Yeah. So it's like it's kind of a thinking man's
it's a sensitive man's bracket because we aren't just saying like you lose next.
We're going to we're going to stop and we're going to talk and we're going to
pontificate. Right. And I think I mean, look, there's going to be probably
arguments. There's going to be disagreements.
And I think at a certain point we will have to go two to one if that happens.
We're maybe not always all three of us going to agree on what moves forward.
So we'll have to go with two versus one.
But I think we'll do it in a cordial way.
We won't be upset about it.
And we will reflect.
If I were to lose one round, I would just go into some self reflection.
I wouldn't be angry. And some of them might not be anger inducing, but some of them.
Yeah. Some of them we might have to like stop and argue, which to that end, do we
just like say or do we do we say the competitors and then we pick or do we is
there a discussion beforehand?
Maybe it's a case by case.
I think it's case by case.
All right. We're going to be sure.
Yeah, we might as well just launch in.
Very interesting if any round is immediately unanimous.
That would be the most shocking thing to me.
What if like all of it was and this wasn't interesting and we were just all reciting
like song lyrics together, essentially?
Well, then there might be a mysterious unheard second half of this episode called
We Have a Late Dinner.
Well, yeah, well, we just put an old I'll just tack half of an old one on
second half of this.
Absolutely. Yes.
I just like a question from the past.
Or we just start talking about Batman's stunt show like 45 minutes in.
Sure. Yeah. Or we just do like we just like it's the best of HelloFresh ads.
We just have like 10 in a row.
Yeah. Yeah. A walk down HelloFresh memory lane.
We'll see. We'll see. We don't know.
This is new territory for all right.
Well, let's get into it.
And if you go well, like we'll figure out on Twitter how to post this.
There's got to be a way to do like a spoiler free post of the list.
Well, we'll post the brackets first.
Just the empty bracket so you can fill in your own bracket as well.
That'll be fun. You can post your own bracket.
Oh, yes. Send us your bracket.
Yeah. Do do one with your friends.
Yes. See if you can reach an agreement.
See if you do.
Yeah. Do one before you've heard our choices and see how much it lines up.
Record a podcast and then post send it to us and then we'll review all of the podcasts.
And then there'll be a final four of the podcast.
We will determine the best fake rock final for Jason.
We'll send it right to Mike.
Mike Jason will review all of them.
And then well, you have the idea.
You're the idea man.
You always have these good ideas.
You love executing them.
Now, do we mean I was going to say that maybe the hashtag
PTRFRF4.
OK, TRFRF4.
Got it. So anything related to this?
And that's where you can go to see our brackets and to participate.
And I think and what you'll find, I had a I had a revelation.
So we determined that it's we're going to we're going to do 16 will down to one.
We couldn't think of a reason to put them into conferences.
So it's not going to be eight to eight meeting in the middle.
It's going to be that other style of bracket that nears down to one.
And, you know, I turn this thing on its side, 16 narrowing down to one.
You flip it on its side.
It looks like a mountain.
It's a mountain.
So we're not just narrowing down into a funnel.
We are going to start at the base camp with our 16 competitors.
And they're all going to race to the peak and see who plants a flag
on fake rock mountain. Right.
It's very exciting. I don't know.
I don't know who will ascend and climb.
I won't say Everest, because that would be biased because Everest.
Maybe it's on the list.
And what if it's not in in the 16 at all?
Anyway, anyway, let's get to the first round.
All right. First round, first round.
Expedition Everest versus the Matterhorn, Matterhorn Mountain,
Matterhorn Mountain. So this is a tough one.
One is kind of a spiritual heir to the other.
Do you reward a classic?
Do you reward the the one that improved on the formula?
And this is, I think, another conflict that's going to come up
like old school versus new school, because we have, you know, Everest.
We did an Everest episode not too long ago, and they were talking about
using lasers and computers and everything to like map it
and how to paint it and all that.
They didn't have that technology when they were building the Matterhorn.
Yeah, they just had like soup in a can and like a legal pad
with a bad pencil. And somehow they built a mountain.
Yeah, yeah. But you got to give them credit for that.
You do. So what do we think?
How do we do? Do we do we always do it in the same order?
Do we just we just throw them out?
We get we got to develop some order.
What's what's everyone's does everyone have a strong opinion?
Let me say this.
Well, this is actually what I was referring to alluding to before.
I like these fake rocks because and my favorite fake rocks are ones that
make you feel like you're somewhere like maybe a geographical place.
That's interesting. But are a little off or a little strange
because that's where we are.
We're not in the real world, but we're in a heightened reality.
We're in somewhere special. We're in a storybook.
We're in another movie, something like that.
So those tend to be maybe my favorite fake rocks,
which is why I choose for this the Matterhorn over Expedition Everest
is my favorite fake rock of fake rocks of these two.
That would be my choice for this round.
I think I'm leaning towards that as well,
because you come to the end of a turn of centuries street
and you look to your right and there's a giant snow cap mountain.
Then there's a medieval castle.
And then there's, I don't know, trees for adventure land.
But yeah, that Matterhorn is so striking,
and especially after a childhood of going to the Magic Kingdom in Florida
to come to Disneyland and go like, holy shit, there's a fucking mountain
at the end of this main street.
I don't care if the ride went away forever.
The ride itself, I think, is fine. It's old. It hurts.
I love the new effects they put on it. I like going on it.
But the mountain itself, I think, would be more of a casualty than the ride.
And Expedition Everest, I like way better. It's incredible.
It's one of the best rides.
But if we're just going fake rocks, I got to go.
I got to go Matterhorn.
Well, and you know what?
It's a pioneer
within the world of fake rocks, potentially the first major fake rock landmark.
You know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to cast my vote for Expedition Everest
just to acknowledge it, because that is where I was leaning.
But that does not affect. I just want it to get a vote.
In a way, like this pairing is insane.
There's another world where Expedition Everest moves on handily.
But the category does make sense to me.
I see what you're saying. And tough choices have to be made.
So I'm going to give it a vote to acknowledge it, because it is a great one.
But I but dancing to the next round is the Matterhorn. Great.
That's what you said. That's what I said. Yeah, to to matter.
So Expedition Everest done, not going to win, not the best fake rock.
Oh, my God. An embarrassment.
That's a surprise. That's a quick right out of the gate.
I feel like. Well, I like that we're starting with it with a controversial one.
Not an easy one. UCLA gets knocked out early sometimes, you know? Right.
Yep. True. It's yeah.
Something some guys come in cocky. Yeah.
I would imagine I don't watch college basketball,
but that seems like something that would either guys are cocky
and then they don't play good in the basketball game. Sure.
Um, round round to Splash Mountain versus Seven Dwarfs Mind Train.
I don't need to rationalize this if somebody wants to go for it.
I got it. OK.
I'm throwing my hat in the ring for Seven Dwarfs Mind Train
because Splash Mountain, despite being a mountain,
I largely associate with dirt and the Briar Patch.
I don't think of fake rocks when I look at Splash Mountain.
There are really rocks in the in the facade of Splash Mountain.
But it's a lot of the Briar Patch. I'm looking at it's brown.
It's a lot of brown that you are.
I associate with like plant life, not rock work.
But Seven Dwarfs Mind Train, you go in a mine.
There's beautiful rock works outside.
You go under a bridge. Really good rocks.
They're good rocks.
But do they have the character of the rocks on Splash Mountain?
I would argue no. I see what you're saying.
That's certainly the obviously the water in the Briar Patch
are the big highlights of Splash Mountain.
But when you start on the ride and you're outside and you see those weird,
ugly, but good like they're brown, but they're, you know,
I can't even describe the color exactly of them.
That is like that is cartoon. You're in cartoon land.
Those are so specific to Splash Mountain.
And the rocks on Snow White are very beautiful,
but I feel like they lack character.
I feel like they don't have the quite the character that Splash Mountain itself
and the fake rock have. I agree with you.
I think if you put any of these other rides up against Splash Mountain,
you have a good some of these other fake rocks up on the list.
Yes, Splash Mountain might lose, but to me, it's Splash Mountain still.
Jason, the the the argument of the argument that you made
was an argument that was in my head.
The that when you think Splash Mountain, you think of a big log
because the top of it is a big log as logs going through it.
There's there's grass and roots and weird wood and tree houses and stuff.
But how are we to punish fake rocks for having other elements
as part of them for supporting other elements?
And I was going to use that argument to knock Splash Mountain out of another
pairing. But the fact that it ended up with seven dwarfs, Mind Train,
I do think that those actual rocks are big boulders.
I think they're I think they're cool. But I
I do think that the I think we're underselling the rocks.
I think the rocks have some character.
I think they're big and odd and bulbous, and they still strike fear into my heart.
You know, I started going on it.
I still get a little afraid.
I got to go with Splash Mountain.
It's a mangled, crazy structure.
It's so it is menacing and cute all at once.
You know, character is important and not really a thing I was considering.
In this round.
So I am going to gracefully bow out and accept that Splash Mountain clear.
Well, it's all this is a polite.
I also want to say we didn't.
There are no bad fake rocks on this list.
No, we did not choose any pity fake rocks.
Certainly, we are.
These are all great.
So if I say something bad about a fake rock, just know I still love it.
You also you've got a variety as I'm looking at a photo.
There's also like, you know, there's there's gray rocks
intermingling with the brown.
It's there's a tapestry of fake rock there.
And yeah, those those odd, you know, like, yeah, the bulbous
rotunda like curving on top.
This is I'm going to show how like not eloquent that I am.
This is not going to be like Thoreau or a poet who's good at describing nature.
You think that Splash Mountain, the whole the whole of it is very unique and beautiful.
But I don't think fake rocks are still the number one.
I don't disagree.
And that's I don't disagree with what you're saying.
I'm just saying that if you take away Briar Patch and you take away any
like little shed or whatever, you'd call it.
I still think this structure is more interesting and is speaks to me more
than just the fake rocks and seven dwarf, which again are beautiful.
But they're a little too almost a little too realistic for me.
Mm hmm. It's not.
That's a bit of a problem.
I think sometimes you might find that realism is what's cool about a fake rock.
But I but I think inventiveness is going to be key.
We are talking theme parks here, and I think that is going to be key
for any fake rocks moving forward.
That's the thing.
You know, that reminds me of like a recent Disney venture,
the the animated sequences in Mary Poppins Returns, like they did
try to do it in the style of the original Mary Poppins.
And I believe brought back some of the hand hand drawn animators to do it.
But there were times in that where I was like,
this is a little too clean, a little too.
Yeah, I agree. It's not dirty enough like the Mary Poppins animation,
the Robin Hood animation, Aristocats, there's a there's a grit to them.
That's hard to duplicate with the after effects or whatever.
Which is that's a philosophy that might favor older fake rocks.
That's a nice as opposed to an actual athletic event in which certainly
a 65 year old is going to lose to an 18 year old.
Not well, not the case in the final four.
Also not the case in like a WWE.
Oh, yeah.
Every time a six year old man beats up a 30 year old man.
What's the most exciting? Yeah.
Yeah, it's a little more populous.
So we got all right.
So Manhattan, Manhattan.
I wrote down the word Manhattan.
I think I got drinks on the brain.
I do.
And I always think like for my private
final four of different childers.
That's my number one.
We both wrote Manhattan and Mike, you're just always thinking of NYC.
That's why you wrote it, too.
So we know our first second round pairing will be Matterhorn versus Splash Mountain.
Yes. Tough one.
Wow. Tough one.
Yeah, boy.
Yeah.
So what's what's round number two?
He keeps advancing up the peak.
Well, this is three.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Who will end up in round number two?
Oh, that's what he just said.
It's splash. I think it's Splash Mountain and Matterhorn.
Yeah.
Oh, I'm saying entering into the next.
I mean, I'm incredibly inarticulate here.
Who are the next two that we're talking about?
The next pairing, Mount Apu Taku from Shanghai, Disneyland's Adventure Isle versus
Grizzly Peak from Disney's California Adventure.
This is a clash of the rapid rides.
The one from 2001, one from 2016.
These are a new century rapid rides, but we aren't talking about the rides,
which are almost identical.
We're talking about the the mountain peaks and the rocks.
Right. Insane to think about these rides
built in the 20th 21st century, that one of Disney's greatest blunders
and then one of Disney's people were concerned it was going to be a great
blunder, but seems to be doing OK like Shanghai seems to be doing all right
in terms of reviews and ticket sales and stuff.
I think it's slowed a little, but I think most parks fall into that after a year or
two of grand opening excitement.
It's great if you watch ride throughs and stuff, which I have because I can't
imagine I'm going to go there anytime soon.
There's some really inventive stuff over there and this is among them.
Oh, yeah. I mean, it's very cool.
Yeah. If you haven't seen this, but this
might be the fake rock that you are the least familiar with.
So Google Image just do Adventure Isle Shanghai.
And that'll show you what we're talking about.
It's a big, glorious waterfall.
It's very large.
I think it's in the in the the 200 foot range.
I have to say I was pulling photos and putting them into a note on my phone for
this. And when I looked this one up, this is probably the one I was least
familiar with. I audibly gasped like I was even on a tiny little iPhone screen.
I was amazed at the scale of this thing.
And I think it gets a little bonus of a favorite of one of my fake rock
types, which is fake rocks with real water.
Yes, that is a selling point of seeing
the fake rocks with an actual waterfall that might come up later too.
And one of my my decisions.
Think about the engineering that goes
into they have to figure out how to make water flow through the thing.
Yeah, this this thing.
This is probably the most insane Disney waterfall I would have to think.
Yeah, I can't name another.
And also, like, that's a cool thing about Shanghai Disney, which we haven't talked
about a ton. They kind of reinvented all of the lands.
They said, why do we have to just especially in the wake of Hong Kong,
Disney, which was just sort of a pretty like stamped copy of of original Disneyland.
How do we blow it up?
How do we make a totally different Adventureland and Tomorrowland and
also how do we adjust to local taste?
Because for, say, Star Wars doesn't have the cultural cash that it does in America.
Uh huh. Uh huh. Sure, sure.
But they love the Tim Burton, Alice in Wonderland.
Oh, yeah. Heavily feed.
Yeah, it's a giant scary queen.
And yeah, the scope of this thing compared to Adventureland,
which is always kind of the most humble land in all of the other Magic Kingdom
parks, but hey, we can't ignore the other competitor.
Grizzly Peak.
This is especially upon opening.
This was kind of the the icon, the silhouette of the park upon its opening.
And that's an argument I wanted to bring up about what makes a fake rock great.
The ability to draw it, that Simpsons rule of that you recognize the character
from the silhouette.
I don't think it always applies, but I think that's a cool facet of a fake rock
that you could do a bad little sketch of it and and you recognize it.
I think Grizzly Peak has that.
Yeah, it does.
For sure. And here's my thing with Grizzly Peak.
And I don't actually know what I'm going to choose yet for the between these two.
Yeah, this is a tough pairing.
Grizzly Peak. I didn't that maybe this is call me an idiot.
Didn't notice the bear until like maybe visit 20.
I agree with you 100 percent.
I'll go a step further.
For a long time, I thought it was a wolf.
Aaron thought that until a couple of visits ago.
And if you Google this issue, many, many people believe that.
And I think maybe people don't even know it's called Grizzly River Run.
And they haven't put that or they know that.
And they still are like, that's a wolf.
That's a piece. That's a nature thing.
Exactly. And when bears like a heart, the heart of California, beautiful bears.
We have a bear on our flag.
And yet still you missed that.
But I don't a lot of people did.
I don't blame you.
I think the problem, though, is I don't know if I should blame the rocks
for this or the location of the rocks. No, I do think I do like it.
I do think it looks good.
And I doubt when DCA first open, anyone was like, this looks like shit,
like lots of the rest of the park look like shit.
These fake rocks. This does look good.
And I like that. It's just like an aesthetic choice.
Like I have an issue with this.
We can't blame the rocks.
So the rocks are the rocks aren't babies.
They aren't innocent creatures who don't know any better.
These were made by Imagineers.
And if Imagineers made something, you can't tell what it looks like or if
there's confusion about what it is.
That like that's on them.
I just think if you tilt it like 45 degrees in one direction, people would notice it more.
I don't know which direction.
Yeah, because bears, I don't associate with bears with howling up at the sky.
I associate bears with like squatting on the ground or looking straight ahead or
something like the bears head should be like dipping into the river to find a
little more Mount Rushmore, even like you want.
Well, I want four country bears on Mount Rushmore.
Gosh, that would win.
That seems like a missed opportunity.
We would be doing the episode.
I would have said, you know what I pick.
And how is there not a Mount Rushmore anywhere in theme park world?
Is there one on whatever reason?
I immediately thought there was one in Jay Ward like rocking or.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
There is one. That's a preview.
I guess we can say that that didn't make the cut.
Did not make the cut.
Jay, which who's on it?
It's like Dudley.
And is it is it all of them?
Is it Dudley, his boss,
Snidely and his controller
is a county.
Her name may be someone screaming.
I got to look this up as I make Meg.
Yeah. Yeah.
It sounds like Meg.
Oh, no, I thought you said, you know, I don't think it is.
No, I just don't.
I stole the tweets of like, it's this.
Stress me out.
Meg, it sounds like that's not it, though.
It'd be a more Nell.
Nell, Nell, Nell, Nell.
Sorry for anyone yelling as in the lead up to it.
But hey, we got it this time.
We didn't leave it hanging like that Roger Rabbit thing.
We all fucked up. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
I was someone on the street the other day and heard them go like, oh, hi, my name's
Nell, someone they were meeting.
And I was just like, that's the first time I've ever met a real life Nell.
Most Nell's speaking gibberish.
Sure. Yeah.
Language they made up.
I don't know.
I got to.
Hmm. I don't know if I even want to.
I don't want to like tilt it one way or the other.
I guess I have to.
I guess I have to vote against Grizzly
Peak, and I'm not happy about it, though.
I so I here's my justification because I'm going with Mount Apu Taku too.
So Grizzly Peak loses points for that Wolf Bear Confusion.
Absolutely loses points for course it does.
The fact that like the park, as much as
you know, I am I I am not nostalgic, but I like to reminisce about DCA 1.0.
But Shanghai Disney seems like clearly a success out the gate.
I'm also giving Shanghai the advantage because that, like I said, looking up
pictures of this, I was in awe and I think awe is a thing that will come up in other
rounds of this, and I was very impressed and kind of like,
oh, maybe I should think about visiting this, although
China seems like it has so much going on all at once.
I think I still find it an intimidating hypothetical travel destination.
Just going in general.
Sure. Oh, yeah.
But I think you absolutely got to dock points for that.
I'm going to say I don't think it is that I think I think this actually is.
I think it's a fun fake rock, but I think it's a little chintzier than other ones.
I think there is a more big budget version.
I could see a version where they, like the Hong Kong Disneyland Castle,
replace this, have a much taller bear that completely dwarfs its surroundings
and where there's no question that it's a bear.
But I think it's a little silly that it's a mountain that looks like something.
I think that's a little I think that's a little goofball.
Well, they were going.
I think what the problem is, is they were trying to go with something like you could
hypothetically see that that could develop in nature and, whoa, that's crazy.
It does kind of look like a bear.
So that's why they call it that.
But it's we're talking about a theme park.
And I want that cartoon bear, that giant
wooden cartoon bear in the sweater at Christmas time face on a fake rock.
Oh, you say push it even more.
Make it. I'm saying, I'm saying like the reason I'm struggling here is because I
we don't have many character rocks, if any.
So I want to reward it for being a character rock.
Yeah. But, yeah, the confusion and its placement.
And I unfortunately have to vote for Taku.
There's still time.
I don't know if this qualifies as a fake rock.
It is a real rock with a thing in it.
But we could insert that thing in Georgia with the Confederate soldiers
in Stone Mountain. Yes, I was thinking about that when you asked if there was a
we could knock out Radiator Springs and put in Stone Mountain.
If that would make you feel better next year, we'll do that.
But not this. We were going to do the Stone Mountain, Georgia episode.
We need to get there.
Bracket of real American icons and hey, put that in your PC pipe and shove it up
your butt. That's the name of the episode.
It has that full sentence in it.
What a weird revelation.
Like three years into a podcast is like, also, we're Confederate sympathizers.
I don't have to complain about Trump or whatever, but tradition is tradition.
So, yes, three childless Confederate sympathizers in their 30s.
Yeah. Also, the Shanghai one looks really nice in the lights.
Oh, you know what? I haven't I haven't seen the night view.
There's a night view that just really looks.
Oh, you know what? I don't think I took night into consideration.
Well, it's going to come up. Yeah, that's going to come up.
All right. All right. Come on.
But what's coming up next?
This is this is a nice one.
We've seen two heart warmers.
The first one we've certainly seen enough of at night and the day.
It is Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
Yeah. And then the Calico Mine Ride and Outsberry Farm.
Calico Mine Ride and Outsberry Farm.
And this is an OG fake rock.
I think it's important.
Yes. Fake rock history, as we may have talked about.
It gave Walt Disney the idea of hiding cues
because some of the line was hidden within the fake rocks.
It was like the first, you know, this is a very clever fake rock.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
And I think the interior of of this thing is pretty fantastic.
When you think about the maybe a lot of people haven't been on this one.
If you haven't been to L.A. and been to nots,
but great interior, the super claustrophobic tunnels,
which are very neat to be kind of stuck in and teetering along in.
And then that part with the
the the organ, what do you what do you call it?
Like when when all the lights hit it and it's it's like petrified rocks
that look like an organ, all of the stalactites stalagmites.
Oh, right. Right. Right.
It's sort of a rainbow caverns vibe.
Yeah, that's, you know, like, hey, very clever interior fake rock lighting.
So I just there's a lot that I think is real nice about these particular fake rocks.
I have to agree. And, you know, I talked about the feeling of all in the previous
round in this one, thinking about these,
I got to give points to nots for the idea of scale.
Like it is so big.
And I have only I've only seen it at night because I've only been the knots
when we were there for not scary farm.
And I was shocked just at the size of this thing and that it was made in the 60s.
Yeah, it's been kicking around for so long.
And it's a park that wasn't exactly flush with real estate.
So to allocate such a huge amount to a giant fake rock structure
is impressive.
That does seem consistent inside and out.
I like when there's logic to the interior and that it isn't just I mean,
there's things on our list where then you essentially go into like
like a soundstage building, like a big industrial building.
It's hidden by fake rocks.
But I do think it's neat that like, oh, this entire attraction is is all fake.
And there has to be logic to the tunnels and what goes where.
Imagine getting lost in that thing.
That three story like middle zone is fantastic.
The problem is going into this.
I was thinking Big Thunder slam dunk because Big Thunder is incredible.
Yeah, sure. But this ride is all fake rocks.
Big Thunder, you're on top of the fake rocks.
You're on the side of them.
But like you're inside the fake rocks.
This might be the most fake rock ride of all fake rock.
Calico. Yeah, Calico. Yeah, that's a good point.
Yeah, I'm still not decided. I haven't decided yet.
I'm just thinking out loud here. I have a counterpoint.
Go ahead. I have I wanted this very much to be on here.
And and I'm passionate about this ride.
I think it's a real hidden gem.
But the other one is fucking Big Thunder Mountain.
Oh, I know Mountain is the pick for me.
Really? There's no argument there to me.
It's it. I mean, all those nice things I said. Sure.
But it's Big Thunder. These are iconic.
Fake rocks. But would it exist without Calico?
But that shouldn't be an argument.
That's that's that's all of them.
Yeah. But, you know, got to have points for the.
I would say if I'm working this out, though, the difference between
Everest and Matterhorn is that they're going for different things.
I do think Big Thunder is taking this and refining it.
Yeah. And specifically, you know, with the whatever you'd call it in the middle.
Is it a not a spire? Is it a spire?
What do you what would you call the big highest peak of Big Thunder?
I'm not sure. Yeah.
Peak spire. I guess.
I don't know. Nice looking turd pile.
Sure. They get littler as they go.
They're little plops. Yeah. Little plops.
I might say the most distinctive Disney Mountain.
The thing when you hear when I hear Disney Mountain, I would say Space Mountain.
But if we're talking fake rock mountain. Yeah. Yes.
Well, if you want. Yeah.
So so yeah, that's that is my struggle here is because of course,
that stuff is iconic and perfectly designed,
whereas the outside of Calico mine is beautiful.
And I wouldn't say even beautiful. It's impressive.
It's a little melty for sure.
The whole thing is a little melty.
And that's just because it's been around so long and they didn't have fake rock
technology. So I'm struggling here because when you go inside,
the fake rocks continue.
And some of the scenes, I would say, still kind of give Big Thunder
a run for their money as far as the fake rock scenes that exist on the ride.
That's true. But I think you have to take into account the all the international
versions of Big Thunder. It's in every part.
I'm thinking about it. There are different scenes within all of it.
And there are internal scenes.
There's an avalanche that blends perfectly or not an avalanche anymore.
But some of them have had it that blends perfectly the interior and the exterior.
I just think for what it does to the skyline,
to the for the way that it tributes our great national parks,
it gets that Bryce Canyon and Zion vibe in.
Right. That means Calico is one of a kind.
Is that extra points in that column?
It is. But, you know,
to what like here's another I'll make that silhouette argument.
I think you could show the silhouette of Big Thunder Mountain.
You know what it is right away.
The wild, the wild, the rocks are very cool in Calico.
I think it ultimately is like a blob.
Yeah, it is a blob. And and I will.
And this one I'm trying to think of this is incorrect.
So correct me if I'm wrong.
This one, a big thunder traveling on the rocks,
the iconic rocks on the outside.
You do that more like for sure.
Everest, Everest, you're kind of on a track through the mountain.
You're on a track here, too.
But you're actually it doesn't feel like you're kind of on the terrain
as much on Everest in a weird way to me.
It's like there's holes in Everest and you're going through it.
As opposed to like we're just bumping up and down and going through.
Oh, I see. I see what you're saying.
I'm not illustrating it so perfectly.
Well, you know, I don't want to I don't want to tilt it either way.
I feel like by staking claim as the guy who decided I could even be argued back.
I don't know. But I feel like I shouldn't.
I shouldn't say more. You can say as much as you want.
I'm not offended.
I keep giving points to Calico and part of it, I will admit, is a personal
of like a novelty of like this is still so fresh and new to me,
whereas like Big Thunder Mountain is just ubiquitous to me.
Like I have known it might be one of the first, if not
the first big roller coaster I ever went on.
So that's because but it's iconic.
It's like ubiquitous because you love it because it's a I'm trying right now
to divorce myself from the rides itself.
I'm trying to strip all the animatronics out of Calico.
Mine.
Ah, good point. Yes, they have nothing to do with it.
Nothing to do with it.
Yes. But OK, so I'm just thinking of that giant sort of three story view
of the whole ride without the horribly oppressed workers.
Some of them will be stripped out for being canceled.
Yeah, right. Yes, of course.
And Garner Holt will replace them with beautiful, shiny new ones.
And it's a beautiful, a massive immersive, I guess,
what I'm looking at, immense space.
But Scott is right.
It's big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
Now you do see you could see a massive scene.
That was shocking to me.
You see a massive mass of low and a massive scene from above.
It's the same. It's the same one.
Same scene.
And you're seeing it from different angles from different angles.
But this but that's what I'm saying.
Scene wise, get rid of the minor robots, because that's what's hard to do
is because there's so many robots on that ride and it's so much so
such a big part of that experience.
If I'm just looking at it, I go, wow, this is big.
This is crazy.
The rocks look a little melty, but cool.
I think the cultural cache of fake rocks does matter.
You can't divorce it physically from its impact in the world.
I think these are I think this is the world's favorite fake rock.
I could not I could not knock out.
I could not in good conscience knock out.
I think ultimately you're right.
But I it's it's it's not tough to make the decision,
but it's tough because of how much I do love the fake rocks of Calico.
I wanted it to be in the 16.
I'm going to keep this.
Scott has put in his vote.
I am locking in for Calico. Nice.
So the call is in your ball is in your court.
But I just sort of said what I thought.
I'm not totally sure.
I'm not totally sure either.
I hate it's big thunder.
All right. Fair enough.
Now, here's what I think.
We had some discussion about who was going to go up against two.
I think it's very possible that if these were different,
I think it's possible that
Calico could have knocked out Matterhorn if they were head to head.
I think that's I think I think there's that's that's a horse race for sure.
I think Calico could knocked out splash.
I do, too. Yeah.
The brackets do info.
Keep in mind, everybody, this isn't a pure list.
We did. These are these are pairs.
Right. And sometimes the pairs make strange bedfellows and people leave angry.
But that's just the way it goes.
Also, I'm sorry for the lack of jokes on the show
because just that's I'm in a different headspace right now.
It's but this I hopefully this all in and of itself.
Oh, it's Joe.
Three of us talking about this is a joke.
And we take it seriously.
We had a it was a pretty robust text thread about it.
I ran my choices by my wife as I do any important decision in my life.
This is why I also buy my wife.
I write it by your wife.
She knows what she's doing.
Very even.
I thought I thought Jason was talking about like a gallon of ice cream in a wig.
What do you think private selection?
You make a little smiley face with the frost.
Yeah. Or if she doesn't approve a frowny face.
Yeah. And that's a bad day.
She is tough, but fair.
The frowny face when she doesn't want to be eaten.
Well, sorry.
Well, that's an argument.
I do win. So.
All right. Call fan art.
Someone draw Jason marrying his ice cream wife.
And back to the.
And back to the tournament.
Who's up next?
This next round, actually, I think, you know, we're talking about interesting pairings.
This one is the opposite.
It makes very much makes sense.
Mount Prometheus from Tokyo, Disney Sea and
Krakatau from Volcano Bay at Universal Orlando.
This is the volcano centerpiece of Volcano Bay.
The clash of the volcanoes.
Clash of the volcanoes.
It makes sense to put them together.
Twenty first century pairings.
Kind of the opposite.
Tokyo, Disney Sea, widely recognized as a huge success.
Aesthetically, Volcano Bay seemed like people were optimistic about.
And people may have cooled about now.
Mike, you seem like you liked elements of this.
I have been to both.
Yeah, you are the only one.
And I do not. So it really you can speak the most to this area.
This year. So Volcano Bay, I think I talked a little bit about it a while ago.
As far as the outer rim of Volcano Bay,
that's sort of closer to a normal water park.
The rides are the slides are a little less themed.
They're fun, but it's nothing special.
I did find that the fake rock itself, and I always forget how to pronounce it.
It's Krakatau. Right.
Correct. I.
A couple, you know, Margarita type drinks in
swam out to the middle of the wave pool and just sat at the foot
of Krakatau and looked up and got pelted with water.
And just I loved it. I was so there's going to be a.
You were baptized and born in Krakatau, born, born me new.
That's how you'd say it.
So like an exhausting late period, like Neil Young album or something.
Right. Krakatau.
More. It would be more about like seeds.
He's obsessed with like seeds and the farmers and seeds.
So the song of seed would be a 2019 Neil Young album.
Yes. Yeah, exactly.
Some baby boomer 20 albums and start doing a story.
There's a story. There's actually a storyline to this album.
Yeah, it's a narrative.
So Warren's Yvonne album that he threw in the trash.
Go. Yeah. His second to last.
Never mind. Let's not put it up.
So I just sort of sat because you can get very close to this.
You can't get as close to Mount Prometheus.
You can get close, but you can't.
So you don't go into the mountain.
Well, you well, I guess that a spoiler for you.
No, I don't care. Oh, you mean the end of Disney?
See? Yeah. No, I know. There's rides in the.
Yeah. You walk inside it and it's incredible.
Well, I'm sort of inside of. Yeah.
Like the area around it, it's not the actual volcano hole.
Oh, sure. Sure.
A hole, I guess, is the technical.
But it's like a campus that
yeah, out from the peak there.
Kill me with a lava hole. I say toss me in.
Jason versus the volcano.
I'll tell you who's winning that fight.
Kill me, volcano.
I meant crack at the.
Do you you don't go into it?
You do. You do. Oh, you do. OK.
Yes, you can walk into it.
Yeah, I thought you were talking to me. OK.
Yeah, but you can walk into it.
You can talk to the spirit that lives inside of it.
It's a person remotely controlling it and it'll shoot you with water.
Is that all? Does that all affect?
Do you consider that part of the rock or is that more of an experience inside the rock?
I think you probably can't consider the spirit stuff part of the rock.
Because we're not just judging the fake rock itself, not maybe the special effects.
Although I did mention the lighting and those are sort of that sort of special effects, too.
Sure. So lighting.
Yeah. Both of these seem like they have very impressive nighttime lighting packages.
Yes, they do.
I would say just from a scope standpoint, looking at the two of them,
Mount Prometheus looks more impressive.
At night, they both look very impressive in Mount Prometheus,
you know, shoots lava out every whatever hour or something.
And as does Krakatau.
But is it like fire?
It's water, light, it's lit.
Projection. Really?
Yeah. And they both I didn't get to see the lava at Krakatau up close,
but it does erupt.
It still erupts like a volcano does.
I need to see a photo of this to make sure I I.
Oh, oh, and it glows.
Which one are you looking at?
Oof. Well, I'm seeing it glowing blue at night.
Krakatau or Krakatau.
Yeah, it looks great.
Yeah, it's so cool at night.
Wow. Yeah.
It's it's it's kind of incredible when you look at it at night.
And it does look cooler at night than Mount Prometheus,
which also looks incredible at night. OK.
I would kind of argue that it looks a little bit cooler.
But the mountains themselves in the daytime,
even though I've been up close to Krakatau, I think Mount Prometheus
probably has a little more mystique because it's set back.
So it's tough. It's a very tough call.
Krakatau has like even just in pictures or video, beautiful water,
that, you know, cascading down it.
I think that that should be said.
How do you feel about this?
Jason, your earlier argument about
that mountains don't get you anywhere, you just just you being a mountain
doesn't make you win, but these are both mountains.
Let's let's take the scale out of it.
How about just the rock, the texture and the rocks themselves?
Yeah, I mean, I don't know.
I mean, well, if we're talking about the can you draw it as an icon?
I think Mount Prometheus has a leg in that category.
Having not seen either of these in person, I don't know.
I feel like Prometheus, the reputation precedes itself.
Yeah, I mean, they're both both of them.
When you go into the parks,
because they're both basically the icons of the park.
Well, I mean, Tokyo has got more even, but but they're both incredibly impressive.
The first thing you go is, holy shit.
And I don't even think crack a toe.
The pictures do it justice,
because especially when it doesn't have anything crack a toe is.
Basically, I'm saying is like Tokyo has all of the beautiful scenery
to add to Mount Prometheus to make it look more impressive.
It's got those beautiful buildings in front of it.
It's set back.
And then there's a whole crazy like skyline, essentially, of different parts
of Tokyo, Disney, and you go, this is a beautiful picture.
Crack a toe. Unfortunately, that's it.
It's alone. It's by itself.
So it's sort of not fair because we're taking them both out and putting them alone.
I don't know. I think I think I start to edge a little closer to crack a toe,
especially and again, it's lighting and I don't know.
We're sort of allowing lighting, especially with that nighttime lighting.
I'm edging. I'm closing in closer to crack a toe is what I'm saying.
Wow. Wow. But if you look at the detail, I do think Mount Prometheus has more detail,
like the rock itself, the texture of it.
It looks more realistic.
It looks like that you see kind of the more like that it it goes from a fresher
brown to a more lava burnt black and back and.
Yeah, it's very subtly. So it's pretty incredible.
I mean, it does look like it's a whole like letter grade up
as far as detail in the rocks itself.
It also I mean, I mean, this is true for both of them.
Both of them like make the park when you hear that this park exists
or is being built and you go and there's a giant volcano. Right.
As part of it, that's when I've been telling people who don't know about Tokyo,
Disney Sea, and sadly, I do know some of those people.
I have to say it's this other Disneyland
that's told it's only in Tokyo and there's this giant volcano at the center of it.
That's like the selling point.
You show a photo of that thing. Right.
And like I said, as opposed to, you know,
fake rock lights, Disney parks of the era, you know, the Oriental Land Company
financing the park, let them go fake rock apeshit.
And for going fake rock apeshit, I have to reward them.
I'm casting my vote for Mount Prometheus.
Yeah, I'm I'm going back towards Mount Prometheus, Prometheus at this point.
But I do feel like Universal did crack a towel at disservice
because it's the only crazy impressive thing in the park.
Sure. And it is.
You know, I think the top who top who payment system, the cashless
wristwatch payment system is a fast pass system.
And then you go and click and it's like the virtual line.
90 minutes to ride one water slide.
That was the first couple of months.
So maybe they've worked it out. Maybe they've worked it out.
So it sucks because I think the photos don't do crack a towel justice.
And especially with nothing to bounce off of it,
it makes it look chintzier than it is because I truly was blown away by it.
There's a video I should have brought it out if I was really going to defend it,
that you would go, oh, my God, that looks unbelievable.
Night photos made that a much tougher choice.
Yeah, yeah, I got to stick to my guns.
But unfortunately, I know it's for crack a towel, not unfortunately in general.
Mount Prometheus just in the day rocks itself
versus other rocks Mount Prometheus has to win.
I'll go ahead and give it to Prometheus, too.
So that's, you know, unanimous that one.
You got it. Also, that there's two rides inside.
Holy shit. Yeah. I mean, the rides don't matter.
But oh, my God. Right.
How much of the park is this facility?
Yes, right. Like if there was a second ride within Radiator Springs,
how insane that would be. Of course.
And then look, there's a nice, lazy river that goes through crack a towel.
And I loved it.
And the mist falls and you kind of go under and I'm dreaming of it
in my head right now and I'm wanting to go back.
But yes, it's Mount Prometheus.
I think there's another like Calico.
I think there's another pairing where crack a towel walks away with it.
Yeah, for sure. That is not this pairing.
So that brings us to maybe another tough one.
We're we're pairing off Pandora,
the world of Pandora and the floating mountains, Pandora,
with the upcoming Black Spires of Black Spire Outpost at Star Wars Galaxy's Edge.
This one is called Where Disney's Money Has Been Going.
Are they called the Hallelujah Mountains specifically in Avatar?
No, it would be you.
I believe they are.
But I mean, not all of the fake rocks in Pandora are floating,
but some of them are.
And hey, that's points right out of the gate.
Holy shit. I watched a video about the engineering of those things.
Oh, my God. How do you make float?
I mean, it's not a totally you don't know how they did it effect,
but it's it's pretty damn impressive.
And I've been there in person.
But boy, pictures paint the picture.
Yeah, I picture.
And they are the Hallelujah Mountains.
I've confirmed. OK, great.
So just in case you want to refer to it as that, just to keep it fresh
when we're discussing now, Black Spire Outpost, the spires,
the tall things poking out.
None of us have seen this yet. Let's say that.
Yeah. Also, in the back story, we've recently learned
that it is petrified wood, which is technically eventually
if wood petrifies enough, it becomes rock.
Oh, I believe that's correct.
Is that right? That is right.
Yes, they're boy. That hurts it. It's wood.
Oh, no, it's fake wood.
It was tall trees that died.
So that is a strike against it.
Oh, shit. But it's on its way to rock.
And I bet part of it, at least the percentage is rock in canon.
Fuck that. I feel betrayed.
I'm I'm giving it to Pandora right now.
I don't want no trees hanging around.
I mean, I lose his points, too, because, yeah, I haven't seen it.
Black Spire Outpost and
don't know what the nighttime lighting package is going to be like Pandora
at night. Beautiful, beautiful trees trying to sneak in there.
This is bullshit. I feel duped.
Is that true of all of it, though?
Some of it has to be like there's a cliff wall outside of
the fires itself are the ones that are the there are.
I mean, there are fake rocks here.
Yeah. And they see like that are this.
This land looks unbelievably impressive.
And seeing these things go up in the back of Disneyland
and watching them rise from that parking structure has been a thrill.
And I like with both of these avatar and Star Wars.
I'm excited that fake rocks are the future.
When Disney puts a big new facility
based on an exciting property into their parks, fake rocks got to be there.
And I love seeing them from the back.
I love that we get to drive through and see the like admire that
that framework right at Washington.
I like seeing them from my beloved Mark Twain.
And I pointed this out last time I was there.
Mention it to you guys that they really do blend nicely with the rocks
that you see from the boat, the rocks, big thunder.
Well, no wonder the train tracks right under the train tracks like similar rocks.
Everything looks copacetic.
They need to get a few more trees in there, but they might just need to grow.
But it's like it's not jarring.
It's not a jarring skyline.
Those new rocks are great.
Yeah. That's the transitional rocks.
I really. Yeah.
Yeah. If those if those count, if those are those separate,
should we have been breaking this down more?
We should have broken it down more.
I don't know that the transitional ones do, because I think of them
more as the train track rocks.
Like they're underneath those.
They their own category.
Should we bump something else and put in the transitional rock?
No, we're too too far into it.
I don't know. I think we can do whatever we want.
That's a vote between us of what's left.
No, I don't think so.
Jason's putting his foot down. Jason's trying to put his foot down.
Wait, what do you think, Mike?
It's your OK.
Let me just so I'm clear on what this proposition is.
We would we would put just the rocks outside of Star Wars land.
The transition from frontier land to fantasy land.
That's what you're proposing.
That's not even the ones I'm talking about.
We're talking about the ones along the train.
The ones underneath the train tracks.
When you go along the river by like the Indian village.
Oh, I see. OK, OK. Yeah.
Those are great fake rocks right by where the beaver is gnawing at the
whatever post. Yeah.
I think the ones you're talking about, I would need to see
the cinematic transition of walking by those and then through the portal
into the land to make a judgment.
Yeah. Thunder trail.
Well, but a judgment, we don't need to go through the rocks.
We're just talking about the rocks that are on the one side.
That are there already along the big thunder trail.
You know, that big, like that big, crazy new rock pops out.
So you can't like peer over.
If you said that an entire category of rock encompasses both of these,
the new rocks that have been put in to transition you into Galaxy's Edge.
And those are different than galaxies.
Yeah, they're transitional rocks.
They you take a big thunder rock and then you just sort of more for a little bit
into a galaxy's edge rock.
But they're in the middle.
They're trying to get you off.
They're trying to get you to what is there a drug that transitions
you off heroin or something?
I'm trying to make a good.
It's like grape juice or something. Yeah.
OK, so well, if we're going to replace anything,
I think we should knock out the Black Spires because we know there would now.
Oh, so we're changing transitional rocks.
I think we should change this round because I like the last few rounds.
Well, we're not going to we're not going to get.
Oh, I see what you're saying. OK. Yeah.
This is too confusing now.
I've been throwing a wrench.
I don't know if I'd find support in this.
I just wanted to make sure I was rocks.
I'll say I'll put the river rocks and the big new rocks
as the rocks because we have all experienced those.
Forget about the Black Spires.
These are the Star Wars rocks now.
Oh, we changed the definition of what the Star Wars are.
The Galaxy's Edge rocks are all right.
It's the one we've actually gotten to enjoy because we have had a number of things
that none of us have sampled before. Sure.
Sure. Only Mike has sampled before. I see.
So, OK. Wow.
Well, we have re we've redistricted some of the rocks.
We've changed the definition. It's not the Black Spires.
It's the it's the existing Star Wars Galaxy's Edge rocks.
But they are up against a pretty even with that.
They're up against a pretty tough competitor.
They're against floating rocks against floating rocks.
I already none of this changes my vote.
I wanted to be bold and say it right away. It's Pandora.
I'm going to go with Pandora, too. All right.
How would it not be the Hallelujah Mountains?
I mean, we don't even know what you would even say.
Oh, they're incredible.
Mountain Savaco.
We wrote we wrote smart park that they're in. Great.
This next round, very excited for
Mythos Restaurant at Island to Adventure versus Mount Mayday,
the icon of Typhoon Lagoon.
These are kind of the dark horses.
These are the dark horses.
And I was going to say, Mythos is my dark horse.
This is my dark horse.
And I as we were figuring out what to eliminate,
I was like, if anyone says Mythos, I'm going to lose my fucking mind.
I also I take it back when I said earlier, this is a character.
Yep. That's the character that's left.
And you know what?
I we hey, this is a long podcast.
I Jason, your enthusiasm sold me right away. Mythos.
Yeah. I'm not even going to talk about it.
This has a character. The character's mouth is a waterfall.
This adds to the skyline of Islands of Adventure.
When you get to the port of the entry, you see Jurassic Park straight ahead.
And then you look to your right, you see this massive fake rock structure
that has no right to be as good as it is in a forgotten land.
The land they almost was an afterthought Typhoon Lagoon.
You see a mountain. It is fake rocks.
But you see the boat. First of all, it's the boat.
The boat takes it. And you can't
you can't give it to rocks
because of what they're supporting.
It's about the rocks, not what's on top of the rocks. Exactly.
So that's two for Mythos. Yes.
I'll mythos as well.
Well, mythos restores quick.
I mean, and we and you know, when we got a we got like a Zeus
barfing water that's not vote for that.
I actually remember being excited that when I found out Harry Potter was going in,
I was like, Oh, does that mean they're taking out that restaurant?
I kind of like that restaurant.
And isn't it cool on the inside to very cool on the inside?
I honestly think that Universal should go back to the drug,
should take more inspiration for their food program from like Mythos
and on Dark Horse and so on, right?
Lombards over the original universal similar menu to mythos.
They might even have the same menu nowadays.
But it's like make more of the food like these two places.
Well, they're like the some of the only quality in Universal Florida,
which is it's tough food in those parts.
It's tough. Yeah, these tough.
So all right.
Mythos has a tough road ahead of it because mythos is going up against.
This is I keep calling this the crowd pleaser conference.
Like these are big heavy hitters.
This last, last round of the first last round of the first 16.
And they are the rocks
is part of the Hogwarts campus in the Wizarding World of Harry Potter
and Radiator Springs,
AKA Ornament Valley.
That's maybe what you technically should, AKA the Cadillac Range.
I don't know what you maybe the whole thing you would call Ornament Valley.
I think it's too pretentious it up because Radiator Springs
really is the city leading up to it.
And I like that we have a list that has names you don't know,
like Mount Apu Taku and Mount Prometheus, you know, maybe no offense.
So I'm going to say as this proceeds, I kind of want to call it Ornament Valley.
All right. Sure. Yeah.
I'm going to toss my hat in the ring for Ornament Valley.
Beautiful. Another scale bump looks great.
Amazing in the day. Amazing at night.
Two separate entrances, two separate like visual experiences,
whether you come around the corner from Flo's or whether you come from
the Pacific War food court.
That's an incredible view.
That is a fantastic view.
And didn't learn about until like the second or third time I was there.
I was like, wait, this is the better way to come,
not through the amazing town, through the back door.
There is no this round. There's no question.
I think I advocated at Hogwarts, not at Hogwarts, not even be in this tournament.
I've been thinking about it a lot.
Actually, this is one of the choices that I've been struggling with.
Jason, when we were saying, do we just put a second round of Star Wars in?
That's what I wanted to bump.
I think we maybe made a little mistake here.
I think those rocks are good. They're very good.
I have no problem with the rocks.
But as the Typhoon Lagoon rule, it's about the rocks,
not what the rocks are supporting.
That's right. I think this was one where it's like, well,
if we didn't talk about some Harry Potter rocks, we were going to hear about it.
I disagree with that. Who was going to be there?
I don't know.
If you're going to be there to write a letter.
Who out there listening right now, if we hadn't mentioned the Hogwarts rocks.
I mean, there's a lot of rock.
There's more rock in that than Splash Mountain.
Yes, but it's not the quantity of rocks we're talking about.
But they're good rocks.
We're not talking quantity. They're good rocks.
They are, Jason, they're all good rocks.
You don't get in the final 16 if it's not good rocks.
Yeah, you're not making it here.
I'm just saying this is there's no contest to this.
This thing is incredible.
I think this is this also an unfortunate.
I think it's possible that Hogwarts.
I was thinking about proposing a
a supporting rocks category in which Hogwarts goes up against Mount Mayday.
And then one of them is still in the race.
But that's not the case.
I don't think they would.
I don't think either of them had what it takes to get into the final four.
I agree. Can I say what?
So we've made it through the 16 and we'll we'll recap what we're left with.
But let's while we're talking about what didn't make it, here's what's beating me up.
I think that maybe Hogwarts should have been out.
Maybe maybe even Star Wars should have been out because we don't know enough.
Maybe even Seven Dwarfs.
I might have bumped Hogwarts or Seven Dwarfs in order to put in
having a lot of regrets about not putting in Catastrophe Canyon.
I'm feeling bad about Catastrophe Canyon.
I guess ultimately, Catastrophe Canyon, which was like part of the MGM
studio's tram tour, their their attempt to do a universal style thing
where everything goes awry and there's explosions.
And then we show you that it was all just an illusion.
The I Survived podcast, the ride,
catchphrase at the end of the shirt that we made of it is based on Catastrophe Canyon.
That is that's neither here nor there.
We'll talk about Catastrophe Canyon one day.
But I you know what? I think these I think these guys got squeezed.
I think maybe they deserve to be in the 16.
But well, they are the first not really argued.
I put Kong Skull Island in there, too.
We that's right. We were going back and forth.
No character squeezed to no character character.
Better than there's a monkey within the then there's a monkey.
Yeah. But it's not scope always.
Yeah. Yeah. I think most of that experience, it's kind of that little courtyard.
Right. Yeah. It's not like I think that if we put that in, that is less
fake rocks than anything else in the competition.
I think I think mass is important.
Scott, in the very initial list, you put down one that I was not at all familiar
with and had to look up and I thought was very impressive.
Yeah. And it's in Fantasia land in Europe and it's called Germany.
In Germany. Yeah. And it's Tehran.
Yeah. Tehran, I think you pronounce it very striking, very interesting looking
Google image. This one, Gang Tehran is spelled T.A.
R.O.N. Fantasia land is spelled with a P.H.
This is pretty cool.
I think if we like were from there had been there, maybe we would have put this in.
But this is a steel roller coaster that kind of twists around real like craggy,
very Skull Island rocks and a giant wall of them.
And it looks like a bunch of bullets stacked up.
It's pretty aggressive and scary.
I think you got to get you got to dock points for that.
It's kind of a roller coaster that's just next to the rocks.
The they aren't really related.
It's not embedded into the experience.
But yeah, there's a little like foreign dark horse that,
you know, might have made a final 17, but not a final 16. Yeah.
Anything else you guys regret didn't make it?
We talked about the rocks in the Little Mermaid attraction in Orlando.
Yeah, that's that may be pretty.
I think that is more interesting than than Kong Skull Island.
I agree. You're opening it up more.
I thought we were also discussing.
Does anything in the Indiana Jones adventure count as a fake rock?
Are the ruins fake rocks?
Is Mara in the main scene of fake rock?
She's well, she is rock, right?
No, she isn't. She metal.
I guess she is metal.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Or like gold or something.
Yeah, the original the initial one.
But when you will the main reveal of
and the one that shoots the bridge.
Oh, yeah, that's a big fake rock.
Yeah. Does that count?
Should that have been in there?
I mean, I think we were going a lot on the outsides of these things.
And I think that might hurt
Cast catastrophe Canyon in my book is that you so quickly go around the corner
and see the iron work holding up the fake rocks.
But that's a big fake rock here.
I mean, that of all of these, that one, I guess maybe should have been.
Yeah. The Mara fake rock inside of the temple.
Maybe so.
But I don't think anything that we just discussed would have made it.
I don't think I don't think any of it would have made it into the eight.
Yeah. Which I guess we can move into.
And also let us know if we missed anything, if we eliminated your favorite
fake rock or didn't even put it in the final 16.
Let us know at hashtag PTR FRF for I'm getting better at saying it as we go on.
It's a two, three hundred empire type.
You dug this grave and now you get to lie in it.
F.R. for fat crap.
OK, so just to run down the full list, the eight that are left, Matterhorn,
Splash Mountain, Mount Apu, Taku, Big Thunder Mountain, Mount Prometheus,
the world of Pandora, the hallelujah mountains.
The hallelujah mountains. Great.
Let's be we got to be proper.
Hallelujah Mountains, Mythos restaurant and ornament valley.
So back to the beginning, Matterhorn V.
Splash Mountain.
Got to give it to Matterhorn.
You go. We don't have to discuss all of these.
It's Matterhorn.
Everything that we said that made me your initial argument, Jason,
now applies. Now I feel it.
And you're going up against Matterhorn.
It's that's that's an icon, an icon of the L.A.
skyline. You drive by it on the five.
If you if you're going somewhere on the five and you can't go to Disneyland,
that's the little taste that you get.
You get to see that that mountain from the freeway. Absolutely.
It's it's so exciting.
You see it in the Randy Newman video.
I love the L.A.
It's it's a part that tugs at the heartstrings for me.
It's got to be. But you're I'm sorry to just pounce on and not
let you know that's OK to two makes two wins.
So what's your vote? What I say is irrelevant.
I'm really thinking about it.
I probably go matter on, though, because I think if you strip away
the fun stuff of Splash Mountain, Matterhorn wins just again,
is all the reasons you said.
So I have to go matterhorn. Yep. Yeah.
The original holding firm
takes us into Big Thunder Mountain after talking.
Yeah. All right.
Oh, sure. This is going to wrap up.
Hey, quicker. What?
Do you have an argument against it?
I mean, I think it's another interesting comparison of old versus new.
I think we should, you know, embrace change, embrace the future.
One might even say seize the future.
And so maybe we should really consider Mount Apu Taku.
Let me consider it.
You know, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
OK, and there's the bit. All right.
What's your vote, though?
If anybody's keeping track of the of the tally.
I think the P.A.
is going to be a good one.
I don't know. I don't know on this one.
Really? You would vote for Mount.
What's a very, very impressed amount?
To Jason's credit and point, it is massive.
It's insane. It's a crazy facility.
And I think if we'd seen it and if we were more familiar with it prior,
I mean, look it up. It feels like it's a little bit more of a
a little bit more of a
more familiar with it prior.
I mean, look it up. It feels it's almost going to feel silly.
If you looked at that and said it was eliminated from a fake rock competition.
Yeah. How could that be the case next to these puny
Big Thunder mole hills?
That being said, here's where I really go to the silhouette.
A big thunder iconic.
Ultimately, Mount Apu Taku is a big, you know, it's a big it's a big wall.
It's a big cliff. It's a very good one.
It's an incredibly good one.
But hey, it's Big Thunder Mountain we're talking about.
Yeah, that's true.
Should we have included the aggro crag from?
Oh, yeah.
Should should the aggro crag?
I know it was it was technically on Universal Studios property.
Yeah, we should replace.
Let's see, mythos with I'm going to kick your ass.
Let's well, unfortunately, the aggregate was not open to the public.
It was only open to snooty good at sports kids.
I wanted to.
Scott was excluded.
I was trying to climb with audiences. Yeah.
Dreamed of climbing that.
As opposed to mythos, open to the public and serving delicious meals on the daily.
Yeah. But that's not where we're at right now.
We're at Mount Prometheus versus the Hallelujah Mountains.
This is really tough, because if this was the final two, you'd go.
That makes sense.
But we're way ahead of it.
Oof. I'll let somebody else talk.
I don't think I can.
I mean, OK, Mount Prometheus is it is a very incredible realistic,
I would say, too. I haven't seen too many mountains in my life in person.
But it is that realism.
It's it's obviously a little stylized and they have the lighting stuff is amazing
and exploring it is amazing.
But but is it more impressive to
recreate the realistic or make the fantastical look realistic?
That's what I'm trying to grapple with right here.
Yeah. I will say, is the effect of the mountains
as incredible as you'd want it to be?
Maybe not of the of the flying of the of the mountains.
And you who's been you only you've been and I only I've been to, yeah,
Pandora as well to see the Hallelujah Mountains in person.
Have you written on the back of the mighty Akron?
The mighty Akron? Yeah, of course.
OK, great. Yes.
Just check it. I forget.
I tamed the beast. You tamed it.
The banshee. You guys been to the Grand Canyon?
You've been to a real no, never.
No, no, no, no, no.
I have been to the Petrified Forest National Park.
Mm hmm. Oh, yeah.
That's a well, is there any sort of like simulator ride at the Grand Canyon?
You could also go on that could be there's like a reason for me to go.
There is. Well, there's a helicopter and you could buy a ticket from
that convenience store in Vegas that is covered in fake rocks
right next to the MGM.
Now I'm sold. It looks like a fake.
It's like it's like where you it's where you buy expensive waters
outside casinos and like novelty mugs that say like sluts party hard in Vegas.
And and it looks like the Grand Canyon.
So so, you know, in that pairing, Grand Canyon versus
Casino Mini Mart that looks like the Grand Canyon.
We're giving it to the casino mini mart. Yeah, for sure.
Now, Scott's just looking at things in the room because I'm drinking from a swell
official swell sluts party hard in Vegas.
Water bottle here. I thought I was inventing.
So you're right. I was. Yeah.
Yeah. Usually come in and the slut swag. Yeah.
You can't you got to make it clear. You love sluts. Yeah.
So back to the back to the world of.
I mean, I've only visited these places in my dreams and flights of whimsy.
So, yeah, like as far as just the presentation of Mount Prometheus
and any any angle you look at it, whether you're back by.
I can't remember if you can completely see it when you're in Cape Cod
with Duffy and friends, but you can see it in many different points of Tokyo,
Disney, and it feels like so many of those places were curated perfectly
to make it look like that amazing radiator springs view.
The second entrance to Cars Land.
Also, I'll second you there, having not been there.
When you Google image Mount Prometheus, Disney, see
every photo is different as opposed to I think that does hurt like crack a towel
that you're looking at a similar view over and over again.
And that this encompasses like so many different vantage points
can be your Mount Prometheus. Yes.
And that's a thing I probably said on the episode about Tokyo, Disney,
where it's like, oh, every single place you're standing is like
the second entrance to Cars Land.
God damn. Like, like there's so many times you go, oh, my God, look at this view.
And then you're just standing on exactly the opposite.
You're like, oh, my God, look at that.
Like you start seeing things in different contexts as we record this.
I'm really close to going. So I'm flicking.
Yeah, that that cars I view.
Yeah, but you're just like you'll be in Cape Cod and then you'll be like,
look at New York over there and you'll be like, wow, it's beautiful.
Like, it's unbelievable.
Then you'll be like down the New York street and you'll see like the big boat
and you'll be like, oh, my God, like everything is like feels so perfectly
designed to make you go, whoa, especially at night.
It seems like you spend.
Does this sound like you haven't been there?
Does this seem accurate about Disney?
See that it's like looking at other Disney theme parks,
but you have glasses now, so you have perfect 20, 20 vision.
You see all these details you could never see before.
That's that. That does make sense to me because I don't think
this is too much of a spoiler, but going through just the New York section,
the amount of little things you notice and just like
an imagineer spent what feels like a day on a little poster
with a bunch of jokes and a bunch of silly crap.
And I'm sure I got we saw like five percent of it.
Geez. Like you just go like, hey, look at this billboard.
Or you write the script for that Pinkerton beating up a union striker.
Right. There's a joke.
There's a joke about like there's a there's a little like warning sign.
I think I think I believe I have this right for train sickness
and warning you about train sickness.
And it's just a goof.
It's just a silly little thing.
Some imagineers docked up to make like an old time like warning thing,
warning sign. But there's just full of stuff like that.
That might be real when trains were still invention.
But there's some funny there's funny stuff.
And if that and I'm sure people have gotten sick on a train before.
But if indeed it is a thing, they were having fun with it like they
you can just feel it.
If you feel like a voice, you can feel like their voices in the land.
And especially like New York land.
So I got to stop and read every sign.
Well, that's why. Yeah. Trouble.
You got to do whatever you're doing days wise.
And we don't know how many days.
No. Yeah. Big reveal.
Come on. You got to double it, I think.
So if you decide to do four, now you're doing eight.
God. I texted Aaron before this and she agreed with me.
So she has already done it.
Oh, no. We all see.
Mike also runs his decisions by. Yeah.
Guys, so you're not wrong.
Aaron runs her decisions by Mike.
So basically, Mike is running all of our lives.
And I ask Jason's ice cream wife to
give me a final like declaration on any of these decisions,
which means Mike's just constantly helping ice cream escape from my house.
So I have a real parasitic relationship with him.
You don't even like sweets.
Mike just tricked you into liking it for his amusement.
He tricked me into painting that white picket fence he got.
Still mad about that. He said it was fun.
It is fun. I also there's another fence I do have outside here
that's actually a little bit more of a fun fence to paint.
If you wouldn't mind.
I just want you to try it out.
But this one's fun.
This was more fun than the other one.
All right. That one was a bummer.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
OK, put your stuff down and we'll finish this while you go and.
OK, well, I'll.
Fun thing for me.
Give me give me the other recorder.
I'll do a second gate episode about painting the fence. OK.
This is more fun than any ride.
So let me dive in. It's like.
Hold on. Hold on.
Boy, I don't think I'm not exactly sure where it's going.
So Tokyo Disney.
I mean, every spot you see it.
Beautiful. Perfect.
However, if we're taking the mountain out itself
and comparing it to the fake rocks.
So you take the fake rocks out and compare it to the other fake rocks.
These in these rocks in Pandora are floating.
You don't see them anywhere else.
They're cool.
They they're they certainly are realistic.
But this there's no fake rocks anywhere
that are above your head like this, that if you're at the right angle are floating.
I think just purely for that fact and for the innovation
and for how unique they are, they beat Mount Prometheus.
Jason, whatever you have to say, just take take your time,
because I need to I need to like think about this for another second.
If you have any if you have any thoughts, because I'm like, this is a really tough one.
I mean, I think it is unique.
I, you know, to peel back the curtain a little bit, the support beams
for holding up those fake rocks are like built into the giant vines
sort of connecting them all,
which is like, yeah, they really had to think outside of the box.
James Cameron is very high standards, high expectations.
So building these fake rocks, they were kind of dealing with that.
Although that said, the Oriental Land Company also very high expectations.
The Japanese people are very high expectations for their Disney parks.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, both are real hypothetical for me, but that floating
might be the thing that tips it.
And I also haven't seen Avatar.
I don't think I've ever finished a Jules Verne book.
I think it's very funny that there's a whole generation of imagineers
who are just tickled pink by Jules Verne, like
well after he was dead.
Once and once an artist dies, you have to disavow their work forever.
They're dead. And so is there.
But I think specific
idiosyncratic to Jules Verne that he was like he was an originator of sci fi.
But back then, like sci fi, everyone was still wearing high starched collars
and four different jackets at a time.
But everyone's still amazed of like he thought he had the idea to
shoot a gun at the moon.
Yeah, that is cool.
That is cool.
That's cool.
You know, does James Cameron have that sort of thing?
So you're now you're comparing Cameron to Verne,
which is cool. Cameron might be our Jules Verne.
He could be. I mean, and he actually he has these ideas.
And then sometimes he just goes and does them like by wetting a tiny can
to the bottom of the sea.
He has his own Jules Verne submarine.
Yeah. So we're going to be like there's going to be theme park attractions
in 100 years where some actors playing.
Why, I'm James Cameron.
I know you're going to say there's 100 years there'll be podcaster attractions.
It's like, oh, certainly, yes.
Yeah. You'll be able to ride our logo.
It'll be a functional ride. Yes.
Yeah, I don't know.
This is so, so close this round.
This may not be the closest round, but we're stuck on it and avoiding.
I think we need to keep moving.
And I think Mike has convinced me with that floating argument.
So I'm going to lock in for Pandora.
Yeah. I mean, I can't.
I think this is a little
I think it's a little insane that we're getting to the end.
And if Mount Prometheus and Expedition Everest are not
this they have not made, I think that's bizarre.
But you know what your initial it's Mount it's rocks, not mountains,
Jason, which I think has been a lot of nice sayings
that have come out of this.
Sure. It's rocks, not mountains.
It's about the it's about the rocks, not what the rocks are supporting.
Yeah. So I have to
I have to I have to agree with this philosophy.
And yeah, just like literally the because like,
I don't know.
Maybe maybe maybe you have to call them different classifications in a way of
is a volcano a rock?
I guess so. I guess these are like several.
These are like more distinctly a bunch of big rocks.
Yeah. And the rocks are instantly iconic.
They instantly take you to a place.
It's a place that I want to go, even though I don't like the Avatar film
too much. But I would like to go there.
I'd like to see that rock.
I just quietly whispering.
That's weird.
It's very funny.
So am I the first maybe to have the opinion
that Avatar is not the finest film in the history of man?
I mean, everyone has an opinion about it.
I sit down and watch that movie one of these days.
Have you not ever watched?
You know what? I've seen a lot of clips on on in-store
demo TVs and every I feel like every time I fly now,
it's an option to watch on my iPad.
And I just never want to make the whatever three hour commitment or whatever.
And I know that it's not.
It's so funny to see it that way.
But Avatar, that's not a movie.
We do have Repertory Cinema.
We have the new Bev and the downtown independent.
We do have places that play
older movies, but you don't see Avatar on that circuit very much.
So I don't know. I'm kind of stuck.
I think I just need to watch it on my normal 30 inch TV at some point,
if I'm ever going to see it.
That is how I ended up seeing it. Yeah.
People who saw it in the perfect clarity are probably angry at this point.
But hey, don't tell me what conditions I need to see a movie.
And it's also like I remember to think and like, what the fuck is going on?
It's the height of the recession.
And everyone's like, you got to pay the twenty five dollars to see it in IMAX,
but three DI Max.
And it's like, are you out of your fucking mind?
Were you really upset about that?
It was weird.
It did seem like an out of like it seemed out of step with the culture
at the time that you had to pay thirty dollars to see.
You have to see this movie anyway.
How's the job hunt coming? Like this is not something.
I mean, I was not making any money in 2009.
But I wasn't.
I was like, oh, the filmmaker said it would be good to do it in the way
he made the movie.
It wasn't like, what a disgusting.
Says like that is also a thing that every filmmaker says, like,
well, you should see it in the theater.
It's like, yeah, no shit. It's a movie.
Like, I know you were so bothered by like Peter Jackson
telling you to see something in like a different frame rate.
Does he say that?
I don't have it was shot in what's what's the double forty eight.
Yeah, yeah.
I did see that in his frame rate.
And I mean, those were Peter.
You'll listen to Peter Jackson, but not James Cameron.
I don't know that you had an option.
And there was a resumption.
The economy was booming at that time.
That is true. I did see all the hobbits.
My family likes Tolkien.
So that was I did see.
I have seen all of those during the recession.
You only went to you only did Nickelodeon's.
You only went and all right into.
I watched a great movie about a guy doing the wash.
Maybe it was also the added caveat of like, if if if you can't see it
that way, don't see it at all.
And it's like, well, how's the script and how's the acting?
Not a lot of people coming in hot for like, oh, the story is really good.
The script's really good. The acting is really good.
The song and the credits is much better than My Heart Will Go On.
But you'd only know that if you heard it in the movie theater,
if you did it on your on your iPod, you'd probably think it was worse.
But you're wrong. The song is better.
The artist is an artist I can name.
Yeah, there's like that's something.
I mean, that's it. I kind of agreed with.
I do think that is a very funny clip of David Lynch going like,
you got to be a fucking idiot if you're going to watch a movie on your phone.
And like, that's pretty funny.
It seems like you just want it's coming from the right guy or girl.
Maybe I did you see the hateful eight road show version?
Did I? I saw it at the dome at the Arclight Dome.
Was there like a road show?
Sure was the overture and the intermission in it.
And did you get a book like a book?
I know. I don't think I saw that. I'm already tired.
We I mean, I have we saw it in Burbank here a couple of years ago with the full
intermission and that was like a night at the theater.
I know it was fun.
Mm hmm. I mean, I do have the movie bill for Mission Impossible
Fallout. We got a program. We saw that.
We saw that.
Hardly. Yes. Christopher McCrory demand.
We see that in a certain.
No, no, no. We volunteered to see it in both IMAX and 40 and 40.
Yeah. Madness. Yeah.
All right. We'll see. We'll end up spending.
We'll all end up spending it like personally.
Two hundred and two dollars on the next Avatar.
Oh, yeah, for sure. There's going to be like only one theater that is up
to the standards of James Cameron.
Well, we got to figure out who's bearing those seeds.
Or who's in the water.
James Cameron and Neil Young both love seeds.
For kind of thing about that.
Neil Young should do a song.
He's our new Jules Verne and our new Neil Young.
Yeah, that'd be great if there was like a credit song for Avatar
and Neil Young song about seeds, but he still tries to squeeze an anti
Monsanto here. Oh, yeah.
The Monsanto years is one of his new album, newer albums.
Really? I saw it bad.
George Bush saw it. He just did the song. Let's impeach the president.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. He he is.
I saw him a couple of years ago and it was at the forum. This real quick.
He came out. He played after the gold rush, which is maybe top
10 songs in my mind of all time.
He played Old Man.
He played, I think maybe, oh, love can break your heart.
No, maybe not that one.
He played like five classics sounded amazing.
Just him and the piano, him and the guitar.
And then all of a sudden he had theatrics
and people in hazmat suits came out Starbucks.
Doesn't he have like a Starbucks? He might make you go.
That sounds crazy. But go to hell, Starbucks.
Yeah. He then had theatrics and people came out in hazmat suits
and like sprayed down the stage and it was an environmental message.
And then he did a bit where like there was some law about like not being able
to like distribute seeds in California.
He's like, so we're going to be distributing seeds here tonight.
And then like people came into the audience with like seeds.
And I was like, what the hell is this?
Whoa. People with baskets.
It was the embarking for Neil, especially you.
You don't think of as like a theatrical guy always just looks like shit.
Are they part of the crew or they like TaskRabbit people?
The seed people? No, I'm not sure if he was doing this at every stop.
Who are the seed people? Yeah. What can we learn from them?
But Neil, yeah, he did some theme park theatrics in the middle of this concert.
Well, what did you do with your seeds? I didn't get any seeds.
I was in the pit and it was mostly up in the seat.
People with the seats.
OK, because it was harder for a person to go through the pit, probably.
Oh, sure. All right.
So let's close out.
I feel like this is going to be another fast one as much as I stand for universal
mythos versus ornament valley.
Yeah, I can't. Yeah.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm glad I'm really glad mythos made it.
Yeah, I am, too. But I think we have.
I think we have a really good final four.
I don't know.
In the final four, no universal entries, all domestic.
You didn't make they they need to step up the fake rock.
I think that is the biggest thing they need to do.
We'll see what happens in that fantastic worlds or maybe not,
depending on what the lawyers say.
Fantastic World's Park.
Are there any prominent rocks in Nintendo like will Donkey Kong have good rocks,
even though they're like our two blocks?
Potentially. If they make the rumor was they were going to like demolish
and maybe mythos to make Zelda.
Right. Isn't that the rumor?
Or no, no, no, no, no, no.
I think they would probably demolish the side.
Yes. Sorry. It's over by there.
Not in the front of the park. OK.
Yeah. So that's the rumor.
So Zelda might have some great, great fake rocks if they do a full high rule area.
I hope so.
And especially Universal Hollywood could use some better fake rocks.
Yeah, but that's very lacking in them. We'll see.
But with the but we oh my God, I think this is a great pairing
because it's kind of like traditional and original and yeah,
old school imaginary versus new school.
You know, I could not have planned this better.
We ended up in a great place.
Just to say it, we will now be figuring out Matterhorn versus Big Thunder Mountain
and Hallelujah Mountains versus Ornament Valley.
That is pretty wild because, yeah, Hallelujah and Ornament Valley.
Those are the two biggest, newest lands, themed lands
that Disney has built domestically.
And I like that old like like classic
has to face off against classic and newest face off against new
because one might trump the other just by being new.
Yes, right. But it's but there will then be a showdown between old and new.
I really like this.
All right. So two classics here,
two titans of the Disneyland skyline.
And I will say it is a boy like looking, looking out from the parking
garage these days of now of the black spires, be they lyre trees or not.
I'm being able to see Splash and Matterhorn and Big Thunder.
It's just so that the mountain range is becoming more robust.
Yeah, it is. It's great.
I'm very fond of both of these.
And it's hard to make a decision where you you knock out one of them.
OK, I've got an argument that I don't think has come up yet
that might be able to help turn it.
What do you guys think it's easier to do when it comes to fake rocks?
Paint them gray or paint them earth tone like orangey brown earth tone?
Because that's a big deciding.
There's a big distinction between these two.
My knee jerk is orangey earth.
But why and why would gray be to you mean like
simulating snow?
What do you think?
Well, no, because I think the rocks are more more gray kind of rocks and the
at the Matterhorn and Big Thunder is more orangey
like in the National Park kind of canyons and stuff.
Why would one be harder?
I guess my question is just do you think one looks better?
Was one than the other? OK, it comes down to that.
I think a lot of what's on our list has been more earth tone.
And for some reason, I think it's a little more difficult to to capture.
I think there's more like
subtlety texture in the more the earth tone range.
Matterhorn, I don't think the word kitsch has come up yet,
but Matterhorn has kitsch.
You think so? Is that a good thing or bad thing?
I think it's a good thing.
I like it. I mean, it's it's everywhere in the shit we like.
Kitsch is everywhere.
And I will say that that is it's a kitschier look than all the other things,
I think, on this list, maybe on the whole on almost all of the original 16.
Yeah.
Let me say this is very difficult.
I used to you go ahead.
Well, let me say a couple nice things about the about the Matterhorn.
Hey, it's the only it's the only one of these
one only one of these fake rocks where there are real rock climbers.
That's that's true.
That's not a thing about it.
But I think it's what a nice little like,
I don't know what a nice tribute to it. A treat.
And then that it's it's realistic enough that
people wanted to climb it like it was real.
Remember back when the sky the skyway went through it also?
Oh, yeah. Before either of our times,
to be able to come out here.
But man, I always loved those kind of sky buckets.
Correct. OK, here, correct me if I'm wrong.
But Big Thunder Mountain Railroad is the pinnacle of a certain type of theme park rock.
It doesn't get any better than that.
Like at the like we've seen that we've seen it at nots.
We've seen it in other parks.
We've seen it in other Disney parks.
But it's sort of it's the it's iconic.
It's obviously a little whimsical, like some of the different, you know, whatever we saw.
What did you say about the plops, the different plops?
I said they were like poops. Yeah.
So they're like a big stack of turds.
I think for me, just because it seems perfect,
I guess I can't divorce completely the ride from my mind,
because I think we called the ride perfect.
But I think probably of this type of rock, it's the perfect version of it.
So for my decision for being the pinnacle of this type of fake rock,
I think I know Big Thunder Mountain is my choice.
I'm going to throw a thing out, which is like
I what holds up when you get when you get up close,
you know, we haven't talked about is touching these rocks.
OK, that's all of them.
Can you touch? And it's fun to touch them.
It's fun whether you're a kid or a grownup, feel that that scaly texture.
Some of them, some fake rocks, I think you touch and you feel the more
that they are metal, you feel the fakeness.
They certainly none of them feel like real rocks, because those would be
those would be dusty.
Those would have, you know, more of a coating.
And they don't they don't have that.
But just when you think about that cue at Big Thunder,
how it's not just what what rises up and forms the Big Thunder skyline.
It's also that you're winding around and into that town
and running your hand along all of those.
Right. And if you like that, every every one of them has has character.
If you know, it's weird as saying we're doing fake rocks.
But these are some of these things are roller coasters with many rocks.
And some of them are one giant rock.
It's a little weird to quantify.
But I think if we're grouping by attraction, there's so many unique,
specific, fake rocks.
Yeah. That's big thunder. Yep.
And I would also say.
I don't know.
I'm sure there's like a different, interesting way to make a big thunder.
I'm sure some new, young, innovative, innovative, innovating mind
could come in and prove to me that this is a better way.
And these are cooler fake rocks.
I don't know. I can't imagine that.
I can imagine the kitschy, better 2019 version of the Matterhorn.
I can imagine a cartoonish mountain like that for the year 2019.
It's not the pinnacle in my mind of kitschy mountains.
I think you could do it better.
I know part of it is just because it's old.
That's fun. And that's kitschy.
But I could see a version that improves on the Matterhorn
and keeps its cartoonish elements.
Is it possible that within this and this might
there's a phrase that I should I should throw in.
Is it possible that within our decision making that there is a Baxter bias?
I think that's definitely in play.
Everybody, people listening know how we feel about Tony Baxter and his baby.
I listened to at 2 a.m. last night, just an old season pass episode,
I think it was a part five interview with Tony Baxter
just because I needed to go to sleep and I needed a pleasant voice.
And I just wanted to hear him like describe like the Sleeping Beauty
ride that didn't get built or.
Yeah, no good voice. That's true.
His philosophy about lands and rides.
And he wins the voice competition. Yes, he does.
But like, does does our mythologizing of him color you of the actual?
And are we?
Well, how is your vote going to go?
I don't really want to. I regard.
I'm just wondering, do we like are we are we are we throwing
the problem is me off the cliff and what is it?
He this was he wanted a rock.
He wanted a big mountain in his park and he pioneered this whole area.
I love it. But is against it like an insane, that insane,
apocryphal story of him sending a postcard that just says, build this,
you know, but it's Louie Louie better than Golden Slumbers by the Beat.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like, sure, that matter was first and Walt did something very crazy,
cool and impressive.
But we can't just go by the past.
We have to say we have to stack them up
unobjectively, take them out of the past.
Yeah. First of all, Louie Louie is definitely not better than Golden Slumbers.
I agree. I'm just saying that was an earlier rock and roll song.
I understand. I say I should have picked.
You know what? I should have picked something a little more innovative.
Well, I think this might be counter to your point,
but I think rappers delight is still the best rap song.
It's all been downhill ever since then.
And all of these swears and gang stories have gotten in the way
of fun stories about trying to hide your food at your dinner.
You know, you really got to you really got to every time rap
comes up in your comedy, you just go off on that long rant like that.
You really got to open up.
Got it right the first time. OK.
And we have just been treading water.
And then I'll talk about that for a little bit.
And then I'll do a kind of like my name is Scott.
Well, that's you love the my name is black.
Yeah. Motif.
They they do.
I wouldn't I wouldn't comment on it if they didn't do it.
It wasn't right. Yeah.
These rappers punch a junk.
Uh, anyway, old conservative like Dean.
Like this is not nonsense.
They just talk over the music, not even music, you know,
which is funny because now a lot of those old old rappers are rich
and probably conservative and old. Yeah.
There is. There's no way to completely remove our biases.
That's the problem.
So we have to try our best to do it.
And then ultimately, whatever is in there, whatever is baked into our brains,
it's just there, I think.
But the maker of the of the rock, I think, is I think if some of these,
among other you associate with a person,
a specific person more than others, and that can be a cool facet to a fake rock.
Do I see Tony's smiling face as we round the bend a couple of times?
Yeah, of course, I see his face in all the rocks, but I can't not see it.
I can't not see the man.
And you just see stars on the Matterhorn because of the blood vessels
bursting in your eyes and skull.
Yeah, it's a rat one.
Me. Yeah. Well, just like in the next category, you know, you can't help
but go on these rides and think about the directors of the films
that they're based on, Avatar and Cars.
You can't help but just see the smiling face of the directors.
Smiling man. Nice way.
And said, Joe, Rhodey's smiling face.
I don't know. One round at a time.
OK, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go. Let's go back.
I don't know. Do you have more?
Do you have more to parse that?
I almost feel like I don't want all of these to be like I almost sometimes
I'm like, should we just both say it?
You should say the same time, but maybe you haven't decided.
If you've decided you should say it at the same time.
No, I'm stuck and I think I just need to make a decision and go go with it.
OK, all right.
Let's do same time.
All right.
One, two, three, go after go.
Then you guys both say it at the same time.
I messed it up already unless you didn't hear me.
I can't. All right.
One, two, three, go.
And after go, then you say it.
All right, here we go.
One, two, three, go.
Big Thunder.
All right.
We're friends again.
Mike's passion to argument about a certain type of rock.
And could we do Kitsch better now?
I mean, it was worth raising.
I mean, I think it's worth raising.
I mean, it was worth raising, but I always knew.
And I'd be sad if Big Thunder wasn't still alive in this competition.
This is a tough one, too.
I'm leaning towards Ornament Valley, I got to say, not just because it's the one I've seen in person.
Yeah, this is I don't want to just get air on that.
Mike, forget about the mighty Akron.
Or it's hard to divorce.
Think about all that.
It's hard to divorce from Jake Solly and all of his travels and trials and tribulations.
But I will remove myself.
I will move that part of my brain while I'm deciding this.
OK, Jake Solly, Johnny working class, Johnny Regula.
There are so many fake rocks in Ornament Valley.
So like you could almost say it's just the thing that you're at, the big like trapezoid that you
go that you round the band on.
You could just do the back wall.
You could.
I feel like I'm forgetting one.
Yeah, there's a lot of good specific.
There's like there's the waterfall when you're around the bend.
And there's the Cadillacs, the Cadillac range.
The Cadillac range is so and that's a very good character.
That's a little character in there.
And the arch that you go through from.
Yes, yes, of course.
So here's so I'm thinking because this is what I'm thinking.
I go, OK, if Halou Yamans beat Mount Prometheus, would Mount Prometheus versus
Ornament Valley, would I say Ornament Valley beats it?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
And I will go back to my original argument that Mount Prometheus, beautiful, is also dressed up
by the most beautiful theme park in the world.
Everything around it is amazing.
All of the views are perfect.
When we're talking about Ornament Valley, it's just Ornament Valley.
There's nothing around it, plussing it up.
It's just when we're looking at it, we're just looking at this massive structure,
these massive fake rocks that they built.
I'm saying there's nothing.
You're saying it's that's a positive because it stands on its own.
Yes, it stands on its own.
All we're assessing is Ornament Valley, whereas Mount Prometheus, it's almost impossible to
divorce it from the rest of the park in my mind.
So does that continue to Pandora?
Because that's in a very beautiful park as well.
It is.
But as I said before, I was a bit underwhelmed for just sort of the placement.
Like when you walk in, it's not sort of the wow you get from Cars Land, either entrance.
It's cool.
I would argue that sort of the best place to be in Pandora is sort of under the
under the mountains and then in the queue for Flight of Passage.
That to me is sort of the most special part of it.
And it's great fake rock stuff.
But if you're over by the Saul's Canteen, not as beautiful of a view when you enter the land.
Not as beautiful either entrance.
The second entrance.
Saul's Canteen?
Whatever it's called.
So Tully.
I always call it Saul's Canteen.
Yeah, that's embarrassing.
Come on down to Saul's Canteen.
That's embarrassing for a big Pandora head like me.
But look, my brain is fried from this too.
So please forgive me.
So that being said, I think I have to give it to Ornament Valley.
I want to live in Ornament Valley.
Yes.
Yeah.
Like that's a beautiful place to live.
And that may be more than almost anything else on this list.
I'm trying to look and see if there's another place I would want to live.
I mean, I want to live all of these places, but.
That's a good question.
Ornament Valley.
I want to live on the top of the Matterhorn.
Hogwarts, I guess.
But there's always like, what if you just wanted to go to school?
Like, what if you just want to get your degree and didn't want to deal with all this
fucking adventures and there's Nazi wizards outside and people keep dying?
Like, what if you're just like, I just want to get a degree and work a job.
It depends, though.
There's got to be there were like peaceful decades at Hogwarts, right?
I presume.
There wasn't a Voldemort kind of hanging around.
I don't know.
I guess.
Yeah, I guess that's accurate.
I assume, though, that maybe we would.
Times a piece.
Yeah, we just saw a tumultuous period of it.
But then all the mischief.
I bet the mischief never went away.
There was always mischief.
There was always whimsical English English mischief.
And since it is a British boarding school, something a lot more sinister,
probably under the surface, too.
But let's move on from that.
Yeah, sure.
So I hate to vote orally again.
No, that's no, that's where I was heading.
But it's Ornament Valley.
Yeah.
You know, hey, let me throw in the alcohol argument.
The ability to, you know, hey, this is unfair to Big Thunder or other things.
And I can't enjoy, it's a crime that I can't enjoy a big old beer in the line for Big Thunder.
I can in Ornament Valley.
And it's one of my favorite places to have a beer in the world.
It makes that single rider go by so fast and so smooth.
It's already a fast single rider.
So you must be spilling it out.
Oh, there's times where, you know, I've had like 45 minutes.
Oh, it's long.
Hanging out there with Erin.
And we've had good deep conversations and just getting lulled into it.
Yeah, yeah.
It's real nice.
And yeah, she's, you know.
Patio flows.
Yeah, if you want to really leisure, you drink the beer on the patio flows looking at the valley.
I guess.
I don't know.
I want to be in it.
I want it to envelop me.
And I like a good amber.
I like more like red beer there to match the red hue of the valley.
And especially if I like to, I don't buy, I buy a beer in the, in Pacific War from Karl
Stress and then walk that through the arch, get in the line that way.
The more scenic route.
That's that's that's maybe the best way to drink in the park.
And what I do when I drink in Cars Land is go to one of the cones,
one of the big cones and get the vodka lemonade.
And there is an amazing sugar like cream they put on top of it.
You know, that is good.
Yeah, it's really good.
And it's not even that overwhelming.
It's like a subtle sugar cream, believe it or not.
And I like getting that and going into the line for Cars Land.
That is I like this is the only place I found this.
And maybe it was just one person.
Maybe if I go back, they won't do it.
If you get the soft serve in the cup at the cozy cone, they will do the dip.
They will dip the cup.
And what happens with that, if you dip the soft serve in the cup, then when the ice cream,
then when the chocolate hardens and starts breaking off, it just goes into the cup.
So then you got all this chocolate at the end with the cone.
It's a race against time.
But they thought I was crazy when I asked for that at one of the other places.
Now, I'll say that last sentence in Peter Laurie's voice.
They thought I was crazy.
It's one of the other say they all thought I was crazy.
A cop is mad, they say.
I like we all I mean, we all just said something that we should all repeat in Peter
Laurie's voice because we're all maniacs who are like, yeah, then we get a beer and then we go
in the line and we relax.
I had a single beer.
I must be mad.
But like I'm just saying drinking by the fake rocks and imagining it's all well in that we,
if you listen to the full two hours leading up to this point, only that was the craziest.
That is a perfect gradient, though, from me, me, me, pure alcohol, you, alcohol with a lot of sugar
and Jason, pure sugar.
That kind of describes the types of the transition like the much like I was going to say,
like the rocks in ornamental valley.
Well, it's not ornamental.
It's not an ornamental valley.
Oh, God.
Ornament valley.
I'm doing this for too long.
So we got to final two.
Final two.
I love the final two.
I don't think like a not worthy one snuck in.
Yeah.
And there's not one in the back that I'm wishing was in there.
Maybe some people listening feel a different way, but let us know.
Hashtag PTRF for four.
But I love what's in here.
And we're we're very southwest, aren't we?
We're very because the various there's I forget which is which, but there's a big thunder that
is Bryce Canyon and there's a big thunder that's Zion and then ornament valley is very
California off road or like Route 66, like between cities and roadside attractions.
So we're covering the southwest.
They're similar types.
It's funny that we landed.
And you know what I think is it's probably not an accident because it's very warm colors
earthy colors back down towards the base camp in the beginning 16, but they're a little more
unfriendly.
Maybe you don't want to reward like lava rocks or like scary rocks.
I think that the like not even realizing the pleasantness of both of these rocks.
Yeah.
Overruled everything else.
Maybe a darker person would have picked darker rocks, but these are all these are joys to hang
out in.
I also know while while you can't enjoy a beer in this line, not a bad place to hang out.
Big Thunder is a place where I'll do a standby line that is a little longer because you get to
and I think it is the rocks.
That's my rule with with the lines.
If I can hang out with a bunch of rocks, I'm great.
But if I'm in some boring building, I'm upset.
It also moves that line moves.
It does.
It always has views, different perspectives, maybe a little less.
It's a little more claustrophobic.
The line for radiator strings, but I don't know.
But you do get different vantage points and sort of see more as you nestle into the attraction.
Here's something to talk about.
There's multiple specific landmarks in both of these in the final two.
Say like, what's your favorite rock?
Maybe that would help tilt it.
That's a good point.
My favorite rock.
I'll go first.
While you're tempted to just say like it's the tall rock and Big Thunder,
you know what's real nice is that that kind of overhang with the dinosaur bones.
Oh, yeah.
I guess that's cool because the dinosaur bones, but you got to give credit to the rocks for
supporting the yes, but it's not about what's supporting.
I think like the big choice for me might be that sort of like speed,
whatever you call that in a car, the like the ornament in the center of ornament valley.
But in terms of like subtlety, I really like the yeah, where you can see the different
gradients as if time has passed, time or water has passed on the walls.
Yeah, that's beautiful.
I mean, nighttime, nighttime on both these rides are great, but it's I don't know.
It's so hard.
I mean, I know it's so easy to go the new one with all the new stuff, but yeah,
I don't know.
I think I'm leaning towards ornament valley.
Yeah, I'm trying to like favorite the rocks are so like I'm trying to think of other than that.
Yeah, the big famous one.
What's my favorite favorite on Big Thunder?
I think yeah, there's so many is the goat standing on a rock or is he standing on a crate?
I don't think I know.
I'm a fan of Jason.
Do you know this?
No, let me see here.
He's on a rock.
Okay.
Yeah.
And he's on a cool ish, a cool rock.
Yeah, nice little nice little stump.
Hey, the fact that they brought think about this, the fact that they brought
beloved property Star Wars into the parks and they had to think about how to like we
have to make this perfectly Nestle next to this Disneyland stalwart.
We have to like build an in between of of Big Thunder.
We're tying together the mythology of Big Thunder Mountain and Star Wars.
They are says something.
Yes, they were for sure when they were making this like those black spires mirror Big Thunder
because they didn't want to ruin the skyline.
It doesn't matter at Hollywood studios because no one gives a shit, but they were very specific
to be like, we want to make sure this sort of fits in when you're like looking far back
that if you're just sort of seeing Big Thunder and Black Spire, you go,
maybe those are all sort of the same thing.
So you could say Black Spire is sort of like a tribute in a weird way.
I mean, would it have that?
Would it have the mountain range if not for what was going to go?
It might not even be called Black Spire outpost because obviously the spires are
the iconic thing, but they needed to put those spires there.
I think if they were going to build something that massive to make it sort of fit when you're
looking at the Disneyland skyline, anything for Florida.
No, no, because they're just it's a big empty area.
Yeah, it's next to the Muppet thing.
Yeah, paint the Muppets off.
Just paint the Muppet stuff people like.
I think you guys should take into account.
I think I think you should look at if you haven't already look at Big Thunder Paris.
Oh, oh, oh, because it's bigger, it's grander, it replaces Tom Sawyer Island.
You're more in and out like this bigger show scenes, you're inside tunnels for longer.
It's it's it's something if we're if we're struggling to make Big Thunder seem grandiose
next to the pure size of Radiator Springs, Paris might do it.
That feel like tricks, though.
Oh, it's an island.
Oh, it's real big.
Oh, it replaces this.
Doesn't that feel like a cheat code?
You can say that's not part of the decision, I guess.
But I don't know that it's a I don't think the fact that it's not.
I just think the actual like look at look at this version.
It's just like a it's a more grand version and probably one of the most successful
upgrades in a way that happened in Disneyland Paris.
Yeah, I mean, that's neat.
But like but we're in a valley as like two of the greatest eyelines like ever,
like not just the one coming through the town, like and in the background of the town.
It's got the back entrance.
So difficult.
Every view when you're on the ride itself, you wish you could be snapping photos the
whole time, but it's going too fast when you go in with that final drop down like under a big rock.
The big straightaway, the views are so grand where you curve into the rocks.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, this sucks.
This decision sucks.
I'm going to lock it in.
I think I'm locking in my vote for ornament Valley.
Hang on one minute.
I mean, do that.
Feel free to do it.
I'm actually I'm going to I'm going to throw a little diss at Ornament Valley.
OK, go ahead and see if that changes.
Does this ring a bell?
Really likes Tony Baxter.
It's that yes, Tony didn't build the other one.
No.
OK, it's a it's a space issue, right?
That ride is so backed up right to Cotella.
Yes, it is.
And the very back wall where it's sort of the rocks are a little more faded to make it look
a little more distant.
I feel the flatness of the of the like like what you know is right against the street.
Does this sound familiar to anybody?
You're talking about the ones that look like the the the the back of a car.
Yeah, the Cadillac.
I you know, I you're saying that doesn't have the dimension.
I agree doesn't have the dimension.
I think they did a good job like facadeing it, like making it look like it has shape
and depth.
Right.
I think it's I mean, it's it's remarkable, but we're being picky here.
This is the final round.
Yeah, that's something that was in my back pocket.
Like, is that a tie?
I think the novelty tops it.
I think the novelty.
That's a fair argument.
I don't think the I don't think I I don't think about Catella being right there,
but I know what you're saying that it doesn't have a tremendous amount of dimension.
If you can, my phone is far away from you, but this is what I'm talking about.
Like, just can you look at that and feel or maybe you can't?
Well, that's a that is a particularly bad picture of it.
Well, that's what I was trying to find.
Because as you get a bad, I'm not going to show you the nicest photo.
But I think that's one of the best parts of it.
Is the fact that it is different?
No, that that is like such a distinct thing.
I think regular people go like, oh, yeah, that's awesome.
Like the band like a Cadillac.
I think that that novelty outweighs what is the thing about it?
It's really it is like it's five Cadillac what hood ornaments?
The tail.
Yeah.
And it's like they represent all different years of classic.
I just want to like this is this is a very specific facet.
I would like to get it right.
Yeah, I don't know.
That's that is the code, the Cadillac range.
OK, and they all represent different years of that's that's cool to use rocks.
You know what, Mike, you're talking character.
Yeah, we're not sure that it's a word.
You know, you can maybe grizzlies to.
Maybe grizzlies to there.
Maybe they're too subtle with the grid.
This is like a subtle aspect of that back wall that if you know it, you know it.
And if not, they just look like the rocks.
I have a long Easter egg.
I will say I started this.
I was sure I was going to vote one way.
And then I switched in my head of like, no, you know what?
I think I'm voting the other way.
And now I think I'm voting back the first way.
Oh, boy.
I've gone like it's been a roller coaster in my head is what I'm saying.
And I'm still not sure.
But this is Jason.
You're locked in.
You're locked in for sure.
Ornament.
I'm going to lock it in.
Yeah, Scott, are you locked in in your head?
I feel like you are.
Yeah.
Yeah, I feel like you are.
I feel like you are.
I think I think so.
So Scott, just say it.
I'm not locked in.
Oh, wait a minute.
But maybe we both need to make a decision.
Maybe you can't be in a time breaker.
This makes it interesting.
I think here's I think I think insist that we both say it at the same time.
If you're going to vote the same as Jason.
And if you're not, say it now.
I got lost in there.
So if you're going to vote with the ornament valley, just say it.
Because then it wins.
It's over.
But if you're going to vote against Jason and it's going to break it down to me,
then we increase the tension.
Maybe you just maybe you just need to make a decision without me.
That's fine.
I'm just saying if you know, you can just end it or you can increase the tension.
I think you I well, I think the best way to increase the tension is for you to
go. Well, I just have to figure out that the best way would be for one of you to
go because I'm getting hungry.
The tension inside your stomach is growing.
Yes. I mean, OK, I guess I can decide here.
I think when you're divorcing yourself from all of it, the history, who made it,
the ride itself, they're both great rides.
I think I'm going to say just because of that goddamn second entrance ornament valley.
I am also going with ornament.
And when's wow ornament valley is taking the final round.
Incredible.
I thought exciting upset.
I thought for sure Big Thunder was going to win when we were going into the round.
I thought about it because I was trying not to think about it to get to the final round.
And I think if you think about it, it was a good idea to just get some discovery.
No, we needed to we needed to delay it.
But yeah, I know it's weirdly.
It's not even the dead center of it.
It's the arch.
The many layers of rocks behind it.
It's that's like got to be one of the most Instagram locations I don't know offhand,
but in my who I follow on Instagram.
Yeah, for sure.
California Adventure, the landmark that it needed.
I think it saved California Adventure in a way it went so far beyond a film that a lot of us
don't really care about.
That's true.
Made by a pervert.
Correct.
It's just transcended pervert.
Um, it's a, it's had so many calling this an underdog somehow.
Yeah, this is very expensive.
Theme park ride is the ultimate underdog.
Yeah, it seems like it though, when you think about the other famous mountains,
because it's not sort of talked about in the same breath as they are.
It's not a mountain.
This goes back to Jason's point.
I keep forgetting rocks first.
My brain.
And a young buck young 2012, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, new on the scene, but not but like clearly it feels like it was always there.
You can't even imagine the park without it.
And not even just because the ride is so good.
I really think that it added what California Adventure did not have was beauty.
And I think they added a moment and a reveal.
It's maybe more beautiful than anything in Disneyland, arguably.
Yeah, I think there's a lot of cool in Disneyland, but like the grandeur,
they just blew up a parking lot and filled it with fake rocks.
Yep.
The stature is staggering.
It's the it's huge.
It's great.
Yeah.
In a way it's like, how could we not have seen this coming?
How could we not have known?
I think the sentiment towards Big Thunder.
But you know what else?
Isn't it in a way a tribute to Big Thunder that it's playing in that same southwest
type of rock?
I think all of the warm feelings we have about Big Thunder we have with this as well.
To Pick Horniman Valley also acknowledges Big Thunder,
which and to pick Big Thunder acknowledges Matterhorn.
I think our lineage was great.
It's kind of like we did it perfectly.
We nailed it.
The one thing that's inarguable is that our order is exactly right.
And even if you use hashtag PTRFRF4, you're wrong and we're right.
Yep, that's true.
We did such a good job at our podcast.
We do a good job all the time.
We just need to acknowledge that.
It's okay to be proud.
It is okay.
And let's be proud.
I'm proud.
Yeah, I'm proud.
Yeah, let's all be proud boys.
Hashtag proud boys.
Yeah.
Let's stick to that PTRFRF4.
I'm very curious.
You can watch.
We'll post every step of this.
Go to that hashtag PTRFRF4 on our Twitter.
We'll show you.
We'll also post a blank bracket and you can see how the how
Horniman Valley ascended from base camp up to the peak, though it is not a mountain.
You're right.
It's the Cadillac.
I'm sorry.
It also has the most names.
You gotta be prepared for that.
Raider Springs, Horniman Valley, which features the Cadillac range.
Yeah.
Cool.
And if it's not complicated.
If you wanted to list all those out, you'd use a few commas.
And you know what makes a great attraction?
Lots of punctuation.
Punctuation.
Punctuation, baby.
That's a future Final Four is the theme park.
That's actually pretty good.
Wow.
Convoluted theme park name.
Because there's a lot more of those coming.
We know that.
Oh, for sure.
They haven't even named the Guardians Coaster in Epcot yet.
That's going to be a nightmare.
Oh my gosh.
Imagine what a full sentence that will be.
Guardians Coaster colon James Gunn is back colon.
Rockets rocket to the moon.
Parentheses maybe figments in it.
Parentheses figment and buzzier in it.
Point.
And then that's only like 25% of it.
Yeah.
I love this.
This is great.
I think it worked out perfectly.
No fights transpired.
And I hope if you were listening for that, if you wanted us to get at each other's throats,
it almost didn't happen.
But that's kind of our podcast in a nutshell, I think.
Sometimes we fight, but it's about things that probably aren't theme park related.
Usually I just need to eat a Snickers because I'm not me when I'm hungry.
You turn into the Honda.
Anyone?
Danny Devito, Hondo Anaka, Elton John, Jackie Mason.
Jackie Mason.
That's not a real one, is it?
From my favorite movie, Caddyshack 2.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
We watched.
Is Jackie Mason still alive?
Yes, he is.
We watched, I think we watched 10 minutes of Caddyshack 2.
I think we watched the first 10 minutes of Caddyshack 2 at Thanksgiving in 2010 in my apartment.
Something like that.
Yeah.
Wow.
You get a lot going on.
What a story.
Well, anything else to say?
I really want to hear.
It'll be exciting when we pause this.
I want to hear everybody's...
Takes.
Takes and thoughts.
And also, what's our next Final Four?
Next April, what should we be getting into?
We have ideas already, but what do you want to see us narrow down?
What are the hot button issues that we can solve definitively?
We will do it.
Let us know.
Great.
I think we got it.
Follow us on Twitter, at podcasttheride, hashtag PTRF4.
Tag us on Instagram with some of your favorite fake rocks.
Let us know if we give us a perspective that might have made something else win.
Email us if you're mad about these results at podcasttheride.gmail.com.
But don't email us something bad for us.
Just email us a note.
And draw a picture of Jason and a gallon of ice cream.
A gallon is not usually how they measure ice cream, but a gallon.
No, you get a gallon of ice cream.
Can you?
Yeah.
Don't you?
I believe so.
I think that's common.
You can buy a gallon?
Yeah.
I mean, usually go pint, pint quart.
I just think it's a pint and a quart.
Next size up is a gallon.
I guess I just don't think about it.
I guess you're right.
I guess it has to be that way.
Email us at podcasttheride.gmail.com.
Have you bought a gallon of ice cream?
Email us and let us know.
Yeah.
I bet you can do it.
Yeah, interesting.
Tell Mike where to do it.
You survived the podcast the ride, fake rock, final four.
That was harrowing.
We sent it to the peak.
We did it.
I'm exhausted.
I'm physically tired.
This might be the most tired.
I want to do a more wrap up.
I think let's strike a silence as long as we can.
All right, bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen, Joe Sillio, and Alex Ramsey.
Engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify,
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at foreverdogteam and liking our page on Facebook.