Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains terror evaders, Minnie and Daisy playing God, and
a naughty penguin getting a spanking.
Scott's back from Tokyo and he's here to tell us all about it.
It's Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, a podcast about theme parks where one of the hosts has finally
followed the compass of his heart.
I am Sid, compass follower, Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
Hi, my name is Mike Carlson.
I have also followed the compass of my heart.
Followed the compass.
Jason needs to follow the compass.
I know, I haven't yet.
I got my taxes done, but I haven't followed the compass of my heart yet.
Did that direct your compass in any particular way or your compass of spending in any particular
way?
More compass of relief because I thought it was going to be real bad.
Are you saying compass or compass?
Does it matter?
I've just never heard that pronunciation before.
Compass?
Hmm.
What do you think?
Is it compass?
Crampus.
It's crampus.
Are you saying compass?
Yeah, like compass.
Compass, yeah.
Okay.
Compass is what I mean.
I guess you're right that it actually is spelled more like.
Yeah.
Compass.
Yours sounds like C-U-M-P-A-S.
Compass, yeah.
Compass.
But that's always how I've heard it spelled or heard said.
Jason's just very fond of CompUSA.
Oh, rest in peace.
Their good values and savings.
Yeah, I'm back.
I have been to the promised land.
I have been to what I think I can say indisputably is the greatest theme park resort on the planet.
Yeah, I agree.
Incredible.
Exceeded expectations.
I haven't seen you guys yet.
There hasn't even been like pre-chatter or discussion.
I wanted to do it all on the air.
Keep it real.
Keep it 100.
Yep.
And Mike and I have done no research to prepare for today.
I love this.
I love it.
Surprised.
I know.
And it makes me very nervous, honestly.
I'm actually nervous about having to drive the thing.
I feel like we're always like co-driving, but realizing that this is like essentially
me narrating my own vacation.
The pressure's on.
I had to get properly caffeinated.
I'm trying to fight the massive jet lag that I have.
I had too big of a lunch where it's going to make me groggy, where I'm not going to
be able to keep the ship on course.
We're just fix on fly.
We're raw dogging it today to come along.
Oh my god.
The compass talk.
It's down and dirty.
That's insane.
And we're pointing the compass.
The compass.
You're the one talking about a navigational instrument putting the word cum in the...
Put cum spice on it.
It's even what they say.
When you see the people singing the song, they say compass.
I think they do.
It's a little...
In the song, and the song that I'm referring to is in the Sindbad's Storybook Voyages ride.
And it is like...
I'd only heard...
I still have not listened to the part of the Tokyo Disney episode that I left.
I need to go back now.
I'm sure we'll overlap some of the territory.
But I do...
I'm aware of certain things about it.
And I am certainly aware that you were very moved by this song.
Very, yes.
And I was as well.
And I'm on the ride going...
I'm like...
You immediately well up a little bit because you're introduced to a town in which everyone is supporting each other.
It is the sweetest thing you ever see.
But still, I'm not like, yeah, but what brought them to tears?
What could have possibly...
And by the end, to totally go...
I think by fighting it at the beginning, it caused it to happen at the end.
I welled up a bunch of times on this vacation in multiple places.
My heart is so full.
This will be the most earnest episode, Scott-wise.
So please, you guys, lob your joke bombs because try to sink this very earnest ship that I'm steering.
And you came back to what can only be described as a United Hollywood.
Hand in hand.
Agents and directors.
Making projects.
Good luck on your renegotiations.
Yeah, I discovered the news that I was to fire my agents while inside the volcano.
Oh, wow.
I was hoping that this news dropping would happen in a dramatic way during the vacation.
And it was lining up to happen.
I was like, maybe I'll be at the top of the Park Hyatt, the Lost in Translation bar.
I'll have a dramatic view of Tokyo and then I'll get this crazy Hollywood shattering news.
But then it got delayed a week and I was wondering what was going on.
And then I'm literally about to board the TeraVader.
And I see an even...
I just check and it's the most dramatically phrased headline possible.
Like, there is no deal.
Fire your agents.
So then I'm brought into a room that is like pumping machinery and sirens and alarms and excavators and like man the hatches.
Mass firings on three.
It was unforgettable.
Jules Berne created an agent firing machine powered by steam.
Can fire 15,000 agents at once.
Well, if it makes you feel any better, the most recent dispatch from the Screen Actors Guild is we have direct deposit now.
So lots of exciting stuff on the Hollywood labor front.
The next time my five dollars and forty three cents of collected Moonbeam City residuals show up, ten envelopes will be saved.
Yeah, that's great news.
We're helping the environment.
Sure.
Yeah, I mean...
So I guess we say spoilers if you don't want to know about Tokyo Disney.
Tokyo Disney, I suppose.
I have no idea how much anybody else was playing my game of not wanting to hear things.
And I, you know, since that episode, I've thought I feel like I was like too strict on it because we've since determined that like you guys felt so much you didn't need to spoil things that I didn't know about Grandma Sarah's kitchen.
Yes.
And I'm like, did I convey like too hard of a spoiler rule?
Maybe I did.
However, I'm glad that I did because constantly around every corner there were things that I had no clue about.
And I thank you guys for for helping me in that endeavor and being fine with me leaving an episode, quitting it halfway through.
Sure.
I was wondering if there was anything that we should have said, but I don't think most of the things you probably found on your own, they're big enough stuff.
And yeah, so you know, you you passed along this book to me that I would really recommend to anybody going.
The TDR Explorer.
Yes.
Tokyo, which that's a Twitter account to write the whoever runs it, I think seem to be there at the same time.
I was always there.
He's the Tokyo Disney Explorer.
I think he has a Twitter.
TDR Explorer blog, I believe.
Yeah, incredibly helpful book.
And I recommend finding this book.
I think it's available for the for the Kindle or whatever.
Yeah, I think so.
Yes.
And it's that TDR Explorer.
Super helpful because I there are there are logistics you have to figure out as much as I didn't want spoilers.
I think about Tokyo in general, there's there's a lot that you need to solve.
The trains are complicated.
The Wi-Fi thing you have to figure out.
But within the resort, there's definitely things to to determine.
And you know, one of which is when you go.
And that is if I I don't know how it was in general, crowd wise.
When you were you were there in like October, it was like Halloween ish September.
OK, OK. Within the window, though, where they had because you said you had our mid September Haunted Mansion holiday.
Yes, they have Haunted Mansion holiday.
They still had started Halloween already because they started early there, too.
But it was like second week in September, I believe.
Third week.
How was that like crowd wiser?
Crowds were bad.
Like not crazy.
I will say that they did seem like they had a good flow.
The crowds had good flows.
It wasn't like anything was like choked.
It was just there was a lot of folks.
Sure, sure.
I think you this may have been you who said it or that you feel I mean, there were a ton of people when I was there, too.
But you do feel the crowd dispersal is just better.
And I can't help but wonder if it does it have something to do with them not having Max Pass and the app and everything?
Well, the app is coming.
Oh, it is.
So we'll see.
I guess we'll see next time we go.
But it's possible.
But you would think, though, because they still have paper fast passes that people be running all over the place.
Sure, sure.
So that would also be a thing, too.
The only thing in terms of that, when the gates open, because I did a rope drop of Tokyo,
Disney and there is so much excitement for the park in general and clearly for the Easter season.
That's like they had to people were out there holding signs that say, please don't run.
Oh, yeah.
It would certainly be your temptation.
And as polite as the Japanese people are, I mean, I wanted to run.
Yeah.
When you round that, when you first see that volcano, I've seen plenty of pictures of it.
But when it is first in your sights, you the mania takes you over.
Sure.
Get me in everywhere.
I will stay up all day.
I will never sit this entire day.
I wonder if it's I do wonder if everyone just like more polite about walking, maybe.
Maybe so.
People also polite, apparently, about asking for the front row.
Single writer is a seemingly not super common there, which helps you blast through Indiana Jones and lost spear raging spirits.
Yes.
Is the like wild mouse type coaster.
It's a smaller roller coaster.
Which is fun, but like you shouldn't wait forever for it.
Before we get into your trip, I remember the one there's probably many stories I forgot to tell real quick.
There's a story I left out of my trip about that coaster.
OK, so I'm walking into the queue.
An employee runs up to me and he's trying to communicate the question.
How tall are you?
And at first I think, oh, he's like, I'm a six, three gentleman.
He's oh, this is fun.
Look how tall he is.
He's like a Herman Munster or something.
And it becomes very clear that he hands me a card and it says that I'm six, three and I'm the tallest you can possibly be to ride this roller coaster.
Oh, and I'm like, oh, oh, shit.
Like, so we're walking through the queue, Lindsay and I walking through the queue going like like an inch taller and I'd be decapitated on this thing.
This is insane.
I've never heard of this before.
So we're like walking through like, should I go on this?
Should I just not do this?
Because they're like because there was a whole like he was talking amongst employees like, should we let this guy go on or whatever?
And then they they were like, all right, it's fine.
And they handed me this card that said I was approved to go on it.
So I was stressed.
I was stressed the whole line.
There's got to be some wiggle room.
Of course.
But I'm just saying still, I was like, this is weird that there was even a debate.
So I got on the ride and I'm like crouched down on the coaster is like hard as I can.
And obviously everything was fine.
But I do think I put myself in such an uncomfortable position.
Like I hurt my back a little bit because I was like making sure I wasn't like going to get decapitated on the ride.
I think really the issue was that the restraints didn't go high enough.
Oh, OK.
I think that's probably what it was.
But still, you didn't ever there wasn't some like overhand.
There wasn't some temple ruin that almost hit you in the brain.
No, but still I was like, I've never seen this before on a roller coaster that I'm too tall to go on it.
Like that's never happened.
I find it weird on that ride that there was a when after the cars did the loop that the loop like shook.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a little unnerving, a little unnerving.
A wild mouse type coaster with a loop.
I'm very intrigued.
Mm hmm.
It was it's it's really good.
You would call it like the best thing there.
Yeah, but especially you single ride it really well themed and it like fogs up right before you you shoot through a little tunnel.
And there's a big there's like ruins like step ruins kind of enticing you in.
It's like a pretty plain coaster, but themed a little better than usual.
But the entrance where there's a waterfall going down the steps, but it's also on fire at the same time.
Incredible. So cool.
It's just a throwaway part of that park.
That's like the 19th best thing in the park.
We didn't go on in the night, but it looks better at night, too.
Oh, I bet. Yeah, I didn't do enough.
Like I saw this in the day and at night.
We didn't either.
I can get into various iterations of that.
Well, to the end of the harnesses being too small, definitely think that the rides are built for smaller people.
Oh, yeah, it's definitely true.
Yeah, for sure.
Finally.
Nice.
A place that doesn't diminish.
It's shorter restraints that don't give me a headache every time I go on a looping coaster.
They have to hand you a form that you sign where you say you are the perfect candidate to go on this ride.
Are you OK being perfect?
Yes.
A blue ribbon you wear.
Mayor of the ride.
So, oh, wait, I was starting to say the time that I was there was fantastic.
It's fantastic if anyone's listening to this for general recommendations because I was there in the second week of April.
And it's fantastic because you're avoiding right at the end of April is this thing Golden Week, which is apparently everywhere in Japan is fucked apart tourism wise because they're very like institutionalized spring break.
So we missed all that.
But it's right before that.
So everything's still really beautiful and cherry blossoms are in bloom.
And that's as cool as it's hyped up to be.
Crowds were totally fine, except that I did end up there on a Saturday and Saturday markedly worse.
So I'd say anybody who can avoid the weekend if your schedule is open, avoid weekends because the difference was night and day immediately.
But boy, I really recommend when I went and especially because I was there for Easter.
It was the Easter celebration.
And holy shit.
I mean, I'm sure it's always great.
But I and I'd heard it alluded to a little the glory of Easter.
I mean, really, every Easter also affected Sanrio Puroland, which I will try to be sparing talking about because we have to just that's its own thing for sure.
Easter at Disney.
Oh, my God.
And I'll lay all this out mainly.
Do you guys know about the mythology of the the U.S.
Toma and the U.S.
No.
Oh, no.
But I am interested because it's Easter like the the cultural like Easter parade Easter of fancy dresses and linen suits.
Right.
Like there's no there's no element of Jesus Christ Easter.
Not remotely culturally in Japan.
I don't think the traditional definition of Easter is totally skewed for just eggs and fancy clothes.
But also, it's not like big gowns necessarily like their Easter clothes are just kind of like in many cases, like sparkly space clothes.
There are dolls of Chip and Dale where they're just wearing these complicated asks.
They've got a spire and it's like sparkly purple and sparkly silver clashing and going back and forth on every part.
I met Easter Dale. That was that was really exciting.
Oh, you post a photo of that. I think I tweeted about it.
I got to have a conversation about Easter.
I was like, well, there's a language barrier here, but I bet he's he's in his Easter clothes.
He must be excited about Easter. So I made bunny ears.
He made bunny ears in return and we hugged.
It's very exciting.
Easter is just it just takes what is probably already like kind of a hyper park and just ratchets it way the right up.
Like like Lindsey got me this crazy Tokyo Disney see Mickey for my birthday, which is insane.
But the clothes in general are already.
Do you remember what this looks like?
Yeah. Wait, spin that around if you can, Jason, without hurting anything.
I know kind of what you're talking about.
He's in this crazy like future sailor suit.
Yeah, it's like he's it's crazy.
Like the clothes already look a little bit.
Yeah. Like, how do you even what is even a touch point?
I don't think we have in our culture what kind of clothes Mickey's wearing.
Sort of like P.T. Barnum sort of get up, but all in like different shades of baby blue.
So a greatest showman. Yeah.
A little British showman, but like a twenty thirty greatest showman.
But with the nineteen hundreds with a tri-corner hat.
Yeah. Like a colonial America tri-corner hat.
The most detailed like buttons and crevasses and the the brightest baby blue.
I mean, this is like the character they dress like these weird like samurai
by way of a turn of the century marching band.
That's like not Easter even. That's their their base.
Right. That's just normal.
Like here we have right now, Mickey and everyone are in like party city style,
like white suits with like splashes of color.
I was no fan of that before. I'm really not a fan of it now.
I think I prefer the Japanese kind of crazy clothing,
not only on the characters, but also on the people in the park.
Like when you see people dressed up together in Disneyland,
there's the Disney bounding thing or there's dapper day.
There's the kind of the retro thing.
And those those are fine. And it's just it's not my bag.
But it's I like a way that people can dress in the spirit of of the park in Disney.
It just seems like cooler or in Tokyo.
It just seems cooler the way people do it.
They were like, here's a group of ten girls and they're all dressed as ham.
How did they coordinate this?
This is insane. Ham from Toy Story or just the concept of ham?
No, not although that would fit right with with Easter, wouldn't it?
OK, yeah, yeah.
They're there when they all form like a transformer, they form the full.
Yeah, the full traditional honey.
Yeah, no. Or like, you know, like a bunch of the sets of two male friends
who dressed exactly the same.
Yeah. Like a little vest and button.
And how do they do this? How do they coordinate?
And it just and it all feels more like then they could go out on the streets
in regular Tokyo and nobody would make fun of them.
Like it's just all like the cool culture is embedded with Disney culture.
They're just one in the same.
Yeah, I mean, I think that's probably true.
I do feel like I mean, I think with Disney now it's still it's it's getting more
melded every day. Yeah.
Like we'll be there in like 30 or 50 years where it's like not even where there's no chance
you get beaten up by Orange County punks if you wore your dapper days outfits into the
Fuddruckers nearby because the punks are wearing like hashtag Disney squad shirts anyway.
Yeah. And a lot of them already. A lot of the punks are already wearing that.
So potentially we're getting closer.
But yes, I know they're wearing some they're wearing something with like a like fifties
pomp and like a fifties swoop Clara Clara Bell.
Yeah. A patch of Oogie Boogie saying Wop Op a Loo Bop.
I think I'm just relieved that there's not a lot of fifties going on in in Japan.
I don't know what my problem is with the fifties, except that actually, as I say that,
I'm totally wrong because Sanrio Puroland, their Easter celebration was fifties rock and roll was Wop
Op a Loo Bop. Whoa. Yeah. Like like like Rob Bob a loop.
It's Easter time. Why are these things? I think there is a certain streak of like because
greaser fashion is like it's a spin on like traditional menswear, which is such American
menswear is a big influence in Japan and vice versa.
Like there are catalogs.
One thing I read about like Japanese menswear, there's a book of like Ivy style,
like of the shops around like Harvard or Princeton or that sort of stuff that is very popular in Japan.
And then it's very popular for menswear enthusiasts in America.
So it's like a circular thing. Huh?
And then one influences the other and it changes back on the other side.
Yeah. Same with rock and roll.
The Japanese, I think we've all been listening to Japanese city pop lately.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Which you know what threw me in the record stores?
I don't know what you call. It was hard to find stuff.
I don't know what they call city pop. They don't have a big section labeled city pop,
but they do certainly have like, you know, here's the giant progressive rock area.
And there's a massive area devoted to AOR, my favorite genre of music.
We're like some obscure thing that I don't even have one friend to talk to about this album.
It's like what they're featuring this week. Whoa. Yeah.
I'll constantly that the tower records and we didn't even get there.
Oh, we got to go. Yeah. Next time. Holy shit.
Because also the there's one in Shinjuku where I stayed and I'd recommend anybody going to Tokyo,
Shinjuku, great central area. I dug it a lot.
But then the one in Shibuya is the like crazy multi-level.
It's the one where when you if you watch the documentary or you hear like, boy, the end of tower.
And why did we reject tower? Oh, but it is in Japan in the coolest building you've ever seen,
which would fit right into tomorrow land and Disneyland, which I obviously was super enamored with.
Tower records, fucking rocks, everything. I mean, the city, I can't even go into the city.
There's so much cool shit. I was starting to head to Easter.
So for a number of years running now, Disneyland took a Disneyland has the Usatama,
who are a bunch of eggs with legs who have infested the park. Whoa.
And they are everywhere. They've made themselves at home.
And the ones in Frontierland are, you know, kicking back on top of the saloon and, you know,
and drinking some moonshine or they've disguised themselves as, you know,
the dwarves over in the by the Snow White Fountain or they're they look like Mike Wazowski
over in Tomorrowland or whatever. There's so many eggs.
You get to do like a visual Easter egg hunt while you're there.
And they've so cleverly designed all of these eggs in a very fun pop or what's the literal?
What am I thinking of the park? Yeah. Or the Park stars.
Yeah, it's so much like that, where it's a really minimal representation of the characters from there.
Up on top of the country bears, eggs dressed as teddy bear and Henry and what have you.
So this just adds this level of visual excitement everywhere in the parks.
They do a version of it in Disneyland, but it's just like kind of painted eggs and it's Chip and Dale
or something. And there we saw one of them recently and they're fine. Sure, sure.
But this is a whole seems like a whole nother level. There's this mania where there's like they're presented
like critters. They're like gremlins or something who've taken over the park.
They've just made it there. I got a picture of one like the lawns in front of the castle there are very golf
course manicured. So they made one look like he's putting he's got like a golf bag and a visor.
My favorite clothing item. Just a regular cloth visor hanging off of this egg.
But so how you know, they're cute and all, but we have to keep the population under control.
How do we do that? Well, with the Usatama on the run parade in which Mickey is piloting a suction machine.
Oh my gosh. I didn't know anything about this. Eggs to try to. That's insane.
That's so fun. It's a population control measure more than it is a parade.
I literally didn't stop and watch this parade, but just look up photos of it was the time on the run.
Wow. Writing a big contraption. It's been they're all helping out.
They've all got Mickey and Donald have their own ways of trying to find the do they have like a big thing of eggs
behind him like he's caught some of them caught a bunch.
Yeah, they're all they're all suffocating. They're all like they're all hanging like fish from hooks.
Wow. He made lessons of a couple of them. No, I don't know.
Look, they're all friends. Ultimately, at the end of the day, he just has to know where they are because it's his park.
Right. Can't get to Disney feral cats. They can't get out of control. Right.
Yeah. When you said they all have their own ways of taking care of it, I was concerned that like Donald was like Eli Roth and glorious bastard.
It's like he's the brutal was like he's like taking them out back. As soon as you said that, I went, I bet Donald has a baseball bat.
Yeah, that is what I thought. Then you said Eli Roth. So we were on the same page.
It's a walking tall scenario. Smashing your mind, bitch.
That's close. I can get to Donald, apparently.
But new this year, I got to be part of the inaugural audience of the first time ever Disney see equivalent of the U.S.
Toma, a genetic varietal called the U.S.
Pio. And here's what they are.
Donald, I'm sorry, Daisy and many were decorating for Easter that year.
And they took an egg and they painted some bunny ears on it. Cute, right?
Yes. Went a little further than that because the eggs actually sprouted ears and chickens hatched out of them.
So Daisy and many unknowingly created a genetic abomination, which are little chicks with Easter eggs and that still have their shells on their bottom and their top.
And those are the U.S. Pia and the giant lagoon show Tip Top Easter is all about you get to witness the birth of many U.S.
Pio's at once. Wow.
They all come out of eggs and like, do you know about this lagoon show in general?
Or did you see some equivalent of that?
We saw the Halloween, the villains party with like waters like like ski do's and there were that.
Okay. And then.
Flying kites off of the back of jet skis.
There was that they all the villains had their own like vehicle in the water.
So each each villain had their own special big giant thing that they were out on.
And then shit. Yeah.
And there's a crazy original song and Hades does a rap in it.
Whoa. What? Yeah.
Apparently at last year's Easter, Andrew Grissom told us they there was a rap done by Max Goof.
He's on. But there was a whole new show this year.
They revamp them every year. Yeah.
You can go by CDs of just the single songs that are 15 minutes long.
They sell CD singles of just the Easter music or probably just the Halloween music.
I got the three disc like kind of best of from that year, but I should have bought more.
Like there's a 10 to 15 disc thing that's on eBay for five hundred dollars of the history of the music of the park.
And I was just showing a picture of it to people in the park going like, do you have this?
And then they would be like, they were so helpful, but no one knew what I was talking about.
So I would have had to have bought like all of the CDs because it's not on there.
And that's one of the big reasons.
I remember you had something up with the CD and I was looking and I didn't seem to be anything, which that be the first thing you'd want to walk away with.
Yes, for sure. And I I've had to rip it off of YouTube.
Do you have it on your iPhone?
It's it should be on my iPhone. It's on my computer for sure.
I think it's probably transferred over. I listen to that song like once a week at least.
I mean, we've been singing it ever since.
And the main I mean, I I'll say this now.
The this was a hard vacation to leave.
We love if we hadn't even done Disney to Tokyo and Kyoto are such fantastic cities.
We're very sad to be the saddest I've been to leave a vacation since I was at Disney World when I was seven.
And one little trick that we did to make us more excited about coming back was going through the airport, passing by the customs agents,
imagining that they were puppet dolls singing a majestic song, wishing us luck on our journey back to America.
And we did the same thing to our cats when we went to retrieve them from Chatsworth, where they were staying while we were gone.
We were wishing them good luck on their journey back from Chatsworth.
And there are cats names are Brenda and Bunny and we called them Bryn Bad and Bundu.
And it really helps.
So any difficult challenge you have in your life, imagine anyone near you.
Don't forget that. Imagining people are naked or in their underwear.
Imagine anyone is a puppet doll wishing you luck on your journey.
It's going to help you through any challenge.
So but just to sum up from earlier, this year's Easter show, which probably won't be back next year, involves Minnie and Daisy playing God.
Yes. And creating life, a new form of horrifying life.
It is a tale of genetic engineering gone. Adorable.
It works out to their advantage.
Well, while you were gone, I watched Gattaca and was under Gattaca.
Not at all. I also thought I had never I knew very little about that movie.
And but I saw the poster and like box art for years and I was like, this is a sci fi action movie.
No, this is a like off Broadway sci fi melodrama that involves a lot of smuggling urine and blood samples.
I haven't seen in a long time. I think it was a cooler was it just there was a lot of interesting like brutalism architecture choices and a lot of interesting coloring choices.
Yeah, but it is really like Arthur Miller play almost of like not a lot of big set pieces and stuff.
Well, you know, as we allow our most beloved franchise is to sort of take surprising forms like our Joaquin Phoenix jokers or whatever.
I would gladly watch the gritty Gattaca style film about the birth of the the Uso Pio.
Oh, yeah. Oh, sure. Great. Yeah. Yeah.
They don't sell Uso Pio merch, though. They do. And it's they do. It's tough.
And I, you know, we have so there's we have friends with babies and stuff.
And and I was trying to find Uso Pio puppets. It's tough. They apparent.
I think they go in. I was finding sites. I think they also have these in Hong Kong.
And it's like there are two left in the entire nation. Yeah, they go like that.
Like a new Duffy outfit or something. Yep. Yep. Flies off the shelf.
I certainly I I definitely get Duffy more now.
I will say that especially when I saw Duffy while waiting for the Tip Top Easter show,
I saw a Duffy dressed as an aristocrat.
This was the most adorable thing. Yeah.
Did you see anyone pushing two strollers around full of Duffy characters?
I definitely saw. I mean, not that, but I saw people like having meals across from their Duffy.
Yep. Yep. And I like that there were little seats that you put the Duffy on to take a photo.
Like in the volcano, you like lean down a little. Oh, yeah.
Seats and like here's the perfect spot for them to have their photo taken.
And in the in this multi barge lagoon show, there's you can there's many vantage points from which you can watch it.
And you could watch it over in Donald Daisy territory or Mickey Minnie territory.
You don't know what's coming until they land.
And ours was the Duffy gang. So while I didn't meet Duffy or watch a separate Duffy show,
I did get to see Duffy. Can I name them now? Duffy, Jelatoni.
Maybe I can't. But I'm certainly more fond of Jelatoni than I used to be.
Oh, my God. He's the best. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, it's not. Yeah. Jelatoni is one of my guys. Yeah.
There's a well, Shelly May, Stella Lu.
And who's the Bird Mailman? Who's the Hong Kong one that our wonderful listeners sent us?
Merchandise from Hong Kong of Cookie of Cookie. OK.
Well, we should tell the listeners there's a there's a lot of Duffy coming from podcast to ride.
Oh, yes. Things have not even aware of what you guys did while I was gone.
We recorded an interview already for part of the Big Duffy episode coming up and we'll be doing the full version soon.
Only a fraction of it has been completed. Yeah.
It's a big project. Sure. It's a little more like a it's a little more like a serial or like a slow burn.
Right. This one's going to be a little bit more of an excavation.
I will be certainly more mentally invested in the episode now, having seen the gang and having seen Duffy and his pals teach the hatched egg creatures ballet and magic.
Oh, wow. What ends up they hatch and then they teach them about Easter.
Some ballet dancers show them and then say, now you go and they they you know, they don't even know how to walk, let alone do ballet.
But they try their best. It's very adorable. Is Stella Lu a ballet dancer?
Was one of them? I don't recall. She has like a yeah, she has like a tutu.
She may have taken lead in that section. Here's the number one thing that happens in that show, though.
At one point, something is yelled and everybody points over to the volcano and the volcano itself yells,
Happy Easter. Whoa. Yeah.
What? Shoot something out to or does it?
There might be like, you know, I mean, nothing special, nothing besides its usual eruptions, the coolest shit ever.
Now we were discussing later. Is that supposed to be a spoiler?
The monster inside the ride wishing Happy Easter. Oh, or is it the volcano itself?
I prefer to think that the landmark, the volcano loves Easter. Right.
Like the lava short from Pixar. Oh, yeah. That guy saying, oh, maybe.
Absolutely. Short I love and I've talked in the past that people were way too mean to those volcanoes.
People vary. People do not like shaming those volcanoes.
Well, I think also they were saying because because they're saying like the the lava volcano is like a like a chunky guy and the woman volcano was like sexy girl.
And that's a trope like where it's, you know, people were that's sexualizing the volcanoes.
That's odd. Why? But I have been like, but for instance, like with cartoons where it's like, for instance, Heathcliff,
when the Cadillac Cats riffraff is like short and stout and looks like a cartoon, but then his girlfriend is as the body of a sexy woman.
What's wrong with that, Michael? I'm just saying that's something that people talk about.
You know, like I think Kevin James and Bugs Bunny doesn't jack like a human man.
But Lola Bunny sure looks like a sexy lady. That's that's the that's like comedians getting with people like Kevin James on a sitcom.
Yeah. Is there some comments on Facebook or somewhere said like our girlfriends and wives are too attractive for us?
Must be a California thing. Yeah. Whoa. That's funny. All right.
Thanks for giving us credit.
Okay. So I've so I've said that the I think that the time of year that I went was was perfect.
Yeah. But there is an outstanding question. The outstanding question is how long how long were you there? Did I go for?
Let me reach into my duffel bag and hang on. Will you have like just a number like a big plastic number?
Will you have like just a number like a big plastic number?
We'll pull out now and reveal to you gentlemen my four day magic.
That's what I thought we should have. We should have asked.
Jason always wins.
Because what people were we ran into some listeners who were asking about this.
Some listeners were asking about how long you were there. People asked.
Well, yes. We didn't know.
But then they said, which I was thinking there because the reason we think is because Tony said for Tony really pushed it over the only
back to our life episode.
Tony got me on Splash Mountain and and Tony.
No, I don't know. I well, hey, your enthusiasm from being there doesn't doesn't do nothing either.
You clearly you clearly had a great time and clearly.
And you know, so you deserve some credit, too.
And now here's here's the caveats. It was a four day passport.
Two of those were half days. Right.
I got so, you know, a first evening in Disneyland, two front to back days and then a little in the morning before before we went off to the airport.
So you kind of did what we did because we really did like three and a half days.
OK. Yeah. So it's ended up being three all told. Right.
Now, so is the revealing of this four day passport me eating crow in a way, in a way, a delicacy in Japan.
So many good crow places in the parks.
So I could grow. I I will say this.
I I will maintain.
I think that four front to back opening to closing rope drop days would be overkill.
I don't think you need that much time.
That is, I I'm still going to hold by that.
I don't know how you feel about that.
He hasn't been. Yeah, I haven't been there.
How much time did you because you were not staying at an official Disney hotel.
Did you spend much time at all at the official Disney hotels?
I you know, I didn't. And I'm usually somebody I like exploring hotels.
I definitely I've said before, I carve out hotel time when I go to Disney World.
Yeah, I didn't really partially because those hotels seem really neat and one of them is right next to Disney Sea.
Yeah. But the parts are so great.
I don't want to spend time in a hotel.
There was even I ran around the mall, expiry, and I tweeted something about the upcoming expiry affair.
And I thought about spending more time.
That's sort of their downtown Disney, although it's removed.
It's not like right next to the parks.
But I kind of thought I'm going to want to spend a bunch of time there in the silly mall next to I didn't really.
The parks are so great.
I had no desire to be in the other places.
The other thing that kept me out of the hotels was they're all kind of recent.
So what I'm after where I'm going to see some like solid nineteen seventy one architecture out of the contemporary
or, you know, the there's 80s throwbacks and some of those other places.
I was like, if they're all built in 2003, then who cares?
Really? I did. I stayed at the Hilton.
You were at the Sheraton, correct? Yes.
I was at the Hilton.
All these hotels are an easy monorail stop.
Boy, one thing I'll say, the transit so easy.
In general. Yeah.
You're waiting no time. It's a loop.
There's only four stops.
There's all the non not the main hotels.
There's Disneyland, there's Disney Sea, there's Xperia in the main train station that gets you in and out from Tokyo.
I don't see any reason to stay in the Disney ones because you're so close to the it's not like in Paris,
all the hotels were so fucking expensive, the main Disney ones.
So we boarded a rickety bus to Radisson that was only 10 minutes away.
But the ride back and forth was so shitty.
It made us not want to go in for the day.
Just tear like this awful shuttle where you're standing and bumping around.
Here you get to board the cleanest monorail.
I in general think that this initial two day arguments now here, I will say this two days, not enough.
I was certainly wrong about that.
I'm man enough to say it sounds like because Jason had always said for it sounds like I was absolutely right.
Before I went with the three days, it sounds like I'll give it to you.
I don't give it to you on everything.
I'm giving it to you on this.
You were right.
You called it.
I appreciate that.
Also, I think I was thinking about the whole situation again.
I don't know that I was like mad that people were going if it was too.
I think I said we should do three with our level of I think that's all I was ever saying.
This is a good point.
For some people, for some people, one day is fine.
I don't know.
I get why people would just do see this friends of ours.
You're like I didn't do to get Disneyland because it's the same as the one here.
Now, for me, a big fan of all this stuff, it certainly isn't.
But in all these micro ways, you're like, well, Space Mountain is a ramp and not the you know, it's a ramp from the front like the way it used to be in Disneyland.
So you got to see that.
And it's kind of the Haunted Mansion from Florida.
But it's different in this way.
Yes, like we're finding all these micro differences.
So of course you need more time.
Yeah, we talked about that on my episode.
It was like, which one is this going to be?
Yeah, like that was a wonderful mix of a lot of Magic Kingdom, which is great because Magic Kingdom perfected a lot of Disneyland stuff.
And then in other cases, totally original to them.
And in other cases, a little bit of a tribute to the original.
It's like it's the better Pirates and Space Mountain because it's Disneyland.
But then it is Florida Haunted Mansion, which I don't know is better, but is interesting.
And then nice to do.
I'm not like super familiar with that one.
So getting to do, you know, the library is part of the ride or her bag is part of the ride.
And then I got what the coolest thing was, it was Haunted Mansion holiday.
So I got to see the Florida version of Haunted Mansion, which doesn't exist.
Disneyland overlay.
Yes, which is very cool.
All right.
So yes, that's for nerds.
So yeah, if you're even slightly a nerd, you definitely need a little more time because Disneyland is going to take you a little more time.
Yes.
You know, if you're listening to this podcast, you were a nerd for this stuff, presumably.
But I would tell anybody, even if you can't even stand theme parks, Disney Sea is this other beast of thing.
It's almost like it's the closest that Disney's come to like a public works beautification project.
It's like something the city needed.
It is so they like made they made Tokyo better with Disney Sea.
It's unbelievable.
A city already chock full of substance and culture and a million subcultures.
The greatest I could I could talk for two hours about talking about Disney in terms of Tokyo.
Tokyo fucking rules.
And they somehow it's such a testament to Disney Sea that it's right.
Right. It was the last thing I did, essentially.
And it's like all I've thought about since even though Tokyo is the best place I've ever been.
Right.
It's a masterpiece in design every which way, because I'm trying to think of any other theme park I've been in like that where I think I said it before, where it's like everywhere you're standing, it feels like it was perfectly designed to be the most beautiful scene you've ever seen.
As if they like as if in every single spot as if they did like a Google Street view.
All right. Now go five feet over here and look every way around you.
And if there's anything cluttering your view, it's out.
Yeah.
Every square inch made the most beautiful place.
Isn't it wild that open the same year as California Adventure?
Yes. It's you know, I've actually been I think I've been saying the wrong date.
I think I've been saying 2002 on the show for a while.
It was literally the same year, six months after California Adventure.
And we get the soap opera Bistro and they get the this beautiful Mediterranean Harbor and they get like the you know this thing that like wildly over invents the Autopia or the motorboat cruise or totally original mythologies.
And and if you I also think I think you could have an incredible day at Disney Sea and never go on a ride.
Yes, that's for sure.
Yeah.
And maybe you did find this.
The one criticism I would hit with Disney Sea is maybe it's missing like one or two e-ticket rides.
But I can see that.
But but also just being there is the ride.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, and now they're there.
It's absolutely mind blowing that they're adding soren.
They're adding I don't know what's going on ride wise, but they're adding frozen tangled and Peter Pan and another new Peter Pan thing that is not the main Peter Pan's flight ride.
Right. And has to be like I think Tony Baxter, I was listening to some old season pass interview with him on the season pass podcast, which you should go back and I listen to those like every six months, I think I listen to him on the flight.
Yeah.
Barnes, thanks for the interviews.
Yeah. So I think he was talking about like they were years ago going like what if we did like a crazy ticket Peter Pan.
So like a full scope Peter Pan with like the I guess probably like a Cars Land scope maybe.
I don't know.
You didn't say that specifically, but aren't they also getting the Beauty and the Beast?
Yes, that's coming to animatronics Disneyland.
That's going in.
Oh, yeah.
OK, as is a big hero six thing, which is not like a crazy ticket thing, but it's sort of like Luigi's Rolican Roadsters.
It's one of them.
I like those kind of attractions.
It looks really fun.
And something else.
I forget what.
But these parks are going to be unstoppable.
Yeah.
There's so much shit.
My like, yeah, the only criticism I could say was like, oh, be nice to have like two more giant rides.
You got to go on.
And then it's like, oh, well, in two years, I'll have that.
Yeah.
Like, I guess are three, two or three.
They're way ahead of you.
How cool is it also to think of going backwards and Disney not saying, well, we already have a ride of this.
Thinking, well, yeah, we have a ride.
But why don't we do a crazy ride of it?
Yeah.
Which is sort of what Star Wars is in general.
There is a Star Wars ride.
We've had it since the 80s.
But hey, what if we did a shitload more?
It's a pretty exciting area to think about.
Well, there's already I mean, it wouldn't be Mr. Toad, although certainly I'd love a car's size of Mr. Toad.
That would be the greatest.
But it's a little like they did.
I mean, I guess you could argue the Snow White minecart is a little bit.
Absolutely.
I don't know.
It leaves something to be desired, but it's very cool.
It's a very cool ride.
So they've they've dabbled in that.
I mean, they have a little luxury, a little bit more autonomy and freedom with the Oriental Land Company.
The company running it pays.
I don't know if the term legal term is licensing, but, you know, there is another company helping run Tokyo Disney that operates a little independently from this.
Uses Disney Imagineering.
Yeah, kind of does their own thing and I believe is partially funded by the Japanese government as well.
You can definitely feel just the infinite pockets of that place.
Yeah. And like what I can only imagine being an Imagineer.
I bet like in the way that Tony Baxter speaks very fondly of the Eisner era because they're like, right when he got there.
Oh, my God, I can do I have like endless resource to build whatever I want.
I bet only second to that as an Imagineer was you're getting put on Disney.
See, and there's no restrictions are on you.
Yeah, are off that.
Yeah, because like just those videos of that Beauty and the Beast ride they're opening, you're like, oh, this is going to be incredible.
And it does. Yeah, it does.
Feels it just feels like they know when running that park that like we everything has to hit this level of good.
Like we can't do something shitty and nothing looks shitty.
That's coming. So not in the least.
Yeah, they aren't cheaping it out.
The only this is really we shouldn't get too sidetracked.
There was that rumor that they were going to build a third park over there called Disney Sky, which I was so excited about.
What does that mean?
And then it's and then it was a rumor and it's not true.
They were just going to expand.
But maybe that was in the pipeline at some point, which also I didn't understand.
And I maybe I said this on the show on my Tokyo, our Tokyo episode that I really didn't understand.
Tokyo Disney Sea was because Disneyland and then see, I didn't get that until we were there, I think.
Yeah. Oh, and Disney. Oh, land, land, sea, sky, sky.
So satisfying. It's so satisfying when I've explained it to people.
Oh, my God. It's land and sea. That's so clever.
Right. It's and I was like, oh, my very cynical people have been like, oh, I love that.
That's so cool. And these on Tokyo Bay like has a practical reason.
Yeah, man, there are views where especially the probably the prettiest zone.
Well, there's the ship is amazing to be on the New York area, but also the area with the aquatopia.
If you're on the if you're waiting for the train that takes you to the New York area, actually that whole train ride,
you have like all of the water internally in the park and they have arranged the views to where it looks like an infinity pool.
And it just goes and goes forever, even though there's a monorail and a service road back there.
There is no it does not connect to the literal ocean, but it looks like it does.
And that's where it feels like it is a beautification project for the city.
Long Beach could have had this. Yes. And I mean, whatever.
I mean, I like what we end up ended up with. But the chili is yes, that's the ultimate beautification.
Outlet Mall empty on Black Friday, a dome where an old insane man's plane used to be and now Carnival Cruise Line boarding and luggage is happening.
It's absolutely insane. And what was the hell was I heading for?
It's it's it's just jaw dropping.
And well, here's the other thing I could say about why I was incorrect about two days and what I can see now.
If you were entirely about getting the rides done, if like if like we're going to do the park, we're going to finish this park,
then you were going to war in that way. For sure, you could do it in two days.
You could maybe do it in less. I don't know.
What I forgot was all the other dimensions of the theme park experience that I never do that in my two rides and wine style of visiting now,
which I cherish very much, but it is a different thing over there.
And there's all of the other stuff that I never do in theme parks.
And let me go through these really fast.
I just a couple areas. And then I haven't said, by the way, from the name of the episode, what we're going to end up doing to keep me on track.
So I don't just ramble forever and ever.
I have isolated what I consider the top 10 rides in Tokyo, not just the Disney resorts, but everywhere else.
And I am calling it rides, but they're not all rights.
I think what I know to are all rights.
I would also like to hear a little about your trip itinerary in general, how you thought about planning it and that sort of thing.
Sure. I can go into that.
I like what I did. As I said, the time of year that I went, I think we ended up with five nights Tokyo, two nights Kyoto, three nights Disney.
I would probably, you know what? I wouldn't even take it away from Disney. I'd just add to Kyoto.
Kyoto is incredible. It would be boring for me to explain it, but oh my God, go to Kyoto, holy shit.
And especially if you can find we were on our way to a bamboo forest that we didn't end up going to, but we stumbled into a park where you can visit monkeys.
There is a hill that you can climb and the top of it is covered in monkeys.
And we thought about having a whole like half day to our trip to go to wherever it is where you can see monkeys bathing in hot springs.
But some people told me that that is a little sad.
Somebody went and said it was a bit of a bummer for some reason.
And that kind of turned me off. Macaques are the type of monkeys, the like red faced monkeys that are primarily in Japan, I think.
But this gave me the taste of monkeys that I wanted.
And you're climbing a hill and you're wondering what the hell is this?
And you're seeing like really confusing warning signs that's like, OK, if you see this face, the monkey is scared.
And if you see this face, the monkey is angry and you're like, those look like the same face.
I don't know what you're telling me. And then we climb.
And it's so steep. It is so much walking and people are coming down and saying, oh, good luck.
And what are we? Oh, no. What are we heading for?
We get up to the top. Huh. I wonder if we're close to the monkeys.
Like big old monkey fight breaks out, spills down the hill.
And we just like back up like I'm as cowardly looking as I could possibly be.
We think about just turning around. All right, we'll just eat shit on that monkey money.
We won't see any monkeys. But we were brave and we got to monkey summit.
And there's there were no other fights. We just happened to see the one that happened.
But it is this incredible city view that you were ignoring because there were 80 monkeys around just walking all around you and getting up on the binoculars.
And like playing with them and turning them of all varieties.
A wise old monkey, a cute baby monkey. It's one of the best things I've ever done with golden sunlight just drenching down from the top.
So go to go to Monkey Mountain. That's not the name of it, but it's certainly what I'm calling it.
Conquer Monkey Mountain and go to Kyoto in general.
So I would do more Kyoto now and maybe a little less Disney, but maybe not.
The one other thing I can say took a bullet train from Tokyo to Kyoto.
The bullet train was going so fast and I'm looking at a map and I'm seeing it quickly were plowing through these cities.
And I thought, you know, at this rate, we would be at Osaka in 15 minutes. Oh, and my wheels are spinning.
And I think, well, we're cramming a lot of theme parks into this trip because there's things I haven't even mentioned yet that I did.
And I'm like, you know what? Now that I know the speed of this thing, maybe I need to go to Universal Studios Japan.
I get I tell Aaron what the bit my wheels are spinning. She rolls her eyes, but it's like, you're right.
No, you're right. Yep. Yep. Yeah. All right. Maybe you're right. Maybe you're right.
I'm thinking of everything. I asked Justin Michael the time zones hooked up.
I was like, would this be crazy? I don't know. I don't think it'd be crazy. It'd be pretty cool.
Jaws and and then I looked at the refurbishment schedule. T2 was down. Oh, and that was enough to break the tie for me because that's like the main thing.
I like Jaws. I like back draft. I like everything else they have. But seeing T2 and we just recorded an episode of that T2.
It was up. Yeah. Would have been really it was the first day it was closed. Yeah. I missed it by one day.
Well, there was a crazy and I'm regretting this now is that when we were there, there was a crazy Halloween thing going on like a weird haunt.
You know, like I there whatever their horror nights is. And it was like you have to know Japanese to do it, which we couldn't do it.
I was like, could we still do it, though? Well, in the summer, they have like a full on like anime like theming like re theming some rides, anime pop ups like.
And it's like for some of the months it's like Lupin and I forget.
I think it is Detective Conan in some languages and then other times it's Attack on Titan.
And so like it changes. They change it up. They do like this thing lasts a few months, but then halfway through, it changes again.
Like so it's a whole like short run sort of thing. Maybe this is that you this is still an area that either might be my being the first person to to go to Universal.
I thought like how proud would I be to surprise you guys? Yeah, that would be great.
That would take a photo under their city walk. King Kong and their Spider-Man photo op where he's like hanging it down.
I mean, I feel like you got to go because they have Spider-Man 2.
Yeah, if you can if you can make sure nothing's closed, they also don't have whatever the crazy I think it's called Space Fantasy, whatever replaced E.T., which I hate, obviously.
But whatever that is looks cool. But that was down to so I think next year if you see your thing after Nintendo opens.
Yeah, yeah, I can see why.
I mean, I want to go take your son have a nice three of you or just the two of you say three is fun.
Three is a fun. There are no one has any qualms about three. Yeah, I really am interested by Japanese baseball culture.
So I would want to take in either a game or yes, yes, Tokyo Dome.
I'll say I did go to Tokyo Dome City. We texted about that a little bit.
And it was during a baseball game and I thought, do I do it?
And then I turned around and I saw the line. It's one of the craziest lines I've ever seen for anything in my life.
So I did not see it. It's supposed to be very intense.
I think if you do it, book a baseball game six months in advance.
Oh, yeah, for sure. They even have standing room, which sounds like a nightmare.
And I read Yelp review. It was like it is a nightmare.
So do it with some foresight. Yeah, maybe you got to go.
Everybody's got to go. If you're listening, you got to go.
Everyone find a way to go. It's so fucking great.
So I was on my way to the non ride things that are why you need to go, which are in a couple categories for me.
Characters. I don't meet the characters I never do.
Only in the rare rare occasion am I like, oh, let's get a picture with many.
You have no choice. You got to meet characters, especially when you walk into the really before their main street world.
Bizarre starts. If you just the courtyard at the front of Tokyo Disneyland,
every once in a while there's just this explosion of characters unrelated, just 12 of them run out.
And do you do people just get up in a line? No, they cluster around the characters
who somehow manage to keep track of who was the last to walk up to them.
It is like seeing a celebrity get mobbed by autographs and they like make time for everybody.
It's crazy. I don't think I saw that happen. That's I mean, there's lineups too.
You wait 90 minutes to meet Duffy or whatever. But these little like character street parties,
I was thinking how so many advertisements for Disney parks over the years have been here's,
you know, like you're partying in the streets with Mickey and Donald and you then you get there
and it's as formal and functional as it could be. This really felt like I'm at a street party
and I don't know who I'm going to turn around and see. I had a great time with the following characters.
Easter Dale, as I said, the gray aristocat, Captain Hook and one of the three little pigs.
I have photos that I will cherish and really good times with all of those characters.
Do I care about any of them? No, I don't like the I don't know which one.
I do boy chip and they're pushing Chip and Dale really hard right now.
They're pushing rescue Rangers really hard right now. Yeah.
Japan and it was exciting to see and I bought a gadget and it's great.
But like these who cares characters were so much fun.
The gray aristocat like grabbed two girls from the crowd and like kind of like like put his hands up to his head
and like spun around like he's they're driving him crazy and he grabbed the girls and walked away with them.
Like you're coming with me and then he backed up to Aaron and added her to the mix too.
So I lost Aaron to an aristocat and then and lots of little things like they're pointing at people's toys
and a girl walked up and had the gray aristocat on her bag and he was like, yeah, there we go.
And then he pointed at a different one that was not him and went no boo. Get out of here.
And then back to him and the character bits are just a blast.
Aaron got to meet Susie and Perla the Cinderella mice who we've had sensed that they have an odd amount of presence in Tokyo Disneyland.
I wonder if we'll get to meet them. We were literally the line was cut off.
We did not. We couldn't meet them, but they saw Aaron losing her shit and they came up to her on the way out.
Both hugger. She said, you're my favorite. They keep so much they like did.
I'm not worthy to her like Wayne and Garth. Wow. Magic.
All of the character performers are incredible.
A pure land, too. It's just like the it's it feels like an elevated art.
It's more like mime or something like these people are so good not to insult anybody.
There's great characters in in the US parks, but holy shit characters.
Characters bathrooms. Oh, yeah.
We just released our tangled bathroom episode. Mike, you were talking up Tokyo bathrooms.
Absolutely right. Oh, my God.
The love, the degree of cleanliness, the seat warming, the options.
If you need a little extra cleanliness help while you're in there, the parks are crawling with children.
I think the US parks have pretty good bathroom cleanliness considering.
However, these are facilities that thousands of babies are going in and out of every day.
So they just are what they are. I didn't smell shit anywhere, probably in the entire city, but especially the parks.
How do they manage that? I mean, I think it's a combination of a very diligent janitorial staff and everyone cleans up after themselves there.
Yeah, it's a much different. There's not as much litter on the street.
There's not that many garbage cans. I don't know if you noticed that around, which does that encourage you to like, hey, hold on to this and throw away, throw it away when you can.
I think that's absolutely. I think, yeah, it's like you carry it home as opposed to so there's no psychological way.
Like, I think you just get used to either not taking a cup with you from the restaurant or you hold on to it so you get home and discard it.
Yeah, yeah. You're annoyed at first. I want to throw it away now.
But then it makes you do it in a place that can handle it. Yeah.
So it's a combo, probably. You know, it's the other thing.
It's a sanitizer for the seats. Oh, yeah. You don't just put down the paper.
You don't say I hate the crumpley paper that you sit on in the bathrooms.
I did so. Those are awful to sit on. Yeah.
They they have essentially hand sanitizer.
You put it on some toilet paper, rub down the seat and then you sit on the seat.
Why isn't that standard practice everywhere? I would like a robot to do that, though.
I don't even want to. Sure. I mean, there's those weird ones that are like plastic that you hit it and it like it's like a conveyor belt that goes around.
Have you seen those? No, no. I don't know. I've seen these a couple of times.
I don't know where specifically, but it's like the seat is covered in plastic.
You hit a button and then it goes like new plastic like rotates around, but you can't tell if it's just the same plastic.
There's no real way to know unless it was covered in shit.
And now it's not. That would be the only way you would know.
You see in hotels a lot now. Their remotes are like, what's the term?
Like bacteria resistant or whatever TV remotes. Oh, I don't know what that they've coded it in something like it's anti-microbial.
Is that what it is? But but you see that every now and then because you always hear about like, oh, the dirtiest parts of hotels like the TV remote.
Aaron sprays them down. That's the first thing she does when she gets anywhere. Makes sense.
Yeah, they can have cleaned all the surfaces, but the thousand people have touched that remote.
The first thing I do, maybe less nowadays because I'm on my phone all the time.
But like when I was younger, I would just as soon as I walked into a hotel room, turned the TV on like without even thinking.
And my parents would tease me about it because you get TV that's not your TV channels or an information channel.
Most importantly, the Holy Grail HBO is good, but an information channel that loops every hour.
There's that time in Vegas when you had to leave the dinner early at the bachelor party because you were feeling a little ill.
And we came back and you were asleep. But the king of Queens was on the TV.
I was probably looking for the information channel and dozed off before I got to it.
It was also the time was about 1030 p.m. Yeah, it was about 10th. I thought it was five in the morning.
But I had a layover in Vegas, like an unexpected layover where they put you up at night.
And that was what I settled on to like fall asleep to. Oh, man.
I checked my luggage, too, so I didn't have another change of clothes.
So I was just like joylessly sleeping in this this strange hotel with like the Vegas information channel on.
I have watched informational videos about the Mandalay Bay Dolphin encounter more times than you can count.
Sure. It never changes. There's no.
I don't want to do the dolphin encounter. I just want to watch this.
Some dull person. Dolphins love being in the desert.
It's really better for them. Yeah. And it's the blubber.
I don't know if they have blubber. What are my what are my categories?
Oh, oh, merchandise. I don't shop in the parks here.
And so much of the merchandise is generic, but they're it's cute stuff.
And it's like one of a kind. If there's something on a ride, you're probably this is if there's some components to a ride that you like, there's probably a toy of it.
And you can and you like I got to have I need to have some little trinkets or a member of this unique experience I had spent so much time shopping.
And and to that end, I've come back with some things for the both of you.
Oh, I feel bad because I get a duffel. I got you such a little thing.
You got a little thing from it. 82 was great. I'm still eating the candies.
I have one. I have one little this is a little thing, but I converted some yen coins into Country Bear Theater.
Oh, oh, crushed yen. What's that? Crush yen. Is that what it is?
So, yeah. And you weren't crushing American pennies. No, it was. Yeah, yeah.
Would have been would have been a little hundred. And these are and specifically for Mike Trixie and for Jason, the Sun Bonnet Trio.
Oh, I'll hand those over. I can also hand these later.
Get them now. But let's see for these are nice. Not bad.
Not bad. Right. And very specific. And like it's not just of the theater in general.
Choose your character. I hope I chose well. Oh, yeah. We forced Jason to be associated with the Sun Bonnet Trio before.
My girls. He likes it. For Jason to commemorate your taste in rides and your taste in treats.
I have for you a little a die cast, a one four or five scale Mark Twain.
There's these wonderful little there's little vehicles.
There's a massive collection and even like a catalog of them. And they're so cool.
They have them for the monorails for the buses that take you to the hotels.
They have for the ride, the journey into the center of the Earth vehicle.
I bought a bunch of these things. I think they're so cool. But I got one of the Mark Twain.
And then I liked this a lot.
A this is a plastic churro that is also a pencil on the inside.
Wow. Vaguely Mickey ear.
Also, if you look at it down there, I like that a lot.
Tokyo Disney Resort, where dreams come true in in churro form, the multi-use churro.
Oh, sorry. Well, we'll see.
And for Mike, I mean, here, brighten your home with this and share this with Lindsay.
But a a tiny plush of our beloved Shandu, the most adorable character here.
I shall hear you very much. Shandu, good luck on your journey to Mike's arms.
Hey, you survived. Congrats on your journey.
Thank you for Shandu that and then and as requested.
Oh, you specifically requested item, a T-shirt.
Well, I'm for sure Venmo. Which is, oh, no, let's call it a gift.
It's from the Tokyo Disney Resort.
This is a shirt that is an exclusive thing that Mike wanted, which is a what?
It's a pastel design of Mickey of of Mickey bars.
Very detailed Mickey bar.
Yeah. So the Mickey Mickey like not ice cream, but popsicles essentially.
But it's his head and they're different colors and they're all over.
And I follow it on Instagram.
There's an account that just posts when new merchandise pops up in Tokyo Disney.
That's how I knew about this.
So I it popped up like you're there or you were going to be there in a day or two.
And I said, I want this.
And you said, like, if you happen to run into it, I figured I couldn't miss this.
And I saw it the first night. So thank you very much.
I won't throw this. So I'll deal with that.
But that's just a design. They don't sell those kind of popsicles.
They do. They do. I have a picture.
One of my pictures, I think I posted on Instagram.
I'm eating that same popsicle. Oh, really?
I didn't realize that because they're very similar to I think someone posted on our Facebook group
and all those old Mickey popsicles that was like Mickey Donald, Minnie and Goofy.
And there were the different flavors and they were the full body.
You remember those? So like I have a great affection for those.
And this is close because it's just a head. Right.
And it's pretty detailed for a popsicle. It's a pretty fun design.
Many, many colors are presented. We'll post a photo of it.
Get one if you go there.
And, you know, speaking of treats, that's the thing to discuss.
But here's what we'll do. Let's let's take a quick break.
And when we come back, I have several mini lists, one of which is my favorite treats of the trip.
And then Scott's Tokyo top 10, the best rides in the city of Tokyo.
Welcome back. Let's continue our journey.
Good luck, Mike and Jason, on our journey through my trip.
So I'm so here we go.
I in order to sort of guide this discussion so I don't just a ran rail forever, I've picked out.
And it was tough to do as tough to do as as navigating the fake rock final four.
Tough to narrow it down to what I consider the 10.
I mean, I guess I'd call them the 10 best rides, but it's also it's a highly subjective list.
It's definitely it's the 10 rides I had the most fun on during my vacation.
But before that, I have a couple of mini lists, which I'll try to make go a little faster.
But one of one of those lists is is treats.
Another thing I'm I'm the least treat of boy of this treat boy laden podcast.
And but, you know, in Tokyo, you couldn't help it.
Everything's everything looked fantastic.
Everything had a giant line and you knew that wasn't arbitrary.
It's not just them being fetishy about we have to try everything.
If there's a line, it's got to be good.
And it was I was always right on.
You know what? I'll also give this update.
Anytime Tokyo's come up, I've been I've expressed concern for Aaron.
My wife is a vegetarian.
And how is she going to fare in Tokyo in general and especially in the parks?
Great. Did great.
There are very few vegetarian options, I will say that.
But vegetarian curry, curry is really good.
There's so much curry in the park.
I love awesome that as their hamburgers or whatever.
That's a that's a great trade off.
That's fantastic.
So and a really good margarita pizza at this sit down restaurants in the Mediterranean area.
Vegan might be tougher.
Vegan is probably very tough.
But vegetarian, we did all right in the city in general.
She had some of the best food she's ever had, quite literally, I think the best pizza we've ever had, which sounds crazy.
I think it is true at a place that I don't remember the name of.
It's in the Nakameguro area and it's on the show Ugly Delicious with David Chang.
I think I'm getting that right.
Look it all up if you want good pizza, Neapolitan pizza in Japan.
It's unbelievable.
But so Disney treats.
I'm going to do these just as three.
Number three, Little Green Dumplings.
Little Green Dumplings, the name for the mochi.
The Toy Story alien mochi, which was very good.
Not like mind blowingly good, but a pretty neat snack.
Are you guys aware of the familiar this?
Did you do it?
Mike? Yeah, well, I didn't do it.
I had a good atomic mochi.
Oh, I didn't do that.
I'm jealous of that.
Yeah. Oh, boy.
I didn't do any good atomic food and we didn't really eat in Sanrio.
The food wasn't so great, but I like that mochi.
Thank you for you gave me that heads up and we just went to like a adjacent food court in that area.
That's another thing in Japan.
Food court food.
All good convenience store food.
Good train station food.
You sent us a picture from 7-Eleven where we posted one and I wanted to hear it's great.
The food is great there.
I mean, you your picture was very funny because it was men's dress shirts next to pornography.
Oh, yes. I was switching back and forth between how quickly you could get from a nice dress shirt to kind of raunchy pornography and then just like great rice treats one step away.
Salary men work long hours.
They kind of need everything in one spot for the convenience.
Yeah. My favorite 7-Eleven treat was the Coke that was flavored to lemon and vitamins.
Vitamin vitamins.
What's the flavor of vitamins?
I don't know. It's just a lemon and vitamins.
So I got it.
Did you do any like hot food from 7-Eleven?
No, I didn't.
I didn't either, but it all seemed good.
I didn't McDonald's admittedly.
Oh, we did too much McDonald's.
Really? Good stuff.
Oh, yeah. I mean, it's not too different.
Not like incredibly better.
I did get like an interesting like tea with turmeric in it or something like an iced tea with turmeric.
They had some cool drinks, but nothing like crazy.
Turmeric.
What did I call it?
It's cummeric.
Oh, cummeric.
Yeah.
Did you do like sodas?
I think like I'm not a soda person even in like weird unusual ones, but I'm told the sodas in the park are cool.
I feel like I did a little of it, but nothing crazy.
Nothing. I was like, oh my gosh.
Okay. Okay.
Well, yeah, a little green dumplings.
Not oh my gosh.
Anyway, you get a little like plastic dish of three mochi and you don't know what flavor it's going to be till you bite in.
But it's I think we got all three.
It's the Neapolitan.
It's strawberry chocolate vanilla.
And they're very cute and a lot of fun.
Good treat.
Number two, a potato churro.
This familiar to you?
You didn't do this?
This was at a cart inside the volcano and a big old line.
And we wondered what the hell's up with that.
It's got to be good for something.
They like come out like in and out and they like, okay, now what do you lives like a preorder situation?
It's that level of intensity.
I don't this.
I think you would both love the potato churro.
I wrote down notes.
It's kind of salty on the outside and then soft and potato we on the inside.
So it's like churro texture, but more like the innards of a French fry.
People say it's like a giant French fry.
But I found it to be almost also a little bit like if you gave like if you let the best chef in the world make a Domino's bread stick, that's interesting.
It almost sounds a little like a can ish.
Oh, I think so.
Yeah, I'm not super can ish familiar, but that sounds right.
Yeah, really unique and odd.
But all the they had like they had a Nemo colors churro like bright orange over by the Nemo ride.
That was fantastic.
You can't go wrong.
I don't even you don't even need to listen to my top three.
Just buy anything you see and it'll be great.
But my number one curry popcorn.
Did you do popcorn?
We had chocolate popcorn.
I don't think I did the curry popcorn.
We did a few.
We did honey over in the poo area.
We did caramel and they're all great and they all make the park smell great.
Anytime you're passing by a popcorn cart.
Oh my God.
There's also like release whatever they consider an Easter smell before the Easter show starts and great smells throughout Sanrio Pureland to like so I could I could have ranked the smells, but I'm not prepared for that.
But curry number one, this like savory popcorn.
So you need chocolate.
I think I'm trying to remember.
Maybe we had one other flavor, but it was not curry.
That sounds good.
There's so much curry there.
Yeah.
So you don't want to go overboard with curry.
And yet this was, you know, so you know, there seem to be like a soy sauce one.
There were a couple of some like Chinese barbecue kind of popcorn.
But I didn't I didn't know how big of a deal the popcorn is.
How big of a deal the collector things.
You can get your popcorn in a Mark Twain and you carry it around your neck all day.
Sounds good.
Would they fill it with egg custard because custards are big there, right?
Too, because I they are.
Yeah, I don't know if I had any custard in the part.
I feel like I had decent custard somewhere in Japan.
But I think you'd be able to find a way or after the day's over, go to 7-eleven.
Just DIY.
I want your custard into that Mark Twain custard and like red bean.
I love red bean as like a filling and stuff and curry and right.
Like if I knew how to make this stuff, like I should learn how to just make it because I would like eat some of the stuff every day.
Yeah, I could.
I know me too.
And it also feels like even though you're like stuffing yourself, it feels healthier on some level.
Yeah, the freshness of everything.
I think just less processed food, more fresh stuff.
I am fighting every urge I have to become that guy who's like, well, so I've just been in Japan.
So I'm doing I'm sort of I'm eating differently because I don't want all that, you know, all that stuff.
It's not good. I'm like and putting I like tempted to put lanterns up in my apartment.
I'm like, I'm teetering.
I'm becoming the worst.
We were doing that bit for months.
All fairness.
It is the country that invented cup noodle as well.
So like, you know, not swings both ways.
Swings a lot of things.
Not everything is the highest taste.
So what you're saying is you don't want to go to the sushi restaurant.
We discovered after this that says like happy hour half off and the happy hour runs from noon till 10 p.m.
It's like so it's half off.
So that's just your prices.
That's your prices for your operating hours.
It's not so much happy hour.
I like that place.
I like it too.
I just think it's funny that they're like half off during the special time.
Trying to trick us.
I don't know if I'm going to like the taste because it's like you're getting fresh fish when you're in Tokyo.
Well, we were watching we were watching and this is a very popular anime, but my hero academia, which is which is all it's hot topics main display.
Now, if you go by in the mall, hugely popular, Lindsey was like, I don't know.
I really got an anime and then we were watching it.
She's like, you know, now that we've been there.
Yeah.
Oh, did it get you on that train?
Well, it's a little bit like, you know, we're kind of like more familiar with the culture now and like, you know, so like it is that's real.
But also like very aware of how annoying it is, how annoying we could be of like, you know, it's a little more connected to the culture.
So like we really like the music and the art that's produced there.
You were skating the most delicate line.
It's exactly where I'm at.
I do not want to be an off putting dude.
Maybe I just have to do it in my own quiet ways.
Yes.
And actually, really what I mean, I can tell you what it means for Aaron, which is she's very committed now to find out way more about the mythology of the anime.
The mythology of each and every Sanrio character.
Oh, yeah.
Less of a lifestyle thing and more about what's that tall carope?
What's his deal?
Yeah.
And she will know.
And we'll talk about it soon.
Hey, wouldn't be Scott Gardner trip report if I didn't rank the three best drinks.
Oh, hell yeah.
The trip.
Number three, the Manhattan at the Teddy Roosevelt's.
I didn't get it.
On the boats.
What do you have there?
I can't remember the name.
It was like a fruit.
It was like a fruit purpley drink with sugar on the rim.
Really sweet, really great.
I'm trying to remember the other one.
There was one other one I had and I can't remember lemon drop anywhere somewhere.
Yeah, but not there.
Yeah, that's like not my genre of drink, but I would like I liked it when I had it.
You know, it was first of all, I also to thank you, Mike.
I might have missed this Teddy Roosevelt's lounge.
I might have been unaware of it.
Had you not talked it up?
The downside of this is that it is demonstrably a better drinking location than even my beloved
Cartay Circle lounge.
Yeah, I think.
Did you did you sit in the main room or did you sit closer to the bar?
We the main room.
Because that's we were by the bar and it's a little less good over there.
OK, we see we thought about going back and bad because you want to sit by those bear pylons.
Yes, in the big area is that we were like, that was probably the place to get seated.
Yeah, yeah, I think it was it was it was pretty good.
It was pretty.
I walked around and I took pictures of all of the Teddy.
There's a little teddy bear.
Just nice to pay tribute to T.R.
Of course, while in Japan, the the only thing that I could take solace in in this excellent
drinking location is that it was certainly no Cartay, Manhattan.
It was nice and a great place to dance more.
Why I'm putting it on there.
It's not as if it was an incredible Manhattan, but a great place to get a drink.
Just a blast.
Erin was pointing out we were in the in line for that bar and she was pointing out just look at the carpet right here.
Even as beautiful as Cartay Circle is, you can feel that the carpet is like a little beaten up.
This place looks like opening day.
There's not one square inch of Disney that doesn't look like opening day.
Yeah, it's wild.
Yeah, yeah.
Incredible.
It's just like a little better there.
Although I will also I'll talk up another thing that we do.
America does better with this.
My number two, the Italian white wine at the Ristorante di Canaletto in the Mediterranean area of Disney.
See, excellent pizza there.
I think I think the only like nice vegetarian meal in the park, but a pretty good one.
And you know what?
I hate to say it.
I think that pizza might have ruined Red Rockets pizza for me.
No, I'm a guest as as beloved as the hamburger pizza is to me.
No, just having like really good pizza.
I mean, there is good pizza, I guess, in the Disney parks.
But yeah, at a sit down restaurant in the you're just you're comparing it immediately to the worst theme park pizza you've ever had.
And I think I've said before, the best pizza is via Napoli or Napoli, whatever it's called in in Epcot and in downtown Disney out here.
It's the same outside restaurant group running the Epcot one is the same.
It is the same people.
I don't know that.
OK, OK, I believe.
Yeah.
And that is yeah, that is excellent.
Yeah, the Epcot one hypes up more that they tried to find the water.
That's a chemical makeup close to the mineral count of Naples.
That I think what I have sensed is that from this really good place I went to that I cannot remember the name of, but it's themed after both twenty thousand leagues type submarines and Beatles yellow submarine at once.
And you take submarine a submarine spiral staircase down to like a Beatles room.
This restaurant in Nakamegaro.
God, unbelievable.
Next time you go, you have to have to go there.
But the this place seems to be very like it's the right water.
It's all there is for ingredients, but it's the best.
And I'm told the pizza has only recently gotten really good in Japan.
And this place seemed like part of that.
Probably.
I thought it was great.
And just nice to have some solid wine because wine, not so good in Japan.
There is one downside.
We are near Napa and in the Central Coast.
It's just better here.
So I'm thankful for that.
I like our man.
I like our wine, but it was nice to have some of that in in Disney.
Also, like everywhere in Japan seems kind of like, do you want the red wine or the white wine?
You have two choice.
Like there's no menu.
It's like which bottle of the two?
There was a tiny amount of selection at this place and it made us very happy.
Beer, very popular in Japan.
Yeah, which is closer to Scotch.
Yeah.
Justin Michael mentioned a place that we ended up going to called Bar Ben Fittich.
It is a very like super like Harry Pottery.
And you just there's no menu.
You just say like what base you want and they'll give you the greatest thing you ever had.
So whiskey is yeah.
Whiskey is killer.
I didn't do a ton of sake.
It was pretty good when I had.
I think I had some decent sake.
Oh, you know, it's another good restaurant in Disney.
See, there's a sit down fish market restaurant in the New York area that looks like a New York fit, an old New York fish market.
And it's like as I think all any fish option at Cartay Circle rocks like every bit is good, maybe better at this place.
So if you're looking for restaurant recommendations, sorry, I don't have the names for you, but go to the fish market once.
Not that hard to find.
But anyway, number one, pretty simple.
The Kirin Ichiban draft inside the volcano.
It's in the bottom level.
It's called the Nautilus Galley.
There's a couple of places you can just get a good draft beer in Disney Sea.
But man, if like when I was if you're chasing that beer in the cars area vibe shit crazy good beer real just simple like I don't know.
There's only one option and they knock it out of the park.
I think there's like a frozen kind to where it's a little bit like ice cream or something.
Yes, I think here in like pioneered that.
And I think it was a thing like Dole Whip.
You could only get it like two places like you get it in Japan or you get it at the Japanese Pavilion and I've caught.
But now I think it's branched out because I think I saw it for sale on like Fairfax.
OK, interesting.
Is the Japanese food is this the Japan Pavilion good food wise?
I think you change it.
There's a new restaurant going in there.
I think that's right.
I don't know.
I haven't had too much at that Pavilion.
I haven't really.
I mean, all of the times I've gone next time.
Curious how legitimate.
Do you guys know this fact about Tokyo Disneyland that there's there was this weird thing.
Meet the world that that's it's what was there before Monsters Inc.
Ride and seek and it was their American adventure.
It looks deathly boring.
Yeah, robots telling the history of Japan.
I've heard of it, but I don't know much about it.
I don't really either.
This pretty hard to watch video on YouTube.
There seems to be an animated stork and the robots seem very good.
But boy, does it seem dreadfully boring.
And the issue with this attraction was always they tell the story of Japan and then they speed you up to modern times.
And they briefly nod to we had some dark years, but then it got better.
And everyone always was like, this is pretty tricky to grace past the dark years.
So it was always an iffy attraction.
I think they wanted to get it out of there.
And now it's a very cute Monsters Inc.
Ride.
But I found this fact out via Jim Hill that they this attraction was developed for the Epcot Pavilion, the Japan Epcot Pavilion.
And they built the building for it.
And it's there.
If you go backstage at Epcot, there's this building that they've never used for anything.
It was supposed to be their American adventure.
And instead they just carted it over to Tokyo.
Wow, that's interesting.
And there's just in fact, because it's the Oriental Land Company, they almost called in the 70s all of the paperwork called Tokyo Disney Oriental or Oriental Disneyland.
Wow.
Yeah, that almost was opened as the probably icky name that would have changed.
I would imagine so.
Anyway, yeah, real good drinks.
And I'll tell you what.
Walking around the volcano with that great beer made me think, well, if beer factored into why I like those those rocks and Cars Land so much, do we screw up?
Maybe we screwed up.
You think Mount Prometheus and all of that is the best?
Maybe I think it might be.
I think I think I had the bias.
I had a hometown bias.
For sure.
We had a hometown bias.
We'll have to see in 2020.
When Jason goes.
I think you could make the argument that Mount Prometheus deserved to be in the last four to for sure.
I mean, that was that was tough in there.
Yeah.
Remember, that was madhouse.
Matterhorn make it to the final four.
It might have.
I think it's a conference issue.
I think if you were like ranking, if there wasn't like pairings, I think Prometheus would have made it.
Yeah.
And I think I mean, look, there were some oversights in the final.
We didn't.
I think we should have somebody pointed out.
We should have put those like blue rocks from Tomorrowland in Orlando in the mix, because those are very fun.
Maybe I've been there.
I've seen them.
They are good and they might belong at least in the bracketing.
So I'm saying there were problems maybe with the bracket, but couldn't be perfect.
I think maybe people are right.
Another one we heard a lot was the Little Mermaid stuff in Florida.
Do you consider it coral?
Perhaps people were even doing the rationale for us.
Well, you can't put it in because it's coral.
But we didn't say that.
You're making up a rule.
Yeah.
That came up with the petrified trees of Black Spire Outpost.
Right.
Well, that's I mean, we'll certainly see.
I'm still very thankful those didn't win a different different ballgame in 2020 with Black Spire Outpost.
And if we've all been to Japan by then, we may need to.
Yeah.
You can cast the final vote.
I at least think it should have been in Final Four, if not final two, if not final one.
I don't know.
Yeah.
I mean, it's pretty jaw dropping.
Skeptical about this Florida Tomorrowland rocks.
I don't know.
I don't know if they blend in with the retrofuturism.
I need to examine them closer in person.
I've seen them.
I like them.
Better than ours.
California rocks.
Let's not talk about those.
It's too dark.
So with that said, I can now head into my top 10 rides.
Finally, we'll be talking about rides.
In this involve, I will include everything in Tokyo, not just not just the Disney parks.
A couple of caveats before I head into the top 10.
As I've said before, Pooh's Honey Hunt was sadly down when I was there.
And I think almost undoubtedly it would be in my top 10.
However, it cannot be as I have not been on this ride.
A good reason to go back.
And there's many of those.
The other thing is we know this like.
All right.
I knew before coming home that I knew that I wanted to isolate at least one attraction and remove it from my main Tokyo episode and put it over on the second gate.
I didn't know what it was going to be, but I figured there's going to be something that I love so much that I can't even take up the real estate of this main episode to talk about it.
And there was an experience so unique, so narratively rich that I can't possibly fit it into this episode.
So I'm declaring right now that we will be doing a second gate episode about the Pan Galactic pizza port, the restaurant in Tomorrowland.
This is non-negotiable, gentlemen.
We will be doing this and as soon as we possibly can, because it's taking everything I have right to not just spill my guts about this thing right now.
I have to contain it.
I have to take a deep breath and save it a little bit.
This is one of my favorite things ever to exist.
I love it so much.
Can you say the name of the character that you like?
Yes.
Why?
In the Pan Galactic pizza port, you follow the the high jinx and the travails of Tony Solaroni.
You also meet his wife.
You meet his mean boss, Mr.
Fusano.
You get to experience his machine in action, the PZ 5000.
And we will be talking about all of this in depth over on the second gate.
So get ready.
I feel you know somebody tweeted an old Disney News magazine article about this thing right before I got there.
They tweeted it at us and I was ready and raring.
I remember seeing this as a kid and I went and found that issue.
So now I know about the making of the Pan Galactic pizza port.
It's so incredible.
We will be doing that on the second gate.
There's a ton there.
I as I said on my Instagram, I think I found my favorite thing of my childhood in my 30s.
Right.
It took till now.
Holy shit.
So we'll see you at the Pan Galactic.
And during which I will also contain my thoughts in general about Tokyo Tomorrowland.
Oh, right.
Holy shit.
And I'll just briefly say here, Rex is a hitchhiking ghost droid.
Thank you for not telling me.
That is a delight.
I think we said that very cool.
That was one of the ways soon as you left.
I think we yelled it.
I know I'm glad I made it out in time because I think we knew we had to keep that one under the head.
But it is we did around the corner and we were like, whoa.
Yeah, yes.
Me too.
As you can imagine.
Oh, man.
And then there's still another Rex.
I oh, boy.
Yeah, there's just there's I'm going to call it number one tomorrow.
And I think it's number one to my really interesting for me for what I'm after.
And Tony Solaroni, that's a small part of it.
So I love that entryway, that blue and white entryway for way the land.
So the spires.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I mean, I feel like that's what they all used to look like.
And they've like kept that classic tomorrow land as they all should have.
What is all this nonsense of having to update it?
As we've said many times, the future is neon.
Just keep it there.
What are you doing?
Tokyo's got it right.
All right.
Let me finally begin the top 10 list and I'll see if I can do this not painfully slowly.
Sure.
All right.
So as I said, this will not include just the Disney parks.
It will not include Universal Studios, but I don't think anything was there that was
open that would have been on the list anyway.
Curious about space fantasy, the ride.
Right.
I don't know if it would have made it.
But number 10, we will start with a non Disney.
And that is and I might butcher the pronunciation of this, the Gekion live coaster at Sega Joypolis.
I have not brought up Sega Joypolis yet.
You didn't go to know is correct.
Absolutely worth some of your time if you're going to Tokyo and next time you go, you got to do it.
Sega Joypolis is like if Disney Quest worked, they if they did it right, if money stayed in the machine,
if they actually change things around, if it was cutting edge technology instead of 20 years ago technology,
although there's still a little of that too, but in a charming way.
Right.
It's amazing.
They've done a great job there.
And it's no wonder that celebrities have spoken so highly of Sega Joypolis on your way out.
You get to see autographs of prominent people who've been there, including Freddie Prinze Jr.
Who visited in 2001 and Leo DiCaprio, who visited in 2000.
So lots of prominent visitors.
I think I want to say Jonathan Lipnicki as well.
So if you want to walk in the in the feet of giants like Jonathan Lipnicki, go to Sega Joypolis.
In general, Sega Joypolis is part of this crazy.
They call it Tokyo Beach and it's this crazy mall zone.
There's so there's a ton of malls and a Madame Tussauds.
And then there was some free exhibit that we walked into where a robot did a drawing of us.
And there was a free VR ride where you get swung around on a miniature kooka arm.
And and there's a mall that has a big Gundam robot outside of it.
And I'd seen photos of this thing and I thought, oh, that's funny.
Big robot outside of a mall did not prepare me for the incredible scope of this.
This robot has to be seen to be believed.
Like it makes you go, why doesn't why don't any of the universal parks have a full size transformer?
That's essentially what this is.
It lets you know this is what it would be like if transformers were real and one of them was about to step on you.
It's and it's just sitting outside of a mall for no reason.
How tall is it? I don't know.
Huh. Could I ballpark it?
It's like two stories tall or not that I think more.
Wow, really? Maybe more.
It looked about as tall as do you know the Maryland in the center of Palm Springs?
Wait, is that there's a big there's a giant Marilyn Monroe.
Really? Yeah.
I've been at Palm Springs. I haven't seen like right in the center, kind of close to the General Store Museum.
Oh, you had to look up that skirt.
Yeah. And it's weird.
Driving a car under. Do you walk under it?
Yeah, you walk around it.
Yeah, it's a little it's a little strange. Yes.
Yeah. Yeah, weird.
Very tall.
Yeah. Oh, that. Oh, the Maryland.
Yes. This whole I recommend this whole area entirely, including Sega Joypolis.
And you can you can buy the rides piecemeal or you can just do them or get a full day pass.
It's cheaper if you go at night.
So we did this three screen rides that are really fun.
Wild Wing, Wild River and Wild Jungle Brothers.
One seems like a ripoff.
Indiana Jones, one seems like a ripoff.
Soren and one seems like a ripoff.
Jurassic Park. We went on the ripoff.
Indiana Jones.
And it's it's a real delight.
There's like a Japanese solo narrating the whole time.
It's like it's better than you think.
Some little indoor ride has a right to be Sega place is great.
There's games in the urinals at Sega Joypolis.
Wow. There is a target that you aim at.
And if you correctly pee on the target, the video screen will live correspond.
And I watched a game where you your character is like Fonzie esque and you were firing snot liquid snot at a nerd.
What? You're like drowning a nerd.
And you're not which is controlled by your pee.
And this is one of like seven options of urinal games that you can play.
So each urinal has a different scenario, essentially.
Yes. You have you got to drink so much water and say good job.
Let's see the energy to play every year.
And I mean, are there games in the female restrooms?
I don't know.
I think you're at a handicap because I feel like right now females have a more difficult time controlling with precision.
Is there a blogger in Japan who's like, well, the was a little concerned about the state of the urinal games,
like nitpicking like Disney bloggers going like, well, there's a bit of disrepair has fallen upon the Mike Finke boats.
Just, you know, the the polygons are not responding as quickly as they should be.
Plus up of those pissing games.
Now that you go to regular urinals, are you like, you know, just like in Tokyo, it's like, it's just like I come on board with a urinal.
It's definitely been disappointed.
There's also there was a Aaron went to a Sanrio Pure Land bathroom that like had a full on light show.
Oh, yeah.
Just like and there was like a script.
There was like a video also that my urine activated at a Sanrio that like where you watch Hello Kitty in space and it starts because I started being it's so insane.
Pure Land is really going to get the short end of the stick in this episode.
Yeah, we'll get to we have to.
I think it did in yours, too.
Yeah, there's so much to say about Pure Land.
Send bad and this we have to know.
We have to shut up.
Yeah, I'm just glad that from now on I can operate from a Tokyo right juncture point in doing this podcast.
OK, but the Gekion life coaster, it's like the heart beach of the facility.
As soon as you walk in, ripping through the second story of this area is a spinning coaster that also does inversions, which I'm told is a rare thing.
I don't think that's common.
So this is just odd little spirited coaster.
It's also a launch sun.
Now that I'm launching, I think it's only my second launch technically.
But I was brave and I don't even like going upside down either.
But man, this thing was so cool.
I think they've like a functional Disney quest.
They have made this park where you can trade the rides in and out easily.
And I think this used to be a shooting roller coaster.
So you're like in the screens, you're moving forward and the screens also moving with you.
And sometimes, you know, when you're playing like a basketball shooting game and it's going back and forth and getting further and further away so it gets harder and harder to shoot.
It's like that with screens like it.
First, the screens right in front of you and then it gets hard.
So it gets much harder to see.
You're trying to catch up with it.
It's kind of a challenging game that you're playing.
It's not a shooting coaster anymore.
It's now like a dance dance revolution where you have buttons under your harness that you have to hit in time and it somehow impacts your ride experience.
I'm not sure how because it's all in Japanese, but like you can change your ride and soup it up more.
The better you do on this thing faster, I think maybe really or it just affects the color scheme.
Like if player green wins, then it's going to be a more green ride that you go on.
It's really inventive.
Are there better rides in Disney?
Probably. But I wanted to shout out Sega Joypolis because it's really well done and really worth experiencing.
I did so shitty on this ride.
I thought I was doing well the whole time.
I got a C terribly grade you.
Erin got a B.
She kicked my ass.
But bad grade, good grade, really good ride.
Recommend Sega Joypolis and the Gekion Life Custer.
Number nine.
Let's start getting into Disney.
I thought should this list only have things you can't do here in America?
Should it only be Tokyo specific?
However, there are some rides that are so much better done in Tokyo Disney than they are in the States.
And I have to honor though they're almost more of a handicap in a way that they have to be that much better.
And one of those is and that is number nine, the Jungle Cruise.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Right. Yeah.
It's more like the Florida Jungle Cruise, which is better than our Jungle Cruise out here.
Oh, I didn't know that.
OK. Yeah.
Because you got you.
There's stuff in there.
Yeah. You go in a little like a tunnel under a bridge.
And that's like, yeah.
And the Florida one is like that.
OK.
So maybe I might be missing out on Jungle Cruise evolution in general.
Yes. I forgot totally when we went back a couple of years ago.
We went on the Jungle Cruise and I went, hey, look at this.
Right. Because out here it's fine.
And I like it going on once in a while.
But it's not in your regular rotation.
No, never.
And I think this one would have to be.
There is so much excitement with the employees.
There's like 20 people wearing khakis on the dock.
They employ more people than most companies in Los Angeles just on the Jungle Cruise.
Everybody's out there so excited you're there.
They get everybody on the car to like yell like I think you like they have pendants of different animals and that you choose.
Are you like an elephant?
Are you a hippo or whatever?
And whatever the sound is, everybody has to make the sound together.
Excited crowds.
They don't do hokey jokes.
They just do like, are you ready?
Here we go.
We're going to see the elephants.
There's music the whole time that gives it this narrative thrust circle of life plays when you see the lions.
And then you go into this incredible projection mapping room.
Is that in Florida?
I don't think it's like that.
I don't think it's to that degree.
The one in Tokyo.
Yes, seems like it's the best.
But I'm trying to remember.
I got my memories fuzzy on it.
So I don't know for sure.
Is did they do the stuff at night?
Because I didn't do this at night, but it looked like it was.
It's really good.
I did it at night.
We did it at night.
So yeah, it was.
Yeah, I'm trying to think.
I can't remember the two of them are now blending together in my head, I think.
So I can't remember if one the projection happens in Florida.
You're talking about like when you go in like the stone, like the whatever you call.
I don't even know what you call it.
Like temple ish kind of kind of a temple.
It's like it's some elephant God.
I don't tell you what happens.
It's just really cool projection mapping and it comes out of nowhere.
It's so neat.
The whole thing just has so much more spirit than the one in Disneyland.
Yeah.
And you know, whatever stupid thing they're going to do to it when the rock movie comes out.
Don't guys don't overthink it.
Look to Tokyo.
Look what they did.
It's just so much more fun.
They only redid it in 2014.
It's pretty recent and they did a great job.
No, no rock robots.
Please no robot.
I know.
We'll see.
I don't know.
It just make.
Yeah.
I P in general, pretty lacking in Tokyo and I'm not an IP snob.
I try to not be an IP snob, but boy, nice to be in a place.
I just I was like every every like sight line is so clear and not cluttered and there isn't
some weird loud temporary way to jam Dr. Strange into this corner of the park or whatever it
is.
Like they aren't at they aren't like screaming at me about Lady and the Tramp for they're
like so much more sparing with all that stuff.
That's true.
Yeah.
I don't know.
No Marvel like anywhere.
Yeah.
Is that because of Japan though?
Is that because of Universal?
They might have agreements are for international because they do have the Spider-Man ride because
they haven't announced anything for Japan for Marvel.
So I think it might be a case of because they can do it in Paris.
They can do it in Hong Kong and Shanghai, I think.
But I do think there's they can't do it in Orlando yet unless it's like Guardians when
they can't do it in Japan.
I think that's right because they would have announced something for it unless Marvel is
not popular there.
I sense that Star Wars is not super popular there.
Is that correct?
I guess I think it's maybe not as popular as it is here, but it's still I don't know.
They haven't announced Star Wars land for Tokyo either.
Yeah, no, they haven't.
In China, it's definitely not as popular.
Yeah, they've had a real problem with that.
Yeah.
You know, because there's like a black actor in it.
That's a problem.
I believe the issue was that they had shrunk John Boyega's face on the poster because he's
like one of the three leads and like he all of a sudden was like in the corner, tiny
in the corner.
Yeah.
We're not going to promise anything, but it's possible this actor is smaller than BB-8.
He may be a little tiny man and you might not even notice him in the movie.
Yes, that's right.
I was reading about a movie called Detective Chinatown 2 in Japan and it grossed five hundred
and forty four million dollars.
Whoa.
So are we going to get rides of that?
Who knows?
Dick Tracy's Crime Stoppers, but with Detective Chinatown 2.
Yeah, maybe.
I'm looking forward to it.
Maybe the general sense of calm and just like the pleasantness of Tokyo is entirely based
on the fact that Star Wars isn't popular there.
Like no one is screaming at each other about this.
They have their own issues.
There might be a few.
Yes.
Anyways, to keep going with the theme of Better in Japan, Indiana Jones and the Temple of
the Crystal Skull.
Yep.
That's number eight.
I thought about putting this lower than Jungle Cruise because Jungle Cruise is a bigger jump.
I felt like I went from like 60 to 100.
Indiana Jones is more like 85 to 100.
But man, it's a good jump.
It's a real good jump.
Yeah.
It's like going on.
And when it first opened, I imagine the track feels nice.
It feels nice and smooth.
Yeah.
It's like operating like at optimum performance.
The car feels better.
The very crisp projections of the bugs.
They don't try to do the weird rat thing that has never worked that well.
There's smoke rats dripping on your car.
That crazy contained tornado when you enter that's lit with blue light.
Oh, right.
Looks amazing.
The head is amazing.
I think the head is probably a little better than Mara in some way.
The head is better than Mara.
I think the main not not in the first tunnel, but in the main ruins room.
Yes.
Yeah.
I think it is.
The only thing I think is better is Mara herself.
Yes.
The big head.
That's the only thing in the skull is cool.
Yeah.
But you're right.
Yes.
The actual big head has more attitude and personality.
Yeah.
But that's it.
I like that they don't do the doors.
I like that you're just committed to this cool room with little like pools of water.
It's the night sky.
It's lit up when you enter that first ramp.
Yep.
What else?
The the bellowing smoke ring monster.
Oh, my gosh.
So cool.
So scary.
Such a surprise.
The sculpted heads spitting the darts.
You don't get day glow Halloween store like decorations.
You get Roman art for some reason spitting darts at you.
It's crazy.
That it's because I think sure we said this is a repeat, but we said like that's always
a part where you talk about the Indiana Jones ride where you go, well, that last stretch
right before the ball is and it's fine.
But it feels like if you're heading to the climax, it should be a little something extra
there.
And this place there is there's a really cool extra angry God that shoots fire at you.
Yeah.
And then there's actually like feeling like a physical presence that's shooting darts
at you.
Yeah.
It just feels more just a better looking room.
It's a more visceral effect because the statues are cool.
And then at the end, Indy, the especially the second animatronic by the by the first
the crushed boulder beat up.
Yeah.
He looks like shit.
It looks like back to their actual Harrison Ford.
He looks like what Harrison Ford looks like if he has to go out in public and speak to
someone.
So upset.
But also more clearly him, I think.
Yeah, I guess that's more like Harrison Ford.
Just better, more kind of spastic animatronic.
So great.
I feel like I had to bump some things that I really liked off the list to put Indiana
Jones on, but I went on a second time.
It's undeniable.
We went on three times.
Geez.
Wow.
Because single riders easy.
Yeah.
Very, very well done there.
So nice that they don't really have that nobody's using that single rider.
What a good little cheat.
Oh, you know what else?
In the line.
When in the lines, not as good as our line because they didn't have to get you all the
way out of the park like they like they do here.
But that room with all the skeletons piled up is just a big old pile like spit out skeletons
as if like a monster took them and just like ripped the skin off like a rib and tossed
them back into the pool.
Oh, like the way I eat fish.
You do it like Heathcliff style.
Like Heathcliff and riffraff.
Yeah, like riffraff.
And then they each bone hits like a xylophone when it heads out of your mouth.
OK, Indiana Jones.
Great.
Number seven, Aquatopia.
Love the Aquatopia.
So strange and unique and weird.
This weird little putt around ride.
It's such a delight.
You don't know what it's going to do when you get on.
It's different every time.
Looks good at day.
We did it again at night.
Really liked it.
I think this should be a franchise in every park.
My I have a new Tomorrowland plan.
We rip out the submarines and the Autopia.
You put in the Aquatopia and Tron.
Perfect.
I agree.
We don't do.
Hey, kids, you want to experience the dream of driving an old smelly car?
Put kids on a clean, like, you know, quiet electric vehicle the way the future needs
to be.
is to survive.
The Aquatopia will show us the way.
But the Aquatopia in the park.
I think that's a good idea.
They're like little Wi-Fi vehicles basically.
And then it's a self-driving car.
Self-driving car.
Thinking because it's also like it's not actually that deep.
It's a very shallow pool.
Yeah.
But that's a good little trick.
You think you're on a real lagoon or something.
Right?
No, I think that's great.
I think it's like the same technology as like the Luigi's Roadsters.
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean, I looked it up the second trackless ride, the first being Pooh's Honey Hunt.
Oh, right.
Still upset.
But there's only five that have actually opened.
Yeah, it's still few.
And then, yeah, Star Wars.
Mystic Man, Red Tetsui, and Star Wars will be.
Yeah.
OK.
They're cool.
I'm glad they're happening.
But this is a very good one.
I love Aquatopia.
At night, we did it once at night.
Very good.
Yeah.
Very fun.
You've got that.
It looks like the best of our Tomorrowland in a way.
The most realized version of weird future past little strips of neon.
That little zone and with the Nemo ride.
Port Discovery, I think it's called.
It is called Port Discovery, I believe.
Very fond of Port Disco.
I don't know.
What's my favorite port?
Probably New York, but well aboard the volcano itself.
I guess it's got to be the volcano.
Port Discovery is, no, Discovery Bay is what Tony's flight thing was going to be at the
Star Wars land is in Disneyland.
So they've stolen Stellatus.
I mean, stolen in a good way from his.
This whole thing feels like this must be Tony's dream.
Like a lot of it feels like what he was trying to bring to the parks.
Yeah.
Prometheus, especially with all the Jules Verne shit that he's obsessed with.
I'm almost glad we didn't hear more of his thoughts on it because I didn't want to spoil.
But he must be very excited about this.
I don't think he worked on it really.
But yeah, I don't think so.
Although who knows?
He could be like they did it all wrong.
He was so funny.
Yeah, because he'll throw stuff under the bus.
I just heard one of those season passes where he was like, he really like let something
have it.
I forget what.
I mean, he was he was he was mad about the name Condor Flats.
Oh, that's a that's a different podcast, I think, which I've also listened to where he
was saying the theming at Condor Flats wasn't wasn't easy to add rides to because in Tomorrowland
or Adventureland, you know what type of rides, but Condor Flats.
What does that mean?
Yeah.
He was kidnapped by a bird.
He also threw some shade at Pleasure Island on that.
That's what I was thinking of.
Yes.
He goofed on the plaques that we goofed on about Merryweather Pleasure and all the backstory.
He's right.
They're disconnected.
It's a fun story.
But yeah, I've I'm of course of two minds.
That's just too much.
Yeah, but let's get the themed attractions podcast.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's what it is.
Yeah.
podcast interviewing professionals.
If you want people who know what they're talking about and know the Imagineers and won't bother
them with dumb ride pitches like we did, listen to that podcast.
And I believe someone who hosts is affiliated with the company that invited us to look at
fake rocks.
Yes, that's right.
Oh, boy.
So preview of a future episode.
You might get to hear us talk about looking at fake rocks.
That's right.
Still develop it.
Yes.
Still in the incubation tanks.
All right.
Aquatopia.
Great.
Number six.
Very excited to talk about this.
Roger Rabbit's cartoon spin.
Oh, interesting.
I didn't do it.
I owe this ride a big apology.
I mean, I don't because the Disneyland version is not what it could be.
If there's a mode, that's the best.
And then B mode and C mode.
I think it's in C mode.
Tokyo.
I was hoping I would have the time.
And here's what happened, by the way.
The first night there, horrible, horrible weather, the only bad weather the entire vacation.
We were like, can we even do this?
Maybe we got to get out of here.
This really sucks.
But we're in Disneyland now.
We're paying for it.
Maybe we should wait it out.
Then rain lets up a little bit.
Everybody goes to everyone in the park goes to watch the projection mapping show on the
castle, thus giving us Fantasyland and Toontown to ourselves.
We were the only people.
Thus Pinocchio, Snow White, Peter Pan, no wait.
I mean, literally, we walked in and sat on the vehicle and it started.
Peter Pan had no wait.
This was insane.
This, I think it helped us do this in less.
Maybe you do need four days if it's crowded as shit.
We had this lucky night where we just jumped on everything.
That is key.
Yeah.
We really missed things for three and three and a half days.
I could see why you would have because on the Saturday we were there, Fantasyland was
a hellscape.
It was horrible.
There was this famous crowded area, the crosswalks, Shibuya crossing, where 19 directions all
cross at once.
There was a part of Disneyland that was much worse than that.
It was just because that's where the fast pass for Small World was.
We could not move.
It was horrible.
But, we got to be there on this magical night where the weather had barely cleared up and
no one was in Toontown.
So, we were in the gag factory by ourselves.
We were in Minnie's house by ourselves.
We just laid down for a while, sat on a nice chair.
I pretended to do the dishes in Minnie's house.
It was great.
But anyway, Roger Rapp was part of that.
I was like, oh, you know what we can do that I bet we wouldn't be able to do tomorrow?
Roger Rapp, I've heard maybe it's better.
It was so much better.
No one was there by that point.
So, the employees were thanking us for picking their ride.
You're here.
Come on in.
Hurry, go.
We still had to do the, even though no one was there, we had to do the entire queue.
But that claustrophobic queue that I complained about for so long, we're in by ourselves,
running through it, looking at everything.
We're in our pictures.
Hey, great.
We have this to ourselves, not claustrophobic at all.
Plus, the lighting's better.
Plus, the paint's better.
Then we get on the ride.
The control you have of those vehicles is incredible.
It's like those in California, they're molasses.
In Japan, it was such precise control that Aaron and I, it's kind of a cab and another
cab and we just each took one to ourselves.
We turned them to face each other.
We were just in the middle of the ride, just looking in each other's eyes for the entire,
you had to adjust a little bit and kind of stay on it.
But we were just locked eyes on this ride.
It was so weird.
The most romantic moment of the trip, obviously.
But we got off and immediately got back on again and they're cheering us.
Yeah, one more.
Everyone in line is celebrating our presence there.
And also, everything worked.
The dip machine worked.
It spit dip.
The shit they haven't done in so long.
It's spinning out of control.
It's bright green.
Every effect looks great.
Roger Rabbit rocks.
I am so sorry that I trashed it for so long, but you do have to go to the Japan one.
Man, that sucks.
It's just a little better.
We had to do it.
Next time you go, yes, I'm sorry to make you jealous.
No, that's okay.
I got to do poo, so we did poo twice.
Oh boy, you got a big one on your list that I don't.
Next time, Roger Rabbit's cartoon spin rules.
Number five, Monsters Inc.
Ride and seek.
It's great.
It's undeniable.
What a fun.
It's good.
I didn't love the flashlight stuff as much.
Oh, how so?
What do you mean?
Too much.
I wanted to appreciate the robots more.
The flashlight is shooting at the robots of the monsters.
I felt like I want to enjoy this more.
Too much busy work.
You could have just sat there.
That's true.
There was no scoring mechanism either.
I wanted a score of some kind.
Well, I think your only reward is making that little ding sound.
If you haven't done this ride, it's sort of like a shooting ride.
But for kids, it's tamer.
It's not a gun.
You have a flashlight and you're pointing at little Monsters Inc.
Ms.
Mostly on hats, but sometimes in other places.
And what it does, I guess, is trigger an effect.
It opens a drawer and you get to see a monster that you wouldn't
see if nobody pointed their flashlight at it.
Right.
But I felt like I was on the spot to do it.
We only did it once, I guess.
I should have done it a second time.
Great robots.
Very good ride.
I just was not as excited about it.
Sure.
That's all I'll say.
Well, then you might be OK with it.
I actually thought you would have the biggest problem with what I'm
about to say.
Heading for next.
I actually thought you would like that ride a lot and that you wouldn't like where I'm
ranking the next ride ahead of it.
Interesting.
But here, I'll just go into it now, knowing it'll be received better.
Number four, Sanrio character boat ride.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
No, I'm not mad about that.
Hey, great.
I thought you would have I was like Michael like Monsters Inc a lot and just that'll
be like too much of a leap.
But we both I think we Monsters Inc, I guess, was a little hyped up maybe for us too.
So I think both of us kind of left it going like, oh, good.
But like I wasn't not like poo or not like any of the other ones.
Sure.
Yeah.
It's really something.
It's yeah, it's the best of it's it's junkie in a lot of places.
It's a junkie, weird little ride.
The end of it is pretty good.
The end of it is like, OK, here we go.
Yes.
All of the characters in their Sunday finest.
If I could describe the story of the ride and you know what?
A lot of places said this is kind of this weird small world rip off.
No way.
It is not that it has a great story.
Hello Kitty wants to have a party.
She sends heart shaped invitations to you in the line and every all of her friends in
the Sanrio universe.
You get to see them all at the magical moment that they got the invitation to her party.
Then they all take flying machines to get to the party, each cuter than the last.
And then you go to the party, which is she's in kind of a wedding dress, but it's not a
wedding.
And her boyfriend is also dressed up, but they don't kiss or anything.
And her parents are there, but it's just a regular party.
Everybody just wanted to see Hello Kitty wearing a nice dress.
And they do.
And everyone goes home happy.
Yeah, it's weird.
It belongs on the list.
It's very strange.
I like how I'm trying to remember now back to it because it's been a little while.
I do feel like the first part of it is like, oh, is this going to be like grow?
There's a gross feeling maybe initially where I'm like, some of these don't feel like they've
been kept up the animatronics.
But I like that too, because you're like feeling like you're because a junkie not kept up boat
ride is fun too.
Although I don't think I felt that I felt the magic.
I felt the I had no problem with the cleanliness.
I felt I don't mean it wasn't clean, but it felt like a little like old.
It felt a little tired maybe initially.
Although it is a revamp, it has not always been Sanrio character boat ride.
Yes, I've read that.
The name is a lot of what I love about it.
I love the bluntness, just the descriptive nature.
A fun ride for you to go on today.
Mm hmm.
Uh, no, I we really liked it.
I got to watch the ride through again to really remember my feelings about it.
It was the last thing we did in the day to we're a little tired, but I was like, oh,
that's great.
We needed to do that.
It's an overwhelming place to be.
Yeah.
What better way to end it than with a boat ride, which I also I love indoor boat rides.
It gave me such shades of, uh, um, the, you know, Norway and Mexico, like claustrophobic
fake indoor sky, even though you're outside.
I love that there's ride scenes and then you're just in the regular lobby and watching people
shop and eat, but you're on a boat.
Yeah, because it goes, it has that feeling of like a weird, not that I've even been there,
but like Mall of America where you're zooming in and out, but it's just, you're going through
normal places, but you're also in like a world, a special world.
So it's, it's inconsistent in what the reality might be.
But then of course there's so many great fake rocks in Piroland.
So you think rocks are good.
You've got all that great stuff.
Fake hill, good, like magic, a little like a fiber optic kind of stars and fireworks
that really come to life during the show.
We will get to Sanrio Piroland.
Even now I feel like I can't talk about it a lot, but really fast.
The thing that bumps this up ahead of some Disney ones is that Disney rides are never
going to give you Japanese weirdness.
And this ride has Japanese weirdness, especially in the area of the character, Bad Batsmaru.
There is a penguin who is mean and has spiky hair and he does bad things in this ride,
legitimately bad.
He's no good boy.
When he, you've seen all these adorable characters get their invitations.
The frogs get their invitations and they're leaping around.
Hooray.
When he gets his invite, he's up to his bad tricks.
He's gambling, he's smoking cigars and very, perhaps in the strangest scene in any ride
in Japan, he is spying on a woman in a dressing room.
She is like, she has, she's like up, she's a bigger woman, I think a cat or something.
And she has, she has like a workout clothes on and he's behind a mirror, like trying
to get a peek.
He's like a peeping Tom.
That's actually on the crest.
So that's on all the money.
If you would look closely at the yen, that's a national pass.
My bills were too small.
If I had had the 20,000, yeah, I would have seen up skirts on the currency.
Really weird, but also very, it feels very Japanese.
The fact that they are a little more like out there with their perversions a little bit
that this children's ride has weird like voyeurism.
So crazy.
It's the, yeah.
I think that's the thing.
Maybe the one of the other things about Tokyo Disney that I was like hoping a little bit
more of that vibe snuck in, which it does in places, but not overall.
Like this, yeah, this feels like, this feels like a totally different tone.
This is a different vibe.
And this is still a children's, supposedly a children's thing.
I watched an anime while you were gone as well, Scott.
Night is short walk on girl.
And it's so fast pace and like mostly delightful.
But then every now and then there is a weird little bit of horniness like that.
So I, yes, I understand what you're talking about.
It's kind of like younger skewing, but like, no, well, it's about like college.
It's about like one, it's a one crazy night kind of movie.
Yeah, it's about like a guy who has a crush on a girl and she's just trying to enjoy it.
They're both enjoying like this nighttime festival and he's trying to get like this
children's book he knows she loves.
And then it gets crazy.
Like there's no, there's very little cohesive plot besides that.
And then there's a crazy gangster.
There's crazy pop up plays happening.
There's spirits.
It's insane.
Like, yeah, there's a little bit of weird horniness.
Kind of.
But I do recommend it was very fun.
OK, neat.
Well, the payoff actually, you know, well, what I'll say in terms of maybe the only place
in Disney where I felt a little more of the like oddness harshness was Pinocchio's Daring
Journey, which is very well done there.
That's Aaron's favorite ride in any of the parks, although probably at this point it's
Sanrio character boat ride.
But she always likes that it's a morality play that people do bad things and then they
get punished.
And that happens in the US one.
But in the Japan one, a lot more cigar business.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like there's like a very long room where you just are down going down cigar alley.
There's 10 different stores.
Indian after giant Indian storefront, smoking cigars.
And then as a result, after that, the children who are turning into donkeys are much sadder.
They are crying thick tears.
They're like gelatinous.
They are so much more upset and just wailing.
It's a much more upsetting version.
Yeah, I remember this too, because it's more like the movie, honestly.
The movie is very upsetting.
Yeah, it's.
And it's pretty upsetting on the Disneyland, right?
But I do remember there was like, yeah, more.
This is much more upsetting than they're much more comfortable with it.
That's how what really feels about actors, right?
Hi, Italy, the actors like for me like that.
But you're near do wells.
Yeah, just like smoke and or Jack brain jackasses.
It's all a metaphor for them.
Them going into Pleasure Island is a metaphor for them joining a union.
Sure.
If you look at just the letters in union or flickering on the pleasure,
or even just United Artists, like you can just like, what do you mean?
They own the play.
What do you mean? Chaplin and Pickford owns the place.
They're all a bunch of fatty our buckles.
Drunken exploits.
So to that end, just like Pinocchio, horrible things happening and then punishments.
Bad Bats Maru spying on the woman.
But then in the next scene, she has him.
She caught him.
He is over her knee and she is spanking him.
OK, that's a heightening punishment.
If I think I don't know much about Bad Bats Maru, but I think he might be
he might not consider that a punishment.
We've got to look into Bad Bats more.
His his backstory and he might have.
Was he in the anime he watched?
He was in Miami, too, for some reason.
Yeah, just just watching fucked up shit.
He just appears in the corner every once in a while.
Then he is at the party, but he's by himself bitterly drinking.
Wow. He looks he's a little like all the other characters are upright and waving.
And then he's sort of leaning against the bar and sort of looks like he's a few in
and teetering. So a ride in which you get to see a bitter drunk.
Yeah, that's great. Something else. Sure.
So that brings us into the top three.
I have little thoughts about other I mean, I could say my honorable mentions
really for we're pretty deep in this episode, I'd imagine. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. I'm getting hungry. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. Well, then let me. OK.
All right. I'll just go.
I'll just go straight to the top three because I'm especially excited about
number three, the Tower of Terror.
I did the Tower of Terror. Wow.
I braved the Tower of Terror.
Thank you for your applause.
I was so excited to tell you that was the triumphant return.
I was in line for Tokyo Disney Sea, wondering, will I do it?
Aaron said, yes, you will do it and you will like it.
All right. Well, that's in a in a person dominating bad bats.
Maru, like a cat bending man, that's a rule over me.
Like a penguin enduring his spanking.
No, she informed me I'd be doing it.
She was correct. Not that bad. Really not.
I hadn't done it. I think like Splash Man, a lot of fear had built up,
although I've also heard it's tamer. Can you attest?
It is tamer. Yes.
Tamer than Florida? No.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, for sure. No, I'm wrong.
Yeah, tamer than Florida for sure.
It feels like the first I know they're doing a crazier thing now.
I think we said it where there's like a for teens where it goes much more up
and down, but it feels like the first ride profile that I ever went on for it.
It's short. OK, feels like a minute maybe or less.
And we were disappointed in it because we're used to like the Guardians
and the one in Florida.
And yeah, we were like, oh, that's oh, we wish it was a little longer.
So, yeah, very tame.
My question now is, but maybe this stepped me up, though, where I could do.
Guardians, guardians.
How big of a leap do you think it is?
Well, I always argue that the worst part of it is the anticipation.
Not that I'm some genius for for arguing that, but and that's what Lindsey says,
too, because it's so like the fear of like, oh, my God, it's going to drop.
And then but that's gone with the Guardians, right?
Because it shoots you right up.
We get a jolt right away.
But that feels like that feeling might be scary.
I'm the wrong person to talk to about that because I love it.
You like launches for that reason.
I'm obsessed with it now.
And it's only in the last couple of years where I've gone on it so much that I like that.
But I mean, yeah, I don't know.
It's just kind of I don't know.
I just find it so fun.
Yeah. And it's anything that I was ever scared about with it was the drop itself.
Sure. So I think honestly, it's like
it is a toot.
I don't know, two times more intense.
A few times. What do you think?
You're distracted by the hits of the 70s, especially.
Yeah, especially. Yeah.
The song starts playing and rocket plugs in and it's like very fun.
I feel like I could do. I might.
I think you can do. I don't I honestly, I don't think.
And I and you know what?
I not only did it the once I did it three times.
I couldn't get enough.
Oh, yeah. So we're going to do this.
All right. And then we'll do the episode.
Yeah, yeah.
The Guardians episode.
Yeah, I probably need to do it before we do.
We'll do it. So when we go to Star Wars land proud, I have a bravery report to give.
And I'm so glad I did.
And the tower stuff is great.
We'll do a whole episode about it at some point.
But the tale of Harrison Hightower, the disappearing idol.
I don't know how they did it. So cool.
This might be one for me.
Yeah, this might be two, actually. I think it's two.
That'd be fair. That'd be absolutely fair.
Yeah. I'd be curious to hear your top three after when I finished mine.
Although I think you would guess.
Well, maybe not. I think I guess.
So, yeah, effects are amazing.
I bought a little shriki keychain.
I love him.
And I only am docking at a couple of points because I don't like when you go into a store
and the character based on Imagineer Joe Rody is presented as a god
being massaged and fed fruit by beautiful women.
I I couldn't disagree more.
I can't imagine anything I would spend on faster.
That's not for sale. You're saying that's decoration.
That's embedded in the wall.
That's what the thing we were upset with with the gift shop is that we wanted some
Harrison puppet or merch or figure.
Same thing with Sinbad. Sinbad doesn't have a plush or a dog or Shandu is everywhere,
but you can't get a good Sinbad toy.
Yeah. And the same thing with Harrison Hightower, where the idol is in there.
But we were like we loved Harrison Hightower so much.
But and is, of course, his manservant, Smelding.
I what's I missed Smelding.
So in the queue, did you do Fastpass all the time or did you?
I did Fastpass.
Oh, yeah, you may have been you may have missed out.
Because when you're we did it twice, we did one Fastpass, one regular.
And there's so much wonderful art in the main
lobby of him pillaging famous things from like
like a piece of Stonehenge or something or him and Smelding Smelding,
like hanging from the basket like this meek looking dude
who is like helping him steal from like Aborigine or aboriginal people.
Like it's such a crazy bit of like amazing paintings
of him just destroying old artifacts and old whatever you I don't know.
OK, so by the end, when you see him, you're happy.
How did in this awful way?
It's like, you know, you know, he's like a villainous.
Yes. And I also think it's crazy.
When we were outside in the queue, there's all these female,
like very busty female statues.
Oh, so like not only is he's like really like Trumpian,
Trumpian building up a heel character.
You're like, oh, this is guy who like thinks he's God's gift to women.
And then you go inside and there's these immaculate paintings of him
doing the worst things to like historical landmarks.
And like he has this like meek
manservant that I believe we want to play.
A listener did some art with me as smelding.
Yeah, I think we said Jason for smelding on the show.
OK, I miss this.
And there's a whole guestbook signed by a bunch of different rich people of the era.
So like going in that main queue, we were just so we were like
wanted more time with the main queue of looking at the art.
Yeah. So by the time he dies, it's totally justified.
He's a total asshole.
So that, yeah, at the end, there's that newspaper clipping of him
with like women and like he's in the old time Scrooge McDuck bathing suits.
And it's like it's such a good it's crazy how much stuff they produced
to build up this guy as an evil shithead.
I am I am a little sorry I missed that.
Huh? Huh? Well, at the same time, it is nice to get a fast pass and not wait.
Yeah, sure.
Especially when you wind up wanting to do it three times.
This is what you're told.
Like you're going to hate it, but then you're going to love it so much
and why can't get enough of it.
And that's what happened to me with this ride.
Well, we'll do that on Guardians, because when we went with Anthony
Geo a couple of months ago, we did three in a row.
Guardians right at the start of the day.
Wow. I'm curious.
I think it'll be a little more.
I think it'll be a little more for me to brave.
But you'll love you love pop music.
So you'll be good at the adventure of what song you'll get.
Yes, true. Yeah.
OK, number two, Sinbad's storybook voyage.
I'm putting it to we've talked about it a lot.
It influenced the trip and made it easier for me to come home.
It was heartwarming. I teared up, went on it twice.
I bought a chandu. I got you a chandu.
I want to remember him forever when he pounces on the drum.
Oh, yeah.
We'll do a whole episode about this.
I will say my thoughts more later.
But oh, my God, the scope of it and seeing this town
supporting each other on both really at the end.
It's also so, so funny how heartwarming it is.
Like we wish you well.
And then he returns and we're so glad you did well.
It is just one note of love for eight minutes.
It's so insanely positive.
Every scene a triumph for Sinbad, every scene.
He faces no adversity.
You've come in at the moment that he has triumphed.
He has. He's probably a little bit of adversity,
but we don't even have to see that.
We just know he's succeeded yet again and he's turned everyone around.
And everyone's now he's playing musical instruments at every scene.
He's singing this glorious song.
And then he gets home and you're like, wow, what a success.
Wow. A bunch of monkeys.
I wonder if he had any trouble, you know, getting in with them.
Or is one of them is one of them trying to like pull him apart?
No, he has joined their monkey drumming band
and is probably better at drumming than they are instantly.
Yes. I like the musician focus with which he's
Yeah. Yeah.
He's he faces no adversity is great from second one till second last.
And it's a great ride.
And did I upgrade this song to best Menken
over part of their world, part of your world?
Maybe I may have in the last few weeks.
I think I said maybe this is number one.
Well, all of my Disney tearing up was Menken related
because I also went to the mermaid lagoon theater show.
Oh, you with your flying aerial. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And it's it's like if you heard that they have this amazing
King Triton's concert show with The Little Mermaid, where
she's on wires and flipping around and the precision of it
and how close she can get to the audience and then screens with the sisters
and great puppets of flounder and Sebastian.
If there was a Little Mermaid musical in your town and it was that
you'd be telling everybody, holy shit, you got to see this Little Mermaid show.
Yeah, it's Broadway. It's above Broadway caliber. It's so great.
It's a good version of Spider-Man Turn Off the Dark. Yes.
Because she doesn't fall.
Would would love an Ursula saying that a theater is surprisingly easy to break into.
Yeah, it's all only docket points for that.
But yeah, yeah, I think you figured out by the end,
there's only two things that could have been the top two.
And it was it was a little bit of a tough choice,
but ultimately you got to go with number one ride in the country of Japan.
Journey to the center of the earth.
Holy fucking shit. What a ride.
I it's really great.
Mm hmm. I heard you had some qualms.
It needed another room.
That's my feeling about it.
That's what I said.
Now we were going on the ride.
We were like, this is awesome. This is awesome.
And it shoots out. You see this crazy lava monster.
You're like, oh, the amazing.
And then that's kind of it.
That's kind of the end of the ride.
Because you could do two more minutes like that.
Yeah. So I think that's the only thing that I would mean.
It's my expectations, of course.
But yeah, you would docket points because it felt like, oh, holy shit.
Now what are we going to see?
And then you're kind of done. Yeah, sure.
You just kind of quietly get off and you go.
Yeah, you go down like a cool zipping fast tracky thing
through some cool fake rocks.
But that's it. Sure, sure.
Yeah, I'm with you on that.
I do just think that the I think
the the world building is so cool.
The line is incredible.
The terrors, which I realized go up.
You're sent into these these these elevators that and there's all of
there's like creepy smoky smells and it shakes around like mad.
And it seems like it's going haywire.
And you feel like you're falling all the way down, down into the center of the earth.
But then you realize, wait a minute, you unload from the top.
So it's an illusion that makes you think you're going way, way down
when, in fact, you're going up, which is pretty cool.
Yes, that's really great.
A track ride system, right?
Test, track, great air, test track, slash, slash cars.
It's in that it's in that neck of the woods.
Breaks down a lot.
Does it really? Yeah.
That was the last fast pass we had for the whole trip.
And it broke down. Oh, bummer. Oh, no.
We did what we did it once the first day.
And then we were like, oh, great, this will be great.
We'll do that. The last thing we go on
before we have to go to the airport.
And it broke down and we like sat outside it for like a half hour
to see if it would come back up. And it did not.
That was over. Very sad.
But we got to do it once. I apologize for that.
We got lucky with it and we did it four times. Oh, wow.
In choosing. Yeah. Yeah.
Somehow like fast passes earlier in the day.
I think you do if you're going to Tokyo, get in there, get fast passes right away.
It's kind of a war when you get into the park and then you can relax.
But grab something as soon as you can. Yeah.
And then your day will be fine.
Yeah. These feel like very packed days, which I know you don't often like to do a lot.
Yeah, you're telling me.
Because of all this other stuff, because you got to meet characters,
you got to have treats. Yeah, we were way more front to back.
We had boundless energy.
We ended up with a very packed long episode, as I imagine we would.
But that ride was just like irresistible to me.
You're totally right about that.
However, those creatures you meet, it's, you know, yeah,
you meet friendly creatures, Daigle creatures, very E.T.
on the way down into the center of the earth.
And then it gets scary and there's explosions.
And there's lightning that you forget about every time.
Oh, God, that lightning.
I thought I was prepped for it, but I'm not.
Then fire shooting out at you.
And when you round the corner and you see the lava monster.
Oh, my God. The scope of that thing.
So scary. Makes a big difference to sit in the front row,
and especially in the seat closest to the monster.
Doug Jones, friend of the show, said, got to do front row on that thing.
And he gave me the translation, Ichiban Sekki.
And they were so excited.
I was like, was this am I going to seem like an American asshole bugging them?
They loved that I attempted to say those two words.
They were like, oh, yes.
And like took me to the side and then ushered me. Here it is.
They were so delighted that like employees incredible this whole part.
And and that was the best moment.
I think the last ride we went on was me with the best seat in.
That's great. In Journey to the Center of the Earth.
That that drop is fantastic.
Again, sorry, I was a militant about spoilers,
but getting to go on that ride and having no idea what's going to happen.
Yeah, incredible.
Sorry if I ruined it for you, the listener.
Now I'm being selfish, but you just shouldn't listen to the episode in general.
But so in a way disappointing, it's not in other parks,
but also how special that you have to do the pilgrimage to go on this incredible ride.
It as a kid, I was always disappointed
that after Indiana Jones, Disneyland went off a cliff.
It was all rocket rods and superstar limo and all this garbage.
And like, why didn't they build on that?
Why didn't it get better after Indiana Jones?
It did only in Tokyo.
It's the evolutionary step between Indiana Jones and Radiator Springs racers.
It's it's fantastic.
Radiator Springs only better because there's more characters,
characters at the end, a better last room.
But I don't think you get cars with that journey to the center of the earth.
Amazing ride vehicle. I got a little die cast to that.
Oh, yeah. I love, love, love this ride.
Choosing between thrills and heart with this and Sinbad.
But I got to choose. Yeah, hell of a thrill.
Love it. People have to go to this park and go on this ride and all of these rides.
Yeah, it's crazy.
I was going to say, like we did
major 20,000 leagues under the sea, which is great.
And the employee was asking us there, which what was our favorite ride?
And that's when we were like really trying to figure it out.
And that's where she was like, and now she's like,
I think we said Sinbad and she goes, that's my favorite, too.
And she spoke English as well.
So I go, yeah, I guess we have to go Sinbad.
And then I think Tower of Terror for the theming, but not the ride itself.
So I feel like over especially in Disney, see, like the theming is almost more
even important than like length of ride.
I think now we're a little spoiled with thrills and what have you and length of ride.
But they don't care as much about that over there.
Oh, maybe not. Yeah.
So it's not as big of a thing.
So would you go is top three Sinbad Tower
journey, something else? Yeah, maybe Poo before.
Oh, man, who's that? Maybe Poo before.
I don't know. I don't know.
I might say it Poo is like four.
Journey is really good.
I think the problem with journey was that it was so hyped up
and it was the one I knew the least about.
Well, actually somebody at least about as well.
But I think when you're seeing the volcano, when you're seeing that,
how the scope of this whole place, I think in my head, I had built it up
was like, there's going to be 10 more rooms after this lava monster.
Sure, sure. And like we're going to be like teetering on a thing.
And there's going to be lava under us.
And it felt like, oh, it's a lot actually smaller than I thought it was.
But that's partly my expectation.
That rush up the hill is so fun, though.
Oh, yeah. The spiraling and spiraling.
I know it's short, but then like and then a light at the end of the tunnel.
And what is is that something good out there?
No, it's a drop.
Yeah, I think I think also that
when we were going around outside,
I think I go, oh, we're going to drop back into scenes or something
that we shot out.
And then I think probably if I had gone out on the second time,
then my expectations were in check.
I know what it was.
Given a better assessment.
Sure. So that being said, since we went in, it's in bed,
I think maybe four, three or four times. Wow. Wow.
Well, only barely because, yeah, only barely a number two for me.
It's all good. It's all really good.
Yeah, it's all.
Harrison Hightower, too, just all of the detail on that.
We were just obsessed with.
Yeah. Yeah. World building characters.
I feel like I feel like we got to cut it off or we'll just do it forever.
And yeah, the top 10 did not help me make it shorter.
There's so much to say.
Go to this place.
I break off all these rides and we'll we'll we'll talk about other stuff.
Well, you know, we'll hit it in other episodes.
Twenty thousand leagues. I really liked.
But the top 10 is so packed. I get it.
No, I don't. I.
Twenty thousand leagues, a little bit lacking as well.
A little bit of something, maybe a finale needs.
I'm sorry. A little hard to see in there.
But all of it, how they do it is really great.
And still so cares.
Neemone, French Sea Rider, I didn't put on there, but it's great.
You got to do it.
That's fun. Yeah.
And also, it's I don't know how much you consider this a ride,
but at Tokyo Dome City, we went on a Ferris wheel where we saw that karaoke
in every sixth car or something is a karaoke car.
And so we got to sing karaoke at the top of Tokyo.
Life highlights so crazy, terrifying.
Aaron hates Ferris wheels and heights and everything, but was brave for this.
And luckily, though most of the songs are Japanese, it did have our three.
It happened to have our three favorite songs.
Wham's Last Christmas.
That's what makes you beautiful by One Direction and Aerosmith's
I Don't Want to Miss a Thing and singing I Don't Want to Miss a Thing
at the top of Tokyo, a life highlight.
I didn't want to miss a thing.
I don't want to miss a thing in this episode, but I'm sure I did.
But hey, we don't have to retire Tokyo here.
The spirit can live in our hearts.
A canon of songs if I've ever heard one.
The Great American Songbook.
Yeah, 100 years when the tale of American music is told.
Those will be those will be the three.
Wow. Wham isn't American, but I have so many questions,
but we need to end the episode.
We should just do another one of these.
I don't know. Oh, my God.
Well, there's also I mean, another good place for it is
a Panglecti Pete's board episode.
We'll definitely be doing that.
Hey, if you have questions about my trip to Tokyo,
if you have questions about going to Tokyo, but the city itself emails
podcast, right, Gmail.
Thanks to all the people who followed our trip at my Instagram at Skiz Gerdner.
Let me tell you another thing.
You know, our trip to Paris was disappointing because that property is so weird.
It was tough getting around Disney Studios.
Paris is as bad a park as Disney.
See is good.
But you know, when you compare these to my two international Disney trips,
you know what I didn't have in France was a bunch of people
I've never met writing me and saying, I'm so happy.
I'm living vicariously through you cheering me on, just like Sinbad's town.
That's what I felt like I had with the audience of this show.
Good luck on your journey, Scott.
So thank you to everybody who cheered Aaron and I on.
It was so heartwarming.
This is the least snarky episode humanly possible of this show.
We'll do jokes again in a future one.
We'll try to. Maybe.
Maybe. Or maybe that's our thing.
We're the not funny.
There's plenty of places being funny.
Maybe that's heartwarming.
You survived podcasts, right?
And thanks, gentlemen, for thank you, Mike, for all your tips
and everything that helped me get around.
I'm like Columbus. I paved the way.
So, yeah, no.
But Jason will be the bravest explorer.
The grand finale.
Jason goes international.
Have you ever?
Only Bermuda, which I believe technically might be a U.S.
protectorate. Mm hmm.
And Scott's only been to Bermuda via a Beach Boys song.
You did a group, but you lumped it.
You went Bermuda, Bahama.
Yeah. And I and I vicariously had to imagine a hypothetical pretty mama.
Yeah, because you weren't married at the time.
I thought I wrote one of the first time I heard that song,
I wrote Mike Love a fan letter and I said, thank you.
I'm living vicariously through you.
Enjoy your journey to Kokomo, a fake place because that's a city in Indiana.
Finding a new hat.
Yeah. Hey, everybody, thank you so much for listening.
Thanks for all your comments and everything.
And there'll be more Tokyo talk to come.
And hey, follow us at pockets right on Twitter and on Instagram
and follow the compass of your heart to our live show.
Oh, yeah. Dynasty typewriter at the Hayworth Theater Friday, June 7th, 2019.
I haven't recorded an episode since this became reality that we're doing this.
Yeah. So excited.
Really want to say what the topic is and what we're doing.
But we can we got to leave some surprises.
Maybe we'll link it before we do the show.
Maybe we will. But you're going to like it.
You're going to like it. But I'll say this.
And not to this is not hucksterism.
I mean, it's a little salesmanship, but tickets are going fast.
So if you're on the fence, I think there's a chance there's no tickets by the time.
There is that is a possibility.
We might have to cut this down.
There's a chance that this will be cut. You'll never hear it.
Good luck on your journey to the dynasty typewriter website.
May your compass guide your mouse to directions are on there.
Allow time for it. That is true.
It's a crowded part. Yeah.
For high density area.
There are lots and valet options.
It is not as beautiful of an area as Tokyo Disney
Sea, but we will be your guides and your heart will swell.
And no one will lock a parking lot right afterwards.
Thanks for listening, folks.
Glad to be back. Talk to you soon. Bye bye.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcast dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcast, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.