Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate.
Today on the show, folks, it's toilet time.
That's right, we're talking the tangled toilets.
Splash.
At Walt Disney's Magic Kingdom,
I'm Jason Sheridan here with Mike Carlson.
You've been waiting, what, a year and a half,
as long as we've been doing the show,
to yell, it's toilet time.
It's toilet time.
And now you finally get to your dream realized.
My dream realized, Scott Gerrider.
That was exciting, I agree.
What a great way to start.
What a delight, yeah.
The tangled bathrooms, and this is one of those
sunny eclipse where I'd be curious to do the general poll
of do you know what we're talking about already?
Because I didn't.
Here's what happened.
My friend Dennis McNicholas, who's deep with this stuff,
texted me out of the blue,
hey, I have a great idea for a C ticket.
Although I guess in this case, it's kind of a P ticket.
That's my, I said that, not him.
Let's not put that on him.
It's certainly a number two ticket.
It's good it's on the second gate.
Hey, that's right, that's the number two gate today.
Sure.
So out of nowhere, a text and a couple of pictures
of this beautiful looking area in Fantasyland,
and I'm like, what is this?
And he says, the mini tangled land at Walt Disney World,
a richly themed area whose sole attraction is bathrooms.
Is bathrooms and phone chargers to benches,
like barrel shaped benches with phone charging stations.
Yes, there is also that.
There's tables that look like logs,
and then some of the logs have little doors
and you could charge your phone.
Now that's a good thing right off the bat.
This is a thing that Disney needs to account for more.
They're involving mobile experiences in the lines,
but there's not a lot of plugs,
except for plenty in my beloved Napa wine zone
in California Adventure.
Although even then you see people like huddling
in a bathroom hallway on the ground.
You know, like one wire's going one way,
the other's going the other.
People are trying to stay as far apart from each other
as they can, even though they're both huddling
around the same outlet.
So to in 2013 when they put this in,
have a good mobile setup is cool.
Good for them.
But yeah, I didn't know about this before.
I feel like you had, Jason.
Yeah, so I knew about it because I remembered.
So this is technically part of the Fantasyland expansion
announced at D23 2009, I think,
and then opened in phases between 2012 and 2014.
And I think a couple things happened.
One, they stretched out the opening
of the new Fantasyland for so long.
People were like, well wait, when is this gonna be done?
So at the time I remember like news sites
just seemingly just hungry for anything to talk about,
any new thing to come out of this.
And then two, reading different blogs from that time period,
it seemed like the snake eating its own tail,
places announcing the tangled bathrooms had opened,
but then more posts coming or tweets coming going like,
why are we all talking about these toilets?
So it's like a self-fulfilling nightmare.
This is internet discourse in general,
the pro and the anti go back and forth in a maddening way.
Yeah, and I truly like it.
I found it a little befuddling.
I still kind of find it a little befuddling
because it's like, well, here's the thing.
They needed bathrooms in new fantasy.
You gotta have bathrooms.
You sure do.
And if they had not themed them,
they would have gotten dragged for that.
So they did theme them a lot
and then they get made fun of for that.
So I don't know, it seems like a damned if you do,
damned if you don't kind of scenario.
I think it's just funny.
I think like it makes sense.
I think, okay, the way it was presented to me in that text,
hearing that they took the time to develop an entire area
and that it's only bathrooms, that sounds very silly.
You go, what?
This is like, it's like a weird like zoning mishap.
Like what hap, like was there supposed to be more here?
Was this a mistake on a form?
How did this happen?
But then you start looking into the reality of it
and it seems like this is pretty great.
It seems like this is a nice chill zone in the park.
If this were my home park, which it is,
and I would probably be talking up
the tangled restroom area as a place to like,
catch a breather.
The bathrooms themselves sound very nice.
People like it theming wise.
I think like it's silly conceptually,
but it seems very pleasant in execution.
The loop, have you listened to the loop?
There's like a tangled bathroom loop online.
Oh, no I didn't.
Of music, very pleasant.
Not unlike a Napa Rose or something,
but then also with a little tangled, you know.
Just some like acoustic guitar noodling.
A lot of noodling.
Great, love noodling.
So yeah, it sounds great, honestly.
I don't think, I'm trying to remember when I was there
if I actually used the facilities.
I don't think I used these bathrooms,
but they blended so nicely into the new fantasy land.
I think I just was like,
oh, look at that's a nice little something.
I just didn't even think about it.
Yeah, I think when I was there in 2014,
I did use them, but it didn't occur to me
until I was leaving.
I was like, oh, this is that thing everyone was roasting.
Like, because I think I was just tired from a long day
or in the middle of a long day,
and I wasn't really like processing at the time.
Well, it sounds like they're just immediately part
of the fabric of the park.
It seems like they don't stick out at all.
They blend wonderfully with the new fantasy land stuff
in general.
Well, I think, I mean, there's also like a tiny waterfall
and a little stream.
Like, so there's a nice water feature.
There is like-
Which gets you in the mood.
Gets you in the mood.
To use the facilities.
You know?
But there is Rapunzel's tower too.
And I think that and the castle at Be Our Guest,
the forest perspectives don't work 100% for me.
I would agree with that.
They just look small.
They look like tiny little things.
Yeah, so I think that was one of the things
people were kind of like, this is what you,
this is Tangled, this is this tiny little tower.
I think people or fans of Tangled,
I think they were just disappointed
that there wasn't anything.
Cause like Gaston has a tavern,
and if it was Gaston's bathroom
and they were really lovely or like manly, you know,
like Gaston would have.
Oh, you get cologne and stuff.
Yeah, right.
There's a tendon in there.
Here's what I-
Dressed as like LeFou.
Here's what I know about Tangled.
Tangled is a 2010 American 3D computer animated
musical adventure film produced by Walt Disney
Animation Studio.
I'm just reading the Wikipedia.
So I-
It sounded very natural.
Yeah, I know that was off the top of your head.
I tend to refer to films by their year in the country
in which they were produced.
Featuring the voice talents of Mandy Moore
and Zachary Levi.
Shazam himself.
Everyone's favorite.
We like him.
The commercials tell us we like him.
Shazam seems like a front.
Like something's wrong.
It seems too cheap to be a movie.
But the critics say they love it.
Really?
That's what's going on now.
Neat, we'll see.
Oh, yeah, wait, if the critics like it,
they've never been wrong.
And also, there can't be anything nefarious
to critics all liking something in mass.
I'm waiting for a supporting Shazam character,
Talking Tawny, the tiger who walks on two legs
and wears a three piece suit.
I love Talking Tawny.
I feel like we're not gonna get that anytime soon.
Maybe, eventually.
Maybe.
We don't have the technology.
You need the life of Pi people to do it right.
I like Tangled 5.
I remember watching it years ago when it was on Netflix.
Some people say Tangled superior to Frozen.
Maybe.
I think that's the opinion I've seen a lot of.
Maybe even a Tony Baxter I've heard say that.
Does that make sense?
Interesting.
I think I kind of, as I watched it,
was making fun of it a little
because all the marketing materials of it,
all the characters are kind of doing DreamWorks face,
that sort of smug smirk.
Oh, that little like to the side folded arm.
Yeah, that was a real disease for a while.
Yeah.
It infected all the companies.
Right.
But I think, I do, I think what we were saying
was just like that I think that's the reason
that it was controversial, not because it's bad,
because people wanted like a real experience out of Tangled,
not just to be able to shit in the Tangled universe.
Like that's really what we're getting at here is that
they didn't get on a dark ride,
but they do get to shit in universe,
which is not as fun.
If it was a property that nobody cared about,
if it was the fox and the hound bathrooms,
you wouldn't have a problem with it.
Or there's little bathrooms up by the Fantasyland Theater,
the former Videopolis,
which are just themes to general storybook, right?
And nobody's making fun of like, what is this?
It doesn't even have a theme.
Right.
I think it's to make the decision
to specifically build this new little hut
for a property that people are excited about
and probably would like a more, you know,
ornate experience for.
That being said, there is the little like hunt for kids.
That seems fun.
Oh, Pascal.
Oh yeah, yes.
You find little Pascals,
who is like a little lizard guy from the movies.
He's a fun, he is cute.
He's a fun little lizard.
I did not, as I watched the movie,
I remember not learning his name.
So I just kept calling him Roy Lizard
because I was like, I don't,
what is this fucking character's name?
I was like driving me crazy.
I like Roy Lizard.
Yeah, I like it.
I like it too.
And I like the little Roy Lizard,
I find the hidden Roy Lizard or his friends, you know,
in the stream and around the toilet building.
There's gonna, he'll be replaced by Rango soon.
Oh no, is that Fox?
Am I wrong?
Is Rango Fox or is it a different studio?
I think Rango might be Fox.
Good question.
Was Rango gonna be part of Fox Studios Malaysia
run by the Mercurial chairman?
Yeah, it was a Rango land.
Yeah, which is now just sitting vacant.
And now they'll have to make it a ride for a generic lizard.
And that's where Roy Lizard might fit the bill perfectly.
No one owns the IP Roy Lizard except for us.
So we better like get a copyright on that right now
before that Mercurial chairman tries to yank it from us.
Bad news, Rango was released by Paramount.
Shit, damn, there's never gonna be Rango.
There is no empty space waiting for a Roy Lizard ride.
Fuck.
Too bad, sorry.
We blew the whole thing.
Can I ask a quick question?
What Disney movie universe would you guys
wanna take a shit in?
Is there one off the top of your head?
Cause I was thinking, I mean,
Beauty and the Beast seems too horrifying, the reality.
Cause the toilets would have to talk to you.
Even the castle, but back in town.
Okay, fine, yeah, you're right, fine.
In that town, they're not alive.
Yeah, and I bet whoever like operates the bath,
whoever like owns and operates the bathroom
in the town square is very nice.
And would like give a hearty hello.
Hello, Belle, nice and clean for you.
Go ahead, take a load off.
I'm going to go ahead and say Big Hero 6.
Oh, San Francisco.
San Francisco is a combination of San Francisco and Tokyo.
So they may very well have nice Japanese future toilets.
And there'll be Toto toilets.
What's that?
There'll be Toto toilets.
Is that the brand?
That's the brand, they make the style here,
but they're bidet.
Scott, you're going to Tokyo soon and you will learn
that most of the toilets will shoot water in your ass.
Really?
Yep.
Do they do it whether I want it to or not?
No, I think you have to hit the button.
I think there's a remote on the floor.
Request for that?
For sure, I'm just trying to remember
if any of them did it involuntarily.
You know, I've never bidet,
so maybe now's the time to start.
Well, you're going to have a hotel room
and that would be the time,
the privacy of that is the time to try it.
I will say that.
In case I go, yeah, ouch.
I don't, nobody else hears me.
I don't like make everyone stop eating in the restaurant.
You don't bring disgrace to yourself in the country.
I will be removed from the,
there is nothing polite about yelling, ouch.
Yeah.
I would say seven dwarves.
I want to see what they were doing in the hut and stuff.
I want to see like, I like the old timey,
like artisan woodwork.
And I think you could have a fun little bathroom
and then you could have all the dwarves names on the stall.
I guess now that I'm thinking about it,
the dwarves are tiny and they'd have to be scaled properly,
but it'd still be fun to go into the dopey stall
is what I'm saying.
Maybe, but life in the past was hell.
And I can only assume going to the bathroom back then
was a nightmare.
So you're saying it might've been,
if they were being accurate,
it would be a hole in the ground in the bathroom.
Probably, maybe a little bench or something.
Yeah, that's eliminating a lot for me.
Like, yeah, Aladdin, I don't want to do,
that's probably not.
But what if anything were in the cave of wonders?
Cause he's got, there's gotta be a crazy type bathroom
in there.
Yeah, and you take a shit and it just like,
kind of swirls into like blue magic.
Right.
And just kind of dissipates into the air.
Yeah.
Who dares shit in the cave of wonders?
It wasn't explicitly a rule that I was aware of.
I mean, I got to shit somewhere.
Where's that?
The diamond in the rough may shit in my mouth.
Take anything you want,
as long as you give me a little something.
Take the lamp, go for it, I don't care.
What's one that I want to, well, I, you know,
probably this isn't unpleasant.
This is not a place that I've ever wanted to be.
The Wally ship, because it's, you know,
it's portrayed as an unpleasant place
and like the ultimate cruise ship.
And cruise ships, as we know,
can have tremendous sewage problems.
So I don't really, and not that I don't really
want to be there, but I have to assume
for the lack of mobility of all of those people
on the floating chairs, the floating chairs
are probably toilets, correct?
Oh, 100%.
I think I said it on Screen Junkies movie fights once
that they're shitting in those chairs.
Oh, okay, you've made this observation before.
Yeah, they have to be.
And then probably some little like,
little sweep up robot comes and cleans you off
when all's said and done.
The problem is it's possible that the chair technology
in Wally is that you're like constantly catheterized.
Ooh.
That's probably what it's like.
It's probably, and I don't know if there's a,
what you would call, I guess it's a colostomy bag
on the other side, right?
Like how would, what's the catheter version of number two?
No, I don't want to be too gross here.
We're thankfully, we're all healthy enough
to not have to know this, thank God.
I'm just saying it might just be tubes, two tubes.
Unless they just, they're just on bedpans at all times.
Like none of, we don't know what's going on on those seats.
Yeah.
They might just be like open and naked kind of.
So everyone's pants have a hole in the bottom.
That's basically what's going on in those chairs.
All of those Wally people are just,
those onesies just have a little,
well, like the onesies that, you know,
like the kids in Peter Pan were like
with a little like flap, you know.
Yeah.
It's that kind of, and probably maybe when,
maybe like the chair senses that you're getting ready
and then comes and like unbuckles,
like a little robot unbuckles the little buttons.
Okay.
That's a really adorable way to do it.
I was thinking of the true, I think,
future nightmare scenario where you're just hooked up
to two tubes and everything just comes out
whether you realize it or not.
But you have like a little whimsical robot being like,
it's time to go.
I think it's in keeping with the rest of Wally.
Yeah.
It's one of those little misfits who ends up, you know,
rebelling when Wally shows up.
Yeah.
And understandably, because if your job is to unbutton
people's onesie flaps.
I mean, we are led to believe people have been on that ship
for generations.
So the full circle of life, you know, birth, death,
lovemaking, shitting, everything's happening on that ship.
In those chairs.
In those chairs, yeah.
Right.
I think they've all gotten accustomed
to whatever the system is.
So, whereas we might think a bunch of bizarre tubes
hooked up to us at all times,
as we like are out in the world and talking to people.
Right.
That's bad for us, but these are like,
there's been 300 years of this by the time we see Wally.
So to use those Wally bathrooms in a theme park,
you would have to be wearing child one piece underwear,
or a one piece going to bed with the butt flap.
You'd have to.
I guess so.
That's a problem, I think.
Yeah.
Logistical problem.
Way too much potential for sick fucks
to take advantage of that option.
Yeah.
Indulgence, it's in their general weird perversion.
So maybe the technology isn't just not there yet.
I guess not.
In theme park land.
Though that, maybe, okay,
I'll subtract the, or it's an option.
They can do this or not.
They can, it can be,
the ride can have waste options or not.
But if the Wally chairs were what went
on the people mover track,
if that's how they ended up using it,
if you just were like, and then like, you know,
Wally breaks you out of it,
and then you get freed at the end.
Sure.
But it would really be the full experience,
if it was that ride and you could take a dump on it too.
When will we have a ride that we can take a dump on?
Well, I'm gonna propose just the house from inside out
that the family lives in
because it was present day and regular.
So the bathrooms are just bathrooms.
And there's probably only one in there.
Yeah, they moved to San Francisco.
If it's like a townhouse, maybe they might have to share one.
Yeah.
I think you go to San Francisco,
you're lucky to have a bathroom in your house.
Sure.
I think it's the one.
I don't remember what they had, presumably the one.
The only other thing is, cause I like old timey stuff,
you know, let's get an Apple dumpling gang bathroom.
Which I guess is now I think that I'm thinking about it,
another hole in the ground.
I'm assuming. Yeah.
I just want to shit in a hole in the ground
is what I'm saying.
I guess if I think.
I mean, you don't have to go to a theme park to do that.
Yeah, you might just want to go to a national park.
You might want to go backpacking.
All right.
You dig a hole, you have a shovel, you dig a hole.
Are there rides there at a national park?
Just the majestic splendor of nature.
I say as they make that jerk off.
I saw it on the Disneyland railroad.
I don't need to go there.
Yeah.
I saw the
condensed version of the,
and if you go to the green Kenyan,
you don't get to see it in the past.
Right.
No dinosaurs.
No fucking dinosaurs there.
Yep. Yep.
Boring.
So to bring us back to the Tangle Toilets
and just to contextualize it for people
who have not been to the magic kingdom recently.
So when this Tomorrowland, not Tomorrowland,
Fantasyland expansion was happening,
so Mickey's Toontown Fair closes,
Snow White Scary Adventure closes,
and what you get out of it is the Little Mermaid ride,
the very detailed robust queue,
Be Our Guest restaurant, and the Seven Dwarfs Mine Train.
So kind of big attractions and a big restaurant and all.
So in that context,
yeah, it is funny that Tangled got the bathrooms.
Yeah, the ball, the famous ballroom from Beauty and the Beast
is now a place that you can go.
Yes.
You can go under the sea with Ariel.
You can go into the Seven Dwarfs Mine
and you could go into where the Tangled characters live and pee.
Yeah, but Tangled was only a few years old at that point, so.
Maybe they didn't know that the love was gonna grow
and that they maybe owe something more.
Yeah.
Is there a seek,
I know there's like a series, a TV series,
but I feel like there's a Tangled sequel in the works,
but the Frozen sequel will probably be out before it.
For sure, yeah.
That's like next year or the end of this year, perhaps?
Is it the end of this year?
It might be, I think.
What do you think they could have done,
what could they have done besides bathrooms
to make Tangled fans happy in the lack of a ride,
since that's a high bar?
Is there a meet and greet right there?
Doesn't that seem like it?
Yeah, I don't think so.
Like that seems like an easy one,
like just put the meet and greet there,
and at least it's like, oh, you can meet them,
and also there's a nice bathroom next to it.
I think the meet and greets have all been shifted to the,
because they doubled the princess fairy tale.
So those are all over there.
Yeah.
But then Gaston's thing is by his tavern,
his meet and greet, because he's not a princess, I guess.
Is there something, why isn't there hair hanging down,
and you can like tug on the hair?
I guess that's not good to do to Rapunzel.
Well, because the other thing is like,
where does this exist in the context of the movie?
Because spoiler alert, she gets out of the tower
pretty quick into the movie.
It actually ends the movie with a very short pixie cut.
But she does like the lanterns from,
there's a big lantern sequence in the movie,
and like the paint, and she paints,
and everything's like very lushly painted,
the pink and orange accents on every,
or pink and purple kind of, everything looks very nice.
It is aesthetically pleasing.
It's very much like the, what is it called?
The fantasy fair out here in Anaheim next to the castle.
It's kind of a cousin to that.
And there are the same like wanted posters
for the characters at Flynn.
Flynn Rider.
And there's a lot of goons.
There's not a lot of characters in this movie.
Although, Paul F. Tompkins is one of the voices
of one of the characters.
Is he really?
He's entangled?
Yeah.
He's entangled a little bit.
Oh, that's fun.
Not represented on one of these posters?
Oh, I can't remember.
I saw some of the posters.
I don't, he's kind of like a little goofy,
drunk kind of goon.
That's fun.
Yeah.
They just needed to make like a drink,
like a drink and pretzel stand next to it.
It just needed some little thing, I think, to not.
Pretzels that are in a braid, like.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Wow.
Really good food and beverage opportunity for them.
And you can only get them right there.
That's an acceptable way for pretzels to be.
It can just be the more Reese's treats like we have,
but you stick the.
I was gonna say also, other than pretzels,
it could just be a bunch of pasta, long pasta,
like her hair.
Oh, you know what I mean?
A braided pasta, and you just eat like loose pasta maybe.
That's the next trend.
Sure.
If it's okay, well, they've established with the cone zone
in radiator springs.
Yeah, right.
A district devoted to a shape of food.
So just anything long and braided goes into this zone.
Angel hair.
Angel hair pasta.
Yeah. Perfect.
Yeah.
Yeah, they like wrap it up for you in a little,
do you eat it long?
Do they give you like a big long tray that you,
like a big hot dog container, like a paper plate, but.
Yeah.
They would have to, I don't know,
that would be too hard if it's a quick service.
Yeah.
Just stick it in the bread cone.
You just stick a bunch of pasta in the bread cone.
I think maybe it's just you hand them a loo,
it just dangles, and that's the fun thing.
And you like, there's a bunch of photo ops of like,
you trying to eat the thing, like the hair from the bottom.
Or like the long candy, like the thin rope.
Like nerd's rope.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, for sure.
This is all, I think that's all it,
you make it, it's a food area and also restrooms.
Yeah.
The fact that all it is is that it was begging
to be made fun of.
However, this place also celebrated seemingly.
Mom blogs love the tangled bathrooms.
There's a lot of lists of the best bathrooms
in Disney World or in the Disney parks,
which I imagine as an area we'll get into at some point,
but the tangled bathrooms immediately on there.
And when I looked up tangled bathrooms on Twitter,
there was a tweet from two months ago as we record this,
from Rachel Zegler, who is the actress who is playing Maria
in Spielberg's West Side Story coming up.
A like soon to be very prominent star
with a lot of followers in anticipation of that.
And she tweeted, thinking about the tangled bathrooms
in fantasy land and then five emojis with kind of that,
like warm and cozy smile and hearts all over the face.
Wow.
And that has 1300 likes.
So like a lot of love.
Yeah.
From an up and coming star on the tangled bathroom.
Wow.
Somebody right under that, like somebody said,
I'd like to get married in the tangled restrooms.
That was a tweet from like yesterday.
Lot of love.
Yeah, I think this actually is an oddly beloved little area.
They do look very nice in the actual,
the stall doors are very,
they're like, look like a castle doors and stuff.
And the ceilings are painted.
They look like wood and they have hinges.
And like all good Orlando restrooms,
from what I remember blasting cold air at you,
a brief respite from the heat.
Great, good.
It sounds awesome.
There's pans all over the wall,
which is, I haven't seen the movie.
There's a thing with pan, she hits people with pans.
Cast iron pans are like a weapon in the movie.
Okay.
That she's constantly hitting.
People are constantly getting hit with.
I see, okay.
So that's a nod.
There's a lot of nods to the,
like if you know the movie,
there is a lot of like weird little, here's his armor.
Maximus the horse has like a horseshoe imprint
in the ground.
Oh.
He's the sassy, kind of like,
were there two silly animals in Frozen or just the moose?
I forget.
There's two silly, Maximus and Pascal
get into a lot of mischief in this movie.
Okay, okay.
And they mug a lot.
He sort of feel their presence.
I think that's, it's getting,
when the hidden Pascals are getting close to something,
but it's not as robust as the Sleeping Beauty dioramas.
If they had something like that too,
like in the windows.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah.
To read the story of Tangle.
That's a little more something.
Or like Figaro the Cat,
like squatting at the birdcage at Fantasy Fair.
That's great.
I make a point of taking people through there
because they might've missed that.
It's an outdoor animatronic.
That's pretty neat.
Yeah, yeah.
Easy to overlook.
Yeah, it's not as good as that,
but it does seem like it might be slightly better
than the theming of Pizzeria Rizzo.
Just slightly.
Wow.
You're just stirring up the pot.
No, I'm just saying, I'm not stirring anything up.
I think we gotta keep it warm
until we all can go make a judgment call.
Yeah.
I'm just saying it seems like it's like slightly,
like there's a few more touches
and it feels like more money went into it.
That's all I'm saying.
I'm wondering if I could just combine
that if I can just get a to-go order from Mama Melrose,
a restaurant I like a lot, and eat it in Pizzeria Rizzo.
I think that upstairs Pizzeria Rizzo room.
Sure.
Oh, kinda combine, then you get the theming.
Combine, yeah, I can get like a wood-fired pizza
as opposed to just like a Red Baron pizza at Pizzeria Rizzo.
What a bizarre scenario that Disney created
their own Burger King McDonald's feud.
Like the same type of food.
Oh, yeah, and also.
One little, in the same little district of a theme park.
And at a time when one of the emerging
fast casual trends is fast fire, flash fire,
whatever you wanna call it, pizza,
like you know, like Chipotle, go down the line,
design your own pizza, cooks in a minute and a half.
How do you not just do that?
How do you not just make that?
Maybe they think it takes too long or something or.
Mm-hmm.
I guess that's not how the rats would do it.
I guess.
They like old-fashioned.
Yeah.
New York pizza, except not nearly as good
as New York pizza.
That's what I've been told.
Already, but then.
You didn't eat.
Very pretty.
I hadn't eaten there, yeah.
This one's looming.
We have to go actually experience it.
So the other, when Dennis texted me about this,
he gave a little background as to why
he believes that it happened.
Which is that the tangled restrooms were built
in the site of the Skyway terminal in Fantasyland.
Yes.
Which in both the Magic Kingdom and Disneyland,
those Skyway situations have not been solved.
Isn't it just still there in Disneyland?
Didn't they remove it in Disneyland finally?
Maybe they have.
I think they finally did.
Yeah, like in the last year or two.
And I think, was it this that finally destroyed?
They finally bulldozed to build this?
I mean, yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah, it's gone because of Magic Kingdom.
Yeah, in Magic Kingdom, it's gone because of this.
That was a little more like,
I think the Disneyland ones up in the hills
and it's easy to miss.
So it wasn't really bothering everybody, anybody,
but this was kind of a bigger station
that was just sitting unoccupied for over a decade,
waiting for something to happen to it.
Meanwhile, there were restrooms
in this area of Fantasyland,
but they got rid of the bathrooms
because they were right next to Peter Pan's flight
and they got rid of those bathrooms
so that they could build a longer interactive queue
for Peter Pan.
Yeah.
Which I didn't know about and I've watched some video of.
I don't know if you guys have experienced it in person.
It seems great.
It's like, because the Peter Pan line in Disneyland
is very boring.
You just go back and forth and nothing happens.
Now there's this whole indoor room.
It's like the nursery and your shadow interacts with,
with Tinkerbell and you end up with Captain Hook's hat on
and magic is happening to your shadow.
I did this in Florida
and I don't know what you're talking about.
Wait, what?
I did that line in Florida or maybe I had a FastPass.
Maybe I skipped it.
That's what must have happened.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well that was probably what happened.
That's probably what happened.
I'm not making up some lines.
No, no, I wasn't accusing you of making it up.
They could have also like yanked some of that stuff
because the Haunted Mansion had interactive stuff in it
in that queue in Florida and they started yanking it.
I think now that I'm thinking about it,
I must have had a FastPass and skipped that fun stuff.
Dennis said that it is very easy to miss.
Like it's barely labeled and if you had a FastPass,
you wouldn't even go anywhere near it.
Interesting.
You go down a big hallway
before you even get to the cool stuff
and apparently it's made it such that it might be worthwhile
to even just sit through the Peter Pan line.
We had to do that too.
That stuff was very cool.
So this whole rearranging of bathrooms
did lead to immersive theming in several ways.
This new line is part of it.
They got rid of just an alpine lodge
that was sitting empty for over a decade
and now there's hidden pascals and lanterns and all that.
So I think this beautification project has been good.
Just it kind of hinges on some inherent silliness
of a property that people like only having bathrooms.
But I'm sure nowadays, back in the day,
they couldn't have done a much smaller scale version of this
but they focused tests, everything.
Do people like this?
Do they like it buy on DVD level?
Do they like it want a ride level?
Do they like it want a sequel level?
Oh sure.
And so it could have been that
they want tangled but we don't have enough fanfare
to immediately fast track a ride
in the way that they fast track the Frozen in Epcot.
Oh sure.
The results haven't been strong enough to justify
let's get something in ASAP.
I think it also takes time for something
to set in as a fan favorite.
They turn the Aladdin show into Frozen so quickly
in California Adventure and I feel like
it's less positively received than Aladdin
which is a couple decades old at this point
but that means there's a couple generations of people
who like Aladdin.
Yeah I think that Frozen was just such a smash
that they were like we need stuff in the park now.
We have to fast track everything.
You caught them off guard.
Maybe the biggest way since under doing
Toy Story merchandise in the 90s.
They were not prepared for the insane popularity
of the movie and song.
I like that now they're getting into
all right there will be like committed Frozen experiences
instead of just like jamming every corner
with some sing along or whatever.
Right and then eventually we'll get
Arendelle in Disneyland maybe.
Maybe.
That's the rumor still.
Oh no.
And then we'll have to rerun the fake rock.
Oh yeah that's true.
Yeah that's potentially a strong
or maybe when we get into Star Wars land
those rocks are gonna blow us away
and we'll realize we were wrong all along.
Yeah.
That may have to be revisited.
Tangled bathrooms strong contender in bathroom final four.
Tangled may also have been like the bridge movie
from like the chicken little era of like Disney
trying to do 3D animated movies
but not quite succeeding in the way that Pixar
even Dreamworks was.
And then when they started.
Bolt.
Yeah Bolt another one.
And then you see like Frozen and Big Hero 6
and like what are the other Disney.
Oh Zootopia.
Oh Zootopia yeah like much more.
And of course.
Like clear phenomena like I never heard a bad thing
about Bolt's Chicken Little maybe more so
but they were not phenomenons.
They've only in the last decade have started to have
truly mega popular CGI.
They point to like oh they started running Disney animation
a little more like Pixar is run
which ironically was a little more like
the original Disney animation was run.
So I mean that could be affecting.
Tangled may have been the early adopter almost
in this trend.
Yeah.
Well you know since we've I wanna keep up the pattern
of that we do some game or bullshit
in these C ticket episodes.
So I'd like to find out more about your guys preferences
when it comes to restroom experiences
in a segment that I call everybody has a crappen place.
Whoa.
Here's what I'm gonna drive out here.
I do think at some point we need to cover
Disneyland bathrooms.
I think that's a whole big area.
We have a lot to say about it.
So I don't wanna do any of that yet even though like
there's I'm sure we could all talk about quality
restroom experiences in the parks.
Well and bathroom breaking bathroom news for the other day
as we were talking about this episode.
Oh right what was that?
So in the news story on the Inside Universal website
Islands of Adventure is now going to have like
themed scents sprayed in the bathrooms
which I'm sure the air freshener spritzing things
were already there.
They're just making an effort to like
we're gonna more thoughtfully order from the catalog.
It's not just gonna be generic.
Will you smell like in the Kong Skull Island
will be banana breath in the restroom.
It could be.
And this is of course a park that also has
a much maligned bathrooms.
The Namor the Sub Mariner bathrooms in Marvel.
You call them Namor?
Did I say Namor?
Yeah.
Yeah Namor and Amor I've heard both.
He's like swimming through water
and under it says restrooms.
What character is this?
This is Namor the Sub Mariner
sort of Marvel's version of Aquaman.
Okay.
King of the deep.
He's like angrier though.
He's angry.
And they theme bathrooms after him?
Yeah.
So like is there are you when you dispose of your waste
does it end up is he in your waste?
Is he swimming through it?
Is he under the bath?
He points at it as it goes by.
Look.
There it goes.
He's angry too.
He's like really mad.
That's one of his character things.
The surface dwellers.
He's a real dick.
Yeah.
He's one of the first Marvel superheroes.
Anyway, keep a nose out for those islands
who adventure toilets.
Well maybe senses would be something in this category
that would make you like a bathroom.
And here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna eliminate theme park restrooms
and I'm gonna eliminate where you live.
Your own personal dwelling bathrooms.
Do you guys offhand have a bathroom or type of bathroom
of which you are the most fond?
You mean in this not here
or you mean when I'm out in the world?
Yes.
Whether it be from your hometown or from your childhood
or here in your adult life in Los Angeles
or even if it's just like this type of place
I like the bathrooms.
Yeah. I got number one with a bullet hotel lobbies.
Yeah.
That's exactly where I'm going.
We may have talked about this before.
Yeah.
Yeah because you get the like the cleanliness
that you would get in the rooms
without having to pay for a room.
It's like they are sparkling, they are spacious
and they're never mobbed.
And I like to get writing done in hotels and hotel lobbies.
And should the task come up while you're in a hotel
Yeah. Great place to do it.
You can take your time.
You're in no rush to get out of there.
I have another very specific one.
So like upscale non-chain cafes
or it can be a chain, but not like a Starbucks.
So like here in LA, there's,
I guess they're technically a chain, but they're different.
There's the Aroma Cafe in one part of town.
Then there's the Alcove.
That's sort of like a place where you're gonna pay
for an $18 sandwich tends to have very nice restrooms.
Yes, I know the Aroma one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's very spacious.
The Alcove is just like a one toilet bathroom.
They're just two big rooms.
Yeah.
They're like, but they're cozy.
I like the cozy.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, they're especially Alcove, very cozy bathroom.
Very cozy.
But sometimes like really nice restaurants
like Mike and I experienced this the other day.
Some of them were like kind of almost railroad
apartment style little restaurants in LA.
You're going through the kitchen.
Like I walked through the kitchen of a sushi
and like Poke bowl place the other day to use the bathroom
and like little asterias, little places sometimes.
You go, there's only one bathroom.
It's in the kitchen.
Although getting a little, getting to pass by the kitchen.
I mean, we love behind the scenes peeks.
So that's kind of a different,
but that's a different.
Keep your food being made.
That's fun.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
With you on hotel lobbies and I'd specifically
like to shout out the Glendale neck of the woods
is a Hilton and a embassy suites
that both have fantastic quality.
Universal Hilton, the Sheraton Hilton,
Universal Hollywood.
Yeah.
Very nice lobby bathrooms.
Fantastic.
Agreed.
Mike, anything?
Almost anywhere in Japan.
Okay.
Oh, I'm so excited.
Yeah, I mean, I'm sure there's plenty of places
where that's not the case, but everywhere we went,
we were just, first of all,
there's like very little litter anywhere on the streets,
but all the, almost all the bathrooms are like just kept up
so nicely.
Like in, and that goes for hotels,
that goes for in just a restaurant bathroom.
Obviously that goes in Disney.
And then all the toilets.
Tragic train stations, like still nice.
I'm trying to think if we did a train station,
I'm sure something like that.
I mean, maybe not nice, but very clean and well kept up.
Like it might not look nice.
It might look like it's 30 years old,
but that's the thing with a lot of things in Japan.
It's like they haven't renovated it
to make it look like it's in this century,
but it's been kept up very well,
which I think I was describing the Tokyo Dome City Hotel.
Oh, okay.
I'll make a point of it.
So yeah, that almost anywhere in Japan,
we, Lindsay and I long for the bathrooms of Japan,
the public restrooms of Japan.
Wow, wow.
So.
Yeah, you can't expect in America.
We've come to.
I don't think.
No.
I think, you know, places do their best
to keep things in order,
but I think you end up understaffed
and there's too many people.
I love taking a train,
but the real redheaded stepchild of transportation.
I mean, airports can be pretty gnarly,
but especially train places.
That said, I would like to finally,
maybe this year or next, get a sleeper car,
take the train back to the East Coast instead of flying.
It takes like four or five days still.
It's crazy.
You have to change a few times,
but it's like, it's not insanely expensive.
And those in the best case scenario,
hopefully someday those have the Wally seats.
Sure.
You're on the go.
Don't even have to leave your little booth.
Yeah.
Recline and unwind and.
Great.
Plug in.
Good pooping time.
Just plug in and you're good.
Just plug in and occasionally go to the dining car
to listen to maniacs talk about why they don't fly,
which seems to be most of the conversations I've heard
of people who've done some multi-day train travel
in America, you meet some real interesting characters
on those trains.
Who are like adamant about and spending the whole time
on there talking about why they're not flying.
Or yes, or the positive or like why they love
being on the train.
Hmm.
Joe Biden.
Yeah, he loves.
Future president.
Sure to be.
All right.
Let's see.
I'm making the call right now.
Well, it's good to know about your y'all's habits.
Oh wait, how about this?
Do you guys, do you ever take advantage of some
of the other, you know, if there's a guy handing out stuff,
candy bars, cologne, do you ever do that?
Or is that a nuisance?
It's only a nuisance because sometimes I don't have cash
on me.
I feel like I gotta give a tip and I try to do that.
So sometimes I don't have cash and then I'm stressed out
cause he's handed me a thing.
And I feel like that just that makes me have to give him
a dollar.
I don't think I've ever taken candy.
Mm hmm.
I think maybe I did.
Oh, Jason's smiling from ear to ear.
Well, I actually have a stranger one.
I did not take candy, but was offered the chance
to buy candy.
We were at the Echoplex music venue.
Yeah.
A year ago.
I think for Lindsay's birthday.
Oh yeah, there's a dance party.
They had a guy in the bathroom selling candy.
And I don't know if you're supposed to,
he was selling Lucy's like single cigarette.
So I like bought a single cigarette
to go smoke on the patio.
You bought one cigarette?
I bought one cigarette, yeah.
Neat.
Wow.
Oh, so you did, but that's a very specific partake.
You never did it again?
Just a special occasion?
No, that one I remember.
I feel like I've taken mints or stuff before.
Maybe a mint.
But I feel like at nice places that have that,
they don't usually charge you for candy.
That felt like, you know.
Did you try to take candy and he was like,
no, no, no, no, this is money.
I stopped.
You had put half of the stock in a garbage bag
by the time he said, no, those aren't free.
There wasn't a sign.
Like I was like, so what, how much do I take?
Like I did that sort of like, and he's like,
oh yeah, it's like a dollar.
And you were like, I've never paid that much.
I mean, I socially, I believe if you ask someone
for a cigarette, a quarter or 50 cents
is the polite exchange.
But yeah, it's a venue.
It's, you know, there's a little bit of an extra charge.
So it was understandable.
Right.
I think you've smoked cigarettes here and there.
And I just, I'd be, I really wish and hope,
and I don't think it's true,
but I wish that you like always smoked them
with a penguin style long cigarette holder.
Well, he did not have those for sale for a dollar.
You gotta bring that to the venue yourself.
Less any listeners worry that was my one cigarette
of 2018 or maybe two.
So like, yeah, I don't indulge very much.
You just do it for the look.
I mean, kids, it is very cool.
We're allowed to say whatever we want
behind the second date.
Oh, you're behind the paywall.
We're unregulated.
How weird, they endorse cigarettes on this episode.
No, don't smoke.
No way, man.
Where'd you think?
Vapor.
This episode brought to you by Jewel.
Currently under investigation by the federal government.
Jewel.
Don't smoke, but always Jewel.
Jewel's rule.
We gotta get.
You gotta indulge in something kids.
May as well be Jewel.
I mean, we gotta get McGruff to record a new single
about like, don't vape.
You know?
I mean, whoever McGruff,
I don't know if there's an official McGruff yet.
Yeah.
I just saw somebody post.
If our episode was not an audition for,
I mean, all of us, but especially you, Mike.
Yeah, sure.
To be the new McGruff, official voice of them.
I would happily, I'd throw, I'd put a reel in,
but if it came down to the two of us, it's yours.
Thank you, I appreciate that.
I think though, if you were to listen to all hour
and 50 minutes of that episode,
you'd be like, all those voices are all over the place.
I don't know if he can do the voice consistently for.
We weren't at work.
We weren't getting paid to be McGruff.
That's true.
You start to take it seriously
when you're handed that mantle.
Yeah.
But like it started out strong
and then it's like at the end it was like.
Like I was trying to keep it going, but it was harder.
Sure.
But yeah, you're right.
If I was practicing, which of course I would.
Yeah, I could do it.
As long as I got to make a McGruff album once a year.
If that's part of the, if you just volunteered that also,
and you know what is the best way
that you could end up sounding the most like McGruff,
smoke a lot of cigarettes.
Yeah.
Start smoking.
Get a cool voice like me.
Carton a day.
The American tobacco industry contributes jobs
for lots of people.
We don't want those jobs going to other countries, do you?
Start smoking kids.
So let me ask you guys in terms of,
cause we talked about like Disney movies
you'd like to go to the restroom in.
Any other intellectual properties
that you wish you could see a bathroom, like non Disney?
Other films and stuff.
Oh, interesting.
I spun out something in preparation for this.
That's not Disney, although it is now.
I was thinking about the recently acquired property,
Fox property of Alien.
And how about this?
Why can't going to the bathroom in a theme park
have a story?
So what if when you enter the bathroom
and then enter the stall,
you are in the worlds of the Nostromo
and you lock the door and you are not just going
to the bathroom, although I mean, feel free,
but you're hiding from the xenomorph
and there's a screen on the door and you can see
the dot or the square representing it coming after you.
So you're kind of, you know,
they got to keep the traffic flowing in those places anyway.
So that sort of hopefully helps speed up the process
and gets those bowels moving,
knowing that it's like getting closer and closer and closer.
And maybe as it's getting closer,
you start involving some of those old Alien
encounter effects and it sounds like in the stalls
next to you, there's a tax going on.
So you got to wrap it up.
Suddenly it's not just going to the bathroom.
It's a flight of fear.
Oh, see, I don't know.
I might have the opposite.
I might be too scared to go, but you just don't.
Oh yeah.
I do like the opportunity for like a Weyland
Yutani branded toilet.
The fake corporation that runs everything in those movies.
Oh, that's a good little bit of world building.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I think it's tough because like that's a great idea,
but I do think you're going to have a lot of people
getting backed up because they're so scared.
Yeah, I'm assuming that people have the opposite problem
and just go.
Uh-huh.
That's one way to get scared and have it relate to your...
There's going to be a lot of like people like with bowel
problems by the end of the first day, I think,
where people are like stuck.
They're back to there.
They'll have to, there'll be like a run on laxative
later that day.
So it's just now become not, not actually the opposite
of why it was built.
It actually, you're guaranteed to not go to the bathroom
in this bathroom.
Cause your fight or flight response would be like,
we got to get out of here.
We don't have time for this.
So that's a problem.
I was thinking about it and this was my concern.
Any like, you know, intense or action movie,
I don't want to be startled in the bathroom.
I want no conflicts in the bathroom.
I want something relaxing.
And so I would like a bathroom based on the 2015 movie,
The Intern starring Robert De Niro and Anne Hathaway.
A very pleasant movie with seemingly no conflicts in it
at all.
And I guess really any Nancy Meyer movie would do.
Later Nancy Meyer.
It seems like there's a lot more going on
in like Private Benjamin, but like it's complicated.
The Intern, you know, big kitchens and big bathrooms,
nice furnishings.
Like up to date equipment.
Up to date, yeah.
Yeah.
I think, look, we were talking about, that's good.
I would like those.
Nancy Meyer's great kitchens, great bathrooms.
Do you have the same problem with Tangled
where Intern fans are furious that that's all
that it's being represented as, is a bathroom?
Cause they've been demanding an Intern presence
in the parks for a while.
Maybe, but I think it is, you know,
I think it's kind of been eclipsed by Book Club,
which is not a Nancy Meyer's movie,
but it kind of exists in the same sort of genre
of like very pleasant movie with minimal conflicts.
Which Book Club bathroom also where you get a copy of,
there's a stack of all of the 50 Shades of Grey books
that you can peruse.
Yeah.
That's what they watch in the, yeah.
So you can read along with them.
Then you just might be too scandalized to go to the bathroom.
Yeah, that's true.
Oh my.
Or it makes you get your groove back
and you march out of the bathroom,
forgetting why you even got there in the first place.
Similar issue with the alien thing then.
Yeah.
Just marching out with not having gone.
We're talking about bathrooms
that are transformative experiences.
I think. It's pretty cool.
I think like there's a upcoming,
we talked about it on the show, the Play Pavilion,
upcoming Epcot thing where they're gonna be
maybe cycling in different.
Now I'm not going where you think I'm going with this.
Gameify shit.
Although I guess we could come up with a couple,
there's nine toilets and they're all shaped like bowling pins
and you have to like shit in the right ones to knock over.
There is that, but that's not what I'm going with that.
I'm not gonna go with that gross.
That's not who I am as a performer.
You're rated PG.
I'm PG, otherwise cursed a little too much on this episode.
We all have.
You could put in different experiences.
I think that's what they're talking about with play.
You can sub in.
Jim Hill was talking about the potential for moving in
like an old attraction and you could kind of experience it
in VR or in a big screen,
like the way that the Imagineers test out new rides.
So I wanna make sort of maybe a generic bathroom,
but you would move with maybe a group of whatever,
say the bathroom as 12 people could use the bathroom at once,
20 people at once.
So there's a line for this bathroom
because it's highly themed.
Well, there's a show really.
And you would cycle in and out
famous bathroom scenes in films.
So 20 people would be taken out of the line.
You'd walk in and stand in the bathroom.
And then all of a sudden a famous bathroom scene
from a movie would happen,
but it wouldn't necessarily be the same one every time.
So maybe you get the cable guy scene
where Jim Carrey comes in and beats up Owen Wilson.
Maybe you get Mission Impossible Fallout
where there's a Cavill-Tom Cruise pipe battle
with a crazy ninja guy who goes through a mirror.
Maybe it's a...
Maybe it's the Godfather when Michael Corleone goes in
to get the gun hidden in the toilet tank.
Very good point.
It could be that scene too.
So you basically are sort of watching a little show
that happens before you actually use the restroom.
So the little flash mobby show or something happens.
Oh, wasn't that fun?
You just use the bathroom like regular.
So there's no problem.
You're not gonna be backed up.
You're not gonna be scared.
The show is over and then you get to use the bathroom
after a fun show.
Wow.
And you're right that the theme park bathroom
of the future should have themes that you could trade
in and out and keep up to date
with what today's audiences wanna see.
Right.
Maybe the cable guy.
The cable guy or the scene where Seabass comes back in
and dumb and dumber.
When is it Harry's or Lloyd is waiting for...
Oh, cause he's waiting cause he thinks there's gonna be
like a sexual encounter in the stall
and then it's Seabass again.
Also in Liar Liar, Jim Carrey beats himself up
in the bathroom.
Oh yeah.
He did a lot of bathroom.
Maybe it's just Jim Carrey movie bathroom stuff.
Sure.
The Jim Carrey, there's like very little Jim Carrey
presence in theme parks in general.
And maybe the bathrooms is the way in.
Yeah, for sure.
All right, well then there's a Jim Carrey bathroom.
That's my pitch.
That's interactive and changes out and it's perfect.
Like the Play Pavilion.
Boy.
Same thing.
Great.
You know, we came in prepared to make fun of this area,
but now it's inspired us to dream of bigger
and greater bathrooms in theme parks.
And legitimately with those Harry Potter weird smells
and giggles and whatever they're planning in the future.
Yeah.
Bathrooms are becoming part of the experience
and let's keep it that way.
I have a little cliffhanger here.
I was on a blog called the DisneylandDad.com
and he was ranking Disneyland bathrooms.
And he listed all the ones you think flows
and Pacific Wharf, whatever.
And then he said the best bathroom at Disneyland Resort?
I'm not telling.
They are the best because they are the most hidden.
Aren't included on any of the maps nor on the new app.
Then he says like, subscribe to his email
and then he'll let you know.
So maybe that's the way to find it.
But I'm wondering, other than the only one
I can think of off the top of my head,
the Tiki Room bathroom.
Uh-huh.
Could be that. Yeah.
But other than that,
do we know what Disneyland Dad is talking about?
I have a guess.
The restrooms in the lobby
are kind of adjacent to the lobby.
In the Disneyland Hotel,
Disneyland Hotel kind of built many decades ago.
You have to go like down these stairs.
They're built underneath.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
I think it might maybe those sort of off the beaten path
Disneyland Hotel ones.
Okay. Well, I'm just saying,
we're going to have to find out what Disneyland Dad
is talking about when we talk toilets next on the net.
We'll make sure we have the answer.
We'll try to outsmart Disneyland Dad once and for all.
Yeah. I just, yeah.
He frustrated me with that article.
So.
Yeah. What a tease.
You couldn't just subscribe to his email?
I'm just money, I think, isn't it?
Oh. Or maybe it's not.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe it's just signing up for an email
which Disneyland Dad will tell me.
Well, if it does cost money
then you know a way to outsmart Disneyland Dad.
Email us at podcasts.
Write a Gmail.
Otherwise follow us on Twitter and Instagram
and keep subscribing to the second gate
for more talking number two.
It's been a blast.
All right.
Yep.
Catch you later.
Bye. Bye.