Podcasts Arise doing a live show in Los Angeles.
Yay, June 7th at Dynasty Typewriter.
It's gonna be fun, we're doing a very special topic
and we have very special guests planned.
No hints right now, just mystery.
Now if you want tickets, go to dynastytypewriter.com
or there's a link right to it on our Twitter.
It's the pin tweet at the top of our Twitter.
You can get it there,
you can probably get a link somewhere else,
but those are the two places
I'm letting you know about right now.
June 7th, Los Angeles Dynasty Typewriter Podcasts Arise live.
Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains wall crawling,
web slinging, silk secretions, radioactive body fluids,
and an eight-eyed look at Universal Orlando's
The Amazing Adventures of Spider-Man.
Excelsior, it's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a show hosted by three men
who describe recording two episodes back to back
as the most dangerous night of our lives and yours.
I'm Jason Chariton, as always my scout character.
That's the famous catchphrase.
It is to me and we'll get into that.
Mike Carlson here as always.
I had no idea where you were going with that.
I was like, I guess we get tired.
I think you were gonna make fun of us for being like tired,
like tired of podcasting after two because it can get.
Well, it's like as harrowing as we get.
We don't face challenges as much as Spider-Man
today's topic.
No.
But I don't know, most dangerous night of our lives
in a way potentially does apply to what I wanted
to talk about and we will get to Spider-Man obviously.
We'll, you know, I'll veer back to that track,
but there's something important that I need to address,
which is that I have recently come across
a rather interesting video of one of you, my co-hosts.
Oh no.
I'm not sure if you can guess.
No, you found it?
But I have a feeling.
Oh man.
You know the man, sir.
Oh, it exists.
It certainly does.
Wow.
You knew it was coming.
That was quick.
I guess.
Not too bad, not too bad, right?
It is the most dangerous night of your life.
For you it's easy.
You're like back at the station, like Jameson.
Yeah, not worrying about like getting sepsis
or Listeria or whatever diseases.
Oh wow.
Yeah, it's happening, it happened.
Let me explain.
If you didn't hear it back on our Expedition Everest episode,
we talked about, I forget even why it came up to begin with,
but there was a giant epilogue devoted to Mike's appearance
on the dearly departed Spike TV show, Mansers.
Right, yes.
Which if you aren't previously aware,
I mean first of all, it's a place where dudes
can find out the answers to, you know,
like can tits fart and that kind of thing.
The answers that probing bros wanna know.
Their language, not ours.
And then it would be in the void of like,
what do you think, can tits fart?
Like that would be the way it would be presented.
I think that's how we got into it,
was talking about Travel Channel voice,
which morphed into Spike TV voice.
You're correct.
That is related, and then Mike,
you revealed a little too much information.
I even went back to check,
and you like almost didn't give the nuggets of what it was.
I was gonna tease it, I was gonna tease it for like later,
but then I said a little bit more about it
at the end of the show,
and then it was just like, all right, here we go.
Yeah, yeah, we coasted out of here.
I hope it was helpful.
I feel like you aired this,
then you can go back to that episode
to hear the allure of details of Mike's horrible shoot.
It's at the end, yeah.
Yeah, we basically tacked on a mini episode.
That we didn't expect.
Yeah.
Which honestly made me feel more bad
about the whole endeavor than anything else,
because this was your first shoot for television,
quote unquote, and yet it was more unprofessional
than this very podcast.
Just a mess with no makeup and hair,
and you were just pointed at
and forced to make out with a stranger
who was upset to have to do it.
Yeah, she was mad about doing it,
and then she stormed off.
Then there was a negotiation happened without me,
and then some sort of resolution happened again without me,
and then I was not filled in on what the resolution would be,
and then I was just told, okay, action.
With no time to adjust back into,
oh, now I get to make out with someone?
What are we doing?
I didn't know, and you can probably see, I don't know,
but you probably can't, because the thing is edited so well.
Well, it's aggressively edited.
That's certainly true.
I think you convey false pleasure very well,
and then so much of it is discomfort
that you were probably able to use
what you were actually feeling.
If I could just say really quickly
how I came across this clip,
because I think I noted in the episode
that I had tried to find it randomly before
without really any clues,
just because you can buy them piecemeal on Amazon Prime.
You do have to buy them, though.
It is $2 a pop.
So with every false attempt, I'm losing $2.
But I'd forgotten about this entirely
until bug main Extended Universe character,
Franklin Lombardo, tweeted a picture of the DVD
of Best of Mansers Season One, which I got.
Right, I saw this happening on Twitter, too.
I think I tweeted, hey, or something.
You just tweeted, hey.
Scott is holding the cursed object.
The Best of Mansers Season One,
it has is the death touch for real?
It has how teeny can a bikini get
before it's legally considered nudity?
And then just how can you get drunk faster?
That's nice and basic.
So popped in the DVD, and sure enough,
it was not on the DVD.
More money wasted.
The joke's on me.
How much money are you in at this point in the story?
I think I've spent, I think in the search for this,
I've spent about 20 bucks.
It's not crazy, but that's a meal or two, potentially.
And I can't tell you how dramatic it was
to be watching Mansers Best of Season One with Aaron,
and around every, it's a countdown from 25 to one,
and the closer we get to one, we lose our chance.
Like, oh, there's only two left,
and then there'll be a bonus Manser,
and you'll go, maybe it's the bonus.
But none of them were, but I was like,
there's gotta be a way, and there was a way.
I searched Twitter for the words Manser's British hand job,
and I went as far back as that could be found,
and I found two tweets, really,
we're going back to the dawn of Twitter.
This is early days of Twitter.
It's 2008, or seven.
A little later, this episode aired specifically
on January 20th, 2010.
It did?
Yep, yep, and I was able to cross-check that
with the air dates on Amazon Prime, and bang,
before I knew it, I had your episode.
It's like 306, 307, I forget which one exactly.
But, yeah, this, you know, really,
I wanna put the choice in your hands.
With great power comes great responsibility, Mike.
Whatever, I could play it if you wanna relive this now,
if you wanna shove it back in a drawer,
but I do have it available for you, if you wish to see it.
Well, the audience, look, if it's content,
and if it's going to draw the audience in,
we need the content to be shared, so.
That was my justification.
I don't feel great about this.
I'm no prankster, I'm not trying to embarrass you,
and I don't think it is embarrassing, by the way.
I think it is an acting job, and it's a.
I mean, it is embarrassing, let's be honest.
I don't know, though, I don't know.
I should weigh in here and say,
today's topic is maybe my favorite ride.
And we're.
We got a specially long line.
And especially there's a dark, yeah,
this is actually a good throwback
to the first opening few years,
when this was the most popular ride on Universal Property.
It's a frustrating wait.
You didn't get Universal Express.
This is like you without Universal Express.
No, it took a little while, and yeah, but that said,
this queue, much less satisfying.
All right.
Well, the faster we get it done with,
the faster we can get to Spider-Man.
Back into it, because.
No, this is important to weigh in with.
I don't want to, this should not be a side track episode,
however.
It should not be, but let's draw it out a little longer,
because I have the email for my call time,
and I do see that it was 2009, which is crazy,
because that's how long I've been in Los Angeles,
and I'm losing my mind.
It was Tuesday, September 8th is when we shot it.
Your call time for Tuesday is 7 a.m. at our bar,
which is located blah, blah, blah.
Your on-site contact is Katie,
I won't give her phone number.
For wardrobe, please bring a variety of options
that you would wear to a club or a bar.
A couple of pairs of jeans, T-shirts,
button-downs, polos, et cetera.
So, you know, a country bear jamboree shirt,
a Oliver and Company ringer tee, you know.
Also, you may want to bring a book or a magazine to read,
because you may have some downtime.
You mean like jugs weekly, like something a man would read?
So yeah, so I remember now, I got there,
and I did not have any downtime.
I mean, I may have it later, but I was literally sat down,
like, all right, you over here.
I was wearing a green shirt,
they didn't look at any of my wardrobe.
I just stood up and they went, all right, here we go.
So that, wow, that is crazy.
So that is, so 2009, so that's,
we're coming up almost on the 10th anniversary.
10th anniversary of your first screen appearance.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Maybe there was something before.
Let's, I mean, should we just play the audio?
I think the main way for you, the listener,
to watch this will be on Twitter,
because the audio's not great and it's not terribly fun.
I even edited it down, I did the luxury,
and I edited it in such a way that you will,
I moved up the appearance of someone else we know
in this very segment.
So you ready?
And the audio's not great, so I'll just play a quick second,
but just for you to transport back to it.
I mean, yeah, play as much as you want.
I haven't seen it in a few years.
I think, can everybody see, okay, we'll find out,
but you'll be delighted by the extra cameo.
I forget who the extra cameo is even.
That's me and British Babe at the bar,
totally ready to play Yashydoodle with your big face.
But wait, dude, something here stinks.
Why should you never get a hand job from a British chick?
At this point, let me just pause it and describe it,
which is that a woman in a Union Jack dress
has spotted you without any dialogue, obviously,
because that caught sex through it,
pushed you against the wall of a bar,
and just started to just whip straight to it,
although making out kind of just on your neck.
You didn't really have to kiss in this.
That's the story, so to fill in a little more
if you didn't go back and listen to the Expedition Everest,
what the situation was was that she didn't wanna make out,
she stormed off the set, the director got pissed,
they went ahead and had a negotiation, came back,
and they didn't tell me what the deal was,
and then they just said action,
and I was so scared and weirded out and confused,
and then she just sort of like gently put her head
on the other side of my neck to, I guess,
make it look like she was kissing my neck,
which she was not, she was barely even touching me.
It wouldn't fool anybody.
It's clearly someone kissing a neck.
Right, and I think I even in the first take
wanted to be like, does this look okay?
This doesn't look good, right?
But obviously- You would be the first person
to ask any question on the set of Mansers.
Right.
I think this was a shoot, shoot, shoot scenario.
Yeah, and I think they were like,
well, we'll just speed it up,
and there'll be an aggressive man narrating it,
and it won't matter, which is obviously what happened.
Late Ots reality TV production was just absolutely dog shit.
As someone who worked a pH of like eight shows,
like terrible, especially right after the writer's strike.
They were just grinding stuff out to fill time.
And it's obviously gotten way better
in the era of non-union web production.
Yes, yeah, absolutely.
Now we live in a paradise.
Everything's great.
Okay, so Mike's up against a wall,
and things were pleasurable,
but now they have turned very sour.
As your buyer, you gotta get out of there.
I'm a whine, oh you a whine.
Did you see the camera?
Yeah, I did.
Yes, I did see him.
Right off the show, and past guest of the show,
Jordan Morris, in the very same segment as you.
I forgot all about that.
Seemingly in a, he's just making kind of a like,
hmm face that could apply probably to any Manser.
He's a very broad, confused man.
A performer who I know is capable
of more subtlety than that.
But I think on Mansers,
you yourself included, everybody had to act
as if they had like, got hit in the head
with a brick a couple times.
Yeah, I had to play it so big,
it was like I was acting at the Staples Center
for the back row.
You have to have your expression read
for the very cheap nosebleed seats at an arena.
Though the camera is four inches away from your face.
Yes, yes.
And I honestly, I remember seeing it and going,
oh man, I played that too big.
I remember thinking that initially.
At the bed at the same time,
it's what they required.
Yeah.
And what other way can you play a man
who has realized there's fecal matter on his penis
and thus height, like at the very end,
and I won't play it, they'll save this for YouTube,
but at the very end, you speed out of the room
in a Wile E. Coyote manner,
leaving a trail of smoke behind you.
Yes.
And she waves goodbye and she still has toilet paper
dangling off of her fingers.
That is how much this woman has just been to the bathroom.
She tried to clean herself.
Which I think is not really,
it really goes against what the lesson was,
is that they just didn't wash their hands enough.
So toilet, well, actually now that I think about it,
no, I guess it's right.
So the idea is she didn't wash her hands.
She just went in and got the toilet paper
stuck all over her hand and then didn't wash her hand.
So now that I think about it, that's actually.
Oh, it is consistent.
It is consistent.
It's horrifying.
I think I would have noticed that too,
if she just had toilet paper stuck to her hand.
When you say you edited that,
did you add any extra sound effects
or that is the direct,
that is the normal cut level of sound effects?
That's as it came.
And though that probably sounded very tinny
as being filmed off of a computer monitor
and then shown through an iPad
and then played on a podcast,
the sound was as unpleasant raw as when I heard it
as you the listener just heard it.
But also here, let me play one more thing.
And Mike is actually not part of this segment.
The reveal of why you shouldn't make out
with a British chick, but this is like.
Hand job.
Oh yeah, why do I keep self-censoring?
Yeah, come on Scott, ass eating is a 2019 thing,
not a 2009 thing, all right?
You don't want a British chick touching your love stick
because British babes have poo pans.
Poo pans.
And they made like a graphic cover of her hand
that looked like her hand was covered in poop.
She did like a talk to the hand motion
and then they covered it in feces,
like a graphic of feces.
In addition to a recession of jobs and money,
we also had a recession of taste in 2008, 2009.
It's funny because this would come out,
if this exact thing played in 2019,
people would say, well, we deserve Trump.
We have brought Trump upon ourselves.
But this played in the, just straight in the middle
of Obama, it's not as if like, you know,
we feel like things have gotten more coarse,
but Mansers was, you know, right at the tip top
of the administration, so.
The hooting.
Who's to blame?
The hoards of like, yeah, I'm gonna ask for straws
and I'm gonna watch whatever problematic movie,
I'm gonna watch Revenge of the Nerds
however much I want, you know,
would be hooting and hollering for that garbage.
Mansers, apparently I think Mansers had the issue
where it was a really highly rated show,
but the reruns would rate just as high as the new episodes.
So at a certain point, they just like had so many produced
because they were very popular for Spike TV.
I liked the show.
I feel like, I like a show where the producers
are shitty clearly, but you know there are people working,
places in the show like editors,
and people are getting in subtle digs
and like, oh let's like twist this on itself
and show that we know it's bad.
That was how I felt about my super sweet 16.
Like that was set up in a very cynical way
to like, let's put these awful girls on display
in the, you know, the vest wealth they throw around,
but you could tell the editors would like cut it
to make them, they'd get in digs at the girls
and the dads and everything.
I think Mansers, I bet like if you talked to a Mansers editor,
he'd be like, yeah, I was trying to be funny.
Is that like, but is it an early sort of paving the way
for like a Vanderpump rules or like the insanity
that everyone agrees that's like,
well this is a trashy nightmare, but we love it.
I think you gotta trace that stuff back earlier
than my super sweet 16 or whatever it was called.
I mean, the Temptation Island is back on USA Network
for God's sake and that's over 20 years old at this point.
I keep seeing, like it comes on after like SmackDown.
Is that right?
Well, we'll watch it a little bit later today.
Yeah, so I'll catch, I've caught a little of it here
and there and I honestly have not followed what's going on.
It seems like just people cheating on each other,
either physically or emotionally
and then feeling bad about it.
That's the show.
In front of cameras.
You've got it, you got it down.
But you were really, you got to be a pioneer in this genre.
A decade ago, I got to do one of these early,
well not early, it was still 10 years
into this trash reality show stuff.
But I just, my main takeaway is I just, you know,
it's no offense to you, I find it unrealistic
that you would be somewhere and a woman
in a Union Jack dress would just leap all over you unprompted.
That clearly is what would happen with a mouse woman
in a red polka dot dress.
A much more realistic scenario.
Yeah, yeah.
Honestly.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
Why?
Like whatever, whatever Foley effects,
like whatever stock effects you can use for free.
Why you shouldn't get hugs from a mouse woman.
She's a mouse, she eats shit all the time.
She hangs out with a dog and a duck.
They eat shit too.
I was just going to say,
Minnie was much more intimate with me though
than this woman was comfortable being
because Minnie would put her snoot right on top of me.
Her snoot?
Yeah, I call it snoot.
I like calling it, I call Edwin's snout a snoot more than,
but it is, it is real.
That's real, look it up.
That's a pronunciation for snout.
But she would just like shove it into me and go skin.
Then the performer would say, kiss.
She would make a kiss noise.
And it happened to me at the contemporary,
happened to me at Epcot Center.
And then I think it happened to me at Disneyland too.
So there was connection there and that's maybe why it's,
perhaps unsettling to watch that video
because you sense how false it was.
It was fake, yeah.
It was just so that you both could get
your $75 for the day.
Yes, and it was $120 I think
for an unlimited buyout.
Oh man.
I believe that's right. That sucks.
And then what extra sucks is that like Jordan
and other people that were, that had to react,
they just did that once and they got one fee of $120.
So he's probably in a whole two or three seasons going,
what?
And then he like makes that like, yeah.
And they can use it for things like, you know,
like, like why is Al-Qaeda good and just?
Yeah.
So I think if they brought Mansers back,
they could probably legally use that footage again.
They could re-edit my footage probably.
I don't have to, I'm not owed anything.
And they could do those.
They could answer those questions.
Why Laurie Loughlin was in the right.
It would be.
Why Sharia Law is great.
It would be funny if Mansers came back as like a,
as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a,
as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a,
a very like political left leaning show that would now try
to answer the true questions that are facing Americans.
Why you have to like these movies paid for partially
by the United States guard services.
And then it's just me, you and a British woman.
Just figure out a way to cut that in.
Well, it like represents like some geopolitical.
Yeah, that's true.
Oil.
Well, they, yeah, they make a special commercial
for the United States army or air force.
And then they make the SAS, the special air service
or the Royal air force in England.
Purpose as highfalutin of a purpose of this can be.
And when you, when you, when you sign that buyout,
you didn't realize it could be used in perpetuity
and on podcasts in 10 years.
No, it's true.
I did not see that coming,
but it's there.
Hey, look up podcasts, the ride on YouTube and, and you can,
you can join in the fun.
Real quick.
Do we answer the question you found it?
It was just a clip posted.
No, no, no.
I, I, I get NASA now and $22 in the tank.
I'm edging, I'm getting towards I see, I see you found the,
I got, I got it.
I almost spent to find this.
I almost spent what you were paid to make it.
I was glad I didn't get it.
It was like at least like, like three hours of your time.
I think honestly, now that I think about it,
and this is a funny thing you do after you've been around
for a while, maybe I put that back in my reel.
Maybe that's a conversation starters.
Or yeah, maybe that's number one on the reel.
Cut anything I was in with a celebrity and it's just that.
It shows that you can go broad.
Yeah.
That's what they're after.
You're scalable.
You're a scalable.
Come on, Seth Rogan, put me in a gross out movie of yours.
Come on.
You see what face I can make when I smelled duty.
You could be used as a reference for sausage party too.
Yeah.
Like as like, here's what an animated character would do.
If they bugged their eyes out,
I'll be like a Sean gun motion capturing rocket raccoon
for the sausage, the new sausage and sausage party.
There is a part they do show.
I think they represent you getting fecal matter
on your penis by showing a hot dog dipped into chocolate,
which as I say it on the one hand, a little upsetting,
but on the other hand,
maybe something that Jason would want to consume.
We talk in chocolate hot dogs.
You can send me.
Usually, I mean, I've heard of chocolate covered starfish
and hot dog flavored water.
Certainly.
Yes, we never thought about just combining two
of my faze these foods.
Well, ignore the metaphor and just enjoy that
on its own merits.
And with that said, we can now get back
to another red suited character of whom we are more fond
than Mike was fond of the union Jack woman.
Yeah.
And that is spider man.
What are the,
I don't know how we would cover.
I'm gonna have to like rest for all the G O Jason talk
for a while.
One of the few fictional, I feel like, you know,
you hear about like millennials being in like a, you know,
forever adolescence or whatever,
arrested development and all that.
And I like to think part of me is, is, oh, that's not true.
That's not the case, but I am like,
I would call spider man a friend.
Oh geez.
I would say like, oh, my friend spider man,
it's like, oh, I'm always happy to see him.
I think the other one or another character,
I would say that about would be R2D2.
Like it's like, I like these characters.
I find these characters very in your,
that's me with the racks.
That's what you see.
You admitted that to Tony Baxter.
I think this, I think it's a nice feeling.
Yeah.
A lot of, there's a lot of friends in theme park world.
So you would think, cause I'm trying to think I would,
when I read X-Men, cause with comics, I was,
X-Men was the first like superhero Marvel comics.
I was way into, and I would imagine living
at the X-Men mansion.
Sure.
When Harry Potter like started, I really got it.
Cause I felt like everyone was thinking,
dreaming of when they would get their owl
and they would go to Hogwarts and they would live there.
But I had the same fantasy about the X-Men's mansion.
I would go to the X-Men's mansion.
Rogue would find a cure for her powers.
And then we would fall in love and I would ice Gambit out.
Sure.
I loved Gambit.
Gambit's a cat, a rogue.
You don't settle down with that.
Right.
I mean, I'm definitely in the comics.
They are in canon merit now.
They've settled down once in a while.
But so, so it was, I guess that's,
I was thinking about that.
Were you kind of fantasizing as a kid about being buddies
with Spider-Man?
Well, I guess I probably was too.
Yeah. I mean, I, I like you was more of an X-Men kid.
Although even as a kid, I was like, in 90s X-Men,
it's harder to square the circle of like,
you go to the school and live with them because how old are
the fucking Jim Lee 90s X-Men?
I was like, Oh, look like they're 35 years old, 40.
And they're all still living at Xavier school
for gifted youngsters, which that was a whole issue
in like 94 and 95 was they changed the side,
the sign to Xavier's school for higher learning.
Cause they're like, Oh no, the youngsters are in a
generation X they're in Massachusetts now.
Right. Yes. That's true.
And then they, they started to change stuff.
Cause when Grant Morrison came in the book,
then he put a bunch of like young people in the school.
It went back to being a full school.
Why are all these old people hanging out?
Why are all these old people with seemingly unlimited?
Because that's the other thing with the X-Men is they either
get their unlimited money from angel from Warren
Worthington's fortune or Charles Xavier's.
We lost Scott already. We've lost.
I needed a break. So that's good. Okay. Good. That's,
that's fine. Have at it.
I'll say this is my ideal X-Men lineup and not characters
wise, I'm fine with rotating characters.
In fact, I think like the Avengers,
they should rotate in and out.
But I think it's five to eight X-Men and the supporting cast
is students, the X-Men comics for the last 10 years or so,
it just been like, here's 30 X-Men, every issue.
I'm look, I'm torn. Look,
we have to get back to Spider-Man cause I can talk of another
two and a half hours about the X-Men's perfect lineup.
Uh, but I am torn on this cause I like a nice small team.
I like the grand Morrison run. I like the Josh Whedon run a lot.
Uh, but, uh, we grew up on an X-Men when X-Men had two teams,
a blue team and a gold team.
And there were about 15 people on each team.
No, it was like six or seven on each team. I don't know.
I think we're maybe we're in the middle. I think was smaller.
I think blue team would be more anyway. Now we have to tell,
we have to figure out, I'll say this,
the difference between me as a kid, um, uh, with,
with X-Men and Spider-Man, like X-Men, I,
I put me more at ease cause I'm like, okay,
at least they all have powers and they could all have each other.
Spider-Man, I was like, Spider-Man's fun and cool,
but Peter Parker's problems stress me out and his supporting cast are all
like frail people or his high school bully who also works at the
newspapers sometimes.
And occasionally someone else with power shows up,
but they're not guaranteed to be there. Like he's, he's kind of on his own.
So Spider-Man's like alter ego life.
Peter Parker constantly struggling, which stressed me out.
I agree with that.
I think I liked the X-Men cause there wasn't so much of that.
I think I liked Spider-Man. I liked the fact that he was a kid.
Cause I liked Robin. I liked reading impulse.
I liked the kids stuff to imagine I was a kid,
but Peter Parker was like two working class and I wanted to imagine you lived in
like a fancy mansion. I was like, sort of, I think,
I think that stressed me out too, where it was like,
he's always in trouble and like he's worried about like his aunt catching him
and he's got homework. And it was like, that's too much pressure for me.
I liked the X-Men where they're all like their parents hate them cause they're
mutants. But then they don't have to deal with them.
They don't have to talk to them anymore. And then that's not,
I'm saying I didn't want to talk to my parents. Don't get me wrong.
I was, I want to hear other problems. It was just,
it was more of a fantasy of thinking the X-Men would move away.
X-Men was soap opera, but I kind of, I liked that more. I liked when Peter
and MJ were married, like they were married for like 20,
30 years and then he got the devil to undo it.
And it's a whole fucking mess. Yeah.
It looks like we're, as far as the team, I think you were closer.
I think it's like eight from my account real quick. Yeah.
Do you want me, I think I can do blue. I think I can do these off the dome. Hey,
do it. Go for it. Gold team. Jean Grey storm,
Iceman, angel, Archangel at the time.
And Bishop eventually joined once he got stranded in our time.
And isn't professor X on the gold team as well.
Professor X is more to the gold team because cyclops led the blue team,
but then storm or I think led the gold team. Did she? I think,
so blue team, I think, no way.
She was on that was she on the white team, right? Sure. She had her later.
That was later.
Blue team, Cyclops, rogue, Gambit, Psylocke, Jubilee.
I think that's it. Beast. Yeah. Beast. You're right. And there's like Gambit.
I said Gambit. Okay. All right.
They'll hang out even though they're on different teams.
So you're that well,
that was a lot of conflict cause Jean and Scott were on different teams and
then Psylocke and Scott had to think for a while and Psylocke and Archangel on
and off for years. It's yeah.
So you would split up couples once in a while,
but then they kind of broke that down pretty quickly. That's a whole,
we'll do that one. We finally build an X-Men ride that we like. I mean,
the storm ride is fine at islands of adventure,
but it's not quite the level of the Spiderman ride. Sure. So,
but Spiderman, I, I, the Spiderman ride, I think too,
and I'm going to give this ride so much praise and researching this ride.
Most of the articles about it are universal acclaim.
So I don't feel as bad doing that,
but I think this is my platonic ideal of Spiderman. Like,
it's like the nineties. It's kind of the cartoon. He's fighting bad guys.
There's a little bit of Peter stuff, but it's more like funny.
It's more like bumbling and funny in the queue.
There's not a lot of stressed out.
Tonally this is the year the Spiderman that you, yeah. It's not too,
it's not too dark. It's not, it's silly. It's still fun. Gotcha.
I get what you're saying. I mean, because it's very,
there's a lot of like nineties cartoon influence on it. Yes.
Especially the queue. I feel like,
cause the characters is that character designs are different than the cartoon,
but in the queue,
it very much feels like J.
Joan and Jameson's office from the nineties cartoon. Yeah.
Inspired by it at least, which famously voiced by Ed Asner,
just for a little, a little trivia there in the, in the ride. No,
in the, or maybe in the ride, we should look that up,
but in the cartoon from the nineties at Asner does J.
Joan and Jameson's.
Fun. So he's another newspaper editor and yeah,
I assume that's what Jameson is. Yeah, he is. Yeah. That's good point.
Lou grant. Then of course he was the head of Mary Tyler Moore's newsroom.
Of course everyone knows that,
but then he of course was spun off into his own show,
Lou grand where he was the head of a newspaper. Yeah. More dramatic. Yep.
Need a good Mary Tyler Moore ride. Yeah. Well they never.
Well that one also will have a photography dark room with hand prints on the
walls and ceiling, but it won't be explained.
If there was a Mary Tyler Moore ride that we didn't know about that it closed,
I feel like whoever texted on our chain, we would have been like,
put a pot of coffee on. We gotta go now. We gotta do this.
It is whatever time of this. Yeah. Like 2 AM.
We have to get together and record this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't think it exists,
but if you know of it, please tweet it us. Yeah.
In a theme park recreation of Minneapolis of miniature Minneapolis,
right? One of the rejected islands of islands of nature.
Let me just say the broad strokes details just in case opening day islands of
adventure attraction at universal Orlando, gigantic ride.
Probably what they like, I don't know what they put their money into,
obviously, but like, doesn't it say,
I feel like this was like the big opening day.
It was technologically years ahead of everything else,
probably cost a fortune.
Everything I think in any of the, like, I'm not sure Disney had,
had gotten there. And if you haven't been on this ride, it's what it,
but you have been on the transformers ride.
Those are clear analogs and it's the same ride vehicle and the same general idea
moving from screen to room screen to room.
And it's thrill ride, but a simulator and this,
this has been so many things that are like this now.
And this was the first and like, like truly unbelievable.
The first time you went on it,
they invented a technique that universal owns the copyright for called squinching
to account for the distortion one would feel about viewing a 3d footage while in
movement. Cause before this 3d footage, you would be watching it stationary.
So they had to write an algorithm,
figure out how if it distorts in this way,
we have to factor in an equal amount of distortion the opposite way.
And that'll balance it out.
So that if you are entering a room with the 3d screen from the left and then
leaving through the right,
the perspective has to perfectly match where your eyes would be over and over
again all day.
And if you just stayed in one place and weren't moving and just stared at that
screen, it would look bizarre and distorted and bendy and weird,
but it also, it only works in motion.
It is crazy when you think about it,
cause it works so well and you take it for granted.
But yeah,
it's like just walking in and like walking into a movie theater and seeing
things from different perspectives.
Like if you walked across a movie theater and then the screen like changed,
so you almost perfectly saw it and it looked like it was coming head on to you
while you were moving.
Like that's impop like impossible.
It is a thing.
It's there's essentially a thing like this in mission impossible for,
Oh yeah.
He in Russia,
he like puts up a screen and land it like,
like lines up with the pupils of the security guards that it moves with his
perspective.
So they can't,
so we can't see the Tom Cruise just down the hallway.
It is his mission impossible level technology.
Yeah.
And the entire thing is like military grade tech net,
like the,
like yeah,
probably the most technologically advanced ride ever upon its opening and
that universal had it not Disney.
I don't,
I was trying to think like,
Oh,
when did Disney top this?
Cause I think universal matched it with forbidden journey.
And it's the same idea with like the,
the attempt at a seamless transition between sets and screens.
Yeah.
Giving you a much more dynamic experience than a pure screen ride might give
you.
And a lot of the people who worked heavily on this went on to work heavily
on a forbidden journey.
And the more I thought about it,
I was wondering when did Disney top this or has Disney top this
flight of passage.
Oh,
it's pretty close.
I don't know if initially,
like I don't know if I was wowed as spectacularly as I was by Spiderman the
first time.
I don't know if I was,
I don't know if I was.
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
But I think it's,
I don't know if it's as spectacularly as I was by Spiderman the first time,
but pretty close.
It's not quite the same.
Cause there's not physical sets,
but as far as immersion and three D and really getting people like absorbed
in 3d screens.
Flight of passage is pretty close.
There's a lot of like augmented screens and things that'll make the other already
like practical sets and stuff,
but no glasses on rice.
I don't, I don't believe so.
Yeah.
Which could help step it up.
I'll say, I'll say this.
The,
uh,
you, this is a rare case of like universal cracks,
a type of ride.
And then Disney does it.
That being the ratatouille ride,
it's a little different,
but ratatouille in Paris is a trackless vehicles,
but moving from screen to room.
And some are big screens and some are small screen.
Some simulate big old drops and some are just like transitional screens.
Not as good, not as thrilling.
The ride vehicles aren't as good.
The, the, the transitions aren't as seamless.
It's a, it's a neat ride for sure.
I wouldn't speak ill of it,
but it's nowhere close.
Right.
So universal for sure.
And probably by virtue of that,
they have patents on stuff on like squinching and the,
the ride vehicles themselves,
like they're able to do it the best.
Yeah.
And the ride vehicles are just so much more like different than the ride vehicles.
Yeah. And the ride vehicles are just so much more like dynamic and then,
and the, this and transformers, which I, I'm,
I do really like transformers as well.
They really like jostle you around,
which really also adds to the immersion of it.
Cause you really like feel like beat up and like,
and my mom thinks now she can't do these rides cause she feels too beat up by
them.
I think, and it seems like when they were sketching out,
like what is this ride going to be?
I think maybe they were going to be like,
I think it was like the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the ride.
The, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
the ride.
The, the, the, the, the, the,idan, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
So,
early on it seemed one of the creators was saying like,
we thought it might just be a simple dark ride.
And then we realized we,
after seeing Indiana Jones in Disneyland,
we thought it was the original ride.
And we were like,
we were going to call it the daily Bugle instead or maybe,
or it was just still called Spiderman or something.
But it was going to be more of an Omni mover.
Which the rumor is that that's what the,
the new one is going to.
That what Disney's Spiderman ride is going to be like more of a
kid friendly, slow moving.
But it's like say like less scary.
I think.
This Spiderman ride can get. Yeah. I think cause, cause there was a rumor,
or a patent was filed. I'm sure we've talked about it before.
There was a patent filed for a ride system that Disney made,
which was a giant arm where it was like a roller coaster type thing.
And you would swing in a giant practical city,
which I think everyone got real excited for cause it even mentions in the
patent, like swing like Tarzan or Spiderman. You've seen it, right?
Yeah. Yeah. To both of you, I'm sure.
And it's like, it would swing this way. So you would simulate swinging.
And then when they announced that there would be like a Spiderman ride,
but then the guardians of the galaxy ride is anchoring the new Marvel land
next year. People were like, okay,
this is not going to be a crazy e-ticket Spiderman ride that we're hoping for.
After that, maybe it'll still get built one day, but yeah, that's what the
rumors are. It's like a slower. Sure. Sure. I'm the mover type thing.
So that's almost,
that's almost what universal did to begin with weirdly.
And then Indiana Jones stepped up to the get is the best example of the theme
park wars.
Absolutely. And this kind of, it is a simple idea of like, well, we had it,
they want it to combine.
We have a motion simulator like back to the future and we have like 3d combined
with practical sets like Terminator, the Terminator show.
And basically these ride vehicles are just motion simulators,
but they move along a track.
Yeah. I'm trying to think now I'm probably jumping all around here,
but I'm the first time I was on a ride.
I'm the first time I was on the ride. I couldn't believe it.
Like I couldn't quite believe that they finally got me into the cartoon.
I guess is what it really felt like.
It was, I, I dis opened in March,
March of 1999 and I, my family went in like June or July.
And I was just so excited of like a brand new theme park.
Like this is incredible. And, and there's a whole Marvel area.
Are you kidding me?
And then the ride, like, yeah,
all of the effects and just the tone of voice for a spider-man in the ride.
I was like, this is, this is good. This is a spider-man I like.
Yeah. Cause in the night, I guess we were spoiled in the cartoons.
Cause there was all the spider-man and Marvel cartoons,
some of them better than others.
The best ones being X-Men and Spider-Man, which aren't really that good,
but they're good and nostalgia good.
And then the last good ones are like the Iron Man cartoon,
which I was so bored by as a kid. Do you remember that?
Yeah, I think that and the whole cartoons were kind of made on the cheap.
Yeah. Although I have to say, I mean, of course,
this spider-man ride got kind of upgraded 4k footage in 2012.
And then Hulk got a bit of a track upgrade and a different Q video in 2014.
And we both have had, got headaches after riding the new Hulk.
Yeah. It did a disservice to the Hulk and it just improved the Spider-Man ride.
Yeah. The Spider-Man ride looks great.
I hadn't watched the new, I hadn't watched the 2012 redo.
I think like the only thing that you might have ever said was lacking in this ride
was that the 1999 era CGI was starting to get a little out of date and they fixed it.
It looks so great. You can all, I haven't been on the new version,
so I can only watch the, I could just watch a video where it's 3D and I, you know,
it's blurry and everything, but even through that, it looks incredible.
So it's all the same scenes, but just rendered so much more dimensionally.
And like those, the, the big moments, like who is it who jumps into your face and screams?
They all kind of do that, but scream I think you're looking for.
A character's name, scream, of course. Yeah. That, that, yeah, they look great.
Everything it's all it's cause everything is the same.
It's like, if you went on it, like I went on it now and I almost forgot that it was redone.
Exactly.
I forgot. I was like, oh yeah, I used to look.
And then I went back because my memory was just like, oh, it always looked like this, right?
It reminded me in a way of like the, while I don't really like the film,
I like, I think it's really neat to see like Tron legacy redo this.
It's the same effects and scenes and bikes and discs, but rendered with decades advanced technology,
but they retained how it all works and like the basic functions of it.
And it felt like that, like, so like so cool to just like, you know, five times advanced animation.
And I keep the same ride.
I have to say the aesthetics of that movie and the color palettes and that version of like the future,
I am really kind of shocked and delighted.
I think I really haven't seen that movie in a while, so I can't speak for the movie itself,
but I think the aesthetics of it have aged very nicely.
Yeah, like we talked about that before of like, yeah, you know how you make it look like the future neon blue neon.
Yes, yes.
Always looks like the future.
They just got to get Tron into Disneyland.
Just put it there. However you got to jam it in.
Like what? Why? How could this tomorrow land problem be?
So we really need to like do an episode that is the tomorrow land problem.
Yeah, you know what?
You know what? You know what I was thinking here?
I'll just pitch this to you guys on the episode that you know, we do.
We do our plus ups and sometimes those can be jokes.
If we just didn't even do bits, it's like all what all right.
It is your job to fix tomorrow.
And what do you do? Oh yeah, that would be great.
Yeah, yeah, that won't be funny, but it'll be important now.
I mean, they'll be fun.
I will make up some tomorrow and characters that you might giggle at.
I won't giggle at them.
They'll be totally serious, but they might have a silly name or something.
But yeah, it'll be all it'll be mostly serious stuff. No jokes.
But this whole but you know, you talk about plus and it up and everything.
Like they they did what you would want to happen on this ride.
They updated it and made it 4K and nicer animation.
And did that give them more business? Probably not.
I feel like Disney would have just kept it the same.
I think it's amazing. Universal just unprompted.
Let's bring it into the 2010s and that ride has 20 more years of life because they did it.
They they said to like there is saw an interview with TheoryCoop and one of the other people who were behind it.
TheoryCoop, one of the still one of the main Universal creative people, oversaw a lot of like their popular rides in the last X number of years.
They asked him like, well, Marvel got bought by Disney in 2009.
Are you concerned about these characters going away?
And he's like, we love these characters and we want this ride to stick around and for the foreseeable future it is.
So we want it to be relevant still. And they just did it.
And is there also something in the contract where they have to like kind of add stuff to things to like make it?
I think maybe not. I think I'm wrong about that.
I think they have the freedom.
I mean, they've upgraded the characters costumes to a more modern look.
Yes, there's so many.
I mean, that's probably a great episode, too.
Now that we're just pitching, I'm thinking of other episodes is that I'm so confused by the contracts for Marvel and Universal because there's certain characters they can use in Marvel Superhero Island.
Some they can't.
And then I'm still confused because for a long time there were rumors that they were going to build a new Marvel ride in Islands of Adventure.
But I think they need Disney to sign off on that somehow.
But why would Disney ever sign off on it?
Unless Disney can get their own Marvel rides.
So there's this whole stalemate, I think, still at this point between the two companies over that.
I do. And I have said before, I love it.
I love how interesting and weird it makes everything.
I love that so much of the land is still stuck in 1999 bankruptcy era Marvel.
And that has to be stuck, I think. Right.
I think to a certain point.
That's why I'm on all these questions I need to know.
Because the land is filled with glorious Adam Kubbert art.
Adam Kubbert, a comic book artist, did a lot of runs on X-Men in various series.
Son of legendary artist Joe Kubbert, brother of Andy Kubbert, another whole comic book family.
I have their cards.
They do a whole line.
The three of them did a whole line of X-Men trading cards that I have upstairs.
The family made a trading card line together.
It was via FLIR.
But yeah, it's just the three of them trading off on the cards and all the hundreds of X-Men characters.
The Kubbert School has produced multiple generations of comic book artists.
And I feel like the actual drawn art does look good.
People still recognize that as the characters.
Because all of that stuff was so ubiquitous in the 90s of T-shirts and baseball caps and that sort of thing.
I believe he drew the finale of the onslaught crossover.
I think that's right. They were all over that.
Yeah, they were the superstars of the 90s for sure.
So you get what Marvel and Universal gives you is more of a comic book come to life.
Whereas Disney will clearly do the more photo real, the like aesthetic of the Marvel film.
Disney? Yeah.
Yeah, Disney will welcome you to a college campus style land where you can be recruited.
You can see every strap on his backpack.
Yeah, I assume there'll be a second wave where it's a little kooky or like the Guardians ride and stuff.
But yeah, right now it looks like Marvel's doing a lot of like shield base like sterile shield base places to go.
Which I'm like less and less into that.
But I liked in Captain Marvel, like spoiler alert, I don't know that they introduced the Kree and the scrolls like all right.
Yeah, more weirder stuff, more weirder Marvel Universe stuff. Absolutely.
Well, I'm hoping that once the second wave of the Marvel land goes around the Hollywood area and California Adventure,
we can get like a crazy career scroll base or some weird shit because it would make sense to do something like that.
But we it's like basically like you're going in the pages of a comic book because let's remember back then we were not spoiled like we are now.
It's hard.
Some I know we have listeners that are younger, so perhaps they don't remember a time when there weren't fifteen superhero movies a year.
Yeah.
When there weren't fifty TV shows, there wasn't a whole DC streaming service that focuses solely on DC Comics exclusive TV shows.
The idea that this all changed exists.
There was no comics ology like you can.
I could get any comic book right now on my phone like instantly.
That's crazy.
I used to be a pain in the ass kid.
I mean, I was a good boy.
I was a good kid.
But I would be like any time my parents had to run an errand, it's like, hey, can we swing by the comic shop?
Look, I went to the comic store right before my dentist appointment today, so I'm still doing it.
I get to drive myself now.
Ha.
Yeah, I am in my thirties.
You get gassed.
Probably shouldn't drive.
I shouldn't do that.
I did not get gassed.
So even so, but yeah, that's all crazy.
I'm just saying, though, that I remember a time when a couple kids in high school read comics and I knew those kids and I was friends with them.
And it felt like an impossible dream.
I remember reading an article on my computer that finally they were going to make the Spider-Man movie because James Cameron was going to do it in the mid 90s.
And I remember finally reading that it's going to come out in like a year or six months and they find because it was a bunch of legal problems with it.
So it's like, OK, cool.
I knew there was an X-Men movie coming out in a Spider-Man movie.
But most things other than Batman had not been treated with a ton of respect or money.
And so the idea that anything on this scale, like Marvel Superhero Island or this Spider-Man ride was crazy to me.
Now it makes total sense that we get a giant big, big budget Spider-Man ride.
But back then, the idea that there would be a movie and the suit would look kind of like the character was, oh, yeah, they got it.
OK, good.
Spider-Man looks like him because you'd always be worried because there was that Generation X show on Fox.
And it's like the only way Jubilee kind of looks like yourself.
And they did that bad Nick Fury, David Hasselhoff, which is great in a different way.
But everything was kind of like you.
I thought I almost kind of thought less of the characters because of the way I felt they were treated in the media and by mainstream audiences.
I know that sounds weird.
But you're getting it.
Sounds true.
You know what I'm saying?
I know what you mean.
I mean, I would tape all of those made for TV movies on my TV.
I would not rewatch them a lot, though.
It was also like, how do you mess up super spy?
How do you mess up teenagers, horny teenagers with superpowers?
Like and they they did it.
They messed they messed up.
But yeah, it just felt like other than like Superman and even Superman was having trouble getting off the ground again.
But like other than Batman, most people didn't know about these characters and take them very seriously.
And we were only going to get them in comics, kids cartoons and then occasional TV specials that didn't really feel at all.
Didn't even have a piece of the reason I liked the comic or the characters.
And it's fun, which is funny, too, because like I think it took a little while, but there is a lot of a claim for the Batman and Superman animated shows and the spin off comics.
I mean, Mark Miller, that one of his first jobs was writing the Superman Adventures comic based on the TV show, and he would go on to write Kickass and Kingsman and Ultimates and all of these like bestselling comic books and ultimately, of course, is like sort of sort of inspiration for some of the Avengers stuff.
Yeah, it's like grounded take on the Avengers grounded, but like, oh, yeah, thousands bad.
Like I've read some of that stuff recently, and it's like a little two thousands badass, a little too matrix, a little too conservative, but post nine eleven George Bush kept America go like this.
He doesn't stand for France or something.
Yeah, yeah, they're beating up.
And of course, the Spider-Man comic, the post nine eleven Spider-Man comic where all the villains are standing at nine eleven crying.
Oh, yeah, well, that's here underneath Dr. Dooms mask, and it's like Dr. Doom kills people all the time.
And then, of course, the one where the X-Men refused to save England because the women all have shit on their hands.
Well, sure.
Yeah, not worth saving.
Yeah, there's islands, though.
There was a mass genocene genocide in the comics.
Yes, the very first Grand Wars and X-Men.
He kills off an entire population of anyway.
Yeah, I feel like Apple Marvel DC feels very like Apple, Microsoft, in a way, where like they like one will excel far past the other.
And then suddenly, you know where the other like shoot past it in terms of public acclaim and the best products and the most like now.
And then sometimes they're neck and neck.
Yeah.
And then it's also like they all just have identical products to each other.
There's so many things that are the exact same thing.
Like I was telling I was I was going to say telling, but boring Lindsay with this the other day that Jason correct me if I'm wrong.
The negative zone is this is the dimensional prison from the DC comics.
Yeah.
And the Phantom Zone is the get it the wrong way.
No, it's the wrong way.
Negative Zone is Marvel's other dimension jail.
Another dimension, but it's not a jail.
Other creatures just live there.
I believe the Phantom Zone is where Superman banishes enemies.
Is that a jail or is that where they send bad guys?
The Phantom Zone?
Yeah, that's a jail.
That's a jail.
Okay.
But they both have zones.
They both have people in and they've like bad guys into the Phantom to the negative zone.
I feel like bad guys are in the negative.
I think that's where Annihilus comes from.
But it's another frontier that the Richards family discovered.
Scott, you are right.
Like not just in terms of like in the zeitgeist of like Marvel and DC jockeying back and forth for relevance, but even just on a practical like dollar share of the comic book market or unit share of the comic book market.
They're constantly going back and forth.
So who's the who's the Dell of comics of 90s?
I think 90s belong to Marvel in terms of how ubiquitous and you mean like it would be Dark Horse Comics.
Because Dell.
Yeah, what's a smaller company that was the equivalent to Dell?
No, no, sorry.
In the 90s.
Yeah, you're right.
Dell was small.
I was thinking in the 2000s, Dell was just just fucking everywhere.
You could trip over it.
Smaller.
Smaller. Yeah, you're 90s.
Image.
Image or Dark Horse.
Yeah, which are still like.
Demi Dell was a Dark Horse that suddenly was dominating and now now gone.
I don't know what's up with Dark Horse.
They still go and sell licenses.
Probably more apt.
Yeah, no rides though for Dark Horse.
I don't think so.
I can't think of the Dark Horse properties of the top of my head.
They have the aliens license, maybe still do.
So the alien from alien shows used to show up in the great movie ride.
That's true.
But no Dark.
Well, I don't think they got any money for their Hellboy thing.
They have Hellboy.
There should be a Hellboy ride.
That'd be a cool one.
Yeah, absolutely.
Anyway, so yeah, so a little stuck in its time, but still a fun land with like a great
with well, a good now coaster and great still like hanging in there.
Twenty year old attraction.
Yeah, yeah.
There's another thing technologically.
I learned that not only is there the patent for squinching, but the type of ride vehicle
is patented as well, which is also Transformers.
And it's a company, Ocean Earing International, built these ride vehicles.
And you hear that name and you go, well, that's what's that like a theme?
And then no, no, no.
This is a Ocean Earing company that built sea vessels that would go like do repairs
on oil rigs that plant into the sea.
And like before they got into the theme park game, Ocean Earing International sent vessels
out that recovered pieces of both the Lusitania ship that sank and the Challenger space shuttle.
Wow.
Like they found a weird little ring piece that was like crucial to why the Challenger
exploded.
And that's the kind of thing that Ocean Earing did.
And then they started making theme park vehicles.
So like the technology is so top notch.
And they got into business with Universal originally because of the Jaws attraction,
which if you heard our episode about that major problems with it of all the opening day
attraction, there were so many problems with opening day attractions at Universal,
especially Jaws, terrible.
Sharks did not work much like the film.
Totally unreliable.
Universal thought the company built this royally fucked up.
We got to talk to people who deal with underwater mechanisms.
And they like outsourced weirdly to this Ocean Earing company who were like, well,
actually the theme park business is fun and lucrative and it can be a whole wing.
So yeah, what a strange lineage.
And the same company, they've made other rides with similar vehicles that are in odd
locations.
I forget the one that's in Busch Gardens, Williamsburg, but there's like essentially
a Spider-Man Transformers kind of thing there.
Is that Dark Castle?
And I think it's gone.
I think it was closed for something else a couple of years ago.
Okay.
And there's another one in Tokyo Dome City where I will soon be and I'm very excited,
but I have just learned that this ride has closed.
It is not there.
There was a essential.
There was a Transformers or a Spider-Man Transformers type ride with this exact same
ride vehicle that spun you around into like crazy, but much more cheaply rendered
anime worlds.
This ride was called Tokyo Panic Cruise and I'm so bummed to learn I don't get to go
on Tokyo Panic Cruise.
When is that close?
When did that close?
I think like last year.
I barely missed it.
And they are opening.
Amazingly, they're opening some new stuff.
Right before I go.
So there will be new things at Dome City right before I go.
I'm really excited.
But I can't tell if any of them are replacements for this.
I don't know.
How do you have the space for a Spider-Man ride and then don't replace it with any?
I really can't.
There's very little information about any of this, at least in English.
It's really hard to find stuff about it.
But anyway, dearly departed Tokyo Panic Cruise.
Wow.
We're on the subject of Japan.
So this Spider-Man ride exists in Universal Japan in Osaka too.
Oh yeah.
Has a very cool facade.
Sort of looks like the museum building that the mummy's in in Florida.
But it says that Daily Bugle across the top.
Oh, neat.
Like it's a historic newspaper building.
Is it kind of a cooler?
It's the only thing like the outside is a little, the comic book style in Florida, while fun,
does seem a little cheaper sometimes.
What has the outside of?
It looks like those marble columns kind of like it's in the New York section in that
part, because Spider-Man famously a New York character, a New York, your institution,
like Robert De Niro.
So on the web, a couple of interesting things.
One, they have this great photo op you can do there.
This is a small picture.
I was having trouble finding a good version of it.
It's just a statue of Spider-Man hanging upside down, but you can get your picture with it.
I think that's great.
There is in the gift shop.
You can buy Spider-Man instant ramen where the little Neru.
This is what these are called.
Neru toes, which is the preserved fish like little circles you get in ramen that have
the little pink swirl.
Oh, look like little Spider-Man heads.
That's cool.
And then my favorite thing on the English version of their website.
And this is actually like really a very good Japanese to English translation.
And I think sells the ride really well.
It says so overwhelming.
It bends reality, an unbelievable immersive experience, encounter a new dimension of
excitement in the world's greatest ride.
I like that really sounds like Huckster Stanley in the mid sixties.
Hawken is where it's like that is just the perfect encapsulation of the ride.
They also use and they don't really use this in Florida, but on the Japan website, there
is a lot of references to this ride being four K three D.
So those are good stats, good stats, good numbers.
Also, that reminded me that the one cool, the one thing that sounded neat about the
more Omni mover type version that they didn't end up building is that they at the end, they
would have taken your picture and you would have gotten to get do a print out of yourself
on the cover of the Daily Bugle.
That's fun.
And that's something they should do on the current ride that exists.
I think the pictures do.
It kind of looks like a photo frame, but like if it was a print out on actual newsprint
that you could frame, that would be, yeah, that would be amazing.
Maybe they can do that California adventure.
Yes, that'd be an idea.
Oh, sure.
It's moving slower.
You can get those pictures more easily.
Yeah.
Guys, save city.
It's going to probably be like a name tag or some ID card.
Yeah.
Well, there hasn't been any employee.
You're worried about this being functional.
It's going to be a functional campus.
I think, yeah, I do think that's the idea.
That's my feeling.
I mean, from the pictures, we don't have the Daily Bugle yet.
The Marvel cinematic unit, or that's true.
So I, you know, I was glad that the new Spider-Man, the Tom Holland Spider-Man, we did not have
to watch Uncle Ben die again, but I would like to see J.
Joda Jameson back.
Sure.
Bring back J.K.
Simmons for all I care.
That's what people have.
Yeah.
People want that.
But yeah, I know.
More well, the bigger star now than then they have.
They don't.
I think they don't like to feel like they didn't.
There is not their version.
I mean, I don't think anyone would be mad at all.
And I'm an advocate for like, just bring Toby Maguire back as his like older Spider-Man
like they were going to do in Spider-Verse.
Like there's a rumor they're going to do have the three Spider-Man actors do voices as well.
I like anything like that.
I mean, wherever we're getting the old actors back, we're putting people together.
It's the one thing about you kind of like that trailer for Shaft.
I was less sold, but I do think it's neat to see while one of them is new, one of them
is not.
There's two old Shafts and a new Shaft.
It's an easy trick and I love it.
And it's a big thing in comics.
Shared universe, legacy characters.
That's what we I know we've talked about before, like DC, like had all these legacy characters
in the 90s like Wally West is a flash now.
Kyle Reiner's Green Lantern.
Yeah.
And then the 2000s, they crapped all over that.
It's like they're still back to the original.
Yeah, went back to the original Marvel has done that to a lesser extent.
Yeah, honestly, the first non Marvel cinematic universe character that will enter that was
cast before is Deadpool.
Hmm.
Dead.
Oh, yeah.
Remain Ryan Reynolds, this version of him, and he will probably end up in some of these
movies.
Wow.
So the Deadpool will be in Disney movies.
That's what Bob Iger has said.
So I think he makes too much money for them to not.
Yeah, it only it only makes sense for sure.
Does did does did pull end up in the parks?
That seems like they can't or they would have to neuter it.
I mean, I think they neuter it probably.
Yeah, it's a ton of money.
Yeah, the problem is there's no they still have to work out the Florida parks and then
they just have to have room for like there's a Deadpool ride would people lose our minds.
Sure.
PG plus PG 13.
How about you know, all of these rides, the one we're talking about has on board audio,
right?
Like you could presumably customize.
Could you like press a button and show your ID to press the button to where you are accepting
the R rated experience of like it's a different imagine.
Yeah, I don't think that's a bad idea.
It would be it's it would be very hard because I think even universal would be too skittish
with stuff like that because, you know, you inevitably a mom and a five year old go on
the ride and mom doesn't know what to hit.
She's like, well, I'm older than 18 and she hits that and then yeah, dead.
Well, the monsters after dark this year, there's cursing on this ride pools here.
The funny is 95 percent of Deadpool comics are like PG PG 13.
There's there's a handful of R rated Deadpool comics, but in the movies it's like, oh yeah,
it's disgusting.
It's filthy.
What if it's like headphones that you put on only and then it's like such you have to
sign like three consent forms to be sworn at.
It's like there's so many checks and balances and then you get to hear the word shit said
officially in a Disney park.
Please shit taco.
I mean, you got to gussy it up.
You got to go to that thing that happens.
I know I've not seen either of the movies all the way through.
I have seen both of them and I can confirm that while shit taco I don't think appears
directly, it is certainly in the same vein as the other jokes in Deadpool.
I see.
That's what you're seeing.
So it's the way that people like Donald Trump is a douche nozzle.
It's that kind of garbage.
No.
Yeah, I think I if I'd be less concerned about the profanities and more, if I could press
a button, I'd press a button to where he doesn't get meta.
If I could stop him from brain, I would only do a Deadpool ride experience where fourth
walls remain intact.
It's kind of trying to put a leash on a wild dog like Deadpool.
That ain't happening.
I guess this ride's not free.
No, no, no.
It's not a moral thing.
It's a it's a comedy snobbery thing.
Okay.
I think I, I think there'll be a lot more Deadpool to come in all media and a ride,
probably third park.
What if California, you know, this is like actually if they let them do whatever they
wanted, like some Deadpool somehow like taking over great moments with Mr. Lincoln and then
like making a profane speech.
I mean, that would be so much fun.
It might have like fly in the 90s, but I feel like now so much of the crap we consume is
like, well, what side are you on?
The good side?
The on the bands of what movie are you seeing opening week?
You know, that sort of crap.
It's like how Disney can now never remove the hall of presidents because there are
good.
Yes.
Is politicized.
It's our sacred good presidents.
But can they have Deadpool run up and fart in every president's face?
The Democrat or Republican or wig?
Maybe.
Hmm.
How would he?
Just because we're blue sky here, how would the animatronic move from president to president?
Ooh, I'm not sure.
Maybe we don't have the technology for that.
Or is it like a sophisticated hologram or is like a screen in front of the presidents
that can dart around?
It's a live actor.
There is an actor whose job it is in every single show of the hall of presidents to fart
on them, how hard in their faces.
How about it's this?
It's those robot stunt performers that they were testing at Disney and they sail one over
the presidents, but he farts while he's flying.
He unleashes kind of like a like a toxic fart spray.
So he shoots out like a Batman six, a sixties Batman style colorful gas that spells the
word fart or like rap for one of those Batman sound effect.
He'll fly over the presidents crop dusting all of them essentially.
And it'll be a Roy.
So they'll just have to take the robot.
They already have the technology and they'll just have to shoot, put a gas canister in
its asshole.
Yes.
You know, technician every time we'll have to just like take like a spray paint can shake
it up.
Yeah.
Just jam it up its butt and then like, okay, slap on the butt.
You're ready to go.
And then, yeah.
So yeah, I think, I think Deadpool takeover.
Maybe that's one of those late night events too, where Deadpool takes over a lot of the
rides.
The rare ride that is only open past midnight.
So they have to extend the hours.
But if you go to Disney, let's say Magic Kingdom past midnight, Deadpool is interrupting every
single ride.
Yeah, I went to, I went to Disney after dark.
I went to the Star Wars one.
I went to the nineties one.
I went to the one where Deadpool farts everywhere and the only food they sell is chimichangas.
That's what he likes.
Right.
Oh yeah.
Like that.
You know what it's like food.
It just sounds funny.
It just sounds.
It's a funny sound.
Spider-Man's fun.
I think the jokes in this are like pretty good.
There's some fourth wall jokes in Spider-Man.
Should we go through, I guess the one thing we're missing is like actually stepping through
the plot of the ride.
Sure.
The primary thing of which, I mean, I don't remember why you're there, but the overargue,
the one line synopsis is that the Statue of Liberty is being stolen.
Well, sure.
Well, to answer your question, you are there to tour the Daily Bugle and see their new
news gathering vehicle, the scoop, which is why it has satellites on the.
That's why it's got satellites on it.
And it is Daily Bugle, the newspaper, even though you're watching like New York one or
something that's supposed to be New York one or something like that.
And it's like, actually, we're watching the news van that picks up like public access,
like local news stories.
Now, the news van is also a news story that he it's like a big deal that J Jonah Jameson
famously stingy invested in this news van.
And it's important.
I mean, there's a gag where like he makes Peter Parker, one of his photographers, talk
about the scoop and he touches it.
And then they usher him away and Windex it.
And then there's a bunch of scoop scientists who they demonstrate how to improperly get
in the ride vehicle and that how to properly get in the ride vehicle.
That's really funny in the opening and the pre show animation where all of these stiff
lab coated scientists then end up in traction and with casts like in the cover in their
bodies and they're they're flying out of the vehicle and everything.
That's a lot of fun.
And also, and then the Jameson very dry simply refers to Spider-Man as there is to Peter
Parker is that shutter bug.
Yes.
He's always calling him a shutter bug.
Spider-Man is a menace or a vigilante, but he trusts us.
We can go in there.
Yes, we can go in patrons of the paper.
The other thing is, I believe they imply that like, well, all of his reporters are scattered
about the city trying to get a handle on this, but they know where it is now.
There's been a sighting and so like we need somewhere out.
We need people on the street.
Okay, so you're getting in the news vehicle to help them gather the news.
Okay.
And they did not anticipate that you would end up in the crosshairs of the action.
No, specifically in the way in the hideout.
Like your very first thing is kind of going through the city and you find the secret hideout
of the sinister syndicate.
Yeah.
So this is a whole thing.
It's not sinister six, which is a familiar title to sinister.
Yeah, which we've talked about in the patron episode, but for some one specific reason.
And usually within, okay, within the Marvel universe, there is both a sinister six and
a sinister syndicate.
The sinister six, usually a list villains, sinister syndicate, kind of like the B team
of Spider-Man villains, but they have, again, rotating memberships.
Oh, cause no green goblin.
Yeah.
So like this, there's no venom, there's no carnage, there's no green goblin.
There are heavy hitters.
Heavy hitters, doc, Ock, Electro.
Do you think Electro was in an A list?
I was trying to think who do you think is more A list Electro or shocker?
Oh, electricity.
You know what?
Electro for sure.
I think it's a list.
I love shocker, but shocker is for sure B list.
Okay.
Electro.
Yeah.
Which one plugs the big plug into you and shakes your head.
It's Electro.
That's a crazy moment in the, it's like a little unpleasant in a way, but very scary
and a neat moment in the ride.
Hobgoblin in this ride instead of green goblin.
Yes.
Hobgoblin is like has his own interesting backstory that is very complicated, like any
comic book character, but like green goblin is walking around the land.
So yeah, right, right.
But they, yeah, he's not on it's because I think they kind of picked which characters
to use and which set pieces they were going to do because they would, if they had this,
if it was the sinister six, they would have had to have a six villain because there's
only five.
Okay.
And they wanted to pack this thing, which that's the thing I, that is very neat about
this ride, that it's all of these villains all at once.
It's like Batman 66.
They didn't just choose one or two.
Yes.
All of them.
They're all running rampant.
Yeah.
And around every, like every screen is devoted to a different one of these villains.
It's, it's a very exciting.
Yeah.
So it's electro doc, Havgoblin scream and Hydra man, Hydra man.
Right.
Yeah.
Hydra man kind of an obvious, yeah.
Water effects are easy to do.
Um, sprayed in the w what's his, yeah, you get sprayed.
He sprayed.
Uh, he, well, that's a funny moment you guys, you, so you go through the hideout, you see
the levitating pieces of statue of Liberty and then you kind of like encounter the villains
one at a time until eventually doc, Oc levitates you.
The first time you see Hydra man, you're in the sewers and spider man's like, all right,
why don't you all just calm down, get back to the bugle and Hydra man rises up behind
him and spider man tries to punch him a few times.
Even though he's like a clear liquid thing.
Yes.
It was much bigger.
Yeah.
Uh, so, and he throws a pipe at you at the end of the ride, uh, spider man tricks electro
into shocking Hydra man.
So it just makes a giant explosion.
Smart.
That's very fun.
I'm glad you're here to explain all this because I had never understood.
I liked this ride a lot.
I couldn't tell you the plot at all.
I didn't know what happened in that pre show.
I'm like, well, it doesn't matter.
That stuff happens.
Fireballs is great.
Uh, do you think scoop and evac know each other?
Oh, do you think they were an item?
Oh, I didn't even, I didn't want to go that far, but yes, I do.
Now that you say it.
Uh, well with six degrees of freedom on each, uh, who knows what, uh, what flurries their
bodies could form into.
Sure.
Uh, transformers introduces the other, uh, transformers uses an elevator system.
So you're kind of on two different levels in that spider man doesn't really do that.
So we've acts on top.
Well, all right.
Save it for bansers.
The answer is when the ride vehicles fucking.
Uh, 13 screens, right?
13 massive screens.
Yeah.
Kind of guy.
Another technological thing of like, this is 1999 before like big blockbuster movies
were on IMAX every weekend.
True.
And before there were like these like semi IMAX screens everywhere, like you had to go
to a theme park to see these giant screens and a sort of boring thing, but a little interesting
is how like the, the audio is big, uh, complicated thing with this ride.
And there's a lot that's on board, but certain things just for realism had to sound like
it's coming from the front or from the sides.
And most times on a ride or in a movie theater, the speakers are behind the screen, but they
had to use a different, they had these special kind of screen and the view wouldn't be able
to hear the audio through it.
So it was very tricky finding where to put all the speakers, uh, much like expedition
Everest.
Like it's, I think it's an underappreciated thing, like all the, the hidden speakers that
are in every one of these rides.
Yeah.
I read somewhere that they, they, some of the speakers that they are by the screens,
they're like in front of the screens and then they bounce the audio off like a vinyl piece
of vinyl or something.
That's crazy.
Wow.
And then there's that other odd thing about this where much of the set design in this
ride is on canvas.
It was printed onto canvas because with all of the technology going into the vehicle and
the films themselves, uh, there was not a lot left over.
Like it would, it would have taken forever and very, very expensive and complicated to
like hand paint a lot of sets.
Yeah.
And plus it would look more comic booky and like you could literally take the assets from
the film and print them out onto canvas.
And that's what helps the seamlessness.
You're like something that was rendered in CGI is just printed and next to you on beautiful
film, like super, super quality canvas.
Uh, I don't know.
It's, it's, it's, it's very well done.
It's very effective.
Helps you feel like you're in an animated world.
Yeah.
And I mean like all the effects kind of were refreshed in 2012 to like the, I mean the
how goblin explosion, him throwing a pumpkin bomb to an actual explosion above you is still
like, it's still impressive.
Unbelievable.
And I didn't know that was coming the first time I went on it.
So shocking.
It's such a big explosion.
It is so close to you.
And if you watch the video, I kept looking up ride videos and watching that path from
the movie, you're by this point, like leaving a room and watching a fireball that's digital
perfectly.
Like it's a, such a specific arc.
Yeah.
It throws it from the screen to become a real explosion going in the same direction in the
room with you.
I think this is like one of the best things that happens in any theme park ride anywhere.
Yeah.
And they re reuse it for transformers.
They use that same thing with you get shot at.
Oh, right.
And in the ride.
Yeah.
I think it's the same thing where it's like, you're, it really messes with your brain.
The whole thing, by the way, just in general, the transitions are crazy.
Like it is just watching a video of it or my memory of going on it.
Like there are points.
I mean, obviously you can tell where they happen, but it's insane how well the perspectives
line up and that there are points where you bug out and you're like, Oh my God, this is
a screen in front of me now.
Like you, sir, you're a little late to it.
Yeah.
I think it's, it's so uncanny how well they did this.
I'm Kenny.
Excellent.
Yeah.
It was so the first time we went on this, his 99, I think, and it's the summer, it
opens.
And I don't know the actual amount of time we waited, but I believe we waited at least
three hours for this ride.
Maybe it was only two.
Maybe my memory is bad.
Um, it was raining all day.
I was not wearing socks.
My feet soaked to the point of like bloating in my shoes.
I've never seen this happen to my feet before or since.
And we went on, I didn't realize how bad it was until after, but we went on the ride and
we were all very wet and cranky before we went onto the ride and we left the ride and
we were like, well, that was worth the whole, that was like, cause of all the things you're
saying about it, uh, that it felt so worth three hours.
It's crazy or what?
Who knows two hours, but, but it felt some insane amount of time, but we like, we have
to do this.
It's the last thing of the day.
And then I took my shoes off and it looked like my, it looked like just a big chunk of
skin would fall off my foot.
Oh, like it looked like, like it was so puffy.
I was like, am I going to lose this?
The bottom half of skin?
I did not.
That's funny.
Cause my family, we waited like four hours for Gringotts.
Like we were there opening summer.
It was still three or four hour waits and it did poured rain that day.
And we, I don't think any of us had your disgusting puffy feet, but we were definitely
waiting in like wet clothes and wet shoes for a while.
Um, again, I, who knows how the star, by the time this comes out, maybe we'll know
how we're going to get reservations for star wars, but I am prepared to soak my feet to
wait for star wars.
If I have to, I will, but I, but it's going to open in the summer.
So I don't know where you're soaking your feet unless you have to stand in a line where
a sewer is broken or something, which I will, if there's an open sewer, I will stand in
it.
If you have to drink some of that water, okay.
If you have to get a handshake from a British chick.
I am willing to do almost anything to get into star wars land, even without rise of
the resistance open on opening day.
Uh, so yeah.
It's going to be a song again.
My family too, we were all in agreement.
Like it wasn't my mom.
I didn't lose dad either.
Like everybody's on board.
I don't remember.
He doesn't always say like, Oh, what a great ride or anything like that.
But I think he thought it was fine.
I'll ask him after this.
But I do remember my mom being very excited about it.
And then I would take her on the transformer ride years later and she'd be like, that was
too rough.
I'd say, well, spider-man is exact same ride.
And she'd be like, I don't remember it being like, well, it's transformers.
I think has worse footage.
It's darker.
It's, it's a chaos.
Those movies are chaos.
It's so hard to tell what's going on.
I think that's spider-man is so clear what the action is.
Yeah.
It's like big, bold colors.
I find the transformers to be like a much.
Even darkened it a little like it was a little more florescent.
I kind of miss how florescent the colors were in the original version compared to the more
like darker movie aesthetic and say spider-man's costume or doc doc doc's got the duster on
like it's my red too.
But yeah, I think it's, it might be partly a trick.
Maybe, but I think she would just, she felt like she doesn't like doing star tours anymore.
So I don't think she was.
That's fair.
I do think it's clear what the action is and star and spider-man then transformers.
Although those transformers, I was just on this ride a couple of months ago.
They are letting that thing get dark.
That screen is dark.
I remember a few years ago because I was way, I was way into it.
I would pop up the universal just to do it and leave a couple of times that summer.
Cause I had annual pass and that screen was much brighter than it is now.
I think there's this whole, I've maybe mentioned on the show a little bit, but I,
I think this is even something, another episode pitch something we can chart here and there.
I, I, I've, I've been thinking about like MVP rides.
What is the best ride in the world when it opens?
I think this might've been one at some point.
I think transformers might've been high on the list, but maybe less so now because there are better,
like better rides of open sense, but also just it itself, the quality is as diminished.
More endearing characters on more recent rides too.
Like the transformer.
Yeah. I mean, I will, I do like the end when Optimus prime talks to you, but I don't have the warmth for him that I do for Spiderman.
I don't have the warmth.
I think Evac is endearing cause he's another character trying his best.
I want to say on record, I do respect Optimus prime.
He does not have an easy job.
Thank God.
There was no confusion about that.
I just want that written down.
Well, you've also have respect cause he's respectful to you.
He really leans in.
He gives you what I like on rides is he gives you a good two to three seconds of a moment to sit with them, which is what I like in star tours.
When the new one three PO gives us a couple like a second to sink in that we're part of the rebel Alliance.
Now I also like that character actor who's the general in the transformers queue.
I forget his name.
He shows up and a lot of plays Landry's dad on Friday night.
I knew you were going to say I knew he was a friend.
There was some sort of connection.
He's in a bunch of stuff too, though.
I can't think of his name.
So yeah.
So Optimus prime tells you so Spiderman doesn't ever quite have a serious moment with you where you feel important.
Do you does that make your favorite themed entertainment character smokey the bear?
Is he always pointing at you?
I certainly like him.
McGruff also points at me and I like him to mean these has commands for you.
I like that.
He's right.
I don't want to correct me now.
Like smokey is I listen up Spiderman at the beginning of the ride jumps on your ride vehicle.
You feel the bounce and it's great.
When he says like this is the most dangerous night of my life and maybe you and yours, but he's still being like funny.
He's like it.
He's a little serious.
I'm going to be more sincere.
You just love this Optimus.
You feel like seen and loved and like you're seated at the right hand of God.
I guess I think that's right.
I think you're right about that argument where Spiderman's warning you.
But you secretly he's like, well, a little help would be good.
I mean, that's funny.
Yeah, that's the character.
He's hanging down upside down.
He takes your picture and everything.
Mike doesn't like that.
He wants he doesn't want him to be funny.
I'm not saying I want Spiderman to change his character because that wouldn't be right for him to do.
But I'm just saying it is nice when a serious person that I respect like Jason who's in charge tells me that I did a good job and he lets me sit with it while he stares at me for a couple seconds.
But there's like I feel like this is the one example of this.
Can you name more C3PO?
He's a serious person.
He doesn't tell me.
But he doesn't expect you respect C3.
I respect him.
But it's not quite the same situation.
But and Star Tours, once we get the transmission from whether it's BB-8 or Maz Kanata or Princess Leia, he turns and he has a couple different things he says.
But one of them is he says something to the effect of looks like we've all just joined the Rebel Alliance and we kind of sit there for a moment in the middle of the ride.
And it is a serious moment.
It's not played for his usual laughs or his head got torn off or something.
It's not.
I like that.
I like it in the middle of the ride or at the end of the ride when you have to sit with a serious beat for and they get I would like it for like 30 seconds, but they give you what feels like a substantial time in like the time frame of the ride.
So C3PO said I love you.
And then and then you just looked into each other's eyes for 30 seconds.
If he says it to me, will that be like a second Rebel spy where he'll choose a different way to cut?
Well, I mean, I think the cleanest thing is you're the spy.
I'm the spy every time.
Well, you're gonna have to make an arrangement with Disney where you're always a rebel spy.
But the rebel spy also C3PO finds you, points you out and says, I love you.
You did a good job.
I think that would be fantastic because I do think this is everybody else.
But yeah, but that's the I love you the most.
I love you the most.
Yeah, I think that'd be good.
You can find a way where he says it more generally and you feel like it's to you.
How about Optimus Prime?
They combine the ET technology and then have all this.
We had this I love you thing to it.
So he's like, you did well out there recruits.
Jason, I love you.
And then he goes person by person in the car and it's newer technology.
So he's very clear.
And then he says I love you to everyone in the car.
Everyone would feel great.
But yeah, but that that was a big backup behind the car while it pauses at that point.
OK, well, there's going to have to expand the ride then and all the cars, there'll be like six different things.
They'll split off.
So the car will split off into different sections with Optimus Prime.
And it'll be easier for loading is what I'm saying.
What if it's after the ride and you just you get to like enter a room like a like a like a confession with a priest or like you're like, you know, seeing a dying person for the last time.
And they give you a moment.
Maybe you'd like a moment alone.
And well, that's good.
I thought you were going to go with like in a confession and then the little thing opens on the side and it's Optimus Prime's eyes.
You're not sure who it is back there.
There's anonymity, but I'm feeling it's Optimus Prime.
How long has it been since you rescued the All Spark?
Say four hail bumblebees.
I think that's good too.
I like all of this.
Sing four of his fun boogie songs.
He's always play his boogie Psalms.
So you want you need more.
Do you consider the Indiana Jones end beat to be in this genre?
No, I ride a heart to hearts is what you know.
That's too.
He's been funny and he's been flipping.
You're not.
You don't want.
All right.
This is the thing I'm just saying.
The thing I specifically like is not funny.
I'm going to do.
Yeah, but I'm going to say serious Spider-Man sometimes sucks at dealing with his clone.
I went back and I said before, I don't necessarily think he should say something serious.
You're looking for your you don't want to throw other things out.
You're fine with the Spider-Man moment, but you want other moments and rides where a serious character.
Yeah, something nice like they tried a few years ago to do Dark Knight Returns in the Spider-Man comics.
And I think it's called the last will and testament.
And the crux of it is a very old Peter Parker has to come out of retirement like in the Frank Miller comic.
But he goes to Mary Jane's grave and reveals that due to the radioactive nature of spider bite and his powers, all of his fluids, all of his bodily fluids were toxic.
So if I have a wife that you have relations with, he gave Mary Jane not powers, but like cancer.
He killed Mary Jane by loving her.
Jesus, this is a mini.
This is a Spider-Man mini series.
I and it is it's insane.
It's one of the things.
So I want an overlay for the Spider-Man ride in Florida where he explains to you that he gave his wife my blood.
We're all sick.
Hey fellow wall crawlers.
Guess what?
I gave my wife cancer with in our marital bed.
Don't share a drink after me.
I don't even know.
All our organs and I'm not talking about HPV, but get that new vaccine.
True believers.
I don't know what that run.
That's that's a weird.
That was I.
Yeah, I don't look that up.
I don't get out.
Yeah, I.
Oh boy.
What have we missed?
Probably toxic semen.
Semen got him giving Mary Jane cancer.
The love making sexually exchanged cancer juice.
We've got character heart to hearts.
I don't know.
The free falls.
Cool.
Okay.
Yeah.
So maybe one of the best endings for a ride ever.
Doc.
Oc levitates you specifically.
They're fighting.
You're fighting about the city.
Doc.
Oc levitates you.
I have his dialogue right here.
I always thought this was very clever for theme park script writing.
Spider-Man says Doc, your aims worse than your haircut.
Spider-Man knocks him out of the way and he goes, it's good enough for your sitting duck friends.
And he zaps you with the, the levitation ray.
You start to rise up above the city.
Spider-Man tries to web you down and pulls you throughout the city because Hobgoblin's like pulling him along in the glider and then Doc.
Oc reverses it.
So you start to free fall.
You're only free falling about like like I saw 10 inches.
It's crazy.
Is that all it is?
That's all it is.
But the walls are moving.
The footage is moving and it truly feels like you're falling out of the sky.
That effect.
Yeah.
Especially.
I mean, now it's, I can, I'm not as panicky on rides.
But at the time, yeah, it was like felt like you were falling.
Like I was so impressed.
It's a massive and I'm a little scared drops.
So like, oh God, oh God.
All right.
Well, it's cool looking and you were not.
And one of the main designers of the ride is like, I know exactly how I know how it works better than anybody.
And it still bugs me out every single time.
Yeah.
And again, another thing where they just stole this for the Spider-Man ride, the exact same ending.
Transformers.
Oh yeah.
Sorry.
She's losing my mind.
Okay.
The heart to hearts.
To go back to that.
Sure.
Would you accept the villain heart to heart where a bad person says, I was defeated at your hands.
You have bested me and I salute you for it.
I think that I'm about to die because of you.
Well, I mean, that would be, I mean, that's a little bit of a bummer.
I would think like Doc Ock kind of telling me a quick sob story about his life and why he got here and then how he's going to give it all up and turn to a life of heroism, heroism and not crime.
I think that'd be nice.
You want to give him redemption.
I will change my ways because of you, Mike.
I think that would be fantastic.
You get a lot more like, no, like when Poseidon defeats the evil Lord Darkanon in the other islet, the adventure ride Poseidon's fury Poseidon's fury or journey to Atlanta, whatever that one day, one day we'll get to talk about all the different versions that it's just so like we do it every time my family goes to universal.
And I think we always do it once.
That's not a rewrite, but I just as a kid, like as I've grown up, like how many times has this story changed?
Like, so, so for you, Poseidon looking you in the eye and saying there were a lot of people, well, there's like 300 people in this show, something like that come in every 20 minutes.
But you Jason helped me defeat Darkanon Lord, the evil Lord Darkanon.
Oh, beloved character.
We all know it love from this.
Uh, well from week.
This is the public domain island and we got to get this park open.
What if, okay.
So say we're in the Ogas Cantina and you're having a drink, Scott, and all of a sudden Rex goes and he points at you and he goes, I'm here because friends like you and friends like you have kept me alive in their memories.
Scott.
As long as, as long as I could toast a glass of, I don't remember the name of the, I don't remember the name of the white wine.
Yeah.
Whatever that Padme white is.
I mean, you know, he could, she could do or Rex could have a Imperial red cab sav.
I forget if I'm getting that right or not.
But he's having the white blend from the planet that no longer exists anymore.
Yeah.
It's great.
So old that they aren't even grown.
Rex says like, this was a bringer show.
And by you being here, you helped me reach the 10 people that I had to get tonight to get a drink ticket.
I'm getting 20 space bucks.
Cause of you.
Yeah, that would be great.
Yeah.
Like that.
Yes.
I know.
Now I understand.
That's the, that's the idea.
If he put all three of his claws on me, on my shoulders.
He's got his little air horn at you.
What's that?
Then he shot his little air horn.
Oh yeah.
Hey, hey Scott, this one's for you.
But I can't wait for the, Oh boy.
Rex has got an air.
Was there any way to make me like Rex more?
Give them an air.
So end of the Spider-Man ride to after Spider-Man pops down, takes your picture.
You get to see a little, a fun little joke.
The beam is aimed in the bugle office.
Now specifically J Jota Jameson's office.
And he's like stuck flying on the ceiling and stuff.
And that's very fun.
And they play the rock and roll rock and roll kind of version of the Spider-Man theme song,
which I am always a sucker for rock and roll covers of that song.
Well, I also kudos to the Marvel cinematic universe for using the Spider-Man theme and like an orchestra.
It's not the rock and roll version, which is better.
But they use like an orchestrated version of the Spider-Man song.
Yeah.
Which they'd Rami versions and the other versions did not.
The Rami version stressed me out because it was so much about Peter Parker's problems and there wasn't as much funny Spider-Man.
And then I never saw the Andrew Garfield one, so I can't speak to those.
But hey, a lot more Nickelback.
A lot more Nickelback.
Yeah.
That's the only, that's the way you get me on this room.
Lead singer of C.
C.
Yeah, we, I think, no, I still think that's not it.
I think we, we did this before on the show.
Have we done that already?
Is it Nickelback or is it just Chad Kroger?
It's just saliva.
It's saliva.
Is it just Chad Kroger?
It's just Chad Kroger.
Nickelback was only going to hold him back from the heights of greatness that he achieved with Hero.
But that was like towards the end of like album sales and singles.
Like he probably made a fortune on that, right?
I would imagine.
I would think.
I mean, creatively though, like, you know, that fucking dumb ass Nickelback bass player was going to ruin his vision if he didn't fly solo.
I see. Yeah.
He, he like Spider-Man had to take matters into his own hands to save the world with music.
Hero can save us, vindicate it.
Was there a third song?
I don't remember the song from the third movie.
I don't think there was a big hit.
Did they just call it?
I don't know if there was a big hit.
Spider-Man Shuffle.
I think Will Smith did one.
Oh, only.
That's what he's dancing to.
A little tale that I'd like to spin.
Does he have a song in Aladdin?
I mean, he has a friend like me, but he should have his own rap song in Aladdin.
Should be a new genie rap that Will Smith does.
Probably not.
The answer is no.
They can't go off script.
Well, yeah, they should throw a whole new world in the garbage and he should.
Fine.
That trailer came out today.
He's both blue and not blue in it.
Apparently I haven't watched it yet.
Well, they added the, the rumor is they added the blue late because people went, why the hell isn't he blue?
He was never going to be blue.
So like there's a couple of scenes where they added him being blue.
But as I pointed out on Twitter, the main thing that they brought to this film is that Aladdin says, really?
The G makes Aladdin like levitate towards Jasmine to go talk to her.
Really?
This is what Aladdin, you know, that cartoon's okay, I guess, but I want, but it's what it's missing is 13 years after the fact, Jim Halpert moments.
I mean, if, if Iago could say that's not even a thing, I would like that.
It's not even a thing.
Is Iago in the movie?
You think he's gone?
I didn't see him in the trailer.
Is Abu?
Abu's in it for sure.
But Abu cut from the stage version California Adventure.
Famously, yes.
Famously cut.
The carpet or real ham though in the stage version.
In the movie version too.
You know what?
That's when the movie, when is this movie coming out?
Is it in a week or something?
Or is it in?
I don't know when this episode comes out.
Sorry to say.
Dumbo's coming out too.
Dumbo's coming out soon, but is Aladdin coming out soon?
Cause we should do California Adventure ride.
Or maybe.
Yeah.
We have.
So we're getting a lot of our internal business done on today's show.
Yeah.
Including showing you an old video I found of you.
A lot of inside baseball stuff here.
It's insular.
Now we have to deliver on this promise of a dry tomorrow, sincere tomorrow land.
Yes.
Crying tomorrow land.
I think we can knock it out of the park.
I think that's fine.
Yeah.
It's all going to be great.
There's a Stanley cameo.
There's multiple.
There's a bunch.
Yeah.
I think they gained more when they redid it.
The one at the, I'm talking about the one at the end.
What is the one?
Well, there's the one he's driving the garbage truck.
That's a new, that's in the new one.
I'm confused by which cameo.
And he's soliciting a hooker on the streets of New York.
He's buying crack from someone.
If anyone asks, my name is Steve Ditko.
Steve Ditko.
Excelsior.
Uh, Spider-Man.
I don't remember why.
Yeah.
So there's the truck one that's earlier, but they've added a little voiceover with him
in the new ending.
And I'm trying to remember what it was.
And I think there's a picture of him in the bullpen on his desk in tribute after he passed
away.
Um, and he's like, I'm going to go to the park and I'm going to go to the park and I'm
going to go to the park and I'm going to go to the park and I'm going to go to the park
and I'm going to go to the park and I'm going to go to the park and I'm going to go to the
park and I'm going to go to the park.
Yeah.
So I don't know if he's a, a, a, um, yeah, I don't know that there's any Ditko tribute
Scott.
This is,
there is a, there is, there is a creator in the, I forget this part in the office.
They have mentions of, there's a lot.
I mean, they're filing cabinets where all of the names on the filing cabinets are like
Mark Gargan.
Or who's like the Scorpion, Mac Gargan.
Gargan.
Yeah.
Um, and then like all the filing cabinets of like, you know, silver sable through x-men.
And then there's the trophy case, uh, has like all the universal creative names on it.
Yeah.
The hidden Mickey is obviously very common, but the hidden Mac Gargan can only be found
on the Spider-Man ride.
Uh, Mac Gargan in the newer movies too, right?
Yeah, I think so.
I think he was one of the henchmen.
He's a, he's played by the game.
He plays Nacho on better call Saul.
Oh, yeah.
I believe he's good.
Uh, he's good.
Uh, Steve Ditko.
I, that's a big hole.
I, I'm fascinated to see if they reissue a lot of that stuff.
Steve Ditko, like never like let this thing did some work for Marvel and DC in the seventies
and eighties, but kept making self published comics until he died last year, two years
ago.
He died the same year that Stan died.
Yeah.
Which is crazy because they were both so old at that point.
He was just making black and white weird comics.
Like he was a weird guy kind of into object, uh, objectivism.
Is that the term?
Like, uh, I don't know.
No, no, no.
Like really weird.
We're still obsessed with like hands and eyes, like in the early Spider-Man comics.
And it was kind of mad.
Kind of mad.
I think he was very mad about if you hand wrote him a letter, it was likely he would
write you back.
Right.
So like you could tell him like, Hey, you inspired me.
You're Spider-Man.
And he would write you something nice, but I think he was very famously mad at Marvel
and yeah, kind of a crank mad at Stan like everybody was.
And he built his own janky ride just in a field somewhere.
You'd have to call him and he'd show up and you could, he'd take you on it.
He'd unlock the barn where he built it.
Yeah.
Just like push a wheelbarrow around.
Sure.
All the characters are about weird or all the characters in that ride are weird little
freaks.
Just like all the first 40 Spider-Man comics where everyone is hideously ugly or like an
outcast from society.
You just stop and stare at a hand for a good 30 seconds.
30 seconds or so.
It's closer to your dream of a ride.
Yeah.
Still moments.
I also believe we shouldn't.
I don't know what the facts are.
Jack Kirby then after a while claimed that he actually created Spider-Man.
There's a whole controversy because Stan and Jack, you know, people say, you know, Jack
may did like 80%, 90% of the work and Stan did 10 and took credit or whatever.
Especially by the end of Fantastic Four.
I think he was right a lot and stuff.
But then there's other creators that like were there and don't say that's what happened.
But then Jack sort of by the end of his life was saying like, go and Stan didn't do it.
He just created Spider-Man 2 and it's very unclear.
Like no one was keeping good records of these things or it was literally just like guys
like, hey, you need to create a whole new thing that's going to be a giant hit in 50
years.
Can you do it by three o'clock today?
And it'd be like, I guess I was smoking and then, okay, here you go.
Here's a Spider-Man.
Here's a character that will endure the test of time.
You'll make multiple movies and TV shows out of him.
I just knocked it out before I got to go home.
Just shitting them out.
Yeah.
Pretty amazing.
Well, you can, everyone can go and enjoy Jack Kirby's shit out drawings in a high tech
environment.
What have we missed?
We covered a lot of ground.
Almost as much ground as the giant acreage of this very ride.
This is one of the biggest ride buildings.
I feel like on that property.
Yeah.
Massive.
I have, I have a fun thing at the end that's Spider-Man related, but maybe not this ride
related.
Okay.
Great.
Are we there?
We might be.
I guess.
We can be done for a while.
Yeah, we can be good.
Here's the thing I would say.
So I know we talked about like universal express kind of, kind of implemented after the fact,
like kind of wonky like stuff retrofitted for fast pass.
The queue for this is great.
Like going through the daily bugle offices, all of that.
So if it's a short wait and you, you do have express pass, try both go through the express
line and then just go through the standby line.
Cause I realized like what looking through queue video is like, Oh yeah, I haven't been
in that room with the little scoop.
There's a model of the car you're about to get into.
And then there's a big projector screens showing some different cartoon segments.
Yeah, that's great.
And see those file cabinets.
I think those are in the express line now.
I'm not sure how they very large extended queue to, which they had to utilize early,
early on.
Right.
Cause I remember waiting a lot outside that first year, like most of it outside, which
I don't know where that went, but yeah, I looked up the touring plans for like mid March,
their crowd estimates and they were like, yeah, early in the day, probably five minute
wait height of the crowds, 60 minutes starting to get in the spring break season, but still
not very long for like a still grade a attraction.
The last two times I went, yeah, we were, I mean, I think we had expressed cause we
were staying on site, but it was still like the regular time was 20 minutes, 20, 30 minutes.
So what do you got?
We're going to do, I was, I want, I have a plea, I have a question for the audience
real quick and then I'll play this thing.
We're going to do a lot more Marvel stuff.
We've talked about it, talked about doing that.
But I just, if anyone out there has seen pictures from a Marvel theme park that we're going
to build in Dubai, like a decade ago, they're the greatest pictures.
They really seem like they would have lived up to my expectations of a Marvel park.
There's pictures of like a crazy time square with what looks maybe like Doc OX tentacles
coming out and daredevils over here on a billboard.
And it's very kind of cartoonish, but not in the way that the islands of adventure is.
It's like, it's like a crazy, it's a little warped version of reality, but it's cool.
And it looks like if they built it, they would be awesome.
And there's expense mansion stuff and whatever.
If anyone out there in the audience knows about this gives us, it has any secret information,
please message us.
Marvel Dubai.
Marvel Dubai theme park.
And you'll see the pictures if you don't know what I'm talking about.
But if you do know what you're talking about and you have more info.
Yes, please just email us at podcast, the ride at Gmail or DM us on Twitter or something.
Because it says it was, there was these sketches were made by a place called Chimera designs,
I believe.
And I think if I click on that, that website doesn't exist.
I think that is gone.
I don't know if it exists anymore.
Maybe it does.
It's another name or something.
So yeah, message us because we want to do something on this.
At the very least, I want some secret information, please.
Yeah, for us to immediately make not secret.
Yeah, I mean, we will keep it secret if we have to.
You can pick and choose what you tell us.
Yeah, we're very good about that.
So if you have any information on that, please let us know because I would love to do something
with it.
But now here's, I don't know, I'm sure I've played this for you guys.
This is one of my favorite Spider-Man things.
Okay, so this is not directly real Spider-Man related.
So there's an album that I did not know about until a year or two ago.
And it is like a narrative.
It's like a story.
Spider-Man gets its own story.
It's not based on like a TV show or anything.
But there's a theme sung by this man, Ron Dante, who sang the Archie's hit sugar sugar
and all the other Archie songs.
And then he does Spider-Man's voice.
Have I played this for you before?
I can't remember.
It's so great.
And I wish my plus up for this ride is if they can figure out, and the movies, if they
can figure out a way to put this song in a movie ride, whatever it is.
So here we go.
Spider-Man rock-omic theme.
It's like a rock-omic, like a comic.
Rock-omic.
Okay.
So let me play this because I love it so much.
Spider-Man is a Spider-Man.
Everybody's talking about that normal Spider-Man.
Amazing, amazing.
How does he get through it?
He moves like a spider, moves like a man.
We're calling superhero your friendly Spider-Man.
Amazing, amazing.
How does he get through it?
He's a killer if he does that.
Wait, no.
Oh, I didn't think about it.
He's a deadly sex machine.
He's a sex suicide machine.
Geez, that's a different, that's a darker movie.
Ron Dante didn't know that.
That was before his confession.
We should not blame the song.
Don't blame Ron.
I will post a link to that.
1972.
Fantastic song.
I'd go so far as to say the second best song ever inspired by Spider-Man.
Obviously behind Shag Kroger and the man from saliva.
I guess we made it.
You Survive podcast, the ride.
That was a blast.
Hey, as I said, go to YouTube where you can see that Manser's thing and some other fun
stuff that we've done and Twitter where you will find the Ron Dante song and learn all
about what a sex machine Spider-Man is and email us any questions, podcasts, the road
at gmail.com or any secret info about Marvel Dubai.
And that's a lot of commands this time.
Yeah, sorry.
No, that's it.
I mean, just every, you know, rate and review us on Apple podcasts and what have you.
Yeah.
Any specific Spider-Man specific commands?
Oh, for the braiding in a review.
Oh, in the review.
Uh, yes.
Uh, let's see if, uh, tell us your a list Spider-Man villain.
Who's your top, top of the list Spider-Man villain?
Or give us your best J. Jonah Jameson rant about Spider-Man being a wall crawling menace.
Oh, so you want them to write like a couple of paragraphs.
It can be one pair.
It can be, you know, just a letter from the editor.
Sure.
Do that.
That is a letter from the editor.
It's a letter from the editor.
Also like to hear Jameson's thoughts about Chad Kroger.
Yeah.
Now he's great.
He's great.
Now that's a singer we can all agree on.
Wholesome rock and roll.
Wild untamed hair.
A true king of the genre.
Uh, well folks, thanks for listening.
See you next time.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen, Joe Sileo, and Alex Ramsey engineered and mastered by Alex
Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at foreverdogteam
and liking our page on Facebook.