Five, four, three, two, one.
Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
My name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
And Scott Gairdner.
Hello.
One of the big ones, we're hitting one of the big ones.
One of the big ones.
One that I was not too familiar with today.
It was 1998, Disney's Hollywood Studios.
Then Disney's MGM Studios.
Yeah, you're right, sorry.
Yeah.
Oh, it was still, okay.
I can never keep track of when those changes happened.
2000s, they changed to Hollywood Studios.
Was it that late?
Later 2000, or mid 2000s, yeah.
And that's when they had to get rid of the hat,
or they had to put the hat, or they left the hat on.
I don't know what the deal with the hat is.
I mean, we're gonna have to do with the hat.
The deal with the hat is it's bad, I hate the hat.
It's bad, yeah.
And it's gone, but they had like a problem
with the rights to use the Chinese theater
as the icon of the park.
Which was separate from using a lot of the MGM properties.
So as long as they blocked the view.
Right, it could still be there.
It's just the view of it was the issue.
That's my understanding of it.
I could be completely wrong.
Yeah, I don't know how much of it is apocryphal.
Yeah, we'll have to do an episode about that fucking hat.
Well the point is, this is sort of an,
this is an awkward era for that park at this point,
Disney, MGM Studios.
And today's attraction is definitely part of it.
Soundstage with Steven Weber.
Yes. Yeah.
Which is to me, like, I have only the vegas recollection
of this, but to me it was like,
it's like part of that transitional era
where the audience is no longer giving a shit
about how movies are made.
But they know that they have to start getting rid
of the original attractions about how movies are made.
Right. So we're seeing the original
Universal stuff go.
Yeah. Or like here in Hollywood,
like Backdraft is seeming really out of date
and they're trying to slide,
let's put the mummy into that thing where you go,
you know, through the stages instead of Back to the Future,
like those little demonstration stages or whatever.
They get rid of earthquake and turn it into that disaster
thing in Florida with Christopher Walken.
Yeah, they're trying to make everything more active
as opposed to, cause like Universal was,
all those initial things were like kind of passive experience.
It's like, not passive completely,
but it's like really taking you out of reality
and you want to show how the movies are made.
But they're all educational too.
A little too educational.
And like referring to a different type of movie.
Like there's a world of difference between,
you know, early nineties movies and late nineties movies.
So they're trying to make things sort of poppier
and bring, you know, fresher talent.
I like it was our, okay, so there's this attraction
with Chevy Chase and Martin Short.
And you know, they've never stopped being relevant,
but still it's weird you're watching
a Chevy Chase movie get made.
So I guess they're like, we need to start getting
some newer people into the park.
So like Drew Carey, right?
This weird sounds dangerous.
Sounds dangerous with Drew Carey,
this very dreadfully dull, like audio demonstration
with Drew Carey who's hot at the time.
And then elsewhere we end up with Steven Weber.
Which is interesting cause Drew Carey at least,
like the ABC merger at Disney had bought ABC.
Drew Carey show, big hit for ABC.
And I think was a few seasons in when Sounds Dangerous opened.
But.
A big part, a big feather in their cap.
Yeah, and before that, like Disney starting to do more,
Disney did used to have more stuff on NBC.
Steven Weber, 98 would have been like coming off of Wings,
which was a hit, but not like a monster hit.
But he was in the family, right?
He was in the Disney family.
He had done, well, yeah, so I was looking at it,
I was trying to figure out why.
Okay, so he is a, this was weird.
He was a voice on the show, The Legend of Tarzan,
which was an animated Tarzan show.
In which he plays Edgar Rice Burroughs.
Apparently the author of Tarzan shows up
in the world of Tarzan.
And he sort of played like you don't know who this is
and there's a reveal at the end.
It's the creator.
Which children would love.
Oh yeah. Children would love.
Was there a, very familiar with classic authors.
Very familiar with the author itself.
Was there a sequel to like Hunchback
where Victor Hugo was a character?
Like, what was this, a constant thing happening?
Well, that's actually the post credit sequence
on Hunchback 2, the directed video one.
It's Victor Hugo just witnessing all this stuff
and going like, huh, this might make an interesting story.
Crazy times in my town of Paris lately.
Maybe I'll write it all down.
Yeah.
In Lion King one and a half,
I think the creator of the anime
that the Lion King ripped off shows up.
Right.
This looks awfully familiar.
Should Lion King rip off an anime?
Yeah. Do you know all that?
I forget that. Oh, I didn't know that.
It's why in the Simpsons joke
when there's a Mufasa type character in the sky
next to Bleeding Gums Mervy that he says.
Kimba. Yeah.
You have to avenge my death, Kimba.
I mean Simba.
I know Kimba or I know the, yeah, I kind of know that.
I didn't even think about that.
I always just think of the Hamlet
because there's so many parallels to the story of Hamlet.
It's also that.
Yeah. Interesting.
Anyway, so he's in the Stars and Cartoon.
What I forgot is that he was in the ABC fan.
He was heading for a show called Once and Again,
which ran for a couple of years.
That premiered in September 99.
So that's like a year out.
So maybe he had like a development,
maybe he was like under Disney contract at that point.
And they're probably like with Superstar limo,
like trying to get people around who are like, you know, cheap.
They're not like you were like getting the
having to get Robin Williams or somebody to sign a contract to be shown in the
play, like it's somebody they're already doing business with.
Hey, can you do a day on this attraction?
Yeah. And I had an experience with that, like as a kid,
like I was one of my weird kid things was I liked Steven Weber a lot
and I liked Wings a lot because USA Network,
USA Network had this promotion for a while called Primetime in the A.M.
And they would show like from like eight to 10 a.m.
They would show in syndication was specifically.
I remember Wings and Ned and Stacey,
which is the sitcom that Thomas Hayden Church left Wings to go do.
That was him and never finish out wings.
He didn't finish out wings. No.
And it was different missing in a different pair title show,
a different pair title show.
And it did run for like two or three seasons.
Like researching this, I realized like so many shows like
Single Guy or Boston Common did get like two seasons or so.
Boston Common was in Primetime in the A.M.
But they weren't showing syndicated friends or syndicated Seinfeld.
They were showing the other NBC shows that were cheaper, probably, to get the rights.
Sure. And I'm trying to get you accustomed to you like these as well.
Right. Yeah. With many viewings, you will start to like Caroline in the city. Sure.
And I mean, Wings did have Tony Shalhoub, Steven Weber, Thomas Hayden Church.
Like a very decent guys.
Thomas Hayden Church and Steven Weber are very similar guys to me.
I think they look similar. I think I got when I
I think when I was picturing this attraction, I thought maybe it was Thomas Hayden Church.
Oh, maybe I think of him as having such a distinctive like cadence and delivery.
I think of Weber much more affable, I feel like.
Well, but not on Studio 60 on the Sunset Strip.
That was another thing.
He's menacing executive Jack Rudolph.
That's fair. Whoa. Steven Weber from Wings is on a new NBC show.
It's about behind the scenes of comedy from the creator of the West Wing.
Sign me up. And Bradley Whitford.
And Bradley Whitford. You love Rob Cordray.
You're going to love his brother.
I got to say, I spent I worked so hard trying to get an internship on Studio 60
because I was out here doing a semester in college.
And did you on the actual show itself or the show about the show Warner Brothers?
I was living at the apartment up the road.
You just thought it was real and you wanted to be part of it.
No. Well, I mean, I wish I could study under the tutelage of Matt Albee and Danny Tripp.
But I just want to polish the microphone where the announcer says live from the sunsets.
Wait, it's like a much more convoluted life.
Yeah. Live from Studio 60 on the Sunset Strip.
Live from Studio. Live from the Sunset Strip.
Now is the time for Studio 60 live.
Get ready. I think it was that.
But so they were shooting at Warner Brothers and no one could be.
Other people tried. No one could get an internship.
And one person got an internship.
And it turned out that it was because she was like her mom was Bradley
Whitford's cousin or something.
And that's how she got in there.
This was the Lori Loughlin scenario of its day.
Yeah. You know, and then we were all a fool.
Like then when midseason when 30 Rock came on, we're like, well, this is infinitely better.
Like this is it was funny.
Yeah. The two. And then you thought like, how can this stupid one survive?
And it did by leaps and bounds.
It blew it out of the water.
By the way, Felicity Huffman hosted Studio 60 within the world.
She definitely. Yeah.
Because and like maybe in the pilot, like I feel like Judd is it Judd Hirsch?
Is the guy who's the guy who cracks up?
Oh, she the host. I think she's the hood of the one that implodes.
Is that what the events?
Because I think he says, Felicity, I'm sorry, you're doing a great job.
Like, I'm having a rough.
Just go get a cup of tea and everything's going to be OK.
OK, one which as the famous meltdown,
that feels like a nod to television for the Sorkin heads, where it's like,
well, Dana from Sports Night is hosting in studio actresses hosted Studio 60.
Again, use people keeping the family together.
Yeah, keeping the company.
He's, you know, theatrical, you know, keeping the company together.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. He's got his his rep players.
Yeah. The author of the play, the Farnsworth invention, Aaron Sorkin.
You have to. That's an interesting like how much Sorkin Disney
park crossover there. I feel like there are a few.
Oh, yeah. Interesting.
I mean, this this is a big one within that, at least.
I mean, OK, we haven't said like, what is the thing with this show?
Like I said, it's sort of in that world of like it's it's behind it.
They're trying to do fresher behind the scenes takes
and that are utilizing, you know, kind of kind of flashier effects.
And it's mainly I guess, how would you describe it?
That he like Stephen Webber is your host as you go
inside a working Hollywood sound stage and learn about
all of the parts of it until something goes around.
Yeah, I think that's pretty right. Park premise.
It's a lot. It's a little bit of superstar television.
It's a little bit of earthquake and tornado and twister.
It's like all a little bit of thing. Armageddon.
It's like kind of all that in one.
And it's kind of like a practical set.
But then like they at least weren't just showing you different video.
There was sort of like a Pepper's Ghost sort of like it looks like they were sort of
in to make Stephen Webber sort of be hosting.
Yeah. What you're saying is like they had this effect that would kind of make him 3D ish.
Like it's the kind of best they could do for like 1998.
It looks a lot better in like Gringotts in the queue for Gringotts.
It looks well, yeah. I mean, they had perfected it.
But he does look a little bit like you can from the white.
There's there's very little video footage of it, too.
But there one like there because this is back before cell phone cameras.
There I can kind of see that I could give you squinted.
You'd be like, oh, is Stephen Weber standing there hosting this?
But obviously, I'm sure it's like a naturally good.
There's a reason why this effect keeps blowing people's minds and the Tupac hologram.
And right. What have you.
It does just work.
But I think it's a pain in the ass to do.
And that's, you know, like when they did the Aerosmith because that's the same,
you know, technique that makes it look like Aerosmith in the recording studio.
And even then, it's a little better. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. This was almost like a test scenario for that, maybe.
But I think they all had to like wear crazy contact lenses.
They can Marino famously unspeaking extra in that part.
I think they all had to wear like weird because they have to light it so bright
and so heavy to make it to make the footage bright enough to appear like it's in the room,
which makes me wonder, is that why Stephen Weber?
Did they throw this to like a Steve Martin and he's like, and what do I have to do?
I have to be trapped under special contact lenses like UV contacts.
Mm hmm. Yeah, I would not.
I feel like Stephen where it can have been the first choice.
And it's not like this is like catered to him.
I feel I feel like it was like a role that like, all right.
And then an actor will be your host.
And it's who they this is who they landed on. Right.
Yeah, I mean, I would assume I didn't because like there's so much
lore surrounding Rock and Rollercoaster about like, oh, it was going to be
the Rolling Stones, but they said no, it was going to be Kiss.
But they said no, you wanted too much money.
And then it's Aerosmith. There's not quite as much.
But yeah, I was trying to figure out like, yeah, 1997 or something.
Who on ABC? Because Drew Carey show
Drew Carey makes sense to host a thing around that time.
They already had him pegged for the other.
You know, they're thinking Tim out like it's got to be.
Yes. Or I mean, or yeah.
Any anyone Richard Karn?
You could even like soundstage with Richard Karn.
Obviously, sure. I feel like Weber over Karn.
No offense, Karn.
No, he has to be on that list shortlist.
Just because you don't like you do kind of recognize the name Steven Weber.
You're more like I know Al when I see him.
I don't know the name.
Yeah, you do now more from like infomercials or whatever.
Well, and it it falls into that weird nebulous kind of area where it's like
Steven Weber is playing himself, but then some of the people
who work in other departments are like recognizable actors,
but they're playing characters like Ellen's energy adventure.
Yeah. Yeah. How it's like.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Uh huh. Because like, yeah, when you go to the lighting department or whatever,
it's like Martin Moll is one of them. Is that right?
Yeah. He shows up.
And then I mean, the weirdest one was that like so they go through all the departments
and eventually they get to director.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the director is Elliott Gould.
So they got Elliott Gould to do the director character.
And there's even like a joke about it where like Steven Weber says, like,
you know, he gives good notes and goes like, yeah, that's a great idea.
Hey, you should be an actor. Yeah.
You should be an actor, as he said.
But it's like, is Elliott Gould sort of on the way down?
Because like soundstage with Elliott Gould is that well, doesn't even
amount of time like these people will do cameos, but I will like
stick around for the whole thing.
But didn't you find like Elliott Gould shows up in like, was it Carolyn in the city?
It did. I sounds right.
I seen there's one where Elliott Gould shows up as himself
and they're like looking through a telescope.
Why did I see this?
Someone posted this recently.
There it's like you were just following around Elliott Gould with a telescope.
I think it was someone posting.
Posting about like Christine Baranski is on.
What show was she on? Was she on?
She was on Sibyl. Yeah.
So there's an episode of Sibyl where she's looking through a telescope.
She realized Elliott Gould is like next door and like he's like in a state of undress.
And then at some point he comes over and knocks on the front door and he goes like,
do you want a better look at like opens his robe and the audience goes crazy?
Does the so is the reaction similar with the director joke?
Does it kill?
I think I feel like I only saw this like once or twice.
I feel like the one time it kind of did because then Elliott Gould kind of like
looks in the camera and rolls his eyes a little like makes a thing.
Yeah. So you saw you.
You did this attraction. So I don't think I did.
I don't have a memory of it.
I don't think I did it.
So because I guess we weren't there because it was open for a very short time.
We would have been in the less than a year.
Then, yeah, I don't think.
Did you I don't I didn't see a confirmation on this.
I saw that there was a thing where they were selling like megaphones sort of,
where you could kind of shout along with the cues of the ride.
So it would say soundstage on like an old time like megaphones.
I think they would. It's pretty good.
Yeah, it is pretty.
I could I could not find anyone on eBay to confirm that they sell the clapboards.
But yeah, you haven't seen the director megaphones,
which is still what we assume sets have. Right.
Even though Tino has a giant.
Yeah, he has one. He might.
He might. And he should. Yeah.
But not JJ. No, no.
They switched to bull horns if they have to.
You just have like a radio shack.
You don't think that wasn't intended to take home.
That's like you would go on the attraction again and like say the
is it because they ask like the audience all has to yell action and quiet on the set?
So you do it with the I think that was the idea that it was a fun interactive thing.
So it would be like we're all going to try it.
We'll all say action. We'll all say cut, print or whatever.
The Harry Potter wand of its time.
Right. The megaphone, the soundstage megaphone.
I mean, that that yeah, that was weird.
Like the interactive stuff was so in its infancy.
But I thought the strangest thing was that for a while,
like they go through all these departments, but they skip the sound department
because sounds dangerous was coming.
And Steven Weber says, separate, see whoever says like,
I'm going to leave that one to my friend, Drew.
And but my God, he pre allude to it.
Yeah, this open first.
So for a while, people were like, what the fuck is he talking about?
It's like a Rosita type, like not.
Yeah, there's a little Easter egg.
What's only for like the shittiest stakes, the shittiest thing.
And then Drew Carey is playing a character in Sounds Dangerous.
So like some wires got crossed.
They did not like check each other's reality.
Oh, yeah. Maybe there was a draft of Sounds Dangerous where he was to carry himself.
And what's the name of the character from Sounds Dangerous?
It's like Detective Godfrey or something.
Or Hobnob.
Yeah, he's like some bumblein.
Huh? Weird.
That is weird. This inconsistent mythologies.
That's a perfect like that's, you know, of the time for sure.
I think, OK, here's what here's the other reason I think this happened in the wind.
Like, OK, the they built Disney Studios thinking will have
like we'll build all these sound stages and there will be actual shows being fit
like Nickelodeon Studios Universal.
All that was filmed in Disney and James Studios.
Mickey Mouse Club's going on and Star Search with Ed McMahon.
Oh, yeah.
And so you would go on these walking tours and you would look down into the sets,
which was a big deal for me.
I loved M.M.C. as a kid.
And you can sit like, well, wow, it's empty and nobody's working down there.
But I could see the actual set.
Then the production stops because after the Disney
Universal war settles down, they they all stop pretending
that they're actually a film stuff at these studios.
But these sound stages are all like in the park.
They're all like, it's not even just like here's the studio area like it is
universal, like you're walking right by them and they're just rotting.
They're nothing. Right.
So like, how can we repurpose the studio?
How can we repurpose the sound stage and make an attraction out of it
by making it a sound stage that comes to life?
So you it's all of the though the effects are neat.
Essentially, if you look through it all, you are just walking through an empty
sound stage, right?
Some cases just totally unadorned.
There's the door. There's the fire extinguisher.
I mean, need effects at everything.
But like, I don't know, they don't like sell it necessarily completely.
It seems like a quick fix.
It just seems. Yeah.
So it's literally then easy to get rid of.
It's like it's not like they made a Transformers type experience.
No, they are to demolish, which that like and that stuff is.
So you're like all of those little demonstrations of like
the parts of the sound stage, which are we I mean, like the departments,
I guess, I guess, yeah, the costume area would be in the sound stage.
But it becomes a stretch.
Like, well, how do you show this stuff when they get to craft services?
The running craft services joke, which as a comedy nerd,
this is very funny to think back that it was Chris Elliott doing.
Chris Elliott was the craft services guy.
And the running joke is that his name was Mickey.
It was Mickey, the craft services guy.
And Steven Weber keeps making jokes of like, hey, you look different.
Where's Minnie?
You look different from the cartoons and all.
And then he keeps eating that cheese, too.
Like that's his of all the crafts.
Like he he's pushing the cheese on everyone to eat because there's just too.
So much cheese. There's just so much.
But he is not Mickey Mouse.
But they know any and he's like, why do people keep saying that?
Meanwhile, he has a big block of cheese that he keeps pushing.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then it's like, yeah, but you got all that cheese.
Good Chris Elliott part like, yeah, sort of like grimy, you know,
I miss him being and he seems like he doesn't show up and stay.
He would like be in commercials.
He'd be little parts in movies.
And he's on Schitt's Creek, which I've never watched.
So I'll continue to assume that it's very good.
People say it's very good. I'm sure it is.
All those people are good. Check it out.
He gives this is all.
And I think the character actors in general, and not to say that Stephen doesn't.
He's like, I don't know. I mean, it's not like he
he just kind of like walks through it with this sort of like
flipping air. He's like tossing off.
You know, it's the one I like is when he's like telling you in general
what a sound stage is.
And he and like, you know, yeah, you know, it's this big place
of the with the tall roof, whatever.
It's kind of like your high school gym, except nobody's getting rope burn.
It's like, that's all right.
Yeah, that's fine.
I don't know. You know, he does it with sort of this 90s
Dennis Miller thing.
So he's fine. But it's for sure there's more to chew on as the craft service guy.
Did you guys ever have to do that in school, like climb the rope to the gym?
Yeah. I never did that, which made the joke seem weird to me
that they would do like, yeah, it feels like a very fifties version of
which have made it work for dads. But you did the rope.
I did the rope. I didn't get to the ceiling.
I don't remember. I didn't get that.
Were there mats like if you fell, were there mats?
There were. There was like a mat, but it wasn't like a big crash pad.
It was like a couple of gym mats.
So I would assume some kids, no one ate shit.
No one like fell on their head as far as I saw.
But I would assume. Yeah.
Because I'm trying to remember.
I for sure did the rope and I did not get very high.
But kids would get high.
So you think there was a chance that they just flipped or like let go
and they cracked their head on the ground.
Yeah. Hmm.
We should look into accident.
We will try. We try to avoid theme park accidents, but the rope,
gym class, rope accidents.
I don't like knowing that my beloved theme parks have problems, but yeah,
some, you know, yeah, incidents at high schools.
Or the rope. I'm sure at a certain point, a rope became detached.
Mm hmm. Had to have.
How sturdy could it have been?
Right. Yeah.
Because they didn't have sounds.
The sound stage is famous grids, which they talk about at length
as if a grid is interesting.
Like the lighting grid and then there's walks.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, they do a whole like the lighting grid sort of has its own personality.
So it's like, are you are you guys ready?
Are the floods ready? And it's like boop boop.
And then they kind of like have that little like Pixar lamp
kind of a movement to it.
That was really fun.
Light has more personality because he can bend all around.
Yes. But like the, you know, what it did a great job of teaching me.
I can't even name it.
Just like the general like fluorescence. Right.
Are there there? No, they just they just like hum.
They literally hum. Right. Yeah.
And they get me. They do that.
Like the work lights when they come on, they do make that thunk
that like when you throw a bunch of fluorescence on, you can hear like,
thunk. And then like they say they're like the crotchety.
Yeah, they're the crotchety.
Yeah. I like when he's when the gels, I like the gels.
He goes, ready gels?
And then the gels that are like a bright purple
and they kind of give a different like mood.
Oh, well, we love they kind of go through like the rain, but and it's a little like
the it's sort of like a little like Tiki room scenario.
The lights might be the my favorite part of all of it, honestly.
That's fun. Lights are fun.
Yeah. They have like a little personality.
I always like something.
And this did I did remember this from being a kid like.
So you come in the one elephant elephant door of the sound stage.
But then it looks like there's a second set of elephant doors
that you're looking at.
And he goes like, why do they shoot on sound stages?
Why don't they just shoot outside and goes, well, sometimes outside
doesn't cooperate and they slide open the elevator doors.
And there's an Orlando like downpour going.
And it's like, but in here, we can make any weather we want.
That's right. They do the like little miniature reveal of like the hard rain.
Yeah. Coming down.
Yeah. Yeah.
I you know what I part that I was always like, all right,
I see why they're demonstrating this, but it's a little like
they take they take a little too far when they when they explain
soundproofing, you know, you got to get into all the like
the nitty gritty of the buildings themselves, like the fascinating process
of the soundproof. Yeah, that takes up a lot of time, a lot of time.
And they've already like glossed over.
We're not going to talk about the sound department.
Not the recording of the sound, but the idea that you need like,
yeah, a quiet environment that at least like they feel like they need to address.
So there's this there's like when they they flip on like, all right,
if there wasn't, you know,
like if you couldn't control the environment and there was no roof
on the place, you know, then your movie would sound like then they like show a scene
from the movie. I forget.
It's like so it's just like some generic touchstone kind of movie.
But you hear like it's the sounds that it's not just like general,
like what you would hear if one plane was passing by.
It is full on World War Two.
It was like a thousand planes and tractors and cats and sheep's bawling.
But then they inflate the soundproofing cloth. Right.
And then that all makes it go away. Yeah.
Which is like, all right.
I mean, you have to exaggerate it to get the point across.
But like who's trying to make a movie during like an air raid?
Why? Why is it so crazy?
I would imagine that they try to just like put normal noise in it.
It wasn't that bad. It didn't read. So then.
Right. So they were just like, well, let's throw all this shit against the wall.
And but the inflatable wall,
seeing the inflatable walls just like puff up all of a sudden,
like behind that scrim. Right. That's kind of a neat effect.
That was a neat effect.
I did think, though, like in terms of exaggeration, I thought they went
they pushed it a little too far, like almost a little condescending
when he's like, we're on the set of a new show I'm on called Order Up,
which is about a big city lawyer who leaves his firm
to take over his family's New England diner.
And so like he's the head of the he's the head cook and manages the diner.
But he also used to be a big city lawyer.
And it's like, I don't it's so confusing.
So much. Yeah, there's so much.
Well, like everyone in the audience is like, OK, that's a little we know that's fake.
That's not a real show.
Which and also and like as a theme park,
you mean we get to go inside a false kitchen.
Yeah. Makes boy, you know, I like going inside Indiana Jones's
you know, into the temple.
Indiana Jones is invading.
But I also like seeing a false kitchen. Yeah. Yeah.
So, yeah, I mean, there's a lot of unexciting stuff,
I would say with it in general.
It's just so what I mean, it's all real.
Order up is the most realistic.
Like, yeah, for sure, that's a show that would happen.
But like, yeah, they're not going to take us into, you know, right.
But then collapsing mine or three cameras, you can only be so interesting.
So they're also showing you movie tricks to like it.
Yeah, well, they do.
So they're like because they have to live in like the order up universe.
Like they have to stay in that narrative.
But that's this that's what this TV show is.
But they do want to show you like stunts and stunt men.
So they're showing you like, I forget what the character's name is,
but a character and it's a real live performer has to slip on a banana peel in the kitchen.
So he has to do a big fall, but they have to show that there's a crash pad there
and he's going to slip on it.
And then they're like, and this is one of the megaphone parts
where you have to yell into the megaphone.
It's like, OK, ready stunt man, Steve.
So that's like a kind of a famous thing that people would like, I guess.
Ready stunt man, Steve.
I also saw there's a whole section of like red bubble shirts.
I didn't even realize this devoted to that.
Like stunt man. Yeah, it's crazy because I thought it's like a hat box ghost of this
where it's like I didn't even realize hat box ghost was a thing until, you know,
10 years ago. But I guess that's a thing.
I didn't even realize that was like a theme park.
It's in the family of Scuba Steve, the big daddy.
Yes, there is beloved toe who Adam Sandler dresses up as right.
A little sexist, though, that they don't allow for the possibility of a right.
So it always has to be a male man.
And for Stephanie, yeah, right.
I think if they were to bring it back, they would have to do.
Yeah, they would obviously have to.
It would have to be flexible to be a gender.
Yeah. Like if you name it, Dana or Joe or something like some sort of gender
neutral, they did the guy that takes you around is named Casey.
And the dialogue refers to like Steven always says, like, like, OK,
you're ready, Casey, which does allow like for gender neutrality.
So they thought of it there. But Stuntman Steve, I guess they're
just like who they did a casting.
And it was like, I think only the guys are going to work for this.
And the joke is Steven Weber, it's his name. His name is Steve, too.
So I think that's another reason why, because he was like, I'm glad that's
this different Steve Stuntman.
Yeah, right. Stuntman Steve, not me.
So they have to call him on set if you have Steve, two people turn around.
But they started saying Stuntman Steve. Right.
So they milk it. So I understand for those jokes, they had to do it.
Because he's got dialogue with the live performers.
So it had they had to choose what I'm saying.
What I also like that to then force them and they like that
the diner has to serve banana splits in order to set up.
Right. That's like its trademark or signature item.
Yeah. And they can't just make that a subtle thing.
Like there's this gigantic sign. Right.
Blinking signs that they can involve it in the lighting demonstration.
A big neon sign today's special banana splits. Right.
But it's a special every day. It's always the special.
They're like, what what restaurant would what short order restaurant
would invest in a constantly flashing?
I mean, one that Jason would go to. Yeah.
I do think of banana splits of like a diner staple, like
because it seems like, oh, that's something, you know, we've been drinking
or you want something sweet late at night or so.
It's it's not a lot of stuff to keep in the kitchen.
It's a few kinds of ice cream,
special bananas and those bananas keep working for desserts, even if they
like a mushy banana can still factor into a dessert.
Yeah. Yeah. Banana bread.
Even if eating the banana is unpleasant.
But like maraschino cherries, crushed pineapple, like that shit keeps forever.
So chocolate syrup. Yeah. Yeah.
I which also the part where the the ice box
open where the big industrial fridge opens and you feel the cold blast.
Yeah, that's cool.
But it doesn't like represent anything.
It doesn't make sense.
The movie like if you're watching the show order up at home,
you wouldn't be able to feel the cold.
It's like neat to be in the audience and have a big blast of cold at you.
Yeah. But what is that showing off?
No, because, you know, most of those things aren't plugged in on a set.
So it's just like that was just a fun thing they thought to do, I guess.
And it is. Yeah. Yeah.
But I'm trying to track the actual narrative of like
if it is literally the making of order up, then, yeah,
why have they bothered to plug everything in?
So it's like so much of it is devoted to such dull, like real movie,
like filmmaking information.
But then there's just huge blind spots of why would they do this?
Yeah, it seemed like they were running out of material to show everyone.
It's like, we need a fun thing here.
Let's hit them with cold air because there's not that much like sound
stages essentially are empty rooms.
Yeah. And they do their best to dress it up.
But I mean, like, yeah, you know, like the like probably the like
not every department is literally going to work out of the same sound.
They're all kind of on top of each other.
And then when you exit like the exit area, it doesn't go into a gift shop.
It does go into a photo op area where you can pretend to be like
a lighting rigger or you can pretend to be Mickey
giving out like snacks and stuff.
You could put on like overalls like to be like a union, like a teamster.
Yeah, like a team.
You could hold a clipboard and a megaphone like Elliot Gould.
And there's the I mean, and it is neat that you could like
like that they have those lights around their phone
and you can pick them up and hold them over your head.
Oh, those are even though those like, yeah, they would be very heavy in real life.
Did you end up like, well, it's more for kids, but you didn't end up
with a photo of like the like, you know, the thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
They're maybe, you know, my there are probably boxes and boxes of Disney photo.
Like, I remember I remember my mom when I was in like sixth or seventh grade,
buying like one of the big Mickey photo albums down there.
And she's like, I'll put all the all the pictures from all the trips in this.
And I think it got a few photos in it.
And it's probably in the box with the photos.
So we got to get you got to find out.
I got to dig next time I'm home.
Well, you know what they do have is that like, OK, so like with with order up,
it becomes tough to like, like they still want to do all their universal trickery.
Yes. Yeah. Like because if we haven't said, it's like one of those things
where you're on the set, but then everything goes, hey, well,
like the real magic of the movies unfolds on the set.
So they want to have, you know, like water flood out, which that works in a kitchen.
They want to do pyro.
So there is like the big flash fire.
The stove on the grill.
And that's the that's legitimately impressive.
That's fun. But then it's a little more of a stretch that they that at the very end,
that a train like a subway train goes haywire
and slams into the into the wall of the restaurant,
which, by the way, would be a cool thing to happen on. Right. Order up. Sure.
Like there. But that's the entire budget of the season.
If you have your your set, actually have a train go through it.
But they I understand they want to bring it to life, you know, in a theme park
setting. But then that sets up that cutting to us, the audience as the extras
going, ah, like you're about to crash into the restaurant.
And then they edit it together, you know, so that you can like
we're in the movie, the train car, and you can like take that tape home.
But do you remember, like, you want to guess the amount of money to like
have that you take home a video of you and the entire audience
crashing as part of a train crashing into the into the restaurant
in an episode of Order Up?
Like three minute video. Three.
So you don't even get to see the whole show.
You don't even get to take home a copy of the whole show.
Well, there's all that, you know, they edit you into an episode.
Oh, right. So like so you're in all of the use.
You get all of the Steven Webbers and like, you know, when the kid like
dresses up as the shorter cook and, you know, the volunteer kids or whatever.
Like twenty five dollars. Forty five for a VHS.
Forty five for late that you're barely ninety eight.
That's barely. Jesus. Wow.
I think it's probably like to turn those things around that quickly.
Then it's you know, it's Disney.
They're going to they're going to gouge you.
But you don't like you.
You barely see from the one that you barely like see yourself in there.
And you're one of like 50 people.
And it doesn't look like you're on a train.
You're clearly in like bleachers of a studio audience.
So the whole thing is like, also, like, yeah, that wasn't going to last.
Train derailing crashing into a diner is a tragedy.
That's not like a funny that they're trying to sell that as like a funny
sitcom hijinks.
Yeah, somebody slips on a banana peel and then a train mows through.
And what scenario is like that?
Why would a train be tiered like?
It gets confusing, too, because they they make a joke about like, oh,
stuntman Steve's fault.
And I couldn't tell if it's like that's the real.
The reality of it is that he drove a train into the soundstage
or he drove a train into the scene.
Is it a thing that's supposed to happen?
Did they plan on that happening on this episode?
Right. Or is it like a magic misfire?
I thought it was supposed to be a joke about like, you know, oh, no,
they got carried away next door or like, oh, no, tomorrow's production
showed up too early. Oh, right.
But then I don't that always got confusing for me there.
And the conceit that like one day it's a diner, the next day
it's immediately a subway car.
They can't trade out sets with that.
No, today's set is order up and then tomorrow is NYPD Blue.
And it's such an inconsistent show because that's that train thing happens
right after a five minute kind of a chunk about how to be a good audience.
Like it's like the most boring part where they're like showing you
how people flub lines and then you have to sit there and like, keep your laughter up.
Like, it's this real dry part about like being a good studio audience.
And then a train, then the train part.
So it's like, what are we doing here?
I don't. Yeah. And but they also can't have
when Steven Weber is enacting these scenes as the owner, he can't
fuck up and go, shit.
Yeah, they have to like, just like, darn it.
Yeah. Shucks.
Screwed that up.
Like that's sort of what he has to do because you can't you can't curse.
And that is usually like, yeah, the sitcom taping, they'll they'll curse
or say something and that'll actually wake up the audience a little
because they get to see a blooper.
You know what I did?
You know what I like? We kind of stepped.
We went to into the ride before this.
They have like a warm up guy before the show starts, which I liked.
But why is he doing like a Sam Kinison impression?
Isn't that weird?
Like he's yelling at the audience so aggressively and I just doesn't make any sense.
Dead by that point.
For sure. Sam Kinison is dead by that.
He's yelling. He's such an aggressive.
Why wouldn't they pick a different stand up?
I guess like a recognizable, like even if people don't know,
they know like yelling comic or like, where are you from?
He yells. He's like yelling at people.
I mean, I get it that that gets the energy up.
It's just such an odd choice in 1998.
Well, it's to like bring it to life.
Like when you have to exaggerate, like in the 50s primetime cafe,
like, you know, the most 50s mom ever. Right.
You need the most abrasive. Right.
You know, I guess.
But then like that like warm up guys that we're dealing with that at all.
Yeah. I mean, I get that it's fun because people are filing in
and they're trying to have some business there.
But yeah, why? That's a extra level of.
Yeah, I forget. What is this?
What is his name again?
Did you catch the warm up guys?
They give him a name.
Ralph. Yeah, that sounds like a.
Yeah, I think it was Ralph because that like that seems like generically gruff.
Like that's like a Jake Sully kind of like.
Jay, oh, you like a guy.
The guy named. Yeah.
Yeah, I think there I think there may have been.
Like an actual like like I think this might be like an inside reference
or something to the guy who did warm up for Star Search like this.
Oh, really? Yeah, that there was there was like an abrasive guy.
It was like I read somewhere that he was he was like
like took it a little too far, took the yelling stick too far
and was yelling at that somebody who was actually hard of hearing.
And like that's why and he's like yelling like why are like like like like,
wake up, why did you come here to sleep?
And then he got in trouble.
Like, no, that was that person was actually so specific.
Like that's so neat.
I mean, that's like it does make me laugh when like every
every park has its own niche stuff that doesn't show up in a guidebook.
But like Disneyland has like stuff unique to Disney, like, you know, the the
oh, Chef Oscar, then the potato dish he invented and and like the swing dancing
and the thing and your feet and the ducks, like the ducks walk out
and the ducks and the cats and all this stuff like usually the mythology of
an angry, abrasive star search warm up guy is not as charming
as they're being ducks in a pond.
No, it's not.
But it's like and that but that didn't even last as long.
Like the swing dancing has been there for decades.
But I guess I think they thought it was a type like the the warm up guy
who's off his rocker.
They thought it was like a familiar stereotype.
Which is funny, I guess, if you're coming up with these ideas in Glendale,
California, I'd imagine nearing.
But like the middle of the country, maybe if they came to Hollywood,
maybe they saw a sitcom.
I did walk and leap.
There's only a couple little videos like but I did see one.
I saw another one.
I think I had to I was looking at like daily.
It wasn't even YouTube.
It was like Daily Motion.
I found it on or one of those.
Oh, yeah. Obscure, obscure sites because this is so poorly documented.
Yeah. But I do think they toned it down.
It was the date was later.
So I think they had to tone down the yelling.
So this is an alien encounter.
Yeah. Scenario where you could see it pre and see it after.
Yeah. Like the Sam Kinnison impression was less coked up, basically.
Yeah. Casey does a lot more heavy lifting at a certain point.
Yeah, for sure. They upped Casey's role, which you know what I like
is the the handing back and forth of the sound stage master control,
like the big box that Steven has that controls the sound.
You know, that little thing, the box that controls all of it, that opens the doors.
You always get that to your lead.
You always let your lead fiddle around with that.
Yeah. Yeah.
So the fact that they're able to like,
I'm actually still not sure how they do that effect of like passing it from
this like, you know, a hologram character essentially right to a real person.
But then like, but it's fun that that sets up the, you know,
like like the back and forth and who's got it and where is it that that sets up
that like like then when then when the kid
has it and like that and he like doesn't know how to operate it.
And that's what makes the set go haywire and the the grease fire shoot off.
Right. Yeah.
Did you catch they say who invents invented the sound stage box?
Did you guys catch this?
No. The inventor.
Yeah, they talk about who invented the box because it's like they do sort of
acknowledge it's sort of a fantastical box.
Nigel Channing.
They tie it together.
You can catch that because he goes, oh, yeah, I got to talk to the creator
of this box. And then he goes, Nigel Channing.
And he throws it away like you were saying he throws a lot of jokes.
So it's referencing Sounds Dangerous and the Imagination Institute.
Yes. At least was open. Right.
So they were this is actually we were talking about how there's a couple
appearances of Nigel Channing now or three.
I forget. I mean, this is just a name only.
Right. He doesn't make it very.
This is the pre-C. Yes.
Tying together that wow, the host of Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
So you watch Honey, I Shrunk the Audience.
He's handing out the inventor of the year awards, but you don't know what he invented.
Right. And finally, it is answered.
It's answered here.
The man. What did you what's the box?
This the sound stage master control master control box.
Yeah. So he so Nigel Channing did work for Hollywood.
He was like, yeah, there.
Why would there be a different like a chain to open the door and a full,
you know, why would you want like a board for the lighting grid?
Why can't it all be in one remote? Right.
Yeah. So I was shocked.
So Nigel Channing revolutionized, you know, sound stage
care and maintenance.
Yes. With this mechanism.
And they kind of like the crew all like kind of scott.
There's a couple punch lines of like actors,
like because it's always Steven Weber or the kid doing hijinks with that control.
And and there that that control box is the thing that makes stuff go wrong.
You know what I like is when Steven presents that
and he's explaining kind of what it is.
And he said that joke about like it's kind of like your remote control at home.
But sorry, folks, even this can't control your VCR clock.
And we can reset your VCR.
Oh, yeah. They only had a couple of years left of that.
Still worked. Still worked at the time.
You still has the VCR, even if it's not your primary mechanism.
And that's true. I don't know how to reset.
Yeah. The cost is
Nora Dunn, who's the costuming woman.
She laughs at that.
The character laughs at that.
She's the only one. The character.
The people in the real people in the audience don't.
But Nora Dunn, Nora Dunn laughs at it.
Right. The false costumer.
Yeah. That's the thing with the costume department also.
OK, we've it's a show with like a what kinds of characters are going to be in a in a diner.
There's you know, you need like you need you need aprons and you need the paid
maybe like a a cop comes in or a New York firefighter or whatever.
A couple of regulars reading the paper. Yeah. Yeah.
But why does why does Nora Dunn need to operate from this like
endless rack of clothing with like, you know, like a like a marching band
uniforms and like, you know, like the 50s space alien in silver.
When are they going to need that on hand for daughter up?
Well, I think it was just holdover from like, remember, the tram used to go
through the costuming bill that would ride through the costuming building.
Giant windows.
You could see all these costume racks.
So I'm wondering if they're just like, well, we got all these costume racks.
We may as well use them.
And the productions have left nothing is shooting here anymore.
What I don't get and Christina are long gone.
What I do like about that that long thing is it's just I think it's probably a setup
for the joke of like Warwick Davis being inside of the clothes.
Him popping out is such a funny thing.
Right. That's such a weird.
It's the big it's that big tall costume.
And then like he's only fill in the pants.
Yeah.
So I like it's just for the joke, I think.
Sure. Yeah.
But when I like the casting, I love when I mean, it's nice to see him.
Yeah. Yeah.
And he says, like, I got to get over to Star Tours.
Right. They're just so in love with the inside.
I think they they feel like like people know the Disney MGM Studios world
and they're going to want us.
It's like the beginning of like self aware, sort of meta comedy almost happening
within the shows.
And it's very 90s like self aware meta comedy.
What I don't get is like if you have Nora done, why wouldn't you have her be like
a sassy witch?
Why wouldn't you have her be another actor?
Like why should I feel like she barely gets to do anything as the costumer?
She gets some funny physical.
SNL. Yeah.
She was my neighbor once and really Woodland Hill.
She lived down. I discovered while trick or treating.
She lived on my block.
No, I've done. Yeah.
Crazy. I don't think she does anymore.
So don't go. Hey, creeps.
Don't go looking for Nora.
Yeah.
Who else?
All of this.
Did you know all of these sequences directed by Peyton Reed?
He did this to. Yeah, he's done.
Yeah, he did a couple of different things for the part.
The back to the future stuff.
Yeah. And he was like the go to guy and the go to go for like,
you know, like filming like small size scenarios, whether it be shrinking
or just filming Warwick Davis.
Yep. Popping out of a costume.
Would have been doing the the UCB TV show around this time, too, I believe.
Yeah, sure.
And I didn't realize this.
Bob Gur worked on that train effect.
OK, that's because he's Mr.
Vehicle. Oh, yeah.
So that's the thing.
Like you I mean, it's legitimately shocking when it plows into the set.
And you have the question like, was this supposed?
I mean, you know, it's all in effect. Right.
Like, but then watching like the clockwork with which it goes backward
and resets and that stuff's fun when they show you.
And look, it's a it's going back to the place.
It's going to they're going to do this 20 more times a day.
Yeah, it's not his greatest.
No vehicle.
But it's in there.
I mean, a lot of talent went into this.
Yeah, it just maybe didn't come together.
In the way they had to.
I think they had a lot of ideas and it just didn't like
it feels like just like a flurry of notes and people wanting different things.
And we have to like we have to promote ABC and we have to promote
Steven Weber being in the family.
And yeah, there are too many cooks.
There is ironically within the world of order of too many cooks.
There is a fondness for it.
And as like I said, there was that sure I didn't even realize
there's a community where they sell those shirts about Stuntman Steve.
And I found a Facebook group about that, like how I found the Pleasure Island.
Yeah, yeah. There is a tribute Facebook group.
It's it's a, you know, a couple hundred strong,
but they are very much into this ride, this attraction.
Really? And they like post about it's pretty active.
Like I had to answer.
I had to answer like a pretty easy like Stuntman Steve question of like,
who are we yelling at through the megaphone?
And I wrote Stuntman Steve, because that's how you have to get
into these closed Facebook groups.
Oh, yeah. Thank God you didn't have to say like Nora Dunn's characters.
No, yeah, they don't want to.
I think you don't even say that you'd have to like zoom into her ID
badge or whatever to write.
But yeah, they just there'll be people post like, hey, remember how good this ride was?
And this traction was and people be like, amen, this is my favorite attraction.
You bring it back.
They should. Yeah, we should. Yep.
That's a lot. That's a very common thing.
Like the like rides ever come back basically.
And wait, wait, wait.
Yes, it never happens.
And like, why would it be this of all the things?
I don't know. But there's people that have a lot of affection for this.
I think a lot of people enjoy the humor.
They enjoy the comedy.
I like if like I noticed there were people posting about like
they like showing themselves like
like ringing the bell, like pull like pulling the crank.
Right. To do the like quiet on set.
Bell and that gag where they bring up like the bulky, you know,
the biggest guy in the audience and he can't do it.
They like lock it like the sword in the stone. Right.
But then the kid reaches up and does it easily.
And that's a good photo op.
That's like a thing that's really fun.
You don't want to remember. Yeah.
Which any if anybody has one of those, you know, send it to us.
But guess the ride.
For sure. Anything has to ring that bell.
If you have any of this material, if you guys in this attraction,
please send us those photos and any merch because there's so
lack of of old.
Not a lot. Yeah, I checked eBay.
There were photos on that Facebook group.
Apparently, when they took this down,
there was a small contingent, like 20 people who took the megaphones
and started yelling at the construction workers,
like to try to get them to stop.
It's crazy.
Which if you if the show you get to see union people
at work within the show, that should teach you.
It is not their fault. Right.
It's not.
There are photos of them at the fences with the megaphone,
the soundstage megaphones yelling at these construction workers.
Stop, stop. Save the ride.
But they had to cut and they would say like cut and print.
They would still use the terminology of directing.
Well, cut, stop.
Stop the take.
They're not using it correctly.
Right. They're just using it.
Yeah. But they did this.
Hey, asshole, print.
Yeah. For a couple of weeks, apparently, they were at they were at this
to try to save the ride.
But I hope they didn't like throw the cones.
I mean, they're wearing hard hats, so it's fine.
But yeah, they're not afraid of some.
And then they lose the cones.
That's dumb to like you should hold on to that thing,
especially knowing the ride is going to go away.
Right. Because I can't find any on eBay.
But they did like they kept the buildings intact because isn't this
what eventually became who wants to be a millionaire, which we just talked.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, of course.
I just like they kept the sound stages.
Yeah. But they were pulling stuff in.
And obviously that train effect was something you that was going to take
some construction, I think they had to widen the wall to get it out again.
Oh, they know they had to like clear a big path to you.
And then they had to take down the famous elephant doors,
not the elephant doors. Right. Yeah.
This is a thing on the Universal Tour, too, like the terminology like, oh, yeah.
You know, kids, do you know those aren't just called doors?
They're called elephant doors.
And it's glazed over one weird little Jason.
And like, I will remember this writing it
in your little notebook. Yeah.
Yeah. That was me for sure.
Yeah. But this is like the people not
caring anymore about how
stuff that you can and you feel you can feel it happening like with that,
that green screen, the presentation that like they lay out green screen
as if that's something you're totally unfamiliar with.
And of course, like a couple years down the line, you know, from DVD,
special features, green screen is everywhere.
And they totally shit that thing where Steve Stevens, like he's wearing a green
sweater. So when the peppers goes to 50 walks in front of it,
then you see him on the monitor and he his body disappears. Right.
And then he's and then he then he walks back and like, oh, sorry, lost my head there.
But like, yeah, also, and it's almost like the only thing he didn't lose
is his head. Yeah. Right.
It's actually the only thing that remained.
So the joke is doesn't quite work.
Has some issues. But I think mainly they I mean, they stopped doing
things like this, like the behind the scenes of the fake show.
Like, yeah, like maybe you'd be interested in how a real movie was made.
But here's our hypothetical sitcom you will never see.
And you could feel the audience going.
So when does when do we see the show?
Is this coming on ABC? Yeah.
Did you did you? This is unconfirmed.
But I read this is crazy. But I read that who wrote?
Did you read who wrote it? No.
Norman Lear. Norman Lear.
Yes. How can that?
That's why I said it's unconfirmed.
The Peyton Reed thing, I think you can confirm.
But like someone says that I don't think it's crazy.
I don't know. One of the message boards on WDW Magic.
And you go deep into the magic and the message boards.
Maybe just like, oh, Disney.
I don't know. Other information.
This is just somebody's claims that Norman Lear wrote the dialogue for this.
It seems insane.
But I guess I could see where it's like, oh, we were going to do like a classic
sitcom, so we want to have that type of pattern.
Obviously, I don't think he's done any other theme park work.
So this seems crazy. Like a consultant thing.
They like brought him down there. He wanted a free trip to Florida.
He gave one note and then was like, very seems right.
Seems possible.
Like if you give me the written by credit, I'll pretend to pay attention to it.
Right. Yeah.
They still have to give him a lot of money.
And yeah, they had to get him and his family.
He's like, oh, my grandkids want to go to Disney World.
Maybe the show is maybe order up is a like
was like a failed normally.
I would have his.
Yeah, maybe that's what they mean by like they like found like the one show of his
that didn't take off.
It's just a note, a sentence he wrote on the back of a Musso and Frank's receipt.
Like, I don't know, maybe something in a diner, a guy moves back from the big city.
Yeah.
More than other episodes of order up, if like we get it, we get a train
crashing through a wall in this one and a flash fire.
Like was this was it always a that seems like a season finale?
Yeah. I mean, so yeah, what was it?
Allie, if you destroyed the said right.
He was also what did you he was a lawyer?
Yeah, he was a lawyer.
And then he became a short order cook.
He came back to take over his family's diner.
Right. So he kind of was the manager and the cook.
And he was kind of doing a little every he grew up in the diner.
Right. So he knew how to run it.
Yeah. He knew how to do stuff.
I never get an actual scene of Stephen Webber on.
He's just like, here we are on the set.
And he tells you the back story. Right.
And then all you see is like the set come to life and the microwave door
opening and closing.
So you don't know what his character is like and how the show,
what the rest of the show would be if it existed.
I mean, my guess is that in the pilot, he's begrudging and then like
he's begrudgingly coming back and then something makes him glad he stayed.
Like the diner is rewarding.
You know what? Probably his high school sweetheart is like a teacher in the town.
And maybe they will finally get back together.
Unless they all of them get burnt in a grease fire,
who seemingly happens frequently in the.
You know, actually, I will also say I think that it's nice when they like
give the pyro like lever.
I mean, it's silly. They make it.
They they make it like you're setting off dynamite in the 30s cartoon,
but that they let the like the littlest girl in the audience like start the pyro.
Oh, sure. That's pretty cute.
That also if you had a video with that, I mean, that'd be great.
But like, I don't know, I'm just I'm worried for the lawyer and his and his new bride.
If I was if I was making it, I would make the season finale be
Steven Webber's ex comes back from the big city and tries to coax him back.
He tries to go to him back to the big city.
You can tell he's really thinking about it.
Like he really almost might do it.
And then the season premiere is the second part.
And he decides to stay in the town.
So it's like Jersey girl.
Yeah, kind of like a Jersey girl sort of thing.
And I do I think the ex girlfriend, the big city ex girlfriend
should be like Laura Flint Boyle or like who was in dogma.
Linda, if you're into Fiorentino, Fiorentino.
Yeah. Good casting. Yeah.
Thank you. Do you think you could procure work
in the industry by writing a spec of order up the
non-existent show from the briefly open attraction soundstage with Steven Webber?
I don't. It's kind of sort of a state the way people write, like, you know,
here's my like say by the bell spec or whatever like this.
This sort of like a hook to it in a way.
Yeah, it is like an interesting hook to it.
Yeah, I don't know. Yeah, we were taught all of order up.
There'd be like the one executive who would go, oh, my God, you're kidding me.
I think I would have even their better luck.
How uploading it and making it go viral than having it an actual sample
that an agent or manager like in the way that people write, like the Seinfeld 2000
score or whatever, like write a Seinfeld episode.
Also, I'm going to guess probably not a good thing to write a spec for,
because I know the show doesn't exist and there's no way of knowing order up.
Probably all white cast.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
If it was if it was 98. Yeah. Yeah.
But weren't all sitcoms right at the time.
No way of knowing. No way of knowing.
Sounds like Steven Weber.
I mean, do we do?
Do we agree with the Facebook group?
Do we want soundstage with Steven Weber to?
Well, look, I didn't see it as a kid or adult.
So I will never know exactly what the situation was or how the experience was.
So from just describing it,
maybe it doesn't sound so great and worthy of bringing back.
But maybe in the play pavilion, when you get to relive old rides,
maybe that's a place for it in Epcot.
Yeah. Once a month, you can go and see the show.
The VR in a VRE way.
It definitely I think it was one of the things I absorbed through osmosis
of like soaking in all of MGM Studio, like all the old signs and the old,
like, you know, lights, camera action, like Hollywood.
Here's the here's how it's made.
I think I did have an affection for all of that and probably pushed me
into the arms of the entertainment industry. Right.
Unforgiving in a way this helped in as much as like seven attractions all helped.
Yeah, they all kind of like meshed together.
Soundstage is the reason you live in Los Angeles.
Maybe I got to go see the real sound stages.
That's also that on the way in that you're in the lobby
and you were looking at framed photos of sound state, like famous sound stages.
Here's Pinewood and here's where they film Mary Poppins.
But sound stages are just building.
Right. I love them. I love sound stages, especially when they have a plaque
that says everything that's shot there.
I'll stop and read the plaque.
And I was like Conan.
I got to work like what was the white, you know, way Goonies was filmed in here.
Sure. It's like weird and fun to think about.
I mean, Robin on the Warner Brothers live. Yeah.
Oh, they must have taken it over.
So many things. So pretty much it'll be like gone with the wind.
We're going with something.
Casablanca, Batman, Robin.
Yeah, it's my favorite.
Ever used the famous Long Beach Dome.
Yes. The cruise ship terminal formerly home of the Spruce Goose.
Now the home of a pre-gaming carnival cruise
slide passengers.
It does.
So when I put that in the row of
some soundstage pictures, like because otherwise it's just you're looking at like
10 tan buildings.
It's like the like the GM plant and test track.
You're looking at a bunch of like industrial roads.
Like this was the peak era of like,
look, a road, a field, a warehouse.
Somebody claims on the Facebook group that you could buy those famous
little toys of those famous sound stages.
So you could buy a little Pinewood toy in a gift shop.
That probably stopped pretty quickly.
I would think.
Make your own penny type like they like molded out a little
build a toy so you could own Pinewood and you can own
and then all the official soundstage from Soundstage with Steven Weber.
You can own, you know, stage eight of that.
Warner Brothers were step by step was filmed.
Wow. Just so it was like the early.
Tea walked inside this miniature fake building.
There should be a Park Stars of the soundstage.
You know, I like park specific merch.
I know.
But would you love this?
Yeah.
I mean, it's pretty.
Oh, I would buy this.
It's pretty wonderfully.
I know.
I think from Soundstage, I own the soundstage.
Like also that the sign off of a pay.
Thanks for coming and I'll see you on the soundstage.
Right.
Little ones.
Why am I really?
Am I going to see Steven Weber on a soundstage?
No, that is not.
That's far from guaranteed.
Yeah.
Now you might.
I'd love to.
Oh, the especially after this, because now I'd be able to bring it up like,
yeah, I am a big Soundstage fan, though I just hope he doesn't listen to it
because we'll know I've said some derogatory things.
He seems cool.
He seems like he's so he did some funnier dying.
So I was going to ask if he ever came through there.
He did.
I forget what the he was in some.
He was in a video called shit.
My Republicans say, which was a very, very, very, very time a reference to the
Twitter and then like it's all also imagine what it would like watching a
video from 2012 of crazy Republican quotes, like whatever Santorum was saying.
Imagine how that compares to the pure batch.
It's the blood in soil.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Funny today.
Yeah.
You know, when you talk though about Steven Weber in.
Combining with theme parks, I think there is an opportunity to do it again,
which is, you know, NBC is sitting on the studio 60 property.
Yeah.
And there potentially is an opportunity to do a studio 60 attraction.
I'm not sure what I mean.
Like maybe the, I mean, if they ever wanted to refresh Spider-Man and replace
Spider-Man with peripheral vision, man could essentially be the same.
I mean, I think there's a good chance, not a good chance, an okay chance that
that for sure happens pretty likely.
Also seeing a, like a live, there's not enough shows at universal, seeing a live
daily depiction of the, I'm the very model of a modern network TV show.
I think you could just put it next to Falon's thing.
So you get a little street there.
Obviously that's New York, but it's confusing that NBC and I think it
isn't the other one NBS.
Yeah.
Yes.
NBC and NBS live next door to each other.
Late night lane.
That's what it is.
If, now if that, okay, now it look, if soundstage is all about tying shit
together, if you're on race through New York with Jimmy Fallon and then you
turn a corner and the villainous Jack Rudolph is like, Hey, NBC boy, let me,
let me give you a taste of the real New York and then tries to smack you.
Oh, sure.
Well then Jack Donaghy can save you.
Oh yeah.
Cause there'll be a 30 rock who was from that's what's confusing.
The 30 rock was on real NBC, but studio 60 was on NBS.
But 30 rock seems to be in a world where there is no SNL or TGS replaces SNL,
but studio 60 does exist in SNL universe.
Cause they'll say like, you know what aired at 1250 the first time Wayne's world.
Like Wayne's world is in that.
Oh, Wayne's world.
It's a, oh fuck.
Yeah.
I never thought about that.
But does the girly show exist within?
I don't, I believe, yeah, I don't believe SNL exists within the girl.
Yeah.
That's also just, yeah, studio 60 is accidentally bad.
Right.
The girly show, I think is like what the self-deprecating people who make SNL
think like, oh yeah, that's what we're doing with our lives.
Right.
Went to Harvard, but so did doctors, but we make this, you know, fart show.
Jokes.
Yeah.
Fart jokes.
Right.
But now is the chance to clarify a lot of the stuff that NBC and NBS tie together,
just like the imagination Institute merging.
Is that, was there, like, there's like an imagination Institute logo on the
the control, the control.
It's on the control.
Pointless world cross.
I like that.
I like it too though.
Yeah.
You know, I don't know.
Was this good?
Maybe this was good.
And maybe it was good.
I mean, if I get deeper into that Facebook group, they can convince, help
can convince me here.
I think there's more to it than sounds.
Danger.
I, is there red bubble merch for Sergeant Hobnob, whatever Drew Carey plays?
And there might be, I should look into that too.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, there's a, I do feel like there's a whole level of this, um, MGM
studios fandom too, maybe I'm not as plugged into cause I'm more plugged into
the Epcot stuff for the Tomorrowland stuff.
But yeah, I do think there's people for whom soundstage is a formative.
That's their Disney.
That's their thing.
Yeah.
Mm hmm.
Uh, so if you're one of those people, you hit the mother load with this episode and
I hope you enjoyed it.
Um, if we missed anything, please let us know.
Yeah.
Did us up because there's, as we discovered a lot going on in this attraction.
Um, but, uh, I don't know, email us, maybe we bring it back.
Maybe, um, maybe we got a petition.
We'll do a part two.
Yeah.
I'm interested.
I will say, and I didn't know this, there's a version of it in Disneyland
Paris, there was, there was, excuse me.
Oh yeah.
I didn't think when I was there, but it's the same thing.
Like a perfect thing to copy now, but was it real Steven Weber?
Was it the, like the French equivalent?
It was the French equivalent.
The French.
Yep.
But we can't, we don't have time to talk about that.
Pierre, whatever.
What an honor for a Frenchman to be officially called.
We consider you Francis Steven Weber.
Of course.
100%.
So the dream we'll get that.
We'll get there.
We will get there.
Who are Francis Scott, Mike and Jason doesn't exist.
Doesn't podcast the right Paris international spin-offs.
That's true.
I will.
We need to brand ourselves and start expanding, but only to the
countries that have Disney parks.
I am interested in that.
We will license our name out and there'll be three people that do our show.
And then we click 80% of the money they make.
Yes.
Jason.
Yeah.
I'm into that.
Okay.
Great.
The Euro is right now.
Sure.
Cash in.
All right.
In that case, if you're interested in being a podcast, the right
international franchisee, especially our guests in Hong Kong or Shanghai,
email us at podcast, the right at gmail.com.
Keep subscribing to the second gate for the more and well, hey, we'll hit them.
I will hit sounds dangerous.
We'll hit monster.
Sound.
Yeah.
We will hit the genre of on the way out behind the scenes rights, as much as you
want or don't want, so give us your feedback if you want to hear more.
Hey, thanks for listening.
We'll, we'll see you on the sound stage.
On the sound stage.
On the sound.
It was on the set.
We'll see you on or around the sound stage.