Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
where your Star Trek adventure continues.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Mike Carlson
and Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
And yes, we are here now to,
if you can imagine there's more Star Trek to talk about
besides the Incredible Vegas experience,
but this isn't the experience, this is the adventure.
The adventure.
But also the adventure is what the Hollywood one was called,
Universal Studios Hollywood.
In Florida, what was it, it was technically really called,
it was part of the Screen Test Home Video Adventure.
Right.
Yes, brought to you by JVC or MCA.
I mean all of them probably.
All of them.
JVC sounds right, I mean MCA owned the parks.
Yeah, it was a parent company.
JVC was presumably showing off videotape technology.
But then also we're talking about
King's Dominion thing too.
This is just catch all other trick shit.
Yes.
Yeah.
So my experience with Star Trek in the parks
is mainly, I alluded to on the full length episode,
was at King's Dominion.
Now King's Dominion, we talked a little bit
about their history.
Came up a little on Kings Island, kind of a sister park.
So King's Dominion in Virginia,
growing up my family would go there occasionally.
And for a long time, the company that owned them
also had owned or had the license
for the Hanna Barbera characters.
So Yogi Bears walking around Scooby Doo.
We go to Yogi Bears Cave.
Flintstone, Huckleberry, Hound picture.
You had to get your picture with them.
Then in the early 90s, Paramount, the movie studio,
bought them and formed Paramount parks.
So then you would see things like,
here is a Wayne's World themed roller coaster.
You'd see Sumner Redstone walking around grabbing butts.
You'd see Sumner in his diaper walking around.
He would have his diaper with the hole for his boner.
The kids area, it's still a little bit
of Richard Scarry's busy town.
But then there's also a Nickelodeon water park
where you're gonna get wet.
That's another episode eventually
is all of the Nickelodeon bullshit.
Some of which was in the Star Trek adventure in LA.
The same space got used for something called
totally Nickelodeon down the road.
Lots of extraneous Nickelodeon crap.
Lots of stuff.
So when Paramount got in there,
there would be Star Trek aliens, crew members,
just walking around you could get your pictures with.
But my big thing, and this was a thing
that I think I've alluded to on the past on the show.
And at certain points I was like, did I just imagine this?
But sure enough, if you Google Star Trek on ice,
it's not a full show.
But there was a show called Paramount on ice.
And three quarters of it really reminds me
of the Simpsons gag, Hooray for Everything.
Like the upbeat variety show that's really about nothing.
There was a Super Bowl halftime show
where the alien lands and sings rock around the clock.
So this is ice skaters.
This is the era of the ice capades
and figure skating is getting very big.
So this is just like, it's an ice show.
It's in an indoor theater, people ice skating
to tunes of music from movies.
You gotta have danger zone with Top Gun, right?
Sure, of course.
That's a Paramount.
Like a foam jet fighter costume fit over their body.
Well, but that's the thing.
They're mostly in generic, like ice capade kind of costumes.
I think the most one was Dirty Dancing is the one,
or no, what's the one with the chair
where she dances with the single chair?
Flash dance with maniac?
There's a chair, someone's skating around the chair.
Around the chair.
And then at the end of the show, they skate to Footloose,
Grease Lightning, I think they skate to at some point.
But then about halfway through the show,
there is a Star Trek segment where people in Starfleet
crew member uniforms start skating around.
Oh.
I'm gonna put this on the TV real quick.
Yeah, pull it up on the TV.
Because I actually have not seen this clip.
Do you have any?
It's like part three.
This is a Star Trek The Next Generation on ice.
Yeah, that's good.
So now it's a lot of very exciting Star Trek music,
but, and there's some spaceships.
There's too much fog.
You can't see anything.
They're playing a theme from Star Trek The Next Generation.
Uh-huh.
There's crew members skating around.
Circles.
The show seemed to do it, like Circles was the big move.
Yeah. Yeah.
And the background is not anything
that looks like Star Trek to me.
It looks more like the Emperor's
of the Royal Room in Star Wars.
It looks like you're looking at the Death Star.
The crew are not known for big kicks on the series.
High kicks.
Here they, I mean, every crew's different.
Every crew's different.
Right.
So maybe, yeah, there wasn't.
Now it's going to get pitch black.
And there's going to be some,
what I think are supposed to be aliens doing wire work.
Whoa.
And then occasionally skating.
These Dayglow costumes don't really show up well
on like ancient VHS.
On some guy's video
that he didn't know would be the only document.
Yeah.
So there you can see they're kind of being,
they're kind of skating.
I mean, they are skating.
But then like there's wires.
And they're flying.
Now they're getting flying.
And their outfits kind of look like
if you drew the human nervous system
on like the Night Man jumpsuit from.
If you put radioactive.
The Day Man, Night Man from It's Always Sunny outfit.
I'm going to finish.
If you put radioactive dye in someone
and then scan them with an x-ray.
So this was just a little segment from the show.
A little segment.
And then the crew members come back, they skate more.
There's no real aliens besides the wire work people.
Right.
And there wasn't a big,
not much of a narrative in this show.
Not really much of a narrative.
They're doing.
Kind of skate towards each other in point.
Yeah.
The complex dynamics and inter alien politics
of the series not conveyed here.
But like. Yeah.
Everything out.
I mean, I guess there's like a mall shop.
A fake mall shop sort of flat
that they skate in front of for grease light thing.
Like, but they spent all of their money on this show.
On this segment.
Yeah.
They got a days of thunder car and skated near it.
I wonder.
Well, there, yeah, there was that days of thunder.
That was the simula.
That was the big like show.
The big simulator show was, was days of thunder.
And then a Pierce Brosnan and James Bond thing,
which I never rode.
I'm so mad.
I always wanted to ride it.
And then there was like Stanley presents the superheroes.
Like one of the many Stanley invents another universe
kind of thing.
Mm hmm.
This, this, I'm, this is underwhelming.
This show.
Yeah, it's pretty underwhelming.
It's got the most dynamic music.
And then we're seeing that the crew is like unified.
They're working together and making shapes together.
Yeah.
And not.
And then the wire work aliens come back.
I will say that theme from Star Trek,
the motion picture that's playing is fantastic.
Yeah.
It's really great.
It's not John Williams, but it's very Williams-esque
from that era of Superman and all those great big scores.
So you can see it a little better.
They kind of look like big butterfly sorts of things.
Mike, do these look like any Star Trek aliens that you?
I don't know what that, no, it looks like.
It looks like the Spitter from Jurassic Park.
Yes, it looks like the Dilapis.
So whatever it's called, Dilapis.
So one thing you could say about this ice show
is that they own a CD you like.
Besides that.
Yeah.
Not a lot of.
That's it.
Nice work.
Anyway, that was the anti-climactic.
Star Trek on ice.
So that was my memory of Star Trek.
I saw that.
Yeah, I would have seen that.
Probably around that time,
there was a couple summers in a row,
we went to Kings Dominion and then over to.
Didn't audition for it.
Didn't consider being part of it.
No, no, if only.
Man.
If only.
I got that lower leg strength up.
I don't think I've ever ice skated in my life.
I was gonna say, you didn't.
My mom made me take ice skating lessons at like 12.
What?
Yeah, she was like, you're gonna need to know how to do it
cause you're gonna have parties
where you'll have to ice skate.
And then I was in a class with like,
my sister's only three years younger,
but when you're like 12, that feels like
I'm way older than my sister.
So I was in like a beginner's class
with a bunch of young kids.
And I felt like a real loser.
Yeah, that's kind of more fun.
I guess I was.
That's because you were.
Yeah, and I honestly, I think there was only one other
ice skating party I ever was invited to.
So.
I went to a, I went to an ice skating thing
with a school group where I had like the walker essentially.
Like, so you know, just like a pipe that I am teetering on.
And then I did one lap of that
and then didn't wanna do anymore.
And then I was ended up sitting just with a mom,
somebody's mom who was a cool mom
who could see that I needed help
and was a kid who needed to know what was cool and stuff.
And then a song came on at the ice rink
and she was like, oh, this is like a good new cool song.
You should know about this.
It's this band Soul Asylum.
It's called Runaway Train.
Wow.
I think you'd like it, Scott.
Yeah, I think I do like it.
And then I think all the kids came back from skating
and I probably immediately like,
hey, so you guys like Soul Asylum?
They ignore me, keep going to pizza.
But I've always appreciated that mom trying to help me out.
And she's right, knowledge of Soul Asylum
is as crucial today as ice skating is for you.
Wow.
We've all had a lot of great experiences
at an ice skating arena.
What do you call it?
An ice skating rink.
Rink.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna say that your mom going,
you gotta know how to ice skate
might be one of the weirdest things you have ever said.
Really?
I don't know why that's so strange to me.
Your mom being insistent on this.
You're gonna have to know how to line dance.
You're gonna have to know, yeah, there'll be parties.
Yeah.
Is there, I'm trying to think, I guess,
I went to a couple roller skating parties.
Roller skating was more common and occasionally bowling,
but at a certain point in time,
we got sick of the bowling alley.
Oh, we had a lot of bowling.
We had a lot of bowling.
That's where the Ninja Turtle arcade was.
Yeah, all of these places had big arcades
and I was much more interested in that and the snack bar.
I was always scared that I would like
slice my own neck with my skate.
Yes, yeah, I'm afraid of that.
I was worried that that was gonna happen.
And anytime I'm watching ice skating,
there's a blade there.
They're gonna slice themselves open.
But it's most likely to happen if you're very good.
That's where a leg would get kicked up near a neck.
Yeah. Yes.
But the blade is gonna fly off the boot.
It is alarming.
It seems very scary to me.
It's a blade.
Yeah. Yeah.
True.
And it's just, people just do this all the time.
My sister, I skated as a little kid.
She did a couple of those shows.
There was a racket, essentially.
This is actually probably a good episode down the line.
There was a place called Santa's Village
and right next to it was the Polar Dome.
And it was in a ring.
It was a big rink and they taught lessons.
And they had, maybe my sister let us use the video.
They would basically, there was a big recital essentially
for all the classes and the show was just,
it lasted four hours.
You were sitting in this rink watching just kids.
There would be a couple features of kids
that were better than the other kids,
but mostly it was just like,
let's throw 28 year olds out onto the ice
and they'll make some formations and then play the music
and get them out of there.
All right, another round of eight year olds, got it.
And then they would sell you like a $30 VHS of it.
Oh, and I had to sit through a few of these as a kid.
If you like $30 VHS,
you're gonna love the main topic of today's show.
That's exactly what we're talking about.
That's the exact price.
It is.
Yeah.
It's so, that is so much.
For the early 90s?
For the early 90s.
My God.
I mean, I was reading a thing,
I don't know if it was Attractions Magazine.
Someone just had an article
about different theme park VHS tapes.
Both Disney's run of sending out VHS vacation planning tapes,
but then also the souvenir ones
of like a day at the Magic Kingdom
or the Universal Studios one hosted by that old man.
Joe John Forsythe.
And they did Hollywood and Florida.
Movies are the wizard's wand
with which cinema magic is made.
I mean, we gotta watch those.
Oh, we'll find a way to piece those.
Those are some of my favorite things.
Yeah, and the Disney ones that are like a fake home video,
sometimes following up a fake family.
Yeah.
Like so that they can capture it
as if you had a nice camera,
which you presumably don't.
And Universal very briefly,
when they first opened that second park,
had like two or three years
where they had vacation planning DVDs.
Didn't last long.
Yeah, I think now it's probably just all digital,
I'd imagine.
But yes, so this is both experiences we're talking about.
There's one in Hollywood and one in Florida,
and both of them devoted ultimately to selling you
a $30 VHS in which you are a star of Star Trek.
From the Hollywood one,
which opened in 1988, official literature.
At each performance,
members of the audience are selected to join.
Captain Kirk and Mr. Spock in battling Klingons,
fantastic space creatures and alien super beings.
Then only minutes later,
you see these scenes videotaped and edited
into actual Star Trek footage.
You may go in a spectator and come out a star.
And we'll clarify the difference between the two.
And I wasn't even clear until the last couple of days,
but there was a similar,
you make a video in Orlando and you're in Star Trek.
But in that one, it's a blue screen thing
and it's an experience only for you and your group,
but you get a tape at the end of it.
The Hollywood one was a show in a theater.
And even if you weren't participating,
you could watch this sort of like,
here's how TV shows are made kind of show.
It was in the theater, which became totally Nickelodeon.
It became some Flintstones thing.
And then for many years was the immortal,
the eternal Shrek 4D.
Yeah.
So this was, yeah, it's a combo.
It was a live show, but probably the main attraction,
you could be picked and be in it and be on one stage.
Like a superstar television.
Physical sets.
Yeah.
Good looking physical sets.
In fact, one of them, there is something that fans
were very excited because the bridge in this one is the,
you explained this already,
something about the Enterprise D or the Enterprise C.
The difference between the enterprises.
Yeah, usually when the bridge is replicated,
it's not usually this one.
Oh, okay.
Huh.
I'm trying to think, cause they, there were two versions.
So the 60s show was the enterprise was just the enterprise,
USS Enterprise.
And then in the movies, they like re-create,
they christened a new ship, which was the NC 1701A.
It's funny it's NC 17, but that's part of it.
Isn't that what it, I mean.
I mean, it's just funny that the film rating is in there.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Naughty film rating that used by show girls.
Oh, is this your dirty mind?
Who's in this crew?
Gaspar No?
Oh, it's N, wait, you know what?
It's NCC 1701.
Oh, okay.
You're missing a C.
But that's pretty close.
And we got this, so then let's issue a correction.
I gotta edit the other one out.
You gotta edit some Cs into the other episode,
but it's too late, unless you do it right now.
So yeah, it's ship recreation.
There's a recreation of, I'd say, the main enterprise,
then you're on some Klingon ship.
And there's the, what is the official name of this?
It's the holodeck.
Yeah.
There is a, probably then the main way
that they advertised it, and the thing I remember
from watching it as a kid, I watched it,
but did not participate.
Too scared for that.
You get to watch audience members disappear live.
On the holodeck, and it's really well done.
I watch videos where it gets a round of applause,
and deservedly so, and thus, at the end,
you watch everything put together, right?
And some of which is like, here's a computer you've shot,
and in this case, they film a live effect,
and it happens right in front of you,
and they commit that to tape, and it looks really nice.
I believe it was a Pepper's Ghost sort of thing,
but it's the same technology that enables
the Haunted Mansion ghosts, and the many great holograms,
the hologram USA, the jewel of Hollywood Boulevard.
The greatest hologram experience ever.
Yeah, so it did seem like that was fun.
I'm trying to figure out, that does seem like-
That was one of Erin's favorite things as a kid,
going, I don't know if she was ever in it,
but she loved that Star Trek show.
It was a lot of fun.
You cover, the sets are really great looking,
you get to see clueless, dopey families
bumble around a Star Trek set.
I think there's a lot of comedy in,
oh, the lines are bad, or here's the part
where there's turbulence, and everybody falls this way,
and falls that way, and they have to explain,
well, it'd look better if you all fell the same way,
here, follow my hand, and it still doesn't work right.
Right.
So it's, I think it was legitimately fun,
and there weren't a lot of shows like this.
Did this predate, I guess it did,
this predated superstar television.
Is that right, 88? Yeah.
Yeah, 88. The next year,
a similar thing opened at Disney and James Studios,
where you're in the chocolate scene, and I love Lucy.
Right. Now, some big things that set this part.
One, there was no original footage shot for that.
They used existing footage
from the Star Trek motion pictures.
Yes. And two,
when they cut the inserts in, you can watch,
there's a few different families
have uploaded their videos to YouTube.
A lot, really.
The Hollywood one, the end product looks like shit.
It looks awful.
The Florida one, seemingly cheaper when you're there,
looks much smoother when they cut the footage in,
and has some great original footage,
original shot with.
The one they cast. The cast,
which we'll get to that, so.
Because in the Hollywood one,
in the Orlando one, they shot a bunch of video.
You're on video, and George Takei's on video.
Then the Hollywood one, you're looking at,
you're combining 35 millimeter film with.
That's true. Like a live variety show
you're filming in a theater.
But it's awfully charming.
The blend is a lot of fun. It's charming, yeah, yeah.
I'm sure these videos are fun to pull out,
and say, hey, send them our way if you have them.
I have not a longer clip, but I started,
I was like, do I try to find some moments
to play of this thing, but there's too many families.
It's impossible to pull apart too many moments.
Dozens of people have posted these on YouTube.
They're a lot of fun.
But there's this one part that struck me funny, especially,
where, okay, so there's the main crew,
and then there's a Klingon problem.
I don't know what's going on.
But then you're introduced to a group of Klingons.
And again, these are all volunteers from the audience.
I think all told, there are 30 or so opportunities
for audience members to be up on stage in the show.
Some are in uniforms, and some are in Klingon foreheads.
Not very good makeup, but you gotta just
throw them on in five minutes.
We're not talking Corvath. Corvath? Corvath?
Corvath. Corvath.
We're not talking Corvath level quality.
No, just tell them it's stripped on.
Did I read, they had to audition to be the Klingons
with your roar?
Yeah, you had to have the roar.
And that's how they would choose the Klingons?
Oh, that's fun.
I don't remember how it worked.
There's also, they made up a little piece of mythology
just for this show.
Let me find it.
But that's probably the funnest part is when,
okay, here's a bunch of Klingons all roaring,
the main thing you're called upon to do,
and reaching for the camera,
and then they also have a pet,
and the pet is played by a little kid
who couldn't handle a line,
but they can handle wearing a funny costume.
So a kid is brought on as a puppy lizard,
which is a Klingon pet described as a cute,
the combo of dragon and dog,
so in all these videos, you're watching this weird little
dragon guy ride around.
He doesn't quite merge with the Klingon world,
but it's very cute.
And then,
what's supposed to happen is an assistant,
like a lower ranking officer or something,
says in Klingonese,
I mean, I don't remember,
it's something about the enterprises try to contact you,
and then the leader is supposed to rip their arm
out of their socket.
And in only half of the videos did I see this work.
But then the main Klingon says,
I mean, it's in Klingon,
but he says essentially fire at them.
And all of the fire at them,
it was just all like especially,
it's definitely the comedy of dads.
It's definitely like dress him up, he's confused,
he's not gonna know how to do this.
And really quickly this morning,
I compiled a bunch of fire at them,
and I'll put this up on Twitter or something,
and apologies to all of the families that are watching.
And apologies to all of the families
that I stole this from,
but hopefully it's fun.
Here's a taste of that.
Luchane limboja!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
Luchane limboja!
And they start to get worse as we go.
Limboja?
No!
My lime blimboja!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Limboja!
Luchane limboja!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Limboja!
Luchane limboja!
Ha ha ha ha ha,
können!
Lin pain Kevin!
Wow.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Luchane limboja!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
I like that one.
That's number one.
Yeah, there's some good ones in there.
Luchane blababla!
Kabbalah!
Blazin' off!
Blah!
I really enjoyed all...
Luchane limboja.
I'll try to keep that in my head.
I finally know some Klingon.
It's not as good as...
Well, it is Sivako or any of the Navi language, but it's close.
Well, that's a word of kindness.
Luchane limboja is a line of war, and now we know it, should we end up in a space war.
So I'll throw that up on the Twitter.
A lot of fun dads, and at one point, like, cool guy who keeps his sunglasses on, like, under the forehead part.
That's funny.
So, you know, they get to do that.
I think everybody ends up, like, tied up in tentacles.
I think the Klingons get attacked by some alien.
And then there's a part where a bunch of, like, psychic brain creatures all speak with their hands.
Did you guys catch that?
Oh, yeah.
And they explain...
They were showing that, I don't know, they could get along.
Yeah, it was that, like, everything you just witnessed was a simulation, and it was to see if the species could get along, and if...
I don't remember if we passed or not.
Yeah, that's exciting.
I assume yes.
Yeah, hopefully.
They're kind of in that zone of the Clint Howard kid.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
The big head.
Oh, right, because the Starfleet crew members save the Klingons at one point, and then at another point, the Klingons save.
Because the Klingons wanted them to.
There's literally, like, murder us.
We have been dishonored by needing help.
There's, yeah.
And then they even the playing field by saving them.
That character appears, or one of the characters appears in the art for this, which I loved.
Did you come across, like, the promotional art?
Yeah, that art is great.
Really good paintings.
Yeah, I'm putting it up on the screen.
This one is just so good.
Oh, yes, those, like, those creepy holographic Spock and Kirk.
Yeah.
Those it's the brain creature.
Yes.
And one where Kirk and Spock are reversed.
Yeah, I see that.
I have that too.
Like two variations of it.
It's but everything underneath looks similar ish.
Yeah.
One thing I think is interesting.
The promotional stuff for this is refers to it as the Universal Studios tour as opposed to Universal Studios Hollywood.
Oh, gotcha.
I don't know when that shift happened, but you do see before, like, the park got built out a lot more than them pushing leading with the tour.
Yeah.
Well, I think it was sort of in the process of happening.
Yes.
And this is one of the first things that you could get out.
You might not know Universal Studios was initially just the tram and there'd be stops and you'd get out at the prop plaza or you do this little show.
But it was not a you don't walk into an entrance like Disneyland and you're in a theme park and the tour is one of the rides.
It was all tour.
So this thing was one of the first the Star Trek experience was one of the first things on the upper lot.
And this was opened along with you know, when you walk around Universal, there's all those like no attraction areas like the Moulin Rouge and Sherlock Holmes is London.
Right.
And all that stuff.
That was all supposed to be that was open with a lot of fanfare.
It was called the Streets of the World and there will be like it's as if these are back lot sets that we could use and they have been used in things.
But you can actually get out and walk around them and shop and go to restaurants.
So this is so Star Trek was part of like this initial early expansion, this open right after earthquake, which was one of their big, you know, also an early attempt at doing Disney caliber experiences in the T2 location.
Right.
I believe with this thing or no, no, no, Star Trek.
No, Star Trek was in what became the Dreamworks Theater and Shrek 40.
What was it?
Did it?
What was it in Florida?
Where was T2?
Was there some T2 connection with it?
Well, it's all there's a guy named Phil Hedema who headed the thing up and who yeah, the Hedema Group's a big themed entertainment company.
He's a guy who became a major figure in T2 3D, but he could like cut his teeth on this.
Also part of this, Gary Goddard.
Gary Goddard.
Fuck you motherfucker.
And he actually Gary Goddard apparently was brought in to tighten the experience up and get it down to like 25 minutes or so.
Because according to the Disney versus Universal book, the first time they opened this and got it on its feet, the entire experience ran an hour and 10 minutes.
Geez.
And when it was done, only 10% of the audience was left.
It was a disaster.
They ended up streamlining it and all of them.
You know, that's the thing.
It is very impressive that this was I don't know how the editing technology worked to where like all these things are going to happen live on stage and then you'll watch it all down in a six minute reel immediately after.
But it was not nearly as tight when it opened.
It was kind of a disaster.
So it needed a lot of retooling, but ended up being a very popular thing.
Ran until 1994 when it was replaced by a Flintstones show where they ride a big pterodactyl around inside the theater.
I remember that being very impressive.
Great.
You saw that live.
I saw that.
That was a lot of fun.
I loved live action Flintstones a lot to a degree that I probably couldn't justify today.
Movie?
Yeah.
Movies?
I loved the Flintstones.
Not movie.
I remember it by Viva Rock Vegas point.
But no, come on.
That's baby stuff.
I don't know.
Flintstones 94.
That is a adult drama about money laundering and fraud.
Colin McLaughlin.
Yes, very adult star.
But Viva Rock Vegas sends up one of your favorite vacation destinations.
That's a good point.
I should check it out for that reason.
I have this very specific memory of really wanting a sequel to the Flintstones and it kind of took too long.
By the time it got announced and there was going to be a prequel, you're like, oh, so it's not Goodman?
The big thing that they touted in the press release of Viva Rock Vegas, well, because we're going to Las Vegas and we're kind of simulating neon,
that we're going to be using some different types of rocks.
That was in the newspaper.
I read that.
I remember thinking.
You remember it.
Yes.
It really sticks with me that they thought that was a bragging point.
Little did you know, fake rocks would be such a thing down the line.
It would eventually be the most meaningful thing in my life.
I had, I think, a similar experience, but the timeline a little different.
Like when Rocky and Bowinkle Nickelodeon got the rights to air the old Rocky and Bowinkle cartoons, and I just remember going, wow, they're showing it on Nickelodeon and Nick at night.
That's cool.
Because it was like a prime.
It used to be a prime time.
What cartoon could work for both sides of the line?
For both.
That's wild.
And then shortly thereafter, maybe a few years after, was the live action Rocky and Bowinkle.
And I went in like with high hopes.
Really?
Because I remember the Tom and Jerry movie where they talk.
Right.
Which now that sounds weird.
That's years prior?
Yeah, there's years between those two movies.
But I was like, well, they did a good job with the Tom and Jerry movie.
I bet to do a good job with Rocky and Bowinkle.
What year was Tom and Jerry?
It's like 94, 95?
Yeah, 90.
It sounded like that.
And Rocky and Bowinkle is 2000?
Was it 2000?
I feel like I was heading towards adolescence by Rocky and Bowinkle, but I remembered like, well, I love the cartoons.
Tom and Jerry 92.
Wow.
And then that Rocky and Bowinkle movie.
I mean, there's one or two fun.
I mean, it's funny to see Renee Russo and Robert De Niro.
So I'm curious, eight years apart, you were remembering the Tom and Jerry movie?
Yeah.
Well, and I think they were like, look, it's Rocky and Bowinkle in their own movie with these movie stars in it.
Like, I think I was just like, this could be really fun.
And I think I remember walking out of it going like that wasn't that fun.
The only blotch in Robert De Niro's otherwise perfect career.
Yes.
Flintstones.
What's funny about Flintstones?
We saw it in the theater and I liked it.
But of course, like maybe Batman Forever and I guess Batman Returns, I remember the McDonald's promotion.
Yes.
So it was so large in my brain for that.
So like I almost like the McDonald's promotional campaign for the Flintstones movie more than I like the movie itself.
I had a very exciting moment where I won the ultimate honor for my kind of kid.
Lunch with a teacher.
I got to go to McDonald's with one of my teachers.
Thus, a bonus visit beyond when my parents would take me, thus opening up me getting one of the other houses that was available.
Like, so probably I had, I don't know, who else's house could you get?
Did I end up with a house of the in-law, Elizabeth Taylor, the mother-in-law?
Maybe.
I got Mrs. Slag Hoople's condo.
Well, how did you get to McDonald's?
Did the teacher drive you in her car?
I think maybe.
I think I was driven around by a teacher.
My school, like my school district had specific, like, teachers cannot drive students in their personal car for any number of liability reasons.
And as it should be, keep in mind I grew up in California where the rules are loose.
Yeah.
I mean, that would be a pain in the ass if like, there would be times in the summer, like this local summer community theater, like directors, if like parents couldn't make it or like we're running late, the staff who ran it would be like, I'll just drop you off, get in the car, fine.
Sure.
But they didn't have the school district, you know.
I reason that it wasn't weird because, you know, to some extent the teacher is a friend of my mom's, therefore not a stranger.
So because she was a friend of your mom's, is that why you got it or was it because you earned it?
I think, now if I'm remembering correctly, this is a, my mom ended up becoming a teacher at the school and this particular teacher is still a family friend to this day, so that might have, I don't, now I know what you're thinking, how did I get that, student of the month?
I think this is the beginning of the relationship between my family and this teacher.
I don't think the wheels were greased.
Because of your academics.
Yes.
Your exemplary performance.
That was what kicked it off, but then my, that fun time at McDonald's must have really, that's really where the relationship became special.
Did you tell this teacher about soul asylum?
So I recently learned of, this, soul asylum may have been after my lunch with the teacher.
I might have been telling the cool mom about what a nice day I had having lunch with a teacher and about how much I love the different types of rocks in the Flintstones movie.
And she might have said, I better teach Scott about a rock band or two.
So this is, this was a reward at your school that you got to eat lunch.
Keep hanging out with a teacher beyond school hours.
Did you get to pick whatever you wanted off the menu?
I believe so.
Okay.
If she had suddenly been, I don't know, maybe there was a price limit.
I mean, maybe I couldn't have said 100 hamburgers.
Although now I wish I had.
My grades were very good.
And you were excited to go just to talk to the teacher one on one or just to get to go to McDonald's and order whatever you wanted.
I mean, McDonald's and during Flintstone times, keep in mind they were all RockDonald's.
Yes, of course.
Knowing that RockDonald's was a temporary thing.
I really wanted to be at RockDonald's, but yes, I love to learn.
I love getting very good grades.
And I threw my probably until high school, I could list a lot of teachers who I like had.
I like had relationships with beyond the school.
That sounds really, that sounds terrible.
I always got along with adults very well.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Where you like see them out somewhere and like we actually connect.
I learned how to make small talk very young.
I got along with adults too.
Okay.
But how many were you friends with?
We all probably share this.
Yes.
I think so.
I think it's a trait that I would call wienerism.
Yes.
I like I like for instance, I started my middle school and I thought that it was going to help me out socially that I coming into middle school was like that.
My mom was friends with the principal.
I was like, I'll be the most popular kid in school because I know Mrs.
Hunter, a lady who wore big moomoo's and had a giant had giant helmet hair and it didn't help.
It ended up not helping.
I hate to say so.
Then it was a desperate bout of shouting soul asylum to everyone in earshot and it never went my way.
I convinced when there was there was a few different Marvel Comics promotions at Pizza Hut over the years, one of which it was like for four or five weeks.
There was a new comic you could get exclusively a pizza at every week.
And one of those weeks was a half day of school week because that was when they would do parent teacher conference.
He would just go for the half day and then the afternoon the parents would come in do parent teacher conference.
And so I convinced I I like sold it to a friend like well, I remember where I'm coming over to hang out that one day like we're hanging out that one day.
You know, there's a pizza hut down the road from your house and we both want these comic books.
He I think he was like, yeah, you're right.
And he got like convinced his mom to take us to Pizza Hut.
Was it a buffet?
I don't know. We did the but I think we just just did the personal pans.
Oh, personal pans. Yeah.
The personal pans is that the kid's menu was the pan, the soda.
That's what you would get for the book program.
Yes. Yeah.
There was a lot of tie in.
We must have all had our reward for book related activities was personal pan pizzas.
And I used to write comic books down on my list because I was such a bad reader and still am.
Yeah, me too.
Bad reader.
Well, yeah, all that promising that promising academic career got flushed down the toilet.
There's something with my attention span.
I think that's the problem.
Now you look very prolific as comic book page counts are just getting cut.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Sometimes it's too much for me now.
But all of the look how much we all learn for all of these episodes information that helps us with nothing.
Yeah.
Day to day it helps us with the boring certain people at parties.
Yeah, for sure.
But when during these records, that's when that's our time.
It's very fitting.
We've got all our nerdy childhood neuroses out on the Star Trek episode.
I think you on this on you mean on the second Star Trek episode, the less good one, the less good one.
So yeah, so Hollywood.
Yeah, this one was a show.
This one had sets.
Did you get both of them were the same in that you had to buy the edited VHS?
I'm guessing it was an upcharge experience.
Yes.
And but your name was in the credits.
I mean, think about that.
That's true.
That they do Chiron.
Seeing your name on your TV and impossible feed at that time.
Well, now, so I yeah, I'm not surprised they charge for the VHS.
But wouldn't you want to be like, well, you're in the show.
It's ten dollars.
Like, wouldn't wouldn't be nominal fee like I mean, thirty dollars.
Theme park.
I know.
But but they used to when they would do shows, they would charge for the VHS.
They would give you a ticket.
They would give you like, thank you for helping us.
Here's a free and it was a free soda or free ice cream or something.
Yeah, that's what the people who do the animal actors, the kids who do animal,
I get a little certificate or something.
But it's a good lesson to learn that like congratulations, you made it as an actor.
And also now you will pay all of these surcharges and union fees and manager agent fees.
And I got those headshots that's going to cost you money.
And the real is going to kind of those classes you took.
That's all going to cost you.
Sure. Yes.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
Sorry. I was going to the kids who with the one that Harry Potter where it's like,
you're the special boy.
You've been chosen.
Here's the one.
By the way, make your mother pay sixty dollars for it.
Yeah.
The most special ones are the most expensive.
Yes.
I don't know.
So there's valuable lessons.
That's why Star Wars.
That's why Galaxy's Edge has a payday loan center in it to cover those insane lightsabers that they're selling.
There's a Unkar Plutz check cashing business.
You're going to owe money to like a bounty hunter is going to come to you at your home outside of Galaxy's Edge.
Yeah. Yeah.
You have to kill a grito.
Pay your debt.
Pay in blood.
I mean, that's pretty much all I have on the Hollywood one.
And so as we said, there's not even like a pre video.
There's nothing.
This is a fun thing and the sets are cool, but you don't get the presence of the actors.
Yes.
Other than in pre recorded clips.
But in Orlando in 91 when this opened a little after the park opened custom material from the entire original cast.
Yeah.
Crazy.
I don't know why you wouldn't do this first for the first one.
Yeah, I don't know.
It seems like I mean maybe they were maybe they might have been harder to get in a way they were still making the movies.
Although also they're like around and on Star Trek sets.
Right.
That's what I'm a little bit confused by why they didn't have any sense.
But this one, of course, and I think we've had a couple of episodes where we love things hosted by people that aren't the best on camera.
Yeah, this is incredible.
I didn't realize it had this.
Yeah.
And this is what I found a couple of months ago and I was like, Oh my God, thank.
Oh, this is the greatest.
Gene Roddenberry, creator of Star Trek, who he says you may know me as the creators.
What else am I going to know you for?
Right.
I don't know.
I'm related to you.
Well, it seems like you might know him for seeming like he's about to break down in tears as he's recording this because fall over or fall over.
I've never seen a man more nervous to be on camera.
The kids in the Star Trek shows, which there are some kids with real shitty grins on their faces the entire time they're doing these Star Trek shows.
So I will just play maybe the whole Gene Roddenberry intro because it's fantastic.
Hello and welcome to Universal Studios Star Trek Adventure.
Courtesy of Paramount Pictures.
I'm Gene Roddenberry and some of you may know me as the creator of Star Trek.
The episode you're about to see is a first.
It's the first time guest stars have ever played the roles of the captain of the enterprise and the Vulcan science officer.
We'll now give you a peek at the rehearsal session that went on between our guest stars and their two directors, William Chandler and Leonard Nimoy.
And you get a little boom mic dip at the end of that.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He there's some punch in.
And I don't know this is when this was in what?
Ninety one.
I hope Gene wasn't like sick and we're goofing on him or something.
But there's there's punch ins on him and he looks like a deer in the headlights.
Like he looks like, oh, you found me.
Like he's so scared.
I don't know why they made him do this.
Keep in mind, this is going to be your this is being shown in a regional upcharge experience at a theme park in central Florida.
So, you know, dozens of people are going to see you here.
Oh, I freak out.
I freak out, Gene, possibly affected, afflicted with cerebral vascular disease and encephalopathy as a result of his longstanding use of recreational legal and illicit drugs, including.
Oh, so you're saying it's fine that we goofed on him now because he was taking drugs.
It's like a bad man.
Cocaine meth.
What?
Meth.
He did meth.
Gene Rundberg did meth.
Oh, it's quite loose.
Sorry.
It's the baby.
All right.
That's fine.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, he did die in 91.
Very nervous on camera.
We're goofing on him now.
And now we look like shit heads.
So good job.
That's behind the buying the paywall.
We haven't proven how good we are from our pleasant teacher hangs.
But don't put them on camera then.
Yeah.
He had a stroke in 89.
Oh, so like this is stroke.
Alcohol and drugs have just destroyed his health and then he had a stroke.
Oh, don't put them on.
Yeah.
It's their fault.
Not ours.
Universal's fault.
Get somebody dude with presence like John Forsythe movies on a wizard's wand or bringing
Hannah and Barbara.
Oh, yeah.
True to this as well.
We haven't been making Star Trek for over 40 years.
We sure ain't.
We got nothing to do with it.
Oh, we go get a sandwich.
Did they do the Star Trek animated show?
Oh, I don't know.
It was a short lived Star Trek.
I watched a lot.
We don't know.
We weren't paying attention.
We don't.
We probably did it.
We hate being in the same room with each other.
This is a comp.
What you're watching right now.
Joseph filmed two weeks ago.
I sure did.
Is that one take too?
No, no, it is.
Okay.
This punches in on him and it's like clearly like maybe days later.
Close up.
And then what he introduces is a directing session in which there is the family.
So, you're the family.
You and your family went in to make this video and you're sitting on some director's chairs
and on either side of you, current modern day, filmed for this Leonard Nimoy and William
Shatner.
This is, this is everything I want to play.
Yeah, I'll play it.
That's very good.
Is the key.
You must let the audience know that you are the captain of the ship.
The trick is to remove all traces of emotion from your performance.
Vulcan's actions are dictated by pure logic.
And remember, the captain is the most important role in the story.
The captain?
The Vulcan?
Come on Leonard, it's the captain that makes things happen.
It's his story.
Bill, get serious.
The audience watches the Vulcan.
Stop.
This victory is pointless.
It is most illogical.
Not bad.
I'd say they're ready.
What about you, Leonard?
Indeed.
I think it's time to boldly go where no man has gone before.
So in case you didn't know, those are the family members chiming in.
Yeah, like as if they were ad libbing.
And you'll see the video.
And then my favorite, one of my favorite parts is that Leonard and Bill, Bill
Shatner put their hands on the hands of the people sitting behind them.
The family is just overlapping.
Before you do a performance, you really want a director to touch your hand.
Yes.
It's so weird.
Just ominously going backwards and their hands hovering.
And also in that whole video, they are looking nowhere near the guests.
The eye lines are way off.
They have very thick blue screen lines around them.
Just harsh shadows.
And then when it cuts to singles, they're in an entirely different room.
The color is so different.
Leonard's close up is the color of the wall is it may as well be two different locations.
They probably weren't filmed together.
Yeah, I don't think so.
Yeah.
They hated each other at this point.
They probably hated each other.
They made up, but then they hated each other when Leonard died, I think as well.
Oh, no.
It's really something that's really delightful.
And that's all they could get them to do.
The rest of the grunts though, all had to go.
They showed up.
Yeah, they showed up.
And I got to say they're doing the work.
They definitely are.
Yeah.
I'm confused a little by, I think I've, oh wait, is it DeForest or is it, Walter Koenig is?
Chekhov.
He's Chekhov.
Which one doesn't have an accent?
He's doing the Wessel.
Well, Scotty is the engineer.
He has an accent.
That's Doohan.
James Doohan.
And then Chekhov has an accent.
Sulu sounds like George.
And then Nichelle obviously is Uhura.
Who's DeForest Kelly?
DeForest Kelly is Bones, the medical officer.
He's the main guy in the footage.
Okay, yeah.
So he's the old crusty guy.
He's a little man.
Yeah, but maybe that's the character too.
Yes, he is the character.
He's over it.
Like his character is sort of like crusty and over it in general.
And I think he was in real life and obviously you have to do this.
I'm sure he was like, oh, what is this shit?
Yeah, you're filming an interactive theme park video.
I believe they filmed this on the set of the other one.
Like the Hollywoods, Universal had the Hollywood set.
So they used that and shipped this over to Florida.
Because it's a smaller, it's not the real set.
It's a smaller scale version of it.
And as we said, a lot more video-ish.
Yes.
Like you were watching, this is like a PBS Star Trek.
Right.
Made in 1976.
But I like McCoy yelling at the family members.
And you know what?
They do need a more firm directing hand because some of them are really
phoning in their performances.
It is.
Often, yeah.
This one, the first one that pops up and we'll link to it,
the video I was playing from, is I think the best one I've seen.
That's like the primary, the first one that comes up.
Their performances are so funny.
It's like a, it's a mom and a kid.
It's a mom and a kid and a dad.
The mom at the Vulcan's pretty good.
Yeah.
But I think that's the kid who's a little too like pleased with himself.
Because of it, it's just so, it's the delay because of the way that they have to do this.
So there's like a nice couple seconds before anyone reacts to anyone else.
So there's this odd feeling in the videos.
Did you guys find you had this for a long time though, starting to act in things?
If a camera's on you, you're smiling like an idiot and you don't even know you're doing it.
Yeah.
That was like the big thing.
I, now that I'm an actor really, but like when I corrected that, I was like, oh yeah, shit.
Every time I've ever had any type of camera on me, I just have that like, huh, hey, look, I'm being filmed right now.
I think some, there's some people who never lose it.
Yeah.
I think that that's, yeah.
One of the big things is people don't realize when the camera's on you, what weird, maybe it's not smiling necessarily, but it is something.
There's some weird reaction.
Cause I took a, when I took a commercial acting class, like eight years ago, the first time I was on camera, I yawned.
Like I, I like kind of like looked strange.
Like I was making a weird face.
I wasn't smiling, but I looked strange.
And then I yawned on camera.
Whoa.
And I didn't even know I did it.
Huh.
Like it was very odd.
Wow.
Like you're just, I think it does something when you're like, feel like you're being watched.
I think you have some little ticky thing.
You have a ticky weird thing that happens and it's different for everyone.
And then you have to like know that you just keep your face like neutral for the most part.
And then if you're doing commercial where you generally with commercials, like you don't even have any lines.
So you just have to like look in the distance and be like, Hmm, like a neutral face.
And that leads about right for most things.
And you haven't, so you don't in most commercials end up having to ice skate.
No.
It did not come up.
It's not.
I have one of these days.
Do you have it on your special skills?
No, that's true.
I don't.
I've had to hang glide and stunt drive.
Oh yeah.
You've had.
I've had a couple.
That's some weird ones.
Oh yeah.
Very weird.
Yeah.
Um, uh, stillness.
I think, uh, Philip Seymour Hoffman had a quote once about like, Oh, you can tell really.
I think it was him had like, yeah.
Yeah.
Pros like when you look at them on camera or like in between, they're still, they're not
fidgeting.
They're not.
That's the, yeah.
That's the one thing I think is a younger person.
I thought it was like, you want to feel like you're giving a lot of effort.
You're like, I'm performing.
So I here we go.
I'm going to do a lot with my hands.
That's a real amateur thing.
It's like, I'm going to really react to it.
Cause she's like, I have to make it feel like something.
And it's like, no, do not do that ticks as possible.
Yeah.
I guess we can't hold these Florida families to, we should, um, they should have listened
to Mr. Shatner and Mr. Neem.
Those are two big directors.
That's better than any of us had coming up.
Three men and a baby.
Yeah.
And body wars and Star Trek five.
That's one of the boringest Shatner, the worst Star Trek movie Shatner directed five is,
but Nimoy directed four.
And Nimoy directed three and four most difficult one at Wales.
Four is fantastic.
Uh, yes.
And he made that sexy lady photo book.
Yes.
He had all this photo book.
He took pictures of sexy ladies.
Oh, he was a photographer.
He was a photographer.
Everyone loved him.
I mean, except his son and he, they reconciled.
There's a documentary about it.
Oh good.
But everything else, he, you know, Nimoy, when there's Star Trek cartoon rolled around,
they tried to cut out like you hurrah and check off or like ensue.
Like they just get different voice actors for cheap and not the real actors.
And Nimoy said, no way.
If you don't have me, you don't do, we don't, if you don't, you don't get me.
If we don't do everybody.
Wow.
And everything like Shatner was not because Shatner very famously, huge asshole on the
sets.
Uh, they've stories about him like going and changing people's lines and closeups.
Like you'd see him go off with the director and then it would be like, all right, you
know, the setup is actually going to be over here and it's going to be on Mr. Shatner and
it's not going to be on Sulu.
And then like him just complaining about like photo shoots where he wasn't like featured
as heavily.
Did they also not get a lot of residuals from the original series?
Isn't there a story about that?
That's a good question.
I'm probably not.
When did the original series in around for like five seats?
No, no, no.
Less.
Less?
Yeah.
Because that's the other two or two and a half ish.
One of the press kits for this, these attractions was like from the very popular TV show.
And I'm like, was it?
I don't know that it was.
I think once it hit them.
No.
They started making multiple movies.
I feel like the movies did well if they kept making them.
And the only reason the movies happened is because of Star Wars.
Oh, yeah.
Because Paramount was like, oh shit.
Okay.
We got one.
What do we have?
Oh, well, we have a star in the title.
Okay.
We'll just do the stars.
We'll do that.
Yeah.
And then, yeah, that's how that reignited it.
I mean, next generation came after both of these attractions or around the same time.
When did that start?
Well, that's in like 87.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
I believe, unless I'm...
Hmm.
I really like the Shatner's advice of you must let the audience know that you are the
captain of the ship.
That's, hmm.
That seems like an understatement.
It seems like you have to do more than that.
Yeah, I know.
This is a much, a very simplified version of advice.
I would take that advice if I were in this video and just right before every line, I
am the captain.
And then, then the line.
Just keep reminding you.
And if I have like a name tag that says captain, just keep pointing to it over and over again.
Man, I wish this...
I'm the captain, Seth the Phaser's...
They don't have enough experiences like this anymore at parks.
Because I would do that now.
We should do that now if it existed.
I was trying to see, could we find this blank and then insert ourselves into it?
Oh, yeah.
That's such a great idea.
I couldn't do it.
If anyone...
Here's one of those like weird source things.
If anyone has, for some reason, the blank video.
The elements.
Have you guys been noticing this YouTube channel, Cow Missing, that is posting all of this source
video like the Muppet Vision, the three monitors all lined up.
Oh, yeah.
Or the Captain E. O'Pree show, but not filmed off a TV in good quality.
So if for some reason this Star Trek take home video thing exists without any people
in it and we could put ourselves in it.
Oh, man.
I was trying to think how do we culminate this episode into something, but we can't
do that.
You guys are both very tech savvy, Scott, you especially.
I would say someone I saw online was plugging those videos like, oh, yeah, look at all
this stuff up here.
If you like them, hunt them down.
If you really like them, rip them off that video because this website, this user could
get banned.
Oh, yeah, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I've done a lot of...
Yes.
Well, look, I was ripping many family's videos today for that thing earlier.
Sure.
Yeah, no.
Well, certain theme park things.
But now I think it's out there enough.
There was this Captain EO work print that now has multiple, but I was like, this might
be gone today.
I need to grab this.
It's fantastic.
And you find out that EO was knighted.
That's important information.
Oh, right.
Yeah, yeah.
Not in the film.
He goes down on one knee and the sword is taken to his shoulders and head.
Oh, yeah.
Very important.
So he's Sir EO by the end.
Unacknowledged mostly.
Anyway, so what we're describing then, after all this intro from Gene Roddenberry, intro
like a little coaching from the directors, then you and your family get to be the stars
of a Star Trek story that is custom filmed.
All of the other actors are in it.
And it's a weird little tale where you end up beamed onto a Klingon ship and you're like
right next to them.
That was the part that jumped out of me that there's a part where a Klingon is saying to
a little kid like I'm going to kill him.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
And a little kid pulls out like essentially a grenade.
Yes.
Right.
But it's not real.
No, it's not real.
It's a Star Trek.
We fooled them with logic.
The dialogue.
Yeah.
The dialogue is somebody says, what about the photon detonator?
And the kid says, it's not real.
It's a gag gift from a friend.
Gag gift?
In the 23rd century.
But what was that supposed to be?
How are you going to you start going and you go into school and you say, hey, look, a bomb
and the schools shut down for the day.
This was well, this is the military, though.
Also maybe things are supposedly very peaceful on earth in the 23rd and 24th century.
So maybe they're everyone could be darker with their sense of humor.
I don't know.
Perhaps.
But this was one of two experiences you could have that the full name I found was screen
test home video adventure presented by JVC.
And the other is called Your Day at Universal Studios.
So got to hunt that down because I'm very interested in what that is.
I've seen that maybe on this same YouTube channel, in fact, or like Inside Universal
or one of the others.
But you can watch that being done by families and you can also watch it being done by Laurel
and Hardy.
Like the characters in the costumes do it to demonstrate how it works.
Right.
And yeah, you get you know what happens in it.
I don't know.
I walk around Hollywood Boulevard.
The real things you do.
Yeah.
But this is clearly the superior one because you spend 30 bucks and you get custom footage
of the forest.
Kelly.
Yeah.
You're kidding me.
Forrest Kelly was talking to me.
He was Kurt to me.
I don't have much to say about the actual thing.
I mean, the videos are a lot of fun.
I mean, yeah, you have to watch the videos to get because we could play clips, but it's
like so it's so specific to watching this family.
You have to see this family because there's so family that you had where the kid says,
I mean, mostly they keep it together pretty good, but there's one part where he says like,
OK, we're being over be beaming over.
That's a lot of fun.
Fantastic.
Do you find this to be a compelling story?
Yeah.
Hey, I was just ranking my Star Wars.
Where does this beat any of the films?
Yeah.
Beat Star Trek five for sure.
Star Trek five.
Well, technically, Shatner directed this too.
That's a good point.
Victory for him.
Star Trek five.
Those Star Trek five is so bad.
It kind of does come around the world a little bit into being good.
Like this.
The movie starts off with the three men, the Trinity of Star Trek, Shatner, Nimoy and De
Forest Kelly in like a national park singing campfire songs.
And then like they're like mountain climbing again.
They're like very old already at this point.
And they're like climbing and then like Spock Falls.
And then he like has like rocket boots and he shoots up like it's such a bizarre.
That's lucky.
I was going to say now that I think about it, it's maybe the best five is actually really
good.
Oh, wow.
You would like it in a dramatic turn.
Five's number five.
Actually, now number one.
This is better than.
One is very boring.
Star Trek 10 is bad too, with Tom Hardy and Picard.
Tom Hardy is like a young clone of Picard.
And it's like kind of unpleasant and it's like not a great send off for the cast.
So let's say Nemesis.
Yeah, Nemesis. Thank you.
And so let's say this one is better than 10 and one and tied with five.
Wow. So the Star Trek home video and it probably depends on the cast too.
Yes, that's true.
The tank said, but this main family that you like.
I wonder if do you think there was like a like a bunch of good actor?
Like people have been like, we're fucking good actors.
Let's roll in there and we're going to show all these families like we're going to have
the best Star Trek tape.
Like, could there be one with like famous actors, in fact?
Hmm. Oh, maybe they practiced at home or before, like before they were famous.
Have to be somebody.
Do you think anyone got discovered off of this?
I mean, it's possible.
Yeah. I mean, we don't know.
We didn't. Joseph Gordon Levitt is for he got all his early success.
This got him third rock.
Yeah. Yeah. They sent a tape of this and he was cast.
Yeah. He said beaming over without any stumble.
There's I was going to say Adam Scott, but I realized I was going to say that
because Adam Scott is in Star Trek First Contact as a crew member.
Oh, really? Like years before he would make a bold burst onto the scene and step
brothers. Boy Meets World.
Tork. Oh, and Tork.
Yeah. Don't forget Tork.
Yeah, that's the main thing. I wish we could do this.
I wish we could still go into that blue screen room.
Jason, I thought of you because the you know, this thing, this this room
where you stood in a square in front of a blue wall was replaced by the Islands
of Adventure preview center, which I don't know if you got to do it.
But you must have been over by King Kong or the mummy.
Right. It was OK.
All right. That's I remember the preview center being in that part of the park.
I thought this was more by like the fake
Gardens of Allah or whatever the fake apartment building.
Oh, I don't know. The fake like, huh?
No, I'm curious.
We should do close to New York in my head.
OK, yeah, that that's where the preview center was.
I have that very clearly in my.
This like when they do like I went to a WrestleMania like,
I guess it was like 22, whatever was in Chicago and they let you call a match.
And it was free at the time, too.
I'm sure they charge for something like that now.
But but that's like I'm trying to think of there's any other equivalent
of something like that.
Does anybody have some make their own music video that we talked about this?
Yes. I mean, that's what I maybe we should do an episode,
maybe main feed episode of the best of all of these different types
of video attractions or something. Sure.
And we ask call for the listeners to send in their best ones. Sure.
And then I will upload
the one of my mother and I at MGM Studios.
I'll tease it. Yeah.
Golden grail or the yeah, the tape is over in is over there.
I have it. Yeah. Wow.
The room I need. I don't have it.
Well, we have digitized maybe back in Chomberg, but I need to digitize it here.
So, yeah, that'll be that's a big that's a big one.
You're saying we're devoting an episode to make your music video booths
where like, you know, two kids don't touch instruments
while Gloria Estefan's one, two, three, four plays.
That is what I'm saying.
But there's got to be there's others.
There's other versions of these types of rides,
but it's the few and far between these days.
Well, because anybody on your phone.
So, yeah, you can just put yourself in it.
Why would that photo booth technology you can put yourself in ancient Rome?
You know, hey, you can look like you got
bluebirds buzzing around your head or you can,
you know, switch your gender in a Snapchat filter
from the comfort of your own home.
Yeah. But what you can't do is make a custom movie with George Takei.
Yeah, I mean, that's
there should be like a Fast and the Furious version of this,
where they have all the actors with a new narrative and they plug in.
They charge it now. What's inflation?
Eighty dollars. I think it would be around $80.
Yeah. Isn't that this one's almost weirder to me that to even do the experience
you're paying that money. Yeah.
You're already in Universal Florida and now there's this upcharge. Right.
But if you're a big fan, you get to wear the outfits that too.
That's an undiscussed aspect of both of these things. Yeah.
You're wearing like, I guess not fitted, but you're wearing like vaguely. Yeah.
Your size. Star Trek uniforms. Right.
That's you ever worn a Star Trek uniform?
I isn't I have not. Oh, wait.
No, I did a comedy show and I was Spock once. Mm hmm.
And I did one where I was Riker, but I wore like a robe. Mm hmm.
As in that one.
So I've worn like an approximation, but not an official.
I've never also been to a Star Trek convention, which I want to go to the big
one in Vegas. They have a big one in Vegas every year. Oh, so I would like to go.
Why do they do that? Or why do I want to go?
Why do you want to go? Because because I like all that bullshit.
Uh huh. I want to go. I want to go take a look and see what's going on. Sure.
I want to see every single person that's ever been on a Star Trek who go to this.
You are all there. You are all there.
Yes, it was over by the mummy who was in that area.
That was all I've been looking at. You've been distant for four minutes.
Trying to figure out where it was.
And yeah, that's where this was.
And that's where the preview center was.
Friends of adventure.
And then I found someone posted a video walkthrough of the Islands of Adventure
Preview Center.
And that's all I'm going to be able to think about for the rest of the day.
Geez. Well, we'll have to do a Patreon on that.
On that video.
On just that video.
But no, I want to I want Mike to meet all his Star Trek friends.
I want him to go to this thing.
Yeah. Reginald, the guy who played Barkley.
Reginald Barkley, the nervous crew member on Star Trek Next Generation.
You can host some panels.
Oh, I'd love to host some panels.
Please. That's true.
We should all be hosting a lot of panels.
You could do like a roast of Jonathan Freaks.
Oh my God. You could like emcee the Roaster Jonathan Freaks.
That is a dream of mine.
They do roasts or you just proposing that happens.
I'm pitching that.
I think that's a great idea.
I would love to roast Jonathan Freaks.
Make jokes about how big his dick is.
Yeah. I would also be kissing his ass.
Yeah. Yeah.
This guy is so charitable.
Let me tell you that you at some point were like,
I would like him to play my father.
Well, I pitched a show a few years ago where he would be my father.
Yeah. So and who did everyone want to be Jason's father?
Well, I've said I've there's two people, right?
Was it one of the Wala Sean?
You had an idea for something and I thought for ages, you would said
Matt Walsh and I was like, yeah, I like Matt Walsh.
He's great. And you were like, no, I said Wala Sean.
And I had to go like, oh, OK.
That's a very specific choice.
But that is very funny.
I would love to be acting.
It would be an honor to to act opposite Wala Sean.
And this show would be played in exclusively in retirement communities.
In Mike's living room.
A 70 and over only show.
It's about two older men in a retirement community.
One is the son, but they're the same age somehow.
Whoa, whoa. My dinner with Andre is way too exciting.
Let's slow this bad boy down.
I discussion of where the keys are.
We saw Lindsay and I and a friend of the show, Ryan Perez,
saw Wala Sean play directed by Andre Gregory, his co-star in
My Dinner with Andre and sitting behind us for the Star Trek
connection, Armand Shimmerman, who plays Quark, Quark, who was a
who they played Ferengi's him and Wallace played Ferengi's.
Oh, that's yeah. Wow.
And so he went to see his friend.
He is. I thought I was thrilled.
We were like, I was running for I was like, oh, my God.
That's wasn't it also one of their birthdays?
It was Andre's birthday. Yeah.
And we walked out into the lobby because it was at the Red Cat,
which is a smaller theater downtown.
We walked out in the lobby and we were like, it was the opening night of it.
And it was a short run.
But people were sort of congregating.
And then Wallace and Andre were out.
And all of a sudden we realized we were in the middle of Andre's birthday
celebration and there was a cake and people started singing Happy Birthday.
And then we were like, oh, shit, like we're we thought it was just like
people milling about after the show.
But I think it was like friends of theirs.
So we were like, I don't know.
And then we were like, should we if we get cake, would it be bad?
Probably would be bad. We shouldn't get cake.
We thought about it for a second.
And then Perez almost did it.
And then he decided not to do it.
And then he instead, he just went up to the two of them
and just said he likes them a lot.
So that was fun. And that was a cue.
And he was like waiting to like.
And then he does a very good Andre impression, which I cannot approximate right now.
But man, did I ever tell you about the time
we suddenly ended up at Wallace Shawn's birthday?
Let me tell you, we were so polite.
We thought about taking some of his cake, but we didn't
because we would have been in play.
We didn't know. Yeah.
We imagined so hard we would take his cake and then we stopped
imagining that because I felt too guilty about even having the vision.
I would take a slice of cake.
Oh, I know. Yeah.
Well, that's why that's the kind of like dynamic that why you need to be in a sitcom.
Yeah. Yeah.
I was also in the bathroom line with Armin Shimmerman.
So there's that, too.
You peed near Armin Shimmerman near him.
Wow. So excited to pee near him.
Great.
That's not the peak of Star Trek fandom.
Yeah. I know what is.
Thanks for checking out more Star Trek on the on the second gate.
Do we miss anything? Is there any?
I mean, we got to the ice show.
Yeah, I don't know.
Please let us know if there was some Star Trek thing.
We have not experienced internationally.
That could be true.
Well, I think one of these things, I think maybe Borg.
The Borg was at a museum.
Was it something in Germany?
I believe.
So if you went to Borg 40 in Bremen, Germany, let us know how it was different.
Yeah. And let us know which Star Trek cast member you'd like to pee near.
And email that to us at podcast the ride.
Or I don't know.
How much do I really want to get these? Yeah, I don't know.
Well, I mean, I'll give you another answer for me, at least.
John Delancey, who played Q in many of the different shows and played.
He was that guy who killed himself on Breaking Bad in season two or three
because of his daughter going in a plane crash on Trek.
OK. So anyway, he I'd love to pee.
He makes very pithy comments on the show, and I imagine he would be very
entertaining while he was peeing.
Who would have the best pee material?
OK. All right.
Well, I don't know.
I don't have to give any more instructions.
We could just end these.
Yeah, let's do it.
One more Star Trek sign off.
What's another one?
Oh, well, what do we do last we did?
We did Live Long and Prosper.
And you said Make It So, which was Picard's thing.
Let's see, was that anything else?
Keep on Trekking is what that one character said.
Keep on Trekking, everybody.