Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains billowing steam,
hard steel rails, a teetering bridge on the verge of collapse,
choo-choos, and a look at the Disneyland Railroad
with guest Mark Rennie.
All aboard, it's Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast,
where two of the three hosts have taken a special
photo shoot on the Disneyland Railroad.
I'm Mike Carlson, joining me as always,
my photo shoot buddy, Jason Sheridan.
I, yeah, that's me.
Scott Gertner is our other co-host,
he has a really weird look on his face,
disgusted I might say.
I don't know to what you refer.
Tell me about your special time.
Well, it was my birthday.
This is a true story.
Let's bring our guest actually real quick
so he can make fun of us too.
Our guest, a co-host of the Fantasy Flix League podcast
and a writer for Gay of Thrones,
which is returning soon, Mark Rennie.
Hello.
Hi Mark. Hi Mark, thanks for being here.
Thank you for having, I'm thrilled to be here.
Wonderful, so good to have you.
Yeah, thank you for making time to talk about trains today.
Love trains.
Yeah, we all do, I think, love trains,
but so back to this story real quick.
It was Jason's birthday, and we went with our friend,
Aaron, to Disneyland, and I learned of a trick,
and I don't know if it's still the way
to get something like this done.
Is you go up to a photographer
that's not somebody with a tripod,
and you ask them, are they inspired?
That's what it said on micechat.com,
which also sounds like a pick up of some kind,
or like a code.
It sounds like cafe gratitude stuff.
I don't know what you.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No.
I feel like I've heard you say,
are you inspired, upwards of 30 times at this point?
Yes.
And it's always the same, it's the pause,
and then so much wonder when you say it.
You say it so, are you inspired?
I think you love this.
If you put a little zhuzh on it,
then the photographers are more likely to go like,
oh right, I have to do this thing once a week.
Not just a spit, are you inspired?
Yeah.
Hey, you inspired?
Hey, dummy.
I should do with that.
Don't say it with an F word.
Hey, hey, hey you.
You inspired?
So what happens when you.
So what happens or happened,
I've only done this like twice,
is that if they are indeed someone who roams
as a photographer in Disneyland,
they will give you a little bit of a photo shoot somewhere,
maybe in a special place that they don't normally do this.
This happened to Lindsay and I
for the first time at California Adventure.
I tried it out, we were on like the main,
whatever you'd call it, street.
Is it Sunset, what is it?
It's the street.
Buena Vista Street.
Buena Vista Street, there you go.
Sure.
And the person I said, are you inspired to,
and she kind of honestly internalized a sigh.
Oh.
And it was like, all right, come over here.
And then proceeded to take photos of Lindsay and I
like peeking around the corner of the shops.
And it was honestly. Wow.
Honestly, too much.
She kept, like we did like 10 different spots.
Like your engagement photos or something.
Yes it was.
We were caught way off guard.
I just thought it would be fun,
like oh, we'll get to go up in a little spot
on the like Carthay Circle or whatever.
Not the case.
We did like 10 different spots all along the street.
And by the end we were like, what happened?
What just happened to us?
Get up on this lamp post, twirl around, claim it.
She didn't, other than stuff that wouldn't be dangerous,
she was saying like commanding us to do stuff.
All right, you over here, hands on her hips, do that.
Like, and just kind of shouting stuff.
And she was nice, but it was clear she was like,
all right, here, we're gonna give you
all the stuff you want, here you go.
So we were honestly, we're like, oh, that was too much.
Okay.
So what did we do when Jason's birthday ran around
or came around?
We were with our friend Aaron.
Lindsay was not there.
Probably was still freaked out from the other experience.
And I went up to a photographer.
By the way, the Disneyland Railroad was shut down
at this point. Shut down.
Because they were doing all the work for Star Wars land.
Yeah, so the trains were parked
at the New Orleans Square Station.
Or at least one of them was.
So there were two photographers, they were walking around
and I went up to one of them.
I asked if they were inspired.
They gave me some like fake banter of like they weren't.
And then one of them kind of was just like,
all right, I'll take this.
Oh god.
Wow.
Put out her cigarette.
So I, and I think I tried to stress, I go,
if there's, you know, it's Jason's birthday.
I go, if there's just like one fun spot or something,
I go, it doesn't need to be long.
It doesn't need to be a whole thing.
And she's like, no, I got it.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
She led us to the train that was parked
over in the New Orleans Square Station.
And we went inside and did a series of photos.
Like our heads out the window.
In the passenger car, in the locomotive.
Like the three of us like stacked,
like peeking out of the locomotive.
Like Jason climbing the ladder on the back of the train.
Yeah.
And then like snuck us into the back
of like the haunted mansion.
The haunted mansion, yeah,
like the little mausoleum crypt kind of thing.
By the mausoleum.
Whoa.
So we have so many pictures of this day.
Did you pay for these photos?
No. No payment.
So you had free photos.
Yes, I mean I have photos on a train.
Photo pass, so it would be free.
But there's no, cause there's no way
to exchange money with a photographer in Disney.
I would feel the need to tip.
Like honestly I should have one.
But I'm sure you're not allowed to.
You probably could.
What's the Disney general thing about tipping?
I feel like they wouldn't take a tip.
Yeah.
Well the guides take tips.
They do.
The guides and the table service waiters.
But yeah.
Oh waiters, photographers.
They told us as a universal tram tour guide,
which I was, they explicitly told us not to accept them.
But one guy offered me a 20 once
and another guy offered me a beer once.
What are you supposed to do?
You better believe I took both of those.
Yeah.
Did he have a loose beer in his hand?
It was closed.
Oh okay.
And it wasn't like, you know,
yeah it wasn't like draft.
It wasn't an open container.
He just like had a bunch in his pockets
and like hey, here's, and it was like,
it was like a cold day too.
So like a warm pocket beer.
And work.
Now what's the doctor already?
What you got in trouble for was leaning out of the tram
when it was parked at the station
and drinking it like above your head,
like Steve Austin does pouring the beer
like a foot above your head.
And then crushing it.
And crushing it.
Yeah.
By a forehead.
Whipping it at a customer.
Yeah.
And yelling at everyone on the tram,
you're mine now bitches.
Wow.
One beer does that to you, huh?
Yeah, you're real lightweight.
I'm a lightweight, what can I say?
Yeah, so we'll post some of these photos.
But anyway, Jason and I had a special little photo shoot.
Mark, have you had any fun shoots on a train?
Doesn't have to be Disneyland.
Shoots on a train?
My parents, well you went to the,
it wasn't a photo shoot,
but the first thing came to mind,
my parents, we were well,
I was like 16, my parents were like,
we're going to the Grand Canyon for vacation.
Like great.
But we took a train, like a fun train,
and then like it got, the train stopped,
and we got robbed.
Oh.
Like when Bandit showed up,
but my brother and I, we were like,
I was like 15 and he was like 17, 18.
And we were like, this is lame.
We were like not in the mood,
because like it was all children,
except for us and my parents.
So it didn't feel cool.
Right.
The only age is that age range where that,
you think all the theme park stuff is lame,
and then you grow out of it.
Yeah, you know, you get over yourself.
Yeah.
So there is, we were talking about how I've never seen
like the Grand Canyon, Mount Rushmore,
all these famous things,
but you're saying there is some sort of themed.
There was some sort of, I don't know where we got,
cause we arrived at the Grand Canyon on this old timey train.
Like it looked like something out of like the old west.
Interesting.
So now I'm- Where do you take that from, I wonder?
I have no idea.
I was like, I wasn't paying attention.
I was busy being bitter.
Yeah, yeah.
Right.
You're on your- This is the same trip when the-
CD plate, you're on a Walkman.
Well also, this was when the Jeffrey Dahmer story broke.
So like on that vacation,
I was like dying for like that week's People Magazine.
So every time we stopped in like a drug store or anything,
I was looking for this People Magazine,
cause I wanted to know everything about Jeffrey Dahmer.
Wow.
And then also- If he was fighting in the Grand Canyon.
Maybe.
There's a bunch of drums down there.
And then also, Divinals, I Touched Myself was big.
What a trip we had.
What a specific.
Yeah, I don't know why I remember that.
I remember hearing that song in the car with my parents
when like, I just want to read my Jeffrey Dahmer magazine.
There is weird, songs do stick out of my head
on like family vacations.
Like when I went to Disney World, by the way,
by the Red Hot Chili Peppers was in heavy rotation.
And I just remember hearing it.
In your brain, you mean?
Yeah, sure.
I'm just saying I can remember certain songs
are like burned into like trips.
It's weird.
Yeah.
I remember going to grad night at Disneyland
and hearing ushers, yeah, constantly.
And I was like, hell no, not at my Disneyland.
Cause you don't want modern hip hop hits.
Cause they play one ain't you?
I want shit like the Grand Canyon,
that dopey music that's supposed to play.
Some ragtime.
Yeah.
I once took a, I was a junior high,
a friend of mine was in this church group
and I lived in San Jose and like, oh, we were going down.
I went along on their Disneyland trip
and we took a late night bus ride.
So like I left at like 10 at night.
We arrived at like six in the morning, whatever,
but someone had a boom box and they played MC Hammers,
please hammer, don't hurt him.
But the entire time the CD was on repeat.
So we heard it seven hours.
So that's what I said.
She fell asleep, but the boom box was still playing.
Wow.
Oh no.
The entire bus ride.
And also like, all right, you got, you can't touch this.
You may have got that prey song,
it's samples when doves cry.
Yeah.
The rest of the album.
Pretty forgettable.
Yeah. I would have to think.
I, I, I'm not sure I've ever heard another.
I was fond of too legit to quit.
Cause you got three hits.
You got Adam's groove to the,
the titular to be legit to quit.
And this is the way we roll.
We roll.
But first record kind of just a delivery mechanism
for the single.
Absolutely.
Calling out.
Ouch.
I think I can take much more of this.
I remember a trip to Orlando where in heavy rotation
were California Dreamin and Life is a Highway.
The original Life is a Highway.
I think because the one was in rotation at Mills
at Universal and the other was in rotation
of like the area soundtracks of the Hard Rock Hotel.
I thought.
And I just heard those a lot.
I was hoping that you were revealing
that you were really like 65 years old
and California Dreamin was sort of like on the radio
when you went down.
Oh yeah.
Summer of 69, Los Angeles.
The man says terrorized.
Yeah, the man says terrorized.
Keep an eye out for me in Once Upon a Time in Hollywood
coming this summer.
I don't want to sound too old
but there was a remake of Life is a Highway
or someone covered it.
Oh, it's a cover on the car soundtrack.
Rascal Flatts and Tom Cochran.
I know the Tom Cochran original, thank you.
Tom Cochran.
Also talk about music forgotten factoids.
Right, I don't know why I know that.
Where's the rest of that artist?
Where else did Tom Cochran do that?
Couldn't tell you who the seventh president is
but I know the original artist of Life is a Highway.
Mm-hmm.
Need a sec.
You okay?
Jason's, we'll cut this up.
Sorry.
Wrong pipe?
Yeah.
Okay.
Too excited about Tom Cochran.
I just got thinking about driving down that highway.
Life is a highway.
Mark, you, I mean we're talking about
the main Disneyland train today
but I know you're a fan of one of the other trains
at Disneyland because of your tat.
You got a cool tat.
I got a sick tat.
What's the tat?
I got a tattoo of the goat with a stick of dynamite
in its mouth from Big Thunder Mountain Railroad.
Yay.
It's my favorite goat. It's great.
Thank you.
And it's like a, it is a really specific,
it's almost like the character,
super closeups that would start
like a Mickey or a Goofy shoot.
Right.
Because he's straight on.
It's an angle that you wouldn't get.
It's like not him in an action pose.
It's more of like his head shot.
It almost needs like a starburst behind.
I thought about adding like a starburst behind it.
Oh, absolutely.
A sunburst behind it.
Yeah.
Like a pork, or like a porky pig, loony jams.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like when they come out of that thing.
Yeah, I just love, it's always, I had a,
my boyfriend at the time gave me a gift card for a tattoo
and I was like, I didn't know what,
I like sat on it for like months and months.
And then one time I was really stoned
and went on Splash Mountain.
And when I got off Splash Mountain,
we had planned to go on Big Thunder.
I was like, I gotta keep an eye out for that goat.
Because I always loved that goat.
So I was like, that's my tattoo I think.
And then I Googled it, made sure no one else had it.
I Googled goat dynamite tattoo, nothing.
Really?
Wow, interesting.
I clicked images.
If I were to Google it now, do you come up?
I don't know, I haven't Googled it since.
Interesting.
I hope so.
You haven't like heavily featured it in a tweet
or anything to like own it in an actual property way.
So many people think I'm like a Satanist or an Aries.
I am neither.
I have no problems with either.
Sure.
I could see it, yeah, like a goat with a dynamite.
It does seem like you're an anarchist or something maybe.
I just like that there's mischief ahead.
That's what I like about the goat.
From a storytelling standpoint, on the ride he tells you,
uh-oh, things are not going according to plan.
When goats are the dynamite.
Sure.
It's sort of a Jurassic Park moment.
Like nature is being reclaimed.
Nature finds a way, doesn't it?
It is also.
In a very stupider version.
Yeah, yeah, much so.
If I think about it, it is sort of implying
that maybe that goat is about to die.
Like the goat is gonna blow itself up.
Could be.
I like to think he drops it in someone's bathtub
and then scampers away.
He kills the humans and he's fine.
Yeah.
Got it.
That's better to think about.
But it's not sparking.
He could just eat it.
I mean, goats will eat anything.
He could just, once you turn the corner,
he could just consume it.
So he'll just die a slow painful death then.
Yeah.
But then he cans and stuff.
Like if you drink a bunch of detergent or something.
Sure.
It would happen to slowly your bowels would
kind of collapse.
But I also love, that's one of the reasons
I like the railroads,
because I like any ride with critters.
Oh yeah, sure.
I like that word.
So I'm very pro-critter.
Yay.
Are you, it's not that word.
Critter country, your favorite land in Disneyland?
It's not actually.
It's not.
Okay.
That means it.
That's fine.
I love the candy shop.
Yeah.
Great candy shop.
Once had the manager of the candy shop
flirt very heavily with my boyfriend and I at the time.
He gave us free peanut butter cookie thing.
The peanut butter, oh yeah.
The chocolate covered peanut butter graham cracker.
He just gave it to us guys.
That's a heavy flirt.
So I married him.
It would be fun to find your partner in critter country.
Oh, that would make sense.
Yeah.
I mean for anybody too.
Like what a story in general.
I mean it's also, that could be the name of a gay bar,
critter country.
You know?
Sure, that's a good point.
That's where I would go.
I do like critter, I like the aesthetics of it.
Like I like things like buildings made of wood.
Like I like that whole west side of the frontier land.
You know, I love all that.
Yeah.
Big time.
I love the waterfall that's right next to the shops
and it's kind of between the shops and the Winnie the Pooh
ride.
Oh yeah.
I find that to be a nice little calm corner.
It's all the way in the corner of the park.
You gotta like make a point of going over there.
That's where Santa is though.
Oh really?
Is that where they do Santa?
Yeah, Santa is back there.
Santa is back there sorted by that meet and greet.
Yeah.
I mean it's where of course the country bears used to be.
I've never seen the country bears.
Wow, that's another podcast.
I'm sorry.
We can't.
But they're not critters, they're too big to be critters.
No, are they critters?
Critters have to be a little smaller.
I think critters are like the size of like
no bigger than a raccoon or like a fox.
Is a go to critter?
I'd say so.
Isn't that like a critter?
So you gotta make, you gotta say they're bigger.
I'm not sure.
I think maybe critters can't talk.
Or they can't know because critters sing in critter country.
They felt the need to change it
because it used to be bear country, right?
That part of the park.
And then it became critter country when more critters
moved in and the bears were executed.
Executed.
Shot in the back of the head.
The critters took over.
That's a good point that that definition,
that implies that bears are not critters.
Critters are vegetarians?
Or you can eat grubs.
You can eat nuts or whatever.
You can eat nuts and grubs.
I'm sure a listener now is screaming at their podcast.
Whatever they listen.
What defines a critter?
They know exactly what a critter is.
So tell us please.
Well critters are defined in a different way
in the film critters.
But I don't think, I think that is a different,
it's a different entomology.
No, Michael Iser wanted a critter's land.
It just didn't happen.
It was gonna be in the beastly kingdom, the unfiltered.
The animal kingdom.
The property he's kicking himself he didn't get.
All this, oh go ahead.
I was gonna do an Eisner, talk about critters.
It's not worth it.
You go ahead.
Well all this talk about definitions
had me thinking about something involving today's topic.
I learned reading about this,
the difference between trains and locomotives.
Colloquially I think they're kind of used interchangeably,
but the locomotive is that front car with the engine
or the boiler that generates the force to pull the train,
which is the series of interconnected cars.
It seems like though train could also refer
to the whole kitten caboodle.
The cars being pulled and the locomotive pulling it.
Oh, so a locomotive can't be a train,
but a train can have a locomotive in it.
I think that's right.
Like a caboose just can't be a train.
No, that's just a car.
That's just a train car.
Hell no.
Not on my watch.
Get out of here you stinking cabooses.
And I'm excited to see if this whole episode
brings out the people who really like trains.
Well I'm sure they're all very reasonable folks
who are just like easy breezy going,
let's get some facts wrong, but whatever.
Absolutely.
Sure as hell a level of train knowledge
is gonna satisfy a hardcore train head.
I did watch. Is a monorail a train?
Interesting.
Of the future.
Now that's a good question because for a long time
the roundhouse where the trains and locomotives are parked
also serviced the monorail.
The original roundhouse that serviced both
has been demolished and I think other stuff rebuilt since.
So where do they go now?
A different roundhouse.
Wow.
Some of the history of this attraction is very dry.
Train facts are dry?
No.
I do.
I mean listeners will know I love riding the train.
Yeah.
I love trains.
I love riding the train.
I have looked into and I'm thinking of like,
oh maybe next time I go back east
I will take the train back.
I will get a sleeper car and do that.
Nowadays you have to change,
you probably had to do this back in the day too.
I think it's like three trains to get to
Harrisburg, I would probably take it not,
get off before Philadelphia but it's like LA to Chicago,
Chicago to somewhere else, somewhere else to Harrisburg.
Can you give us the full route
and look up some times that they might be leaving?
But I'm just thinking about,
I've always wanted to eat a sleeper to sleeper car
and just see the country by train.
That's nice, you should.
What's stopping you?
Take a big train ride.
It's not that much more than like flying back.
I mean it takes four days about.
What are some other reasons?
What are some other reasons you would do it?
Oh it just seems nice.
Jason's top 19 things about trains.
I hear you meet some real interesting characters
who will talk to you about why they don't like flying
but they do like trains.
Because they're deeply neurotic probably.
I would think unless there's, yeah,
maybe there are conspiracy theorists on the train
that could tell you some fun conspiracy theories
about planes.
Oh yeah like radiation kind of stuff.
Something like that. Chemtrails.
That weird Boeing fix in the news a lot.
Let me ask Jason and then I'll throw this out to everyone.
As a child or now, did you have a conductor's hat
and a train whistle?
Didn't have a train whistle.
My parents were pretty good about tricking us into not,
like pushing us towards non-noisy toys.
I don't think I was a child.
I think I had some like kazoos.
How about the hat though?
That's what I'm really looking forward to here.
I feel like there had to have been a conductor's hat.
I feel like maybe.
Because we went to a lot of,
I feel like there was,
Strasburg, Pennsylvania has a historic train museum
and exhibits and stuff.
And a short steam locomotive circuit that you can ride back.
Why'd you move here then?
Yeah, sounds like heaven on earth.
Well to see Travel Town, which I still haven't been to.
Oh go to Travel Town, it's free and fun.
You get your fix.
There's this wonderful thing called Travel Town
that's very close to the Disney lot
where he almost built his original little train park.
And apparently he was talking to the city of Burbank
about how can I connect.
They were trying to figure out,
they were on the way to building Travel Town
and Walt reached out, can there be a big train
that connects to where I'm building a train?
Yeah, there's a ton of connections with the train
and Disney and Travel Town and the LA Live steamers,
which they have a bunch of old trains there.
Walt was inspired by some of those train cars of like,
oh let's make ours look like this.
And then the Carrollwood Society is over there.
The Carrollwood barn that Walt built in his backyard
was preserved and is in Griffith Park
and open one day a month.
And they have a lot of the original miniatures
Disney had in his backyard.
Now that I have not done
and I probably should have done before this podcast.
Yikes.
I wanna make sure we've covered
everybody's childhood hats though.
Yeah, that's what I would have to get back to.
Scott, yes, train hat?
No train hat.
Whistle?
No whistle.
I think I liked Travel Town a lot
because I grew up around here, but I had no other.
I didn't have any take home train affinity.
What I did do at home was I had a little raft
that will inflatable raft in the pool
that was themed after the jungle cruise.
And I would do little mini jungle cruises for my sister
and I'd be the skipper.
And I'd leave toy animals around.
I'd put a snake in the pool filter area.
That's cute.
Yeah, and there were kinda like rocks surrounding my pool.
So I pretended like they were little caves and stuff.
I liked that raft a lot.
I remember it having a cool design.
That's my observation.
I had a raft with a cool design.
Cool design.
I'm not bragging.
Mark, hat, whistle?
No hat, yes whistle.
Really?
I'm in the boat too.
I've been to, Sacramento has a great railroad museum.
You get to walk into a dining car.
There's no food.
But you get to see how people used to ride the rails.
It's a real hoot.
There's one part you could walk underneath the train
that's very scary.
Cause you're walking underneath the engine.
Oh, interesting.
You're like, oh, this thing is so heavy.
I would just be turned into a puddle if this fell on me.
Oh, sure.
It's like elevated mass, but with a train.
That exhibit at LACMA.
The big rock at Los Angeles art museum.
You mean the big rock.
The rock one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I love a train also though.
What a hoot.
Literally a hoot.
I'm trying to think.
I said no hat, but now that I'm thinking about it,
I may have had a hat.
I had bandanas.
I had for sure a bandana.
I feel like there's a picture of me.
Now I'm thinking it might be a different kid.
I may have been tricker.
I'm thinking of a photo specifically.
I'm thinking that there's a different kid
with a conductor's hat and a bandana.
I don't think hat for me, but for sure whistle.
You got it.
For sure whistle.
Are you thinking of a milk carton?
No, I'm not.
There was a kid's trick or treating.
A kid had a conductor's hat.
It was not me though.
I think I was Oscar the Grouch.
Hey, that's neat.
You were jealous of that train.
You didn't know costumes could be so cool
until you saw that conductor kid.
I think I thought trains were boring as a kid.
I think maybe I still do.
It's a real flipping attitude.
You could list, as Jason is doing,
you're listing cool train things,
and then my counter is just like,
I don't know, it's boring.
It's like a dumb opinion to have,
but I liked any mode of transportation
that was just different than a car.
My favorite thing, the St. Louis Arch,
have you ever been in that?
Oh, I've taken that.
Those little round spheres,
they go up and then left, up and then left, up.
It feels like you're taking a shuttlecraft.
Inside the St. Louis Arch?
That takes you up to the top.
Yeah, you're in these little round elevators.
I didn't think I knew you could go in there.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, there's an observation deck at the top.
Oh, terrifying.
But isn't it just, are there windows in the arch?
Yeah, there's like four windows.
What?
I feel like I've only pictured stone.
It's like the Washington Monument.
No, in some ways, the elevator ride's the best part.
You can also go in that.
You can go in the Washington Monument.
Yeah. Yeah.
Are there windows in it?
Yeah, did you see Spider-Man homecoming?
He saved his friends.
No.
Boy, I don't know anything about our monuments.
Wow.
And when I drove across country to move out here,
I did the, you could buy a combo ticket.
We got there just in time because it was about to like,
the last ones for the day were ending,
where you got to ride a riverboat up and down the Mississippi
and then also go in the arch.
The Mississippi at that point, muddy and disgusting.
And you get to see it from a boat
and from above equally muddy.
And did you know you can go inside
of Thomas Jefferson's head on Mount Rushmore
and look through his eyes?
That's available to you too.
I know that one's not true.
And Washington's mouth is a slide.
You got to spit out the bottom.
It's a big tongue.
Yeah.
You just fall to your death?
Mike has a pad down there.
Oh, okay.
It was a crash pad.
But you drop like 300 feet per fight.
That's terrifying.
It's a taller pad than a normal pad.
Oh, I love a tall pad.
Yeah.
It'll get you, don't worry.
Mike is recalling when he saw pictures
from the filming of North by Northwest.
Sure.
His brain is as muddy as the Mississippi.
The old Mississippi.
Mm-hmm.
So yeah, as a kid, I think trains for me, boring.
No offense, but I wasn't, I now really like,
I'm not some insane train person,
but I like riding the train.
I think it's fun.
It harkens back to an old time transportation.
It's nice.
I like all that stuff.
But as a kid, it was like,
I don't want to ride the train.
Space Mountain, please.
Like fast, cool space.
Go on the Disney train.
I did, I think, but it's not a memory
I cherish as a kid in Orlando.
Well, the Disney World one is a lot simpler.
That's, yes, that's also true.
It is more practical, I think.
I mean, the trains are good for getting
to the other side of the park,
especially in Florida, where it's much bigger.
I think it was many years before I went
on the Disneyland train actually
and realized there was cool stuff on it.
I don't think, I think it was many years
into going to Disneyland before I even made that loop
to see all the fun stuff.
It's also one of those things,
once you get older, like, oh, I just,
I would love a good sit.
Oh yeah.
It's like a nice 20 minutes.
And also the people watching is great.
Yeah.
You get a nice aerial view of the park,
especially like towards the background,
Toontown and stuff.
I like to get on at New Orleans Square
and get off on Main Street.
Oh yeah.
That gets you most of it.
There's nothing in between Main Street
and New Orleans Square.
You see some like Mardi Gras heads, that's about it.
And there is one Jaguar.
Right.
And it's built up by the narration.
So be careful in Adventureland.
You don't know what could be around,
lurking around any corner.
And then it's one still Jaguar.
A statue.
Yes.
A false Jaguar.
That's a good route.
Yeah.
I've never thought about what a favorite one is for me.
That's definitely a, I like the,
I think I like New Orleans Square Station the most
besides the main one.
Yeah.
I think that's the best one.
That's a good one too.
This isn't very far,
but taking that up to Fantasyland
can save you a lot of walking
because it's up at the north part of the park.
And also you end with the big finish.
You end with the dioramas, with the Grand Canyon
and the dinosaurs.
You might have picked the best route
if you're not gonna do a full circle.
That's a pretty good one.
The Grand Circle Tour.
Slightly less than a full circle.
I do like doing a three-quarters circle.
I like doing the Grand Circle Tour
and then I get off where I wanna go.
What do you mean?
You like go all the way around once,
do the Grand Circle Tour
and then get off at New Orleans Square or Toontown Station.
Okay, so you're using it, you get a full ride.
I get a full ride.
You get the full fun ride
and then you use it as a practical thing.
And then I get to where I need to go.
Interesting.
Really?
I don't think I've ever done that.
You stick, you loop around more than.
I think that's what I did the last time I was there.
I've never done that.
I like it.
I love going through Splash Mountain.
Sure, yes.
Yeah, and of course the Grand Canyon,
which I didn't realize until researching this episode,
the Grand Canyon came first
and then after the World's Fair ended,
they moved the dinosaurs from Ford's Magic Skyway.
They moved that scene next to it.
I also didn't know that.
So, yeah.
If you, if you.
If you were.
I know what I did.
That's just a fact.
I was just trying to, I wrote down all these facts.
No, no, no, no, no, I actually, I did,
that sounded weird.
I did find that interesting.
Yeah.
Yeah, the Grand Canyon was there in like 1958.
I think what's weird about it
is that it's presented as one full experience.
This, by the way, it's possible you're listening to this
and you've not been to Disneyland
or you don't even know that thing is there
because Disney World doesn't have this.
No, no.
Disneyland Paris does not have anything special
on the train, but I didn't know also
until researching Tokyo Disneyland
does have Primeval World.
There is one other Primeval World.
I missed it.
On the train.
I missed that too in Tokyo.
Yep, yeah, guess you did.
I may have as well, but maybe now
I gotta do it.
But the, anyway, if you get on at Tomorrowland
or anywhere before it,
anywhere approaching the Main Street station,
it's this really fun grand finale
where you see some cool dioramas.
One is mainly a diorama with some animatronics
and then you go back in time
to the kingdom of the dinosaurs.
And I think my takeaway thinking about Grand Canyon diorama
and Primeval World for a while,
there's always been a disconnect to me
that they presented like you are in the past
of the Grand Canyon.
Is that what's going on?
It seems like it.
But now we take you to millions of years ago.
But are you, but you don't see canyons really.
I thought it started, you see Grand Canyon
as it is now and then you go back in time.
No, that's correct.
But in that transition, are we time traveling
somewhere else or is it like back to the future
where you travel in the same physical space?
Oh, I never thought about it, I don't know.
Because is that, yeah, is the dinosaurs,
are they in the Grand Canyon in the past?
Well, they don't show the Grand Canyon.
They don't.
Maybe it's just not formed yet.
Are they implying?
Oh, maybe, maybe it's pre-canyon.
Pre-canyon?
Are they implying the asteroid?
The asteroid made the canyon.
That is shoddy science.
It's erosion made the canyon.
Mmm.
Not every school child knows that.
There's a river.
All right.
There's layers of sediment.
It would be fun though if the asteroid did it.
Very strange strike.
Yeah, that's all over the map.
That's not a big round hole.
Maybe it bounced around a lot.
This asteroid needs to get its act together.
It's pretty goofy.
It's like a...
It's a crazy hole, you mean.
Disney history, that's a little bit,
it's like the Inglorious Bastards history
where Hitler got killed.
Right, that didn't happen?
It's a flight of fancy.
Yeah, apparently it didn't.
I'm surprised to learn that too.
I wonder if he's gonna do something
in Once Upon a Time in Hollywood
if Manson gets shot in a bank or something.
I do feel like that is gonna happen
in Once Upon a Time in Hollywood.
Like some false...
Sharon Tate lives in Manson.
Oh.
Something weird like that.
That'd be cool.
We'll see.
Hmm.
Can we also incorporate that the asteroid
was a fireball that Zeus threw or something?
Oh, from Hercules?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh yeah.
He's up in Greek heaven.
I'm showing also how much I know about mythology.
He was mad at somebody and he threw a lightning bolt
and then turned into a comet that killed the dinosaurs
and formed the Grand Canyon.
Is it a character from Disney's Hercules as well?
I guess we're talking Disney, so we might as well, yes.
Let's tie it into that.
All right, that makes sense to me.
Rip, torn, wait, who was Zeus?
James Woods, of course, Hades.
That's Danny DeVito, the other one.
The sidekick.
Rip, torn was somebody.
Was he?
Was Rip, Jason, are you looking it up?
I'm looking it up.
Rip, torn.
People are screaming right now.
It keeps happening.
Locomotive.
Just yell train.
Well, doesn't matter, we'll figure it out.
Just interrupt any sentence.
Horde.
In the middle.
Rip, torn was Zeus.
There's a great lightning strike effect.
Oh yeah, it's great.
On the diorama.
Yeah, yes.
Very effective. That's kind of new.
Because they just redid the diorama,
they made them pretty, plus them up, I guess.
Yeah.
There's very striking, beautiful dioramas.
There's a storm in the background.
Yeah, that new stuff.
There's a bunch of pterodactyls swirling.
Pterodactyls, very scary.
Children do not like them, so I think they're great.
Have you witnessed that?
Like kids freaking out a little.
It's also one of the few rides,
and also another I love any ride with quitters,
and any ride that has pitch darkness in it.
I feel like pitch darkness, like in our highly,
everyone loves to sue everybody.
It feels like so dangerous.
There's something edgy about taking the mass public
into pitch darkness to me.
Like it feels like it seems like dangerous in a way.
Like, ooh, this is like a real old timey thrill.
And enclosed spaces.
Yeah, seatbelted in.
No, anything can happen.
So like, yeah, you could switch positions.
Rip toward a Zeus.
Oh, thank God, thank God.
Good pulse, guys.
Jason Sheridan with a breaking news alert.
Return is Zeus.
Both the motor and the engine trains,
the cars are the whole thing.
In spring, as of spring 2019, rip torn.
Zeus.
But back to your regular-
Columbia Gorge is what they call the new thing.
When you talk about lawsuits,
and people bumping around and stuff,
my favorite thing that I found in my research
was that in the early days of the Disneyland Railroad,
they had cars that were themed after cattle cars.
And so, you know, there were no seats.
They're just like, it's big planks,
like you're keeping animals in a pen.
And so you're like, okay, so there were like a couple cars
that passengers didn't get on, they were just themed
as if there were livestock in there.
No, Walt put people, guests could go in the cattle cars
where there were no seats or restraints of any kind.
And specifically, old Imagineer and animator Ward Kimball,
who is a train enthusiast like Walt,
said, hey, that's weird, don't you think?
Maybe that's not safe to have people
just standing on a train.
And he's like, no, I want people to feel like they're cattle.
Well, mission accomplished.
In a lot of ways in Disneyland.
Space Mountain Lion, geez.
Yeah, yeah.
I also, I came across a crazy thing
from like the opening month,
within a week of Disneyland's opening on July 17th, 1955,
a brake man pulled the switch
connecting the Disneyland Railroad's main line
with a siding at Main Street USA,
station too soon as the Retlaw 2,
they called them Retlaw 1 and 2, the original trains.
And what's Retlaw?
That is Walter Backward.
Walter Backward's Retlaw.
Yeah, really laying it on thick.
That's the kind of thing that I saw in books as a kid
and thought, that is so clever.
And then I go tell my fellow students,
don't you think that's clever?
And they would turn and walk away.
As my childhood.
So we pulled the brake too soon.
The caboose at the end of the freight train
had not fully made it across the switch when it was pulled.
And as a result, the caboose's front set of wheels
traveled, like basically jumped the tracks,
traveled along the main line towards the passenger's chain,
swung to the side, colliding with a concrete slab
and derailing on impact.
During the ensuing commotion,
the erring brake man, presumably to avoid disciplinary action,
quietly left the scene, exited the park
and was not seen again.
So this guy disappeared.
He got the first ghost in him.
He ghosted him.
Yeah.
Anyway, I was trying to read that
and got very confused reading that.
But basically, yeah, the brake man disappeared into a crowd
never to be heard from again.
What year was that?
That was 55.
That was within the opening month.
Wow.
When you could do that, when you could disappear
and start life afresh.
Right, start a new name.
Good old days.
Yeah.
Like Mad Men, Don Draper style.
Yeah. Exactly, yeah.
Now people would find you.
I've said multiple times before,
have I dreamed about driving east from Los Angeles
until I run out of gas and starting life anew?
Yes, many times.
Will I do it?
You get to like Arizona?
Yeah, Arizona, maybe even still in California.
Who knows?
Who knows what adventures await?
Don't just do it, derail a train first.
Yeah, go for it.
I mean, that's, yeah, that is good.
You know, if we're going back into the history of the thing,
not that we have to be super detailed in all this,
but okay, Disneyland really exists because of the train.
That's what's important about the train.
It was that Walt got into model railroads
and he started thinking, is there some place
that I could put up a train and have people come ride it
and have dads and kids and moms all hang out together?
So it's so crucial to the DNA of the park.
And it grew out of him having a train in his backyard,
which was the Carrollwood Pacific Railroad.
Which he had because he was a polo enthusiast
and suffered too many polo injuries.
So he had to find a new.
A doctor suggested a safer hobby,
and that's why Disneyland exists,
because Walt got fucked up.
People are so weird.
Polo is an insane sport.
Yeah.
Horses and clubs.
Oh, it's that one.
That's what polo is.
Yeah, you're swinging, whacking hard balls while on a horse.
Because Walt had, what a fun,
I mean, it's not funny if you had to live with it,
but what a funny ailment where he'd be like,
ah, my polo injury's acting up.
Because that's what would happen.
That's written about in many a biography of Walt Disney
is old polo injury.
That comes up, really?
Yeah, we were talking about it a little bit with the crafts
when we were at Club 33.
He was talking about Walt's old polo injury.
Oh, right.
And he was quizzing waitresses on Walt's polo injury
and his nurse.
Because he had a nurse.
Yes.
And the theory was that there was something going on.
Right, right, right.
But the polo injury, I think it looms large
in his history in general.
So then I imagine Walt had an old smoking doctor
who was like, I don't know, take up trains, maybe?
Just do something different.
What else do rich people do?
Trains.
First things first, keep drinking.
Yeah, right.
Smoking, smoking, of course, yeah, keep at it.
A lot of butter on your steak.
They were drinking in the doctor's office too, I assume.
He had a little bar over weblogger.
Big bottles of chili.
Yeah.
So anyway, so.
I went back to the polo.
Polo too dangerous.
But remember, diet custards.
Stick to diet custards.
Yeah.
In all, I just got that big Disneyland history book
and I've seen pictures like this before,
but there's a lot of pictures of Walt in a tiny train
with the hat on with his kids going around.
He was way into this.
My neighbor growing up, he was a British guy,
he had in his garage a train set that would lower
from the ceiling of the garage
and take up the whole two-car garage.
He built this whole mechanism himself.
So there's something about,
I don't know what it is about like older,
when you get older, you wanna play with,
you wanna be master of a domain or something, I don't know.
What is this?
Psychologically.
Yeah, is it like a God complex?
Is it a, you're trying to like.
Maybe we're like, I have, my life is chaos,
but at least this has order.
This makes sense.
It's like a Reverend Lovejoy's trains on the Simpsons.
Bobby Bockela too on The Sopranos.
That's like a later Sopranos thing,
is Bobby's love of trains.
Right.
My great uncle got me a train set for Christmas as a kid
and it was very hard to put up.
And I didn't know, I thought it was fun
to make a little track and then send them around,
but I think I put it together maybe twice and that was it.
Yeah.
So I'm trying to think like now that I'm an older person
and I collect many a toy,
would I, if I had room, would I have a train set?
A train going around?
I'm not sure, I don't know.
I think there's a meditative quality to it,
like setting up the tracks and the little buildings
and the trains and if you're painting,
I mean, once you get to painting miniatures,
that's a next level sort of thing.
But anyone who is mechanically,
like my stepdad is an engineer and he,
yeah, he likes train stuff.
He has a train set up in his basement
and yeah, likes going to museums, this sort of thing.
I think he doesn't really work on cars though.
I think there might also be people who like tinker with cars
and like train stuff is kind of adjacent to that.
So.
It's like they all got a touch of that welcome to Marwin.
Yeah.
You know?
They're all processing something.
Yeah, it's like that.
It's a world where you didn't get beaten up
and you don't have bad war memories.
Yeah.
Janelle Mone loves you.
But I think if you are inclined to taking stuff apart
and putting stuff together, like the train thing.
I was never into like die cast.
I remember the first time my dad got me a,
like a, there was like a car on a box
and like, oh cool, like my Batmobile toy.
No, this one you put together yourself and you paint it.
Oh right.
And he took out that little particular paint
with the tiny brush and that smelled really crazy
and I just totally glazed over.
I don't want to put my toy together.
Are you crazy?
I think I had a Batmobile model
that I never put together, I'm pretty sure.
I had a next generation enterprise.
Oh, did you put that together?
I put it together.
Whoa, that must've been hard.
It was hard, but I would never put the stickers on
because I would always get the stickers wrong.
So I would just leave them off.
And I was bad at painting, so I never painted them.
How big was it?
It was like a foot.
Okay.
Pretty good foot and a half maybe.
I hung it from my ceiling.
That was a toy I always wanted.
I'm talking about more of the action figure one that came.
Sure, sure.
That was one I always wanted but never got.
I think that design holds up, next generation.
Oh, it's fantastic.
It's also the best TV show ever made.
Did you guys ever do, have you guys ever talked about
the Star Trek experience at the Las Vegas Hilton?
It's on the list.
It's probably coming up.
We've been wanting to get to that one.
It's probably coming soon.
And more fun Star Trek stuff
that I discovered in the last month or two.
I did it and I was very sad when it went away.
Oh really?
How was it?
It's amazing.
It was amazing.
I won't talk about it if you're gonna talk about it later.
Well, I don't know, give us something though.
Something we might not know about.
Well the cool thing is, they make it,
when you're in line for the ride part of it,
they make it seem like you're just in a line
for like a Star Tours type thing.
So like you queue up in your rows like that.
Like you're waiting for the Star Tours door to open.
But when you're on that, when it's about to start,
the lights go down, the lights turn off.
And when they come back on,
you're standing on the transporter bay
of the Star Trek Enterprise.
Oh right.
I've read about this.
And that was like in a crazy effect.
I was like, and then you're walking through the hallways
of the Enterprise and then you walk onto the bridge.
Do you have any idea how they did that effect?
I think there was four walls around you
and then like they raised.
Wow.
When you're in the dark.
That's pretty nuts.
It was great.
And then you walk through, get onto a shuttlecraft
and have like a Star Tours type regular
flight simulator thing.
This is a thing.
It was great.
It sounds great.
There was multiple versions of it I've learned.
There was a scarier version.
Maybe the board were involved.
But I think as a kid, as soon as I saw space stuff,
fuck you trains.
Like I was not interested.
No, sure.
The end I saw Star Trek or Star Wars
and I was like, this is awesome.
Trains boring snooze by frontier land.
I like big thunder, but this isn't a spaceship I'm in.
Like I was way more.
Once you've seen space, how do you go back down to a train?
No.
A mine cart maybe.
Maybe.
But everybody be leaping from tracks
and landing on other tracks.
It's still got some adrenaline.
I bet there's, I bet by virtue of this,
I think in 1955, having a train be one of the primary
attractions in your new amusement park,
it reflected the times.
Of course.
But I bet today there's a lot of people
who are into trains primarily because of Disney land.
As opposed to it because it's not,
there's not as much affection for that in the culture
and people don't grow up with Westerns
and Davy Crockett and that world of stuff.
Like it feels as alien to them
as any actual alien thing is to us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like what is that?
It could be from the future.
Who knows what it is?
It's so crazy looking.
Disney ingrained in the train enthusiast community
in America because the machine shop at Disney,
the Disney Studios built the first two trains.
And as they added trains, they just kept buying old trains
to restore as they needed new ones.
So that's where a lot of those came from.
Some were custom made but some were decommissioned
and let's get it in the park.
Yeah, get it in the park and repaint it.
And Disney has gifted or donated or in one case
there was like a trade, like older train cars
or older locomotives to museums or collectors
or sold stuff to collectors.
Well, so here's a crazy thing that happened
to me a number of years ago.
I went up to San Luis Obispo or a little bit above it,
there is Santa Margarita.
It was a wedding at a place called
the Santa Margarita Ranch
and there was this sprawling property, super insane.
The reception's in a giant barn.
And then after the ceremony is done, a train pulls up.
What do you mean a train at this property?
And the train says Disneyland Railroad.
Whoa.
And they tell us this was the original Disneyland train.
And I'd never looked further into it.
And like, so what do you mean?
When was it decommissioned?
So this was ret law one is what I was on.
If anyone's lucky enough to go to some event there
or sometimes they do public events up there.
But that's what they have.
It is one of the original like day one trains.
And what happened is they are more of like
traditional train cars, like interior cars with windows.
And if you've been on the train lately,
by that I mean since the 60s,
you know that it is not, it's not enclosed cars, right?
It's like the stacked seating so that you can facing out
so that you can look at the dioramas.
When they put in the Grand Canyon thing in the 50s,
people did not wanna have to be peering
through these tiny windows.
And they started like getting rid of those cars.
And plus they were falling into disrepair anyway.
So these train cars were, they were,
the theatrical ones quote unquote went in.
They were all commissioned around the 74 I think.
And they got moved up to this ranch,
which was like a blast.
I think they were like falling apart when they left Disney
and just bumming around the property.
But they have been beautifully restored up there.
And the coolest thing is that apparently one time
there was a film festival on this ranch.
And as part of it, there were robbers who rode up on horses
and robbed the train.
And one of the guys was in a bandana.
And when he pulled down the bandana,
it was David Carradine.
Whoa!
Kung Fu!
Yeah!
Kung Fu was robbing your train.
He doesn't need this money, you rich actor.
Unless he didn't play it.
It might've been pre-Kill Bill resurgence yet.
Those enclosed cars I believe are called combine cars.
And Walt liked them because it reminded him
of his days as a boy.
He was a news butcher selling newspapers and candy.
A news butcher?
News butcher.
They called it a news butcher.
News boys were called if you went up and down train cars.
That's what I call Jeff Zucker, you know what I mean?
I'll tell you.
I'll tell you what.
Yeah, he was a news butcher.
If they had had a news butcher on that train,
you could've gotten one of your
Jeffrey Dahmer People magazines right on the train.
Can't you imagine?
And a big lolly.
A dream.
And a big lolly and a big stogie.
You could've been sitting there having a stogie.
What an obnoxious teenager I would've been.
What an obnoxious, yeah.
It's closed now,
but there used to be a restaurant called Poe Folks
down by Disneyland in Orange.
It was like a Southern theme.
And they'd had a thing where up towards the ceiling,
a train, a little model train would go around.
Those are some of my favorite trains.
Whenever you see a train in a restaurant,
going through little fun dioramas.
Let me tell you another good Orange County train.
Mike, you know where I'm going with this.
Well, maybe.
We were there once together.
But in Buena Park on Beach Boulevard,
on the way into Knott's Berry Farm,
there is a McDonald's that has a model train inside.
That's robust.
It's like a, you know,
I mean, not a bigger than usual,
but like on the larger end of McDonald's.
And the train goes all around it.
Super detailed miniature.
But the craziest thing about this McDonald's
is that the sign in really big,
like kind of like fancier,
more like fiber optic lighting
than you usually see at a McDonald's
has this big cursive logo, McThriller.
What?
McThriller, why?
You go in, is it because of trains?
That doesn't make sense.
Those words still don't tie together.
There was apparently at one point
a simulator ride in this McDonald's.
But there hasn't been since like 1989.
And yet they never change it from McThriller.
Were you traveling through like McDonald's land?
Like was Ronald McDonald there,
like shooting Nazis or something?
I don't know.
Blowing away fry guys for trying to steal.
Third Reich fry guys?
Why have you turned?
Speaking of trains.
That's at those are trains I don't like.
Yeah, Wal didn't consider that with the cars.
And maybe people want some escapism.
Don't remind people the recent events.
No, this was, I don't know what the simulator
at McDonald's was.
But boy, if there was a McDonald's ride.
There's gotta be some YouTube video of this McThriller.
Somebody in the audience has to know.
There's nothing you want more after you have
a nice big greasy McDonald's meal.
It's like a motion simulator is the perfect thing
to ease my stomach.
Oh man, it's Friday in Southern California
during the Easter season.
$2 filet-o-fish sandwich running right now.
I would love to pound a couple of those bad boys
and hop in a 3D motion simulator.
Get jostled for a while.
How about like a body wars where you go inside Grimace?
He has like a tummy ache and you have to go help him.
And you get to see how McDonald's food digests.
Clogged arteries.
Sure, seasonal overlay where you go inside Uncle O'Grimacy.
His Irish uncle.
Yeah, you don't see a lot of St. Patrick's Day seasonal overlays.
It's like a diseased liver.
Oh yeah.
He's a drinker but not from McDonald's.
Obviously no liquor here.
I don't know where he's doing it.
Grimace, you have to help Grimace donate part of his liver
to Uncle O'Grimacy.
Oh no.
You have to use the front of your ship
to like slazer off a little section.
They should do a Galaxy's Edge Millennium Falcon level ride
where you actually do the incision.
Like you as a group have to perform the surgery
on Uncle O'Grimacy.
Get out.
And you get put in a scuba suit
and like swim out into his innards
and remove the purple ulcers.
Oh.
But wait, would that be healthy for Grimace?
What if the ulcer.
To have an ulcer?
Well, but he's purple.
Oh so.
What are his guts?
Well he's like a neon green maybe,
like a lime green or something.
I guess so.
Yeah, purple is healthy for Grimace.
That's a good point.
There's gotta be some cartoonist or some deviant art person
who's drawn like a diagram of the anatomy of Grimace.
I'm sure it's more detailed than you want.
Yeah, absolutely.
His blood is milkshakes?
I mean his blood's gotta be.
No wonder he's depressed.
That actually might be canon.
I'm so lethargic.
That might be canon.
He's kind of the Eeyore of their world.
Absolutely. That's true.
This is like Maya Rudolph's character in Away We Go.
Remember her job was drawing medical textbook illustrations.
I've never forgotten Away We Go since I've seen it.
Weekly viewings.
Weekly viewing, sing alongs.
It is shocking that there's not a full scale
McDonald's theme park.
Yeah.
You would think with the amount of money they have
and the legit affection we all seem to have
for these dumb characters,
you would think there would have been a full scale
somewhere McDonald's.
It would have been cheap as shit but.
Sure.
Orlando, they have that massive Orlando one
where you can still get pizza and pasta and stuff.
They certainly have interesting McDonald's restaurants
but you'd think there would be like a full scale.
The McDonald's by my house growing up
but it was always a treat to go.
We never got it regularly but they had at the kids table
like two saddles you could sit on at the kids table
and that was always a thrill.
Wow.
Just a different way to sit.
Yeah but as a kid you're like this is great.
I'm sitting on a saddle eating a cheeseburger.
Yeah.
What more do you want out of life?
Isn't some regular meal.
I'm not some regular kid.
Sure there's no, and you didn't need back support
when you were a child.
That's fine.
I would hate it now.
The best and scariest thing I have is just going inside
of the Play Place officer Big Mac mouth.
Oh yeah.
In like tall thing you would climb.
Oh sure.
And we all had that memory right?
Yeah yeah.
Scary.
They had like it was a piece of play equipment
and it was inside of his mouth but it was elevated.
Yikes.
We had the Chuck E Cheese where I grew up in San Jose.
There was one of the Chuck E Cheese, they're big,
the band but there were like tunnels under,
the band was elevated but you could crawl underneath
and like little mazes.
Whoa hold on a second, cancel the train talk.
Pull the car around.
This was a two story Chuck E Cheese.
Oh my god.
What?
Yeah, it was cause you could get very close
to these animatronics.
Wait what did the tunnels do?
They were just like little mazes, I don't know.
There's also a room that was just a strobe light
where kids could just like jump around and.
This feels so decadent it feels like God would be destroyed.
Yeah.
It was the strobe struck by lightning.
Could you watch the show from the tunnels?
No.
It was just there were his tunnels.
But it was always very scary going up that close to them.
They're frightening.
There was also the Elvis one, the hound dog
who would sing but he had like his own little lounge room
and you could sit in little stools in front of him
and the stools would bounce up and down like umpapa style.
You're telling me.
Like the Captain Eo seats, chairs that move along with.
Just stools but like add a little bar in front of the Elvis.
You're telling me that Jasper T. Jowls, the dog.
Yeah.
Had a special room where you would move.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Oh wait.
This is a hound dog.
Oh wait you're right, you're right.
Elvis themed.
There were other bands.
Yeah.
That's why it's gonna take us a year
to get through Chuck E. Cheese.
I sent you that picture of like all the Chobas pizza
characters, were some of them held over?
I don't know.
Cause what were the boys, there was the Beach Boys parody.
There was a Beach Boys group, were they like the Beagle?
I think they were all dogs.
There was an Elvis dog, there were Beatles dogs,
there were Beach Boys dogs.
I have a memory of Gorillaz too.
I think I thought the Beach Boys were Gorillaz
but I think the Gorillaz were something different.
It is funny to me like it's an Elvis parody
for kids in the 80s and 90s who wouldn't really,
would kind of know who Elvis was.
And then you know all the Looney Tunes and syndication
or stuff where like there's cartoon Marx brothers
or cartoon Humphrey Bogard.
James Cagney, everyone's favorite.
James Cagney, what a good reference.
Well like our kids 50 years from now
when you mentioned The Rock, are they gonna know
what the hell we're talking about?
That's true, no.
Yeah, will they know Ninja and like the Dolan twins
more than The Rock?
Like what are they worried about?
We have like on the Guardians ride,
if one of these actors does something crazy,
pulls a Jussie Smollett, you know what I mean?
What are you gonna do?
I wonder if they have, the people in the world
has not like really had to reckon with this in a big way.
Right.
Yeah, I don't know what, and well,
and you know what we're coming up on is like,
wait although is Depp fine?
What do we determine about this?
He seems like a piece of shit,
but it seems like he skated by for this vlog.
Well, because he hasn't been convicted of anything.
Yeah, right.
But we heard he's, I'm fuzzy on Depp.
Is it bad, is he supposed to be no more Depp?
Well, yeah, I think there's a feeling.
Unless you're JK Rowling,
which he's totally on board with him,
I think everyone else is a little bit like distance.
And we all know she's been making very good judgment
on him lately.
Oh, yeah.
JK Rowling.
If I could describe JK Rowling in two words,
it would be normal and the second word would be regular.
Yes, just like my poops.
Yeah.
But it's something they may have to reckon with,
I mean I guess in that case they just remove,
maybe that's easier to just remove a robot.
Just with a hammer a couple of times,
that's all you gotta do, just make them look different.
Look like a different.
Bash him into a different facial structure.
I have here, I believe this is the character
you're referencing maybe.
That looks like him, yeah.
King was a lion.
Oh, a lion.
A nine foot tall animatronic lion named The King.
Nine, wow.
That's what it says on the showbiz pizza wiki.
And I just, when I go to the tiki room,
hearing that clicky clacky on the end
brings me right back to that,
because you could hear these were not smooth.
Are you kind of fond of the clicking?
I love the clicky clacky in the tiki room.
It's so like, it's a true, talk about time capsule,
it's a true time capsule.
Maybe that's my version of liking the clicks and pops
on vinyls, you know?
Exactly.
The way they used to do it.
It's better with deafeningly loud hydraulic sounds.
I know there's stuff at Disneyland that has changed
and will continue to change over the years,
but if they took out the clicking and clacking
of the tiki room, I think the cognitive dissonance
would just drive me insane.
How do they dampen the clicking?
Don't ever, don't dampen the clicks.
Don't dampen the clicks.
Hashtag don't dampen the clicks.
I have one request from the audience.
If you live in Ohio, a king cat exists
at Jungle Jim's grocery store in Fairfield, Ohio.
What?
However, it seems to be in poor condition.
The king can be seen in left corner
in the back of the dining area in the showroom.
So if you live near Jungle Jim's grocery store
in Fairfield, Ohio, please send us a photo
of this animatronic.
This grocery store sounds like a paradise.
I agree.
There's a restaurant with a lion in the back of it.
I agree, I don't know anything else about it.
Also, if they have cans of Skyline Chili, send us some.
I hear it's not as the same as getting it in the stores,
but you know.
Yeah, don't send a meal.
Don't mail us a fresh from the restaurant Skyline Chili.
Maybe Jason.
Well, yeah.
That'll keep.
How long?
Eight days.
Chili keeps.
They would eat it on the trail.
If there's one person listening who lives
a couple blocks away from the Fairfield grocery store
and is now feels like.
This is our mission.
This is a call to action.
But I flash to they get too excited.
They like, I'm going there right now.
Speed out of the car, get T-boned by another car.
Oh God, don't put that on us.
No, I don't.
Jeez.
Someone's been watching Vice too much.
Be safe is all I'm saying.
I'd be excited too if my local grocery store
had a call to arms related to it.
It might not be there, honestly.
Who knows when that Wikipedia was last updated.
Or they'll get there right as it's leaving
and the person can go, wait.
They're just ripping the head off.
All right.
Make the incision.
I was gonna say, I will offer a free
lifetime Patreon subscription if you send us the head.
Whoa.
In general, if we get sent any robot heads,
you're in for free.
Yeah, but it has to be a certificate of authenticity as well.
You can't, well no, I take that back.
If you can make a facsimile of any of our
beloved animatronics heads.
Who is making these certificates of authenticity?
Why are those authentic?
Yeah, that's a good point.
You can't make a certificate of authenticity.
That's a very good point.
It's a big thing in California.
You can't sell autographed books and stuff in California.
You can't sell that as this was autographed by the author
unless you have a certificate of authenticity.
But I don't understand how you do that.
Can't you just forge that?
Yeah.
There's a man named Authenticus who sits on a tall throne
and he does all of the stamping.
Authentic inauthentic.
So if you don't pass the Authenticus test.
It's interesting, all our democratic rules.
What a terrible job.
It seems so boring after a while.
It was fun the first few years.
That's how living.
I gotta find something else,
but it's hard when your name's Authenticus.
You get tied into a certain line of work.
Term limits and torts and bills and laws,
but we still honor Authenticus.
We've all agreed.
Yeah, hey, some systems just work.
Yeah, that's true.
He'll teach his son, Authenticus Jr.
He'll change horses in midstream.
He's 150 years old.
How long have we been talking?
Do we need to get back to the trains?
Yeah, I would like to get back to the trains.
Where are we at?
Oh, we've been doing about an hour and five.
Okay, great.
We still got plenty of train time.
What else?
Since the 2000s,
the trains have been running on biodiesel.
They used to just run on diesel.
The Disneyland Railroad now runs on biodiesel.
I do love that smell.
The smell of the fuel.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Am I crazy?
No.
That's part of the atmosphere of the park.
You can't tell when you go by the Autopia
because it smells like just pure gas,
but other than that, you can smell.
Oh, also the cabin, the burning cabin,
doesn't burn anymore.
No. No.
You used to see that now.
It used to be because it was attacked by Indians.
And then as someone knocked over a lamp,
and now everything's fine.
They changed the story of life.
It was an attack zone, and then it became just an accident.
They were under an Indian attack, yeah.
There was a lot more Pawnee kind of crap in Disney,
and the burning of the town,
and the armory and stuff.
Yeah.
And Zorro would come in once in a while.
Zorro would show up sometimes.
The guy who played Zorro would come and help.
Help?
Like nodding pots in the bathrooms?
Yeah, yeah, he would operate a ride or two.
Oh no.
Two per car, please.
Quit slicing Z's into the customers.
Come on.
Yeah.
How else would you know he was there?
I didn't know the train used to be,
there were two different,
so they used to be able to run two at once,
and you could either get on at Main Street,
or get on at Frontierland,
but you were taking it all the way around.
It was a round trip, and light off.
You would have preferred that.
I mean, I think that would, it sounds fun.
You didn't have a choice.
You didn't have a choice,
and then eventually they stopped,
like okay, no, it's one track,
we're gonna run multiple trains on one track,
and you're gonna be able to get on and off.
But I didn't realize when they introduced E-tickets,
the train was always the highest level ticket.
The train was an E-ticket until 1982,
when they got rid of it.
All the way to the end, really?
Yeah.
That's why I didn't realize that.
The trains weren't even like a novelty form
of transportation back then.
It would be like, here's a bus ride for us,
you know what I mean?
That's true.
People probably took the trains
a lot more than we do now.
Yeah, but I think they have always been expensive
to maintain.
I suppose so.
A lot of moving parts.
I guess people weren't taking old timey trains.
That's what E-tickets going for,
is old polish and brass.
See that brass?
Yeah.
Most steam trains, I think, are not existing in the world.
That's a rare form of train these days.
Which is like, they need to be maintained
by people who know what they're doing.
I remember there's a whole talk of when
they were gonna do the Star Wars,
what was gonna happen to the people
that operate the train,
because they're like some of the only people
that know how to maintain a steam train.
You can't just furlough these very valuable,
specific knowledge sources.
Right, so they had them telling you about the train
if you wanted to walk over there.
Which we did a few times.
To give them something to do?
So if you walked over by the trains when it was down,
they would be just like wandering around.
Usually I think all they would do
is help you pull the thing to make the whistle.
The whistle was a thrill to pull the whistle.
Did you do that in your photo shoot?
I did it a number of times.
I can't remember if we did it in the photo shoot.
I don't think we have a picture of the whistle.
I think we were concentrating more inside the train itself.
Yeah.
Because the whistle, we were talking about the whistle
on the other side of the station.
Yeah, they had a solo whistle just set up separate.
What else?
The caboose, okay, so you can still ride the caboose
is sometimes on the tracks.
I've never gotten to ride and I've tried multiple times.
The Lily Bell, which is the restored parlor car.
And did you guys know who the first person
to ever ride in the Lily Bell was in 1976?
Is it Nixon?
Emperor Hirohito of Japan.
Wow.
Putting the past behind us.
Building bridges, mending fences.
Did he give it an emperor's kiss?
I can only imagine, I can only assume.
I wonder if they felt like,
well, American technology is really far behind.
Yeah.
This is the best they got.
I was not impressed from my trip.
Yeah.
Crush the Americans.
We have nothing to worry about.
Yeah, have you asked to do the Lily Bell?
I've, like, I always heard that if you went to City Hall
first thing in the morning and you ask,
is the Lily Bell running?
And if it wasn't, if it was on the tracks
and it wasn't scheduled for a special event or VIP,
you could get a ticket for it.
Now I've heard if you have to go to Main Street Station
and talk to the employees if you can do it.
And then I feel like I've also heard
it's been relegated to the tours,
to the additional tours.
I think maybe Club 33 gets you on there too.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I can't just have anybody walking on that,
like, spilling a drink.
No, it's filled with like beautiful memorabilia,
Disney family photos.
That's too, yeah, like this, right?
That's it? Yeah.
Yeah, it looks really nice.
I rode in when I did my VIP tour last year.
I rode in a different car, but not the Lily Bell.
You rode in an inside car?
An inside car, yeah. Oh, really?
There was only a few people in there.
Oh, what was in it?
Just some benches.
Was it the caboose? Different benches.
No. What's that?
Was it green? Yeah.
I think that's the caboose.
Yeah, we rode in the caboose.
I have pictures of me alone in that from another time.
Why were you alone?
Alone in the caboose.
Well, no, I was with someone, but they took the picture.
I am solo in the picture, looking like a pig and shit.
I like the idea that you just set up a camera
with a timer and you were alone in the caboose.
Alone in a caboose could be like a great one-man show.
Oh, kidding?
Yeah, what brought you there?
Are you gonna get out?
Are you there to kill yourself?
Suck in trained fumes until you die?
That's the theme, though.
Oh, yeah, couldn't do it anymore.
That's too bad.
Not a good place to kill yourself.
Yeah, that Lily Bell, that looks nice.
They really should do some insane high-end event
because sometimes they'll do like a,
give us $1,000 and you can eat breakfast
by the hippo at the Jungle Cruise.
Finally.
Yeah, we've all been asking for it.
There was a Haunted Mansion version, though.
There was a dinner.
There was a full dinner in the portrait hallway.
Do you think they'll ever have,
I want $1,000, I'll give you 10 grand
and I want an actor playing Walt Disney.
Just to walk you around the park?
Yeah, will they ever have a Walt Disney character
walking around, do you think?
I don't know.
I think that's dicey for them.
It's a good idea.
It's the divide between the family, the estate.
The estate's its own little thing
that works in cooperation with the corporation,
the Walt Disney Company.
The Walt Disney Company has their version of Walt
and then the family has their version of Walt
and then they're both very protected.
Yeah, I mean, it's interesting because he is now
heavily marketed everywhere in the park.
Clothes and prints and posters.
Quotes he didn't say.
I love flying drones.
Mr. Gorbachev, tear down this wall.
Yeah, but so it is all.
I love Kesha.
All you need is love.
Yeah.
Purple rain.
I only wanna see you standing in the purple rain.
They should do some mashup shirts of Walt Disney,
like make him look like Doctor Who or something.
Great.
Yeah.
Ooh, yeah.
Yeah, or him with Star Wars Kai.
That makes more sense.
Him with probably property saber and stuff.
Sure.
Right?
Yeah.
You just figure him like in the conduct,
because he would put on the train guy outfit
and he would drive the trains around
even though he was not a train engineer or fireman,
which are the two positions that.
Was he that barman who like derailed the train maybe?
Oh man.
Like he was wearing a disguise
and that's why they never saw that man again.
Whoever that guy was.
I would love a Walt shirt where he,
with just a word bubble that says like,
I fucking love trains.
Walt.
What is this, Disneyland?
Too edgy.
Taking something good and making it seem weird and perverse.
Whoa.
Got him.
Whoa, David Lynch over here.
What would Banksy call a Universal Studios scary ver,
Doom-a-versal studios?
Yeah.
Uh, yeah.
Studios, I don't, I'm gonna have to.
I can't, I'm too tired.
Doom-a-versal works pretty well.
Say that for now.
We should do a Disneyland episode as well.
I don't think there are any critters at Universal.
Are there?
Well, I was thinking about that.
Those were kind of critters, but not anymore.
Now are there any?
Do you consider the Minions critters?
No.
Okay.
I feel like a critter has to have furry.
What about Woody Woodpecker?
Yeah, see a big presence in Orlando.
I've never been to Orlando.
I've never been to Disney World.
Everyone says Disney World's bigger than Disneyland.
Like, I don't care.
It's certainly bigger.
You don't believe him.
I don't believe him, sounds like a myth.
What I think is that swamp air's getting to your brain.
You're just humid, that's all you know.
Nothing could be bigger than Disneyland.
That doesn't make any sense.
I don't need the castle to be bigger.
It's not about the size.
Sure, I hear that.
It's about the charm.
It's about the tarps covering it
while it's getting repaired.
So mynicechat.com can complain about the rest.
There's real problems in the world, you know.
Then a rusty shingle.
Maybe that's what's good for you.
If we stay mad about these little things,
then we don't have to be mad about the bigger things
that we can't control.
Well, maybe we should rise up and tear down against these.
It's time to move on from childish things.
We could still be mad about shingles, though.
All right.
We'll do a shingles episode, too.
You know, Walt, would you be allowed
to dress as Walt in the park?
Oh, I saw, in Tokyo, during Halloween time,
there were a couple people dressed as Walt for Halloween.
Really?
You were in Disneyland with Walt?
Yes.
Walt Cosplayers.
I sent somebody a photo of it, I think.
That's kind of like dapper days, isn't it?
Because that's all, you could just.
You could get away with disembodied Walt for sure.
Yeah, it might not be clear what you are exactly,
but you would know.
Your little pencil thin mustache.
Is there an iconic Walt costume?
How do you be him?
Well, somebody with the statues, I guess.
The person in Tokyo was painted like the statue.
Wow.
Like copper?
Yes.
Like somebody you'd see over outside the movie theater
in Burbank doing a dance or something.
Which I see regularly.
I see Lumiere regularly over in Burbank
doing a dance outside.
What?
Yeah, a person dressed sort of like Lumiere with lights.
There's also a full on rave light,
bodysuit man that dances, too.
I gotta say, for as sleepy downtown Burbank,
as normal as Burbank can be, the buskers are very odd.
There's a guy I've seen in front of the AMC,
he will sing along to music,
but they're not the karaoke tracks of songs.
They're the full.
Oh yeah.
And he just sings over the actual singer.
Yes, sure.
There's a lot going on.
Yeah.
It's jarring.
It is the nightlife in Burbank.
You wouldn't think, but on a Friday and Saturday,
that place gets going.
You could get saved in front of a Skechers.
That's true, too.
Sure.
You find Christ, then you go eat raw cookie dough.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, a little too much.
Too much.
That cookie dough business, I give them a year.
I, I-
Does a cookie dough business?
Yeah, you just eat raw cookie dough.
It's like an ice cream parlor, but with just cookie dough.
They will mix it with ice cream,
which Mike has said is much better than just the raw cookie.
I have, yes.
Is it good?
No.
It's much better than something else, but still not good.
Jason, I'm both excited.
A friend of mine had said, cause I was saying,
oh, they're opening this cookie dough place in Burbank.
He goes, not, it's not good.
Whatever it is, he goes, it's,
cause they have, this has been popping up around America.
It's cookie dough places, much like ice cream.
You'd see, oh, M&M cookie dough or whatever,
sprinkles cookie dough.
And I went in there and I ate a little bit of it
and I was like, oh my God, no, like it's too much.
Too much sugar.
It's way too much sugar.
Too pure.
Too rich.
It's not like, cause some cookie dough is,
they like treat it beyond what regular cookie dough would be.
Yeah, well there's no eggs.
You can't, you know, they remove the eggs.
Yeah, so that, so it's just,
I can't imagine it's gonna last.
It's like,
But it has been popping up,
the different places have been popping up.
We better do the episode soon then.
Shut your mouth.
Two hours on a cookie dough place?
Yeah.
That's fine.
I imagine we could do it.
I can't handle, like, I don't really like liquor neat.
Like I need ice or soda water or something.
And I think maybe you were saying if you add ice cream
and they mix the ice cream with the cookie dough,
it helps a little, but.
Add liquor, man.
I mean, maybe if you add liquor.
Add some tequila to that peanut butter dough.
Sure.
Swirl your sprinkles.
Yeah.
It would be fun if on the train they could,
like if you could have like an old fashioned
or like a Manhattan.
Yeah.
Or the ultimate.
Or even a Saks-Barilla or something.
Oh yeah.
They need a little selection.
That's like any ride you can comfortably eat on,
eat and drink and like put your feet up.
Well they do let you, don't they?
They do, they can take you up.
They don't really bother you.
I'm eating popcorn on there.
They're not supposed to, but I don't think they say anything.
What are they gonna do, throw me off?
Sure.
I dare them to try.
I'll go on something else.
You know, I got this tattoo.
Never gotten to the front of the line at Big Thunder Mountain.
Do you always show it?
I don't consciously go, um, but I don't not show it.
But if you have, let me ask you this,
while walking up, have you rolled your sleeve up before?
Well, usually I run hot.
So I always got short sleeves on generally always that.
Sure.
What if it's a real chilly winter day though?
Then I know I won't make a point to show it.
Not if I'm wearing a comfy hoodie or something.
I would if I were you.
I would really like make a show.
At least maybe get a sticker.
Do you get remarks from the employees?
Never.
Really?
Yeah, nothing.
I get more when I wear a button with a birthday.
They're just not noticing it then.
They must.
You're being too modest.
I guess.
I don't want to be in your face.
I think one day, yeah, the next time you go,
really lay it on thick.
I just wear a shirt that says like,
ask me about my Disneyland tattoo.
Sure.
Oh yeah.
And a big arrow pointing to where it is.
Yeah, yeah.
I would hope.
Yeah, you deserve more.
Then they'll give you a drink on the train.
You deserve more for doing that.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
Show some respect.
They're a plucky mom and pop operation.
I'm supporting them.
They need you as a customer.
So I think we'd be remiss if we didn't talk about how.
For years, the Disneyland Railroad was sponsored
by the Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway.
And as such, the locomotives are named
after the former heads of this rail company,
CK Holiday.
We'd be so remiss.
I can't tell you how remiss we'd be.
E.P. Ripley, Fred Gurley, Ernest S. March,
and the one outlier, the most recent train,
named after former Disney employee, Ward Kimball.
Ward Kimball and Ollie Johnson, of course.
The man who expressed the concern about.
The cattle car.
The cattle car being dangerous.
Train enthusiasts, Ward Kimball and Ollie Johnson,
helped learn about trains and the train community
and rebuilding trains and that sort of thing.
Is it like, truly, I feel like the rides aren't sponsored
like they used to be anymore.
Like FedEx presents Space Mountain.
You know what I mean?
Duracell used to be Star Tours.
It's not as often.
Ziploc just started sponsoring Splash Mountain.
I don't like that, that seems cheap.
What a cheap product.
But they have bags to put your little stuff in.
That's why you get the bags now.
You get a little bag.
A hack my family's been doing for years.
Well before the sponsorship.
I just feel like Ziploc doesn't go,
Ziploc feels plasticky.
But Critter Country feels like.
Zippity doo dah.
Are they taking advantage of that?
Are they doing Ziploc?
Zippity doo dah?
I guess so.
Just occurred to me now,
but it would make a lot of sense, right?
I guess Ziploc feels more like a Tomorrowland product.
The House of the Future type of a thing.
It is an amazing innovation.
Yes.
I'm still blown away by Ziploc bags is what I'm saying.
That feels like a first year Disneyland attraction.
Like, zip bags, zip the bags of the future.
Come to Zipland.
You can play with one, not take home.
You can just look at one and handle it
and then put it back.
All right, you've had your time.
Five minutes, give it back.
A better splash mountain than the sponsor of like.
Like cow hide or something?
Logs, firewood.
Dura Flame?
Dura Flame, sponsor of Splash Mountain.
Dura Flame is good, yeah.
That's great.
Can you get a little piece of wood on the way out?
I always do.
I give you wood.
No.
That's all right.
But that's a pretty good deal if you come back to you.
I mean, you have to like have the patience
to carry a log out of Disneyland with you.
Yeah, but I mean, it's a free log.
People buy clocks and like things.
Yeah, that's true.
People buy framed art.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But not quite as heavy as a log.
Sorry, just to correct myself.
Emperor Hirohito rode in the Lily Bell in 1975, not 1976.
Oh my God.
Didn't you say he was the first?
He was the first.
I'm still writing your letter.
Yeah, he was still the first.
Still the first.
Just off by one year.
And who is the, who's Zeus in Hercules again?
Riptorn.
Okay, just making sure.
And did you have a train conductor's hat?
Jory's still out, but leading towards the end.
We should do recaps more often.
Scott, this is, you know, the current train stations
were not always the train stations.
Of course, there was the Frontierland station.
For a brief time, there was the Videopolis station.
Oh, you know it, a little extension of Videopolis.
Little extension.
Which there wasn't, there used to be a Fantasyland one
that disappeared entirely, and there just wasn't a stop
up there for a long time.
But I think in the effort to have all the trains
running at once, they're like, well, we need more stops
to make that possible.
So you got a little extra Videopolis.
It wasn't like quite, there wasn't much aesthetically
going on, but I just like seeing that word
in a second place.
My favorites, the Disneyland 80s dance club.
Oh.
That they put up to get the MTV crowd.
That MTV crowd.
Yeah, yeah.
So when they built Toontown, did they reroute the track?
I think they, well, you go under the train, right?
So I think they just put foam rubber up
over the Videopolis station, essentially.
Oh, no.
I think it's the same station.
The track's been rerouted a number of times
over the years.
But they try to not do it.
That's one of those Disneyland 101 things,
that the train sits atop the berm,
and there's a lot of stuff you can do
construction-wise at Disneyland,
but you can't really move that berm.
So that's why Indiana Jones, you gotta walk
all the way under it, and a lot of the rides out there,
same with Pirates on a Mansion, with Star Wars,
pretty significant that they had to move the train track.
There's a left turn now, the first left turn.
There is now a left turn.
Now a left turn.
This is not what Walt intended.
There was.
Yeah, that's getting the mice chatters.
That was an aggressive response that people had
when this news was announced,
because they were gonna shorten,
or shrink Tom Sawyer's Island a little bit,
and then now the route was gonna go
in front of the Rivers of America,
and people were fit to be tied.
They were so upset about this,
because they thought they were gonna lose the island.
They thought that this was gonna make
the whole thing short.
They thought Mark Twain was now maybe not even gonna happen,
or it was gonna be two minutes long,
and they were all wrong.
It's beautiful.
It's better.
It's really good.
It's honestly better.
Yes, it's a Disneyland enhancement.
The first time you and I took that,
brought the new train, that was a great day.
That was, I was legitimately impressed.
It is prettier, there's new stuff.
It's so much more scenic.
Yeah, yeah.
I love those canoes,
because I didn't do the canoes for the first time
until a couple years ago,
and you see more critters than you've ever seen before.
Yeah.
There's all sorts of critters.
A murder beaver.
He was chewing on one of the posts,
holding up the train bridge.
That's fun.
Yeah.
Good for him.
That's easy.
That's a critter I love.
Maybe that's my next tattoo, the murder beaver.
Ooh, yeah.
That's a good one.
He's industrious.
Yeah.
He doesn't give a shit about your infrastructure.
And he's protecting his beavers.
He's providing for his family.
Yeah.
Yeah, you have to respect that.
All of those bodies will soon be in the water
for his family to eat.
He'll take their wallets.
Oh, yeah.
And their watches.
I don't know what good money is for beavers,
but shiny coins.
I love a shiny coin.
Yeah, that's a cool thing for them to build a nest out of.
What does a beaver in?
Do you guys go to Tom Sawyer Island?
Not really.
No.
I think it's a hidden gem.
Yeah.
There's scary things in it.
There's more caves, more tunnels.
Well, it's kind of piracy still, right?
Or it's pirates lair at Tom Sawyer Island.
Yes, I guess it's not Tom Sawyer, Tom Sawyer.
Tom Sawyer.
I saw it.
When he can't make it to the bathroom,
he's a Tom Sawyer.
When he gets too scared.
Yeah.
Tom Sawyer Island is still in Orlando,
and Aunt Polly's, the restaurant on Tom Sawyer Island
has reopened up.
They do like sandwiches and stuff on the island.
They do pretty simple PB&J and pulled pork sandwiches.
Yeah, you gotta enjoy it now.
There's a restaurant on the island.
I mean, I love a restaurant on an island in general.
Sure?
The restroom on Tom Sawyer Island should be Tom Sawyer.
There you go.
That would be good.
That makes sense.
And then it's still male Tom Sawyers
and female Tom Sawyers.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let me gripe real quick.
Yeah.
Why aren't all the cars,
why aren't all the seats in all of the cars facing out?
Exactly.
Right, because some of them face forward.
Right, so no drivers in those.
Exactly, so it's such a bummer
when you're waiting for the train
and the front facing ones pull up.
Oh, I don't know about that.
What are you talking about?
Well, it's a different experience.
It's a worse experience.
It's a hurt your neck.
I wanna turn to my right.
No, thank you.
I'm sitting forward.
Of course, if you go way to the left
and you're trying to see primeval world,
like how, that's a pain.
Well, maybe that trip you just enjoy
the wonders of real travel.
Wait, are you telling me no bit
that you don't get a little disappointed
when you get the Disneyland train with a car
that has the front facing seats?
No, because I've gone a lot.
Whatever pulls up, I gets in.
That's what life has provided and you will accept.
I guess that's a Zen way of thinking about it.
Very Buddhist.
But it's bad.
They should have them all front facing.
I don't know why you would ever want to.
I would not be upset if they replaced them all,
but I don't mind terribly.
I wonder if they just fit more people
with the front facing ones.
What's that?
I wonder if they just fit more people in that way.
I don't know how that works.
That might be right, but who cares?
At the very least, they should give you guns or something
to interactive shoot things.
It should be like Buzz Lightyear on the train.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That was a pretty good plus up.
Yeah, it gets, I don't want to shoot a critter,
but maybe some guys, a bandit of some sort,
a Billy the Kid, an outlaw.
Would you be comfortable shooting a dinosaur?
If it's attacking me.
Okay, if it's an aggressive, so the train goes really close
to a, you're kind of looking at some pterodactyls
in the distance, then all of a sudden,
ah, there's one right in front of your face.
If there's a triangle with a neon lit up triangle on it,
I'm gonna shoot that fucker.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you only see triangles.
I've been on Buzz Lightyear,
because when I went with my nephews,
they were like, it was one of the only rides they could do,
because they were like three,
so I've done it like 10 or 20 times,
and so I know where all the hidden things are.
Oh yeah, the one that's not lit up in the tunnel.
Yeah, the ceiling ones, and yeah, yeah,
I like to think I'm pretty good at it.
Sure, sure.
What if you could like, if you like hit a big target
that made like a big boulder, or that made the asteroid fall.
Oh, that'd be fun.
Crush the dinosaurs.
That'd be good.
That'd be created the Grand Canyon.
Uh-huh. There you go.
The biggest target creates the Grand Canyon.
Man, I mean, that would be great.
I still, would I trade, would I still be okay
with the front-facing seats if I got guns?
I'm still trying to think about it, I guess.
I don't know, because if you're in the middle with the gun,
I feel like you're never gonna,
you're not gonna get anything.
It would be great if you were facing out and had guns.
What if they added a monitor on every car
that had Jimmy Fallon in it?
Doing like a fun bit or something.
Okay, all right.
I've always loved trains.
I've definitely, for sure, way before this,
loved trains the best.
Yeah, now I'm seeing it and I'm loving it in my head.
Oh, seeing him in a little conductor uniform.
Yeah, he'd be great.
Oh, he'd be like so sharp.
The choo-choo song.
I saw a video where Rami Malek touches his hand,
like Jimmy Fallon's hand, and he flinches.
I think he does not like being touched
or he doesn't like his hand being touched.
Look it up.
All right, we'll look that up.
Is it still sensitive from when he had his accident?
Well, he kept having like three,
like he fell down three times, right?
Yeah, but he got the ring caught on the counter,
I think is what that story was.
Was he just like, pretty drinking too much?
He eyed away.
All he had was a vodka drink, then a whiskey drink,
then a lager drink, then a cider drink.
All right.
He's too 90s nostalgic.
He takes too many ideas from old songs.
Yeah.
Speaking of train drunkenness,
the video of when they reopened the train
and they had Lasseter in a conductor uniform.
Oh no. Jesus Christ.
That's not an image we need.
Because he was sort of like,
he was kind of the PR guy for the train thing
and really just selling, the train's a big part of Disney
and we're so excited the train's back.
But that was like the first that I was like,
something's up with the Lasseter.
That was your first red flag?
He's so red and so puffy.
Well, because he bought a train
that I think Ward Kimball used to own
and they put it on the track for the grand opening,
this other train.
He's a train weirdo too,
because in that documentary about his house,
he's got a train going in and out of his room.
I feel like you can't be into trains and Hawaiian shirts.
It's one or the other.
Too many train things.
Too many red flag things.
Too many, it's unsettling.
Either trains or...
And then also working animation, no, no, no.
What if, maybe you could be into like Tiki stuff, right?
That's totally fine.
Honestly, isn't Tiki just cultural appropriation
on every level?
That's a thing I've talked about.
I like it, I have a couple over here.
But I don't disagree with what you're saying.
I know.
I feel like you just even putting this out there
is gonna make it bad, so maybe we should cut this out.
Okay, cut it out, cut it out.
No, no, it won't cut it out.
Tiki will be over once this podcast,
the right episode comes out.
We just killed it?
Yeah, it's over.
Tiki's canceled.
Trader Sam's just become Sam's.
It's just an old guy.
Hi, welcome. From Cheers?
Yeah, it's just Sam from Cheers.
Can I get you a LaBats?
Is this a fake memory I have?
I remember the final episode of Cheers.
Sam takes off his toupee.
Is this a memory that I've made up in my brain?
I thought he just turned the lights off.
He hangs it on the light switch and then turns it off.
This might be one of the stuff,
sometimes you dream things and then you keep remembering
for so long you forget that it was sourced from a dream.
Yeah, I think I've made it.
Ted Danson, we're talking Ted Danson's character.
I have this vision, it's in front of Carla.
And it's like the bar is closed
and it's like a vulnerable moment
that he takes off his toupee.
Well, I don't think it's the last scene or anything,
but maybe it happened.
What about the end of the series?
I've always thought of Ted Danson
as having a very thick head of hair.
Because I know, I've looked it up on YouTube,
couldn't find anything, so maybe I'm insane.
That sounds familiar, but I don't know that that's a,
I found a pic, here's Sam holding hair.
That's just a hairy found in the bar.
He's just doing a DNA test.
I think you're mixing stuff.
Maybe you're mixing things up.
I might be mixing things up.
She's like shocked.
Yeah, he has his hair still in that.
All right, all right, maybe I'm just mixing things up.
I usually don't like to share dreams I had,
but I remember I shared on the show
a dream I had about booking hotel reservations.
This is a different dream I had last night.
I just remembered it.
It was that I was going into the Star Wars hotel
that's being built in Orlando
that's gonna be very immersive
and you won't even see any windows outside.
And it was so, the dream was so methodical and unpleasant
that they transported us to the hotel somehow with magic,
but then all of a sudden I had no clothes on
and we just got thrown into showers.
Whoa, Jesus.
Like a weird bio-Matrix type thing
where it's all of a sudden we're all nude
and going hustled somewhere.
Like 12 monkeys.
Yes.
Time travel.
No, no.
And I woke up with, I had a little headache
when I went to bed, but I woke up with a bad headache.
So I had a stress dream about a very realistic space hotel
that I went to and going through
what you would actually have to do to go to a space hotel
and get decontaminated before you went on a space station.
Too much attention to detail.
Yes.
Like all this stuff off camera that Poe Dameron
or Leia had to go through in A New Hope
where they are tortured off camera.
That is what you experienced.
Oh, and Han gets.
Oh, and Han, of course.
Yeah.
I think you were thinking Han gets tortured in a pair.
I don't acknowledge the actual terrifying torture
that happens to all of our favorite characters
when they're not swinging lightsabers around.
I hate to share a dream, but this is very quick and stupid.
Please.
I used to, I would be excited for movies.
I would dream them before I saw them.
And I was at the time very excited
for the Flintstones movie.
Who wasn't sure.
How are they gonna realize this?
What's it gonna look like?
I can't imagine.
But in my dream, the movie was a concert film
of Flintstones on ice.
And I was so disappointed.
Whoa.
I was like, that is the worst possible version
of the Flintstones movie was a concert film
of the Flintstones on ice.
Is Flintstones on ice real?
No, I don't think so.
Okay.
That's what I was wondering.
As we see, I have an active, inaccurate, imagined brain.
Well, I mean, there was at Universal Hollywood,
there was a Flintstones restaurant
for an obscenely long time.
Like when I first went in 2006, it was kind of a stand.
I think we all want that big ribs, those big ribs, right?
I guess that, yeah.
I did have ribs.
But there were so many sitting out in the sun,
just rotting away.
It was a gross restaurant.
And you'd walk by and you'd get hit with that smell.
You'd get hit with the bad barbecue smell.
There was a cloud of it, like just on the main hub
when you were walking in.
And it was by a midway, too.
It was by games and stuff.
Is this in Orlando?
No, it's here.
No, this was Hollywood.
It's the entrance, it's exactly where
Harry Potter entrance is now.
Oh.
It was this big Flintstones thing.
Wow, I missed that.
Flintstones on ice is just Fred eating the big rack of ribs
with no dialogue or music.
And then just sauce splattering on the ice.
Yells at Wilma to go away.
Trying to get some peace.
There would have to be little animals
as the skates, though, too, that were acting as the skates.
Oh, yeah.
Like an upside down baby stegosaurus or something.
Oh, no.
Jesus, like biting it with his teeth.
A baby?
He doesn't understand.
This is the most unpleasant Flintstones job.
A baby who's being crushed by a fat man
who's with his teeth just grinding.
But it's a living, Scott.
It's a living.
He says it with a lot more fear.
I guess it's a living.
My Pillsbury Doe Boy impression, too.
What else did we miss?
What else trains?
What did we miss?
The New Orleans Square Station plays
as the Morse code of the opening day speech.
Oh, yeah.
Set it.
Very good.
Hit us rapid now.
They traded one of the original train
called the Ward Kimball.
They traded to Cedar Point for a different item.
Oh, fact.
Yeah, items.
Item trades.
We've kind of skipped around Primeval World.
Can I say one more thing about it, which is,
I think it's,
is this just me or do you get this feeling
when you essentially watch some dinosaurs
just living their lives and then there's not enough water
and they're lapping it up in those kind of scary,
emaciated dinosaurs or trying to get the last few drops
and then scary Tyrannosaurus scene
and it feels very apocalyptic, like comets coming.
Do you get this vibe, because it gets so scary,
do you get this weird narrative feeling of like,
well, let that be a lesson.
The dinosaurs brought this upon themselves.
For us.
It's a lesson for us, not for them.
No, I think it's telling us
that these dinosaurs were fucked up
and they deserve what they're getting.
I was like dread from when I watched it.
What should the dinosaurs have done differently?
That's what I can't figure out.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
The dams, I guess?
Yeah, they wanna have more water.
They should have been beavers.
Well, most people should be beavers.
Yeah, I guess so.
Is there any way to do that?
I didn't know that the music that's playing
is from the movie The Mysterious Island,
which is a different movie than Island
at the Top of the World.
Both movies made by Walt Disney Studios.
Walt Disney Productions.
Well, we know where the island on the top of the world is.
It's on top of the world.
Mysterious Island could be anywhere.
Yeah.
Sorry, I prefer that one.
It's more open-ended.
There's a weird connection,
because it's a mysterious island
based loosely on the Jules Verne book,
an island at the top of the world
who was gonna be a big influence in Discovery Bay,
which got the lack of success for that movie.
I do love that music though,
because it has that 50s dramatic of like,
oh my God, there's dinosaurs.
But then post-Jurassic Park,
I feel we're more into the wonder.
It's either wonder or horror.
But the music in Primeval World
feels more spectacular.
Spectacular, yeah.
Kind of Godzilla-ish, a little bit.
Big, big old drums and kind of booming brass.
Oh my God, speaking of drums and dinosaurs,
then Jurassic Park, if they get rid of those drums
before the T-Rex drop,
you know in the Jurassic Park ride,
there are amazing, it's literally the drums going,
I see what you're saying.
If they get rid of those drums, I'm gonna be livid.
Don't know, don't know what the drum plan is.
Oh yeah, look, I'm on the Inside Universal message board
a lot, but there has not been a lot of talk about
the drums and will they stay.
The Jeep doesn't have to drop, just keep those drums.
That Jeep didn't work for a long time, I feel like.
That was, yeah, a very inconsistent Jeep.
But maybe, I would say let's put like
a Chris Pratt animatronic playing drums to really make,
like where's it coming from?
Where's that music coming from?
Oh, he's like rocking out, like he twiddles a drumstick
beforehand, he's real cool.
A mouse rat reference.
Yeah, from Jurassic Park.
Or Bryce Dallas Howard's there with her arms crossed,
shaking her head.
Yep.
Just like, get a load of him.
I hope there's a ton of Bryce Dallas Howard animatronics
and a ton of Chris Pratt animatronics.
It's just gonna be on screens.
Aaron, Aaron!
Do you want a little spoiler?
Yes!
Audience, spoiler alert, I probably said it
on the show already.
There's gonna be a dinosaur fight at the end now.
What?
It's T-Rex versus whatever that big one was
from the first one.
They're both real dinosaurs.
Oh, that's fun, yeah, I'm into that.
Real dinosaurs.
They're real, yeah.
They've gone mad!
They just made Jurassic Park?
It's actually over.
They've learned nothing!
Yep, and they just like have a collar around them
and they just pull them back each time.
That's not gonna work.
They said it's fine, they said it worked once.
They can't get a Jeep to work, they're gonna do this?
They need to beat Rise of the Resistance,
so they're just gonna open it and see what happens.
They just wanna beat them to the marketplace.
Make a real Indominus Rex.
Here's the thing I like on the train,
seeing into Splash Mountain.
Yes!
Because sometimes in the year,
Splash Mountain is closed for maintenance.
Well, it's not running with closed for maintenance,
but sometimes it's just too cold to ride Splash Mountain.
Right?
And I just wanna see the big riverboat.
I love that riverboat.
What a joyful, that's so muppety.
Yeah.
Very much so, absolutely.
Just a bunch of animals singing.
I don't like those cats though.
I find them unsettling.
They're a little, they're just weird, I don't know.
They just feel off to me.
Not critters.
Cats aren't critters?
Not in my book.
No, they probably are critters.
Cats are critters.
What if they're feral cats?
I would call those critters.
Yeah, I call them critters.
They should be.
But as soon as they're adopted,
they're no longer a critter.
Right, they're dead to us.
Well, you know how we could figure out what critters are?
What animals were the capital critters?
Oh my God.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Those rats?
Were they all rats?
A bunch of sharks, if Washington has any, in spaceship.
Well, we'll look up capital critters.
Are you looking up capital critters, Scott?
I am, but you know, I shouldn't just Google
and we'll figure it out later.
Yeah, we'll figure it out later.
We'll do our Patreon.
Capital critters episode.
Oh boy, I'm really scraping the bum, bro.
Capital critters and fish police.
Oh boy.
You know what, I also like that
Grand Canyon music when you come in.
Don't, don't, don't.
Oh yeah, that's like classic music, I think.
Real mosey.
Or it's, it's Bach.
Something like that.
Or I didn't recognize the name of it.
I'm not sure, I like that though.
That's one of those good.
I like that there's so much like 50s, 60s music
being played on kooky instruments
throughout Disneyland. Yeah, yeah.
And that's some of it.
It's like a radio, it's the music you would hear
in a radio play about a cowboy going down the trail.
Oh yeah, somebody going into some weird little
McMoman Pops shop, some weird little saloon
or general store or something.
That's gonna be some fiber.
What's that?
Raw fiber.
Using raw fiber.
It's what you'd hear when a cowboy was taking a load off.
Yeah, I need an empty jug.
Sure.
A little rope, a bindle.
There's some charts on a bunch of Wikipedia pages
about like transportation stuff has charts sometimes
of the routes.
Oh yeah.
And it was pointing out that like,
well technically you can disembark the train
and transfer to the monorail in Tomorrowland.
And vice versa, you could disembark in Tomorrowland
on the monorail and then get on the train
like you were, you know, transfer a bus to train.
A transfer.
And I thought that was very novel.
Yeah, if you take, all right, I'm taking the train
from New Orleans Square to Tomorrowland,
transferring to the monorail.
And going to Ralph Brennan's Jazz Kitchen.
Oh.
As far as Jazz Kitchen goes,
Ralph Brennan's got the best one.
Gotta be.
Certainly in the conversation.
I bet there's an emerald out there
that's giving him room for his,
in terms of labeled jazz, name labeled jazz kitchens.
Emerald Lagasse's Jazz Kitchen?
I bet there's one.
A blues patio?
I don't know.
Here's something for me to research.
Are the beignets better at the Ralph Brennan's quick service
than the New Orleans Square beignets?
I do love seeing just blasts of powdered sugar
on the ground around New Orleans Square
where you just see people just making a mess.
Sure.
I like those, I'm not a big fan of them,
alcohol-free mint juleps.
What's the point?
Yeah, it's just kind of a minty.
I might as well have that.
Mouthwash.
Yeah.
That's gotta change.
When Star Wars land rolls around,
we've talked about it too much.
Doesn't have to be all alcohol, right?
Isn't Orlando all Disneyland you can drink everywhere?
You can't walk around with it in Magic Kingdom.
There's some restaurants.
But there's a lot of restaurants
where you can get wine and beer now.
Is that some Christian scientist thing?
It's some weird message board, Walt wouldn't want stuff.
Walt loves it straight.
He wouldn't want Gay Days either, but we got that.
Sure.
Yes, but that was a fit.
Disney only officially recognizing it in the last year.
And people have snuck in alcohol for years.
And they still don't call it Gay Day.
They still are like, do they say even Pride?
It's unofficial.
And in fine print, it technically says,
you chose to be gay days.
Oh, I see.
But they've been marketing Rainbow a lot.
Jesus is crying day.
They've certainly merchandised it.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
My favorite is seeing straight guys
who accidentally wore red that day,
very aggressively holding their girlfriend's hands.
I've seen that a few times.
I once, actually, Andy Richter told me
that he did that one time.
He wore the Gay Day color and I had a Gay Day.
I feel like I heard that story too.
And he was down there with Andy Daly, with their kids.
And they're like, look at this beautiful couple.
That's a good couple.
Yeah.
Sure.
Oh yeah, but Walt, with that weirdness,
you know what Walt would want is to make a lot of money.
Yeah, right?
That's the number one thing Walt would want.
He would like to profit.
No unions.
Sure.
He'd be very happy with the pay structure, I'm sure.
Although maybe if Walt came back from the dead,
on Gay Day, saw that there was alcohol available
in one small section of Disneyland, in this one cantina.
In Ogres Cantina.
Which you have to get to past
the rearranged rivers of America.
He would go apeshit and start sawing down that train track,
just like the-
He'd be joining the Beaver?
Yeah.
Get me in on that entire train derails.
Bob Iger would not be allowed to drive the train nowadays
because of OSHA.
Like when the Mark Twain first opened,
they weren't sure how many they could fit on it
and almost capsized a couple times.
My God.
Because they tried to squeeze 500 people on it.
I think 300 is max capacity now.
If I look like I'm gonna be number 101,
I'm not getting all that thing.
Why do I wanna be crowded on a boat?
I mean, it is a leisurely boat ride.
But I don't wanna be packed like a sardine.
I wanna be able to walk around.
Of course, you wanna kind of a porch to yourself.
I wanna mosey.
Yeah.
What a strange-
I don't wanna be crammed onto the Mark Twain.
Sure.
You wanna feel like you're on that carnival shit cruise
or whatever.
Right?
What a hellscape.
I think they should bring back selling refreshments
on the Mark Twain.
That'd be fun.
That would be fun.
Even just chips and soda.
They should get them water guns.
Water pistols, they could shoot the crowd.
Oh sure.
Oh that's fun.
It should be nice to be refreshing a little bit.
I don't know why I have this 12 year old boy's idea.
It's harmless.
It's harmless, yeah.
When everyone gets a slingshot.
To tie it back to potential injuries
and Walt inflicting train injuries,
the one fact we missed
with the Sorted History of Train accidents
is that his backyard train, the Carroll Wood,
at one point derailed.
The derailing didn't hurt anybody,
but as it derailed, the steam thing broke.
And started just shooting steam,
hot steam copiously across his backyard
and a five year old girl got burnt in the leg.
And that was what made him go,
maybe I should run my train
in a more professional environment,
not just in my backyard.
But I feel like see, let someone else drive it, right?
Wasn't that part of it?
Oh maybe.
I don't think it was him.
It was that mysterious man again.
Oh no, that bar man.
The Walted of the skies, yeah.
Why do we keep letting that guy drive the trains?
The wood man.
But if that little girl hadn't gotten burnt,
maybe there wouldn't be a Disneyland.
Imagine how wealthy you'd be now
if you got scolded by Walt Disney.
I want half.
All right, fine, here.
Thank you.
What is it?
Or list which characters I own.
And Epcot, I want Epcot.
So do we have any other Sorted History?
Do we have any plus ups?
I mean I really like the plus ups that they've done.
And I really like that diorama
and the little plus ups to the diorama.
I want more little things to happen along the route.
Like not a ton, I don't want it to get gimmicky,
but little stuff happening along the train route.
The art-o-topia side is kind of disappointing.
Yes, that's the least.
That's kind of the worst stretch in terms of
unique little things.
Unless you're passing by a parade that's about to go,
which you can see some videos of.
And the wave at you.
Yeah.
The inside out characters or whatever.
You get a little private parade.
The forest could be thicker
as far as looking out onto normal land.
Sometimes you can see too much outside.
I don't care for that.
I want to be immersed.
So more trees if that's possible might not be possible.
Yeah, that's Star Wars forest.
And the forest dividing frontier land in Star Wars.
It's gonna take a few years for that to grow in.
Yeah, that needs to grow in a little more.
It takes time.
In 20 years maybe I'll be very satisfied
with the thickness of the forest.
Give it time.
But now I'm not.
I'm not happy with it.
I think more, add a couple more cars on
and let's get some of these,
let's get some drinks in there.
Let's get some premium experiences.
Like a gambling car.
Gambling, now you're talking.
Roulette.
Yes, a roulette car.
Now, yeah, Walton would not have wanted drinking
or gambling, but he's dead.
He's dead.
Welcome.
Yeah, let's get a high stakes poker game going on
in one of the cars.
Booby Girls.
Yeah, that's, let's do all of it.
I don't think that's their official title, but.
Close quarters.
They're like, yep.
Their butts are in your face.
Yep, that'll be, hello.
Well, they own FX now, so we could get a Fosse Verdun.
Oh.
Dying.
Or some rescue me cast members.
Oh man.
Are those like attractive actresses?
They save the train catches on fire.
The burning cabin.
Oh, they put out the burning, yeah, that's the.
Dennis Leary's rescue is putting out the burning cab,
that's why.
Available on Blu-ray.
Don't know what this is, look it up, kids.
The train is racing the Mayans Motorcycle Club.
Oh no.
Uh-oh, but the Sons of Anarchy are here to save ya.
Archer could be gambling and drinking on that train.
What would he say?
He's outrageous.
How about on the end of the train too,
one of those hobo things where you pull.
What do you call that, the two sided things.
Like a push cart or something?
Yeah.
And that would be like a sought after car.
Obviously you'd have to be harnessed in or something.
Maybe just have, you know what,
it might be too unsafe for guests.
So just have some hobo character actors on the back
doing that behind the train.
Yeah, but I wanna see it in action.
You wanna see it move, okay.
Yeah, I wanna see that, that's fun I think.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I just want that cabin on fire again.
Cabin on fire for sure.
Cabin back on fire.
And do some with Autotopia.
Are you a pro, get rid of it?
I mean, I never go on it.
Yeah.
Well it's, you will fuck your leg up as an adult,
or at least I do.
The last two times I end up so sore.
Oh yay, cause you have to push really hard.
And then you're like, you're weird and cramped.
Your leg is like so sore.
It is weird.
I guess it's for children or something.
It is for children who just wanna pretend
that they're driving.
And it always seems to be popular.
So I'm like, I'm one of those,
not everything has to appeal to me.
Yeah.
Like I'm okay if there's something there
that doesn't appeal to me.
But I don't know, it just does seem like,
it seems like very 90s now and just,
there's nothing nostalgic about it.
I mean, at least not to me,
but then if it's nostalgic to you,
if you were a kid when you first did it, I guess.
Can they like reduce the footprint?
Can they make it smaller like the Disney thing?
Are you probably getting a lot of money?
Yeah, I mean, it doesn't look very nice.
It smells bad.
You just go through trees.
It's noisy.
You're not plussing it up.
You just go through trees.
There's nothing happening.
I mean, that uses so much gasoline
and the subs use so much water.
It's not the most environmentally conscious area of the park.
Most wasteful area.
Should we just get rid of them and put in solar panels?
Sure.
Just a field of solar panels?
Yeah.
That's it and you just look at them.
Brought to you by AOC.
It was.
Oh, sure.
I don't want her values destroying the Disneyland I love.
Your values.
It was gonna go away when the first,
that supposed first round of Star Wars plans.
Oh yeah, it was gonna be a speeder bike through Endor.
What are they gonna do with Disneyland?
Yeah.
Oh my God, there's so much you could do there.
It was gonna be, Inventions was taken out
and then Autopia and it was gonna be a speeder bike
that went in and out and then over there
would be like the forest of Endor and you go through.
But it seems like Star Wars land is bigger than Tomorrowland.
Oh, well.
Is it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna try everything there.
Oh, I don't.
Cause if it's bigger than Hogwarts,
Hogwarts is probably about as big as Tomorrowland, isn't it?
You think?
Yeah, so Hogsmeade, most of them are about 12 acres
and the galaxy's edge is gonna be like 14 acres.
So it is bigger, it's bigger than Radiator Springs.
So pretty big.
Pretty big.
Let's talk about like Tomorrowland should be the next thing
to get redone.
I guess, yeah, what do you do?
Just a past version of the future?
We've said neon lights.
Something, yeah, neon.
Just neon lights.
Neon, tronny.
Like a troncoaster.
Like a shitty bar?
Sure.
Yeah.
Sure, yeah.
Fine, fine.
It's better than what they got now.
Dive Barland?
Okay.
Yeah, sure.
You're fine with that?
A like B minus Dive Bar is better
than a lot of Tomorrowland currently.
That's true, there's not much going on.
I just like Space Mountain and Star Tours.
There will be a time, I think,
and it probably won't be for 10 years,
but where you will just have one narrow walkway
to Space Mountain and everything else
is under construction.
My God, everything else is torn up.
Very much like California Adventure was for years.
Yeah, Star Tours gone, Buzz Lightyear gone, all of it,
and they'll do a full on reconceptualization of it.
They're building a restaurant in Epcot
that's like a space station.
You look at these massive high def screens
that look like you were eating in a space station.
That's fun, so maybe you spiral out from Space Mountain,
take inspiration from Space Mountain
and build out from there.
Well, what else is like?
Because in the line for Space Mountain,
you see the hubs and the other.
That's a good idea.
The problem is-
I guess it's like a mail,
it's like a post office, intergalactic post office.
I guess it is.
Is that what we wanna do?
You got a letter stamp from space.
You buy some stamps in space?
The problem is it'll be IP based, unfortunately.
They don't really have anything.
There's no good space IP.
Nobody cares about Tron.
But that coaster's good.
They built one in Florida.
Yeah.
So maybe we, and believe me,
the Jared Leto Tron reboot is coming.
With Jared Leto, who's he gonna be?
He's Flynn's, I don't know.
I'm a virus, he'll be a virus.
You arrive where you go to Mars in 30 seconds.
Very exciting.
That's the solution.
Well, anything else?
Plus ups?
I think we've completed the Grand Circle tour.
Wait a minute, we missed one big thing, y'all.
Your attention, please.
Disneyland limited.
How awesome is that?
That is like fabric of the park.
Yeah, the sound just transports you back there.
Scary for some reason.
Yeah, I know, I get a little weird dread from that.
It makes you feel like you're in trouble.
Yep.
I mean, it's cool that it's scary.
I like that it's scary, but it is scary.
It's a weird kind of scary man announcement voice.
Because it is like a quality of a voice
you'd hear in the Haunted Mansion or something.
Yep.
That's why it is one of the voices in the Haunted Mansion.
Who did it?
I was looking it up, I couldn't tell.
There's a guy named Jack Wagner
and there's a guy named Peter Rennaday
and there's conflicting information about which one it is.
Well, Jack Wagner was the guy
who called the voice of Disneyland for a lot of times.
Peter Rennaday, a very good voice imitator.
He was the guy who came up on 20,000 Leagues.
He was imitating James Mason.
Oh, gotcha.
And he's Mark Twain on the Mark Twain.
Yeah.
And he's Henry in the Country Bridge Embry.
I think it is Peter Rennaday, not Jack Wagner.
I was very disappointed at the internet's information
on this subject and I will not have this reflect
on my record.
It could be.
And I don't know, star rating on iTunes.
The information wasn't there.
It could be Rennaday doing Jack Wagner.
That's it, it's Rennaday.
Which is my guess.
They couldn't afford Jack Wagner.
No, I think he's long dead.
Maybe they blended the two, you know,
like Rey and Force Awakens, you know,
how they used all three.
They used like four different Ben Kenobis.
Or BB-8 is a bunch of people.
Crazy.
Ben Schwartz and Bill Hader.
Yeah.
And all of us, audience might not know,
we also, for episode nine we did some,
we can announce it, all,
Mike Jason and I all did some.
We're all BB-8 beep-a-booms.
We got paid with exposure?
That was a little weird to hear from JJ Abrams,
that like this will be great for you guys.
We're out of money.
You don't know how, like,
you might get a lot of other work doing bleeps and bloops.
Jason is BB-8 when he gets flustered.
Yeah.
Ah, son of a bitch.
Shit, god damn it.
But once you run it through the filters,
you can't tell it's swearing.
Yep.
Sounds just right.
So, what else?
What do you got?
No, I don't really have anything.
I like that voice and.
Your voice is fantastic.
Oh, well there's some fun YouTube videos
of train enthusiasts talking about the Disneyland railroad.
Oh, boy.
So, keep an eye out for them.
Wait, you said these were fun videos?
Some like nice old folks.
What's that?
I don't doubt that they're videos,
I just doubt that they're fun videos.
I think they're fun.
All right.
Because they seem to be really enjoying it.
They're having a good time.
They enjoy sharing their knowledge.
And yeah, train people seem to,
like they're connecting, like,
and then the original cars are at this exhibit
and this museum and this ranch and that sort of thing.
More knowledgeable than I am
about the full lineage of the train.
Jason, can I give you a quick Sophie's choice?
Better train Disneyland railroad or Casey Jr.?
Oh, I think it gotta go Disneyland railroad.
Okay, I thought it was gonna be Cumber.
Casey Jr. is pretty novel,
but you can't beat that Grand Circle tour.
Okay.
I once rode on Casey Jr. during the rain.
It was great.
In the train car.
And I've also been on it during the fireworks.
Oh, that's fantastic.
That was amazing.
I think you're right in the thick of it.
Yeah, it was great.
It's a nice little trip at night.
It felt like Mario Kart.
Yeah.
Oh, neat.
Like you just won.
I just won when I'm on Rainbow Road or something, you know?
So Casey Jr. during the fireworks
and Jason's tip, do a five quarters train trip.
Devote 25 minutes.
Be like Jason, five fourths.
Hey, I just realized,
is there a Casey Jr. sequence in the Tim Burton Dumbo?
I believe there is.
I don't know the details,
but they're selling a popcorn tub now.
Casey Jr. and Dumbo at Disneyland.
That seems like a dart.
We'll see.
Yeah, weird vibes around that one.
An hour and a half of it is the crows.
No!
Why did they do more crows?
They laid too hard in the wrong direction.
They locked the theater doors.
You can't leave.
Oh my God.
I keep watching those crows.
That's an unpleasant way to end, talk about those crows.
Do you know what's really funny is the,
let's get ready for Dumbo.
You heard that in an ad?
It's Michael Buffer.
This is, unless I'm dreaming it,
unless this is my dream.
Let's get ready for Dumbo.
I have not seen that.
That's wild.
Really bizarre.
Michael Buffer fans love the movies.
Is Buffer in it?
I don't know.
Might just be his voice.
Or they dub Michael Keaton with Michael Buffer's voice.
Or they just got it sound like,
pay him 50 bucks and then Michael Buffer is like,
could it be Peter Rennaday?
It's Peter Rennaday doing impression of Jack Wager,
doing impression of Michael Buffer.
Rennaday, you scamp.
You done it again, Rennaday.
You done it again.
Rennie, thanks for being here.
Mark Rennie, you survived, but gets the ride.
Thank you for having me.
This was a dream.
What I do know is real.
Yay.
Well, where can people find you?
Or exit through the gift shop?
Or what do you get to plug?
You can find me just at Mark Rennie,
Twitter and Instagram.
I don't post a lot, so it's not an imposition, I don't think.
I have a show if you're in Los Angeles,
May 12th, Mother's Day.
It's called Those Magnificent Moms,
but I host it with my actual mother
and it's a bunch of comedians doing bits
with their actual moms.
Oh, fine.
It's a good time.
Oh, great, great.
May 12th, 7.30.
Sure, yeah, it's a great show.
We'll play a little bit.
Unless you have, that's it for the plugs.
That's it, no more plugs.
Game of Thrones, Gay Thrones.
I do not write on Game of Thrones.
No.
I write on the Gay of Thrones.
Funny or Die's Gay of Thrones with Jonathan from Queer Eye.
Yeah, coming back soon
because the television show is coming back soon.
Yeah, I think our first episode will be the Monday
or Tuesday after the premiere.
Great.
Cool, yeah, fun show.
Us, Podcast the Ride at Gmail,
Podcast the Ride Facebook group.
We have a subreddit.
We have, what else?
We have shirts. Twitter and Instagram.
T-Public. T-Public.
Patreon.com slash Podcast the Ride.
A lot of fun, crazy crap on the Patreon,
McGruff, Music Career, you know,
a bunch of other stuff we did.
And wants to be a millionaire.
And please, if we missed any deep train info,
email us, all of it.
Train guys, you know what to do.
Yeah, yes.
We're certainly hearing from them.
Coming back.
Coming back to the station.
Everybody get off.
Choo-choo.
Forever Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason universo,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen, Joe Sileo,
and Alex Ramsey.
Engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.