Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast is a wild character crossover featuring favorites like Donald Duck,
Mickey Mouse, Ariel, Garfield's girlfriend Arlene, Jeffy from the Family Circus, and that
incorrigible Nimgaloo.
All that plus the return of Souvenir Smackdown.
Will a bizarre new Disneyland wormhole be opened up?
Spoiler alert, yes.
It's Mickey's Full Harmadge on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, hosted by three grown men who love themselves a good animatronic
duck bottom.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Jason Sheridan.
Thanks for the boost on that one.
Where is the lie?
You know?
I mean, yeah, we loves what we loves and Mike Carlson.
I'm here and what an edgy comment.
Yeah, I know.
You said it in the most aggressive way possible.
It would be that is saying that like, I think my mom who will be listening eventually to
this, she'll be like, that's cute.
She'll say like, that's nice.
That's the type of humors you would like more of.
Because we made it bottom and not.
Yeah.
Even rear would be too much.
Even in quarters.
I just built up around Jason saying, what's the gist?
Something about an animatronic duck bottom?
I just liked that moment.
Not the horniest part of the show.
You wouldn't?
You don't think so?
Of the Philharm Magic of today's topic.
Mickey's Full Harmadge.
We'll get to it.
I don't know what you mean or what your pursuit, what your.
OK, I'll just come out and say the palpable chemistry between Ariel and Donald Duck.
Oh, yeah.
Very uncomfortable.
There is any between.
I think it's entirely one sided.
I think Donald's swimming after her.
He is horny, though.
Yeah, she's touching his face.
But she's not.
She's just being like, oh, you're a cute duck.
She's not like.
But that song plays a little different when you sing it to someone.
That is a sounder to Donald, but she wants to be part of his duck world.
I'm saying it.
I don't think that played a little romantic for me.
Well, that's not the reason I have this.
Gadgets and gizmos are plenty.
Now, that joke is too far.
That's a little bit too suggestive.
Scott, I would appreciate if you would go back to the clean material.
No, I don't. I don't think we shouldn't.
We usually like to do a little ramp up to this, but no,
I don't think I think Ariel is just going about her business.
And she goes back around.
Let's consider it here.
And then she like kind of pinches his little cheek.
And then she goes back to singing about wanting to be part of the human world.
That's my take, at least.
It felt like they were flirting.
It felt like new love.
I mean, he's into her.
I just don't think vice versa.
She's just charming naturally.
But I don't think she was wanting to express anything other than friendship.
To the duck, to this duck swimming around looking for his hat.
You know, I wanted to see where it went.
He goes for the kiss and she moves out of the way.
She's performing.
But I'm saying like, there was art comes.
That's what I'm saying about the whole thing.
The whole entire thing is performance.
I see. Yeah.
Uh huh. She's a Hollywood phony.
All that affection isn't real.
She would have made every stripper I've ever been to.
She would have been to.
Now we're getting to some stuff.
She would have made out with Donald if she was into him at the end of the thing,
or at least kissed him on the lips or something.
Like some day I know a stripper will do with me.
Kiss you on the lips.
I'm going to kiss her and it's not going to be a
eel with lipstick.
Yeah. As up to Donald.
Up to this point, every strip club you've gone to, you like lean in for the kiss
and then like they move out of the way.
You end up kissing like the bouncer or something.
And then it's a big kerfuffle.
He does a big smooch.
It's like a like a Roman statue.
That's why they have those around.
And you get electrified by the taser he carries.
Yeah. And I've thrown out onto the street.
That's interesting. That's my life.
Few too many Chardonnays, pal.
Yeah. The bricks.
Um, we're talking about Mickey's Philhar Magic, which is a 3D movie
that is a 4D movie, if you will,
that is in almost all of the Magic Kingdoms at this point.
Or not Magic Kingdom, not in California.
Oh, yeah. It's I'm sorry.
So it's in it's on almost every property.
It was at Disney World in 2003 and somehow didn't make it
into California Adventure until this very year.
This year, a few months ago on multiple continents.
I was shocked to learn that.
We're in Orlando, Anaheim, Paris and Hong Kong and Tokyo.
I passed by it there and did not go in.
That's a good way to save time.
Well, in Tokyo, too. I missed that.
I believe so. I think I saw.
I mean, I did not go in it and see it.
But yeah, it's a it's an attraction that, you know,
started at Disney World and came out of the gate fairly strong.
And I feel like was well regarded and replaced the much needed to be replaced.
Just a Lion King puppet show, which was probably very good when it opened.
But these things are in their course.
And it was, I think, fairly well regarded at the time.
And there were immediately rumors.
Well, does it make it out to to California?
Do they maybe put it into the Muppet Space,
which has been playing to a quarter of a crowd for many years?
And the answer was always no, they couldn't put it in there
because probably the big thing about the movie is that at some point
it goes black, the screen.
And then when you come back, the screen is much larger than it was before.
There's like a reveal of a mega screen,
which is a move a lot of these attractions do now.
It happens in the DreamWorks theater.
And so the answer is always, well, it couldn't come to the Muppet Theater
in Disneyland because it's not wide enough to do that.
And then all of a sudden, a couple of months ago, they're like,
and I remind us to put it in.
Yeah, this was like a the it's called the largest
purpose built 3D screen ever made at the time.
150 feet wide, I believe over 30 feet tall.
I didn't know how big it was. Wow. Yeah.
And it definitely wraps a lot more in Florida.
Bigger than T2 3D.
Not that you have screen dimensions in front of you,
but I'm trying to remember from having gone there.
I don't know if that's one consistent screen.
There's like big metal beams between.
This is the largest continuous screen. Interesting. OK.
Now in DCA, yes, they retrofit at the standard Muppet screen
and stuck some sideways DynX widescreen TVs on the walls
to kind of simulate a wrap around.
I think what if you aren't picking this up, listener,
we maybe were not thrilled with this experience.
I mean, the experience itself, because we all went down together
to see this, and it's probably very rare that we all experience
an attraction for the first time together as a unit.
And we had fun doing it.
But we sort of walked out quietly
and didn't discuss it much further,
which is probably what everyone else in the audience did.
It just sort of it landed with a little little thump.
And that was it.
I thought taken on its own.
The movie is is charming. Yeah.
And people had told us before, like, hey, if you're in the Magic Kingdom,
don't sleep on this. Like, don't skip it.
And I can see the appeal in its original iteration with the giant screen.
And I also have to say, I watched a couple
ride throughs of the Florida one and that Donald Duck Bottom
wiggles a lot more.
And the gag is a lot clearer in Florida.
And thus the audience is a lot hornier.
Yes, a lot hornier out here.
It felt a little more a statue that shifted a little.
And maybe you think maybe somebody's just up there shaking it around.
Shake it, just poking a broom at it.
Not even fully awake themselves, like a sleep in a chair and kind of like
kicking it with one leg.
Yeah, I the audience, it was not packed in there.
And as we left, I didn't get the sense of, oh, people going, wow,
like that was great or anything.
We all just sort of had a slow trudge to the exits.
And it was like, OK, great. OK, this is here.
At least they're using this for something other than just movie previews.
Yes. So that's good. Yeah.
But that aspect ratio. Uh huh.
Well, yeah. So we all sound like we came from a funeral.
It's not that bad.
Mainly I'm avoiding at the top of the episode, we're still in the first
10 minutes or so that we've just told people, like, so we're talking about
a boring thing we didn't like.
Yeah, we're all I feel like we got to like, get the positivity.
Yeah, I'll get I'll I do a positive stuff to say.
One, this is a nice.
I think it's it's fun to see the hits.
This is definitely you're seeing
the greatest hits from a lot of musical
90s Disney stuff, 90s and then Peter Pan and Fantasia also.
Which compared to like the more Broadway centric 90s songs,
the Peter Pan one kind of stuck out like,
you know, why suddenly do we go back in time? Yeah. Yeah.
I like seeing this.
It reminded me how much I liked these movies and I like these songs.
I think it's very funny.
The idea of like it's the some of our greatest songs through over the years.
And it's mostly Donald getting owned like Donald just getting his ass
kicked through movies.
I like that.
I less like that.
It's called Mickey's Philharmagic and he's barely in it.
It should be called Donald Duck's Philharmagic. Yeah.
Or Donald Ruins Mickey's Philharmagic.
I would disagree.
I think it's it is actually fun that it's a misdirect.
You think it's like you're going to see a concert that Mickey is going to conduct.
And then Donald fucks up and takes the hat and travels through IP.
He travels through other IP.
It's a great description of the plot.
Yeah. Donald takes a hat and sees IP in progress.
Development of the attraction, I think, is interesting.
This is one of the times that Imagineering has worked with another department in the company.
They worked with Walt Disney Animation to make this.
They got Glen Keane to do the animation for Ariel again.
Really? He supervised redoing it as in 3D.
And apparently this was his first time working with CGI.
And then after this, he went on to work on Tangled.
Oh, wow. I know.
Kidding. That's cool.
But we talk much about Glen Keane, the most who did
Ariel, who did Bell or the Beast.
He did the Beast.
And I'm sure I'm forgetting another big one.
But yeah, one of like one of the great animators of the late 80s, early 90s era.
But the thing I like about him is that he's the kid of the family circus.
Keane artist. Yes. Bill Keane.
Bill Keane. So one of those kids is him.
He's Jeffy. Yeah, I guess he's Jeffy.
Could be Jeffy.
Scott, you did a very funny series many years ago.
Where you inserted a drawing of yourself into Family Circus.
Scott meets Family Circus dot Tumblr dot com.
That was a Tumblr I did.
It was very funny and mean.
Like you like all the gag is you show up and you're mean to the family circus kids.
If you took you take one because it's just a one panel circus frame.
So I added a second, which in many cases was me adding a punchline
that was not previously there in a punchline free script.
But yeah, I was mainly just like correcting the kids.
That's how it started was just like it's pronounced spaghetti, not just being
just being helpful.
And then it became then I started within the world of this having sex with the mom.
I was breaking up the family circus,
which now I realize is animator Glenn Keane's mom.
How you are having sex with Glenn Keane's mom.
I made a comic, a fan comic where I have sex with Glenn Keane's mom.
You were cuckolding.
Yeah.
In a literal sense.
Mr. Keane.
The actual illustrator now deceased of the family circus.
Yeah.
I boy, this is a bad one for Mrs.
Carlson if she's sorry.
It's got I don't know.
Look, there's no way she understands.
There's no way those the kids with the little lines that they leave behind,
those dashes that you follow, the grandparents who are ghosts.
Like, I think we've all had enough of family circus.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It felt fun to come in and be a little a little combative.
And but also, I mean, the admittedly, the the plot with the wife was kind of
because I was like, she's got all she's kind of got going on.
Yeah, I was.
She I don't remember what the dad just is kind of like,
like just a regular kind of frumpy glasses dad.
And then the wife's kind of like a hot 60s lady.
Yeah.
So what's the name?
Is it Helen or anything?
Could we look at it?
I don't know.
I know.
That's a good question.
Family.
Oh, God, I bet it is.
Family circus mom.
What's her name?
Thel.
Oh, her name is Thel.
Is it true for Thelma?
Thel's a pretty good name, honestly.
Cool.
Yeah.
Thelma Karnke.
Yeah, right.
So it passes Thel and test.
She has an interest.
Well, another great thing to put on a list of great qualities
about battle.
Thel does sound like a replicant from Blade Runner,
like Deckard's after Thel.
It's like a girl in Tron.
Like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I am Thel.
Wasn't I'm a thousand years old.
There was a period where we were trying to think of you
playing Jeffy in a family circus movie.
Am I wrong?
I mean, look, I got to work.
Hashtag Jason for Jeffy.
Jason for Jeffy.
Jeffy all grown up.
I would like to river.
No, no, no, no.
No.
Oh, you want the classic.
I want you to play him as a six year old.
I do think family circus.
All the comic strips are right for the Riverdale treatment.
Oh, my God.
Well, you want to see.
I don't know if I think you want to see them grown and
again, let's say horny and mysteries and cults.
And yeah, I don't know.
High and Lowis, maybe family.
Dagwood.
No, Dagwood.
Like Dagwood, like a blood Dagwood means bloodline.
Heathcliff. Yes.
Crank Shaft. Yes.
Lock.
Beetle Bailey.
Lock horns. Lock horns.
Yes. OK.
Family circus.
Foxtrot. Foxtrot.
Right there.
Foxtrot is right ready to go.
Mark Trail. Yes.
Yeah. They've got to grow up someday, though.
And sure.
Mark Trail would be awesome.
A CW Mark Trail would kick ass.
I would like I would like another Garf.
I would like a Garfield movie played straight.
Like we were talking about straight.
What do you mean?
I want a Garfield movie that's good.
I want a good Garfield movie that looks like the comic strips.
But you mean played straight like no jokes.
No, like not live action with the CGI.
Like I want like an animated.
I want an animated Garfield.
You want an all animated Garfield played like the played like the comic strips
once in a while.
Funny comic strip.
Yeah. Yeah.
Occasionally, maybe once 20 years ago.
I don't feel like the problem was ever with the Garfield movies.
Of all the problems you could have with it, I never felt like not capturing
the tone of the comic was one of them.
I'm interested in what you were thinking, like what your Garfield movie would be.
I don't know. It just kind of came to me like
you just feel like we haven't had a good representation.
Do you want to see the barn that barnyard gang to like from the com?
Is that what more you're thinking of like the cartoon Garfield?
Yeah, I thought the cartoon did capture pretty well.
And it had the full supporting cast with
Arlene, Arlene and Nermal, Nermal,
John's girlfriend.
Yeah. I don't remember if she was actually in it.
I didn't like that barnyard gang, though.
You did or you didn't? Didn't. Really? Yeah, really.
I think I did like them.
I like the idea that a show would have like a second.
Well, I get bored with the main stories of almost every show, so I like it.
All right. And then there's another thing going on.
I was uninterested in them.
But if you're if you're going to ask me if I liked Heathcliff's Cadillac cats,
which I know the hell, yes, I did.
All four. I love those guys the best.
I didn't give a shit about Heathcliff.
I wanted the Cadillac cats.
I wanted to riff raff and Hector and the other one.
I think I probably I may have never encountered these cats.
That's how much I hated just the intro of Heathcliff.
The song Heathcliff, it's the best theme song.
No, I hate that song. What?
This cannot be a first opinion.
Anyone? I've never heard that before.
That's really a good song.
I think I don't like fifties.
I don't like doo woppy, especially like down in the 80s doo wop.
That's a great theme song.
Heathcliff annoys me for this is this has been raised on the doughboys.
I forget where they fall on it.
Well, the comic strip is nonsensical.
It doesn't make any sense.
It's less about the cartoon.
The cartoon. Yeah, because the comic strip, if you even read it,
whoever is making it still or if it's just a rehash, it's nothing.
It doesn't make any sense.
So you liked the cartoon or you didn't like.
I didn't like the Heathcliff part of the cartoon.
I love the Cadillac cats part because they lived in the junkyard.
They were very cool.
And riff raff had a car that transformed.
It was like he could make it into like a living space.
He could make it into a cool like Cadillac of some kind.
I truly am seeing the Cadillac cats for the first time ever as we speak.
Really? And observation number one,
horniness, a theme in this episode.
Well, he had a hot girl.
He was a tiny little cat and he had a very tall, sexy girl.
Short kings unite.
So his little like Dom DeLauise had a scarf.
And how does he land a girl twice his size?
He was that cool.
And also, this is the thing people complain about, that everything is sexist.
Confidence.
Because like it's like Lola Bunny or we've talked about this before, where
the cartoons, like the male cartoon is like a dumpy.
Looks like an animal.
I'm actually going to take the other angle on this and say that
it's heightest to go like, how did he get her?
In this case, in the Cadillac cat.
All right. Fair enough.
There's a lot of unfair judgments put on shorter men in society.
I believe that to be true.
So I see what you're saying.
I'm looking at a picture of the whole gang, of the other half of it, too.
And Heathcliff has a Heathcliff is with his exact equivalent.
And then Cadillac cat is with somebody twice his size.
I guess I should not be heightest about this, but they're
that pairing is a lot stranger.
I'll tell you that.
Well, I think you would like the Cadillac cat.
Yeah, character and confidence goes a long way.
Stuff do they get up to?
They're like up to no good a lot.
Like not nothing, I think, too, too dangerous.
But there's like they're like hot characters in this show and they're up to no good.
And you liked it.
Yeah, believe it or not.
I think it was a lot of having to do with the transforming car.
I think I like that he had like kind of a transformer type car.
And I thought I thought Hector specifically, which is the one with the tie.
I thought he looked cool and I wanted to like look like Hector.
And I liked Riff Raff's hat.
Why are you wearing a Dom Delahue's hat all the time?
I guess I should. I guess I should age into that.
It's your style. Or captain's hat.
Yeah, or captain's hat.
You should be a jughead hat.
Yeah, yeah, a lot of options.
We should put it up to a vote.
What kind of hat should Jason wear?
Could we talk just about Cadillac cats for the rest of the episode?
That's fine, because clearly we don't have a lot to say about.
That's why I like some of the some of these episodes,
there's the too many things episodes where we are all stressed.
We have to jam it all in.
I kind of like these ones where like I feel like we have open
landscape to talk about whatever the cat like.
Let's check in with how each other are doing,
because I don't have a lot to say about.
I feel like you're coming in with a bad attitude, though.
Maybe I am. Maybe I am.
It's to be fair, it's more about the jamming it into California Adventure
and less about because I did walk out of the Disney World one
whenever I saw it like a decade ago, thinking that that ain't bad.
At the time, it was interesting to see the characters converted into 3D.
Yes, that would have been very important thing to note that maybe you haven't.
Now, of course, 3D, Aladdin and Beauty and the Beast and Lion King
are all that we live for and talk about.
But yes, these are the new classic canon of today.
But at the time to see actually the very first one you see,
especially because when you're not you're not sure where the attraction is going.
And I think the big reveal of the big screen and what all of it is,
is when Donald is like there's just like a candlelight and it's dark otherwise.
And Donald's like, huh.
And then there's more light and it is Lumiere.
And then you get the 3D Fide to be our guest.
Yes. So seeing it like, oh, I see.
So it's going to kind of step you through these great moments
and in a new dimension.
That's kind of fun.
And I did like it when I when I first saw it.
Did not read as well on this because it just seemed like.
And now we're using all of the normal size movie screen.
Yeah, I think. Did they start using all of it?
At some point, they switched to all of it.
Well, that's the problem.
And you know what? I did.
I looked it up and it's the same thing that happened in Paris,
where it only went in.
They only put in PhilharMagic in October 2018. Right.
And I watched a video of it and it's the same aspect ratio.
It's the same cut.
So if we had to explain this,
if you see it in Florida, there's a there's a really nice
frame with like musical instruments, golden and there's musical instruments on it.
And when the part of the show happens, we're going to watch a concert
that Mickey is conducting.
It fills up that whole screen and then everything goes dark.
And then it comes back up and there's a much, much bigger screen.
Big reveal. Really cool in Paris and in California Adventure.
They have reduced the screen with digital curtains.
So we're just not using all of the screens.
And the big reveal is, oh, they're using almost the whole screen
because still, for a lot of it, at least for be our guest,
there's just like a black bar at the top.
So it's like a letter boxed.
It's so strange.
I was like, they letter boxed it twice almost like
we were trying. You're trying to figure out the numbers.
I was saying it's two thirds of one one eight five one
divide one eight five one into thirds
to multiply by two.
You need an equation. It's an un-pioneered aspect ratio.
Is there a plus up way for them to have done this?
Because obviously putting these in these theaters are just quick fixes.
There's specifically California Adventure, like this theater.
All of this area will be redeveloped within the next five years, I'm assuming.
We see something right.
That it's all tied, I think, to the Eastern Gateway, which will come back soon.
That's my prediction.
That's what I explained the Eastern Gateway.
Yeah, it's basically the that we're going to build a parking garage
on the other side of harbor with a bridge.
They were going to shrink sort of the entryway into California Adventure
because you would go through security over on the other side of harbor
by the parking garage.
And then Anaheim, of course, when there was a less friendly government said,
don't do that, it'll choke all the businesses on harbor because you'll just
you put a bridge over harbor and made it inaccessible from the resort.
And they said, Elysium rules.
The rich people go above.
And Disney, instead of saying, oh, well, we'll just make a little walkway to harbor.
They said, fuck you.
We will not build this the way we wanted.
And then that because they they pulled that, then they lose a lot of real estate
that they were going to be able to develop out into the Esplanade.
I see. So there would have been like it would have.
California Adventure can then like bleed into the Esplanade more
because it's going to be a very narrow or a much more narrow walkway into
or into the main hub of Disneyland.
So the main thing is we it's been rumored for a long time that, I mean,
already some some Marvel is going in.
We lost Bugs Land and we lost it's tough to be a bug.
But presumably more Marvel will end up in that Hollywood area.
How much is the question? Right.
And it's and this this sort of dull on its face
parking bridge issue impacts that ultimately.
Or the expansion area behind Cars Land.
I think you can build out into that.
Yeah. And there's there's one behind the tower that they were going to
supposedly build the Avengers coaster, which who knows?
We haven't heard what is going on with that.
Or if they just say, fuck it, we're imploding that Alpine Hotel
that's right on the property.
Y'all had your chance.
Just like they just invade it and drone strike it.
And that's their that's their property now.
Like they have a new fireworks show and they aim the fireworks at the hotel
and blow it up. Oh, whoops, whoops.
Made a mistake.
Yeah, the way they put this into DCA and I I I don't mean to just say
I didn't mean to imply that just you had a bad attitude, Scott,
because my reaction to the execution of this would be described as,
well, this feels a little craven like this
because they put up the posters of like the fake.
There's a bunch of fake movie posters as you walk in and those are cute.
Like Jeannie sings the blues or like Hades, a character
they can never have the same actor do the voice again because he's a lunatic.
Like there was a poster with why not? Who is that now?
I don't know, because he's been censored by all the social media networks.
Yeah, so there was like fake
posters for musical acts with your favorite Disney friends.
And that led to a pre-show area that was just some more
cheapy flat screen TVs not really showing anything.
And good point in Florida, that pre-show area doesn't seem to have much either,
but at least they have some fake chandeliers and stuff like you're going into a concert hall.
Right. There's a little more because it was built for it.
But the real thing was the entryway sign. Yes.
You notice this?
Well, I would call it the most pixelated logo anywhere in a Disney park.
If you just look at the like, I think
if you go to California Adventure, look at that sign that used to be it used to say,
sadly, I'm up at Vision 3D and now it's a Philharmonic sign.
And just look up at Donald.
Donald looks like a not fully rendered PlayStation 2 character.
He Donald needs more polygons.
Yeah, it's I guess really I am cutting it some slack because it's better than nothing.
And it's been what was literally in there before?
Was it a preview of a wrinkle in time?
I think for three years they were showing five minutes of a wrinkle in time.
There was also the Pixar short film festivals.
They were running a bunch of Pixar short film festivals for a little while.
It was the Frozen sing along.
And then Nutcracker Four Realms was also the previous three years
had been a preview of Nutcracker in the four realms.
Boy, these Disney previews.
This has been quite an era. Yeah.
So this is I'm cutting it slack for that reason,
because it is absolutely better than those things.
It definitely is.
And I think if they had just done this five years ago, I feel like.
Sure. Yeah.
I think it's just so strange that suddenly and any fellow nerds listening
maybe caught this happening that like Mickey's Philharmonic opening in three weeks.
And we all went, what? Why? Right.
And I guess the idea being, well, let's just jam every corner of California.
California Adventure was stuff.
So to maybe pull out some crowds might be gone to Star Wars.
The name of the game is Galaxy's Edge alternatives.
We should also say we're recording this.
This will likely come out after we've been in Galaxy's Edge.
So we should say like, we're not the same people that we will be.
No, our voices are going to sound different.
Yeah, it's going to. Yeah, it'll be like sort of a post like acid trip
where you're different forever. Right.
So this will be the last.
This will be the last artifact of us before.
Unless or the change, unless we somehow have
we're so disappointed by it that we think Mickey's
Pharma magic was better, who is better than the Falcon.
What world?
I can't even imagine that world, but maybe that's right.
Maybe we will say, you know what? The Falcon sucked.
If the ride breaks and like sprays oil at us, then maybe if we're disfigured.
That would be the most eventful thing that ever happened to me at a theme park.
So I'd be excited for that to happen.
Plus like it is for story.
What a story.
Plus you'd ring out your clothes and hey, free oil.
Hey, free oil.
You know what hydraulic fluid goes for nowadays?
Jason rung out a glass of hydraulic fluid and into a glass after the ride.
And he's coming up. He's coming. He's winning.
I'm ahead. He's ahead.
That's what I meant to say. You keep it in the fridge to like,
yeah, oil up any rusty gadgets you got around the house.
Yeah, I have a lot of like Wayne Zelinsky style
doodads and gadgets. Breakfast machines.
Yeah, breakfast machines.
Sausage shooters.
Dressing tie tying machines.
Yeah. So the Fjllharm magic.
It's it's it's better.
Yeah, it's better. It's glad it's there.
It's better. Yeah, it's like
it's clearly we're just like throw this in.
We got to do something.
What movie do we have lying around? We had that idea.
Yeah, that was a bad idea back then. But whatever.
It's better than nothing.
Is it really going to draw anyone away from Disneyland?
No, not currently.
It's not drawing anyone now.
I mean, it's a new thing that there's probably West Coast people
that have not seen it.
Families will probably I mean, there'll probably be kids and families
who like it, although the audiences that we were with seemed a little checked out.
Yeah. Yeah. We did get sprayed with water a lot.
They were leaning on the water sprays.
Yeah. A little too much isn't always a Disney thing.
And I like that.
I like that maybe I'm not sprayed on a Disney ride with water or hydraulic fluid.
The best I maybe this is a full two and a half hour episode,
but the best water spray in a Disney park.
I'll decide it now.
Sinbad in Tokyo. Oh, I don't even remember a spray.
You go into the after you're out of the village, when they say goodbye,
you go into like a dark area and there's a storm and you get a little mist.
Oh, that's right. Right before.
And it's so great.
It's more pleasant than other ones.
I think we still went.
Sure. But if we have to say the best.
Yeah, yeah, I guess it would be.
I can think of a better water mist or spray Disney experience.
It's not I mean, well, it's something to I think the worst one is the one
I did in the fake Soren in Canada, where it's a sprayed Aaron and I
and a ruiner contact for the rest of the day.
Not these. That's not what we had to go Disney.
I mean, you can say sprays, best best spray or
I guess you could say like putting your hand out for the water on Big Thunder,
because then you can control the amount of water you're getting.
We hate that, too. Really? Yeah.
Every time we you'll our star go to reaction is.
Ah, OK. It's always it for us.
So you tell if you tell me you like one, I'll say, ah, or not.
And I'll probably say, ah, I've got one that always makes me laugh,
but it's at Universal and it's at the end of the Jurassic Park.
No one's following my rules for this exercise.
It's too limiting.
At the Jurassic Park boat ride at the end, when you are pulling back into the queue,
one of the spitter dinosaurs pops up when you think it's over
and like hits some people with a spray.
I'll say I'll say everyone. That's an a for me.
It's a funny because people if people aren't looking and aren't expecting it,
they think the ride's over.
I felt very fortunate as a tour guide.
One of the most unpleasant sprays is on the tram tour in Hollywood,
where spoiler alert, when you pass by some, you know, three
Jurassic Park jeeps, then in the bushes, some spitters spit at you.
And as a tour guide, I was the only person with a window blocking me from this.
So I never had to worry about it.
And everybody else was a sucker.
Would you consider the old it's gone now,
but the mist where you would see Captain Barbosa on Pirates of the Caribbean?
No, that's fine.
That was not so thick that it like stayed on me or anything. Right.
Yes. That would that felt so like intangible.
And so maybe that's your favorite.
If you consider that, I just don't think that's even a spray.
It's so little of a spray.
I don't know if you can call it a spray.
You're right. It's not a surprise.
One's probably.
Soren doesn't have any water.
No, thankfully, no water.
It's obviously Splash Mountain.
You get soaked, depending on where you are. Sure.
But yeah, I guess you would call this spray.
So is there a tough to be a bug one? Probably.
Yeah, I think so, but I don't remember where it is.
Uh, the T one million exploding is a spray at the end of T2 3D.
There's not a ton at Disney, though.
No universal every ride.
So we couldn't do a final four or there'd only be four if we did it.
Yeah, we'd have to do it universal.
We'd have to add universal in.
Copy vision.
Yeah, I like it. OK, when Foggy does Fossey.
Foggy, Foggy Bear.
Foggy bottoms. I've been misspeaking a lot today, too.
He does that. Doesn't he do the flower?
He you get a little flower.
That one's fine. They didn't go overboard with it.
OK, just a little bit. Yeah.
But this felt like universe this the application of it in this felt universal.
It felt like too much water.
I think because they do it in the two sequence.
So so just chronologically, there's a whole big intro where they're not ready.
And Mickey yells at Don't like we're not ready.
Like, Donald, don't touch my hat like they're going to get ready for a concert.
Donald, of course, touches my fucking eye of the star.
And also not to side check you for telling the story too much,
but before that, in the pre show and then while you're sitting,
just a lot of business of like, we're almost ready.
We're polishing the brass.
Yeah, not a thing you usually hear at a professional performing environment.
Yes, at a stately opera.
People are not assuring you that the opera is going to happen.
And it's not very professional.
And it's not fun like Muppet Vision pre show banter.
No, great little bits and stuff.
This is just the Disney characters assuring you that they will be ready soon.
And all doing very like workman like jobs.
Right.
Mickey gets to conduct and thus many Donald and Goofy have all been deployed
as his personal assistants.
They're all fetching him waters.
Yes, it's weird.
Yeah.
And this this has like a literal hat on a hat because Mickey is both a conductor,
but has the sorcerer's apprentice hat at his disposal as well.
Yes, he's now the pupil is now the master.
Yeah.
And he is in the mold of the sorcerer.
And thus and so now when he conducts,
because he steals the hat to conduct and now it's both.
Now he's but he has permission.
He killed the sorcerer.
The sorcerer is dead.
Right. He slayed him.
And now the hat is his.
Yeah. Yen said is in hell or at least some sort of limbo.
Oh, that's right. His name is Yen said.
Yeah.
Anybody can you listening at home who doesn't know that fact already?
Know what you said is if you reverse it, it's the name of the one true God.
It's the Illuminati.
They're trying to communicate with us.
Yeah. OK.
So, yes, the sorcerer's apprentice, the events, the sorcerer's apprentice are done.
And we're not talking Jay Baruchel sorcerer's apprentice.
We're talking original.
Oh, gee. That vaguely with the cage.
Yeah. Wow.
I only know this because I want all this Disney promotional company.
I edited Facebook content.
And I remember I might have said this on the show already, but I just remember a lot.
Nicholas Cage rambling, prattling on about
I also think about playing Balthazar.
You know, you got to remember Balthazar is real.
That's a good cage.
Hey, thanks. That's only that's my cage keyword is Balthazar.
Oh, man. Here's something to recommend.
The the Blu Ray for Spider-Man into the Spider-Verse
has making of feature X that feature both
a Nick Cage talking about the movie because he's Spider-Man noir.
And a very old Avi Arad Arad Arad Arad Arad.
Avi Arad. Yeah.
A long time Marvel producer, but bought Marvel when he was a toy biz with like Perlmutter.
Yeah. And still has producer credits on like the Spider-Man movies, at least.
Maybe the X-Men ones.
And I believe he's a maniac.
Yeah, him and Cage are out of it.
And he's like behind the scenes things.
And just hearing the cage go like, my Spider-Man's a little rougher.
He fit right in with Philip Marlowe and Sam Spade, Raymond Chandler.
I was watching a clip of Nick Cage from the Superman Lives costume fitting last night.
And he's going on and on about Superman and what he's going to do.
And he's in the outfit.
And I looked it up. He was 33.
And I lost my mind.
Like how younger than us?
Yes, younger than all of us.
And he's weathered already.
He's got that voice.
And you're like, oh, my God, we should be happy then.
You're not so weathered, I guess.
I'm downright boyish compared to Nick Cage at 33 trying on weird Superman.
I hear a Nick Cage now go like the movie just goes to show that anyone can be Spider-Man.
It's very fun.
That sounds good.
What are we saying that we're like, OK, everybody's doing grunt work for Mickey.
So he can put on a little music show.
Donald starts fucking with the magical hat and the orchestra, the magical instruments go insane.
Well, we've missed we've lost over that that when preparing for the show,
Donald has to take all the all the lots of instruments out of a bag.
And then those do those come to life and perform rather than musicians being there.
Thus, once again, nobody's getting paid.
This has got to be Skirting Seven Union rule.
There's like 78 people in an orchestra all not making their salary because he's just going straight to the instruments.
Mickey, you're a bad employer.
Your theater should be shut down.
Yeah, that's got to be against some like musicians equity or something.
Yeah. Yeah.
Support musicians.
Do not automate orchestras with magic.
Yeah, that is a cause for you to take up.
I think. Yeah, it's important.
So so yeah, then.
All right. So Donald puts on the hat and then they all.
They all start. They start playing Mickey Mouse's theme song.
Another great thing.
What if I get a lot of instruments together and what if I get instruments together and I'm a play my song?
Yeah. And then I'll go home.
That seems to be what his plan is with the show.
Donald, as we know from the theme song from the opening of the Mickey Mouse Club, hates the Mickey Mouse song more than anything.
Donald Duck, he tries to say.
He's mad. He's jealous of Mickey's fame.
And he doesn't have a song.
But no, he has a song, but he is he's even mad at his own song.
Yeah, but no one but Donald Duck.
Why? He's still like still mad.
He's very much Sally area in this.
Would you consider this? Would you consider Disco Duck his song?
No, that's not related to him.
That's still again more people stealing.
That is not an official Disney movie.
Yeah, he's just doing what he's doing a Donald Duck voice.
Yeah. Yeah, he was the original Mickey, not crediting musicians properly.
Hmm, too bad.
So all of that happens and then and then the instruments go crazy.
Yeah, they attack him.
And then you you do go to that moment I like where it is black and then the flame comes up and it's Lumiere.
And they're starting strong. It's a great song. Be our guest. Great song.
That animator came back as well.
Oh, really?
Nick Ranieri.
Really?
Came back to do Lumiere.
Oh, but you know who didn't come back for any of it?
The voices of the actors or of the characters.
Yeah.
Clearly, it's all just original audio.
Oh, yes.
And a lot of Donald is original audio.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Of Clarence Nash of the original voice of Donald.
You can hear the audio recording.
Like the quality is poorer, like especially on like some of his yells.
You can hear it's like a clip from the 60s or something.
The current voice actor only recorded five new lines for this.
Everything else was like old stock.
Probably Disney pays by the line.
And they're like, we can only we only have $500 for him. $100 a line.
So when Donald's humming be our guest, that's new guy.
Right.
Okay. If it refers to something explicitly happening, but if it's just like,
Here's my problem with this show in general. It's just the recordings from the movies.
Donald doesn't really interact that much.
He is just in the background of these famous scenes getting hit or owned or whatever you
want to call it.
Sure.
A lot of fun to be had with Donald singing along or getting into like some sort of
altercation with like Lumiere, the main characters.
There's a lot of fun I feel like you could have with Donald getting in there and really
messing the songs up or something.
I like the brooms hitting him with water in a row.
I like some of the stuff, but it's really just you're watching a
CGI version of a song you know, while a picture in picture little thing happens with Donald.
An unrelated story.
Unrelated story in the promise of if you pitched me, Donald goes through Disney history,
screws everything up. That sounds fun to me.
But this version of it, I'm assuming to save money so they didn't have to get a
rerecorded version of everything.
They might've been worried. I'm realizing about like maybe the guy was going to like
hurt himself doing Donald's voice because I just did Donald for one line and I'm like,
yeah, I'm like choking a little bit.
I'm going to you guys keep talking.
I'm going to get water.
I've been stifling it.
That really fucked me up.
All right.
Boy, much respect to Clarence Nash and Tony and Selmo.
Just go over the sink.
Yeah, I'm going to cough up a storm.
Get something over the from the sink.
You okay.
So be our guest.
Sort her as apprentice brooms.
But do you do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I know what you're saying.
I mean, we did get the introduction of the greatest love story of our time.
Donald and Ariel.
The Little Mermaid.
So I get there.
She's interacting with him, but the songs are the exact same.
It would be fun if Donald took a verse and said what he wanted to be part of.
Does he want to be like if the scenes were under new management, some might say.
Sure.
But that's that's the fun.
I think that's the promise of a premise like this.
Yeah, that's true.
Get Donald's doing fun stuff with the songs and it feels like you're just listening to
the exact same which you are the exact same song and you're getting a little
piece of business here and there and it feels it feels like I'm not seeing a new experience
as much as I'm seeing a little some cute little gags, but I'm just listening to the
soundtrack from the movie.
I already know very well.
It doesn't feel like a fun special movie to me.
That's what makes the whole thing to me uninteresting.
I've got a short tangent because it's music related.
I put we post that picture a while back of the I had found the like two disc Disney World
soundtrack I bought years ago on CD and I was listening to it again at my car and it
struck me how odd it was and I'm like what year is this from and it's copyrighted 2008.
So there is some strange stuff on it.
Like I was driving along, did not expect to hear like the Tiki Room song until
like halfway through and then stop stop like the under new.
It's got the under new management Iago song on it.
Be careful with that Iago voice.
Let me tell you from experience.
No, I'm not doing it anymore.
Scratchy.
I survived, but just barely.
And then the like second song on it is a thing called Main Street Medley, which for most of
it is like little snippets of like long way to Tipperary long way to Tipperary or like
sure or Clank Clank Clank with a trolley.
But then there's an original song about how like it's Main Street today and we're happy
to see you.
Oh, I don't know.
Like it's very odd.
So like 2008, I guess I don't even know where I would have bought this.
Disney World.
No, but I wasn't there in 2008.
I think maybe I was in Disneyland and I was like, why do they have this year?
Guess I'll buy it.
You think it's odd that you were in Disneyland and there's a CD that has a
song about Main Street being nice?
No, but it's the Walt Disney World soundtrack that they made.
I think they were selling in Disneyland.
That's not like Disney, Tokyo Disney, where they sell like CD singles.
Yeah.
Isn't it weird?
Are they have like, it's just like you buy the it's like expensive CDs and it only has
one track on it.
It's 15 minutes long.
Yeah, I bought a three disc set to try.
I wanted to get everything, but if I were to buy all the music at Tokyo Disney, it would
have cost me a thousand dollars.
I think like physical media more there.
Well, yeah, they haven't gotten into the streaming thing as much.
Yeah, but yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I have not.
I would like to hear that Main Street song that you're referring to.
Yeah, I gotta dig it out.
I gotta finish listening to it because I think there's some more.
You got it in 2008.
And I listened to it then and I forgot like this whole thing.
It's been on his to-do list.
Listen to the rest of the tracks on the thing I bought 10 years ago, 11 years ago.
So the entire Obama administration passed.
Anyway, so yeah, part of the world.
I've already established beautiful chemistry.
So I just I was watching that as we were talking to refresh my memory again.
So here's here's what happens that I do.
I see some of what you're saying.
She takes his little feed ease.
She plays with his little feet.
He takes his snoot, his little snooty and his feed ease.
And she plays with his feet a little bit.
And then she kind of like gently touches his bill.
Yeah, so like lovingly touches his bill.
Still, I read that I see how you,
oh, Donald could misinterpret those signals.
I will say that.
I'm not saying it's a full arc of a love story,
but I'm saying it could be the start of something magical.
But let me let me say this.
If people saw the way I was affectionate with Edwin, our dog,
would you think maybe Edwin would get the wrong impression that I was in love with him?
Do you sing to Edwin?
Yes.
Does he quack back at you?
No, he just like rolls around a little bit.
But like if I I play with his paws, I like rub his snoot.
I'm just saying like Donald is a little cute animal and I don't think Ariel is.
But he's sentient.
Yeah, yeah, he is.
But Edwin is different.
Edwin is a little sentient.
Donald speaks.
Yeah.
Yeah, but he doesn't.
She I don't think I think she can't under she doesn't know that.
I get the sense that she's not even reacting to what he's doing because she can't hear it.
It's like one of those cartoons where the animals speak, but like the humans don't know.
She's not reacting to any of his noises.
She's just like, oh, look at this cute animal.
And she plays with his little feet.
I'm just saying it's not dissimilar to the way I play with Edwin's feet.
And I'm saying that Ariel is not coming on to him at all.
She's just like, oh, this is a cute animal.
And Donald is misinterpreted.
I can see where his his his misunderstanding is coming from.
Well, are you ever playing with Edwin's feet and then he gets a big old boner?
Not the feet, but he certainly has gotten a boner while I've been playing with him.
But it's not because I was.
Sounds like he's getting the wrong message.
He has been known to hump.
Yeah, he humps me all the time.
When you sing all of part of your world to Edwin, Edwin gets a boner.
Yes, maybe.
But I'm just saying I can I can understand why he maybe gets the wrong idea sometimes.
Sometimes when I'm like playing, I think, yeah, he's getting the signals mixed up.
And if I'm on the ground, he will get on the back of my leg and try to hump me.
So that's what's going on.
I'm just saying Ariel is not interested in Donald in a real romantic way.
Donald is thinking that she is, but it's not the case.
That's all I'm saying.
But I see what you're saying, because she does.
She does touch him and it's a little coy.
Hey, Edwin, here's a little test.
Look at this stuff.
Isn't it neat?
Wouldn't you think?
Not interested in it.
Mike does it.
He might want some water.
Don't be so coy, Scott.
OK, so so moving on for part of your world,
it goes to I Just Can't Wait to Be King.
This is the thing I noticed.
This is the only song all the other songs take place in locations.
I Just Can't Wait to Be King is kind of a dream sequence.
Abstract.
It's like this in the real.
How would you describe this?
It almost becomes like a like it's a simplified paper cut out worlds that we go into.
There's 3D Simba and 3D Donald, but everything else is like
the animals from Brian Fellow's Safari Planet opening.
Yeah, like pillow paper cut outs.
Like montage isn't quite right, but like in singing in the rain where they go into,
they start doing the scene from the movie and then that takes over.
You like enter this hole.
You enter the Broadway melody.
I find this to be sort of a successful sequence, I think because I tend to like when 3D movies
don't just do and it's 3D characters and they're fully rendered.
I like when there's some style like in Spider-Man, Turn Off the Dark.
That there's not turn off the dark.
That's the fuck.
Fuck.
It's so in my head.
That is what you meant.
I mean, yes, I like everything about that.
Spider, what's that?
Spider-Man into the Spider-Verse.
I don't think I ever could have produced that so lodged in my head is Turn Off the Dark.
I like that there's different styles and 2D with like 2D rendered as 3D is
often much cooler to me than 3D rendered as 3D.
That's what you're saying.
Or Lego movies a little in that way to like a kookier.
Yeah, it looks cool.
Yeah.
Spider-Verse is incredible.
Like the way they replicated certain artists, comic styles and animated it.
Oh, there's the references.
Yeah.
The way the Kingpin looks, the way Gwen Stacy looks.
Yeah, that was I had just seen it recently and it's so great.
First time I teared up at a movie in a long time.
Spider-Man really?
Yeah, when Miles catches him at the end, catches Peter at the end before he lets him go.
Oh yeah.
Peter says, what if I mess up again?
I'm like, oh no.
Oh yeah.
I tear up at movies all the time as I get older.
I don't even have to like it.
I could not like the movie and I could tear up at something.
Sure.
Yeah, I don't know if I can handle a new Toy Story this summer.
Oh, and they're really going to put the pedal to the metal on the emotion.
I don't think it's going to get me.
I think they've put too many stories.
The story's over.
I'm kind of criticizing it in the sense that I think like they went in like,
well, we got to top the last one, which to me feels like a recipe for like too much.
Yes.
It's a pattern now.
Yeah.
And how do you top the last one?
No, I don't know.
The lesson's the best.
Looking the specter of death in the face.
Yeah.
It's very heavy.
I don't know.
We'll see.
I'm sure I'll like it.
But Aladdin might do it too in that I'll just be crying like,
I can't believe I don't have that money anymore.
I don't have that $12 anymore.
Will Smith's once promising career.
What happened?
But yeah, I just came here to be king.
This sequence also makes the most effective use of the side screens because abstract.
You know what?
Okay, I will say this.
I don't mind what's happening on the side screens.
No.
It's not great.
Okay.
If you're in the Muppet Vision Theater,
they're using the screens that used to just exist to imply that the theater got banged up at the end.
Yes.
And now they're doing a little more substantial with bonus water or bonus clouds in the Peter Pan sequence.
It's kind of like I'm told, I still haven't done it and I want to.
I want to see one of these Screen X movies that just stretch abstract imagery to the side.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah, there's one in Buena Park down by our beloved knots.
But this, I don't know, you put extra abstract giraffes and monkeys over there.
That was fun.
Yeah.
I mean, if you can't do like the DreamWorks theater Kung Fu Panda,
that is a pretty seamless wraparound there.
This isn't that.
It's not that.
But yeah, no, I like the abstract.
They also drew abstract like Donald and the Sorcerer's Hat at the one point,
like spinning by Simba's head, like in that style.
Oh yeah.
I like that.
Yeah.
Mainly just to hear all these classic songs in one place
and every once in a while interrupted by my hat.
My hat, I need the hat.
In the background.
Yeah, not really mixed properly.
Like the I think you should leave sketch Bozo dubbed over.
Oh yeah.
Oh, fuck.
I don't know, Guns Entered, Jacks Off.
Am I supposed to be here?
I hope I don't jack off.
The Tim Rouds and Netflix show, it's so good.
But you know what we haven't really talked about also is like what,
and talking about modding out the Muppet Theater,
are Styler and Walder still up there?
Where is everything?
That's a very good question.
I think they're still up there because it's very expensive to remove animatronics.
So we're just looking at a curtain because these are unused balconies at this point.
They used to have characters popping out of them.
Bean Bunny, Statler, Waldorf, this great animatronics just sitting in a coma state.
It's labor intensive to move them and also if they're hydraulic fluid powered,
then you have to concern yourself with disposing of closing off hydraulic lines,
disposing of fluids and so this is why Buzzy sat untouched for so many years.
Otherwise, Jason's gonna get it all.
Yeah.
Yeah, you should do a hydraulic fluid heist.
Like in The Simpsons when Homer and Bart were getting the grease.
The grease.
Oh man.
You just go into those balconies and suck out,
just have a long tube and suck out the hydraulic fluid with a length of hose.
This means hydraulic fluid for his cuckoo clocks at home.
My clock.
I don't know what hydraulic fluid is used for.
Yeah, I don't either but I assume it's for Jason's cuckoo clock collection which
honestly I've known you for a long time and I've made up a lot of funny specifics for your life
but I haven't come on, I haven't thought of cuckoo clock collection which makes a lot of sense to me.
Sure, that is a good movie shorthand for like this character's a little quirky.
Yeah.
Right?
But nice sometimes too.
Gepetto's nice.
Maurice is nice.
I'm sure Mr. Magorium's got his share of cuckoo clocks.
Oh for sure.
I think it would also make sense for you to be doing something at home,
tinkering to where you need like the big glasses that make your pupils look very big.
Oh, that I can put up and down depending on how much.
Just like Wainsolinsky, yes.
Oh yeah.
Sure.
I don't know where to get them but you need some good eyeball expanding glasses.
Trying to figure out the perfect ratio of like mustard relish onions on a dog.
I don't like those big pumps because like then you end up with one puddle and then you have to
smear it around.
Oh man, if you were the Dom DeLuis beret and the goggles.
Oh man.
Wow.
You should really start becoming like one of these fancy men, Disney like dress up men.
I think that's really a look that you should do I think.
Yeah.
Maybe for your birthday I'll buy you a full outfit.
Like a duffy style outfit.
Yeah.
Crazy old Jason came in here talking about some kind of beast.
He's out of, he's a loon.
That does feel more fun than like all the 90s like vintage 90s and pattern shorts and stuff
coming back like hypey shit in fashion right now.
I don't think I can pull that off.
Go back to the 1890s.
But if I go back to like, yeah.
Not even the 1890s, like I don't want to be like an old timey guy but I want to be like a quirk,
like an old timey kook.
Now that's something.
Yeah.
That's a style you could own.
Don't you have like a cabi hat that you wore for a while?
That I wore for a while?
Didn't you used to wear like six or seven years ago you had like a cap you would wear
maybe on like a special occasion.
If you had like a sport coat on you would wear like a floppy cap.
Am I wrong or is this a fantasy?
I don't think so.
You never have a hat like not a baseball hat but you didn't have like a little floppy cabi hat?
I think there are pictures of me like wearing one in high school or something.
I think I found one at a Goodwill.
I'm sure I've pulled it out for like shows or stuff.
Do you have, do you know where it is?
I have a box of hats.
Sure.
I have a box of hats of like four boxes of props from years of doing comedy.
All right well.
So do I.
I have every prop from any video I ever made.
I want them to go away.
Yeah I know but I feel like.
Get rid of them but then.
I might need this sweater from Steamroller's not just for crushing people again.
I do like that sweater.
Sure.
I have a rumpled Grimace costume that's just a sheet with Grimace's face printed out.
It's a nightmare.
Duck taped to the front of it and it's the scariest thing but I will not get rid of it.
I've used it twice in five years and there's really no reason I should keep it but it's truly
like a nightmare and I but it's like my favorite thing.
I was grimace once for Halloween and I just got like green or just purple fabric and draped it
Oh yeah.
Myself.
It's a.
Yeah good costume.
Yeah I did it for too but every time I do it he'll look worse because he's been in a rumpled
mess under my bed and I think it'll just be funnier if I have it in 20 years from now
because it really will.
Grimace was homeless for a little while.
Yes.
Sure.
What else.
So after I Just Can't Wait to be King back to back you can fly in a whole new world both
flying sequences both kind of feel a little like an afterthought.
I guess he gets tossed around in the clouds a little more.
They're not not magical or in a whole new world.
You don't get a lot of Peter Pan time I feel like that gets to the short end of the stick.
You get a little bit of it but yeah it just it's not a satisfying experience.
None of this feels satisfying to me.
It's not the ultimate rendering of these classic moments.
Yeah.
No.
I'm also I have another question which is why so if this hadn't happened if Donald hadn't gone
from IP to IP would they are these characters all just like in a Groundhog Day loop singing
their famous song every day every second.
Well if we're talking about a multiverse in general I think there always is going to be
a version of you we're doing like there's a version of us doing this episode forever somewhere.
What.
In the multiverse.
This one.
This specific one.
Over and over again.
Those poor guys.
Yeah where this is just a loop there.
So I think I like to think of it like that where it's just he's accessing a timeline in a multiverse
where he's getting right to those important moments in those characters lives.
Yep the important the most important moment for Aladdin was the magic carpet ride.
The most important moment in our lives was talking about the Cadillac cats 45 minutes ago.
That's so far my favorite part of this episode.
Uh the ending is Mickey scolds Donald.
Donald gets back to the orchestra show.
Yeah.
Somehow Mickey scolds him they do a little bit of music and then the tuba shoots Donald
back to the back wall of the theater his little butt wiggles.
And yeah there's a mild animatronic in the back where if you ever looked back in the
Muffet Vision 3D show to see the Swedish chef projecting or later with the musket.
And then a cannon.
And then a cannon yes.
Yeah they use that same space.
Here's what I say.
And that's fun I think we all like that.
That's like the best thing.
Start there start with that start with the tuba shooting Donald into the back and go from there.
Sure.
It's like Kurt Vonnegut always said write 15 pages and throw the first 10 in the garbage
and your story should start at page 11.
So where would you go once he gets shot where would you go from there?
I don't know but I want to see what happens from that that's like the best part and I wish.
Right.
I don't know I wish there was more.
Where else do you want to see Donald's butt show up?
Yeah where would you want him to be more in the 80s Disney movies he shows up in the rescue
on Scuttle or no Scuttle's in Little Mermaid what's the name of the of the bird in the rescuers?
We don't know.
The rescuers down under.
We mentioned this recently and I couldn't remember we talked about a Soren that was that but I
couldn't remember.
And there's two different birds because they.
It's a Benny and Lenny the Cav situation extremely similar the second one was John Candy.
Right.
And I don't remember the previous.
Yeah.
I watched rescuers down under a lot and I did not watch the original rescuers a lot
because we didn't have it on tape and also I found it scary.
So yeah I don't know I just think like all the all the property should come together at the end
it should you should see Aladdin and with you know with Lumiere like there's sure so much fun to be
had with this type of premise and it's just not delivered and I'm sure that the Imagineers
whoever were putting this thing together had fun ideas and there was some practical reason why the
suits were like we can't do that that's not we just need the songs that's the cheapest way to do
it.
Yeah.
People like the songs.
The answer is the global recession.
Right.
That's the look we just need it all we want to put in is money for the basic 2000 rendering of the.
We're not paying Jerry Orbach an extra dime.
Right.
Gilbert Gottfried really stands out too that he comes in and just squawks and it is such a
squawk that doesn't interact with whatever Donald is doing.
Right.
Even though they brought they had already brought him back for Enchant Tiki Room under new management
so bring him back again.
This thing I think in Florida had a lot of buzz because at the time
it was probably cool to see them in like 3D animation.
I think probably at the time people like oh this is neat we get to see the classic surrendered in a
new way but I think in 2019 it's like it's pretty unimpressive it's not bad looking but it's like
yeah okay these are competent CGI versions of the exact same sequences I know.
Yeah.
Okay it's the same song and there's a little Donald fun but like it's just the it's like
10 percent of what the premise is in my mind.
It's nice that I think it's nice that there's something in that theater like.
Yes.
As we said it's nice there's something.
California Adventure especially I feel like is a park where like the really good stuff
there is times where the really good stuff can fill up a little like get really long wait times
and you're like oh no what do we do now.
They have less swell at least this won't have a line.
Yeah so like and that sort of stuff is like Monsters Inc, Little Mermaid and now this so in
that sense it's not bad it's nice that there is like a little show and it's bad yeah I think
kids if you have kids if you really like these movies like yeah this is fun but I wish that
projector was a little brighter like all of these projectors are aging.
That's what I said before we went in I said because I had seen I had done this in Florida
a couple years prior and I was like man this 3D is rough on my eyes like hopefully it'll be
upgraded for this and I won't hurt as much and no it was not it felt like a magic eye
where I would have to kind of like really focus my eyes to make the 3D work very well.
Like I think there's probably something where they would have to go in and re-render the whole
thing in a different type of 3D to make it so it didn't hurt.
Yeah there's also talk about like cheaping out a little and you know weird retrofitting to a
facility that's there. Back when this thing opened at Disney World in 2003 our pal through
our ears Jim Hill wrote an article about like here's what you know here's what it could have
been and here's why Imagineers had to cut corners. Apparently this was going to debut
for the first time anywhere with the 2005 opening of Hong Kong Disneyland and it was going to be a
rare thing like that was so chintzy opening day Hong Kong Disneyland this was going to be a rare
thing that is only there here's the first place you can see it but it was they got done with the
movie sooner than expected and Disney World started like they started thinking well can we jam it in
there and basically it was going to have a premiere there was going to be a premiere in a retrofitted
new theater in Hong Kong Disneyland with a custom pre-show that would have set the stage for the
film that was to follow and because the movie got was on track to get done sooner they said you
know we're just going to put it in in Orlando and the lobby whatever we don't have time and no pre-show.
It does feel like a big a nice pre-show. Yeah yeah would have helped. Yeah because there's nothing
yeah there's maybe like clouds swirling around so I think this I think there's been a domino effect
potentially from that decision from not just letting it be its ultimate version in Hong Kong
right building it out from there but I have something else to say about this Jim Hill article
I'd like to read you the headline of this article from 2003. Go ahead. The headline is
did Disney execs unintentionally slip Philharmagic a Mickey? Mr. Hill. I don't need to be Mike's mom
to be offended by that headline. Watch out for the salt and pepper shakers on the table because that's a reach.
It's a different time 2003 was a different time. You know what I thought this opened in Orlando in 2008
so that is extra bizarre to me that we are in 2019 getting a 60 year old attraction out there. So late.
So very late. Also yeah that headline doesn't quite if we're really like one to like trying to figure
out the analog for the joke it would be like did it I mean I get it that Mickey is a is a
famous drug you put in someone's drink to knock them out. Yeah but it should be more it just
it should be like I'm not gonna be able to think of the joke but it should be more like
cutting it off at the knees or like popped its tires or something like slowed it down.
They poisoned the ride. They put it to sleep. If we're noting the joke headline. Yeah and we are.
We certainly are. We've noted a lot of different ride jokes too over the over the course of the
last two years as well. That's the problem with some of these things they're just done and tossed
out of the world and nobody expects some nerds to scavenge and analyze it years later but
the internet never forgets. Yeah so I'm looking at you Jim Hill media article from 2003.
I'll come up with it. Maybe in like a couple months I'll have it.
I'll have what I think is the better maybe headline for it. I guess that's where you gotta
give him credit. A deadline was looming I guess. He had to do it. It's I get it. Jim Hill's publisher
Jim Hill was demanding an article that day. Jim Hill is his own J Jonah Jameson so he's got like
a voice in his head yelling like you're watching me Hill. Yeah well that's how you do it. You have
to be a self-starter and I think we all should sort of have a J Jonah Jameson in our heads.
That's your tip for productivity. Yes. Have a mustache man yelling at you in your own head
of like I gotta get it done. We have to have it done by 3 p.m. tomorrow. Get me those pictures.
I do like that. We're like you know we're in an era where people are tweeting
you know a lot of you know like writery advice and here's how why. I think you can get a lot
of retweets from that like a good you know young writer advice. Put a tiny J Jonah Jameson in your
head. Well editors are the first jobs like cut. Fact checkers and editors first to go you know at
writing places. Newspapers and magazines. Imagine a mean old man or a Luke Green or somebody. Yeah I
could turn I think I could turn this into a full blown like seminar workshop probably. Find your
inner J Jonah Jameson. Yeah I could fill up arenas and I could do a whole I could have a whole racket
out of this. Probably. Yeah probably. Cut five sentences from that and get me more pictures of
Spider-Man. Yeah sure. Okay but so I mean this has been plugged into California Adventure and it's
in most of the other parks somewhere and also via Jim Hill there's been discussion and rumors
that maybe there is some revamp of this. I don't know if you guys caught that but that maybe they
do a new edition of Philhar Magic much like they would do with Phantasmac where they get in
you know let it go. Right. Because there is you know we need to find one place in the theme park
universe where let it go can play. Right. But anyway I mean there's like
are you potentially excited or about or interested in like all right well I'll pepper in some newer
sequences. Does that do anything for you? Does that do anything for me? Is if it's done like this?
No not at all. It's just it's another like greatest hits with a little bit. Keep in mind Donald is
still grasping for a hat. If he's still grasping for the hat but if he can sit like let him sing
like whatever. That's not how he sounds but let him sing it. Like let's see something fun like that.
Let's like let's let him get in the story more. If that's going to happen then I'm interested.
Like I well that's what I want but if it's just going to be we're going to hear the exact same
version of Adina Menzel singing let it go. No thank you. Pass. At the very least let's get more
characters. I don't even see Goofy on this thing. I don't want to just hear Goofy. He's my favorite.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean I like that. Let's get something going where I can see my favorites. There was that
show I think Jim and Lynn were talking about it pretty recently. The Mickey Mouse clubhouse is that
it? Where like Mickey ran a nightclub and all the characters are there. Yes. Oh yeah. Like that's fun.
Okay sure. I just like it does seem I want more characters. I want more interaction. I want it to
actually feel really specific to my experience at the park and not just like I'm listening to the
exact same song. Sure. Yeah. That's what I'm looking for. They just laid one new element over
something that already existed. Yeah. Well you know I was thinking if they're going to put new
movies in it's very expected to do Frozen or Tangled or what have you but in the many many
years since this experience was created Disney's bought a couple of new movies. Oh interesting.
I mean you got your Marvels and you got your Pixars but you also have the entire Fox archive
and I thought well what about you know some of the films that Fox has done in the early 2000s
part of the Fox films Wikipedia that I looked at. Go ahead. And maybe you could put some of those
in you know. What if what if Donald you know got like what if the hat ended up on a golf course
giving Donald the opportunity to interrupt a backswing by Bagger Vance. I mean that sure.
What the famous Bagger Vance song that he'll interrupt the famous musical number. I do that
is an old video I did also when we're talking about my old things. Oh yeah I like that video.
Yeah I did a Will Smith Bagger Vance. So y'all my name is Bagger Vance.
What was it? Time to do the Bagger Vance dance. It was the rap he did for Bagger Vance. Yeah yeah
if he had done a credits. Sorry. There's that guy on Twitter who does those all the time.
Oh Dan. It's funnier than what I did. Yes there you go. But you know also he could
you know you could the the hat could go to medieval times he could get caught up in a
ultimate joust gone wrong with Martin Lawrence's Black Knight. Oh wow. Sure. Who wouldn't love to
see Donald's interacting with. Sure. You know he could I mean scariest he's already been underwater
but if you wanted to do a new underwater sequence and you know somebody a little less fun than the
Little Mermaid. What if Donald got stuck in a pool with swim fan. Don't forget Disney owns swim fan.
Sure. I'll be honest I did forget. I think we all forgot and let's never forget we all must
remember one thing it all began with a mouse and now the mouse owns swim fan. But don't forget all
those fox animated movies we like Ice Age, Epic. You could interrupt you could interact with my
favorite Steven Tyler's Nimgaloo. Yeah. I think they were. Who are you? I'm Nimgaloo.
I think Nimgaloo that is good. I really that's my favorite so far. Nimgaloo is very small. He
could like sweep up Nimgaloo and then Donald puts the hat back on. He's got a Nimgaloo crawling
around his head. That'd be great. Yeah. And also if you wanted to do you know that corner of the
park has guardians and monsters after dark. If you wanted to do a darker one that's just for parents
well what if the hat flew all the way to France and ended up in the in the backpack of Maggie
Grace right before she's taken by Albanian sex traffickers in the world of taken and now you let
all the events of taken play out but Liam Neeson is after Donald. He's after his daughter but without
knowing it Donald is stuck in the backpack. Right. He's trying to get his hat back. That's
fun. That's cute. That would make that story cuter. And you know you could do that's a perfect
excuse for new dialogue as he can grumble about you know Albanian sex trafficker.
Hopefully do they do they have classic dialogue from that old guy where he says Albanian sex
trafficker in any of his old curtains. Oh maybe. He might have just been talking about how he was
going to use one. Well don't forget there's also three. His personal life. There's three takens
and one of them Liam Neeson gets taken. Oh yeah. And because there's like a sequence where like
the daughter is in the apartment and he tells her where to find a grenade in the apartment
and she's like I think it's a flashbang and he's like hold it hold it hold it throw it in the air
because he he can tell by how far away the pop it like how far away they explain he can like
tell like OK that was that far it sounded that far away. I've been in a car for five minutes so
this is the mile radius I've been in. Why haven't I watched the other takens. Yeah I haven't seen
them. Yeah. So maybe Donald could be the one getting taken. Sure. Or doing the phone call.
Have that duck quack. Make him quack. I'll listen to the quack and listen to the echo and the
reverberation. I have a very specific set of skills. Let him do it. I will find you. I'll kill
you. That's I mean that's great. That's obviously more than they want to do though with these moves.
I'm just saying keep your expectations low for the PhilharMagic story. It will all have to be
with pre-recorded Liam Neeson. It has to be the characters have to have said the things they said
before and have to be reused I think. Unless they go all out. I hope they do. I hope he gets taken
and sees Bagger Vance. I hope that does happen. Every one of these yes and when we need some saves
him he can say oh boy. My Donald's getting there. I just don't want to blow out the pipes. All I can do is
are quack quack quack. That's it. That's much better than what I did. But I can't talk like that. I can just talk. No I can't do that.
I don't think I can do the duck trick. Yeah that's it. All right well those are great ideas for
plusing this thing up. But hey since we got a little extra to this is finally a topic where
we don't require two and a half hours minimum. Right. We can do something we haven't done in a
very long time which is souvenir showdown. We've had a couple of these in the past. Isn't it Smackdown?
I think it's Smackdown. Could be. It's been long enough we don't know. Nobody's really holding
us to the fire. Souvenirs Smackdown. I'm surprised I got that close. I got half of it. Yeah that was close.
Sure. The classic segment which I'm now told is called Souvenirs Smackdown. I think. We all go
onto eBay and we try to find the oddest piece of Disney or universe or theme park
merch in general that we can possibly find and we'll have each other guess what we think that
would or should cost. Who thinks they have the least weird one? I think I do. Okay yours famously
the first one you did was not weird at all. No not weird at all. What was it? I don't remember.
It was something about orange bird I think. Oh yeah yeah. I think it was weird. It was a children's
inflatable pool toy with the orange bird on it. I went and found an actual interesting thing as
opposed to an oddball oddity. Okay. So let's see what we've got. So this one but the thing that
has always struck me with this with the eBay culture in general is the massive price. You know
how the way the price can fluctuate on stuff. Sure. So this is I have a picture here to show you.
Tomorrowland opening day Disneyland classic cup collectible 1998. So this is from the infamous
Tomorrowland redo. I'll show you that. Oh no it hurts. It's a souvenir plastic cup. Okay.
Sort of a gold steampunky top. Yes. Okay. How much do you think this sells for? Well let me ask you
this. What did you check? Is it what's how it's listed or have you checked and seen that the
same thing has actually sold for the money? How what it is currently listed. I see okay.
Okay. Because sometimes I do see things that are listed as like a thousand dollars and if you
search for the same thing and sold it sold for much less or there's nothing else there's no
precedent even for it. So it feels like people are just guessing. Yeah. I'm going to guess that is
three hundred dollars. Okay Scott. Then I maybe I got to go higher to make it crazier four hundred
fifty dollars. Well gentlemen I'm here to tell you that you have any number of choices of how much
you want to pay. You can pay thirty two dollars. You can pay eighty nine ninety nine. You can pay
a thousand dollars. You can pay a hundred and twenty five for the same. You just want to buy
the topper for the same product. You can find it listed numerous times on eBay for any price you
could imagine. So that's okay. So do this real quick. Search for it and hit sold items completed
items and it'll show you exactly how much it's been selling. It is actually sold. I mean with
the actual the prices that you tend to see the most tend to be about twenty four ninety nine.
Okay. So somebody was getting like that's a reasonable price. So that's probably how much
it was. It's one listing when I first found it was one hundred ninety nine ninety nine. So that was
two hundred dollars. They they're the ones who came down to eighty nine ninety nine and that one
comes with a collectible coin. Oh, which I actually think you should just sell on its own.
Sure. Sure. Might go for something. Yeah. So without a coin, people are trying to sell this for
close to a hundred bucks more or a thousand bucks, whatever price your heart desires. You can find
in this list. I really want to pay a thousand dollars for this. I thought it was very strange.
This kind of this thing that it seems like a lot of people are like, yes, I have this opening day
for New Tomorrowland sort of thing and I'm going to flip it. And there's just a dozen or more
people with the same thought. And you can and I will have this item for sale next to it, the same
item that costs a hundred like hundred times less. I bet I could get one of these for seventeen
dollars. Oh, you can also there's other listings for just the topper. If you just want the top of
that bottle, you just want the straw. Are you thinking about getting it? Not really. OK,
it's not a thing I have affection for. OK, I think I was just I don't even remember how I found it
searching around and then I just couldn't not find it. I just kept finding pages of it. Right. I
think everyone needs to send them to you. Somebody has one that you would send to Jason for free.
Sure. Is that good hydraulic fluid holder? Actually, I'll say that it is. It does look
like it holds a lot of liquid, so it would be good for storing hydraulic fluid. Right.
Well, that's great. All right. You two tell me about your weird ones.
Well, yeah, you want you want me to go for it? I think so. Go for it. I'm pretty I'm pretty
pleased with this and I'm pretty pleased that, you know, we have we talked about doing this months
ago and I'm really happy that it's still up there. And I think you guys will recognize it when I spin
it around and show you. But first, let me read the title of the item, which is Hard Rock Theme Park
Mick Jagger Rolling Stones Lip Statue artwork. Look at this guy. No. Pretty familiar. We know him
from Hard Rock Park. It's a statue that slips and the teeth are piano keys and a big gross tongue
sticking out of it and weird mismatchy legs, ones in like a kiss boot and ones in a more of a
Disney shoe with tiger striped socks. It is one of those bizarre sculptures that was created for
Hard Rock Park and it is just on on eBay. Very small description. Rockin' Lips Statue. Unusual
Rockin' Lips Statue from Hard Rock Theme Park. Wow. This fiberglass masterpiece of artwork is
11 feet wide, 12 feet deep and seven feet tall. Great attention grabber for a business, concert
halls, theme parks or amusement parks. Very different. Designed after legendary Mick Jagger.
Call for shipping information. Maybe less, the description not super interesting, but it is,
you would go to pick it up in Georgetown, South Carolina and it is an odd user on eBay
called Po Boys Discount, which otherwise is just selling like industrial kitchen equipment.
Like they have like a flash fryer or their most recent item put up today is a
souvenir bottle of popcorn kernels from something called Studebakers Myrtle Beach.
So go to Po Boys Discount if you want a Mick Jagger lips statue, but also
you know, a electric thermo food finishing oven for $400.
It is weird. I do not know why they ended up with this. What you are saying is they have a
warehouse. Yeah. They have a warehouse to hold bulk goods. It is all bizarre kitchen
bullshit, which might be useful if you are trying to start a restaurant in the Carolinas.
Also may have been a lot like an auction lot that they bought from Hard Rock Park.
This might all have been used. That is a good point. All those barbecues or whatever.
Actually their second most expensive item, the Cleveland Tilt Skillet. It is a brazing skillet.
Makes soups and the large yield can produce 40 gallons. So if you want 40 gallons of soup,
go to Po Boys Discount. Would you guys like to put a ballpark on what you might purchase that for?
Five grand. Jason?
Yeah, I was thinking around there too. I will go higher. I will go 10 grand asking.
It is a little bit lower, but you are closer in the over under. It is $8,000.
$8,000. I could pay $385 for the next 24 months.
Did everyone go like, oh the Mick Jagger statue? When you guys think about Hard Rock Park and you
think about that statue, do you immediately go like, oh Mick Jagger?
No. No.
It actually feels more Steven Tyler-y to me with the big tongue.
It also just feels like a little generic rock and roll. The lips and the tongue wag and rock
and roll. That rock and roll divorced from all known rock and roll.
From the way anyone actually listens to rock and roll. No, but apparently they are,
I take that description to mean they are scientifically exactly structured to Mick
Jagger's actual lips. So there you go. Wow. Piece of Hard Rock Park history. It never stops. The
tale of Hard Rock Park never steps unfolding. When we have Binkowski on, maybe he just has a
couple lying around. Oh man.
Like prototypes. Maybe they'll just give us one for.
They'll just give us each one lip statue. That's what I'm hoping for.
All right. Mike.
Okay. So this is probably a full episode if I really want a deep dive, which probably people
would say we're good, but let me show, well, okay. Let me describe what this is first and
then I'll show you what it looks like. Rare VTG 1950s sterling silver,
Chuck-O the birthday clown wishing ring Disneyland.
Chuck-O the birthday clown. And let me show you what the ring looks like. Here it is.
I have it on the TV. Here he is. He's Chuck-O the birthday clown. Now that didn't work how
I wanted it to. Now you might say, I get so many notifications from Disneyland. So when I put my
phone, so that's Chuck-O. Here's the thing. Chuck-O is a real clown. He died about 10 years ago. He
was a local Los Angeles clown and he had a TV show where kids would celebrate their birthday.
And like, it was a long waiting list to get on Chuck-O's TV show, like a five year waiting
list to celebrate your birthday on Chuck-O's show. And Chuck-O not only, actually now I should put
that actually back up. Chuck-O not only has this wishing ring that they would give out at Disneyland,
he also, and this comes with it, was the menu for a restaurant at Disneyland. What? So gourmet
Disneyland children's plates. Oh, children love grilled filet of soul. Roast turkey, broiled lamb
chop, ground around steak patty, jello and cream. 25 cents. What the fuck is bib juices? Bib juices,
no idea. Pear and cottage cheese salad. I mean, hamburger in a bun with cat soup. Yes. This isn't
says copyright 1961 and it's the happiest clown in town. It says, and Chuck-O's face is on the
other side and it's terrifying. Yes. Well, wait, go back, go back. I think I know the menu is a mask.
The menu is also a mask. So you can wear Chuck-O's face. You can wear Chuck-O's face. Look, there's
eye holes. And here is a headshot of Chuck-O on KBC seven, our local affiliate. Chuck-O the birthday clown.
So Chuck-O was a local LA children's performer who had a Disneyland present. Yes, that is correct.
That's why I'm saying Patreon exclusive Chuck-O. We have to learn about Chuck-O. We have to learn
about Chuck-O. Now you might say, please, can you play me Chuck-O's theme song? And the answer is,
yes, I can. How many months have you been sitting on this? What many months? Oh my God. His name was
Randy, Randy Runyon, I believe was the man's name. And here is his theme song. The heir to the canyon
fortune.
Too much echo.
I hate you, Chuck-O. So there's Chuck-O. He was a legend in Los Angeles. Chuck-O dumped over.
So Chuck-O, yeah. Did you find out more about his Disneyland presents? That's what I have. I'm
trying to figure out what restaurant it was and I can't. It's not easily accessible for me here. I
should have done more. I honestly, I forgot to look. We're going to be like, who's the
reporter in Zodiac? We're going to be like at the LA Times building asking to see their microfiche.
Like, sorry, we're trying to figure out Chuck-O. We've almost got the whole picture put together.
Here's the, I'm finding there's a, oh, Disneyland Hotel is where the restaurant was. Oh, weird.
So that's a little, that's kind of why it wasn't. Right, not in the park. Not in the park, but they
did essentially have a mall built into the Disneyland Hotel for a long time. And he would
open the coverage of the Santa Claus Lane Parade, the Hollywood Boulevard Christmas parade, which
still happens to this day. He would bust through a big drum and bow and salute. That'd be the
beginning of the TV coverage. He also made a lot of appearances at supermarkets and shopping centers.
He'd pull into say the Topanga Plaza, my childhood mall. And there'd be thousands of people as far
as you could see. Thousands of people would show up. He was very popular, it sounds like.
Yeah, totally missed this guy. Chuck-O. Chuck-O. He was at Disney. He opened, wait a minute,
after leaving television, he opened Chuck-O's Party House at Jungle Land in Thousand Oaks.
Jeez. What's any of that? I don't know what that is. We gotta get there.
This is the history of where I grew up. I don't know about Jungle Land or Chuck-O's Party House.
So that's why we gotta do it. That's why I said we gotta do it. Patreon on
Chuck-O's Party House. This is, he may have died a few years ago,
but like they say, nothing stays dead forever. No. Chuck-O's still alive.
Chuck-O does feel like, this feels like the start of a Stephen King work.
If we wanted to find out more about Chuck-O, we could read his biography written by his
widow Millie, the biography from 1994, which is called Our Clowns Hatched.
This is terrifying. Chuck-O. Maybe Halloween Patreon.
Oh no, I'm too scared. We don't all love haunts now, Mike.
I don't wanna go to Chuck-O's Party House. Would you rather go to Halloween Horror Nights
or go to Chuck-O's? Well, luckily I can't go to,
I'll talk about Chuck-O's Party House, but if it was still there, I wouldn't wanna go there.
And I don't wanna go to wherever it used to be. It's haunted.
Yeah, it for sure is haunted. Where is he buried?
Oh, my under this apartment. Oh no, Mike's pulling off his face
to reveal Chuck-O's face. I'm Chuck-O.
He was always a local clown. He's shoving bib juice down our
throats. I gotta figure out what bib juice is. It's weird I don't know what bib juice is.
For sure you drink bib juice. You just don't know it.
What does it mean? I don't know.
It sounds to me like if your bib caught all of the various foods that have spilled on you as a baby
and then it was all combined into a mush. Yeah, maybe.
So maybe it's like all the kitchen's droppings like ground up.
Is it a name for like, it looks like it might be a name for the juices that come in bags that are
put in boxes and you put the boxes in the dispenser. Maybe.
Do you know what I'm talking about? If you ever look at a restaurant next to the soda fountain,
there's the juice dispenser. Those are boxes and those are industrial boxes filled with bags of
juice. Why would you buy that? Why would you sell it as that?
Bib juice. There'll be a Patreon on bib juices too.
I'm very unsettled now. Do you want to guess how much that
wishing ring plus the menu and the headshot. That's a lot of stuff. If you're a Chuck-O fan,
that's invaluable. Let me guess $600. Jason? I'll say $100.
$425. $425. Oh, okay.
So I win the over under. So Scott wins that.
Wow. For all that Chuck-O memorabilia.
That doesn't mean that I have to have it now. That means that you've bid on it with $600.
You offered $600. You won it. That's where bib juice comes from.
So these are like hotels. The orange juice dispenser machine, I guess is known
in the beverage industry as bib juice. Well, don't throw that beverage industry
insider shit at me. Yeah, I don't.
Tell me on your menu what it is, Chuck-O. Even ground round is an old food turn. There used
to be a chain of restaurants called the ground round. That's the only way I know. It was like
an early Benegans TGI Fridays kind of place. They would bring you popcorn instead of bread.
Fresh pop, buttery popcorn. I like that.
Yeah. Free bib juice.
Free. The ring was not mass produced item.
The woman who's selling her aunt worked at Pars, which is a jewelry company at this time,
and told me they were commissioned for a celebrity's child's birthday party
and were given out as party favors to the children who attend it.
There were only 50 ordered and the extras were returned back for credit.
Here. This is a real
hardcore Chuck-O fan delight. Was this celebrity arrested and
put away where they could never? Doesn't mention that.
Yeah. Never terrified children again.
The extras were returned back for credit because the people who received them died mysteriously
soon after. Wait a minute. Check his fingers. It's the ring again.
Oh, it's the ring again. The dozenth kid this month.
I. Yeah. So, all right. So this is-
Chuck-O might be one of our greatest discoveries on this podcast.
Chuck-O, I think this is another, we have to look into a lot of different IP purchasing,
like Marvel McFay, of course, famously and other characters.
You mean that we own the rights.
So we would be able to control Marvel McFay and like license movies and stuff.
Bear Metal Family.
Chuck-O.
And I think Chuck-O, I'm sure the family owns the intellectual property on Chuck-O,
but perhaps that's something we look into when one of us takes over the mantle of Chuck-O.
Did Jason, are you interested?
Yeah, you did. He pointed at me so fast.
I'll be Chuck-O if you won't. I will take over as Chuck-O. I will declare that. But if you want
Chuck-O, I'm willing to give it to you.
I mean, if my country is asking me to serve, by which I mean being Chuck-O,
and if the curse is not giving me any choice.
Well, maybe it is. Maybe it's more like the Harry Potter wand and the Chuck-O. When we
get the ring, it'll choose one of us.
Yeah, it's not going to fit all three of us.
Obviously, because Jason and I are both willing, it's of course going to choose
Scott and Scott will have to become Chuck-O.
No, I'm a host. It's a parasite that you're going to buy that mask. You're going to take it out of
the envelope and it's going to come to life and press itself against my face and be my face.
Yep. And you will.
And my blood will become bib juice.
And podcast the ride will be hosted by Mike, Jason and Chuck-O.
Scott is...
I'm more fun than Scott was.
The ratings go through the roof. America looks Chuck-O.
Sorry, Scott.
You're always missing something.
You are unfortunately Harvey Dent and Chuck-O is Batman.
Chuck-O is the hero we need, but you are the hero we deserve. Unfortunately, Chuck-O.
If I can fight it off and Chuck-O only takes over half of my face, then it's exactly the Harvey
Well, what if you were two-faced with the Chuck-O?
Oh, no.
Wow.
I want wine. No, you want bib juice.
Oh, man.
The podcast the ride is hosted by... The next episode we'll start with,
it's a podcast hosted by two theme park fans and one man whose face was half taken over by a clown
mask and he airs out his soul's intergrievences in every episode.
I feel like fan art is really called for right now. I have to say.
Oh, no.
Scott Two-Face.
I'll only look at half of it.
Scott Two-Face as Chuck-O.
Well, Scott, how are you fighting Chuck-O today?
I filled a barrel with bib juice. I'm trying to age it into Sauvignon Blanc.
In seven years, the bib juice will be sweet wine again.
That is the end.
Stop it. Stop, Chuck-O.
Aaron's my wife now. No, you stay away from her.
She is also unfortunately Chuck-O.
Our clowns hatch.
The run of the rings leapt into her ear and crawled into her brain and made her Chuck-O.
Oh, she's Chuck-O now.
This is no longer the PhilharMagic episode. It is the Chuck-O episode.
I never thought I'd miss the PhilharMagic episode so much.
Oh, God. We barely survived Podcast The Ride. I'm going to have bad dreams forever.
I almost choked to death trying to do a bad Donald. This was a harrowing one.
But go to Patreon.com slash Podcast The Ride where eventually, unfortunately,
there will be a Chuck-O episode.
Hey, meet me there.
I'm Chuck-O. I'm Chuck-O. Scott's Chuck-O.
Scott's Chuck-O.
Oh, no. Stop it.
I'm getting out of here. If you want to plug anything else, do it yourself.
All right. Well, you go to all of our stuff, Podcast The Ride Instagram.
We can email us, PodcastTheRide.gmail. We're on Twitter at PodcastTheRide.
Email spam. That's what I want. I want viruses.
Classic Chuck-O.
We have shirts at T-Public, but we may have to add a Chuck-O shirt,
an unlicensed Chuck-O shirt. We have to ask the family if that's okay to do some Chuck-O merch.
Scott-O, Chuck-Scott.
Once you put the shirt on, you could never take it off.
The shirt will become one with you. You will laugh like that forever.
Honestly, it's a better way to live.
And just a reminder to all our listeners, sometimes dead is better.
Sometimes you don't want to bury the Chuck-O ring in the pet cemetery.
That's true. So I think, yeah, that we're good.
We'll see you later.
See you in your dreams.
This has been a Forever Dog Production, executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bowham, Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook.