Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate where we have just returned from the exotic
kingdom of Agrabah as witnessed in the 2019 remake, live action remake of Aladdin directed by Guy
Richie. How do you feel boys? How you doing? I feel like I maybe had a full podcast length of
thoughts in me as soon as we left the theater, if we had recorded it from our seats, but in the time
it took to leave, get a bite and get over here, which was, you know, what 45 minutes or so it's
all gone. This movie is like already vanished from my brain as if Jafar made a wish and made it never
happen. As if his infamous red staff vexed you and forced you to forget your opinions.
Weld me into a famous, one of his famous spells. Now, one of you was the first one to propose
seeing this movie. I think this was, yeah, I think this may have been my fault.
And now I'm, I don't know, buyer's remorse. I walked in thinking it was going to be more of a
catastrophe than it was. More of a train wreck than it was. And I have to say there was stuff I liked
in it. You know, this isn't, this is our, our, one of our, the newer topical epi, you know, we did
galaxy's edge. That was topical, you know, we did the live show and that came out very quickly,
I guess, technically topical and we're doing, we're about to record one, all our thoughts about,
you know, the bar subpoena and, you know, we're going to be topical in that regard too. Yes.
You know, we're going to branch away from the theme park stuff a little bit. Sure. But yeah,
for now, this is tangentially related. Yeah. Hey, no, we're getting right to it.
Three weeks after the three week. To me, the part, it was funny, like the longer and longer we got
away from it, the funnier it got. So you're saying three weeks was the funniest though? No, I'm saying
it could be even fine. I'm saying we could put it out six weeks from now. So where would it not be?
What time period would it not be funny? And would it be a year after it came out? And any other time
would have been funny. To me, it would have been funny if we did it two years from now. I think
that would be very funny because yeah, it's kind of, it feels very ethereal. Well, no, no one will
watch this film in two years. Probably not. There will be zero views of this film in 2021.
It is. Yeah. Now. Okay. So let me say something positive, though. Yes. It is good. It is good
that a big blockbuster American made movie, uh, it stars a primarily middle Eastern cast
in a movie industry that primarily, uh, casts, uh, middle Easterners as the villains, uh, in a country
that has a lot of issues with a llama phobia, uh, Islamophobia. I was going to say, is that how you
pronounce it? Islamophobia. Um, until we say the word right, we won't be able to solve the problem.
Yeah. Uh, uh, it is, it is good that this was such a hit, uh, now. So you saying that it's going to
let you be able to trash it guilty conscious, uh, no guilty conscience. I do think that is a positive
thing. I don't know why, uh, Lily white British man, Guy Ritchie had to direct it. That was,
I mean, I guess, I don't know. I mean, maybe he was had a passion for telling the story. I don't know.
I suppose. Yeah, maybe everybody knew that when Guy Ritchie got his hands on the, if you want to,
if you're going to see the famous marketplace through Guy Ritchie's eyes and you're doing
parkour between those alleyways and hopping around on those tents, he's going to bring that to life
like you've never seen. And we weren't, we all whisked away. And I, I said, just don't like
someone somewhere must've been excited about that. If we, when we get the guy who made that
movie like floating away with Madonna, when he gets his, let's get Madonna's ex-husband.
I think that might've been the early, they just wanted to hear Madonna stories. I'm going to say
now here's one of my criticisms. Not enough Guy Ritchie indulgent bullshit, like not enough quick
cuts for me. Not enough like, cause I like those two Sherlock Holmes movies. You put that they're
on cable. You put one of those on, you zone out for an hour and a half. You don't have a lot of
room in these movies. I don't think there's not a ton of time or time of room for you to like make
changes or no, there was like one Abu bullet time kind of flip where he catches the lamp.
There's a slow down. Oh, so by the way, spoilers too, I think, cause we have to spoil the movie.
I think, Oh yeah. Well, all right. So spoilers. And with that in mind, Jafar gets too greedy
and he ends up becoming a genie and he gets stuck in a lamp forever. Um, big spoilers, big
spoilers. I suppose our, is that the genie fucks the genie that is not real. He does not. We don't
spread that vicious rumor to the genie fucks. I mean, I guess he eventually does eventually does
fuck. You're right. That's fair, but he's not the genie when it happens. So that is spoiler alert.
A former genie. Yes. So tell me about your husband. Well, he has been alive for a thousand years and
I met him while I was a servant. And now he's not a, he's been a real man for three years in
which time we've had children and now, and he's grown a very handsome beard. Yes. And we see all
the world in our nice boat. It's a bookend that is only in, that is a like 0.5% of the runtime of
the movie. It's important to know that Will Smith has a beard and sails the world with his children
who are named before they exist. Um, and it's all the whole movie is being told from that perspective,
except never in the middle or at the end. Yeah. I don't know. I'm interested. Like they were like,
well, what's the genie's arc? And this is actually interesting because I thought I actually did see
that clip of him like going with his love at the end of the movie, but I wasn't thinking that far
because I was hoping that like we could get a whole series of sequels and we could redo return
of the, of Jafar and then whatever the third one was called and we get more of this, but it seems
like they really cut it off there because it seems like he doesn't have magical powers anymore at the
end of the movie. Cause Jeannie in the cartoon was just a fun Jeannie. He didn't have the little wrist
restraints and he could still do crazy fun stuff, but it seems like now Will Smith is just a man.
But it does, I mean, Jafar does say at the end of the movie, like I'll get you, I'll be back.
Like true. But I'm just saying, I guess there's a way and like, oh, I had my powers after all.
Like just a quick, if they did return of Jafar in this, this, this lineup in this,
in this way, would they have to then in keeping with the pattern, Will Smith would not come back
and he'd be played by Seth MacFarlane. It always has to be the Jeannie and the second one only has
to be played by the voice of a cartoon dad. I think, yes, I think Seth has been on TV now for
a few years. So I think he's ready to go for another go at the feature film world, which he took.
And I want to know what he'd look like if he was fucking jacked. Oh man. Let's see Seth MacFarlane
with like 70 more pounds of muscle. Yeah. HGH Seth MacFarlane. That's something we all didn't
know we wanted, but we now know we want it. The Jeannie was so jacked. It was approaching like
body horror, like Cronenberg level. Like, agreed. Yeah. The, the never had a friend like me sequence
looked like it took place in the twin peaks of black lodge in the back where you were the backwards
talking man is. I, I was comfortable with his physique. I thought that it was, I didn't have
really a thought that like, it's too weird or I'm too grossed out by it. I thought it was fine.
But the combined with the blue, giant hulking blue muscles. I don't know. I'm surprised that
Jason would say that he had a problem with it where comic book fans, you know, there's plenty
of characters that are blue and are jacked up. Oh, I didn't, I didn't mean body horror as like a,
as a bad thing. That is just a description of what it is. Like, uh, this is a counterpoint.
You were wrong scenario. You're saying it in a nice way. Yeah, I'm saying it as like, that is the
thing that I am pointing to, but yes, there is like a Rob Liefeld like exaggerated physicality.
I just think body horror generally would dictate that you found something horrifying
and not pleasant. I was thinking more of it as like a genre-y kind of thing. I, I think-
Is there a body, is there a horror body horror movie where somebody just gets fucking strong?
Is that the horror? Just gets strong. Well, the Josh Trink Fantastic Four sort of.
They unlock the process of getting the powers. Oh yeah. I guess that's sort of a,
that's more of a mutantism. Cause it, yeah, if he just got jacked, let me, that's fun. Let's get that
movie going. No horror there. Just a body, just a good looking body. I mean, now it's, I mean,
I think the reason probably why I wanted to do this, I thought, you know, we like to sort of,
we like to watch schlocky things and kind of quote unquote dunk on them as it were. Uh, and from the
early signs, the early footage made you think that the genie was going to be rendered just horribly.
And I think it did look markedly worse in those first few previews than it did in the, in the
finished. Yeah, it looked fine. Uh, yeah. I mean, all bizarre and all like not nearly as lovable as
the like detail-free Robin Williams genie, but it does make me wonder why do they, what is the rush
to get these things out where like we need to get out a 70% rendered, uh, with blue characters in
general. It happened with the genie, it happened with Sonic. People are upset about the rendering
of our blue characters. And they're upset about the re-rendering of Sonic. That's been really the
next. Did it come out already? I feel like some, I saw some sort of image. Isn't there, isn't there
a new one? I don't think so. Look it up, please. Cause I think you probably, somebody was trolling
or somebody was making a comedy, uh, Sonic. There's no way dentures were photoshopped into his mouth.
Yeah. I think, I mean, obviously look, uh, the studio system is a mess as far as movies are
concerned. You know, these things get released dates before they get a writer and director,
for gosh sake. Sure. So yeah, that's probably the problem here is that, uh, stuff isn't ready. Um,
so I guess you have to judge these things on the basis of, well, live action Aladdin is going to
happen. Like that, like what's my solution to anything I didn't like about that movie
could only be solved by none of it existing, but it's going to exist. So you have to judge it on
its merits. Did Guy Ritchie do a good job with the thing that would happen with or without him? Did
Will Smith do a good job with the thing that would have, would have been Josh Gad had he not said yes?
Right. Gad was number two, probably. Do we know, was there a number one or was Will always number
one? I would think Will would be the number one choice. Yeah. Like that makes sense to me. But
should it have been because here's the like Will Smith, here's things that the original
genie did that Will Smith cannot do. Lots of voices and sing. Well, here's what I will say.
I would, I appreciate, I believe I liked this movie the most of the three of us.
Yeah. I think I'm in between. What I liked about it was unlike maybe a Beauty and the Beast,
uh, they didn't feel like they had to imitate the cartoon. I felt like sometimes you're watching
some of these other ones and they're like trying to do an impression of the cartoon
and that really is a bummer. That kind of, so like Will Smith can't do Robin Williams.
The guy playing Jafar was not doing any sort of version of what Jafar in the movie was doing.
And I kind of appreciate that. It lets me like forget the stuff that would sort of take me out
of it. I think were the songs. Cause you'd be like, Oh yeah, that song from that other movie.
Yes. And like the rest of it tonally is not like, it doesn't quite jump ahead of the bread line.
And he still sings. Yes. Like, yeah, like they hire this actor and still make him sing like a,
like thirties guys and dolls man. Right. Like that's the, that's the thing that it didn't sort
of fit with me, but I kind of liked that. Like Will Smith is, is at least not trying to do,
cause like who would be the equivalent of voice man now? I, I, Rich Little, perhaps.
Now it's Rich Little. 80 year old Rich Little. It was Robin Williams to update it.
Jonathan Winters past. Did he do a lot of celebrity impressions? He did a lot of voices,
didn't he? Yeah, but we need celebrity impressions. I think again, Seth MacFarlane.
Seth MacFarlane or Frank Caliendo. Frank Caliendo. That's one idea. I think I'd like,
I think how I would like this movie like 10 times less budget and it's Frank Caliendo.
That would be, I like the idea of that too. That's a good word. I can't deny. That may have been a
Zucker brothers, you know, that we just missed. Like that could have happened. Yeah. Like movie.
Yeah. I'm into that. Pretend like, pretend I'm your coach, you know, like I'm John Madden, let's say.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean the first, the first, the original Aladdin, what did it have going for it?
It had some great Broadway musical style music and it happened during the Disney animation
Renaissance, you know, with Little Mermaid and Aladdin and Lion King. Directors who would come
off of Little Mermaid. Is that correct? Musker and Clements are the directors, I believe. So
they're, yeah, they're polished from this movie. It went really well and took it right into another
great one. And, and you know, lots of looseness, animation stuff, stuff you can get away with in
animation that translating to, I think when we were walking out of theater, the phrase I said was like,
well, that was, it's much more expensive to do 2D animation, but you do have more freedom,
but it is cheaper to do after effects. Cause like some of the C, some of the CG stuff in this was a
little, I mean, it didn't help that felt like another AMC that was not bright enough. Like that.
Yeah. We saw end game on a screen that was not bright enough at the AMC. Although we're all
used to these, these IMAXs now. So what are we, what's the, that should be the standard I feel like
of brightness? I guess so. I feel like, but I feel like I never have that problem at the
historic Vista, the one screen theater. And well, that's, yeah, they're, they're much more on top,
excuse me, on top of it than like a big multiplex, I guess. Yeah. What's up with the, now we say,
where's the, where's the brightness issue? Is it in the projector? Is it the screen itself? Does it
need a coat of bright, blindingly bright pain? Is it the footage? Cause we were having this problem
with Game of Thrones. I feel like it's some sort of bulb. I feel like a bulb needs to be better.
I think it's a bulb. I'll play play for the bulb. I'll get one in there. Every time I walk into a
theater, I'll just hand them a bulb and say, insert this please. Yeah. We should all carry around a
bulb when we go to a movie. Just to make sure we visit a theater. Cause it's, yeah, I assume it's
a bulb, but somebody correct us if it's not. I wish it was a live show. Cause obviously five people
would be like, no, it's the, it's the this. Yeah. Yeah. It's the first one we've done since the live
show. And yeah, Jason, I really feel like you were the most supported in several scenarios where
here you'd be just hanging on the vine. Yeah. Let's going, what are you talking about? You got so much
support. Yeah. And is it now, and now I'm worried about the next scenario where you don't have
people shouting, no, Jason isn't insane. And here's what the thing was. I, you know, I, it's just a
thing that I'm just used to. So it was nice to have some support. I, we were saying early like that,
thank you to everyone who came to the live show a million times. Thank you. The warmest crowd I
have ever seen. So fun. Very nice. You know, the, the satisfaction down the road, it comes, it comes,
you know, I don't need a Greek chorus backing me up every day. It's okay. But I would like if then,
if at a future live show, somebody shows up with a handwritten list of like, here's every time that
Jason was right and you guys shout them down or didn't listen or weren't curious enough to
find it out for yourself. Didn't know your English history. Didn't know.
Britain's wars, a list of 36 points where we were, we were wrong and Jason was right. But I will
admit, I will be the first to admit, I do not quite know what's going on with dark digital footage.
No. I think, yeah, as Mike said earlier, like the deadlines are kind of in place before the work
starts, you know? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Weird system. And it's based on a company's financial quarters.
It based on like, well, we need one here and we need one there and we need one here.
These movies are also just such a count on a steadfast money makers because parents just go,
I don't know, what am I going to, we got to kill three hours.
Cause like this is three weeks in and this, we were in a full, it was like full screening.
Part of not doing it right away. It was like, I don't want to be in a sort of empty theater so I
can kind of laugh at it. But there wasn't enough to laugh at and packed, not a seat in the house.
Yeah. School's out. School's out. Nice. But still three weeks later. Three weeks later. Yeah,
that's true. It's a steady, it's a dependable. It's going to fill the Disney coffers.
Yeah. For a little while. Which maybe we have to thank this film because ultimately some of that
money goes into the stuff that we like. Yeah. Some, yeah. In some ways, cause like if it's a
Tomorrowland scenario and it bombs, there's $200 million that were, was, was counted on.
And now we don't get a nice thing. And especially with that, we don't get a nice Tomorrowland.
But I pray to God we never see a Will Smith genie in the park. Imagine the day that there's like a
big hulking. Explain to me what your vision of the Will Smith genie in the park looks like.
Cause then I'll decide if I don't want to see him or not. Okay, there's like a flying carpet ride in
Florida. Like it's a little cheaper flying carpet ride. If they like put a giant Will Smith genie
with his big outstretched arms on the top of that and your carpets were like giving you a real good
view of his abs. They have, there's the carpet ride in Orlando. Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Dumbo. And it's just, they put Will Smith in the middle there. Center of that. If it was all,
if the carpets are surrounding and he like tells jokes every once in a while,
like he has a projection face and he tells jokes. It sounds good. You want to see those abs?
I just said better. I said better. Blue nips. I'll say this. Hulking blue nips. I'm comfortable with it.
We all perked up when the credits started because then there was a Will Smith DJ Khaled song
and we're like, oh yeah. Like that was another thing where it's like, I want more Guy Ritchie
bullshit and I want it more of that. Like I want it more. Yeah, yeah. It is the most distinct part
of the movie. Yeah. If he, if Friend Like Me was not a more traditional version and it was a Will
Smith rap like he used to do in the late nineties, I think we would have liked, now the average
movie goer, would they have liked it? That's the question. Cause these are made, these movies are
also made for the average folks to come in that aren't thinking about this thing as being kind of
a cynical move perhaps and just going, oh, I like that song from the movie 20 years ago.
Would they be upset? I don't know. Cause we all cheered when we heard the DJ Khaled version.
Because of course he yelled DJ Khaled right at the top. That's a spoiler. It goes black
and then to credits and then straight to DJ Khaled. Yeah. Really crazy moment. If DJ Khaled was
Khaled, Khaled, whatever is in the cave of wonders in the movie. Like,
Gene comes out and does, I mean, that would be awesome. That's the plus stuff. Yeah. I liked,
you know, some of the visuals and stuff in, in the black lodge, some of the body heart, like I liked
some of the visuals there. I thought Friend Like Me was pretty good. Friend Like Me is when it felt
like the movie woke up a little. Yeah. So I actually thought that version, I felt like the
first couple songs felt a little weird and the instrumentation was a little weird. It felt kind
of like, um, the arrangements were strange for a lot of these songs. Yeah. It felt like kind of,
instead of like, oh, this is a cool take on an old song. It felt a little more like karaoke version
or something. I mean, it's a cover movie. Yes, it is a cover movie. Sure. But Friend Like Me,
I did like some of the sequences. I thought it sounded okay. I thought it sounded fine.
It was like, can your friend do this? I did like that. Yeah. God, I wanted more of that. What's
wrong with you? You liked the Will Smith beat boxes. That's cause I was hoping there was more
of the DJ Khaled type rapping. So when he gave me a little- But do you like that because it's sort of bad?
Because it's sort of hokey. Well, this is the question. It's hard for me to answer at this
point because I was watching this thing and I was like, I don't know what I like. It's hard at this
point for me to really figure out what I like truly, like what I love and then what I am
entertained by. Cause like if Will Smith beat boxing is funny and weird and interesting,
but am I laughing cause it's like bad? I don't think so. It's just like Will Smith doing like
a thing I would imagine the Will Smith genie to do. So I'm entertained by it. I don't know that
I'll ever be able to solve this equation completely. But I didn't hate it cause I know
there's movies I still see where I go, oh, I hate this part or this is stupid. But I like that part.
I don't think there's anything where I'm like, oh, it's so bad. I like that. You think it's just genuinely
that's cool. That's funny. But I don't, it's not like I'm saying it like excitedly. Like it's my,
what's the last movie I really like? I don't know. Last Jedi. First reform. Last Jedi.
First reform. The favorite is a great movie. Favorite's great. Yeah. But I'm not saying it's
like that, but I did like, oh, that's, I like that. I mean, it's like that. That's the vibe of it.
I'm like, I like beat boxing. I recognize the conundrum that you kind of proposed earlier of like
they, how do you, you have to do something that he can't just do Robin Williams genie. Like a few
days ago, I watched the friend like me scene and watched Prince Ali and the cartoon version.
And it's so dynamic and it's so like, I mean, it's written for Robin Williams. Yes. But like
all the animate where you can illustrate and make them turn into anything in animation,
like they do barely a quarter of the gags in this one. That said, it is like a full screen of,
of dancers and people and stuff. And I do like the, like all the dance sequences in this movie,
I thought were very fun and interesting. That was kind of different. That's what I'm interested in
these live action stuff. When they start to, to, um, go a little off, like they start to do
something a little different than the animated ones. And, uh, so like the dance sequence where
Aladdin does a backflip. I liked when genie's controlling him. Yeah. When genius controlling
it, that was like a fun physical gag. Um, there was other stuff where it's just like, well,
the cartoon version, they didn't have, they didn't justify this, this heart. Like it just was like
all this stuff about where's a Bob well on a map or like, do we really need to pick apart that logic?
Um, yeah. Is that fun at all? There was like three extra conversations about like absolute power
corrupts absolutely in this version that I think was covered in three sentences in the original
version. Well, the original, you got what? 90 minutes. Is that right? Yeah. 90 minutes.
Why could this not have been 90? Why was this two hours 15? I think they wanted to,
I'm sure they were like, well, Jasmine doesn't have a ton to do in the original cartoon. Right.
Sure. Let's give Jasmine more to do. She has a song that feels, is it new? Is the song song?
Cause it feels like totally different. Was it Menken? No, it's a different person.
Not diverse. Uh, and the song is the shortest song. This is a black history month is the
shortest month scenario. Is it the same song twice? I don't know. Early. And then one happens when
she's about to be arrested. It becomes a music video for a little bit. And it's not the song
that Jasmine sings in the Disney's California adventure version of the show where it's like
about it being a bird in a cage. She has a whole nother song. And then the Broadway Aladdin has
additional songs. Yes. Call a proud of your boy is one of the songs, which I've heard is inspiration
for the proud boys group. The all right group. Yeah. Yeah. Which was not intended. I think Menken
wanted it in the original movie and it didn't fit. Yeah. Menken's idea was not that it was going to
be an all right anthem. And Pepe the frog was originally one of the characters that the genie
turned into. Right. It was a rejected sketch from a 93. Right. Yeah. There is like a,
the movie, the sequence of a lot of Jafar becoming the salt and is interrupted for a music video.
And then she makes an impassioned monologue to the guards, to like the lead guard. Yeah. Hakim,
I believe. Yeah. Well, I said that Huck, it seemed like she was trying to say that you shouldn't
always support the leader of the government over, you know, what logically makes sense,
which I just read as Hakim is Lindsey Graham or another Republican Senator that you feel like
they're not doing the right thing right now. They're good people. Under Mr. Tribe. Deep down,
they're good people. We should, that's, that's what Biden, that's the Biden philosophy.
Yes. Everybody calmed down. My platform, everybody calmed down. Once it already calms down,
we'll sort through this mess. And he's still in the lead. So if we had, because clearly there's
someone in the process of writing this had some, some Trump ideas. If we had to map it all. So you
think Hakim is Lindsey Graham and if he just had a change of heart or Mitch McConnell, yeah. Right.
That's what the, I mean, that's what whoever, whoever's idea was things. Yes. Uh-huh. That's
the kind of parallel. So Trump is, so Trump would be Jafar then obviously. Right. But I was proposing
is Trump the Sultan and Jaf, and deep down he's good. And that Jafar is Stephen Miller,
who may, I, there's very little photo, photo and video of him. We don't know a lot about Stephen
Miller. He may walk around the white ass with a literal snake staff and hypnotize. So that was
another change. Jafar does not turn into a giant snake. These CGI movies love giant snakes and a
giant snake does appear for one shot. And then some snails, snakes a little. Yeah. The conclusion
of the movie, a lot of the stuff from the original happens in a different order, but like there's no
Aladdin sword fighting. Like as a kid, that's what I like. Aladdin grabs a big sword and then he
stabs the snake and like, yeah. Right. They didn't do that. And then Iago doesn't do jokes anymore.
Yes. He's got a couple of lines that are kind of funny. He's got a couple of lines, but yes,
that was another. It's not full of ice cracks. He's more of a real parrot. Yeah. Another thing
that happens in these, these movies is like the comedic relief. Then he's just played straight in
the live action where the Sultan was like a doofus in the original one. Yeah. A little more goofy.
A little bit goofy. And yeah, Iago was just Gilbert Godfrey doing Gilbert Godfrey, just like
Robin Williams was doing Robin Williams. So well, and in, and then Jafar was not funny in the first
one or in this one, but he was like a bigger, crazier villain. I think if I have a big problem
with this movie, it's that everybody got flatter. Everybody, like everybody just became more of,
I don't know, they're a guy and their, their philosophy is what's interesting and say more
of the comedies put on Naseem Padrad, which is an interesting attempt at something, but I wish like,
why can't the characters we know be a little funnier? Yeah. Aladdin, I think has one of the
interns of like big animated movies has one of the most interesting openings with Arabian Nights,
like the, the guy, the guy in the marketplace, the weird, uh, creeper kind of looking guy,
Robert Williams, which is Robin Williams. Um, uh, uh, yeah. And then they go to the cave of wonders
and he eats the first, the guy who wasn't the diamond in the rough. And this one, I think,
you mean that he eats something, right? Yeah. What cave eats the person.
The narrator ate the traditional middle Eastern dinner. Um, it slows down the movie. It takes a
while. Uh, uh, orders more stuffed grape leaves. Um, uh, yeah. And that I feel like, yeah, it was
flatter cause it was Will Smith singing it and, uh, real auto-tune-y, a little auto-tune-y and then
you had to see every character and it's just like, well, you're kind of, I'm, I know we kind of know
who these characters are, but you kind of taken the mystery away a little at first opening. So
sure. Um, yeah, but they got to dance around that line. That's offensive, but I don't remember what
the line is, but, uh, that people were like, cause that was a big problem at the time.
Oh yeah. There were protests about the, uh, um, it became something real generic. And this one,
this one, they changed the line in Prince Ali. I forget what it is originally, but Will Smith
sings like, we heard your princess is hot. That's a weird move. That's changed. That's a new line.
That is the original line. I don't know. How do you know it's changed then?
Because people are posting about like, why did they change this line to the princess is hot?
I got to find out what this original line is. It's, it's something much more innocuous.
Well, we did keep is the word nae bob, which I, it's funny to hear. That's one of those funny
culture clashes is Will Smith, like rapping nae bob. That's like a vaudeville word or like a
Marx brothers word. Well, I just looked it up. It is apparently, there we go. And nae bob is
a conspicuously wealthy man driving his fortune in the orient, especially in India during the 18th
century, privately held East India company. Uh, Hey, that's a historical thing. You didn't get
there, Jason. I didn't get there. Well, I guess that's like, um, uh, uh,
Oh wait, but a nattering nae bob, a nattering nae bob is a phrase used by vice president Spiro
Oh yeah. So of course his famous phrase. Yeah. Is that really an, of course, uh, that, that was like,
I feel like that was what was headline worthy back then is, is though the, do you hear the vice
president called someone a nattering nae bob? Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, this was the idea. This,
this was as offensive as a politician. Yeah. It's like, uh, in, in the musical Annie, there's a lot
of period ref of like never fully dressed without a smile talks about like dapper Dan and
Bo Bromley, which were both like Bo Bromley was like a men's, he was, uh, uh, like, oh, men should
dress in this way. And dapper Dan was a style of, um, hair bo bo Bromley, uh, bro, bo Bromel,
excuse me. But in the song it's your clothes may be bro, bo Bromley as in like, yeah, bro,
Bromley ish is what you're saying. Um, he was like a guy who was like, oh, men should dress this way.
And it was more conservative. And there's a sixties band called the Bo Bromwells. Oh,
I never knew what that was about. I think I assume there was just a man named Bo Bromwell in that time.
Yeah. But no, in fact, boy, more of this great, more of this great anachronism. You're walking,
what's the word, not treasury, the glossary of old timey stuff. Boring. Bullshit.
I have the answer here. Uh, Herger. Yeah. The original is perjure princess was a sight. Lovely
to see. And now Herger princess was hot. Where is she? A lot more aggressive.
I guess it's just aggressive. This is really though, a thing where it's like, it is tone.
Tone is the thing here. We always talk about tone, but it's like Jason and I talk about tone.
Oh, okay. That's one of our favorite topics. Thanks for filming. I love talking about
tone. Political tone. You know, what are you saying? They are sort of saying the same thing.
Optics. One is just, it's all optics. One of one, they're the same. They're saying the same thing.
One's just the new one's just a bit more aggressive. A sight. Lovely to sit like that.
Doesn't sound that that sounds very, you know, Broadway eat, but it doesn't sound like
children would be confused by that. I think it's still clear and simple.
You think children don't know what hot means? No, I, hot sounds dumb. Or like hot sounds like
they were like, Oh, we let's simplify that. Let, let's make that more modern. Like why change that
at all? Why would you, why not? If you're going to change it, why not change it to jiggy? I was
going to say, herger princess looked like a snack. That would be very top. Well, yeah, you know,
that was one of the stand for your princess, right? Cause you say snack. You've been using
that vernacular, but would that be too aggressive for Disney's Aladdin? Uh, that yeah. No, I think
that is okay. You would say that's okay. Cause I think that's on the level of hot to me. Cause
snack is like, I'm going to eat you up. That's a very aggressive. Doesn't that sound like, uh,
you know, something that aunt would say, like, I just want to eat you up. I mean, like about
somebody handsome on TV, like Chris O'Donnell, Chris O'Donnell from, uh, um, like Mark Harmon
from, uh, uh, from N, uh, NCIS New Orleans. I believe. Yeah. So Donald is, or is it a Los Angeles?
He's on NCIS. Um, yeah, snack. That was the missed opportunity. I was saying is, um, the genie never
dabbed. It was really, well, I said, I was really pretty confident that Jeannie would dab in this
and he did not dab. Yeah. I, but maybe we're finding we want things like that to have happened.
I think I wish this was more of a train wreck is what I'm getting at. I think it might be like
more fun to me if, uh, well, of course I know. Yeah. I mean, if it's, if something's like an insane
disaster, it is fun. Yeah. Um, I think though that I sort of settled into the movie early when I kind
of felt like, Oh, this is like a pretty good ABC and I don't even mean this is that much of an insult,
but it's like an ABC Sunday night movie version of Aladdin. Cause it's like, all right. I like,
I liked everyone in the movie for the most part, but there was, there was the feeling,
there was not maybe a feeling of the like big important fairy tale. There was a low keyness
to a lot of it, which I'd like I settled into and I was like, I like these, I like this guy. I like
this girl. It's on it's a, uh, it's a, uh, 1997 Cinderella or a Drew Carey. Yeah. And it's not a
bad thing. It's just you, you might be wishing it was like the animated version, which felt like
such an Epic. Um, but like, I don't know. It doesn't feel like a film. It doesn't feel like
you're really like go to a place and see Epic shots. Like it's all, it's all video gaming and
T a video gamey and TV, but I never questioned it if it was on TV or if it premiered on Disney,
we'd be raving about it on these Disney plus, you know what? There's that like they just put
an Aladdin movie on and it's got the songs, but it's like pretty good. Everyone's fun. Like I like
those actors are fun and they seem nice. And it's like a Greece live hairspray live. Yeah. Oh yeah.
With the Fed, with post, with a post department. Yeah. A lot of people. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. At one
point filling the entire screen for a while as we filed out a thousand people. What's my feel? Why
do I, I sort of like the live musicals, partially because I'm impressed by the live thing when
they've done them not live. I think there was a Rocky horror that looks like,
so inessential not going anywhere near that. But why do I kind of like the live musicals, but not
this? Well, I think that the S I think that they're set up in a way like by Disney to be like big
event movies and they have built up and they're really like, they're really holding them because
cause they use the same songs. You're like, well, I'm remembering the other movie I saw when I was a
kid that I loved that everyone's loved for 20 years. So like when you go with Beauty and the
Beast and they kind of try to do it exactly right with a couple, like exactly the same people go,
not quite as good. And then the Aladdin, I don't know they had much like as much of a vision for
it, but you're like, well, I, I, the other thing I like, and I've, it's been with me 25 years.
So your brain is naturally going to go, and then I could do going to the movies also is another
thing where it's like, I paid money and left my apartment to go here. So there's a little bit more
of an expectation. I feel like in that way, but yeah, if you were watching it on TV, I feel like
our people would be like, oh yeah, everyone seems cool. I like this. And it will now go into that
world and just be on forever and people will probably be fine with it. But like, you know,
it's a perfect example of the fine of it is a whole new world. You would never, the whole new
world is not bad. There's nothing bad about that sequence finishes. And I turned to Charles,
who we saw it with and was like, well, we got that done. Like it doesn't, it does nothing new or
innovative or, but nothing wrong either. It was really the wonders of the world. They just kind
of flew over some swamp land. Like in this one, like me, I did feel like there was some thought
in like, oh, these are some fun ideas we'll throw. That's not that aren't from the movie. Like we'll
throw some ideas in here that are versions of the old thing. And I don't know if him being a waiter
is kind of the same, but it's in a different way. And there's a different, there's different things
that I remember now from it. Whereas, you know, whole new world is like, I don't think my memory
exists of that sequence. I don't think I can remember it. I remember listening to the song.
I remember thinking the song sounded good, but not better. And nobody's singing it better or worse.
Yeah. Cause like not one. And you'd think of all the things we're going to use modern technology
to take you on a carpet ride. It's going to be so epic. And it's like, we'd yes, you know,
did they do the whole new world scene? They sure did. They did get done. Yeah. Maybe they didn't
have like kind of an interesting take on that. Does carpet get like torn to shit? Yeah. No,
I mean in the original. Oh, I don't not like that. I'm just shitting this one. And then Jeannie puts
them back together. So are we led to believe that the carpet is not alive even though it.
It's unclear if the carpet is dead or dying and then Jeannie. And then Jeannie with a new soul.
I guess so. One of the first diamonds in the rough that Jafar kills his soul is moved into the.
Like the last person who died in Angrabah becomes the carpet. He can't bring people back from the
dead, but he can move souls around. He can kind of shuffle souls around. Yeah. You go here.
Shell game of souls. Yeah. Yeah. That that was, I would have been traumatized by that as a kid.
I will say Abu has some funny reactions. There's some Abu reactions. I really like
when he like shifts his eyes or he's nervous, like a lot of the CGI stuff, those are the true
heroes of these movies. And I do think like you're getting so much mileage out of stuff that they
make. Like, obviously they have to make half of it or 75% of the movie, but you know, there's a
lot of nice little monkey business. Character acting. I guess I'd agree with that. And I think
we all agreed with the carpet was just like perfectly moved from one medium to the other.
He was the same. Yeah. He was the same. Yeah. Good job. He was the same. But I like, I like this
more than trying to have everybody just copy. Like if this was Guy Ritchie's like here, we're
going to do sort of a low key Aladdin. Everyone's going to be sort of like 21st century. They'll
wear like fun, colorful outfits. They don't look like the other movies, but they're like colorful
and like, we're just going to shoot it. Like a TV movie. I think that was his take when he
went into pitch at Disney. He was like, here's my, here's my idea. We're going to get it done.
We're all going to make a lot of money. I'm not going to stress out about it. I'm going to go
find, I'll go find some like Bollywood dancers. They're going to be great. We're going to have so
much fun watching them. We'll all applaud when they're done and then we'll go home to our families.
Yeah. And Bob Iger was like a tear in his eye. He was like, God bless you, sir.
The finest pitch I've ever heard. And this is the greatest. I'll stay on for another five years
to oversee you making this film. Aladdin, you know, the actors who were Aladdin and Jasmine,
they did a nice job. I thought she was a good singer. Um, the, I mean, again, though, the
animated Disney Renaissance movies, all they needed was like, well, we need the voice, right?
And we need the pipes to be right. We need the singing to be good. The look doesn't matter.
They had to find like real actors around the same right age who could also sing and like who could
do, you know, he had to do some stunty kind of stuff. I'm sure there was stunt men.
Correct me if I'm wrong about this is a sort of a thought I just had.
Correct me if I'm wrong. The end of the cartoon movie, he tricks Jafar and he says, you know,
the genie is more powerful than you are. And then Jafar says, make me a genie.
Yes. I think this is an improvement in the ending. That gray area. There's a running.
Yes. So to back up, I think this sort of corrects a little bit of a logic leap or it is just, it's
a little more seamless for me is that in the movie and the new version, um, Jeannie explains,
you have to be very specific with your wishes. It's a gray area. If you just say, make me a
prince, cause he makes a different prince, which I think is kind of a funny joke.
That was a decent sidekick.
And then at the end, Jafar, he tricks Jafar into making himself a genie, but Jafar says,
make me the most powerful creature in the universe. And he leaves it very vague. So Jeannie then can
make him a very powerful genie who gets trapped in a lamp, which I like a lot more because it's,
I see it makes more sense to me that you could trick Jafar that way than have him actually say
Jeannie. Cause he might think if he thought Jeannie in his head, he would think I'm going
into a lamp, aren't I? So I like that. No, no one cared about that. Only me.
I was questioning your use of the word. I liked it a lot more because that made me think you
might like tell someone about you're going to call your mom and say, so, Oh, I gotta tell you
about this. Um, so they fixed the wording and the only person I would tell is our friend Andrew
Grissom. And he would let me talk about it for 10 minutes. And then I either, he hate, he didn't
care or he really did like it. I wouldn't be able to tell cause he's too nice, but I don't think
I'll tell anyone this. Thanks for sharing friend. Yeah. That's what he say. I don't think I'll tell
anyone other than you two and everyone who's listening to this. I did really, I honestly,
when I say really like that, I did really like it. I was like, Oh, I like that. I like that punch
up. That's great. I like that it paid off, but like it's kind of in the vein. There was like one or
two moments where like so much in movies nowadays, like the comedy is so self-aware or self-referential
to me. So you're saying characters commenting on stuff. So that was kind of right on the line for
me. The idea of calling out the gray areas. Yeah. Like that was like a running thing on the story
though. I think that was commenting on the nature of wishes in general versus what he's making,
making a meta commentary. Calling out, he's commenting on Jeannie rules. Right. But I think,
I don't know that's Jeannie is meta in general. So he gets away with it. I mean, yeah, that was
the one he wasn't as meta of course, as the California adventure Jeannie. No, which is,
but how could you be? Yeah, that's literally impossible. He's the most meta. Sure. He wished
to be the most meta being in the galaxy. Yeah. And he got his wish. Tenfold. There was,
I'm trying to think, I was hoping, cause I have a lot of the Jeannie's from California
adventure's jokes in my head at all times, but especially this time watching this movie,
when he says, I can't bring anybody back from the dead and I can't make anyone fall in love,
whichever order he says that in California adventure Jeannie always used to do a Dr. Phil.
He said, I couldn't, I can't make anybody fall in love. And he would do like a Dr. Phil voice.
And that's one of the ones he would always do. So as soon as Jeannie was saying that in my brain,
it was like, is he going to do a Dr. Phil voice? But he did not do it. He did not. There's another,
if they'd been a little riskier and dangled on the, they're on the line a little more and
Will Smith became, how's there not one celebrity impression? At least one. Yeah. They did stay
away from that. Like the yodeling cowboy or something. I appreciate them not, the yodeling
cowboy. You remember the kid or the yodeling kid. Sorry. He dressed like a little cowboy in a yodel.
Is this a topical reference from 1899? If we were at the live show, people would be like, yes,
the yodeling kid. We all love this. Jason, no, it's from like a year ago, the kid who yodeled.
I don't know what you're talking about. Thank God they didn't put the yodeling cowboy in, although,
or then they do and entire audience that was sort of listless through it stands up and screams.
I'm not that out of it. Like I know like topical things. Walmart yodeling kid.
What is this? He was yodeling in the Walmart. His name is Mason Ramsey.
Oh, Mason Ramsey. I can't make anyone fall in love. I can't turn anyone into Mason Ramsey,
the yodeling Walmart boy. You all know. It would have been funny if there was like a meme,
if like Jeannie turned into a meme from when they were shooting it that we have forgotten about now.
That would have made me laugh. He turned into pizza rat for a second. He turned into pizza rat.
Keyboard cat. That's 10 years ago to friends is pizza rat on a slice of pizza.
I realize that I was silence in theater. I just go ha.
I wish they had waited like a week before the movie came out to shoot all Will Smith stuff. So
it could have been the most topical. Absolutely. This is him on Ellen dressed as a little cowboy.
I really, I would cop to knowing the yodeling boy. I don't think I remember seeing him charts
for a little while. I remember Ellen breaks kids all the time. She does kids all the time.
So it's possible again, everyone's mad. Now it's God and I for not knowing the yodeling boy from
Walmart. Sheridan Pierce from. Don't be mean to Jason. You know the yodeling boy. You're just
pretending you don't. She's on Dear White People and she was on what was the show?
They just canceled on Netflix. It was the remake of. Canceling a show on Netflix.
Was it one day at a time? She was on a couple of Netflix. She knows that yodeling cowboy I think
has done on a few comedy podcasts and done at UCB before. But it's very funny. So I'm backing up to
what did this movie came out a couple of weeks ago? Like around like May is May 25th sort of
around the neck of the woods. Something like that. Let's or how about here. Let's even go back a
little further to May. I'm looking up like OK May news from May 19th. What he would have said.
2019. So what let's figure what would the genie do about. I'm skipping the first one because it's
very dark about Trump. Oh he holds up the Mueller report and then he's like hold on a second. I got
to take care of something. He blacks out a lot of the census. Like the agreement the genie agreement
has says redactions like the Mueller report. Oh that's funny. OK great. Michigan congressman becomes
first GOP lawmaker to back impeachment. So if somebody betrayed Jafar then the genie could
turn to camera and say who's this guy? Representative Justin Amash? I'm on Friday May 19th on the CNN
recap and Sunday marks the 25th 25 years since MTV first launched its trailblazing social experiment
the real world. Oh wow. Are you guys getting those long getting along as well as the 25 year old show
broadcast on MTV? Well it would have been like Aladdin's like not following the gist of something
and and then the genie says like man you're dumber than Puck. Yeah that's good. All right
hey let's have a house meeting Puck. And then he would have said turn to the camera and said happy
25 years MTV's real world. We're thinking of you this week. Nobody thought you made it but you made it.
You know when they when they ultimately win against Jafar he can say wow we won just like
the horse war of will won freakness steaks the famous race in Baltimore.
Yeah these I mean these would have been good these would have been good for sure. Yeah yeah yeah so
next Aladdin we would like there to be holes in it. There's a great plan where they and then they
do it like SNL style movies coming out Friday let's get everybody together on Sunday. Right.
And let's like do a little topical workshop and make sure that it's super relevant by whatever
Memorial Day 2021. I mean the next one could be a buddy moot because like Aladdin and genie are like
equal power levels now. Actually Aladdin is now royal he's past him the genie is but a simple
fisherman now. Oh that's right yes with the fakest beard in the history film. It's like he's playing
Abraham Lincoln in a play in 1936. So yeah so what is Aladdin 2 then? Like we know they're on the ship
does Aladdin have to like make a wish with Jafar do a wish deal with Jafar to make
Beardwill Smith into a genie again. He has to like trick him to get him to also be a genie but then
save the last wish to get him back on the boat again. I mean they could combine two and three
was king of thieves and Aladdin's father comes back. Oh yes deadbeat dad right. Deadbeat dad yeah
the king of thieves. The king of thieves. Which is different than the prince of thieves. Right. Who was
Robin Hood. Kevin Costner Robin Hood I think. Right he was the prince of thieves. Yeah. What if not the
prince of tides. Not the prince of tides. Not the prince of darkness the devil.
So we'll get there it's the prince of tides will be in there let's get all the princes and kings
from all media into one movie. What if Aladdin because he's he's like doesn't feel like Jafar
got enough of his comeuppance just goes and rubs the lamp because Jafar now has to do whatever he
wants and he uses those three wishes to humiliate Jafar further. To make him like punch himself in
the dick. Yeah wish one. That was a more unnerving body horror because Jafar Jeannie was big and he
was flesh colored so those extra muscles were real really popping. You found the muscles less creepy
when it was blue. Yes I think the blue was like a little you know spoonful of sugar. I guess I'm the
only one. I guess I'm the only one on the podcast comfortable with big muscles giant muscles. Well
you're a wrestling fan so you're watching them all the time. That's a good point.
So but even giants like you know three story men with muscles. So wait a minute you would love then
a wrestler whose theme was being the Jeannie. Oh well we've had. His gimmick is being the
especially the topical Jeannie. Kevin and you know Kevin Nash of Magic Mike he's super shredder. Okay
okay. His first one of his first gimmicks I believe in WCW was he was Oz the great and powerful Oz.
Which the Turner owned Wizard of Oz so they could use the IP. Oh wow. So he was Oz. That's pretty
good. So he's that's not he's not he's a he's a I think in the in he wasn't a fraud in the wrestling
storyline like Oz actually is. He wasn't then small behind a curtain though that's a good move.
That is a good move. Another wrestler then goes and finds the curtain and he's just a little wimpy
guy back there. Yes. And Kevin Nash on the in the ring is just a hologram. Yeah. Right.
Help me show Jason have I ever showed you a picture of what Oz looked like with the mask he wore.
That is a crazy mask. There's a couple of jokes about big beards. You got big wizard's beard.
I don't know why. Neat. That is more clear like my reference point when you said like what about
am I the only one who like big muscley guys and this was like I recognize the artistic
America of Tom of Finland a he a man a cartoonist a long dead cartoonist from Finland I believe.
Audience totally on board. Very Tom of Finland. Very muscley homoerotic men very muscle bound men.
What's the in what era? I'm not sure when the Tom of Finland guy passed away.
When's Disney going to buy Tom of Finland? When will Disney buy the homoerotic
beefcake art of Tom of Finland? So you're comfortable with the Will Smith genie because
he reminds you of old homoerotic art. I'm saying no I'm saying I'm more comfortable with that than
blue genie. Oh more so. Blue genie's proportions were just kind of odd because I did appreciate
that he did have the genie like tail that he didn't always have the but then when he was blue he
sometimes the genie had genie legs I feel like this genie didn't have the blue the big plant pants.
You wanted him to have those blue pants or the big plants you were scratching your head like you
have a real like problem going on that you have to work out here. I'm just trying to think there was a lot they had to justify like Aladdin going like look more normal or Jasmine trying so hard to find a babwa on a map. Right.
It's like we don't that's fine we don't need you it's magic it's the magic is the answer to all these questions.
Yeah speaking of magic I am now lost in my google results for Tom of Finland.
Yeah I agree this is more pleasing aesthetically even are there gigantic penises bulging out of
very tight jeans yes would I rather look at this than the Will Smith genie probably. Yeah you got it too.
That is the the art style don't mind us listener we're all just looking at Tom of Finland.
Finland those draw some of those drawings were on a stamp in Finland. Wow that is how much she is
beloved as a national hero. The bulges. Oh my god this is insane. Yeah this is yeah fan graphics I think has put out a bunch of his stuff.
Interesting. I also don't know if this is related but I'm now I'm looking at a painting of that
famous painting blue boy and there's a penis bursting out of him that's you talk about body
horror is this bigger than the blue boy himself there's a these oh well okay that's just a full
on erotic one. This is an erotic one. I can't see from where you are. Here you go. This podcast we're so bored by
Aladdin now we're all just looking at erotic art. Yes I see men of hulking men of many professions
are all performing one task together. Very significant significant cartoonist significant history of comics.
Save your money. It is pride month it is pride month Tom of Finland a big yeah sure home erotic. Stay home and look at Tom of Finland instead and
crank up the brightness on your phone so you won't have the problem in the theater of watching watching
dim muscles look at the brightest muscles you can bring your own home and it's all free. I think you
could bring your bulbs if you're gonna go out just carrying your gonna see if you're gonna see a movie
let's get those let's get those muscles lit get those muscles bring your bulbs everybody bring the
bulbs I want to see a movie line where everybody's carrying a light bulb you want yours we'll use mine
we'll use mine tonight which one's the brightest how many times will you use?
Yeah I think my feeling with all these movies is I do wish we could go completely I've said this before
I'm sure but completely off the cliff with them let's just Dumbo meets Aladdin if we're doing
live action let's just totally let's just dump everything on top of each other and see what
happens oh let's bathe in this garbage pile together I've just regurgitating our childhood.
We were kids in the the Marvel the four issue Marvel versus DC era so you know we're on board
for crossovers so yeah I just like let's let's go nuts let's let's if you're good let's do six
sequels to Aladdin and the tramp and Bernard and Bianca like rescuers meets lady fine great yes the
carpet falls in love with the living foot rest from Beauty and the Beast and it's an unrelated romance
tale fine it's really sweet and they get broken up by that feather duster but then they they
they patch it up and get back together how about Jafar Jeannie turns LeFou from Beauty and the Beast
into a Jeannie and finally Gad can be a Jeannie the great and powerful LeFou yeah so LeFou I'm
lining up for that yeah why not let's just do let's go crazy we also haven't talked about you know
what I here let's I'll give them this the maybe the craziest component that I wasn't sure that I
liked and now looking back it is something they did different was Iago becoming giant I loved
Iago becoming giant Iago becomes like a big scary dinosaur bird yeah so let's match that up with
Dumbo and also then then uh Jafar the Jafar Jeannie also makes uh Dumbo a rabid so there's
Dumbo is like now like an evil elephant and a big fight in the sky just 90 minutes of pure fighting
between Dumbo and giant Iago that's great tearing at each other the big bites with the beak making
each other bleed the most violent movie Disney's ever released yeah fine they're gonna need to get
some leaders the reason we have to go to the theater to see it and it's a horror show
animal nature versus man man versus animal animal versus um do other animation studios copy this
do illumination are there live action minions the studio of Ghibli do a live action Totoro
live action minions look exactly like tom from Finland I guarantee you this is the only review
of the 2019 Aladdin that references Tom of Finland and it's all because of you
huge penises busting out of those minion overalls yeah yeah I don't things are a little more wild
in Europe the history of comics is a little more interesting actually to speak with me from Finland
that's probably the same right uh not quite they're all bikers
their definition of banana is a little bit different
I'm sorry it was Rich Little
what did I object to Rich Little coming back uh I think I think I did hear tell that that they
were thinking about Shrek real life oh is that the move there we go he's coming back in in some form
but I've heard back but they want to potentially it's yeah it's live action CGI Shrek so who's
Shrek Mike Myers they're not gonna it's not gonna be him as much as that would be maybe it's just a
voice yeah but you don't think they would Will Smithify it they don't just make it I think and
I don't know that somebody can probably prove me wrong already but I feel like I heard they wanted
everyone back for voices but it's a different medium but it's a different medium I heard
that could be totally out the window or that was just a rumor no way change of plans it's DJ Khaled
I'm Shrek! Here's another one! Shrek baby! Shrek is all the way up!
and then Eddie Murphy still Donkey? um that'd be great I guess so you think no though um well if
it's I don't know who would DJ Khaled vibe with hmm that's a good question it's Lil Wayne he could
be Lil Wayne uh we can do multiple versions though that's true let's just make five competing
Shreks all going at once and there will be a point before the universe folds in on itself where
we'll have like a five Shrek movies released in one week like in 20 years everything will just be
so crazy well I see like it'll be in six to seven minute parts on Kweeby and then two years down the
line the rights are released to be a two-hour movie after Kweeby releases them I like how you
say Kweeby Kweeby well it's anyone's best guess because I say Kweeby but technically because so
Kweeby if you don't know and you will know soon the thunder of Kweeby is coming to your town
the hand of God is coming down from the heavens to deliver you quick bites quick bites of entertainment
the former head of dream jerks
the dream jerk himself Jeffrey Katzenberg has a new site coming your way and yes and he's Mr. Shrek
as well uh and also I just I was just talking to our friend Anthony Geo about how he was behind the
show uh father of the pride as well yeah that's it that's maybe a topic for us is the Siegfried
and Roy NBC uh CGI show that had to debut after Roy was mauled by one of the comical tigers
voiced by John Goodman Montecor um Montecor is who mauled Roy that's the name yep was Montecor
portrayed on the show specifically he had Montecor was the famous tiger I think I am sure
John Goodman as Montecor what's the show called pride of the father of the pride cheese okay so
that's the series whoever wins in Dumbo versus Gianniago has to face off against Montecor
I'm combining every universe father of the pride come out the fall after Shrek came out um I think
maybe yeah it's around that same time could you imagine like Shrek was such a huge hit when it
came out and it's like now we're gonna do it on tv and people are not interested well I think that
I think I'm not making this up that donkey did a cameo on father of the pride there oh my god
there is no way that donkey did not do
but I think that is too specific to have thought of the safest money bet besides putting a dollar
on everything but I'd also bet that it's not Eddie Murphy I don't think it was Eddie Murphy
I've already found a few interesting things okay yes please this is now a slash it's a father of
the pride this is our Hollywood week superstar limo the new Aladdin movie Hollywood baby
John Goodman was Larry and I don't see Montecor last name Larry Montecor it does not say Larry
Montecor the bloodthirsty lion it doesn't say lions what are they what's the what actual species
tigers tiger okay yeah um I will so so I was just scrolling through and something that caught my eye
is that Kelsey Grammer is on the show as himself what and Matt Lauer is on the show as himself
oh no why didn't you say if only Montecor could have taken his rage out on Matt Lauer instead of
Roy and Dave Foley is on the show one episode as Kelsey Grammer's cat what I have also confirmed
that indeed Eddie Murphy was donkey okay I'm glad I didn't place an official bet there
uh is there one other thing I saw like oh did you catch Carl Reiner as Sarmati yes yes so that's
oh and Orlando Jones as snack whoa wow the simulation is real he's always well undoubtedly
then that character was always looking like a snack well with that tied together there's nothing
I think there's nowhere else to go with this but we'll boy I like when a good idea spins out
father of the pride episode to come in your way there are into the dream jerks archives 14
episodes of it do we have to watch all of them I guess the father of the pride saga I believe my
friend Tommy Blanchard wrote for father of the pride wow 6.9 on the scale of ratings so not the worst
out of a thousand their folklore on the DVD 1226 reviews too so it's not like it's got 10 or
something not the worst show not the worst geez well maybe I gotta do a behind the scenes delve
too uh we should do a Montecore episode too we're committing to two now before we've even known
okay let's do father of the pride and then we can talk about Montecore on the episode oh wait no
because Montecore is different than so we have to do an episode all about the lion the tiger the
moldy man but they the reason I don't think that's that grisly is because Roy was like no Montecore
was trying to help me Roy absolved the the tiger so it's not like now I don't know if he was doing
that just so they didn't kill him but they were they both were like no Montecore was trying to
help he was confused I believe that Roy was like I was having a stroke and he tried to save me which
I don't know if that's true I think he just like took a hunk by like giving him CPR just taking a
bite out of his throat I guess I don't know complete series 199 oh and that was a dollar 99
yeah huh I didn't boy that's the if they put that on quibi then everybody subscribes
everyone subscribes they gotta watch something until the sun goes down to watch Steven Spielberg's
horror show do you know about this that you can only watch at night you can only watch
Steven Spielberg horror series from sundown to sunup I was gonna who's gonna stop me
the algorithm what you literally can't you can't yeah that I actually think is kind that's like the
tingler level of novelty that's like the internet version of like a little shocking device in every
chair wow wow um kind of interesting yeah Montecore passed away in 2014 the attack happened in 2003
and Siegfried and Roy said that Montecore sensed the horn was having a Roy horn was having a mini
stroke and was dragging him to safety rather than attacking him and then there's a statement in this
article from USA Today that says animal experts have disputed that theory so yeah and then wait
I'll then in that timeline when did father of the pride come on the air that's a good question let
me go back wait 2004 so it's like a year after 2004 2005 is what it says for father of the pride
imagine working on that show and going into the office that day and finding how's everybody doing
not good yeah oh what I didn't check me I was on vacation I haven't checked my email what's going on
you know we're not all not checking email so much so you know so frequently it's 2004 so we don't
necessarily have it and have it on our phones or anything yet so and it's a guy who previously
worked on an animated show but Melanie Griffith and tippy hedren's family
not again cartoon I do end up with a real life one more time um yeah all right let's get out of
this episode and start the research for father of the pride everyone's asking for it this is the
podcast's awry guarantee we're not we may not enjoy blockbuster 2019 releases but we could not
be more excited to dig up a two dollar copy of short-lived sitcom father of the
I hate wait a minute two dollars that that and that includes the donkey episode
are you sure you've priced this correctly sir yeah the complete series okay this to me this
is more valuable than a lamp in the cave of wonders um you survived podcast the ride and
but will you survive the father of the pride special we'll find out I don't know next week
how quick do you want to do it let's order that copy right now can it be here by tomorrow morning
we'll get this will be the first one we get out this is the first time we do two back-to-back
patreon episodes yeah okay so we did it we stayed up all night we drank a ton of coffee
and we've seen all the father of the pride twice all right so we'll see you tomorrow