Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain doll-faced genie clones, forced dancing in
the hand of Tom Bergeron, and the zombie-like resurrection of 2014 references from Sharknado
to Adele Dazeem.
Can special guest Paul Rust escape the cave of topical jokes?
Find out as we cover Aladdin, a musical spectacular on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the podcast hosted by a crazier cast of characters than the Jersey
Shore.
My name is Mike Carlson, cold for applause, that would have killed in the Hyperion theater.
There's many Jersey Shore jokes in the Aladdin, a musical spectacular show.
Joining me as always is Jason Sheridan.
Scott, you had a joke too, did you want to do it?
Oh, I was just going to say that we all, the three of us love theme parks so much, without
them our lives would be empty, like Kim Kardashian's head.
Which is a real verbatim joke.
And I just want to say that I'm glad we're finally doing this attraction so we can answer
the question of if the dress is black and blue or white and yellow.
Yet another real joke from the show.
I'm in such a good mood already.
Let's introduce our guest, he wants to get in on this topical fun.
You know him from Netflix's Love.
Ladies and gentlemen, Paul Rust.
Thanks guys for having me.
Yeah, let's chomp it at the bit there.
Oh my gosh, once you start spouting genie lines, everybody wants to join the party.
I have a potential intro for you, which is, our guest today, he's a great guy, he's not
an exotic mammal like Snooki.
That is also a verbatim joke that I found.
The first time I was made aware that you were very into this show too, is when Jason and
I were on Herald Night, like seven, six years ago, and Neal Campbell was giving us notes
and I had told a story in the monologue about seeing this show and he was like, oh, Paul
loves the Aladdin show at Disney's California Adventure.
Well that's awesome because then that means that was like my ticket to get on your guys'
podcast.
Yeah, he said that.
Planting the seeds before it even existed.
And it was watered over the last years and then the stem came out and now it's in full
bloom, it's awesome.
Yeah, full plant today.
Do you remember what your story was that you told about the Aladdin stage show?
I think I was just telling a general story about how I was obsessed with it and how a
lot of the jokes would sort of not even really relate to Aladdin.
I think the thing I said specifically, which I had just seen was, there was a line from
Aladdin and then Genie just turned to the audience and said, Snooki.
And that was it.
And I loved it.
Everyone who's ever been with me there didn't love it.
Yeah.
Because I would drag everyone.
You would drag it every time.
You would say, well, we could go buy that.
We could go see Aladdin.
Which is what you do with all the weird bullshit there.
The man tea party?
He bangs on a big drum, we gotta go.
I do.
Well, he Mickey drumming is one of the best things you can see in the park when he's a
guy in the suit with the drum.
He's really drumming.
It's great.
It's Miles Teller in there.
That's how he got trade for whiplash.
He was the Mickey drummer.
How do you get the drumming out without the paparazzi pounding him?
Yeah, you can do it in a Mickey suit.
Then you can do it in front of J.K.
Simmons.
But no, I think you are hitting on what is the delight of the Aladdin.
If you're a comedy fan and a particular fan of a particular type of comedy, you get it
in spades at the Aladdin stage show.
That is my favorite part as well.
The ones that don't even link that well at all.
No.
I feel like they have a parallel or antecedent in the spoof movies of who are the spoofers
of the movie.
Friedberg and Setzer.
I love those and I would go and see them on opening weekend.
I love them so much.
Really?
Wow.
You went to the theater.
I'd pay actual money.
We're talking like epic movie, date movie, disaster movie.
Meet the Spartans.
Other things started using the movie title premise.
They ducked and weaved and got out of it with things like Meet the Spartans so they weren't
associated with that trend anymore.
They started hiding what they were doing.
Yeah, because they were writers on Scary Movie.
Two of the seven writers.
It's actually a funny joke of all the things they ever did.
With all those movies, I would always be like, I love them.
People would be like, well, ironically, right?
I'm like, I don't think so.
I'm laughing in the same way that I laugh at other stuff so I'm not going to judge it.
I'm not going to try to analyze it.
If you're getting joy from it and laughing, then you can't intellectualize that too much.
I would lose my mind at the genies jokes.
The one I most remember, I felt like I wanted to spew it out as soon as you guys were all
sitting there.
Maybe I should save it because the only one I totally remember without having rewatched
videos.
Oh, just have it.
The genie comes out and he was able to stick his belly out, push it out tight and do a
big ball.
He was like, I'm feeling like Bretany.
He looked down and went, oops, I did it again.
I'm not going to lie.
I'm laughing at that.
I don't quite understand it.
It's like what Mike said.
They're just grasping.
It's just a reference that the audience recognizes.
He says it in a funny way because they are good performers.
I will argue they are pretty good performers.
Oh, yeah.
Then that has evolved towards the end of the run.
As Bretany says in her Vegas show, he moves his mouth but no words come out.
She's lip syncing.
Bretany has been a real source of humor for that Aladdin series and the Kardashians.
The Kardashians, Dr. Phil, Snoopy, Dr. Phil, Justin Bieber, who all also factor into the
epic movie and turn into those films.
Those movies are the same sort of thing.
There's not always a joke there.
It'll just be like Borat is over there in a swimsuit.
Remember that?
We all laughed at that the first time.
I think what it is is when you're a kid and at school you have a talent show and then
people do Wayne and Garth.
You'll be like, Wayne's world.
You're like, well, I guess this is comedy.
We've seen this before, so we all agree.
We touched on this a little bit when we talked about the Bill and Ted show at Universal Studios
Halloween Horror Nights in a similar vein.
First of all, my whole, I've been mad ever since about when I was in middle school and
somebody, I worked really hard on a sketch that I wrote that was original and then the
most popular kid in school just got up and said, I'm Austin Powers.
Yeah, baby.
Everybody went ape shit.
I probably should have learned some lesson from that.
Instead, I went the other way and got really furious and stayed furious.
I'm less mad at this one because the guys were fun, nice guys, and they did it well.
This probably places my exact high school year that there were people killed at the
talent show when you're singing the Trogdor song from Homestar Runner.
Wow.
Is anybody else a Homestar Runner?
No.
I think I blew up my high school in particular.
But less mad at that one.
Austin Powers, come on.
Yeah, because with Homestar, you're like, okay, you were at least inside enough to pick
it.
Yeah, you're showing that you know the slightly deep ring.
If you breathe air, you're pleased.
Austin Powers.
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And he didn't even do the voice good.
He barely committed.
He did not study the British Isles.
Austin Powers' voice also heavily featured in the run of the Genie for sure.
It's like a living caricature stand at a theme park.
When you walk by and you see they always have an Austin Powers, they always have a Tom Cruise.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And they look really gross.
Yeah, when I'd walk by a caricature stand, I'd say, I'm repeating a joke I say to my
friends, guys.
It's pretty cool of me.
I'd go, guys, it's so nice to Tom Cruise to stop by every caricature stand in America
to let the...
Mike Myers comes in costume as Austin Powers is really nice too.
But yeah, there is a particular, I guess this is its own genre of theme park is the live
performance.
I know you guys have done Terminator.
Yes.
And that one is more the voices are recorded and they just have to mime.
Aladdin is the actual, they are speaking.
So you get that energy.
Yeah, and singing.
Yes, and singing.
Improvising.
And flying.
And showing you that they thought of stuff that day, which is like, you know, you can
roll your eyes at some of these jokes that they are like including things that just happened.
It's probably fairly unprecedented.
Do you think they have a group of writers off stage who like if something just pops
up in the last hour, we got to...
I have information on this in the process.
Well, real quick, let's like go back in case no one else knows what we are talking about.
Aladdin, a musical spectacular, ran from January 2003 to January 2016 at Disney's California
Adventure.
13 years.
An impressive run.
Thanks, Trump.
10 months later, he would be elected.
2016 ruined everything.
Bulma replaced in 2010 by a Toy Story musical.
Oh yeah.
Which was shelved and then now replaced by Frozen.
Yeah.
That's where the toys go.
Woody and Buzz put back on the shelf.
Which is the rumor of what's going to happen.
We are still deep in the rumor of potentially Country Bears goes away in favor of a, which
is always been the way in Disneyland for a long time, but in Disney World it might get
replaced with a Toy Story thing.
So we seem glum today.
When I walked in, I noticed all the lights were off and there was candles lit.
We had not been speaking to each other.
We were wearing shrouds.
It was kind of awake.
Kind of awake, kind of sitting shiva.
You don't usually sit shiva before the death, but we were getting ahead of it.
So I'm looking liver lips McGraw.
You had some time.
But yeah.
Speaking of seeing movies in theaters, I saw the Country Bears movie in the theater because
I was like, this is the last time there's going to be a full on people in suit movie
for the rest of my time.
Anytime now that there's going to be creatures, they'll be either CG or half CG.
I guess we had Unkar.
Unkar Plut.
Yeah.
He was on the suit.
He was on the menu.
Country Bears, I feel like were the last time we really could get.
Entirely.
Full suit.
Last time we went full suit.
And then you know that there was like a warehouse that was really unpleasant and like costumes
dripping with sweat.
Really?
Well, I don't know.
Can you imagine the process?
Yeah, the physical like putting those things together.
There was a guy who worked at Conan who built all the suits for Ninja Turtles 3 and he had
a picture of like, I don't want to say sweatshop.
It's not a sweatshop in that there's bad types of labor being employed.
Just like, yes, yeah, yeah.
So much sweat.
Yeah, yeah.
Just like costume after costume.
Like there's racks of 70 of them.
It seemed so intense.
Wow.
Just reeking of a BO.
Yeah, sure.
I think they in the suits had to like go out of commission for a couple days once they
were worn for a couple hours.
Some just shredded.
Some gotten rid of and turned.
Who shredded them?
Who's around?
I think I might know one guy.
I had to pick.
The the chewy suit when you hug Chewy at Disneyland, there's a musky.
There's some sort of a not necessarily.
It's the suit that smells not the human, I think.
It's but it's like a grandma's basement.
Yeah, something's going on there.
He's hugged a lot of people and he's a tall college student that's like six, eight.
What do you think is the process of cleaning for those?
It's a good question.
I know Disneyland has to have its own dry cleaning thing.
They're like go off campus.
Send it home with the guy.
They wait until they get back from college break.
Because it was like a laundry basket.
Thanks, mom.
I'm happy to do it.
It's just nice having you here.
I'm happy to clean any Minnie Mouse outfits.
You want me to throw it in?
Throw it in with my stuff.
Your dad's stuff is in there too.
I thought it made sense to group it in with the towels.
Oh, you can toss anything in with the towels.
That's fine.
Wait, what do you think of Country Bears?
There's been this debate on the show and our friend Doug Jones really stands by it.
And I think we've spoken ill of it.
What do you think of Country Bears?
I remember taking my niece to it.
So I had probably adjusted some expectation levels.
I was in college and taking my niece.
So I was probably already like this might suck and that's okay.
And actually I think I remember being pleasantly surprised.
There might have been a little bit too much irony.
I think if I remember it correctly there was a little bit of trying to beat the Shrek coolness.
You know what I mean?
We're bringing this into the...
The thing I always hate about when people go like,
It's a kids movie that there's jokes that the parents can write too.
Most of those jokes are dumb.
The jokes for the parents are like a reference to American Idol and Shrek.
And it's like, that's for the parents?
And also kids like those jokes and parents like the kids jokes.
Parents laugh just as much as donkey farting as the kids do.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why do we have to figure out who laughs the most?
We have to figure out who likes what movies.
Everybody likes...
Yeah, probably.
If you look at what family movies end up on a critics best of list.
They don't have crap like, they don't have a reference to something that happened a year ago.
Like Spider-Man or Coco or whatever.
Adults jokes is strange.
If you go back and re-watch those Shreks,
there's some jokes in there that you're like, oh my god this is...
Those spoof movies, I think it's Disaster Movie.
They actually have a newspaper in it.
And on the newspaper it's the date that the movie came out.
And it was almost like their joke of like, this is how long this movie will last.
It won't even pass the expiration of the release date of the movie.
Wow.
Really?
Yeah.
Those guys are pretty cool.
That is cool.
Yeah, that is.
We're impressed by them.
I've never been done in a movie.
I know, right?
You haven't ever seen the actual date of the movie.
My birthday once was on a Thursday when Cheers came out.
And I remember they said, my birthday is April 12th.
And for whatever reason they needed the date in the episode of Cheers.
And on my birthday, April 12th, they said, April 12th in the episode.
Wow.
So that was another time that art invaded the date.
A wonderful phenomenon.
But you compare this to like the second golden age of Disney animation or something.
And Little Mermaid, Aladdin, Lion King.
The jokes in that are pretty tight.
I mean, Aladdin has some good Robin Williams kind of jokes.
But those movies would take so long to make.
They wouldn't cram topical stuff in there.
Oh, yeah, right.
The jokes are a little more evergreen in those ones.
Right.
Like if they did an Iran Contra joke or something,
then Little Mermaid would probably stick out.
And even the genie impressions.
Those are more like Jack Nichols.
That's that less.
Pretty perennial.
Rich Littles impressions that could play in the same spot for 40 years.
He does impersonate, I think, George F. Will in that movie.
And I don't know how many kids were like,
yes, conservative commentator George F. Will.
Is that something about quid pro quo?
Quid pro quo.
I had no idea what that was until now.
That is George F. Will.
Wow.
Still around.
Still commentating.
Still complaining about how the game of baseball is played.
Oh wait.
Maybe not George F. Will.
Sorry, it's the guy who gets in the...
He would get in the fight with...
They'd go into a cabin and these two writers would have a fight.
William F. Buckley.
Buckley.
Buckley was in his house.
Yes, I got the George F. Will, William F. Buckley.
He was an initial guy.
Yes, the F.
Good thing I didn't say Paul F. Tompkins.
We know that's not correct.
We know that.
Yeah, when Paul F. Tompkins debated Gore Vidal on Cabot.
That was a whole different...
Do you think if in November 92 when we went and saw Aladdin
if the Genie had done an impression of Paul F. Tompkins
we would have been able to appreciate it?
I don't think so.
It would have been a tad confusing.
The Philadelphia comedian?
Yes, a local...
Never appeared on television.
I didn't hear of him.
I did have one of those things though where...
Do you ever have the thing where you watched a stand-up
when you were younger and then you remember a joke
and then the person starts saying on stage, like,
oh, I saw this.
It happened to me with Paul F. Tompkins.
When I was a freshman in high school maybe
I saw a stand-up on Conan make a joke about
how this relates to Disney.
He turned on the TV and at like 2 a.m.
the Apple Dumpling Gang was on.
Sure.
With Tim Conway and he was like
what family is watching the Apple Dumpling Gang
at 2 a.m.?
And he was like, oh, it's for alcoholic fathers
who wake up their kids and are like
the Apple Dumpling Gang is on.
And the kids are like forced to watch it.
We're gonna be a family.
Well, because he went backwards and his first album
was like older material that he was refining.
Is that in there?
Yes, I think that's why.
I think he was going back to the first
which also included Crushed Pennies
another theme park.
So he was really...
We gotta ask him about all this stuff.
He's fully...
Were you guys saying it was the sort of
the Disney Renaissance?
Did you guys see Aladdin in the theaters?
Do you remember?
Sure, yeah.
I saw it at the El Capitan.
My parents took me to a special El Capitan
which I think was the first time I ever went there
and that's an incredible theater
when you're eight or whatever.
Yeah, I remember that showing very strongly.
And they do the shows beforehand.
Have you ever done El Capitan lately?
No, I've heard it's fun.
I don't think I've done it ever.
I did a Toy Story one and two there.
Oh, that's good.
Six, seven years ago.
Was it as old?
I moved here in 04.
Was it always dazzling and lit up
or was that part of a Hollywood Boulevard
renovation thing?
Was El Capitan always...
I saw it there.
I saw them there not first run.
I saw them there six or seven years ago.
It was like a double feature.
I see, I see.
Yeah, I saw one of those
Disney nature documentaries there
a few years ago and that was cool
because before the show they brought
some live animals out.
Oh, really?
To get to see some live animals.
In a really enclosed setting.
What did you see?
What did they bring out?
Oh, I saw a goat.
I remember thinking,
these aren't animals that we're going to
get to see in the jungle.
These are just like petting zoos.
This is what you could get.
This is what you could get every day
for a month.
And I think I saw...
I don't even remember seeing Ratatouille
there.
But before the show...
Unleashed rats?
What's that?
Do they unleash rats?
Have them cook for you?
They had a Ratatouille suit come out
but...
What's your...
Were you fond of Aladdin
previous to all this?
Yeah, I think in that initial
you know, if it's sort of
what the...
Leaving out rescuers down under
but that four
the sort of run from
Little Mermaid, Aladdin
or Beauty and the Beast Aladdin
Lion King, right?
Felt like kind of a piece
and then I felt like after
Lion King when it was like
Pocahontas starting there is when I
Pocahontas...
I was 14 when I came out.
Even Lion King
I remember sitting in the theater at age 13
and being like, I might...
I'm going to see this because it's a
zeitgeist-y thing right now.
I'm not necessarily going because I'm
dying to see
you know, because I was like really cool
with bad complexion and
terrible stroke up.
You're going to start growing up.
People can't know you like kids still.
No, I gotta grow up
to be more hideous.
No, but I loved Aladdin so much
and I remember
yeah, losing it.
I laughed so hard through the whole
movie and then I remember
a month later is when Toys came out
that Robin...
That other Robin Williams movie
and it was such a bait and switch
to go from
within three weeks to Aladdin
and it's like a laugh vest to like
I don't know if you've seen Toys but it's like
it's an allegory for
military
weapons like
the industrial military
complex and they're using
a toy company to build weapons
and it's like Barry Lemonson's
hippie like, hey man
think about the toys you're making for your
kids.
That's right.
I got the lesson of small soldiers too.
That's a very odd movie.
Yes, I saw small soldiers for the first time
ten days ago.
Yes, I went on a big
Joe Dante made it.
Oh yeah.
I watched 11 Joe Dante movies in nine days.
I had a really
I went on a Dante fest guys.
That's a fun ride.
There's a lot of fun movies in there.
Oh boy.
I was just listening to a podcast of his.
He was talking about
going to Disneyland.
Oh, he was
remarking about how he couldn't believe
he couldn't remember the ride
but he was saying
they were talking about Song of the South.
It really demonstrates how
people weren't plugged into
sensitivity that that ride
could have came out in 1989.
It was based on Uncle Reema's stories.
It's crazy. It was one of those which
I'm sure your listeners have, other people do.
Where he was like, what's the name of that ride?
Oh my gosh, it's based on Song of the South.
Then I'm like, Joe!
Love your movies too!
Get with it!
I loved it and I remember laughing
so much and then when it came out on video
watching it repeatedly.
It really did
kick off.
The fact that this show ended up being
full of topical references
and then
Trek before that.
I don't think any of that happens without Robin Williams
cracking open
the kind of comedy you could do
in an animated movie.
I'd go even so far to say he also
was the person who
there was, I know
other celebrities would have done it previously
but that there was marquee
value in knowing
this celebrity is
the voice of this person you're watching
which a lot of times
you don't give a shit.
You're sort of like...
Jaja Gabor
doing Bianca.
Isn't that
Bianca or is that Aristocats?
Was it Ava Gabor
or was it Ava on Green Acres?
Jaja is hers.
Which would have put a five year old
Mike into the seat.
That's true. So for me, that one would have gotten me there.
But now when it's like
James Gandolfini
and Megamind 2
and it's like...
actually that being James Gandolfini
is also good.
He's very excited about the Gandolfini family.
But there's a lot of weird even like...
But I think Robin Williams after that was like...
Yeah, which I think he was trying to avoid.
He didn't want that to get cracked open
and he also apparently didn't want
to step on the box office
of toys.
He thought he would fuck over toys
Disney.
Yeah, and it sort of disappears.
His whole thing was like don't tell people
that it's me.
And then you don't have to pay me as much because
you're not using my name to sell the movie.
And then I think in the commercials
they started showing
him in the recording studio.
Oh, they pushed that footage
that just seemed like
we're going to film it to have it to show behind the scenes.
And then they started using that more aggressively.
Okay, okay.
When they have the behind the scenes stuff
of somebody in the animation studio
doing voices and stuff.
It reminded me of...
Nick Weiger wrote a sketch once that was
it was Phil Collins
is in a recording studio
and he can't concentrate on singing
the Tarzan song because he keeps
blowing takes because he wants to share
all these new facts he's learned about dinosaurs.
So it'll be like
I'll be in your heart.
He's like hold on fellas.
I don't know, a brontosaurus.
But when I saw that sketch I said to Weiger
I was like, you know, the way he did it
was the thing where when somebody's wearing headphones
and they have the one headphone on one ear
and then off on the other.
And I said to him, you know it's really funny that you
wrote that sketch about Phil Collins
because whenever I imagined
somebody in a studio
with one headphone off and one headphone off
like he did
I was like I think of Phil Collins because
I saw this video once of him doing it
and Nick was like that's why I wrote the sketch
I have an image of Phil Collins
with a headphone piece.
What? I think I have that in my head too.
I've seen that.
I think that was for publicity for Tarzan.
They were playing that flip a lot.
I've seen that. For sure I've seen that.
He famously, he more than anybody
is associated with the one headphone on
method is what you're saying.
Does he also maybe do that
and then in like do they know it's Christmas
or something else where we would have seen him in a studio?
A lot of them do I think that.
They're having the one headphone on.
That's pretentious.
It's an affect.
My favorite is when sometimes now
they clearly like stage those
filming date like it's not like
they just brought a camera in
there's the cardboard cut out next to them.
Yeah the Toy Story
like all those Toy Story things they're showing now
for Toy Story 4. It's such like
well lit and there's just like Toy Story
pictures up and they're like doing lines from the movie.
You know Tim Allen came in there
hungover looking puffy
and reddish shit.
Came in
in like sweat pants
like one leg up and another leg
down and then like Tim
we were recording today we're gonna shoot some
video. Anyway
wah wah wah.
Okay sorry sorry sorry sir.
Then a flurry of construction
equipment flew by and made him look
nice.
Also those are very
anytime I've had to do voice
stuff everybody's always been very
supportive but
it can make you feel very vulnerable
because you're just like by yourself
and you're watching other people watch you
and you don't have anything really to connect
with. So I would think
bringing a video camera in there
probably something people wouldn't love.
They're gonna catch you playing with the music stand that has
the carpet on it so it doesn't
the music stand so it doesn't rattle.
Yeah so it doesn't rattle.
That is interesting to play with.
Any situation I've been in
I totally, Phil Collins method
the one headphone on Jason Sheridan's method
play with the flavor. Play with the carpet music
stand. So your voice
doesn't bounce off the metal. I think it's good
to play with the carpet stand because it
sort of shows you're just relaxed.
Hey man we're just having
fun playing with this carpet.
That's a good way to trick people
into thinking I'm confident.
Thank you Jason.
You're owning the environment.
You're marking your territory.
Okay so Ronald
Williams cracks open this whole area
now we can reference celebrities
and stuff in animated
films.
Do you think that's been, I know voice
actors get angry
about it. I would if I was like
man they're coming in on our territory
and you know. Yeah like people like
I don't know if they've complained specifically
but you're Billy Wests of the world
who are really professional and do tons
of voices are like
well this is a celebrity comes in and does a regular voice
I spend all this time and come up
with a voice that's perfect and then
it's just like I don't know here comes
not that I'm upset at him but Seth
Rogan he's just doing his voice.
What's the point?
To me the word like Robin Williams
makes sense because he's in
some other world he could have been purely
a super over guy if he hadn't done all the other things.
But like one of those
boring DreamWorks movies
like Roe Del Dorado or something
as Brad Pitt. Brad Pitt who I think
we all like in many things
but I'm not like his voice
of course.
It's great dynamic voice
only removed from his
physicality. It's like don't take away those eyes
please. Yeah come on.
That is also
that is the name I was going to
I just started saying that
because I think Megamind was the peak of that
because it's like okay Will Ferrell is the kooky
villain that makes sense but it's just like
then the superhero is Brad
Pitt. He's in that too.
I think that's him but his voice
like you're saying yeah he just sounds like a
guy if you're not looking at Brad
Pitt it just sounds like man. A big part
of the Pitt package is the looks.
It's the looks.
So yeah on
some ways I think it's good because it
opened a door for like
I referenced the donkey
earlier and I
love Eddie Murphy. I think
as the donkey did I ever tell you the story?
I took the same niece I took to
Country Bears. I took to Shrek 2.
It was like the last 20 minutes and you know
in the last 20 minutes of a movie when things
are wrapping up you're actually kind of a lot of
times relieved. You're just like okay.
The movie is wrapping up. I gotta go home.
I remember I was like oh it's wrapping up.
Donkey was making me laugh so hard
I was like I'm gonna have to wait
another three years
until Donkey comes back.
I was so sad
so there's times
that I do like it guys but then
there's times where it's just not
as necessary and you wish a Billy West
could have. Sure. It must have been a tough decade
for you. We haven't had Donkey in a while.
It's in the worst years
of your life. I'm all referencing
things that happened like a year
year and a half after 9-11.
We needed the most
cheering up.
Shrek. The first
Shrek was summer 2001.
Is that the end of the 20th century?
Is that where we are?
It's like Woodstock
before Altamont.
We had Woodstock August 16th.
We had Shrek and Moulin Rouge.
Combining
all of pop culture.
Old songs. Putting them in new settings.
It flattened it all. Yeah yeah.
It's like a bookend.
And then Glitter.
Was Glitter right after 9-11?
I believe so. Wow.
Or was it right before? It's somewhere around there.
Oh Glitter was around the
yes because it was celebrating the time in New York
that was pre-9-11.
Yeah. Those were the tough
ones where
the New York
movies that were on the
shelf for the next like 6-7 months
and you'd see Twin Towers
you'd have to have them.
I had a friend
who, you know it's weird you're
with a group of people in a living room
and you're watching like
what's the
movie
Greg Metola did where they're all
in one car together.
It's not called the Car Poolers but
that's the idea. They're all in one car.
And they're trapped in a car.
But they're driving into New York and they see two Twin Towers
and my friend went
you know that's just
like a warm up.
It's a way to be like okay we all are thinking this.
You have to acknowledge it in a way.
Yeah. Just some like
mmm mmm mmm.
And you're almost like
you maybe have an initial reaction of being
mad at the movie like how
could they. Come on. It's an old movie.
You can't be mad.
Greg Metola you didn't know in 1995.
Should have known. They had
targets on them. Day trippers?
Is it Day Trippers?
Day Trippers. Yes.
I looked it up. I didn't know.
Wow. Crazy.
That's smart.
You guys just watch it.
We'll turn away for one shot.
Day Trippers is
on the compass. It's Day Trippers
is at the top and then the inverse of it at the south
is the 25th hour.
Which is only 9-11.
Which is the 25th hours so
much is about.
That's the yin and yang of New York representation.
Well you know
on September 11th 2001
the Hyperion Theater
was still in its infancy
still in its first year
that's where the show is at California
Adventure and why in 2001
they were showing something called
Steps in Time. Did you guys look into
Steps in Time at all?
I just noticed it and honestly I didn't.
I didn't because I know we'll have to do
a separate episode.
And then a messy cook.
Who knocked over the spice rack.
Steps in Time
followed by Blast, right?
The Power of Blast.
Which was like a condensed
Broadway like Stomp Ripple.
So proud
legacy.
So proud that things can blast your ass.
What was the Power of Blast?
It was sort of like Stomp
but a little different.
A little cooler I bet.
There was a part where there was a big
row of drum kits and
there was like 16 people all playing drums
at the same time.
Stuff like that.
I would imagine
if they could work out the rights
a Blue Man group would go over
very well franchising with a Disney
Universal Studios.
Universal?
And they replaced, they evicted
Nickelodeon Studios
where all of our favorite shows were filmed
as a kid.
Wait, down in Orlando?
So you know where all that and
Clarissa were filmed and such.
Yeah that's now home of the Blue Men.
There's an infamous home
video within the Rust family
of
we went to Orlando
in 1990
and so
MGM had just
opened up and Universal
had just opened up. I forget which one
but we went to Universal and all
it was the first few days so all
the rides were breaking down.
It was really a bummer.
We can't go on Confortation?
They didn't even have the Back to the Future ride yet
it was like
a little bit of a disappointment.
But we went to the Nickelodeon Studios and they had a
big sign up that said
Double Dare Auditions. I'm like
holy moly.
This would be a fun game to play.
And I get to be on TV
like I always dreamed
and they said auditions
were that day
but they said
we're not shooting until next week
so if you're not here next week
don't audition today because there's no way
you could ever be, it's a waste of our time right?
Yeah.
And I knew that
in my nine year old brain, I'm like
I know we won't be here but I still
was just angry at the injustice of it
and there's a perfectly
composed like
moment in our home video where
it's zoomed up on the Nickelodeon
Studio Splat sign
and it zooms out
and as it's zooming out it's panning down
and my dad's
my mom's narrating it
and she goes, my mom's holding it
but my dad's narrating and he goes
poor little Pauly
didn't get to be on Nickelodeon
right?
And I'm like marching up to the camera like
angry like so fussy and marching
and I'm like pissed off and it's like one of those
Sean Penn getting mad at the paparazzi
like don't look at me right?
You know like shove it okay?
So as there's
I put up my hand
and I swat the thing and
guys I was a good little boy too
I just wanted my parents
to like me and know that I was a good boy
so me doing this was crazy
and if you watch the video
I hit it and then
you hear my mom go ow!
and then you go well you hurt your mom I hope you're happy
and I'm like this is the worst now
wow!
I'm a monster!
and then the camera pans over to me at the
and this is the very end
and I met with a choice which is
like the camera's on me now
I'm so hot with anger I'm mad that I hit the
camera I can either
say I'm sorry
and cry and be embarrassed of that
or stand my ground and let them know no I'm
mad so when the camera went on
me I like stuck my tongue out
but if you like freeze framed it and
did like scene by
shot by shot progression
as soon as like the tip of my tongue
starts coming out of my mouth I've already
like started crying cause
I'm regretting having stuck my tongue out
so it's like this perfect like
ahhhh!
wow
a lot of emotions get stirred up
when you're at theme parks guys
absolutely yes as you're telling
this I am having memories
of like a moment of friction
or a moment of frustration at theme parks
where everything is so loud and heightened
as a kid it just gets heightened
a million times I think so because it's also
you're just dealing with
the things that's so frustrating
when you're a child which is like
wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
and you're just like how am I gonna just find a way
to kill off boredom here
and so you're you know
you wait and then you get the ride it's awesome
but then I
think it's that and then also just like
it's like it still happens when
I go to Disneyland or go to a theme park which is
like in your mind you're like the whole reason I'm
here is for fun and so
it's a little like I don't know if you guys ever read
that Jonathan Franzen book Freedom
but he describes freedom
as he's like freedom
is this idea that's
great but as soon as you don't get
everything that was promised by it
it's the first thing that instantly sours I'm paraphrasing
but it's like the same thing with Disneyland
it's the happiest place on earth
if I experience 10%
unhappiness this whole thing's
fucked you know so I think
that was a little bit of the yes you're supposed to be
having a perfect day and
I can only imagine for parents too like
if your kid picks
this day to freak out
what a sin that you threw the
money down I didn't even think about
the right the parent side
which is just like
I'm exhausted
and you're making this difficult
for me
let us have fun that you're throwing a tantrum that you can't
be a double dairy dork
I had two older sisters
I'm sure for my two older sisters
and my parents it was like the funniest thing in the world
dorks getting so upset
about not getting messy on
TV
what a miserable life you can only be
in Universal Studios once and then not
also in turn be a TV
star instantly
you must be as a parent you must
be like constantly fighting the urge
to laugh and laugh at
your deeply upset child
it must be so funny
at all this
little ball of emotions
punching and putting tongues out
yeah it's also yeah
when you can
their
frustrations match yours then it's
like you're like oh I'm not too far from
being a baby all the time
still a baby in me
two degrees away from being that at all points
so what's at the Nickelodeon where do they
they have a Blue Man Group theater
separate ticketed
kind of like yeah
so you could never be
on Double Dare
that dream is over
I don't think it was Universal's call I feel like Viacom
was like oh the lease has
ended they move the time
wait they move the time capsule remember the time
capsule yes they moved it a couple times
now yeah but isn't it in the hotel
no no now it's in Burbank
not far from here at Nickelodeon
yeah now they have an actual place
where people work and not like a theme park attraction
is it right over is it the one over by the
car dealership yeah
it was put down in 1990
right so when is the
so yeah was it 50 years or was
92 because I remember
watching it and thinking like boy I'd like
to see that thing open it's a shame I won't
live that long
I did the math and I thought there was no
way I would be alive at
well that was foolish
at the time but now that we're getting
closer it might not be that
wrong oh yeah
we'll be underwater
and then Nickelodeon's two tied capsules
will float by and we're like oh yeah
it might be it's
the last remnants of humanity
that game boy in there
that old game boy
the moon boots I think
I think I thought of it
because there were so many different promotions where you would
get like a free thing or you go on like that
KB Toys shopping spree
in my mind like whoever opened it
was gonna just get all that free stuff and I was just
jealous of whoever opened it
well they're gonna get that game boy and
probably Mark Summers kid who's gonna get it
anyway
jealous
somebody steals it that is what will happen
we should steal it yeah
but I was there for that opening that summer of
MGM and I remember going to see
Muppets live
there was people in costumes
oh that's right oh the not the puppet show
but the costume character
Muppet size they were man sized
it was beaded
yeah
I remember Miss Piggy came out
with a pink feather boa and saying
personality you know
I've got personality
personality and a pink feather
like blew off
her feather boa and landed
at my feet and I picked it
up and I held it in my palm and I was like
I will never lose this
and I did
I thought like
this is gonna be very important
I have a more upsetting version
of like free show piece
that I got at a theme park
Six Flags Great Adventure
had a lethal weapon boat
like stunt show
and at the end of the show they were
giving out the spit of bullet
casings to kids
so
the prop department of the crow
good you need these
those are in a locker
those are in an evidence locker somewhere
yeah just blanks bullet casings from blank
cause like the casing is the same
whether it's a blank or a bullet
it's probably somewhere in my mom's house
in a box somewhere yeah
gotta find that bullet casing
at the end of the world you'll be like
trying to find that bullet casing to
put some ammunition in it to save
oh yeah
I know it was here somewhere
to protect your time
capsule
and then I think
at that Universalist I saw the Ghostbusters
live show just to bring it back to the
live shows and I think that was a
mouthy lip-synchy
one yeah I think so
it was kind of 50-50 yeah live actors and some
projection we haven't talked about that
one yet that's a good
it was pretty cool I remember the set being real
fun and
you said something to this extent
but like I think
when you're a kid and you
love movies and TV
shows and entertainment so much
the exciting thing is just the
whatever it says it's just like
the immersive thing of just like oh I'm in
a movie right now and so
I remember Ghostbusters
really
that show I'm not even the biggest
Ghostbusters fan but it was just like I remember
thinking like oh man I'm seeing actual
Ghostbusters costumes and I'm seeing
actual you know slimmers
sure
but the
Aladdin show might I think
of all the live and I did see the Bill
and Ted ones and those are great
I'm seeing the hats
and the air guitars
the real air guitars the vests
the vests, the dancing Mitt Romney
I remember
I went to a
I think
Paul Abdul came out and they sang
that bitch is crazy
oh my god
people were not super forgiving
of there was Brittany
in that there was a lot of like it's bald
Brittany she's gone
going psycho watch out
she had a chainsaw
I think that's something that happened in that
the treatment of Britney Spears in the media over the last
25 years
that stuff was only like
wasn't that all within the deck
maybe like 2006 or so
yeah I guess
she's fat and looks like shit and she's crazy
people are so off
I remember that driving me crazy cause
it was a little like
somebody starting
a fire in a field and then driving
five miles away and being like
can you believe this fire
we all were responsible
for Brittany's meltdown
and I would be like
we don't get it two ways we don't get to destroy her
and then have fun about her
there was like a two week period where she
in the late 90s early 2000s
where she was like cool look at this new pop star
she's not the villain
and then two weeks later
it just became
the media just made her a villain
for over a decade
for one reason or another
and then that timberlake still gets to walk around
cock of the walk
not being funny
doing celebrity voices
in animated movies
making everyone at the super bowl mad
twice, twice
oh you're right
and he got off
mad and then indifferent
indifferent last year
those are the funniest video where like
I think that thing was well produced for
TV and if you're watching with all the camera
moves it was kind of exciting but then when somebody
posted on Twitter here's what it was like
in the stadium
very far away and it's just really
they aren't playing
to the audience
it's there at all
you see all these grips just move chunks of equipment around
go go move it move it
my favorite is when they have those people
like they pay the people to be
excited because they send all those people
out on the field every year
every year it's the same thing and if you were like just watching it
casually you probably wouldn't notice
be like oh yeah there's an audience there but it's like people like
unnaturally
moving their arms in a way that like no one
in a concert even like Beatlemania
that would look strange in the front row
of people at a Beatles concert
like the America's Funniest Home videos
I remember that audience
seemed like gassed or something
because they were just like out of their
minds just laughing
when I first moved to LA I went to a taping of
America's Funniest Home videos and they were
playing Hey Ya during the like warm up
period oh yeah and I was like dancing
in my seat to Hey Ya and I looked over
and I saw Tom Bergeron like
walk over to our producer like point at me
I was like oh boy what's going on
and then the producer
came up and was like Tom wants you to come down and dance
I was like okay
it was like the audience warm up
thing he was like come here we're gonna play
that song I saw you cutting some moon why don't you dance
out here and like a monkey
boy I'm like yeah sure and I started dancing
and then he was like let's make this like a
commercial spot
so then they were like watch America's
Funniest Home videos tonight you might see
something like this and that pan around like dancing
crazy they never
aired it but I do
have on videotape the episode that our friends
are in and we're all like going out
of our minds with over gesturing
and like laughing too hard and Tom
Bergeron will say so we'll turn to each other like
shake our heads like oh can you believe this guy you know
but
the saddest part of this story
is after it was done
I was with my friends
I'm still friends with you know Campbell and Mike
Cassidy and we were walking out and I was like
this was like three weeks
I'd been living in LA I was like
if I walk out here I'm blowing an opportunity
I could get a
writing job out of this
so I like
we were out of
the studio I turned back
around and I walked up to like
a crew guy and I was like
I was the guy who danced
I've actually thought
before I could write some of the
jokes for America's funniest
videos do you know
who I could talk to about that
and he was like I don't know anything about
that man I was like okay
I walked out
Wow you can't
knock the hustle though
some of the NSDTK
guys wrote on America's funniest
videos and so I didn't know that
yeah
what was their process
so they walked up to some guy
they walked up to a better guy
or the same guy he just didn't
like you for some reason
hey can you help me get a better job
than yours sure buddy
I'd love to
I'm just here to help
we're gonna be saying can't knock the hustle that's what I will be
whispering as you try to leave today and I
start pitching you new love episodes
you'd be like I don't know
anything about that pal
what was your name again
I had some Randy
ideas
yes I don't know I don't know
anything about that
it's done man
what do you think I'm gonna do with this
sure sure
oh my god wow that's incredible
the Hyperion Theater
the Hyperion Theater I was saying
we're going through a lot of pop culture history
and I realized since we haven't talked about
the Hyperion Theater for any reason yet
we have to talk about
a major piece of history
with major talent that happened on that stage
and that is Kelsey Grammer's
fall
that's where it took place
where it happened yes
a lot of people don't remember that
wow
the reason that you know
that it was at Disneyland somewhere
is that the joke that he is telling
before he falls is something
you just catch a little snippet of it but like
it's a small world pretending to be
a UN interpreter oh dear lord
he's 98%
done with the joke he said oh dear
lord that is so profane I hope he
apologized for the profanity
that he said in front of those people
that's the sweetest thing he's like
forgive me for my
vulgarity
you said oh lord
although the sound cuts out in the video
that you can see of it and he apparently did
say oh shit
but that was cut out of what we
all have seen from it
yeah yeah
if you analyze the tape
so that little section that he
falls down in we see
that little section all the time when we watch
Aladdin we do and what happened
was if you look at a picture of
the stage from any performance
of Aladdin it's all weird and
carved up because it's like starbursts
and the reason he fell
it was not a flat stage
he knows what stages are like
oh he's killed so many
that was the problem he's so accustomed
yes but he's never performed
on a starburst stage before
he didn't fall into the pit where the genie comes out
of did he?
no he's like between
star shapes
Robin Williams did
he fell into the pit the genie came out of
what happened?
genie you're free
I don't think that's what happened
I don't think that's a apt way to describe that
there's the
thing when he shoots out at the top
and then when Jafar comes out later that wasn't where
he fell
he would fall onto the Jafar puppet
that was just waiting down there
he landed on the snake
puppet what if he landed on the snake and then the snake
shot up shooting Kelsey Grammer
into the ceiling of the Hyperion
oh dear lord
now he fell
front of the stage and here's what's
I'd never heard him speak about
this video but on YouTube you can
look up him talking on a Jim
Norton radio program of some kind
and he tells the rest of the
story and they're like hey that video is
real funny man and he's like yes yes
I know and people enjoy it
you don't realize is that I
the side of the stage split
my entire leg open and
I performed the rest
I did the rest of my presentation but I did it
with I was bleeding
through my pants
because it is a
hard angle it's like a 10 degree angle
and he so it
did tear his leg
open when he went to the hospital
he did the before he did like the rest of his
half hour or whatever and then straight to the hospital
where they said this is like
worse than motorcycle accidents we've seen
oh my god and he also
and they're like so you know like what were you thinking
when that happened they're trying to make it funny and he's
like well I thought about my grandmother who
when she broke her hip
it was the beginning of the end
I thought that I had broken my hip
yeah it was like a terrible
thing for it was a very
grim fall
the story I had to heard about it was like I think
on the office they
wanted to use the clip they needed a clip
of a funny internet thing
and they were like well
they went to the people to
Kelsey Grammers people and they're like
we'll let you use it you just
have to pay us and they're like okay how much
do you want and they're like
half a million dollars
it was like a number that
you would never pay because
Kelsey Grammer must have been like yeah I don't
we don't need that out there anymore
Niles will have a field day with
this he said
do you think that was off limits to
joke about like
when the genie con like the next time
they did Aladdin
oh yeah probably
it's like when William Shatner got roasted
they were like no dead
wife jokes no wife drowning jokes
that was like on the back wall in the
Hyperion theater was like no
Grammer jokes and they're like what
we can't do wordplay
now I feel like
G-R-A-M-M-E-R
not M-M-A-R
the genie got fired for doing a Kelsey Grammer joke
once I do feel
I feel like a real genie because I'm in shackles
yeah
I remember you know the
genie shackles come off at the end of Aladdin
I remember
seeing the movie and then seeing a
TV spot for the movie
and they show a last scene where he's like
we're going to Disney or something like that
and he doesn't have the shackles
on in that briefest
moment I was like they've spoiled the movie
they've ruined it
people now know that he's not insane
if it was a Marvel
movie now they would have put the things
on him because they do that they
digitally put stuff on like
in the trailers to fool you
so that is absolutely
something they would have done to not spoil it
like they put in like
Thor was missing an eye at the end of
the Ragnarok and they put his eye back in in the
trailer so you wouldn't know that he lost an eye
in the movie I feel like that's partly
because the people
who are in charge of making decisions like now
are people like us who when they were kids
they saw Aladdin was ruined for them
when Roger Rabbit was nominated
for the Oscars I remember they did this cute
thing where like when we come back it's
the best animated short and they
cut to a shot of
the audience and it was like normal
person two empty seats
that they Roger Rabbit like Mickey
and Minnie Mouse sitting there like waiting for the
Oscars get announced
and then two seat fillers
came and sat down where
the animated characters were sitting there was this
like weird combination
of human
like my lip on it
it's like
what the fuck
like they were
like this woman sat
on a Minnie drawing it was so
weird like they got in a
flying machine
kill me kill us
kill us put us out of our misery
that's smart but that would have never happened
if somebody what I'm saying our
age would have been
running things they're like come on man
I don't want to promote nightmares
for people did you see the Aladdin
remake yes we did
we did an episode on our Patreon
oh I guess that one
yeah just tying up
some loose ends from that
so
well a couple of things the ending
of the actual of the original Aladdin
means the genie is free
but he still has all his
powers so they have just unleashed
a mad god on the world
that they cannot
control anymore so it's good he's benevolent
the movie kind of
the live action one it's a little cleaner
so the lyric change
this was a thing that we
touched on briefly but we didn't have I didn't have
it in front of me in the
original animated Aladdin release
there were the lyrics
in Arabian Nights
where they cut off your ear
they don't like your face
it's barbaric but hey it's home
where the heat is in
where the sand is immense
and the heat is intense
so what's the it's where it's
so then for the VHS they change it to
where it's flat and immense and the heat is intense
it's barbaric but hey
it's home and I've got a news article
at the time people are like thank you for
changing the cutting the ear off thing
you still have the word
barbaric in there we would like
you to change that and Disney representatives
says that line will not be changed
so they missed that
and of course live action Aladdin
introduced a new character we did
neglected to talk about that is not in the stage
musical or the animated one Euro Trash
Prince
Euro Trash Prince
another prince in
the movie before Prince
Ali shows up
Raja behind the back of his pants
yes so in the
new movie he's like a German like
this kind of potty boy
like sort of thing
that was weird that was
a weird addition
that's a little odd
Raja bite his pants
I don't think so
you don't get the heart boxers
isn't that the heart boxers
I love heart boxers
I call those TV underwear
I thought boxers
hearts are not
I thought that was TV underwear
because I always saw me in briefs and my dad in briefs
I didn't think boxers
I thought that was like a comic
conceit
or to get around the fact that like they can't show
guys walking around in briefs
that's probably partly it too
that it disguises
things a little bit more
it was like illegal it was an FCC mandate
to put our son
I think in the Will Ferrell era
comedy
it went from boxers to briefs
what's funnier to see on screen
uh huh uh huh
we used to be love the hearts on
boxers guys but now
we like briefs that's how hard and
do you think
you've been naked
in things to some extent haven't you
I have a I'm in my
briefs in I Love You
Beth Cooper I'm wearing
Spider-Man underwear
and they had to go through
Marvel to clear that
the only way it was cleared was because
Chris Columbus was making
producing a fantastic four movie at the time
so we had enough of a connection
that they allowed it to happen
like the second the Jessica Alba ones
those yeah yeah that weird
you could not have worn Spider-Man underwear
yeah because they had the logo
and I still have those
if you guys would have spelled them
please
that's why we brought you here
you have to ask
wow wow
that's a real throwback then to not be in
like to be in comical
underwear as opposed to
on Love That Was a conversation I chose to wear
boxers in a scene and we talked about how
isn't it funnier to see
somebody in briefs and then the
conversation of but are we
past that have we seen briefs too much
should we do
what's the new comedy underwear
post briefs
briefs world
what do you think we live more in post 9-eleven
or post briefs
briefs I think
for sure I think it's briefs
the one we live with more every day now
I have not seen the remake so I don't know about
Euro Trash Prince but
sounds like a character I
I have still been describing Aladdin
as strangely okay
like strangely okay strangely
as some parts I'd like it exists
that'd be my poll
quote on the poster
they hold up a
parchment at some point that has the date of the
movie on it
we won't go down a hole guys
but when
I remember sitting in the theater with
The Last Jedi I was like
ancient Jedi text
alright
I'm not even a big Star Wars fan like
others you know but I was just like
oh so these based on books
what this world
has paper
yeah like I haven't even seen paper
in this world let alone that they have tomes
that they refer to
had nobody read a book in a Star Wars movie
ever I'm trying to think there's no parchment
ever I don't think there's any parchment
that gets passed around
if you go to Oga's Cantina
and Star Wars Galaxy's Edge which I've
done three times now it is like weird
it's not quite paper on the menus
it's definitely it feels a little more
leathery or something
so they're
a bantha hide or something
you know
paper
not some bantha hide they're huge
that would be perfect for the Aladdin musical
it might be too
too specific
the conglomerations
would be too much
Star Wars land that would be perfect
they would reference things in park as well
that would get a big laugh
so what's in the Hyperion theater now
let's replace the Frozen
is it the Hyperion
does Olaf do topical
no he does not
he does not it's a longer show than
Aladdin it's pretty good
is it a full hour
15 or so it's like an hour
because Aladdin is 40 was 45 minutes
that's already pretty long
but it's an hour it's like an hour
so instead of annoying
pop culture jokes it's the annoying joke
of somebody going oh
so that just happened
is there one of those
in Frozen
I love Frozen but
it's wall to wall
so that was a little random
one of those
whatever the flavor of
what the flavor of punch up
people is at the time
I guess that's the things
you don't like in Shrek and the things you like
in Frozen
I have a theory of
if you really like this joke in
alt comedy wait 10 years
and you'll get to see it in all the commercials
you want to see
if you really like it
just wait 10 years
but
yeah I guess I haven't seen
the Frozen show but it wasn't
the thing I did like about the Aladdin show
was the 45 minute thing that
for people who aren't necessarily
right it's like a nice way
to kind of be like
and also the sort of line thing is
kind of figured out you just go and it's like
you get there you know your
promise to see everybody goes in
it's fairly
it feels fairly
it's easy it's easy
I think it's a people of
1984 seats
it's a giant theater
George Orwell would love that
it's a giant
there's three levels
I've sat in all the levels multiple times
you gotta get every
perspective you gotta get everything
I've sat in the very back I've sat very close
I sat there on the
the like invite
only or AP
like last show
press conference they had
we gotta get to that
well there's not so much there
but we saw the show
and then everyone came out and talked about it
all the actors came out and talked about it
and like the Jasmine had been there for 10 years
she had been
no she had been there the whole time
there's that thing said the Jazzman
Billy Crystal
Billy Crystal's Jazzman
character they have somebody play
he fell off he didn't break character
it's like a man
it is funny hearing that
I didn't realize it was like a cut up stage
cause they would use it for presentations
and stuff sometimes they would use like
executives managed to not fall off the Kelsey Grammar
were you up close enough to see
the hair and blood encrusted
parts of the Kelsey Grammar
no, it was
bones
reeks of Frasier's bones
they haven't washed it out
did you
now people can't see Aladdin
but out of all the vantage points you got
was there a prime one?
I like sitting very close for things
so I feel like dead center
that's good
maybe fifth row
you still get a little bit of a stage picture
were you afraid he was gonna roast ya?
I was hoping he was gonna roast ya
like go to Rickles you'd hope for it
there was a Chinese man
in the front row
there was an older couple next to him
they staged it, they put them there
so Jeannie could have at them
I've thought before
after how many Don Rickles shows
how many like frail male
egos have had to be boosted on the ride home
by their wives
I mean I know he makes jokes but
you're right
he's mean, he's mean, he shouldn't make those jokes
just doesn't line
you know
some things are just too
it wasn't just me, some of the other guys
I don't feel bad for me
I feel bad for the Polish people
across America
I just feel
unfair to all of them
the thing I remember being really dazzled by
with the Aladdin show was the magic carpet
it goes up
and I felt some fear
for the performers
when they're on
over the audience and around
the show is actually good
it is good
there's sets
when Jeannie comes down the stairs
there's a ton of Jeannies
friend like me
that's awesome
I was afraid of those Jeannies though
they're like doll faced men
they're doll faced men
and in fact
here's all of them
if you zoom into one of their heads
that's pretty terrifying
there you go
just with the crooked eyebrows
I have it from
so this is the cruise ship
version, so this is still running
on the Disney fantasy
sort of like a touring musical version
scaled down a little bit
all the numbers are still in there
but the masks look extra terrifying
those might be worse
it reminds me of one of my favorite mystery science theater movies
which is called Devil Doll
here's a picture of Devil Doll
I bring it up almost every time
I open a bottle of wine
which is a lot
because the dummy wants to drink wine
and there's this odd exchange
I want some wine
I know what wine is
give me some
but you're just a dummy Hugo
almost every bottle when I open the phrase
I know what wine is
hold on
wait a second
which came first?
Ben are you being driven to drink the wine
because of Devil Doll
it's all Hugo's
Hugo hypnotized me
those matching
like when the
old 60's Planet of the Apes movies
you can see that they can't
have the budget to fashion the best
masks for everybody
so if you look closely in the background
reminds me of the end of
Three Amigos
remember when they come back and they all dress up as the Amigos
so when you're first seeing it
you think like wait how are all
three Amigos in different spots in this village
and shooting everywhere and then they all step out
and they're all wearing costumes but then they reveal
that they're kind of like shotily made
I was like I wasn't looking at
the shotily made ones when I was getting tricked
I think the Hyperion though
you're so far away from the genies you don't
realize oh their mouths aren't moving
those are masks because that's the chorus
it's a spectacle
but at the cruise ship it's a full chorus
and just dolls
singing at you
Disney corporate is finding out they're getting like 50 people
jumping overboard each
why is that? and then they look and they're like oh it always
correlates with the masks
and the fun like me number
I think that's heightened so much by the
movie
and I would put this guy
on the short list of
the five geniuses
who could still be alive today
but aren't and I wish they were
Mr. Howard Ashman guys
who wrote all the
I think the reason that
we probably stayed in California
Adventure so long is because the songs are so
good, the songs weren't good
but Howard Ashman
you know he wrote Little Shop of Horrors and then obviously
all the Little Mermaid and
Beauty and the Beast and stuff but he
passed away from AIDS and
Fran Liebowitz has this line about
AIDS took
great artists but also took the people
who could be the people who
loved art and gave money
to it they also died so that's why
this sort of
last 30 years has kind of been a
turn to anti intellectualism
or anti art because there's not enough
people around who
would love it and hold it up
anyway whenever I think about that line
I think about Howard Ashman I'm like oh man
I wish Howard Ashman was still alive
write music for us
I mean like not that there's good
there's a lot of good Disney songs past him but he
certainly was yeah he wrote a lot of
the good ones yeah I wonder like some of his films
Menken still alive Menken wrote
a new song for this
yeah does he write with Tim Rice now
or who does cause
is he alone? There was some Son Heim
no wait not Son Heim who am I
thinking of?
did he ever do a Disney who did
no it's a similar name it's like Steven
Schwartz or something oh yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah
that was a wrong stab on my part
he did a musical I was thinking called Children of Eden
Children of Eden? Oh my
we are all Children of Eden
guys so that's what that musical is
this is where the episode turns and
Paul has some uh a guy he wants
to tell us a lot about
Paul's gonna need a pamphlet now? Verses?
I knew another guy with magical powers not a lot to say
you guys like Mickey Mouse
I know a pretty cool guy too
did he write
there's like a new Jasmine song
as there is in the film but a different new
Jasmine song? Menken wrote
the to be free song that's in this one
okay yeah which is
interesting cause I heard that
that she has that song because Howard Ashman's
thing always was he writes
really good songs about
I'm stuck here and I wish I could be out there
and I'm stuck here and I wish I could be out there
and I think he wrote
for the original Latin song a Jasmine song
that was that and they
ran out of time or they had to cut it
but he's so good at writing that you know
Ariel's a
part of your world
and Little Shop of Horrors Somewhere that's green
is basically note for note
the same song
and then Belle obviously
it's all full of that stuff but
yeah and like
Lion King I remember when the music came out
the sacrilege but I don't like
the music for that it was like two
like
yuppie baby boomer
Paul Simon-y
Earth
we're all on this Earth
which they stuck there with Phil Collins
and Sting and stuff
that's Broadway you're getting further away from Broadway
yeah and more into kind of like new agey kind of
stuff and the thing that I liked about
Howard Ashman is there is a little bit of
a little like cervic
can be kind of
snotty and stuff so it added a little bit
of a little edge
yeah yeah yeah one of those documentaries where
I'm trying to remember the moment I think it's is it him
described like in Belle when
he's like she sings the word
alarming okay it's in Wakey Sleepy Beauty
when he directs Belle to sing the word alarming
and he just says Barbara
it's Barbara and then you hear her
do it that way and like she didn't even need
to audition what that would
sound like or whatever page or arrow
I was like oh I know exactly what that means
it's a cool little moment yeah and that same
moment in the documentary he comes into the booth
and he's like trying to explain to her like
this is how you feel in this moment and then she
starts singing it's like oh she took the note
and I've actually watched that and thought like
oh that's good direction you know what he did
he found a way to get her to sing exactly
how she was supposed to do it wow wow
that's really magic any like behind the scenes stuff
where you can see the note given and then
watch it
so much behind the scenes stuff is a little like fluffy
but like Jurassic Park
is a good like him like
talking to Joseph Mazzello and then you go
oh yeah wait he just explained like
exactly what makes that seem great that's funny
because I was watching an interview with Tarantino
and he was saying before
he started directing he'd watched as many
behind the scenes stuff to see and he was like
the person he most gelled with directorally
was Spielberg he was like
oh the way he talked to actors he
was like that's how I think I should talk to actors
wow
yeah the
the
what was the Spielberg movie
you saw that he it was
Jurassic Park
a little film
have you heard of it
I think you've heard of it
I was trying to think that Tarantino could have seen that one but
before you
he was like boning up right before
Reservoir Dogs
he was directing something lately
crap
I used to work at a company pretty
close by here that was
I logged footage for behind the scenes
features on DVDs
so I would just like watch all the raw
footage that they shot
and I can't talk about some of the stories
on my guys but afterwards
I'm in there so
crazy things that
it was me and like three other guys
and we worked the night shift
and somebody would come in and walk in
and be like
you want to see Al Pacino choose somebody out
it's like okay
we were DMing about that one oh yeah yeah
we were talking about Jack and Jo yeah yeah
I already told you that one
wait I was maybe that's an off mic I don't remember
that's so cool
but yeah it was a
fun job
yeah
well we're I mean you know at a certain
point we just have to start listing jokes
yeah I'm sorry
okay here's
thing that always bothered me about this
Abu cut yeah Abu cut
not in this yeah
but Iago pretty good puppet like he
gets to do some fun stuff yeah
I think they were just figuring like Abu doesn't get to talk
so who cares because carpet
is a person as well carpet is fun
carpet is a hit
we love aerial acrobatic
carpet like it's very
impressive it's like I
got the novelization on tape
of rookie of the year
they cut out
entirely the Daniel Stern character
what he's fun
yeah he's funny but it's like cutting
out Abu yeah
oh they can do it I guess
nothing really is affected by it
you can scrape off the
chocolate off the top of my cake
it doesn't mean I want to eat it
why are they so pressed
for space on the tape
as read by Dan Hedea
you know Dan Hedea
and I remember
there's a line that my friend and I
we got on a car trip we were at a gas station
we saw the rookie of the year novelization on tape
we're like let's listen to it we listened to it
and it was Dan Hedea there was one line we listened over and over
where he was like Henry saw his mom
kiss a new boyfriend made him want to bloth
laughter
oh my god
do you have that still is that available
I don't I don't I would like to find that
there are a lot of celebrity read novelizations
I don't know
it's so funny to be like a novelization
of a movie which is already like
if you're reading a novelization of a
kids movie you're already pretty
not that they did
and listening to it
we're a lot of steps
removed from the source material
the blues brother show at universal studios like
the understudy
for the blues brother show
at universal
is like
eight steps removed from actual
blues music
Dan Ackroyd and John Belushi's
appropriation of that
Universal Studios Hollywood
and then the understudy for that
laughter
who gets to do it if the fake Belushi
but what was that sorry
I don't know
I watched an interview with
Dylan White
10 year veteran of the show
he was on the Tiara talk show
which was the talk show we listened to
and we heard about Cal David
aka Sonny Eclipse
the robot from Florida's Cosmic Race
who does lounge music in a restaurant
in Florida
in the disney world
he's an alien who does lounge music
so the way
check him out
he does great sets all the time
so there would be two genies working
on one day
and one of them would have the early shift and one of them would have the late shift
and they'd come in
and talk to each other about what
their ideas were
and they'd collaborate
and they'd talk about what was going on during the day
and they'd throw ideas at each other
and then they would
so they had a rule if one of the genies came up with a joke
another genie couldn't tell that joke
until the other genie had done it
successfully so you couldn't like steal someone else's idea
you could help it
help them with it but then once they've done it
you could do your own version
so he describes what would happen is
they may have a joke
and then different genies would put it different places in the show
so you get your snooki different spots
and a different read on the snooki joke
so he was like
it was so fun
constant just collaboration
just talking over
the new show every night
they loved it
oh my god
so it was what I honestly thought
because I was always dreaming of them on the radio
I could use this for Genie today
oh this sounds good
these are interesting headlines
I could use this
yeah like the comic
he wakes up at 11
or like your friend
grabs the newspaper and that's when his job starts
looking at the headlines coming up with jokes
I would imagine too like he's at like a family reunion
and his uncle's like pitching him Genie stuff
you're like oh
my uncle won't stop pitching me Genie stuff
he doesn't get it
he doesn't get the voice of the character
I tried to write down every reference for the one show I watched
I wrote down so many of them
I watched the very last show
so they were milking it
it was like 50 minutes longer and they were milking it
and the Genie did a bit where he said the name
of every actor who played Genie Jafar and Aladdin
so he says like a few dozen names at some point
but just writing down topical references
I think it was about 30
there was a point when he first showed something
one show where I was like
I keep rewinding because I'm like you gotta be kidding me
Jason the stenographer
how did he do that
it's hard yeah I was trying to keep up too
deal or no deal in 2016
it's wild
yeah a 45 minute show with 30 jokes
that's like a pop culture reference every minute
I was exhausted
I just kinda wanna read them as fast as I can
that's what I was thinking
it's just a melee
it'll be torturous for us
we'll try to catch our breath
good luck I'm so sorry
we'll edit out your stifling of laughter if it's too distracting
it's like those pop-up dirty games
of like you're not gonna last 5 minutes
this is gonna be excruciating
try to last but these Genie jokes
okay Genie jokes about patriots football
Genie jokes about Abercrombie and Fitch not wanting
people that look like him to wear the clothes
Genie says that he can't fulfill your wish to be part of One Direction
and he's like
I'm gonna go with the Genie
you can't fulfill your wish to be part of One Direction
even though there's a spot open
and he says Zayn is going in the wrong direction
no wishing for more wishing
except you can wish for Justin Bieber to get deported
this is it from a different show
can't make people fall in love
but cause unions fall apart all the time
like the union in One Direction
I made it clunkier but it was a jack-of-all-trades
I thought they were gonna have an anti-union thing
what screen are they?
can I do a related Bieber
we just throw them out
cause there's a number of spots
making anybody come back from the dead is always a spot
I can't make anybody come back from the dead
if I can't do it for Justin Bieber's career
I can't do it for you
audience goes ooo
that's the only one of those I ever found
Genie all of a sudden just goes
SUPERSTAR
like Mary-Kathryn Gallagher
I can't bring anyone back from the dead
I used that already on Betty White
that is a cool-ish one for the cruise ship
cruise ship
it's usually pretty sticky
it's a lot more like crazy cause it's random
not a lot of topical stuff in that
the dirty show at 11
like Teatro Martini
down at the Pirates dinner
that's another episode
I also think the Betty White reference
what was the name of the guy who
played the Genie?
Terrence White or something?
oh oh oh oh it was Dylan White
sounds like a little bit of nepotism
going on
shouldn't his name be Dylan Blue?
what with the character
he plays
and some of these jokes too
I think he would have liked if you had like
went up to him and done that he'd be like
I gotta use that for Genie
I can't make people fall in love thing I thought it was gonna be
they wouldn't say it I can't make people fall in love
I can't keep Kelsey from falling off this stage
can't make you fall in love like Bella and Edward
from Twilight
that's in there
oh thanks for the from Twilight Genie
did you ever leave the show
Paul and then go back and think to yourself
I'm blowing an opportunity
I go up to one of the ushers
and I'm like I think I could run Disney World
I could live in the castle maybe
this is my favorite
he goes stay out of the light Carol Anne
which is a poltergeist reference
very impressed with that one
who's he saying that to what's the circumstances
that somebody's
towards the light
I watch so many of these I can't remember
there's like a run where he does
stay out of the light Carol Anne use the force luke
groovy baby
he gets
an applause break
he's saying be yourself
Aladdin and saying a lot of similar
the message of the movie
essentially
there's one where he does the full
like Luke I'm your father no that
can't be Paul he does like the full scene
himself
he does it with that Luke whiney
no I can't be Chad
I thought he was funny
impossible
he tells Aladdin that he's a smurf
that's working on his dad bod
whoa
similar to
is that in his reveal cause a lot of the reveals
yes yes who are you I'm Magic Mike
the later years
that's not dissimilar from
he's like I eat someone used their wish to make
that new Terminator movie get to the
walker get to the
is a reference to get to the chopper
which is a different Schwarzenegger
movie
he says he tells Jafar that he's so
mean when he's on my space Tom
won't even be his friend
that's from 2019 actually
they brought back the Aladdin
show
oh he's
back before when he says like just like
Dr. Phil I can't make somebody fall in
love with you call that the John
and Kate rule
I believe it's John and Kate plus eight
wait and he's saying
they've
unclear it's unclear exactly
what he's going to do they love each other
well they got divorced
it was love was real once I guess
Dr. Phil okay he always
uses all the time that Dr. Phil
he always says Dr. Phil like Dr. Phil
I can't make anyone fall in love with you
what is that based on
I have no idea what that's based on
it's not a romantic
show it's not something he's like fixing couples
all the time it's like no general
it's a Venn diagram crossover
of like a celebrity
that all four quadrants
understand yes and then
it's a voice that's easy to do
yeah yeah yeah yeah
Gangnam Style he definitely did Gangnam Style
for sure I remember
seeing him do it this is
the actual time capsule yeah
all these Aladdin shows we should just
put all of them on one
compact disc and
bury it and then that's all we need
and when we go back and read it we're like oh yeah
yeah that's what it was like to be
alive this is
an ultimate collection of pop culture
all right so I went do you I
have two from the
2003 version
I have a question which is the did the
topicality ramp up as the years
went on the answer doesn't seem like they did
but was not absent
from 2003
and I think I there's a
joke for me and there's a joke for Scott because those
are the only two ones in the and so the
first one he comes out of the lamp and he
explains how long he's been in there and he tells Aladdin
that he's missed every episode of I
Love Lucy
and it gets very little reaction
even in 2003 really confusing
and then this other one gets no reaction
too and he says that he
can't make someone fall in love with you he tried
it once and Liza Minnelli will
never forgive me
wow a David
Guest joke
2003 I didn't
I didn't get it right away
pretty good pretty good
oh man not a bad joke
how do we tilt this podcast
there's no justification for us
to do a David Guest episode is there
we can find
we can find something
we're doing the El Capitan Theater because there's a
Ghirardelli ice cream shop next to it so
I need an excuse somebody can
shine a light on what the link is to make
David Guest
I'll just do a bonus
people who visit
Disneyland are known as guests
so yes
got it
thanks
justify
all I'm left is my Twitter
I gotta get a little more
oh yeah go for it go for it
okay he calls the Jeannie Sham
wow bunch
he does get a little political
in the dreaded year of 2016
towards the end he says
the carpet flies away
and he says I haven't seen a rug fly away
like that since Donald Trump's hair on a windy day
you probably killed it
probably killed it
actually the longer pause
after a punch line the more
I love it
that's so bad I'm just gonna like rest
in the
minute let it age
there was that second
to the last Aladdin performance
where the Jeannie didn't do any topical material
he just sat down at the piano and sang
Leonard Cohen's Hallelujah
I'm not giving up on neither should you
let's see
something about three wishes
because three is
all you need
he says things come in threes
wishes blind mice shark nato movies
one of the big joke zones
also is he's messing with Jafar
who has to stay straight they don't let these people
respond to the Jeannie in any way
as though it's like a hey can I make you a crack
kind of situation especially with Jafar
so a lot of disses of Jafar
he wants to be an all powerful sultan
alright fine here you go you're the sultan
I want to be president too Kanye
2015 I think
because that's when he started talking about that
he says
to Jafar are you mad because
John Travolta mispronounced your name
too
I was there for that
I remember that
the future Frozen show that will be
replacing them
yes, Adina Mendel
let's well receive the Frozen one
partly because there's less generation
Aladdin was around for 20 plus years
when this
closed
so the parents and the grandparents and the kids
all liked it, Frozen opened
less than six years after the movie
one generation
I personally remember
a lot of honey boo boo references
when I went
I remember right after the Oscars he made an Angelina Jolie's leg joke
the leg
she stood in that kind of
stress way
do you think this show
partly ended because you couldn't do
topicality
in a post Trump world anymore
you know the writers were just like
all we can do now is just make
Trump jokes
like Jon Stewart you just kind of wasn't up to it
I've been at this shit for
a similar run of time as Jon Stewart
I think you could map them perfectly
and that's why the Genie
is testifying before Congress
you could say we've been missing
Genie's comedic voice these last couple of years
and we've sort of needed it in the dialogue
the Genie might have been able to fix all of this
when I watch those old Genie clips
I'm like I wish he was still here to talk about
what's happening now
Genie gave that a passion plea to Congress
last week though
yeah it was for the first responders
of the first prince's pants being
bit
what?
the first prince who got his pants
that was a disaster
year after year
no reparations to repair
the pants
we're not playing for the threads
Raja I forbid
you from having any daughters
Raja?
it's like the Raja
understands English and is also like
you're not going to let me fuck?
I'm going to fuck that carpet
here's a really
specific one
right before the stairs
march
this is a come downstairs Madonna
what?
did she fall?
yeah
other people falling
was fine
it's not the one that happened in our house
yeah
hello Baymax
or hello I'm Baymax
they were doing that
two years after
the Euro 6 came out
not to be the comedy police here
or whatever but
there's a lot of punching down going on
with this Aladdin show right?
a lot of ladies
a lot of non white people
I don't hear a lot of
powerful
straight white guys getting called
to the mat too much here
this little hegemonic family
is all coming in being like please
reestablish the status quo for us
weee
do you consider Baymax
a white guy?
at least it's all
better than the Bill and Ted show
when we analyzed it a little while ago
it was 90%
very mean gay jokes
yeah
actually I was going to bring this up
the thing I really like
about Disney's
well I'll say it more in the negative
the Universal Studios
I don't like their
tone
their sensibility
their sense of humor is sort of like
we pranked ya
we embarrassed ya
in front of everybody
they'll get a volunteer
somebody who's offered to help them
and then they're like
you're a piece of shit
and everyone's laughing
what I love about
and I know that's what
Universal has to do
when you're the punk kid
not everybody likes you
and what I like about Disneyland
is like
it's not just wholesome
it's pretty friendly
the genie can get a little blue
I want to get moved to your twitter
but I have one more thing to say
somebody walks out of a room
and he says bye Felicia
yeah he pulls the bye Felicia
and here's my thing about
bye Felicia I still
I never figured out what it was
I don't know the source of it
it's from Friday
it's a character in Friday everyone hates
so why did it get popular like two years ago?
it became popular
on twitter
as like a fuck you
I think it
came up on black twitter
was then taken by marketers
by like Nancy Pelosi
yeah by like Nancy Pelosi
so we say to Trump
it was a long time short hand
for like you see you can go fuck yourself
basically
but has had a resurgence
alright well I've outed myself
as having not seen Friday
do you think
is Felicia Day
in Guardians of the Galaxy?
no
I know what you're thinking of
it's the other actor
because I was hoping that the Guardians of the Galaxy
ride next door
would overhear
it's Karen Gallum
yeah sorry
they're similar looking
he also says I like
your weave carpet
yeah he says that a lot
I like your weave
also he
pronounces Jafar the Sultan
and then sorry
Miss Philippines is the Sultan
a reference to Steve Harvey
Miss Universe
yeah
another not white guy
and you know what
oh but he
you said one of these
he took down Prince Charles
but he
he did some white guys
he said his chest
was like the Patriots football
he had press on it
he said here you play Tom Brady
which if you're
listening Mitch I'm sorry
he's gonna be mad
he's like
worst fucking play ever
refuses to go to the Disneyland ever again
I always have
so
I feel like to wrap up
what we should do is
this is the first thing Scott asked me
when we met
he said did I heard you have a Twitter account
for the genie from California Adventure
and I have
I have it it's still active
Mike I remember this but I didn't know that was you
that was me yes
what is the handle for people to follow
I think it's time I haven't tweeted on it
in literally 8 years
whoa
it's time for him to come back
let him out of the lamp
at topical genie
topical genie
I remember the picture getting to the
yes
wow
these are reading my own jokes but a couple of them for you
there's no one more evil and agrobot
than Jafar except the lawyers in the Casey Anthony
trial
I almost spat
food out of my mouth
these are better they age
they sat in the lamp and they're even funnier
yes I'm a genie why all the questions
what is this Jay Leno's 10 at 10
wow
if you reference the green car challenge
I'll be really impressed
I think I did here
riding on an elephant is the only way to travel
well that or participating in Jay Leno's green car challenge
yes
I'm gonna just shake your hand
now you guys know why you do it
so that's the
shared sensibilities
you can read all the rest of them here
but let's tweet one out
right now
what do we think what's topical
sorry I put everyone on the spot here
the news now
is all about concentration camps
so there's something a little lighter
let's try to get away from that if we can
I'm told the kids
like something called Fortnite
Fortnite's good
got it
oh wait that's what I was thinking on the way over
are there lives in
Fortnite like do you have infinite lives
okay so then it's like
I can't make somebody come back from the dead
make somebody come back from the dead
back from the dead
but I can start a new
game of I forget what the term is
the waiting area or the lobby
I can only send them back to the lobby in
Fortnite is it called the lobby
I think you're thinking too hard
this isn't Fortnite
I would all caps it
spelled F-O-R-T-N-I-T-E
what was the last tweet before this
hold on let me tweet this
and then I'll go back
this isn't Fortnite
okay got it
last one
10-7-2011
and I can't raise the dead
sorry recently deceased character actor
Charles Napier
and then I just wrote
Furby in all caps
wow the Twitter is bad
because I was asking
I love that somebody who follows that account
and the last 8 years
forgot
well also
I
I had a less successful
endeavor
that we would tweet back and forth
through each other I was at Topical Green Goblin
a topical account
based on the green goblin
spider-man turn out the dark
specifically the letterman appearance
around the same time
so we look at the replies
that will come back too
that was beautiful
that's the start of a new
let's try to keep this alive
this episode
if the only thing it did was bring back
topical genius
topical green goblin
you should come up with a topical
oh yeah
who else does jokes
just Shrek
in the waffle cart at Universal Studios
I mean anybody could
topical Shrek
topical waffle cart Shrek
I meant topical donkey
topical waffle cart donkey
yeah and all of the jokes
have to tie into things you could order
at the waffle
yeah
that interaction thing
you guys
talked about it
ET the ride
oh yeah
he would say your name
my friend Matt
and his brother Brad
they went with their friend Jeremiah
and when they were leaving
ET was like goodbye Matt
goodbye Brad
goodbye friend
yeah if he can
process money just as friend
give up
I think a good Twitter actually also
is just ET goodbyes
and then you just tweet
and ask to be a goodbye
I'm just that
well Neil Campbell I remember
kind of giving me up because he said ET didn't know
Neil's name and he was like
the one human who's left
this earth and stepped on other planets
you should love Neil Armstrong
yeah
maybe he's mad at him
in fading space
you should have a lot of respect for the one human
well there's been a few
but the most famous
oh my god well we've really achieved a lot here
so thank you for
inspiring it Paul Rust you survived
podcast the ride
much appreciated
what a fun topic
and let's exit through the gift shop is there anything
you'd like to plug oh yes
oh
you know just follow me on Instagram
and you can see announcements for fun stuff there
yeah you're on tour
don't start with that yeah
oh and also I have a
podcast as well so if people like
listening to podcasts I have a podcast with Matt
Gorley that celebrates the Friday
the 13th movies it's called
In Four He's We Trust with Gorley
and Rust yeah
even if you don't like the Friday the 13th movies
it's a fun listen yeah you guys are
funny guys it's awesome
and obviously follow us at
pod
oh no no no
Topical Genie
that's it I guess really we should
we should have a Gmail set up
for him too if you want to submit your own Topical
jokes oh yeah sure
I'll set that up by the time this is out
or just DM Topical Genie
he'll keep his slide into Topical
he would say that
yeah like during
like one break ahead of the bread line
he like slides in like I haven't seen a slide like that
since my DM yeah
which way do I go left
right or is this Tinder yeah
so let's not plug into Infinity
at Topical Genie
and all today only one bit of homework
all I have to say is Snooki
Snooki baby
forever
dog
this has been a forever dog production
executive produced by
Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan
Scott Gardner, Brett Bowum
Joe Sileo
and Alex Ramsey engineered
and mastered by Alex Arshay
for more original podcasts
please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on
Apple Podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts
keep up with the latest forever dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at foreverdogteam
and liking our page on Facebook