Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the second gate.
We're here at the beautiful, destroyed Placid Palms Resort.
We're talking Typhoon Lagoon today.
Disney's second.
Destroyed for the better.
Destroyed for the cooler.
Yeah, Disney's second water park after River Country USA.
The freshwater water park that made everyone ill.
Is that correct to their stories of,
was it not chlorinated enough to fight off?
I believe it was not chlorinated at all, right?
That seems crazy though.
It's the old swimming hole.
I know what it is, hold on, let me Google that.
I wasn't prepared for that,
but hearing that out loud is insane.
It does sound insane.
Well I don't know that for sure.
No, I know, but that is sort of the draw.
Like it's the old swimming hole,
but how would they not have a,
like that's maybe when they started.
Hold on, let's look.
You guys talk amongst yourselves.
Well the water park was a more,
less tamed industry at the time,
and the rules had not been sorted out,
although the rules of a public pool had been,
so I don't know what to tell you.
Okay, I'm looking at, okay, I'm trying to load.
Keep in mind at this time,
if you stayed at the Bay Lake Resorts,
you could go out of your hotel building,
walk down to a beach, and swim in fresh water.
Sure, okay, so I am on a website
which I've never seen before.
It's called themainstreetmouse.com,
and this is the Mainstreet Mouse.
So many.
Mainstreet Mouth Mythbusters,
River Country and Haunted Mansion Myth.
So let me see if this is.
Was the Haunted Mansion chlorinated?
Yeah.
Was River Country abandoned due to water contamination?
Let's see here.
Well that's different. That's a whole other issue.
Okay, fine, that's not exactly the myth
we're trying to bust here.
I'm curious anyway if it was.
In 1980, there were four deaths in the state of Florida
connected to the amoeba,
there's some word I don't can't,
some sort of infection I can't pronounce.
Sure, sure.
One of these deaths was connected to River Country,
but the park did not close for another 21 years.
Well that's the bacteria stuff.
Yeah, I mean this is all for a River Country episode.
We will learn to pronounce the name of that amoeba
by the time we do River Country.
We'll all run drills and all be able to spit it out.
And it'll be, maybe we'll spin the amoeba off
into its own character episode.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Dive into the River Country amoeba.
That sounds nice.
A Disney character,
the people who met him never forgot about him.
I have a park star of that amoeba as well.
So I'm partially, I'm partial to him.
People said it was in bad taste
when they introduced that amoeba, but he's so cute.
Yeah, yeah, he looks like one of the Olympic mascots.
Yeah.
The rare deadly park stars
that are in the alligator that attacks them.
Oh God, thank God we're in the second case.
That was the other, yeah, that was the other thing.
You could walk down to the beach,
swim in water filled with wildlife as we learned.
I guess, maybe you're right.
Maybe there was no chlorine in that,
but that seems insane.
It does seem insane,
but the 70s and 80s were a different time, you know?
Yeah, but the nights were swimming in the 90s.
And the 90s were different.
Oh true, yeah, River Country was still going.
No, it closed in the 2000s, or 98.
I forget.
Folks, are we all shit?
We don't know shit about anything
unless we're doing the episode about it.
Yeah, I mean, sometimes casually we do, but like.
No, never.
If anybody's holding us to the fire
on River Country statistics, they shouldn't be.
I'm feeling defensive this morning.
Real chill vibes.
Chill vibes this morning.
We all were at the Cantina last night also.
We had a late, Jason and I had a late night
at the Disneyland Resort.
Yeah, it was not worthy this time.
Octave lower than it normally is.
Yeah, we're feeling the chillness
of the Typhoon Lagoon, of the park.
And we're also, it's a Sunday morning, a rare Sunday.
Yeah, for us this is early,
but you guys were on Splash Mountain at midnight.
At midnight, yeah.
Potential diseases marinating in your laps.
Oh my God, I got so,
that second to last drop on Splash is the killer.
The one in the middle, like pitch black.
Yeah, yeah, the second to last.
Second to last, yeah.
Not the crazy drop, but the second to last one
is the one that will just,
literally if you're in the front,
just dump two gallons of water.
Yeah, it's not spray.
It's the water readjusting,
it's the log dipping into the water level.
It's like two people with big gallon buckets
just kind of throwing it over the top of the log
into your lap.
That's what it is like for me.
You can simulate it at home
if you just sit in a chair in a living room
and just take a Home Depot bucket
and pour it on your legs.
That is the Splash Mountain,
that is the real experience.
That's the real, yeah, that's the real.
That's the real shit.
If you're giving yourself a foot bath
and then drop it on the way to the couch,
that's Splash Mountain.
Yeah, the main drop is nothing.
No, that I think they can,
they can control how much splash it is
depending on how cold it is.
Right, because you're just on a runner,
you're not actually,
like until you get back into the water,
like you're on a little track.
Yeah, but you're doing,
so you did this as late as you could have possibly done,
as cold as you could have possibly done,
although it's the summer.
Yeah, it was like 11, but 58 I think we got in line.
Wow.
We tried to use a FastPass.
It was closed and then we just go in.
Just walk on.
There was no one ahead of us, no one behind us.
Yeah, fast to certain,
but yeah, I've had a couple of those lately
of like pre-getting the FastPass
and realizing all bets are off for the last 10 minutes.
Yeah.
That's still, I mean, that's still when people say,
when do you, when, or they're not crowds at the park,
it's like, well, very start of the day
and very end of the day.
Sure, yes.
Is still your best bet.
So wait for those quitter children to go to bed.
Yep.
Yeah.
They don't have to podcast in the morning.
They have very important work like we do.
Yeah.
Talking about the Disney World's second water park
has opened in 1989.
See, look, facts, I got them.
Facts.
Cool.
It's not too early for me to have facts.
Here at Typhoon Lagoon, you can,
it's not just water level readjusting,
you get wet all sorts of different ways.
Lazy rivers, wave pools, like water being dropped on.
Scuba diving at one point.
Uh-huh.
Sort of, I mean, by that I mean like floating
at the top of a pool that you're out of within a minute.
Yes.
Yeah, all kinds of wet.
Whatever wets your whistle, your whistle will get wet.
June, 1989, so not, so within a month of MGM Studios opening.
We're about, by the way, this is pretty close to,
we should have timed this a little earlier
and then it could have been literally at the 30 year mark.
We are. Oh yeah.
We're still in June, so we are celebrating
the 30th anniversary, happy 30th to Typhoon Lagoon.
A belated, we should have gotten you something, but.
No, we didn't.
But a late podcast is better than nothing.
Yeah, we, this one, yeah, I think, what is it?
Like we should have, is there gonna be like a big event?
You know how they do have like a big haunted mansion event
coming up in Orlando for the 50th anniversary
of the haunted mansion,
and there'll be a big Typhoon Lagoon event?
Probably not, right?
Well, what they've been running a lot lately
is like these glow events.
Where it's like Typhoon Lagoon is open late at night
and there's like glow sticks and neon and stuff.
Yes, I watched some, and it's,
Rex from Toy Story is like raving, essentially.
I mean, that's fun.
Have you seen a photo or video of that or anything?
No. I think I've seen a photo.
Party, I forget what he has.
It can't be like a pacifier.
He has something that's sort of like a rave nod.
I mean, Rex with a pacifier
and like all of those plastic jewel,
like those bracelets, like that would be incredible.
Is it like Rex, was there a short or something
that this is based on?
Like why is Rex?
Yes, doesn't he like, yeah, like there's like a glow
in the dark situation in the tub.
He like meets all the toys.
That's so that's what this is.
That's right.
Okay.
Yeah, so that's, I guess you get your Rex, Phil.
I was, I saw Toy Story 4, it's good.
I needed more Rex.
Yeah, yeah. More Wallace Shawn, please.
Not a ton of Rex, yeah.
You were saying it's, maybe they don't service
the old characters, but they do have to,
yeah, they now are fitting in 75 main characters.
It's so insane.
It is insane, yeah.
So yeah, not enough Rex, but you guess you get him in this
and then you can go rave with him at that.
I hope they have this.
I hope they have this when I go next.
I know they don't get rid of this.
This is, if he's sort of leading the rave
and the other Rex is a DJ, all the Rexes are sort of like,
I guess if you're a Rex, you're into EDM these days.
All the Rexes have SoundCloud accounts.
They're all popping Zan.
Yeah.
Whatever the robotic or toy equivalent of Zan is.
They're all Huffin plastic.
Oh wow, there's a, look at this colorful drink
you can get at the Typhoon event.
We've lost Mike for the hour.
There's a big sucker as well.
It's crazy, it's sticking out of it.
Oh, you can trip out on a drink with 3% alcohol content.
It's pretty fun.
It doesn't even have alcohol in it at all.
It's maybe zero.
It might be zero.
Mike won't be able to tell the difference.
As we've learned, Mike won't know either way.
It doesn't matter to me.
It doesn't matter to him.
Well, he does know because if there's no alcohol
or very little, he declares it the best drink he's ever had.
I think I've witnessed this three times.
Yes.
Well, there's your place for it to get non-loaded.
Yeah, and there's also, at this H2O Glow,
they have this bath,
that's where they have the bathtub Sunday, Jason.
Oh, well yeah, so this park also has the sand pail.
The, oh, this, oh no, this is something different.
Yeah, this is a bathtub.
It's a little bathtub.
There's a bathtub with two little rubber duckies in it.
Wow, that's very cute.
And you can get ice cream and they have sprinkles.
And I think that it looks like there's,
how big of a bathtub are we talking?
It's hard to tell.
I think it's like a little plastic novelty bathtub.
Not one that you can actually get in in a horrible fashion.
It would be funny if it was like a baby bath,
so you know the ones that you,
like if you have a baby, you put it in the kitchen sink,
fill up.
I mean, that would be a lot of ice cream.
Bathtub party Sunday, vanilla ice cream,
confetti cake, whipped cream, and chocolate rubber ducks.
Chocolate rubber ducks.
Nice.
They're topped with sprinkles
and served in a novelty bathtub dish.
They have a, oh, Woody's boot.
You can eat ice cream out of Woody's boot.
Why'd you want to do that?
Woody's plastic boot.
Oh yeah.
That's pretty good.
They had that at Golden Horseshoe for a while.
If you were promising somebody something and said that,
or if you made a bet and said it didn't work out,
you would eat your shoe, this is a good like cop out.
I'll drink from a different character's shoe.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you mutter that under your breath,
I will eat or drink out of a different character's shoe.
It's like a German beer hall.
They have the big boot beer mugs, you know?
Mm-hmm.
The glowing unicorn is the drink I like.
And it is non-alcoholic.
Violet colada with a glow cube,
rainbow whipped cream, edible shimmer glitter,
and a twist candy lollipop, available at Leaning Palms.
They added another word of something
that you shouldn't be consuming.
Edible shimmer glitter.
I just carry some around.
Is there a Play-Doh floater too?
Why does it link to that New York Times article
from last year that says, what is glitter?
The expose about the shady glitter industry.
Oh wow, I didn't read that.
Really?
Something ripped the lid off a glitter?
Yeah, but I think there were still some mysteries left,
did it?
Anyway, it's going into Mike's lungs.
It's going into Mike's digestive tract.
I carry some shimmer glitter to sprinkle on a lot of things
when I go to a fancy restaurant,
because I like to season my.
You spike regular drinks.
If you're served in old fashioned,
let me get some glitter in there.
Like a chef who carries their own salt box.
You carry glitter and sprinkles.
Needs a touch up.
This is good, but I could make it better.
So this is modern day.
Yeah, so that's modern day.
Before they could dream of the outdoor water raves
that are now possible.
No, they just dreamed of a, what's the backstory?
The backstory is that this was a lush tropical resort
that gets hit by a typhoon.
Yes, and it's like all of it.
It's like a, I think also a volcano erupts and an earthquake
or it's like all the things happen in an hour.
And thus propelling surfboards through trees
and flipping boats upside down.
And most famously propelling a ship many, many feet
up into the air to like crack back down
onto the top of a mountain.
Yes, Miss Tilly, the shrimp boat.
It was a former shrimp boat.
The first shrimp boat in theme park,
in themed entertainment predating the Bubba Gump.
Yes.
Was the Bubba Gump, wait, was the ship called the Jenny
or something, what was the, I don't know.
In Forrest Gump?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, that's a good question.
Was the boat called the Bubba Gump?
It doesn't matter.
Either way, this got to, this put shrimping
into themed entertainment first.
Yes.
That's, yeah, great backstory.
The Placid Palms Resort was now leaning palms.
A small harbor had been cut off from the sea,
trapping an overturned boat and thousands of colorful fish
and a couple of sharks.
That's why they had like a reef where you could swim
and meet like all the, like fish that shouldn't have been
there all got like, I guess, flew out of the sea
and plopped into a different pool.
Yes.
Yeah, biological anomalies.
To this day, the mountain tries vainly to dislodge
its unwelcome burden, the ship with an enormous geyser
of water every half hour, which I've heard
that the half hour geyser burst is not only a fun touch
in the park, but also a way to let parents know
it's been half an hour if you're like clocking the time
that your kid is in the wave pool or whatever.
A wise tale of two, oh, wait.
I was gonna say, yes, if you've eaten,
like you have to wait 30 minutes to go back in.
But maybe also if you're just trying to time out,
like should my kid not be in the water
in the wave pool for three hours straight.
My memories of the Typhoon Lagoon wave pool is that
in terms of wave pools, it was too much.
Those waves were too big.
How old were you at the time though?
Under like 13.
But even now, I feel like it brags on the website.
It's like six foot waves every 30 seconds.
Well, cause they were trying to up the game
because this was by no means the first wave pool,
but it was the first one that you could surf on.
And they sometimes do close it down a section off a part
of it to do surfing lessons.
So they were trying to, yeah, have it be more,
more raucous than the usual.
Just kind of things bob around.
Yeah.
So you're not, I don't, I guess you're just not a surf pool.
Got no, had no surf pool queen.
Oh, no, no.
I did boogie board a lot growing up.
I liked boogie boarding.
Me too.
Yes.
I was a big boogie boarder.
Very satisfying.
Catch wave, ride it all the way in.
All eight feet.
Yeah.
The other thing I didn't like about that wave pool
was that you were staring at an imposing stone wall.
Like a 20 feet stone wall.
If you go all the way out there,
yeah, that's a pretty like severe.
Yeah. I could see why you'd find that kind of scary.
Which it is, I mean, it's practical.
It's meant to hide the massive machinery used
to generate wave pools, water slides,
move water up to water slides.
Cause there's water slides and paths
in Mount May Day as well.
Okay.
So all of the machinery is like they have to.
Yeah, I think all of it is kind of hidden in that.
Cover with planks and such.
Yeah.
I was, I got interested in the,
where wave pools came from in general.
Yeah.
I guess they existed in, they existed in Germany.
And then like, there's a couple in,
there's two in America that claim to be the first in America.
But the important one is that there was one
in Decatur, Alabama.
And this was spotted by a guy named George Malay.
There is this incredible Grantland article
that I don't have the name of it handy,
but that's about the men who birthed the modern water park.
And it takes you through the story of George Malay,
who was a SeaWorld investor,
maybe primarily responsible for SeaWorld,
initially starting up.
And then he moved on to start Wet n Wild in Orlando,
which probably without Wet n Wild, there's probably,
I mean, that's the first real modern water park.
And probably there's no Typhoon Lagoon without it,
without Disney wanting to cut into that business.
But George Malay is this crazy, like militant guy,
like an oddly, so people compared him to Patton.
He was really severe and he looks like
a crazy Keenan Wynn dude.
He's like, like weird curled mustache.
He just seems like a guy, like a shell shocked man.
Should have been a member of Sea maybe.
He looks so much like, yes, absolutely.
He looks like any of those guys, Bullion or what's the other,
who's the mystic?
No, no, not mystic.
Mortimery Mystic.
Who's the Joe Roady in Harrison Hightower?
Yeah, yeah, right.
He looks so much like both of those guys, absolutely.
He was a guy who, he was 12 years old,
living at Pearl Harbor during the bombing.
Oh my God.
So he slept through, or he stayed awake all night,
clutching a BB gun in case anybody came in.
So he's this super, which made him a little unsavory
in the race department as he went through his career
as a water park man.
In fact, they opened this gigantic slide
and called it the kamikaze.
People in the 70s were trying to convince him
this is not a good idea, but he's got his opinions
about who he's got his opinions about.
But anyway, this guy.
I cannot wrap my head around a child's war trauma
leading to water park dictatorship.
Yeah.
Leading to, that is a different brand of weird
than the Schlitterbond brothers, like those guys.
Well, the article is about the two men
primarily responsible for water parks in this country,
George Malay, this like Patton dude.
And then in the 70s, it kind of gave away this
to Jeff Henry, the Henry brothers behind Schlitterbond.
And they're considered like the kooky 70s,
like easy going, experimental.
They were like Jim Henson or something
compared to the militant nature.
They even down to like the Henry brothers were like,
how about foam on the slides?
Or how about like a soft little pool
at the bottom of the slide that you crash into
instead of just it's concrete
and you scrape your knees the whole way down.
Like George Malay built like rides that banged you up.
Right.
And yeah, and they like interacted a little
and they asked Jeff Henry in the article,
did you, what'd you think of George Malay?
And he said, he's the meanest man I ever met.
And I'd like to leave it at that.
Wow.
Another, I shouldn't just make this all about George Malay,
but this article was so great.
There's also a thing where he like,
he had a meeting with, he hated the hippies.
He had anybody with long hair and beards.
And he had a meeting with a guy who he was gonna
maybe try to do some work with.
And he went, or there was a, he went out in the hallway,
saw a guy who he regarded as a hippie and just like,
hey, we don't allow long hair in this office
and tried to like, you're gonna have to leave sir.
And the guy was like, I'm Raleigh Crump.
I'm who you are taking a meeting with today.
Whoa.
And he had to apologize and deal with the fact
that maybe a hippie could have some good ideas.
And Raleigh, maybe he looked different as we went on.
Some of the early shots of him,
he looks just as square as any Disney Imagineer
with a rolled up or short sleeve dress shirt or like,
maybe he had long hair at this point, I don't know.
But still like the idea that he's like,
could spot a hippie just from the look of him.
Maybe they didn't even have to have the tight eye
or anything on.
It's that Simpsons joke where Mr. Burns
making the baseball player cut his sideburns.
Maddingly gave those sideburns.
I don't know what you think sideburns are,
but the whole history of Watergate does give away,
it starts with George Malay and then Jeff Henry
kind of takes it into the 90s and 2000s
and he takes it too far with that slide
that killed that person.
And he's now being sued by everyone
and even was arrested for meth possession.
Oh, wow.
That's the update on Jeff Henry.
Hippies in the 70s, manslaughter charges in the 2000s.
At least George Malay didn't kill anybody.
That's true that we know of.
Yeah, sure, yes.
Who knows what Universal found
when they demolished Wet n Wild?
Let us never speak of this.
Unmarked graves, littered Wet n Wild.
A lot of bomb shelters for when the shit went down.
But anyway, that is the guy, George Malay,
his crimes were kind of taking ideas
from little podunk water parks and just using them.
So he's really responsible for the Lazy River,
which you have at Typhoon Lagoon.
And for popularizing the wave pool.
And he also is responsible for the modern water park layout
where the wave pool is the first thing you see
when you come in and it's all centered around that,
which also Typhoon Lagoon.
There were other wave pools
that are hidden way in the back.
You gotta go find them.
He wanted it first thing you see,
you're gonna wanna sit here all day,
big grand vista as you come in
and something you wanna go tell your friends about.
So without this crazy military man,
probably no Typhoon Lagoon.
God bless him, except for the older races.
Except for LD, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nevermind.
Cool mustache though.
Yeah, cool.
This is, I mean, Disney and Universal both will,
are often not the originators of stuff.
There's plenty of stuff, they both originated,
but they will, yeah, similar to this guy
doing it to podunk water parks,
then they see him doing this at Wet n Wild,
which is now part of the Universal property.
Universal bought it and demolished it
and expanded onto it.
Is that where Volcano Bay is,
the old Wet n Wild site, or is that?
Is it, or they don't build it?
I don't know.
Is that where they have the fourth park, yeah.
Well that's not, or yeah,
is the Wet n Wild site where the new one's going?
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe that's right.
But it's all recent Universal expansion
in the last 10 years they've bought up property.
Well my mom would be really upset
because my mom was always so freaked.
Like water parks in general,
I've said this before on the show,
we're the enemy, wave pools, we're the enemy.
Like we were taught to fear the wave pool.
She was very freaked out.
Why is that?
She didn't want it to drown.
She thought we were gonna drown easy
when a wave would come over and knock us down.
Was there ever a scare?
Was there something where you tumbled for too long?
You just didn't even get to that point.
Never got to the point.
Can I ask, how often did you go,
because you grew up in the Midwest,
how often did you go to the ocean growing up?
Almost never.
Pretty much never.
So like, I feel like we were less concerned with it going.
Because you were so used to the ocean.
We were used to the ocean, which is chaotic.
The waves are not every 30 seconds.
They are whenever the ocean,
whenever the tides decide.
Well we went to Noah's Ark in Wisconsin Dells once.
Sure.
That's a water park?
Yeah.
It's a big water park up in Wisconsin Dells.
And we went once and I think,
maybe my sister, maybe my sister,
my mom got freaked out, maybe something,
like she started coughing or something once
when she got too much water.
Maybe, maybe.
But we had to lie and say,
I couldn't go to my friend's birthday
that was at a water park every year.
Geez.
So we had to say like, oh, we're going.
There was a, I believe the story was that my parents,
we're all celebrating my parents' anniversary
and it was always falling on the same weekend
where my friend would invite me to his water park birthday.
That's a convenient refillable excuse.
Yeah, sure.
So yeah.
And they didn't, it wasn't in the social media age
where it's like, you could have cross-checked it with,
celebrating anniversary and it's in October
and the kid can go, wait a minute.
In this scenario where your friend is caught on
to the third year of you making this excuse
and decides to get to the bottom of it
by looking at your parents' social media.
That is the age we're living in.
So luckily, yeah, we skated by,
their anniversary was like around the same time,
but we didn't celebrate it.
Let me ask.
Yeah, what do you do?
I still find it awkward.
How do you celebrate your parents' anniversary?
Yeah, you don't.
Unclear.
One time I left a big like spray painted sign
on their garage door that was just an inconvenience
more than anything.
I was like, happy anniversary.
I don't know why I did it,
but just so they pull up and see happy anniversary
and then they had to like take it down themselves.
Just start filming,
because there's writing on the garage.
They didn't have their glasses on,
so they thought it said like Helter Skelter.
They thought Raleigh Crump wrote it.
Yeah.
These damn hippies.
Why didn't George Malay kill them all?
Mike, can I ask though,
was it at like a local town water park?
Yeah, somewhere not too far.
Your mom may have been right on that.
Like we had a-
Sure, they were shittier.
They had a local, like I don't think I ever went,
there were some birthday party,
I never went to any of there,
but it was like two or three water slides
and a very tiny pool next to the I-95 on ramp.
So like-
Yeah, I mean, I forget what-
Probably poorly staffed.
Raging Waters was maybe what it was?
Raging Waters is a chain.
Yeah, are there's multiple of those?
Yes, I believe Not Soaked City
was at one point a Raging Waters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't think it was.
I think Not's built that from the ground up.
Oh, okay.
I say with my vague SoCal knowledge.
Let's see here.
So many looking up things today.
Raging Waters Los Angeles,
Raging Waters Buena Park.
Oh, maybe it was.
Hold on.
This is very exciting to learn.
Well, hold on.
I think it's-
We're waiting for Google results.
You know, there's that certain
Paramount Park, Cedar Fair kind of section of the industry
that is constantly buying each other and merging and stuff.
Yeah, to a confusing degree.
All the weird up for grabs like Miscellany.
Yeah.
Yeah, the Riff Raff.
Those are the lost toys of the theme park world
to put it in Toy Story terms.
Water parks are interesting.
I think we're all on the record
as not being water park guys to any extent.
I mean, I liked them as a kid.
I really liked Typhoon Lagoon growing up.
Yeah.
But I sort of, I've said this before, I think.
My wife has turned me against them with her fear of diseases
and she's probably not incorrect.
I think it helped my immunity
going to all of these places growing up.
Going to theme parks so much
and going to the water parks and all.
Oh, it like battle tested you.
You like faced a lot of diseases.
Yeah, yeah.
And certainly the Petri dishes
that were comic book stores.
That helped too.
I think my parents' big argument,
well, when we were in the vacation club,
it was such a cheap add-on
or they would just give you the water parks for free.
There was all sorts of,
they did a lot more deals back in the 90s
because they were trying to get like middle-class people
like in there.
Now they mostly want rich people, very rich people ideally.
Maybe buy a home at Disney World.
Yes, that's the new.
That's the new subset.
We're gonna have to do that and then review that.
Well, sure.
That's an episode coming up.
We all split a McMansion in that,
what's that, it's called like Golden Oaks or something.
I have a thing from it in the mail.
We can be Pat Sajak's neighbor.
I don't think there was a Raging Waters,
but I'm confused because there were.
Because I don't think it existed before.
There were multiple not soaked cities though.
There was one in Palm Springs
and one in San Diego.
You know, I should do,
maybe a future episode is the weird abandoned parks.
Like the one, like if you've done that Vegas drive,
what happened to that water park?
It's just like rusting away.
And I think there's another one on the way to Palm Springs
or it's maybe just like rarely open.
There's like a big pyramid.
It's maybe in like San Bernardino area.
I know what you're talking about.
But I'm sure there's multiple abandoned water parks
and I'd like to know what's going on in there.
Are there like mega crocs growing inside?
Like you went inside one of those slides.
They've just been incubating and growing and growing.
Crocodiles or the rubber shoes?
Like mutated rubber shoes.
People may have left stray crocs around
and yeah, all of the various like water diseases
are making them grow and grow.
Maybe a mega croc will put on mega crocs
and then start ravaging San Bernardino County.
Yeah.
It'll be a fun movie though.
Oh, so my family's big thing with the water parks
at Disney World at least was always,
this was always the give and take of like,
well, we could do it,
but that's one last day in the parks.
Like any sort of thing.
It's like, well, we're going to the shopping village
one day, let's try to get it all done.
Because if we come back, it's less time at the parks.
We're less time at the pool.
What's gonna make it so hard for us
when we have to ignore the parks
and do 13 straight days of research
on the Disney Springs saga?
Yeah, it's gonna be pretty irritating to go on no rides,
but you know, that's what we're just walking through.
Hopefully by that point we'll be owned
by Monsanto Productions or something or some.
The Monsanto streaming service?
Yeah, Monsanto streaming service.
So we're like making, you know, like, you know,
mega bucks for, I'm sure they spring for streaming.
Sure, well they're paying us in Monsanto bucks
in Monsanto's script and they're putting us up
at the Monsanto Inn in Orlando.
So we get paid in like corn syrup.
What does Monsanto make?
Yeah, corn syrup, seeds.
We can exchange.
Yeah, proprietary seed blends.
Yes, seed blends not yet released to the market.
Sure.
Great, I'll sign that deal.
Sounds good to me.
Mike, you mentioned the mega crock would be a good movie.
Do you think the backstory of Typhoon Lagoon
would make a good movie?
What would the ship getting, you know,
a ship landing on a mountain, what a story.
Yeah, you know, it would be like a very,
too intense for a child I think maybe.
Yeah.
The movie might be a bit scary.
A perfect storm, just a very serious.
I believe this is a movie kind of, a few years ago.
The Chris Pine movie?
No, Ewan McGregor and Naomi Watts.
What?
At a resort in, like an all-inclusive resort,
a hurricane hits and it's like trying to survive.
The impossible.
Eugh.
Well, I say this because I ran into this bizarre piece
of info that, and this is backed up because it is still
on this writer's website that apparently there was
a Typhoon Lagoon script written at the time by a writer
of Who Framed Roger Rabbit, Gary Wolf.
So there was a script of the story and somehow it was deemed
not crucial enough to make, but there was a press release
when Typhoon Lagoon opened where Disney said,
this is an unprecedented undertaking whereby a motion
picture and a themed attraction will perfectly
complement each other in a unique demonstration
of the abilities of the Walt Disney Company.
So they thought they were gonna build this water park
and then that will be the backdrop for the film.
Right.
So we're getting two uses out of it.
Wow.
What happened there?
Just totally abandoned.
Yeah, I mean, there's been so many abandoned park specific
things over the years.
Sure.
Like the big thunder pilot and so yeah, I wonder,
was it bad?
Did someone say this isn't that fun of a story to what?
I mean, people had to die in the narrative of this, right?
On Typhoon Lagoon, like.
Yeah, it's a little.
Maybe not in the Disney version.
Well, how would a ship.
A ship flew around and it was fun.
It was like bed knobs and broomsticks, the hijinks.
A ship shoots out of the water
and gets like impaled essentially.
It's like the bottle episode of a sitcom where it's like,
oh, there's a tornado warning.
We gotta hang out in the basement for 30 minutes.
You know.
I'm just saying there, you would have had to really do some
like, show all the characters float to safety
from the whatever, to Typhoon, of course,
into the lifeboats, I guess, to make it like,
oh, the ship, are we all here?
Yes, we're all here.
Okay.
What if there was like a pre crystal skull situation
if they all got into an industrial strength shrimp fridge
in the boat.
Oh, there we go.
Everybody's just hidden in there,
but that like protected them enough from the,
but then it becomes the adventure of climbing down the ship,
down the mountain and like everybody leaning too far
and then the ship's tilting this way
and they're worried it's gonna snap in half.
Oh, and then they inflate life rafts
and slide down the mountain.
And at the bottom, they're like, hey, that was pretty fun.
Maybe these are the fixes.
Maybe these were the fixes though
that would have made the movie happen.
Well, who owns the, so do we gotta talk to Gary Wolf
and get this moving?
I'm sure Gary Wolf, I'm sure Disney owns the script.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And like Hollywood loves jerking people around
on screenplays and ripping them away from people.
So yeah.
Gary Wolf's script.
Give us the script to punch up.
Disney plus, baby, you know you need that content.
Yeah.
If Disney plus doesn't become every single property,
every ride.
Yeah, every ride, everything we've ever covered
on this show has to turn into.
The motto is just quantity, not quantity over quality,
just quantity.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
So I want my, so I should start going in and pitching,
like it's, imagine the story of Tony Solaroni
in the Pangolite to Pizza Port,
you got it mixed with a little bit of chef flavor.
Or it's the other, or it's, what's that,
what was that Bradley Cooper asshole?
The Burt?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a little bit, let's say it's Tony Solaroni's Burt.
And Jason's thing is the Mark Twain movie,
the Mark Twain Riverboat movie.
Yeah.
It's just about the boat, not about Mark Twain.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a documentary about you sitting on the Mark Twain
for an afternoon.
Yeah.
It's like, or it's like Southern bells,
like wishing like, like we haven't had a good captain
around these parts in years.
That's good too, yeah.
Well, hello ladies.
Hello.
I think I'm a little lost.
I'm still getting acquainted to town.
Well, we can help you find your way.
Oh, capital.
This sounds like it's gonna be
some sort of like a sexy romp
on the Mark Twain with Jason.
Three Southern sisters competing
for Jason's affections on the Mark Twain.
Okay, well actually that's really great.
I was one trying to figure out what ride
would be the most fun to pitch to Disney Plus
and like a Don Draper sort of like,
it's not, it's your childhood.
It's not just Aladdin's magic carpets.
The carpets fade away.
You only remember the good stuff.
You don't remember getting stuck on it.
Well, that's when it's, if it's a thing
about the mad tea party, but it's a bizarre scenario
of people getting trapped and like boiling hot cauldrons
of actual tea.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
Why can't we make dark shows out of these rides?
My pitch of course is just Fast Pass the movie
or Max Pass specifically.
That's just you on a bench for an afternoon.
Well, yeah, it's a very exciting movie.
You were showing us how you refresh the other,
yesterday at the park.
Like, and then you refresh like this.
It's a very tense, exciting movie.
It's like a Mission Impossible movie for me.
I'll do it like 50 times, he said.
Guys, drop everything.
Our Matterhorn pass for 525 can maybe be superseded
by a new reservation time at 510.
And then it's all characters going,
wow, it's really great that you told us this.
This is very valuable information.
This is great.
This is gonna optimize our time in a new way,
in a great new way.
Thank you.
We'll be able to start mobile ordering diet cokes
sooner than later.
It's honestly, it's not, that sounds like a great movie.
That sounds tense though.
So Typhoon Lagoon, the number two most attended
water park in the world.
Blizzard Beach, number three.
Number one, Chime Long Water Park in Guangzhou, China.
I believe this was the same statistic
on the Blizzard Beach episode,
but this is the updated 2018 numbers.
Beat them by a few hundred thousand.
Chime Long, 2,740,000 guests.
Typhoon Lagoon, 2,271,000 guests.
Mm-hmm.
So second most popular, but number one in America.
But on the plus side for Typhoon Lagoon,
you are allowed to use Google and the free internet.
That is true, yeah.
There's less restrictions.
You can get whatever you want on Alibaba,
our new partner, Alibaba.
What is Alibaba?
Is that their search?
Amazon.
Oh, they're Amazon.
Yeah.
Okay, huh, huh.
Which I assume is nefarious in some regard.
I think it's just, it's like anything,
but it can be like very unregulated.
They have, it's got a charismatic chairman named Jack Ma,
who like always does like rock show
at the annual like shareholders thing.
What?
I watched a special on it once.
Whoa.
It's like, like he plays music.
Oh.
Like the company presentation.
He doesn't play the wing song rock show?
Maybe he does.
Oh, I just went, I was wondering if you meant rock show.
Yeah.
What does he do?
He performs a rock and roll show.
He performs a rock and roll.
You don't see Jeff Bezos doing that.
No, he wishes he could do that.
Where's your album, Jeff Bezos?
Yeah.
Forget the money or your math.
Oh, I would love divorced billionaire album.
I would love to hear like,
I've just had a lot of feelings I need to process.
Well, all these guys might be in the Eddie Murphy scenario
where they make albums and then give it
to their underlings to release.
And they like, hey, so did that album ever come out?
Oh yeah, it's number one.
Isn't that the rumor with Eddie Murphy
that he like thinks his music is.
Is that right?
Yeah, I don't know where I've heard that.
That like, I think he thinks that his albums
are always coming out and like America loves them.
Wow. I've never heard that.
I mean, I know like he, I thought he had just like
made a bunch of albums and then like
never really releases them.
But then that one song, Red Light,
a couple of years ago, you remember that?
I sort of.
Reggae song he released, I think Snoop Lion was on it.
Okay. Maybe I'm making this up.
Maybe I'm creating a scenario where he's so protected.
He's like this king who thinks that all of his.
Another hole in one, sir.
It's the same like Trump or something.
I hope that's right.
I hope he thinks like, he's like, it's like, okay.
So the top selling artists of all time,
the Beatles, you, Mariah Carey.
He's like, wow, that's great.
All right, anyway, back to doing weird stuff.
Doing whatever it is I do.
Yeah.
Okay.
You've crushed Garth Brooks into the ground.
Oh wow. Five times over.
Congratulations, Mr. Murphy.
A bad Photoshop billboard magazine.
He's on the cover and he's like, wow, this is great.
Shall I put out another press release
about a coming to America sequel that will never happen?
Yes, please.
That would be insane.
If that does happen, did you guys see the story
going around about Eddie Murphy on the set
coming to America, grabbing John Landis by the throat,
choking him and grabbing him by the throat.
And then Landis was still being an asshole.
So then he started to choke him.
Whoa. I did not read this.
Some insane thing.
I mean, I had heard that he like made everybody,
like that he, Landis had to like direct via middlemen.
Like that, like Eddie would not talk to him anymore.
So he had to like go talk, like tell the guy like,
here, Tom, go talk to Eddie.
I mean, I would believe that. Yeah.
That is like a bull in a china shop
encountering a second bull in a china shop.
It's amazing. But different types of bulls.
Yes, different types of bulls.
I'm guessing.
Well, it's like Millennium Falcon smugglers.
One bull can run left to right
and the other can run up and down.
So.
Amazingly, they landed the ship.
Yeah, they did.
Coming of America is a very funny movie.
Then one of the bulls had the worst bull child
in the history of time.
Oh.
Anyway, Typhoon Lagoon.
Typhoon Lagoon.
Let's see, what else?
Let's talk about Typhoon Lagoon's original character,
who now, well, now if you were gonna make a film out of it,
now it'd be easier because there is some great mythology
to go off of Laguna Gator.
Laguna Gator, now less clean than Ice Gator,
the Blizzard Beach mascot.
That's a pun, Ice Gator.
Yes.
But Laguna Gator.
What is he?
He's just a gator?
He's a gator, he's a gator.
He's a funny gator.
He's a fun orange gator.
Yes, who surfs, he's very cute.
In canon, is it that he's related to Ice Gator?
I mean, they don't know.
They seem pretty.
They look very similar.
There's no, like, oh, they're first cousins
or second cousins, twice removed or something.
Right.
Right, we don't know.
I think we should add that into the show,
into the movie or show.
That seems like right for the pickin', you know?
Yeah, figuring out the lineage of Disney blizzards.
We will figure out how they are related.
Are they brothers, are they second cousins,
what are they?
Give it to us and we'll do it.
Are they lovers?
We could introduce.
Could be, oh, now that is the way to go.
Ice Gator and Laguna Gator are husbands
and one of Laguna Gator,
he didn't have the last name Gator,
despite being a gator, he took Ice Gator's name.
Oh, he took it.
I would like to introduce the sort of country mouse,
city mouse dynamic and introduce Riv-a-gator,
which would be, I mean, this is an original creation.
So.
Somebody isolate that clip of Jason saying.
Riv-a-gator.
I won't do it.
Like House of Cards, Kevin Spacey.
Oh, man.
Come on, it's not what you.
Give it with the tail of Riv-a-gator.
Put a third gator in there.
I like it.
Yes, for a defunct water park,
but still.
And his Riv-a-gator story is also about him moving
to a new town and being fawned over
by three Southern bell gators.
Sure.
Come on, new gator in town.
Does anyone know where I can find
the big hunks of raw chicken?
You are definitely playing Riv-a-gator.
I mean.
Motion capturing at least.
Oh my God.
If not regular, just prosthetics.
I would love to just destroy my legs and hips
by trying to do like the full gator.
Why do all the other gators.
You're on the ground.
You're walking on two legs.
Oh, okay, that's probably better for my health.
Ice gator.
They do kind of walk around on two legs.
Maybe because he's a country gator.
He's like, I still walk.
I can't do this fancy city.
Hey, you, if you're playing the character,
it's open to your interpretation as far as I'm concerned.
So if you want to walk around like a gator.
I'll have to workshop.
I'll have to go rent a black box theater to workshop.
Like Mike Myers' workshopping love guru.
Yes, like Mike Myers' workshopping
at the People's Improv Theater in New York, workshopping.
He's got a new character, folks, a limited run,
a new character.
That was the salesmanship of him workshopping
the love guru in the mid-2000s.
I bet it was killing there.
Yeah, probably.
Probably.
I'm excited to see a secret show with him.
Yeah.
And if you're watching it live,
you are not getting his face superimposed
onto a child's head.
That is that kind of thing is what makes that movie.
Yeah.
But yeah, start doing your one man show.
As Jason performing to crowds of two.
I have to workshop.
Me and Mike Myers and Sacha Baron Cohen,
we need to flesh the characters out a little.
You gotta live.
It's like the Marx brothers, they'd like tour it
before they.
Yeah.
Jason Sheridan is Rivagator.
Rivagator.
Make that play, that play bill.
Yeah, yeah.
Somebody's gonna do that for us.
As for Laguna Gator, there's this amazing art,
this is legitimately beautiful to me.
This, here he is looking over.
Oh yeah.
It's May Day over the sunset.
It's beautiful dusk.
It's legitimately great artwork.
And I went down this rabbit hole of all of the mythology
of Laguna Gator that you can pick up by going to his house
or his shed or shack or wherever he lives
because there's a lot of clues just based on what's
on the wall about this otherwise not really fleshed out
character, we know that he likes Surfin' Reptile Magazine.
Right.
And he has a cover up in his shack of Surfin' Reptile
Magazine with a pretty sexy girl gator whose name is
Kathy Kamen, it's not particularly gatorified.
I don't know, the Kamen name after the Kamen Islands,
I assume?
I guess so, yeah, yeah.
She's an international gator gal surfing invitational
gold medalist.
So this would go against, I guess, him having a husband
if he, but maybe he just admires Kathy Kamen,
maybe he's not.
There was a question in the blog that I read this on,
like is Kathy Kamen just like an idol of his?
Is he having crush on Kathy Kamen?
Is he actually dating Kathy Kamen?
Is that like a Farrah Fawcett where it's just like,
oh, this is an iconic character that, or a person
that he likes, animal that he likes.
And it's a classic poster.
If you're a surfing gator, you for sure have the famous
Kathy Kamen poster.
Cause like, would he have a post, it's a poster, right?
I think I saw that picture.
It's like a blown up magazine cover.
You wouldn't, if he was dating her, would he have a
magazine cover of her on the wall?
That's a little weird.
If he's proud of her.
Yeah, but wouldn't it be a photo of the two of them?
Yeah, more likely, I suppose.
That would be weird.
Yeah, maybe it's just a crush.
Maybe it's just a crush.
Yeah, yeah, it's an aspirational.
But this of course goes against what we just said
in the narrative of him being lovers with the ice skater.
Or they were married before and his last name was,
that's his last name.
He's Laguna Kamen.
Oh, I see.
And then he had a crisis and realized it wasn't for him.
And he was in love with ice skater all along.
Yeah, that works.
Everything's fluid in Gator country.
No, River Gator, are you by as well?
Whatever.
Don't put those labels on it.
Whatever way the Delta takes me.
We're gonna do a Patreon exclusive where I just
interview River Gator for an hour.
Can I speak to River Gator?
Riv-uh-gator.
That's like that old bit that you and I would do just for us.
No one wanted this where Yogi Bear would interview
Peter Bogdanovich.
I think it was the other way around, but yes.
Or vice versa.
But you would do Yogi Bear and I would just be
Peter Bogdanovich talking about making movies in the 70s.
Yes, yes, no one wanted that.
This isn't a bit anyone can recite like who's on first.
No, I don't even.
I don't even.
We would both essentially just say things
that that character would say.
What does Peter Bogdanovich sound like?
I don't even know that you had like a break Bogdanovich.
I don't think I can do it now.
We were listening to the Orson Welles, Peter Bogdanovich.
Oh yeah, because I had all those tapes.
You had all those tapes.
I had all those files of that interview.
A very boring interview.
Did you have literal tapes?
Did you buy them from the bootleg market?
Yeah, when I met Mike, he was a tape trader.
He just had VHS and cassette tapes everywhere.
Makes sense.
If you're gonna trade tapes,
you'd wanna get into some bootlegs of Laguna Gators band.
Do you know about Laguna Gators band?
I don't actually.
Oh my God, he's got a poster.
This is another clue from his place.
He plays with the Beach Gators.
Oh man.
Talk in my language.
I miss the Beach Gators.
And they're all named, there's pictures of them.
Boy, you think that a water park
isn't gonna have original mythology and original characters,
but there's so many.
Laguna Gator is the lead singer, obviously,
but you got Scarf on the bongos,
Wipeout on lead guitar, and Gnarly on bass guitar.
Wow, Gnarly.
Gnarly seems to have, he's got a big,
one of those classic Southern hats over his eyes.
You can't see his eyes
because there's such a dip in the hat.
I think Wipeout is my favorite because he has stars,
he has star sunglasses like Bootsy Collins.
Oh yeah, so that's cool.
And some of their songs are listed.
Two girls for every gator.
They had human girls.
To eat, potentially, that's the question.
A little grim, but oh well.
The little old gator from Pasadena.
That's good.
Not really a swamp area,
but I guess a gator could be from there.
And gator vibrations.
And little surfer gator as well.
So they cover.
Gator vibrations.
Was scribbled down five minutes before the deadline.
For the printing, was they, to get the stinking goes?
Yeah.
Yeah, the other ones kind of make sense.
That one nonetheless so.
If you were picking up gator vibrations,
you'd have to get the hell out of wherever you were.
That means that that big gator came to life
at the abandoned water park.
And it's shaking like Jurassic Park.
Do they sense vibrations in the water?
Is that the justification for that?
I think the justification is it starts with a G.
Yeah.
So anyways, please Disney make these songs.
We want to hear them.
But there's, I didn't know until looking at Typhoon Lagoon,
there's a lot, there's even more mythology here.
There's a fucking robot.
The first robot on our side.
Misadventure Falls.
Yeah.
Yes.
Sorry.
New raft attraction, new in the last few years.
That brings the Society of Explorer and Ventures.
Yeah, sea baby.
Sea baby.
Yeah.
Merry Oceaneer.
Merry Oceaneer, because when you look at those oars
that were put up at the tropical hideaway,
a lot of them, I don't know who they're referring to.
And one of them is M. Oceaneer.
I didn't know what that was about.
But I guess that's a character that existed
in cruise ship mythology.
Right, right.
Which, oh my God, there's so much to,
I didn't know we would be responsible
for knowing cruise ship stuff.
But I guess we are when it comes to sea.
But Merry Oceaneer then made it into Typhoon Lagoon via,
this is a slide where you are like seeing her collection,
I guess, things that she's gathered up in her wanderings.
And you get to meet her parrot companion, Duncan.
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
And, oh, Merry Oceaneer also is a portrait
in Mystic Manor, apparently.
Okay.
So it represented in that way too.
But yeah, probably the first purely water attraction
with an animatronic.
And it's kind of on the lift hill
so you couldn't splash it and short it out.
People I'm sure have tried.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, even I would sort of like to
if I could watch a robot explode.
What about Duncan though?
Yeah, Duncan's cute.
I don't want to hurt Duncan.
It's a recent, it's the last couple years animatronic,
so it's got that fluidity.
It's really great.
One of the longest water rides in Orlando,
is about two minutes.
Wow.
You think about water slides and water coasters.
They are pretty fast, pretty speedy.
But this is nice and long.
And yeah, there's lots of sunken,
there's treasure and stuff.
Did you see the diving bell?
When you enter the queue,
there's the big Merry Oceaneer diving bell
that like a one person submarine that you get inside of.
And on the bottom of it is a warning saying like,
I come in peace, I believe,
written in the Atlantean language from the movie,
Atlantis, The Lost Empire.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
Jeez.
That level of detail on just for this
piece of set scene making.
And that's new, is that new or is that there from,
No, I think that's when they put the ride in.
Right.
There's this big diving bell right at the entrance.
That's funny.
And Confuet, boy.
Maybe another final four is Disney's languages.
Atlantean would be one.
Or maybe just theme park languages in general,
because I guess Klingon in Star Trek experience
would have to count.
But the Indiana Jones Mara language.
Navi.
Arabush.
What's Arabush?
That's the Batu language, Star Wars language.
Okay, I didn't know that.
Yeah, there's gotta be more.
Does Yoda's language count as language?
Like backward talk?
Yeah.
Yes.
Backward talk, which is the canon phrase.
Don't look into it further.
Sure.
Yeah, a lot of, and then just, do you have to count then,
do English and Spanish have to count as well?
Because they are used at Disneyland.
I would think that is in there.
We have to rank what's the better language.
So we've made it to Klingon versus Spanish.
What's the best language?
I think Klingon's gonna win, unfortunately.
It's my favorite language.
Not the first, or yeah, around the same time
as Misadventure Falls.
Crush and Gush Water Coaster
is also have some theming to it.
It's themed after a dilapidated fruit processing plant
and is sponsored by Chiquita.
So you can have the experience of going to Latin America
and having a coup d'etat to have your factory
eventually be overrun and abandoned.
So you can pretend that you were in the last empty crate
of spoiled bananas.
The last helicopter.
The ramps have like, I thought, like I was reading about it
and it said like, the ramps are fruit themed.
And I was like, oh, were there pictures of fruit?
That could be fun.
And I looked at the video and it's just ramps
that are stamped with like the words, coconut, banana.
So it's like the cars on Mr. Toad or on Snow White,
which just says the name of a character.
It's a fruit.
Yes, Tell Toad Show.
But how often can you pretend to be multiple items at once?
Like when I'm on that ride,
I can pretend that I'm 12 coconuts.
That's a good point.
If you're after pluralism.
If you're trying to not cosplay,
cosplay is fruit or something.
Well then, I mean, then you just wanna dress as the,
yeah, yeah, then just being Carmen Miranda would do it.
Right.
Or Minnie, Minnie used to be,
I remember like the Polynesian had like one of the men,
either the room service menu or the pizza menu
or had like Chiquita Mickey or Chiquita Minnie
with the fruit headdress.
Didn't she, wasn't there a big float with the headdress?
Yes, and there was a big float.
Oh, in the Mardi Gras.
But like they had it in the hotel stuff too.
Another competition, best fruit headdress
on a Disney character.
Is it, doesn't like Timon end up in one in?
Oh yeah, yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
The whole thing is there's no food left in the kingdom.
Because that scene happens at the height
of the Scar administration.
Oh right, right, right.
There's no food or water anywhere.
So how does Timon come across fresh fruit?
I mean, that's one of the flights of fancy
dream sequencing kind of moments.
Oh, we aren't like meant to believe that that is literal.
No, I think that's like Bugs Bunny.
I think that's the equivalent of like putting a hole,
like drawing a hole on a mountain wall.
Sure, I see what you're saying.
Or they're just so hungry, they're hallucinating.
In that point, we'd go to the POV of the hyenas.
Yes.
I think they know the good spots.
I think Timon and Puma know sort of where to look.
Well, they're kind of on the outskirts, right?
So they may be out of Scar's control.
They're in the neighboring country.
How far away is where Timon and Puma live
and the pride rock?
That's very unclear.
Because for them to have not looked over there
and found food there, I mean, Nala does eventually,
which is why Simba comes back.
But is it two hours away?
Is it five hours away?
Very good question.
Or because I was watching it and thinking,
what if it was just like kind of around the block
and just nobody ever bothered?
Like Simba's journey as he went like a thousand feet away.
But to an animal, yeah, who knows what their sense of time
or sense of space and distances.
So yeah, perhaps.
They'll explain it in the live action one,
like really explain.
Yeah, exactly, like over explain.
They'll give the longitude and latitude
of all the places around the pride rock.
All the characters have pedometers for some reason.
How many steps are all the lions given?
There's a B story of someone trying to get their steps in,
of like Nala trying to get her steps in.
Just a refresher for the listeners,
water slide versus water coaster.
Water slide traditionally moves the water up.
So the water flows down and you ride the waters down.
Water coaster mimics a roller coaster that has,
it provides both descents and ascents.
So you go up and that can be done using water jets,
conveyor belts or linear induction motors.
I am not smart enough to understand the mechanics
of a linear induction motor.
No, you're not, huh?
Do you?
Oh yeah, I know all about it.
You're just ignoring all the skills you have
from engineering school.
Yeah.
I believe also, I think the water coaster technology
potentially pioneered by the Jeff Henry,
the meth possessing.
Oh wow.
Or I think.
Slitterbond, yeah, I think Slitterbond.
All of the water technology came from
strange, unsavory people.
I think the first.
I think they were after,
I believe it says the first one was in,
or no, I'm sorry, these are different types.
But yeah, you're right.
New Braunfels, Texas.
Hey, there we go.
If you remember also, by the way,
that when we'd covered Slitterbond a long time ago
and I read this crazy email where a guy was like,
yelling at his own brother,
hell is where you both belong.
Judges will eat you both.
That is the man responsible for that horrible accident too
now, it's like, what a crazy,
how could these water park people be so fucking bonkers?
The water turns people insane too.
The chlorine, the bromine.
Draws the insane people to it, I guess,
because they were crazy before.
Yeah, yeah.
I have to look into who made Noah's Ark
and Wisconsin Dells, if there's a mad man behind it.
How much of that is Noah's Ark is public domain,
you don't have to pay,
it's a convenient water-based thing that everyone knows.
Was there religious elements of that park?
Nothing overt that I noticed at least,
because the last time I went I was probably 18.
I don't think so, but that's worth a look, certainly.
But that's another water park theme that like,
yeah, a lot of people and animals got on that boat,
but everyone else drowned in the fucking flood.
So that's another ghoulish premise for a water park.
Yeah, yeah, an initial rapture, yeah.
Rapture, climate change, these are the,
volcano, these are the three storylines for water parks.
It's almost sacrilegious in the idea that like,
we're gonna have a fun time in the middle of the great flood
that killed most humans.
But it killed a lot of mostly bad humans,
the ones that God wanted to smite.
So it's good, we should be celebrating.
That said, the Sodom and Gomorrah buffet,
well reviewed on TripAdvisor at the Noah's Ark water park.
I see there's an ad on the Noah's Ark website
for the Father's Day flop.
Which shows a-
So is Father's Day considered a religious holiday?
I don't know, there's a man about to flop
on his belly into the water.
We are so sorry we did not cover the Father's Day flop
for this podcast, we have let you down, our audience.
Yeah.
Next year we will be flown out by the Noah's Ark people,
and we will cover it live, we'll do play by play
like a sporting event, the three of us.
This podcast is gonna get real sad.
Folks, the dads are here and they're ready to flop.
You know, I liked podcast the right when it was about,
you know, Big Thunder Mountain,
but it's been about the Wisconsin Dells
for the last year and a half now.
It's less relatable.
What have we not covered from Taif?
Oh, Humonga, Cowabunga.
Oh yeah.
Those three enclosed, the speed slides.
I gotta say, I like water slides.
There's never one for speed slides.
I think as I got older, I tried them,
but like, I like the kind of curving water slides
where you splash down and like a little pool,
or like a pool that's like three feet deep.
I'm not wild about the ones that go like straight down
and the water is like an air break.
Those always like freaked me out as a kid.
I think I'd done like one or two smaller ones,
but I never did the one at Blizzard Beach
where the floor drops out and drops you.
There's a similar one at Volcano Bay as well.
There's like a little red, there's like a little red cabin
you go in and then it just drops out.
And I didn't do it either,
but I'm wondering if I should do it next time.
I would try it now.
Cause it does seem, that does scare me
and it seems unpleasant,
but also everyone does it and it's fine.
I'll say this, I'll try most attractions,
but like there's the two things I am not wild about.
One, standing up coasters, which I have ridden before,
but they are not made for a person of my stature.
I see.
Cause there's kind of like a bicycle seat sort of thing
that goes between your legs.
And that is unpleasant
cause they think you're much taller.
Well, the mummy coaster at Universal
is very unpleasant for me, a taller man.
Because you're scrunched in so much.
Cause it compacts my genitals.
Yes.
But for me, it's all just right.
Perfect for baby bear.
The average bear, sorry.
So stand up roller coaster.
The other thing is that thing you see at carnivals
it has different names, but it like spins.
Oh God.
And it's, you go inside, you stand inside
and the walls are mats and you kind of lean against the mat
and then it spins and it spins so much that the G force,
then the floor drops out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And you're just pressed against the wall.
I like that ride.
But are there ever,
there's no sort of belts or restraints or anything.
It's just gravity.
Yeah, we had the Gravitron.
Yes, that's like the one generic name kind of thing.
Yeah, and I loved it.
And there was no belts.
Have you ever done this?
No.
Do you know, have you ever seen one?
Oh yeah, I know what you're talking about.
Yeah, it's a big like UFO that spins around essentially.
So yeah, you would get inside
and there was no restraints or anything.
So when the thing was going so fast,
you'd be pressed against the wall
and you could do also, you could like turn upside down
sort of in the thing. Yeah, you could do bits.
You could do any like, yeah, you could move around.
I mean, you couldn't move so far,
but you could do whatever you wanted
within your little space probably,
cause you couldn't get like, it was hard.
The forces would keep you mostly in place,
but you could spin around yourself.
So I would like spin around in a circle
while I'm being pressed against the wall.
It was fun, I don't know, I loved it as a kid.
I like that.
And that wasn't too scary or anything.
You think it'd probably be better for a child,
probably better small.
Yeah, I would imagine that I couldn't fit
so comfortably on it now,
but maybe there's a big gravitron somewhere.
Maybe.
But speed slides, what you have described
in Volcano Bay, I am intrigued by that.
I think the novelty aspect would override my fear aspect.
We were up there and I was like,
I don't wanna do this and then we didn't do it,
but I feel like I should have been forced to do it.
I should have shoved me in and ran away.
Did she do it?
No. Oh, okay.
No, no, she didn't wanna do that either.
Yeah, those, yeah, I'll do it next.
Okay, I'll pledge I'll do it next time.
I'll pledge to you, the listener.
Humonga cowabunga.
I'll do humonga cowabunga, I'll do whatever.
Gangplank falls.
Gangplank falls. Well, that's just a family
raft ride.
I'll do gangplank falls.
That's my pledge.
I'll do sitting in the wave pool.
I will do Castaway Creek lazy river,
which is one of the ones you can use a tube
or you can just kind of float yourself and be propelled.
I always like that.
If I want.
None of us are allowed to go to Ketchakitty Creek,
the unpleasantly named child play area.
For the best, we not go there.
Don't go to Ketchakitty?
Yeah. Bullshit.
I don't, this came up before,
before we get too far away from it,
I hate to get us off track again.
At Noah's Ark, they have something called
the 4D Dive-In Theater, and there's a picture of the rock
from Journey to the Center of the Earth on it.
In our 4D theater, the fun comes at you
from every direction.
You'll duck flying objects, feel every splash
and even smell what's on screen.
Part eye popping movie, part hair raising ride.
Totally unforgettable fun for the entire family.
So we got to investigate what that is.
The Journey to the Center of the Earth 3D Water Ride.
So it's still possible to go see the rocks famous
bee flight and experience it yourself.
Yes.
All right. Anyway, back to the type of.
A movie made, the budget for that movie came
from a country that no longer exists.
That always, see, I remember the summer that came out.
I was like, this ain't a movie.
No, this ain't real.
Is that River Gator commenting?
Oh, this ain't, this ain't real movie.
It's in variety, but I don't believe it.
I don't go for motion pictures.
Just give me a washboard and a hootin' nanny
and I'll be entertained all night.
Here's something we haven't talked about.
The food options at food options at water parks.
Never, never like amazing.
I remember when you went to volcano Bay
that the opening summer, they were really pushing.
It's like the food and drinks are fun and good.
And it seems like they've already scaled back on that.
Yeah, they were trying to do something interesting
with the food and then in two months
it's a chicken sandwich.
Typhoon Lagoon, you get that sandpale ice cream
that comes in a bucket.
And then everything else seems to be like various iterations
of burger, maybe burger with guacamole or pulled pork,
something a little interesting.
There's like rice bowls and acai bowls.
Like they're branching out a little,
but like people are eating this stuff on the go
in their bathing suits.
So it's not like you can have fine dining or something.
Jason, you mean you don't wanna eat a jerk chicken
Cobb salad while you're sitting by the pool?
I mean, that is probably one of the fresher items
available for sale.
It just feels like a lot to have to deal with
while you're there.
Sitting on a lazy river too.
Real jerk chicken, like I feel like so much.
You eating a big salad in a lazy river?
So much like lightly spiced grilled chicken.
They're like, here, jerk chicken.
It's like, oh no, this isn't good.
You look, I've had real.
It was like kind of flipped twice in some way.
Yes.
You know, like little trough of powder.
Yeah. Yeah.
They have an Italian deli sandwich on the menu.
That's all it's called.
It doesn't have a fun name.
Italian deli.
And then they, yeah.
If you're a kid on crustables, you can get a turkey sandwich.
Sweet. Exciting.
Yeah.
The other place is called Let's Go Slurpin'.
Yes, the bar is called Let's Go Slurpin'.
All right.
I like that.
Approved.
So that's good.
There's still like, the names aren't that fun
for these drinks though.
There's a Typhoon Tilly, which is fun.
Okay.
And a Pina Colava, but it's like Grand Margarita,
Banana Cabana.
Well.
Banana Cabana's fun. Banana Cabana's fun.
That's fucking fun, Michael.
Okay. Half of it's not fun.
Half of it's fun.
Yeah.
I want all of it to be fun.
Banana Cabana is fun.
How do you guys feel about Cabana rentals
at pools or at like water parks and stuff?
I never go for it.
Yeah, I don't ever.
It's just because it's always like $200.
Yeah.
It's not like $20.
And then you can end up just in a chair
two feet away from.
Right. Yeah.
It's not that, it depends what it is.
But like in Vegas, especially never,
like it's so expensive to like buy a shaded area.
It's like $500 or something.
Yeah.
So yeah, very, I probably never, we've done maybe once,
but I can't remember.
I'll be in the lazy river at the MGM Grand Pool,
probably tomorrow.
Wow.
I'm heading over there,
which is in the space where the MGM Grand Adventures
theme park used to be.
So sadly departed, but pretty good pool area,
but it's pretty like, you know, it's pretty clubby.
Yeah. It's pretty loud.
And if you're not particularly a fan of Pitbull
or whatever, it's, you know, you got no tropical theme.
It's not just like, like,
I want generic Calypso playing quietly.
I want Cassio Calypso.
You are hearing Flowrida and Lunch Money Lewis.
There was.
I'm guaranteed to hear Flowrida and Lunch Money Lewis.
Lunch, yeah, we all know Lunch Money Lewis.
Yeah.
I like a douchey pool a few times a year.
I went, I was in Vegas just a couple of weeks ago,
and they had at their douchey pool,
which wasn't that douchey, honestly.
It was pretty nice at the park MGM.
They had a DJ and a live saxophonist.
Whoa.
Like Questlove was coming on later,
but we had to leave and go to the wrestling show.
We didn't get to see Questlove there.
We saw him at the club the night before though, DJing.
But there was a man playing live saxophone
walking around by the deck over the DJ, which was awesome.
That's a good idea.
It was great, yeah.
Was he playing in a way coordinated to?
Yeah.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, he was like soloing over the music.
Jeez.
And we didn't even realize it
because he was sitting down closer
to the DJ booth for a while.
And then I was like, that's nice.
Like, are they sampling the sax over?
And I looked over and there was just a man playing sax.
Wow.
I was like, this is great.
Yeah, I like that.
The only way it'd be better
is if the sax was also blowing bubbles.
They could figure that out.
Well, if he was in the pool with us,
like doing it and bubbles were coming out.
Destroying his instrument.
It's a waterproof sax.
Or it's like the coral sax from Little Mermaid.
Oh, okay.
With that fish head.
Yeah.
It may look like it was made out of coral.
Scott, is there a quiet pool at the MGM grant?
It's literally labeled quiet pool.
There is a quieter end.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can happily report that.
But yeah, even that, there's still the faint strains
of Lunch Money Lewis.
What's this?
Is he the, does he rap?
Does he do the hooks?
He's one of the, he's on the Pitbull song,
Greenlight flow ride on Lunch Money Lewis trade versus.
I see.
Pitbull.
You know Greenlight.
This is the official song of WrestleMania a few years ago.
We heard it a lot as we were watching.
The lead up to it, they were really playing that song a lot.
Because if you watch a six hour WrestleMania,
it's like you hear that theme over and over.
And then of course they come out and sing it.
Right.
Maybe there's an upcharge this year at the pool
where I can ride Lunch Money Lewis around the pool.
I can ride him like a floatie and he'll take me around.
All of them seen performing in a big puffy bathrobe.
So a lot of camaraderie.
That's why he's your hero.
Yeah.
Wow.
Bathrobe where's he gonna stick together?
What have we missed?
Surf doggies.
There's a food option called surf doggies.
That's cute.
Yeah.
I did not go to, I haven't been,
I did go to Typhoon Lagoon years ago,
but I did not go in the last couple of trips.
We did Blizzard Beach.
Cause it's more colorful and more 90s.
This is such a much more like,
this doesn't feel stuck in the era that it was made
because of the way it was made.
Like the-
Oh yeah, we were saying, yeah, yeah.
Blizzard Beach is very 90s
and the plasticky nature of it.
Right, which is good.
I mean, that was the idea, but it is like a little bit,
you can feel the 90s in there as well.
And this one I think probably is a little more timeless.
Tropical is pretty timeless.
I mean, I like the blues and stuff,
the blues and whites of Blizzard Beach.
I do find soothing.
It's like a wild berry pop tart.
Yes, that's perfect.
Yeah, yeah.
Which is in the most 90s food there is.
Yes.
In my mind.
Sure.
And your optimal beverage would be a wild berry pop tart,
just like-
Shoved into that rainbow drink
I showed you earlier. Into that blue Pepsi
or crystal Pepsi.
No, the drink from the H2O.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
And then all of it in a bathtub,
in a little plastic bathtub with chocolate.
But if you then could sit in a bathtub as well and-
Yeah, like-
In a small bathtub.
I don't know why, like what's,
Kanan's all that character, Pierre Escargot.
You know, we all know it.
Pierre Escargot was pretty good.
He was pretty good.
And he was like pretty dialed in.
He was like, so like exactly as confident as he is
on this set out. Yeah, really.
Now. Yeah.
Yeah.
It's like what, 15 at the time?
Yeah, God.
Or younger maybe.
They're doing the tapings right now for the,
all that reboot. Sure.
We love a Pierre Escargot cameo.
I don't think that's out of the question.
No, I don't think so at all.
I think it might be due to unwillingness
to pay a Kenan Thompson salary to Kenan Thompson.
Oh, to do it?
I think he's been in some of the promotional stuff.
I think he's doing a sketch or two.
I'm not sure.
I don't think he's appeared.
I think they all have been.
He does the, oh, if they got Lori Beth,
then they'll for sure get Kenan.
Lori Beth and the other guy.
I think it would be great if it's like,
they need a job in the sketch.
Yeah.
Oh, I know it'd be great,
but I think he's a tougher.
You think he's just. I guess so.
He's just showing up.
He definitely has a producer credit.
And he says the open, he says, stop, look and watch.
He does, he's taking, he's there, Darrell Hammond,
is what he is. Okay.
Kel, Kel has definitely been in some of the promotional stuff.
Kel's in it a bunch.
Yeah. Yes.
You seem like you know a lot about it.
I have oddly checked out all that.
I'm not sure why.
It sounds like you have insider information.
Yeah.
They released a very odd video on Twitter.
That's why I know about it.
Yes. I'm funny.
I saw that.
Yeah. That was weird.
But I saw the.
It was jokeless rap about being.
It is.
That is why I've looked into it.
But friends posted videos like of the tapings
and like the kids are in silly costumes
and they're very, they're.
Just got back from the taping.
Good news, silly costume's still part of the show.
They're in silly costumes, they're getting laughs.
And it's like that this seems better than I'm funny.
Like this seems better than the.
Okay, yes.
I'm funny.
I'm so funny the rap misrepresented.
I'm so funny.
Yeah.
Okay, okay.
The people are going to the tapings and live tweeting.
Yeah.
I think there are tickets available.
Are we going to a taping?
I guess we are.
I don't know.
I just want to, I'd be much more interested in a water park.
You see like one of those Nickelodeon water park settings
should include bathtubs where you can pretend to be.
Piers Cargo.
Yeah.
I think that's good.
I like that.
That is the water park innovation I want.
Well, what else?
We should probably start winding it down.
The shark reef has been closed since 2016.
You could swim with sharks,
like kind of like nothing, tiger sharks.
There was, people did not really like this experience
because the water was very cold
and you were just supposed to swim in a straight line
for a hundred feet and then get out of the pool immediately.
Yes.
And of course it was an upcharge.
God, really?
That too?
Yeah, that wasn't included.
You had to pay extra to swim with the animals.
I will say Disney does sell a pass of like unlimited visits
for just the two water parks.
And if you're a local, if you live close by,
that's not bad.
Florida gets hot in the summer.
So like, yeah.
Couple of water, 50, 60 bucks, just go to the water park.
But I should also be,
if I'm gonna do that upcharge for the shark,
I should be able to like rattle one and take it home.
Yeah. Okay.
Grill it and eat it.
You wanna buy a shark.
Yes.
I'm taking a shark home with me.
Sure.
Just if I finds it, I keeps it.
Okay.
That is your motto.
Yeah, yeah, famously.
Jason, did you look through the menu
of the Happy Landings ice cream?
I believe I did.
Okay, anything, because that there,
as you mentioned earlier, the sand pail,
that's obviously the big thing.
Yeah.
I don't think there's anything fun really,
other than that on the regular menu.
It's that, I think it's mostly soft,
like the same soft serve as Blizzard Beach.
You know, you maybe switch it up, get a float.
But I mean, the novelty of that sand pail is special.
And you've never gotten the sand pail.
I've never gotten it.
No, I think that was introduced after I've been there.
Maybe not.
When we all go to Orlando,
you should have like one like big thing like that a day.
Oh, a day?
Yeah.
I mean, we should get the kitchen sink then.
I don't think I've ever gotten a kitchen sink.
You should get the kitchen sink, yes.
Yeah, okay.
I see where you're going.
We're gonna end up in Orlando for 28 days
with eating ice cream, breakfast, lunch and dinner.
Out of sinks. And a separate dessert also.
Eating out of bathtubs, out of sinks, out of pails.
Flights out of custom made flight containers.
Pails, shoes, shoes.
The Ample Hills in Los Angeles,
they just put it in a little,
they just put the mini scoops in a dish.
Like at the boardwalk.
Well, Ample Hills, as you know,
Ample Hills is next to my beloved Abracadabra.
Yeah.
So you get hammered and then you go over
and have a flight of ice cream.
And then walk into Epcot Center through the World Showcase.
And you're like, this is the greatest moment of my life.
Nothing better.
This is the greatest few hours of my life.
That classic hat trick of alcohol,
dairy and a footpath in humidity.
Oh, just the makings of fun.
I'm so fine with such fond memories of being there last year.
Mike sees no irony in what you're saying.
No.
Yeah. I'm like, yeah, humidity is great.
Jason and I are humidity fans.
Yeah, we do like humidity.
I think I can handle it, but there is a,
the scales, you know, the scales must be balanced.
If you go too much in the alcohol
or too much in the ice cream direction,
you end up feeling like I do today.
So you just have to eat a ton of dairy
and drink a ton of alcohol to keep it all balanced.
Right.
And it's gonna be a ton of humidity.
And sorry, go running on that footpath.
Hey, yeah, yeah.
So if you go out, go all the way up,
like if you go out, like all out,
yeah, you're right, it's fine.
So eat like a, you know, eat a tub's worth of ice cream,
balance it with a sink's worth of liquor,
and then go run.
Sure.
And show for a sprint.
Yeah.
And go see the American Adventure.
And then go watch Mark Twain
shake hands with Benjamin Franklin.
Caffeine ice cream, has anyone made caffeine ice cream yet?
I think.
You've seen caffeine gum.
You mean like energy ice cream?
Like energy ice cream?
I'm sure that exists.
That feels like an untapped market.
Like Monster Ice Cream?
Yeah, that'll keep you going at the parks.
Yeah, sure.
There's energy vape.
Right.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, I filmed a weird shady commercial for energy vape.
Energy vape.
In Canada.
Oh yeah.
I'm not sure the product exists anymore.
And I tried it at the end of the shoot
and was up all night.
It was a nightmare.
Wow.
Wow, wow.
It definitely worked.
So yeah, of all the things I could say, for sure.
Wow.
I can, yes, my terrifying sleepless hours.
Can we give them a plug if they're still around?
Yeah, I'd rather not.
It's actually a felony to promote it anymore now.
Okay, fine, fine, fine.
Since the incidents.
Fine, fine.
Yeah, no, the factory is now abandoned
and that's a viable theme for a slide,
an abandoned energy vape factory.
Yes.
Now the head of that company in real life actually
landed a shrimp boat on top of a volcano.
So kind of ties it all back together.
And of course the mascot is the vape gator.
Vape gator.
Hey, what's up fam?
Vape gator here.
Hey, thanks.
He sounds actually too nice.
He sounds too nice.
I think vape gator would be a dick.
Go.
And he'd talk at 10 times that speed.
Yeah, vape gator.
We've made some more IP today though, so that's good.
Yeah, yeah, several types of gator figured out.
We got anything else?
I don't know, I don't think we might have to.
It's fun, it's tropical, yeah.
I just, you know, watch out for that stone wall.
This is a lot of like weird unpleasant tangents,
but hey, it's a good water park.
You should go there if you're in Florida.
Yeah, kick off summer right.
And then go to H2O Live, honestly.
Yeah, H2O, wait, what is?
Isn't that what it's called?
Is that the Jimmy Buffett or the non-Jimmy Buffett?
You're right, because Jimmy Buffett's water park
is called H2O Live.
Live, you're right.
With like retweet racers.
Oh, it's called H2O Glow Nights is what I'm talking about.
Go to H2O Glow Nights.
H2O Glow Nights.
Typhoon Lagoon.
Don't go to the water park with like, you know,
canceled catastrophe or whatever that water slide is.
Go to both of them.
It's by the Amaco.
This is the one that has the rainbow drink I want.
So take a picture of it or send it to me in the mail.
Great, all right, well, Easter Vibe Bug has the ride.
The second gate, thanks for checking us out.
Happy summer, and if I could send things out
on a truly unpleasant note,
there's one thing I missed that George Malay said,
and you know, if you're thinking about getting
into the water park business
and you want some advice and to know how your,
if your water park is succeeding or not,
here's a real quote from this Pearl Harbor survivor
about building a water park.
Hey, when they're nipple to nipple and bun to bun,
we know the turnstiles have really spun.
Oh.
See you on the bow.
Oh, God.