Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate, presented today in dazzling color.
Come in and see comedy, adventure, pathos, comedy again.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan and Mike Carlson.
We are in color, today's attraction is not.
Oh wait, yeah, I guess they aren't in color.
The thing that I said is not applicable.
Some of the shorts things were in color, right?
They were, but decolorized for this attraction. I believe all black and white.
Is that right? They changed it back to black and white to make it fit better?
I think everything, I was in there a couple months ago and I thought they were all black and white.
I could be wrong, but I feel like what I read online was like this is in color, but it's in black and white in this attraction.
Well, you immediately have a question about the attraction we're doing today.
Something we don't know, but that is the Main Street Cinema, a mainstay since opening day.
Opening day, and if you're listening to this, the day that it comes out, hey check the date on your calendar or on your phone.
It's July 17th, that is Disney opening day.
Disneyland opened 64 years ago today, which is why we wanted to do something from opening day.
And this was an opening day attraction on Main Street.
But you know what, it's recently relevant.
It has been in the news, it has been an absolute firestorm, impossible to avoid the controversy.
This location, it's one of the only things on Main Street that is not a shop.
And in June, well, let me read how it was said on our good friends WDW News Today.
Here's how they put it.
They seemingly held out as long as they could.
While Walt Disney World's Main Street Cinema was converted into a store all the way back in 1998,
it seemed like Disneyland would never pull the trigger on the conversion of their 1955 staple.
Well under the Bob Chapek administration, you never say never.
That's right, it happened.
Disneyland's Main Street Cinema is a shop.
Yeah, it's a shop. My boy's a shop.
My dearest Rebecca, war is hell. I fear I shall never gaze upon your face again.
The picture of show has become a shoppery.
My six beloved screens remain, but also some plushes are being sold in front of them.
Some generic, like the pictures.
Mickey and his American flag, thick sweatshirt is now set up in front of one of the old movies.
Some really, really generic shit, like from what I saw in the pictures.
Like the stuff they sell at the exits or in Florida they sell in the airport store of like, oh fuck, I forgot to get so and so something.
Big jacket that says Disneyland on it.
Big jacket, Disneyland, 2019 baby.
Stuff that could be counterfeit.
Stuff that could be counterfeited.
So this, in June last month, the Main Street Cinema became a store, which I was like, yeah, didn't this happen already?
And I guess that's what I was thinking of, was Disney World.
Disney World.
It's been a store for a while, but they still play the movies inside.
And it happened here, and people, the internet got really, really mad, and then they undid it.
So like a week later, it is now not a store.
For now, yeah.
For now.
Yeah, people, they tend to make changes, if the public outcry happens, they tend to make more changes quicker here in Disneyland, because there's so many locals.
This is though, this is an example of this weird theme park Twitter, where everybody has a different take.
I mean, this is also just Twitter.
Everybody has a different take.
Everybody rushes to judge everything, but then everyone is looking for like their own unique take.
So people were like, wow, Disney bowed to the pressure of the fans with their outcry about, oh, don't turn this into a shop.
Then there's some people going, you think Disney listens to any of us?
No way.
They're just testing stuff out.
It must not have been a success.
That's the only reason they removed stuff.
So there's be like, some people, they don't even think the outcry is why.
Yeah.
They just like maybe weren't moving merchandise and that's why they got pulled.
Who knows?
They did swing the other way because now there are benches inside so you can sit and watch the movies before there just used to be a slightly elevated platform.
Which I'm sure everyone is upset on Twitter will go and do.
Everyone will do our beloved activity of sitting and watching each and every of the six films playing simultaneously.
I don't.
Who cares?
This is one where I'm like, who cares?
I guess I'm happy they aren't selling merch now, but was I mad?
No.
Does it change my life?
I mean, I like it.
I'm prone to go in for a few minutes, but I won't.
Absolutely.
This is the way a human being should be.
Yeah, I am more.
I am the one probably in most outings to Disney and various groups to go like, yeah, we go Main Street.
So yeah, I'd watch Lincoln.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, because Lincoln is the other parallel, but Lincoln is still like a much bigger deal.
Yeah.
Bigger show.
I do.
If I'm being honest, how many times in my hundred and forty trips to Disneyland have I been in here?
It's probably two.
Yeah.
It's probably two, maybe three or four.
Honestly, it can't be more than that.
So as much as I was like, I will acknowledge that my first is nothing sacred.
They're selling clothes in the Main Street cinema.
Then you're like, well, they sell it in literally every other place on Main Street.
Every five feet, yeah.
And this isn't even a thing I go into ever.
Like what?
And then I looked at it and then I was trying to figure out a way to still be mad, even though I had like sort of made myself feel less mad.
And then I came upon the, well, it looks like crap.
The way they have all these things displayed looks bad.
Oh sure.
If it was all Steamboat Willie themed and they were checking you out on an iPad, if it was less, it was more thoughtfully done.
I bet I would have less of a reaction to it.
Like maybe you take the plush and you put them and they're like all along the screen and you can pick one out and you buy it that way.
There's got to be a fun way.
It comes in a little popcorn curtain.
Yeah, we should crack this now.
What if they sold popcorn in there?
That'd be good too.
Sure.
We're already plussing up trying to help Mr. JPEG with his problem.
Okay, there has to be some stuff that is not just a generic like big, big dog type jackal.
This is what they seem to have in their big mouth.
I remember when the Florida one changed.
I remember like, oh, this is a store now.
Like, but the movie's still playing.
This is weird.
Like it was weird.
Sure.
And I think, but as a kid in the late 90s, you didn't have YouTube.
Like I watched all this, all the shorts yesterday and today on YouTube because they're all there.
Many of them, they are uploaded by the Disney Animation account in like restored, like decent resolution.
Yeah.
Although not with the not uncut in Steamboat Willie's case.
It's the edited Steamboat Willie.
What happened?
Oh, do you know about the cut?
Okay.
It was a mother pig and like a dozen suckling pigs.
Mickey picks her up and like shakes them off.
I don't know why.
Well, I do know why because these early Mickey shorts are all just Mickey fucking with other animals.
Yes, all animal abuse.
The animal who can squeak and talk a little bit is torturing the ones who cannot.
Yeah.
Or squeak in a different way than him.
Mickey comes off real bad in all these shorts.
Yeah, Mickey does not come off great.
So he just shakes them off and then, I don't know, bounces around on the pig.
It's very straight.
It is straight.
I'm not actually, I'm not mad they cut it out.
But it was like a weird, it was the weirdest thing in a sequence of extra weird things.
Yeah.
Like you said, goat eating a ukulele and music notes and then you wind its tail and it plays Turkey in the Straw.
That was the height of comedy in 1928.
Like no one topped that.
The height of music.
No one topped that for years.
Yeah.
I mean, it is a very like sort of mind bending metaphysical thing to happen.
You eat sheet music and then play music from your stomach.
Oh yeah.
It's crazy.
Like the interesting stuff.
There's tons of interesting stuff in these early ones.
Like more interesting than a lot of animation now.
Yeah.
Like I posted a while back on my Twitter a scene from the movie Storks where a bird sings, How Do You Like Me Now?
That song that was in every commercial and movie trailer for a while.
Are you saying that's a good thing?
Like literally happens in the movie.
Or a bad thing?
No, I'm saying that's dog shit.
Oh, okay.
But like, yeah, there is lots of fun, interesting stuff in these Mickey shorts.
What was the movie I just saw?
There's a new Alec Baldwin animated movie.
Not a boss.
Not in the boss baby universe.
I saw the trailer for this.
What is it?
Do you guys know offhand?
Is it the spies movie?
Will Smith one?
No.
Wait.
It's a blue sky.
Disney owns blue sky now.
Oh, so this is a Disney film that I'm talking about?
Technically, yes.
I'm just finding something called Totally Spies.
Man, I don't know.
Maybe it's not that.
No, Totally Spies, that was a TV show.
I can't figure out what this is.
But yeah, when you think about the weird sorry state of animation today.
But then there's plenty of into that video game Cuphead.
Cuphead, yes.
Cuphead, yeah.
Oh yeah, that's great.
Crazy Fleischer, early Disney kind of influence.
And like, that's awesome.
Feels very like the hand drawn, got that cool squashed.
Oh, what I'm talking about is Arctic Dogs.
No, this to me is the nadir of I have no idea what you were just talking about.
I saw this trailer before Toy Story 4.
The we were just talking with with Paul Rust about like the when it's a really generic actor so they can advert like what that Robin Williams being a Robin Williams s characters.
The genius given way to some boring actor.
Yeah, right.
And this is the ultimate the main star of this movie, Jeremy Renner, his voice.
The voice of Jeremy Renner.
Singing star Jeremy Renner.
Oh, the Heaven Don't Have A Name.
I never I didn't do it.
Why you texted us the other day?
You didn't.
I didn't do it.
Did you see the covers?
No, no, I missed.
The listener has to go on this with us real quick here.
Okay.
While you look that up really fast, Jeremy Renner is the voice of Swifty.
Baby.
And then elsewhere, Alec Baldwin and James Franco, just James Franco still these Lemmy more interesting voice.
What's so great about Franco?
The voice, the famous voice of Frank.
Which Franco Dave?
James.
Oh, Connors come back to her.
Yeah.
So if in case you didn't know, Jeremy Renner released a single.
And it's got the song is called Heaven Don't Have A Name.
And that's like the Mr. Show two times by one minus one.
Yeah, right, right.
And here's a little bit of it for you.
A lot of synth.
You got to like that.
Oh, she tastes like lipstick and.
Oh,
no, no, no, no, no.
It's like kind of like a fallout boy song.
Yeah.
Now you are the cover songs, though, right?
Did I what?
His cover song.
Oh, no.
Big cover.
I know.
I don't think I did.
Okay.
I have to first off, I learned about this from the very funny podcast.
What a time to be alive.
Check that out.
But I am so glad I get to share this with people who haven't heard that.
This is the Main Street Cinema episode.
Yeah, Mary and we'll get back to Main Street Cinema.
The right way.
Yes.
The house.
Hold it closer to the mic.
Or don't tell as far away from the mic as you want.
God.
Closer.
Mike is pointing every direction to get Jason.
No, no, no.
That left right.
God.
I'm just glad there will be a graphic.
Look at that.
Oh, boy.
Real smoky.
Ooh, the crow of the later years.
Okay.
I'm just glad that to know that there will be a next generation of Hollywood vampires.
Unlike regular vampires, Hollywood vampires do die and somebody's going to have to take their place.
I just learned that that name has been around forever.
The Hollywood vampires.
Did I say this to you before?
I'm not sure.
That they used to call like Ringo and Harry Nilsson and Alice Cooper in the 70s, the Hollywood vampires.
And I was like, well, how does Johnny Depp?
What the what?
Johnny Depp is our George Harrison.
It's like how we call ourselves the Algonquin Roundtable.
Oh, yeah.
Same thing.
What are you going to do, Dorothy Parker?
Sue us.
You're dead.
Oh, boy.
Jeremy.
Well, hopefully he sings then.
So that's culture now that back in the day you turned a goat's tail and turkey in the straw played.
Sounds better.
Turkey in the straw.
It is better to get a star.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I was thinking how I was watching in room TV in Vegas and all the music is, oh, how like, you know, how much music changed from like 1961 to 69 was unrecognizable.
It was not even close to what it was at the beginning of the decade.
And now it's 2019 and we're in like year 20 of, oh, like that's that is music now.
There's no there will never be.
We finally landed on what music is and it's chance to the heavens.
Rock rock and roll specifically is the OO because we still have old town road going strong.
That's why I like when you think about it in the grave.
Do I want to sit and listen to old town road?
Maybe not.
But I like that it's a new thing.
It is not what it's not that.
That's probably why people were so resistant to it.
Isn't that the deal that the country people are like not on my charts?
Initially.
Initially, I think.
Right.
Now everyone likes it.
I think it's really Ray.
I like it.
I love when Billy, oh man, Billy Ray, the Billy Ray remix.
I didn't really care about the Diplo remix.
I have not heard all of these remixes.
You know, all the songs now.
I mean, Billy Ray was the big one.
Yeah, I know that.
I know that.
I'm not totally out of it.
Yeah.
We'll cover each mix of old town road its own way.
Boy, now I'm you know what I thought is that we'd go into this episode and be like, oh,
this old tiny garbage.
But I'm now I'm like, I'm really fond of the cinema of 1910s after that little trip.
I mean, the cartoons that they play in there now are visually still very interesting.
Some fun site gags.
Of course, they didn't come along until the 1970s.
Early on, they played short films like A Dash Through the Clouds.
1912 Max Senate drama about biplanes and The Noise of Bombs, a Keystone Cops movie.
And then the one you know, this one is very influential in the history of animation.
Gertie the dinosaur, the Windsor McKay cartoon from 1914, not the first animated movie, but the
the first animated dinosaur, first animated dinosaur.
It was like dinosaur mania back then because they were just starting to be found.
The bones are getting getting dug up and they were in the public consciousness.
Also first character, like character with personality.
And supposedly Walt took Windsor McKay, the animators son around the lot and said, really,
your dad, like this should all be owed to your dad.
Like he kicked open what I do.
For sure.
Yeah.
He literally said, yeah, it was a nice thing to say.
He's not going to.
And he said, well, can you give me some money?
Yeah.
No, no, my boy.
I'll put your I'll put the dinosaur in a theme park.
Yes, Gertie the dinosaur represented in Hollywood Studios is an ice cream shack.
I watched all of the Gertie the dinosaur short.
I did not realize the live action elements involve a bunch of rich old men going to dinner
and a dare that Windsor McKay makes with another guy that he can make the dinosaur come to life.
And if he wins, the other guy pays for the nice dinner.
This is the plot of Gertie the dinosaur.
So it's mostly live for the beginning of it.
It's live action.
And then it's like, all right, Gertie, come out of that cave.
And then the the cards in between each animation is like Windsor McKay telling Gertie the dinosaur
to do stuff.
But it is crazy to think that he did that all by hand.
And there's a sea serpent, too.
There's a thing he eats.
There's there's so much going on.
But for the rest of the short, it's very boring and determinable.
It feels like a lifetime.
I assumed it was some big fun dinosaur adventure.
It is. It is. Once the dinosaur shows up and then it even like Windsor rides on the back of the dinosaur, which the animator, the animator is like standing on it.
Yeah, I'm going to watch this. I haven't seen this either.
It's worth looking up.
It does feel very long.
How long is it?
Twelve minutes.
OK.
So and then, of course, they all shake hands and it's like you did a good job.
And then the other guy takes the check for dinner and pays for it.
Wow.
Well, well, Windsor McKay with Gertie the dinosaur invented an animation technique that is still used in everything to this day, which is that he was like drawing the key frames essentially.
Like in a five second piece of character animation, drawing like the big, you know, the start of the sentence and when the person gets really mad and then sinks down and gets sad or like instead of drawing it in order, drawing like the big tent pole frames and then filling in the middles, which is sort of how that's that's how everything works.
Like storyboards, essentially, you know, like let's convey the big emotional moments and then everything else is an in between.
And somebody asked him, why didn't you copyright that technique?
And he said, if any maniac out there wants to waste their life doing 60,000 drawings in a week like I do, they can have at it.
That is illicit.
That shows up in the short too.
He's just surrounded by stacks and stacks of drawings and stuff.
Wow, really?
Also hugely influential in the comic book industry from Little Nemo and Slumberland.
Like that was a crazy early broadsheet comic strip in newspapers.
What's the comic strip?
It was a strip.
Yeah.
OK.
Because they have Little Nemo falling out of his bed in Islands of Ventures.
Yes.
Toon Lagoon.
Yeah.
So probably owned by one of those by United Features.
Syndicate or whatever.
Would you believe that I have more material about the other old silent films that were shown on opening day?
I would hope because I shot my shot a little.
I didn't watch any of the other ones.
Would you believe that I have more information about the 1912 Max Senate drama about biplanes?
I was hoping you would say noise of bombs.
I do well a little bit about noise of bombs, but the Max Senate drama about biplanes is a little interesting because it, you know, in 1912, flight is new.
And there so there it's filming real planes and they're filming a real pilot named Philip Parmali, who trained under the Wright brothers, who was the first pilot ever to transport cargo to fly a plane that had stuff to deliver in it.
So Philip Parmali was really the original Baloo and his life was the original tailspin.
Wow.
He also flew the first plane ever to drop a bomb, which I think was on to Mexico.
So great.
Wow.
And then he filmed this movie.
So he was an early pilot on film.
And then several weeks later, he died in a plane crash.
Well, he died the way he lived.
The original Baloo died in a plane crash.
Not like the real Baloo.
No, he's still alive to this day.
And still having heart troubles, but it's that's different than what you still drive a flying a sea plane, though.
And OK, I can tell you that Max Senate to Max in an early silent film pioneer Max Senate Studios still standing in Los Angeles.
Oh, and fountain just east of sunset, like around the corner from Jay's beautiful Jay's Bar, one of my favorite watering holes in Los Angeles.
You really like Jay's.
I do like Jay's a lot down the street from the historic Vista, another L.A.
landmark, Matt Senate Studios is weird kind of triangle shaped building that's just still there and it's still called Max Senate Studios.
Really?
Just named in his honor.
I think it's just soundstages studio space still also still up, but not a studio.
Keystone Studios, which is where if you were driving, if you were leaving like the sunset, Alvarado kind of area and getting on the two freeway going north and you're passing by a jack in the box and a public storage building, the public storage is was the Keystone Cop Studios.
Where they shot the noise of bombs.
Yeah, one of the original films at the Main Street Cinema.
I don't know a ton about the noise of bombs.
What I did write down the 12 Keystone Cops movies all told there are only 12.
Wow.
And this was the ninth one, it said.
Oh, an IMDb.
They would just run down the street.
They would just film stuff of like cops and bad guys running down the street like the camera guy would set up real quick and then go like action and just run down the street, interrupting people's lives.
Real traffic.
Yeah, sometimes.
That's why.
Plowed into by a actual fire truck or by Philip Parmaley landing his plane on.
Yeah.
I the plot of the noise of bombs is for miscreants get revenge on the police chief by planting bombs in his house.
Huh?
It's not a good thing to do, probably.
No.
Although I don't know police chiefs can be not so good.
Maybe.
If it's like the LA confidential police chief kind of had a comment, you know.
Were these shorts that Walt liked?
Did you find anything like that?
Like why these movies?
They must have been.
I mean, a lot of them are historically significant enough that maybe that's why he picked them.
Did he have a crush on what's her name?
Mabel Norman?
Maybe.
Well, every young gentleman did back in the day.
Jason still does.
Mabel Norman, a very big silent film star of her time.
You have a big poster of Mabel Norman on the wall.
I believe one of the few women comedian and women comedic characters like who pulled a big salary back in the day.
Now I'm just pulling stuff I vaguely remember from You Must Remember This episodes.
That's OK.
That's if you want to.
If you really want to hear this.
Where's the place for that?
I think it's Hollywood Babylon.
Fact checking Hollywood Babylon she shows up in.
She was a.
Yeah, she was like maybe the first big female comedy film star.
I'd never heard of her until having to look in the Main Street Cinema.
She was like a railroad tracks damsel in a lot of those kind of movies, but she flipped it.
She then saved the man paving the way for Dudley Do-Right.
And she ended up being like a mentor to Charlie Chaplin in early days.
She directed the first movie in which The Tramp appeared and she helped him make the transition out of vaudeville because he didn't know how movies worked.
He's like, why is everything shot out of sequence?
This is all confusing.
Yeah.
Maybe Norman showed in the ropes.
And also she was apparently the first star ever movie to break the fourth wall and do a little aside to camera.
Wow, really?
They information with their eyes or with a look and to show that, you know, movies can know that they're a movie.
And that is why John Krasinski keeps her picture in a locket.
John Krasinski's patron saint.
Wow.
How about that?
This is spurring.
These are like that's what was interesting to me is that all these movies, these were all were literally shown on opening day in fifty five and they all they are all pretty notable.
So they're well chosen in that reggae.
It was not some random movies.
And to end to that end, another weird historic first this I just when I just read in the list, like this is totally mundane.
Fatima's dance.
Yeah.
Risqué belly dance sequence performed by Fatima, famous dancer of the time.
What I did not know, this is people call this the first censored movie.
She is due.
She is revealing a very mild amount of skin as she does the coochie coochie and the charo dance.
The eventual charo dance.
Yes.
So all the pioneers that they have ever do have paved the way for Krasinski and Charo.
And this was deeply shocking at the time.
It's like a minute of footage of somebody shaking their belly around a little bit, but it was very shocking.
I think there was not a lot of like portrayal of Middle Eastern people or culture in movies.
It was shocking in that regard.
Apparently, like women would go to see this and go, can I be watching this?
Is this OK to watch a scantily clad woman like it like drove people's fancies of flood.
And eventually they made another version of it where she turns and suddenly there are big white bars on the screen.
There's like a big fence blocking the no skin that she is showing.
So this is like a precursor to Elvis and like shooting him from above the waist.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yes. The most mild sensuality.
Right.
It's possibly portrayed on film, but it was so shocking at the time.
Wow.
We have to put a digital fence, I guess, not digital.
You know what I'm an obstacle fence.
I'm upset that this isn't still playing in the Main Street cinema.
That's what I'm upset about.
I think I might rather see all this stuff that I agree.
It makes it more weird.
You can watch on TV.
Yeah, surely these are all public domain at this point.
I think many of them are.
Yeah. Oh, the Mabel Norman to directing.
There were women directing and writing silent films, silent like one realers or features even.
It wasn't until talkies that like a woman directing.
That's obscene.
Like there were women.
It went backwards.
Yeah, it went backwards.
Strange.
Because of whatever, because of the studio system, because of money just pouring in and just.
That's pretty wild that the first Charlie Chaplin movies were directed by a woman that long.
And that she isn't like that.
I didn't find out about her until the theme park podcast.
Behind a paywall.
Yeah.
And perhaps neither did you, the listener.
So, hey, I've all of these movies shockingly interesting.
I did not find anything interesting about dealing for Daisy in 1915 William S. Hart Western.
That isn't I don't know, nothing there or Shifting Sands, a Gloria Swanson melodrama.
Literally Gloria Swanson, though.
That's an interesting.
So it could be a good star.
Yeah, I just don't have any facts about it.
And the other thing that used to play here, Universal's Phantom of the Opera would play sometimes, including a Phantom of the Opera walk around character who would stand in front of the theater.
This was going around Twitter recently.
I sent this to you guys a week or two ago.
This picture, there's a couple of them and he's scary.
Yeah.
He's scary.
Like, horror nights level.
This is.
Chukko's scary.
Yeah.
It is Chukko level scary.
Chukko.
We have Chukko's coming.
Don't worry.
He'll be here.
Some might say he's already here.
He's coming on to you, Scott.
Stop it.
But like I think of like a rolly crumpling like keep Disneyland weird.
Like this is weird.
Just like a Phantom of the Opera hanging out on Main Street.
Yeah.
Like it doesn't make sense now because everything is so on brand and like safe and whatever.
But like it would be fun to just have the Phantom of the Opera like we walking down
Main Street and he's just like hanging out outside.
For sure.
Yeah.
Like that'd be great.
I don't know.
Do you agree?
Yeah.
That's a weird like the cool lost Hatbox ghost kind of yeah.
60s Disneyland kookiness.
Yeah.
Because like you it says it.
There's a picture here.
Lon Chaney thriller Phantom of the Opera.
And there's just a terrifying man spooking children out front.
Yeah.
Like more.
Let's bring him back to that.
There's maybe a point in time where you could see that and then walk two doors down and
see Steve Martin doing magic.
Sure.
And then go buy cigarettes three doors down.
My bras and my rolling papers and bras.
Yeah.
It was certainly strange.
This is an interest.
This is a like I think now everybody if if you're sort of new to Disneyland or don't
know much about it you're probably walking through Main Street and are like what's the
cliff notes of Main Street.
It's oh yeah this is like an old timey area and it's a bunch of stores.
Yeah.
This the Main Street Cinema does take you back to when it was more of a recreation
of a weird little marketplace and similar to what Knott's Berry Farm had up the road
where it genuinely is a place where you could buy jams or a bunch of stones or whatever
the hell Knott's sold.
Yeah.
Well and if you think about when it opened in 55 these would have been period appropriate
I mean period appropriate for Main Street ish time frame but also old movies like if
they were showing Mickey shorts from the 20s or 30s in 55 they're not that old.
That's like they were showing like a Little Mermaid is actually it's now is 2030.
It's like shit.
It's like showing that old show Friends Now.
Yeah.
Can you believe people dressed like this.
Can you.
That is one of the most popular things on Netflix still.
Not anymore.
We're coming up and they're taking it down right.
Please if you're listening to this sign the petitions we have to make sure Friends stays
on Netflix.
I thought they were taking the office down.
I think it's all going.
Or are they taking all the NBC Universal stuff.
I think eventually it all moves.
See So Too baby.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Yeah.
See So Round Two.
That's what they're calling it.
The mistake we made the first time is we made new shows.
It is now clear to us.
No one wants a new show anywhere on the earth.
Single guys back.
Dabney Coleman shows back.
Shaking the fat man.
Yeah.
Whatever that was.
NBC bringing back coach again.
We're coach.
We heard you loud and clear.
I also feel like it was it probably didn't make sense to me.
It's like we have Mickey and other places in the park.
This is about real like what it was like 30 years ago like to go to the cinema.
That's what I was when I was a boy.
Yeah.
I guess Mickey.
If he's portraying the early the 19 aughts you have Mickey Mouse yet.
Walt is portraying a time before when he was only in this timeline.
Walt Disney is only eight years old.
Right.
So he's does he's not made a bunch of cartoons yet.
He's going to our old pharma.
It's also like speaks to the Disney people like I'll always argue when people are like a little shocked that I go.
Yeah.
I go to Disneyland a lot and they're like I just don't I don't understand it.
That's like allude to the fact that it's for children and I'll be like it used to be less for children.
It used to I mean there was still a lot of stuff for children and families to do but it was cool.
It was a hip place for adults to go and there was like stuff.
I guess it was.
They go see the movie on the play.
You drive down.
I'm not saying like it was only in the 50s and 60s.
I like this argument being like but it was cool for adults in the 1960s.
Yeah.
So it's not a problem that I go all the time.
Of course I'm just trying to justify like an alcoholic trying to justify like this argument.
No no one cares.
I'm just saying though there was more like stuff that I feel like like that.
Well dad will enjoy that.
That's a little something for father.
Well that my mind is much more cynical.
It's people say oh you got to do that a lot.
I was like yeah what dumb bullshit do you like.
Oh well sure.
Westworld like what TV garbage game Game of Thrones like yeah all that good stuff.
All that good stuff that everyone complains about.
You get real mad.
I just yeah.
Well that's you know with my like wine centric way of doing things if people think that's crazy.
But what you don't want to go like have a bunch of good wine in like a in like a fake canyon and then go on a fun fast ride.
Yeah.
It's a it's easy to justify.
I feel.
Yeah I try to I could try to get where we're preaching to the choir right now.
Well sure.
Yeah.
Anyway these are all excuses you can feed to your friends and family.
We'll do a whole Patreon of excuses to your friends and family.
It was cool once Fatima was there.
Yeah.
You could see a woman's stomach.
And then there's of course the old universal excuse mind your own business fella.
If you go to universal.
Huh.
No just if just at each time.
I see I see.
Like why why.
I thought you had a specific universal argument to make and it was just get out of here.
Well then because it's a little body or it's a little it's for adults.
Yeah.
Still got that chip on its shoulder universal.
You're just saying it's something to say to anyone who's disagreeing with anything that you are doing.
Yeah.
Well why.
Easy.
Easy killer.
Would you shut up.
Next time somebody questions your theme park thing or anything you're doing.
Shut up.
That's pretty good but do you also have another arrow in your quiver.
What is that.
Counterpoint.
You are wrong.
You are wrong yeah.
Always that.
You don't want to go to that well too much.
It gets less special.
No I know I'm just saying remember you have it.
But it was friendly he said in a friendly way.
Yeah right.
Well what else we got.
Hey you talk weirdness.
There is this Tilly the mannequin ticket taker.
From Marceline.
Walt's hometown.
Yeah.
She's wearing a Disneyland name badge and it says her hometown is Marceline Missouri and that's where Walt Disney grew up and that's what Main Street is based on and you know going down this rabbit hole.
I think probably on yesterland saw pictures of the real Main Street that it is based on.
It stinks.
It's a bad story.
It's not like pretty like the Disneyland one.
Maybe it was once maybe like somebody maybe they've taken off all the awnings and the crests and everything.
Now it's just some boring street.
There's a tool store there.
Nothing's going on.
Why can't you buy tools on Main Street now.
I bet you could.
You could probably you could walk out of Disneyland with a saw in 1958.
You go honey I'm going down to the Disneyland to get a saw.
Well can you pick up.
We need a new hose as well.
All right.
Yeah yeah yeah.
I need a bra.
Can you swing by knots.
Get some jam.
And stones.
Yeah.
You could pick up any.
It was like a mall.
It was like the ultimate shopping destination.
You can get anything you want.
Yeah I don't I've seen that Main Street but I did not look at it to refresh.
So in my mind it looks like the Disneyland and that's the way it's going to stay.
It's well it's they're portraying the Marceline that never was.
I was looking through because this is closed in Florida.
Yeah well it's art is there.
It's the art of Disney now.
And they closed it in Tokyo too.
There was a cinema as well.
And then you do you know they had a movie theater.
And then did you see what Hong Kong's is.
No no Hong Kong's is Main Street Cinema.
My journeys with Duffy.
Oh yeah.
Smart is also a store.
Okay.
It is just built.
Because this is 2005 when these things are starting to close.
And then when Hong Kong opened so they did build a new Main Street Cinema.
Yeah so it is Main Street Cinema.
But it says my journeys with Duffy and it's all Duffy merch and stuff.
So it's a very vibrant thing.
And if you see the picture on the Hong Kong website is Duffy and his traditional sailor suit and sailor cap and cookie holding some waffles.
That's what she likes.
Because that's what cookie makes waffles.
Yeah.
She likes what Donkey likes.
So what is journeys with Duffy.
It's a store.
Is not a movie you watch.
That happens in there.
I don't believe so.
Okay.
I believe it's just a Duffy store.
Weird.
So they decided to.
Much of a journey.
Put Duffy.
Yeah not so much of a journey.
But at least Duffy's involved.
And that's good.
That's what I'll say.
And then I don't believe there's a Main Street Cinema in Shanghai.
I didn't see it.
I don't think they even.
Yeah I don't think so.
I don't think they fucking bothered.
I don't think.
Yeah I think some of the international ones are like do they have the context for.
They've never seen a movie before.
Turn of the century small town America.
Was there not one in Euro.
That's a good question.
I don't know why I didn't come upon that.
I didn't see it.
Yeah I don't.
I didn't see it listed.
Yeah so maybe there just was never one.
Should we maybe talk about the basic of this place which is that.
Because if you've never been inside which is very likely.
People might even think that even at this level listening to our Patreon.
People might think that this is just a facade that says movie theater.
I was going to say.
And nothing's happening in there.
I bet 90 percent of people that walk down the street just assume you can't go inside.
I think so or that yeah once you do it is just a store.
But in fact yeah you walk past the mannequin ticket taker.
Who does not take your ticket because she's a mannequin.
And you get in and there are six movies playing at all times in a circle.
And they are all playing in these little screen tableaus with like curtains.
And then kind of a one dimensional backs of heads.
Gracie Films logo kind of audience.
And it's a nice little set up.
When I do remember to go in there I go this is a well art directed little room.
It is very charming whether or not you sit and watch the Disney cartoons.
Right.
I like yeah it's a it's a charming little building.
It's dark as everyone points out it's air conditioned.
People like that it's a nice little spot to take a little breather because it's there's never anyone in there.
Yeah a lot of backup on Main Street if you need a good place to like wait for Main Street traffic to calm down.
Yeah you can do worse.
I do wonder like I know that recently they just added it to the attraction list on the app.
I wonder if there's any like plus up to it that actually makes it more of a destination because it doesn't.
Benches.
Yeah you said they added benches.
Yeah they added benches.
In Florida they never did this here but in Florida in 1994 they showed the Mickey's Big Break which was an original short commission for MGM Studios Disney MGM Studios in 1991.
What was that?
So I watched that.
That is about Mickey and Donald are throwing a football around in the house and they accidentally shatter a picture of Minnie and Donald and they're like we ought to replace this picture.
And in lieu of just buying a new frame they dress up like Minnie and Donald to go to a department store to get their photo taken.
Minnie and Daisy they pose as their own girlfriends and wives.
They pose as their own girlfriends and get into hijinks getting dressed.
Lots of appearance Claire Belkow makes an appearance.
Mortimer Mouse shows up and tries to get Minnie to leave Mickey for him.
But it is Mickey.
It is Mickey Mortimer Mouse.
Mortimer Mouse.
Describe Mortimer Mouse.
He is sort of a grungy looking tall mouse and he says like Mickey leave leave come come with me leave.
Minnie leave Mickey and Mickey drops the act and goes oh soak your head fresh boy.
Whoa.
Soak your head fresh boy.
Another Jason comeback at it.
If you want to replace Counterpoint you are wrong.
Soak your head fresh boy.
Next time I suggest recording in a live setting you're going to say that you're going to take soak your head fresh boy.
But that is a phrase divorced of any time period that I could associate.
Like I could not soak your head and then fresh boy.
Like seems like they Frank it like reverse engineered an insult an insult and a behavior to go do that is not foul language that is clean but just sounds like nonsense.
It's a good euphemism.
Yeah.
For the for what it's covering for if you were more ribald with it you'd say yeah.
Right.
Go go fuck yourself yourself.
Go drown yourself.
Go drown yourself you creep.
Shit boy eat my shit.
And then at the end Minnie and Daisy come back and they're very touched they went through all this trouble but they're like oh we hated that picture.
They never liked that picture anyway.
And then they put a nice picture up.
So it's nice.
It's fun.
And it's very the 90s look of the characters.
There's a gag where Mickey calls up goofy and says I need you to take a picture and goofy walks off screen and then comes back on holding a giant frame picture he's like all right I got it.
Where do you want me to.
Gosh where do you want me to take it.
And he's like no take a picture with a camera he's like oh take it.
You said take a picture you mean take a picture like that.
There's some fun fun beats in it fun moments.
Is there is there any boyfriend or girlfriend or husband or wife out there who could successfully pose as their own mate who could who could convince someone they knew that they were.
Oh I there has to be honestly somebody has to look close and look like each other.
Yeah I bet they could.
The voice of mannerisms would be the hard part.
Yeah.
Yeah I don't think I'm like gonna go nobody's gonna think I'm Aaron.
No.
I walk around saying I'm Aaron.
I bet Rich Little could pose as his own wife.
I think that he's good enough.
He can do it all.
What can he do yeah.
So Rich Little appears on a lot of Patreon episodes.
Coincidentally his wife sounded like I'm Mrs. Little.
Mrs. Little sounds like Nixon and it's perfect and he does it all the time.
If he needs a call and like make a change to the bank account that's in her name he can do it whenever he wants.
He shouldn't be doing that at all.
I say it's okay.
I authorize this.
If Mrs. Little does it it's not a crime.
It's got to be somebody somewhere.
The movies themselves that play currently showing now show.
Yeah.
And has it been the same lineup since they made the switch and was that in the 70s or so.
I couldn't find a good answer to that.
Mostly yeah hard to tell.
But I think by and large mostly the same lineup.
These are some of the bigger early Mickey cartoons I think.
Sure yes.
And I it seems like you watched them.
I thought to watch them last night as well.
I lined up every TV and screen and laptop in my house.
I surrounded myself with six movies.
Yeah.
Turn from one to the other.
I turned off the lights.
The audio coming from Rex.
Yeah yeah yeah.
I played silent movie peony through Rex and then led him around by hand.
Yeah.
Because we're going to watch the dog napper.
Rex you excited.
I got a bad feeling about this.
Well I guess so chronologically plain crazy was the first one right.
The first Mickey cartoon.
First appearance of Mickey.
Which in that regard it's nice to have this thing here as it is a nod to the original.
Yeah.
Shorts into the animation history laid by by Walt and Mickey themselves holding hands a
mere mere feet away.
Yeah.
Partner statue episode.
I'm sure coming at some point.
Playing crazy is fun.
Mickey gets inspired by lucky Lindy Charles Lindbergh.
He looks at a portrait of lucky Lindy at one point and then tries to ruffle his hair in
a mirror to look like him.
And there's a couple very funny.
I don't know.
There's a funny moment where look Mickey looks like a sleaze bat if you pause it.
Mickey's got ruffled hair and he's smiling real weird.
He was sleazy though in the old days.
Yeah he was more more of a cat.
Well in general and in all of these because they all involve him hurting animals and a
lot involve him pulling a gun.
There's a couple of really good moments.
Or a rifle.
Yeah well there's a rifle but then he's the specifically in the dog napper he's just got
like a pistol.
He and Donald both.
They're cops.
Yeah.
And they say what does he say it's like like like hands up you viking.
Hands up you viper.
Yeah.
Calls him a viper.
These movies were more serious.
Yeah.
Then everything was more for adults.
Yeah in fact.
OK so plain crazy.
Yeah the Lindbergh.
Everyone had Lindbergh fever but I read a quote from of I work so insistent on clarifying.
Yes Lindbergh is the inspiration for the plane stuff.
But Mickey Mickey's vibe was done done in the way of Douglas Fairbank senior who he referred
to as the superhero of his day Douglas Fairbank senior very handsome looking very confident
yeah adventurer type.
He was like a swashbuckler swashbuckler.
Yeah.
The Indiana Jones lineage kind of runs through him.
Yes.
Yeah.
And Charles Lindbergh of course a noted racist noted anti-semites.
I don't think I knew that.
Oh yeah.
Very Mike Lindbergh racist.
I didn't know the very racist.
I could have seen older guys of a different time you would assume there'd be something
there.
But no I didn't know about racism.
If there is a if there is a person he didn't like of another race he'd say go soak yourself
yourself.
What's your boy.
Soak your head.
Fresh boy.
So Lindbergh.
Yeah.
You know plane.
I don't I don't need to say things about every movie but plane crazy.
It does.
I like that there's POV in it.
That's pretty nuts that an animated movie in the 20s has like you like you are the plane
and like avoiding obstacles and how the hell do you draw that like like 2D movies have
had to employ 3D technology today to figure out how to get right.
It was right.
He's like to emulate the POV of a plane path that early on.
Yeah.
It is insane.
Was the moose one with the shotgun.
Yeah.
Is that the one he's like shoots.
He thinks he shot Pluto.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
He weeps.
What if I kill.
He thinks he kills Pluto.
What if I die.
It's the same.
Yeah.
On the ground with like just like the line for his eyes.
They use a fake sexy moose to try and lure the moose.
Yeah.
Well the card yeah those cartoons are wild.
They let it play for a while.
The moment of Mickey.
Yeah right.
It's not like he goes oh no and then like he pops up.
Yeah.
What have I done.
It's really what have I.
It's heavy.
So dognails.
What have I done.
It's heavy.
So dognapper I think was probably the most entertaining of them I thought.
Yeah.
Where they're it's just it's an extended like gunfight.
There's so many like crazy.
It's like a long action sequence.
Mickey and Donald.
A car chase.
Yeah car chase.
Where they're firing.
Where Pete and Donald are firing rounds at each other.
Big thick guns and firing big thick bullets.
It's pretty nuts.
Pete with his peg leg and a couple of these shorts.
Oh yeah right.
Oh and that yeah I kind of thought maybe he only had a peg leg if it was a boat situation
like Steamboat Willie.
But I guess he always had a peg leg but not in a goofy movie.
No.
Correct.
Or Goof Troop.
No.
He was not an oddly in the 90s peg legged man.
Because today if you unfortunately lose a limb you have an option besides a big peg.
Unless that's what you want.
Is there a doctor in America that will prescribe you a giant peg as opposed to a prosthetic
leg or something else?
Stand by my guns.
It's just it's gonna be better for you.
Those things will break.
They'll shatter.
They'll.
Somebody will think it's a real limb and press on it too hard and it cracks down the middle.
But a big peg sturdy.
Tried and true.
An old peg.
Just stay away from termites.
You should be fine.
I've also said that before that I literally a month ago just realized that Pete is a cat.
Yes.
That I was stupid and thought he was a dog.
Yeah.
Pretty stupid.
Go drown yourself.
Soak no sex.
Why do I forget it every time?
We just said it.
Soak your ass fresh boy.
Soak your ass.
Soak my peg fresh boy.
Soak my peg.
Yeah.
I will do all of those things.
Soak my peg suck boy.
And then yeah they so dognapper is about Pete stealing Minnie's dog.
Yeah.
Fifi or something.
Stealing it yeah.
And then and then immediately the chase is on because making down our cops and then they
fire guns and then they corner Pete in a warehouse and then a big blade like a circular log cutting
blade comes to life and oh just owns Pete for three minutes.
It just follows him and follows him and like it shreds his butt a bunch of times.
It's nuts.
They're like John Woo movies or something like there's so much gunplay and violence
like and it's all like so well done.
Yeah artistic.
And there's it's long shots.
Yeah like the you follow Pete in the blade for right you know like half a football field.
Yeah a lot of yardage in these single these shots.
Children they were primarily for children.
Yeah I guess so.
So I guess the older generation was tougher I suppose.
I feel like you could not get I'm trying to think of an equivalent I mean I'm sure there's
like I guess the like Toy Story 3 when they're all going to die in an incinerator.
But most things you know you don't get Pete faced doom like that.
Yeah.
On the regular.
Years ago.
Mickey.
We thought he killed his best friend.
Yeah.
That'd be like the crux of a Toy Story today.
And it just casually happens in the middle of some Mickey cartoon.
Huh.
Oh God.
He turns the gun on himself.
There's no other way.
No one must know.
And he turns to the breaks the fourth wall.
Don't you tell anyone.
Or you're next.
Oh my God.
You're complicit.
These secrets die with me.
Come closer to the screen.
Swear to me.
Swear to me you won't tell anyone.
Cut your finger.
I want you to rub it on the screen.
I found an article that refers to Charles Lindbergh as one of Hitler's key American
friends.
Hey.
Boy.
That's not just casual anti-Semitism.
Had a campaign was part of a campaign gave us big speech about America first.
America should stay out of the war.
America first.
I've heard a recent president say that statement too.
Yes.
This came up in the election.
This happened in September of 1941 and then we were quickly drawn into the war.
Exactly.
You saw it.
If there was some racist pilot he'd be invited to the White House lickety split.
Oh my God.
He wouldn't even learn his name.
He'd just be there.
We should dress Jason up to look like Charles Lindbergh with an old time pilot's outfit.
And the big scarf.
And just say racist pilot gets doxed on Twitter and see how fast you get invited to the White
House.
Oh yeah.
And getting like a medal of freedom.
And get the fast food meal.
Get the fast food feast.
Yeah.
He orders for some reason you 200 Big Macs.
Just because he likes that little the image of it.
He's a hungry boy.
Racist pilot.
Racist Jason is one of the best pilots.
Sorry Sully you're number two now.
He's the finest pilot he invented piloting.
He's the first pilot and the best.
Racist pilot Jason says Hitler a-okay.
And like immediately you get a call from Stephen Miller.
We'd like to see you here.
You're a great American.
Santa Monica's favorite son.
But then yeah that's when you spring out and unleash a big circular saw to cut up Trump's
pear leg.
Yeah.
Bend the other saw so it bounces around.
It would make sense.
Chased around the entire White House gets destroyed.
It would make sense if you learned that Trump had two peg legs the way he walks.
You'd be like oh yeah I can see that.
He is a guy who would insist that peg legs are the best type of leg.
Yeah.
And he goes and like he goes and speaks to the military and tells you you got to get
the peg leg let me tell you.
Steady as well as that.
Three three peg leg appearances in these.
Steamboat Willie.
Oh yeah.
Traffic troubles.
Mickey picks him up in his taxi cab.
Of course Mickey a taxi driver before he was a sea captain.
Right.
We learned in the Duffy.
Can you imagine if like in the Duffy origin any of this nonsense happened.
The Duffy origin is just like Mickey goes out to sea and then maybe he gives him a nice
teddy bear.
Wasn't like.
He doesn't use a crane to pick Minnie up by her underwear and drop her music notes at
ukulele.
Yeah.
There's a lot of play of Minnie's underwear in these early.
With the weird little like the little like fluff on like on the leg part.
The frilly part.
Yes.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Strange.
Very strange.
And speaking of strange Mickey's polo team.
Yeah.
Featuring a cast of thousands.
The biggest stars of their time.
Right right right right.
Because Mickey and friends are playing a polo game against all the biggest celebrities
of the time.
Yes.
Like Looney versus everybody else.
Did they did this before like because one of like Looney Tunes this would happen all
the time too.
Where would you like Humphrey Bogart and it would be like celebs like Peter Laurie.
Peter Laurie.
Yes.
Peter Laurie for sure.
Yeah.
This has a very Looney Tunes vibe.
Maybe it's just the presence of those celebrities.
But yeah with the pop culture references something not very present in Disney cartoons
otherwise.
But then on top of it in a Mickey and Donald posing as their wives way they all of the
celebrities and Disney characters have horses who are like them.
That is very funny.
Yeah.
I mean Oliver Hardy on top of the thick horse.
The thick boy horse.
It's he's pretty cute that thick horse.
Yeah.
And then like Harpo Marx rides an ostrich that has big yellow Harpo hair.
Who else?
Stan Laurel and Charlie Chaplin.
And then the Mickey's team was Mickey Mouse Donald Duck Big Bad Wolf.
And then he's credited just as the goof.
Yeah.
Well he was his original name was movie stars versus Mickey Mausers.
Those are the teens.
So what Goofy's original name was like Dippy the goof.
Yes.
Dippy dog.
But yeah it was Dippy dog the first and then it was Dippy the goof.
Was it really Dippy the goof.
But there were like multiple.
I like Dippy the goof.
Maybe we should go back to that.
The referee was also Jack Holt another like western star adventurer like handsome guy.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
It's all these recognizable names.
Mickey Big Bad Wolf and Laurel and Hardy and this is Jack Holt.
And you knew who Jack Holt was.
No I looked I had to look that one up.
OK.
But you can I call it Clark Gable.
Clarabel makes out with Clark Gable in the dance.
WC Fields is there and seems irritated of course.
And then the three little pigs are sitting with Shirley Temple.
Oh which is very disturbing because it leads to her like acting like a little pig.
Yes they all showed their little bottoms.
Yeah.
Oh bad news.
Do not like that.
Although I kind of like that you know besides blowing the houses down you don't really get to see the Big Bad Wolf and his ability to do anything with his mega breath.
And it's kind of fun to think you just walk around and make whatever he wants happen but blowing really hard.
Yeah.
So it was fun to see it in a different context.
Like if somebody gave him the finger in traffic he could just go and then their car explodes.
Yeah kind of an antihero in this one.
Kind of helping the team win but still up to mischief.
Yeah yeah it's kind of fun that they're they're letting the villain play and let his villainy is OK since he's with us.
Yeah.
Pretty.
Imagine if you were somewhere sitting next to a big cow lady with a bell on her on her chest and she grabbed you and kissed you.
How disturbed you would be.
I'm worried about having this nightmare this evening.
Now the forcible kiss of the cow woman.
Which sounds like an old play.
Yeah.
That's an opera.
That's a classic.
So I.
1889.
I believe Dippy Dog's first appearance is in the book Dippy the Goof.
So he is Dippy the Goof but he is Dippy Dog in the book.
So I guess Dippy the Goof is what they're calling Dippy Dog and that's like a year before then they start calling him Goofy.
Yeah.
Also a lot of these a few of these shorts features Donald's voice is the same but he's long faced Donald.
Long faced Donald I'm really glad they got rid of.
He's unpleasant looking.
Yeah.
Extremely.
Definitely matches his mannerisms more.
And he also says you viper while holding a gun and then Pete like puts his big gun over.
He like makes Donald insert his hand into his gun.
I'm creeped out.
I'm like I'm going to need to like calm down after this episode.
I'm just describing disturbing tableaus.
Yeah.
They're not as disturbing if you just watch it.
No they're saying describing them out loud is really unsettling.
Pete Mickey jumps in a barrel Pete riddles it with bullets and you're like oh my god and then thankfully the barrel falls over and you find out there's a hole in the floor that Mickey has escaped from and comes out the other side.
Right.
But for a brief moment.
But you're expecting a corpse to roll out of the barrel that's got like bullet holes in it.
Yeah.
And then you've got Steamboat Willie historical piece of animation.
It's almost like weird to see it in motion so iconic is the still when I was watching it last night like I was like have I ever watched this?
Just him driving that boat is such you forget it's even from a movie.
And then the rest of it is less iconic such as at the end when he lands he's done a big barnyard symphony on a boat and then Pete shoves him back into the kitchen and he's next to something labeled potato bin and then he has to angrily peel potatoes and then a bird laughs at him.
So he clocks the bird with a huge potato and then smiles to us and that's the end of Steamboat Willie.
Again animal abuse.
It's nothing but animal abuse.
Doesn't go out with the same bang.
No.
Doesn't have the same resonance as that little whistle that they used before Disney animation.
Right.
Piloting and singing the little whistle.
Maybe they should change it up though and switch it to him just with the potatoes at the end or at the start of the animation.
Oh yeah switch it out him throwing a potato at a bird.
Yeah.
That's the start of all the movies now.
Go soak your head.
Start your fucking bird.
It all started with a mouse angrily peeling potatoes.
It's fun to see watching these back to back.
It's fun to see the evolution because the 30s I mean they're all have good beats and good moments and stuff but the 30s one you can tell they have it down.
Like this is like within five years or like this is what a Mickey Mouse cartoon is.
Sure.
There's a lot more experimentation a lot weirder stuff I think of the earlier ones.
Yeah and the earlier and then I was I think it's in that Walt Disney biography that you know that one the one that I've read one of the only books I've read in the last 10 years.
They were talking about Mickey and like early on here is like they're yeah they're testing stuff out and Mickey's personality is crazy.
And then they would like go on to like take parts of Mickey's personality and just give them to like Donald and other characters.
Yeah.
So Mickey Mickey ends up being like very boring later on because all they were throwing everything at Mickey and then like he was the corporate mascot all of a sudden they're like he can't be firing so many bullets at people.
He can't be like so mean and weird.
Did you read the one with the big yellow font on the cover or the one with Walt standing in the doorway.
Honestly I was gonna say both.
There's that I feel like he's standing in the doorway and there's yellow font.
Kind of.
It's closer to his headshot.
Yeah that's the one I read.
So that is the one that I think got more press and sold more but I think the other one is the one the family endorses.
There were two biographies that came out within a decade of each other.
Isn't that bad then?
Mike broke the family's wishes.
You're not a true fan.
I forget which but I mean I feel like they both got good reviews but they came out within five years of each other.
Yeah the biographies I read was not it was like was pretty honest about like all this stuff.
The communist stuff and.
Walt liked to throw potatoes at birds.
Yeah yeah and he loved Minnie's underwear.
Like that's all in there.
Yeah.
He often kissed cow women.
Yeah yeah.
Insatiable attraction to female cows.
Right.
The company did not like that.
We've mentioned Looney Tunes a couple of times.
I have to say I may have said this before I think Mickey's the better every man like the better cipher but Bugs is the better comedian.
Sure.
Bugs Bunny I think is funnier.
Sure yeah.
Mickey can be funny.
I feel like especially the newer ones have very funny moments.
Yeah I like in the newer ones that they've gone back to him like being like freaked out and weird and.
Nervous.
Bugs was very much like very in control and cool.
He is cool.
Bugs is cool but Mickey was not cool but I like that they're leaning into him being weird and bizarre and awkward now.
Well he has a meal he has like a different job every episode like he's always in over his head and that.
Leads me to.
Making sure it's a real fun.
Yeah.
Those are real good and that and the ride is based on those which is very good.
Seems like that'll be good.
Yeah that's exciting that they're going that way.
You know if we're talking about reverting things to the way that they used to be.
I have always been a big fan of when the cartoons start and you know whose cartoon it is because it's their giant face.
Oh yeah.
Staring at you.
Smiling.
Huge huge shading grin at you and there's a like a starburst behind them and I believe I think this was this should have been a fundamental of cinema that never changed.
And I think that today when you see a comedy.
It should have the star of the comedy looking at you in front of a big starburst.
If you go to see a Seth Rogen movie the Seth Rogen movie should start with Seth Rogen's big face.
If you're seeing even a like more tame like a Duplass Brothers.
Mark Duplass.
It should be Mark Duplass.
How else are you going to know who's in the movie?
Right.
Am I watching a Mark Duplass caper today?
Awkwafina's head coming at you.
Huge Awkwafina at the beginning of Crazy Rich Asians.
Big Gad.
Big old Josh Gad looking at you.
He's made for it.
Out of that I will say about Josh Gad.
He always has that Mickey smile naturally.
Well they're best friends.
Oh Josh and Mickey are best friends.
Oh no sorry it was Tony Hale and Mickey are best friends.
Yes he's best friends with Tony Hale.
Now in that special that we watched it was a Mickey's birthday special and before there's a funny little banter scene with Tony Hale it should be a big picture of Tony Hale smiling at you so you know it's a Tony Hale caper.
I agree.
And you want it one of all eight members of NCT 127.
Yes yeah yeah.
I probably got that wrong.
Please don't tell me.
Multiples in there totally fine.
Yeah.
Serious movies too.
Moonlight.
It's a big.
Okay across the board.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Even if it's a sad movie.
I want to know who's who's movie it is.
They used to do that in comic books too.
The little Marvel logo at the top with the price and everything used to have the characters in the little price box.
Yeah I like that.
Yeah.
That was good.
You would know who was on what team at any given time.
So when we have our TV show three faces.
Yeah.
All at once.
Yeah all at once I think.
Hi.
Yeah.
Hey.
Like getting squeezed unpleasantly.
Well the face I always think of that I don't like is of course you can't do that on television.
Oh yeah there's some big scary faces.
Some big scary faces there that turned me off of them but I'm willing to go back.
Are they kind of like were they kind of like not sepia toned but like that sort of colorized Ted Turner color like had that weird color look.
They were tinted strange.
Yeah.
And it was all Terry Gilliam rip off.
Right.
I didn't realize till way later seeing Monty Python.
Oh they just took.
Yes.
Just straight up.
Yeah.
I didn't realize it until like three years ago.
I was like oh yeah.
One thing you shouldn't be able to do on television.
Steal the work of other artists.
Yeah.
I wonder if they ever noticed.
Terry Gilliam ever watched you can't do that on television.
Was he ever up in Canada watching some.
Perhaps.
Watching TV shows with a budget of a hundred dollars.
It's weird that the sliming is something that maintains your solis from this very unpleasant.
Yeah.
I would run out of the room my mom said.
Like if it was on I would run.
Are you scared of Barth?
I was.
I don't even know what that is.
Barth was a dirty chef.
Oh I do know Barth.
Yes.
Yes I do know.
I hated him.
I think with a TH I think he was Barth.
Oh.
And that's the worst name too.
It's a really bad name.
This is around the time of or a few years before of What Would You Do.
No not What Would You Do.
I loved What Would You Do.
What was the one on the ranch.
The kids on the ranch.
Hey Dude.
That I think came in 89.
We're starting to hit 89 99 anniversaries.
Of course we talked about the anniversary is smooth recently.
But everything from those times starting to come up.
Sure.
So you want Hey Dude back.
I never liked Hey Dude either.
But I didn't give it a chance.
Aaron and I were just talking about this where that was the one her mom was like no shut this fucking show off.
I don't think she swore.
Right.
That was the you wonder like is fun going back to your childhood and thinking like my parents must have hated a lot of stuff.
And that was the one for her was and looking and like Hey Dude is good in my memory because in my memory it's like a gripping Riverdale character drama and secrets unfolding.
I'm sure if you watch it is the cheapest public access.
Yeah.
I think Salute Your Shorts was probably bought here.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
I didn't care for either of them from the title on.
Well sure.
Yeah.
I bet people I bet that show had a lot of attitude a lot of.
That does not honor the fly coach.
Right.
There's no fly coach for shorts.
Do you think they did they do shorts at half mast if a camper died or if there was a tragedy.
Or if the morbidly obese camper died.
Or what was bad that happened during the run.
So the original World Trade Center bombing did they make the shorts be at half mast.
You know what I don't know if they dealt with it.
We'll find out.
I'm not sure that the shorts were a daily event.
Yeah.
How long did it run Nixon died in like 93 or 94.
Did they honor its memory with the whole Nixon episode.
Hey I might not respect a lot of stuff but hey that guy President you got to give him respect man.
You respect the office.
Well we've talked about all the great media of time from salute your shorts to plain crazy.
What do you think if this place turns merch again are we upset.
I want to outrage.
I want them to gut it then and make it like cool.
A cool place to buy things.
That's what I want.
Like just look the racks the haphazard racks in front it looks shit.
So figure out a way to seamlessly integrate buying things into the Main Street cinema and I'm on board.
I'm I'm easy in this regard.
I think if it's like black and white Mickey if it's like throwback stuff for Steamboat Willie merch and they make it a little more tasteful.
They could get away with it.
Or yeah if they switch the cartoon if they rotate in like Mickey over the years could be fun.
Like that's interesting that they just had Mickey's like 90th birthday.
Right.
They should have just done all the Mickey over the years and had a bunch of shorts playing there.
For the 50th anniversary or maybe a different anniversary showed unearthed or opening day footage.
Oh yes.
Like not the special not the Ronald Reagan hosted special but like somebody's footage.
In color.
So being able to watch color Disneyland footage from 55.
That's a pretty good use of it.
I think they should do more stuff like that.
Yeah I would agree with that.
Fun stuff maybe once in a while you go in and there's a character hanging out.
Sure like you just have to watch a movie with.
Yeah with the Phantom.
The Phantom's in there sometimes and you can walk watch a movie with them.
I don't need any movie previews.
Those movie previews are always kind of a drag when they dedicate a screen to that.
Yeah.
I think I think changing stuff out making that an interesting place to go for some reason.
Making stuff like reasons you would go back a lot to like little fun stuff like you never really know what's going to be in there maybe or you never know.
Plung the archives a little more.
They do those Turner Classic movie Disney nights of like some shorts and some live action stuff some history stuff.
Some nature documentaries like.
Yeah.
It was totally randomized and you didn't know if they just plugged in all the shorts from 28 to 58 and you didn't know what.
Oh yeah that'd be great.
Yeah and like one of them was like a ride through of inner space or something.
Journey through inner space.
Like some weird old ride thing like stuff like that.
I feel like you could suck 50 people in.
World's fair footage.
100 people in an hour.
Legitimately how expensive could it be to make that for somebody to like curate.
Yeah.
I think every but a new thing every month you know the old Chuck E. Cheese pace.
Sure.
Yeah.
Just a little like and it was somebody would freak out over by us if we had that job.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Leonard Moulton already does it like as a hobby like he already does.
Throw Moulton in there.
Yeah.
Let him do it via satellite.
He just has to drag drag some clips into boxes or just send an email saying play this now.
Yeah right.
Legitimately good angle having him curate like Tarantino taking over the new Beverly.
Yes.
Moulton.
We said now Moulton's curating Main Street Cinema.
Sure.
Have him beam in every day at 5 p.m.
Just like Jimmy Fallon in a dream.
Yes.
Yeah.
I don't yeah making it sort of a respectable like Disney archive.
Sure.
Yeah and that would eat a couple folks.
Yeah.
I mean they could even like you they go even crazier and like have like legit like interesting
screening things in there and like have you make a reservation.
And we're doing that for a little while at Lincoln like annual pass holders.
I caught they showed a wonderful world of Disney about one of the parks.
It was like Thursdays for a few months.
Annual pass holders could go to the Lincoln Theater and they would show a wonderful world
at Disney from the 50s or 60s.
Sure.
That was neat.
Yeah.
Or my last suggestion will be show the Oscars in the Main Street Cinema like when we watched
it we watched the Oscars a couple years ago.
That was great.
In Lincoln.
In the Lincoln Theater.
Wow.
Yeah.
They did that.
Wow is right.
Yeah.
It's an annual pass thing.
That was the last time the Main Street Parade came back forever for the last time.
The Electro Parade.
Oh that's right.
Yeah.
God constantly.
They trick us every time.
Yeah do something interesting in there.
If they let the fan outrage if we can say that's what it was we should teach them.
It should be a teachable moment.
I hope people are going in there now.
If it's driving more people in there very good.
Fine.
Well you know that in the last couple weeks there's been a lot of people going and planning
and really determined like doggedly determined.
Okay I'm going to sit and I'm going to watch it.
They're angry while they do it.
They're like making a point.
This is great.
Honestly best thing in the park.
Yeah.
They make it pictures of them from a lot of dragging people in.
See make it look like it's full.
I mean that's true.
Periscoping it.
Yeah.
I can't believe we got in here the line outside is so crazy.
They're taking boarding groups just like Galaxy's Edge.
But two is empty.
Main Street cinema full.
But you know what if the Disney brass ever tries to take away this beloved attraction
again you know what we say to them.
Soak your head.
Fresh boy.
Hey JPEC.
JPEC.
Soak your head fresh boy.
You survived podcast the ride.
We should sell that on a shirt.
Yeah we should put that on a shirt.
Yeah.
I guess the right check I sat on T public for soak your head fresh boy shirts and if
you if we ever do anything on the show that you don't like hashtag soak your head fresh
boy on on Twitter or Instagram.
But please don't actually soak our heads if you see my god no.
Please no.
I would fold like a card table start crying.
And if you're a cow lady hands off that bell away from me.
All right.
Thanks for listening.