Five, four, three, two, one.
A lot of people have asked when will Podcast The Ride
do an episode about an escalator?
More specifically, multiple escalators.
Four escalators.
Four escalators to be specific.
And the day is finally here.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
I'm Mike Carlson.
Joining me is always Jason Sheridan.
Hi.
Scott Gairdner.
Yeah, and you know, I was thinking we could do the thing
where we like downplay and be like fake excited
about the mundane things.
But I'm really excited to talk about the Starway.
As soon as we, you know it's a good topic
when we have the idea in an episode
to quickly turn it around and do it.
We can't wait to do it.
And this is, it's a great day.
When is Space Mountain coming?
When is this one coming?
When is Guardians coming?
Slow down, killer, slow down.
Yeah, gentlemen.
We got a bank of escalators to talk about, friend.
Gentlemen, we met at Disneyland a couple,
like a week ago or so.
He goes, when are you gonna do Space Mountain?
And I was like, we're gonna get there.
We have a lot of important things.
And I didn't say specifically,
we were gonna talk about escalators before,
but that's, I knew in my head.
Let's just say there's an episode coming up
that involves the stars,
that involves slowly going up a hill
to find much excitement on the other side.
And that is the Starway.
The Starway.
Look folks, it's like golf.
It's a long game, you know?
We don't wanna burn off everything
in a one year, two year span.
Or sometimes we don't wanna burn off anything.
Yeah.
Should we wanna just sit and talk about escalators
for a while? Sure.
Yep, so here we are.
Universal Starway,
in case you don't know what we're talking about.
Because of the weird setup of Universal Studios,
this is a bizarre workaround to get people to an area
that's very, very, like how many stories below
Yes. the main park.
If you have not been out here,
Universal Studios Hollywood, of course,
a theme park built out of a movie studio,
which is an incorporated city within Los Angeles County
that happens to be built in and around a mountain.
We can call it a mountain, I think.
A large hill, a mountain.
Sure.
Yeah, I'll call it a mountain.
Give them the credit, yes.
Yeah.
Which, you know, inspires some fun and creativity.
I'm not sure that we would have the Jurassic Park ride
where they're not that slope to deal with.
Right. That seemed to me like
if we build a flume into the hill a little bit.
Yeah.
And use that double nature.
So we got that out of it.
And, but yeah, it's this bizarre
where a lot of the theme park stuff
was on the top of the hill and some was on the bottom
and they wanted to expand.
And where do we expand?
We don't want to expand on the bottom.
They set up this lower lot area,
but what are we gonna do?
How are we gonna get people down there?
Lots and lots of escalators.
Lots of escalators.
Recently, four rows of escalators,
for a long time, three rows of escalators.
The big Starway fans will know that it is now four.
They added a fourth bank.
Replacing stairs, is that what happened?
So there's a set of stairs on one side.
I think there was a second set of stairs
that they cleared out to add another bank of that,
which is four.
It takes four escalators each trip up and down.
You had to go up four escalators.
So this is gonna get confusing.
There's a bank of four across.
Left, right, up, and down.
A bank of four across.
But also, four down.
Four down, and those are also connected by little walkways.
Little landings.
Progressively less interesting landings.
I want to give credit.
Because that fourth set of escalators added
within the last two or three years,
Inside the Magic, a popular theme park news blog,
put up a video of it.
And I have to give them credit for this audio.
["Pirates of the Caribbean Theme Park"]
Opening a Baywatch or something.
The most exciting, dramatic public,
I can only assume public domain music,
covering a four to five minute video
of riding an escalator.
Drama foreboding, mystery, intrigue.
Those are the key words you'd search.
That is like a syndicated show from the 90s
that takes place on a beach, the start of it.
That's the start of the theme song.
It's Thunder in Paradise, it's Baywatch.
Just a drum, exotic drums.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Surf riders.
Baywatch nights.
Wave kickers.
Relic.
Well, mine was real.
Relic Hunter.
What's real?
I don't know about Relic Hunter.
Oh, Relic Hunter is Tia Carrera.
Oh man.
Carrera?
I think Carrera, yeah.
Yeah, it was like a syndicated where she was like
a Lara Croft style excavator of, I'm surprised.
This is a...
Don't know it.
Is Cleopatra 2120 on your radar?
That sounds familiar.
Cause that's in the same genre of like...
Never seen it.
Sexy badass woman does a cool thing.
That's more spy, I think.
That was a team of them.
It was a team.
Oh, it was VIP.
And then VIP, of course, for Panmaners.
Valerie Irons Protections, yeah.
What does it say in there?
Valerie Irons Protection.
Yeah, cause...
Her name is the VI?
Yeah, her name is, she runs a bodyguard protection agency.
Irons.
Yeah, we should do...
We'll do a Patreon on Relic Hunter and VIP eventually.
Oh, for sure.
Can do, we're slowly stretching the confines
where to me, if it's like theme parky
and it's silliness and campiness, I think it counts.
I'll guarantee to the listener,
we'll get to Relic Hunter and VIP before Space Mountain.
Yelled, for sure.
That is a guarantee to you, the listener.
Yes.
Some many topics we're afraid of.
Yeah.
Cause what do you do when it's gone?
That's not on your checklist.
Well, in fairness, Mike is afraid of those shows
because they are a little sexy.
A little sexy.
But they are sexy, not sexy, like too sexy
that they couldn't be on Sunday afternoon on WGN.
Yeah.
I've been doing a Baywatch dive recently
because I don't think I realized how sitcom bad it was.
Yeah, oh yeah.
I think I thought it was just, it was like stupid action
but it's a lot more like...
But it, but it didn't, didn't, didn't, didn't, like,
like, like, oh, CJ, it's very high jinky.
And so with that, like, from my recent Baywatch experience,
if you're not into the boobs or the butts,
around any corner is a crazy old man,
like, who lives in a trash can and calls himself fella.
Or like, you know, guest stars of the past,
like, Connie Stevens or who played the talk show.
I mean, I just found one with Jay Leno.
Didn't you post one with Geraldo?
Yes, Geraldo.
Yeah, yeah, credits to Brennan Campbell who alerted me.
If you're looking for celebrities on Baywatch,
there's one where, with Geraldo, and does he play Geraldo?
No, he plays an unrelated nerd character.
That's how Brennan conveyed it to me.
I could not have watched this episode quicker.
And he's playing a nerd, but he's clearly very tan
and very buff.
So you, like, no dorky shirt is going to hide that.
And it's a lot of to hassle off, like,
but I can never be like you.
I don't have what you have.
But he's like, I think maybe more in shape than.
I'm sure he is, because as we've said on the Little Mermaid
episode, he's as jacked as King Triton is now.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, he came up.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because he's so chiseled and he's got that sloping crotch
thing.
The D'Angelo video crotch.
Yeah.
What do you call that?
What actual part is that, like, V?
Your pelvic?
Yeah, I guess.
If you got a jacked pelvis, like Batman suit.
I just call it dinner.
Right?
What?
Right, fellas?
Yuck.
Oh my god.
Get me a bib and a fork and knife.
Gee whiz.
It's the most outrageous thing anyone's ever said on the show.
No, it doesn't even make sense.
Eat me some pilv tonight.
It makes sense to me.
It's highly sexual in nature.
It's a come on, in fact, to the old D'Angelo.
Your usual bow tie is spinning and your dickie has curled up
and slapped you in the face.
Like when Big Bird dresses up.
That's what I'm wearing.
I have to say, the world of Cleopatra 2020 and Relic
Hunter and all that, all of those TV sci-fi sets are often,
these sets and effects are often just awful.
And it kind of nails in the chalkboard to me.
But if I could walk through that set in a theme park,
I'd be like, oh, this is pretty good.
I like this.
Oh, that's a good point.
Sure, sure, sure.
Your standards are different.
Yeah, standards are different.
Yeah, we loved every Knott's Maze.
Like, wow, this is like the most, this is the best art design
I've ever.
Yeah, short term seasonal attraction.
Great.
12 season Highlander TV show.
I don't know.
Yeah, the graphics on UPN's Deadly Games,
my favorite of all these short lived shows.
That's the one, of course, where Christopher Lloyd plays
Sebastian Jackal.
And they go into a computer and it's like the net.
I think they call it the net or whatever.
Like the web maybe.
Brent Spiner plays a very Joker-ish villain.
And they speed him up and it's good.
Look it up.
Speed him up?
Yeah, it's like he's doing something quickly.
I mean, they did that to honestly,
they did that to him on Star Trek when he was doing something
his data because he could type very fast.
That's something he could do as an Android.
But on Deadly Games, he's going through like fucking something
up in a lab or something and they keep speeding it up
to make him seem like scary or outrageous or like,
I don't know, or like superhuman.
Like he's able to dash from place to place like a ghost.
Yeah, yeah.
But yeah, look up Deadly Games, another Patreon
that I will guarantee before Space Mountain.
Yeah.
We'll do the character Sebastian Jackal.
He gets the character episode before Space Mountain.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
But for now, hey, let's live in the now
in our dream episode we're currently doing, The Star Way.
Now, I mean, it is unique.
No, I can't think of another theme park
that has a giant system of escalators
to transition from one part of the park to the other.
Is there any other multi-tiered theme park
that exists on two different planes?
Well, there is a Lionsgate vertical theme park
opening in Asia, but we don't know.
They haven't revealed all of that yet.
Sure.
We don't quite know what that looks like.
Disney Quest is multiple floors.
Yeah, Disney Quest is multiple floors,
but it's still inside.
But do you get to ride a mall,
but essentially a mall escalator with a very slight covering?
I can't think of many other escalators
that have to withstand rainfall.
Yeah, that's a good question.
Oh, that's true, yeah.
I have some escalator facts.
Oh, great.
Did you also get the facts from
Probably the same thing you did.
Keepitupdavid.wordpress.com?
No, I didn't.
Oh, wow.
I went to somebody's website that was about
staying fit at theme parks,
and it seems like this guy lost like 100 pounds
and uses theme parks for fitness a lot.
And it is true that if you were to go up and down
the starway a couple times, that's a major workout.
The stairs on the side of the starway.
You would have to do the, yes, let's be clear.
Yeah, the remaining stairwell is what you would have to do.
Quarter mile long though, this is a quarter mile long.
That's kind of, that many stairs are pretty brutal.
I've done it, I did it once.
I don't remember when, but I did do the stairs up once
and it was crazy.
It's, yeah, it's bad.
Especially in the summer, don't do it in the summer.
Down is okay.
Oh yeah, down is fine.
I think I've done it down, yeah.
Yeah, down, down, historically much easier than up
when it comes to stairs.
I'm saying folks, folks, you heard it.
Yeah.
Breaking news.
But your facts.
Oh yeah, my dry facts.
There are an estimated 700,000 elevators
and 35,000 escalators in America.
Oh, these are not starway facts.
No, no, these are just general escalator facts.
I didn't get them from keepitupdated.com.
No, no, no, keep it updated.
This is from eesf.org, which I assume is some sort
of like government board that keeps track
of escalators in America.
Over 245 million riders take an escalator daily.
About 210 billion riders travel on elevators
or escalators each year in North America.
So there you go.
Wow.
People use it a lot.
Keep it up escalators.
Yeah, escalators though, not as,
it seems like they're not as widely used as elevators.
Well, hang in there.
Yeah.
Preferable.
I enjoy an escalator.
You like an escalator better?
I like an escalator better.
Less likely to get stuck in.
Although I've never gotten stuck in an elevator, thankfully.
Well, I would say that's true,
but if there's an accident sometimes on an escalator,
like we'll get to, I think here, it could be real bad.
It can be horrific.
Yeah.
It's true.
There's a bunch of people just sliding down
and landing on top of each other.
It's a horrible thing.
Yeah.
Hopefully it just stops and then it's fine.
It just turns into stairs.
Sure.
I just got to go to, I just rode on perhaps
the most crucial escalator in all of history,
the Trump Tower escalator where at the bottom,
Trump officially announced his candidacy
and told everyone that they aren't sending their best.
And what I didn't know was that at the very end
of that escalator is a swirly handwritten sign
that says Trump's old fashioned ice cream.
They try to convey as if he invented an ice cream formula.
He perfected a good buttery,
the way it's supposed to be made.
There's no picture of him with an old ice cream scoopers,
like a little paper crown.
No, there's not a cartoon version of him.
There's not a big head caricature bobble head guy,
which I wonder if maybe that was presented
in the initial design and he was like, no,
it makes me look like a fool.
Burn this.
That pushed his sense of humor.
A caricature is too comical for Trump to like it.
Yeah, I think he would want him to be
a young and sexy character
that had nothing to do with ice cream.
Like a hot 20 year old version of Trump.
In a suit.
That's what he would want.
Yeah, right, in a suit and that would be on the wall
of the Trump's old fashioned ice cream.
Yeah.
It doesn't make sense.
He's standing nowhere near an ice cream of any kind.
Yeah.
Well.
No napkins, that shows weakness.
Absolutely no napkins.
The other Trump ice cream is his Olly G segment.
Oh, oh, that's right.
Where he pitches a.
His Olly G pitches him ice cream gloves.
And Trump is very proud later.
He claims he knew it was a fake thing.
I mean, he does leave during it, but.
Yeah, I guess you gotta give him credit for that,
that he does.
But he's a performer.
He knows a ruse when he sees one.
Right.
He's very keen to the entertainment business.
So yeah.
But.
So was that the most exciting escalator ride you ever had?
I think so, knowing that was the spot,
and I went down it and did not realize
till I turned and looked back, oh my God, that is it.
I didn't know that I had just written it.
Is there a more important escalator in history?
Perhaps the Starway?
Yeah, I would, I can't think.
Yeah, I think that's probably at this point,
not for a good reason, but yeah, historically.
It's really.
No other world leader.
It wouldn't have been possible for Genghis Khan
to announce anything via escalator ride.
And it's such a perfect, that whole video of him
coming down the escalator to announce
is just the perfect encapsulation, like the whole thing.
It's just so perfect.
It's terrible looking.
He's coming in like it's a mall, right?
It's like, yeah, you landed in a mall.
It's like Trump's bar, Trump's pizza,
and then right at the foot of the escalator,
Trump's ice cream.
So just know if you're thinking about that moment
that he was staring at a sign that said Trump's ice cream.
Sully to mall food court.
Like a twisted version of a thing we all know and love.
A mall with escalators.
With like marble and 80s fonts.
It's a thing I would absolutely love were it not for.
Anywhere.
The underpinnings of it.
Yeah, it's a shame.
But luckily, I don't know if people know this,
but if you go across, if you look across the street
at Tum Tower, there's a lot of people
giving the tower the finger.
Oh, they're doing it.
Right, right, right.
We're gonna wear it down one finger at a time.
And of course, a nice transition to the starway
is someone related to Trump as well.
Oh, good point, yes.
Is Billy Bush, who does a lot of the,
well, all of the narration.
Does he still?
I don't believe.
He's a lot more minions now.
He was replaced by minion noises.
But for many years.
Is it just pure minion noises?
There's safety warnings and music
and a generic theme park announcer,
and I feel like a lot of banana.
Really?
I didn't know that part of it.
I've heard that, but I don't know
that that's all over the place.
I mean, they play Happy.
That's the memory I have now of it in the last few years
is that Happy is constantly playing on the starway.
Happy is constantly playing.
Happy is Universal's theme song.
It's there when you wish upon a star.
Yes.
Billy Bush, yeah, took over.
And the Access Hollywood, was it just him?
The Access Hollywood Access.
I don't remember if Nancy O'Dell was in there.
It was never Pat O'Brien.
Never Pat O'Brien.
Yeah, they didn't have ownership of it
until the Billy Bush era.
Of course, at the end of the Universal tour
for a long time, your reward at the end
was to take a picture with a wooden Billy Bush in Nancy O'Dell.
So they had a big presence in the park around this time.
Starting in 2006, 2006 was when that went in.
I have a confession to make.
In high school, there was a stretch of time
where I watched Access Hollywood a few times a week.
Really?
The Daily Show came on at seven.
The Daily Show re-air from the night before,
which I would usually go to bed around that time.
I watched the Daily Show re-air
and then flip over to Access Hollywood.
It was on?
It was on and I liked to entertain,
I liked knowing about movies coming out
and TV coming out and that.
Was there not a 730 Seinfeld or Simpsons?
I feel like on various channels at various times,
there's reliably 730 is a slot I associate
with one of those shows.
Our Simpsons was at 630.
Sometimes there was a Seinfeld,
but they'd move it around a lot.
But I know what you mean.
Was Entertainment Weekly opposite?
Because where I'm from,
Access Hollywood and Entertainment Weekly
on at the same time.
Entertainment Weekly?
Entertainment Tonight.
Oh, Scott, I'm losing my mind.
Yeah, I think on at the same time.
I think Access Hollywood aired on NBC
and I think I just usually would turn on NBC as default.
Extra had their own space carved out.
Extra's not part of this horrible game.
Yeah, I guess.
This bloodthirsty, this blood sport.
Yeah, Billy Bush.
I remember not having good feelings about Billy Bush
even before everything.
Just because I tend to have a weird visceral reaction
like this smarmy guy who doesn't really do much of anything
and has no discernible talents
and just kinda talks and has good composure.
I is not a type of person.
I am like, hooray, I'm glad they're on television.
But what's the difference?
And I agree with what you're saying
and I'm thinking out loud.
Is the difference with him and Regis
that Regis is just old and we like Regis?
Yeah, maybe I just inherently try.
I don't know, I think the past versions of these people
were stranger and funnier.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Even Dick Clark is always pointed to as the original that
but I find he seems a little more sincere
and is associated with picking good music
to present to America.
But it's also screwed many people out of royalties
and there's a whole controversy surrounding him.
Well and as Michael Moore conveyed
and I forget which one in Bowling for Columbine,
all the shootings are his fault.
Oh right.
And that weird part where like,
yeah, you did this sir as he's getting in a van
and Dick Clark probably doesn't even know
what he's talking about.
Right.
So all the shootings are on Dick Clark's hands.
I hate to keep pitching Patreon episodes
but then Dick Clark had a restaurant chain as well.
Uh-huh.
And there was one in Schomburg.
Oh.
Also in Schomburg.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Why was it so, is it just like middle of the country
just makes it chain restaurant?
Yeah, I mean it's Woodfield I think specifically.
Yeah.
Because this was in the mall next,
the outdoor mall next to Woodfield.
Okay.
Did you have a Cheeburger Cheeburger?
That was a chain based on the SNL.
Cheeburger?
Cheeburger Cheeburger.
But wasn't it just Cheeseburger?
No, they must've spelled it.
Yeah, they spelled it in a weird way.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I didn't even know that was the.
CHEE.
I know what you're talking about
but I don't think we have one near in the suburbs.
I remember one of their things was that on the table
there was a box of trivial pursuit cards at every table
so you could pass the time while you waited for your food.
Wow.
And then there was some eight by tens of SNL cast members.
Acroid.
Of course.
Those Greek guys who barely spoke English
would not be able to play trivial pursuit
and probably don't have a working knowledge
of American pop culture.
Probably not.
Although I don't know that Billy Bush
had much working knowledge of American pop culture too.
Probably just read whatever is it.
Seems like a husk of a man.
Yeah, yeah.
Member of the Bush family as well.
So that got that going against him.
I think George W. Bush's cousin, is that right?
Something like that.
Or nephew, maybe?
It was like an optical illusion looking at that man
and it would bug you out seeing the Bush in him.
Yeah, right, cause it was there.
Him and the number of times on the Starway
they would play the Access Hollywood sting,
it would just drive me crazy.
I mean it's a long, seven or eight minutes on an escalator
does feel long.
Is that how long the whole thing takes?
I believe seven to eight minutes depending on crowds.
It's pretty fast to get you that far down.
I would have told you it takes you 20 minutes.
If you asked me yesterday, I would have said,
oh like 20 minutes before I looked into it.
It feels long.
So I was gonna say, to me the Starway
is a pretty big barrier to entry for me
even getting down to the lower lot.
I've had an annual pass and during the entire City Walk
saga where I had a pass and we were up there all the time,
how many times did I go to the lower lot?
Maybe once, maybe not at all.
Wow.
Because you got Harry Potter,
you got the best thing in the park on the upper level.
I don't like Transformers that much.
I don't, you know, now I'm more of a launch queen
than I was then but I was not doing Mummy.
Jurassic Park is a no for me.
So that hurts it all too.
I guess, all right, if you look at it from a different angle,
some of the best rides are on the lower lot
but it's ones that I avoid.
But also just the inconvenience of,
I also live not that far from the studio
so it always feels crazy to me that like,
taking the Starway feels like I took the longest,
secludedest route back to my house.
Right.
When Homer perks in the furthest end
of the nuclear plant lot
and then it's butting up against his backyard.
Right.
That's how going all the way up
and all the way down feels to me.
I'll give a tip though,
if anyone is visiting and needs to not,
like do all of Universal in a day
and don't wanna feel rushed,
if you get there when the park opens,
go straight to the lower lot,
you can do all three of those rides in an hour or less.
And then you have a lot of multiple times too.
Multiple times probably.
Now this may change when Jurassic World opens,
hopefully this year.
But yeah, you can,
most people immediately go to what they see on the upper lot
or immediately go to Harry Potter or the tram tour.
I feel like a lot of people go right to the tram tour.
Don't do that.
Sure, don't need to.
Yeah.
And then Nintendo is going here too.
So that's a certain point.
And there will be so many people on this starway
and it will break, it will buckle.
The whole thing will fall off the side.
Yes, the entire starway is going down day one
of Nintendo, I'll feel horrible if I predicted it.
And I hope that's not right.
Like the blocks in Mario Brothers level that like fall
if you stand on them too long.
Oh yeah.
The starway will keep moving.
Keep moving, keep moving.
I'll say that, I mean, they need to that lower lot.
There's some weird, like there's restaurants down there
that are sometimes open, sometimes never open.
There is an ice cream stand down there where like we got,
look, we brought the crazy ice cream from Florida,
big milkshakes and stuff that seems to close much earlier
than the rest of the park.
Oh, that's, cause that's happened.
This is the experience we had, is that right?
Well we had that, I think I had it one time before,
but it's a weird holdover of universal,
we ran down there though.
It was busy days.
We ran down there right before close.
And I think you had your eye on that ice cream
and it was closed.
Well we blitzed through, I mean,
we did at least transformers.
We wanted to do something else.
Yeah, but I was like, oh, maybe I'll get an ice cream
down there and it closed.
Nope.
They have all, they do have the fun transformers,
like for greeting or the characters greeting people
and goofing on people too.
So that's cool.
What I remember about the lower lot is that it used to have
a big billboard for coach on the outside of a soundstage.
And a lot of coach, on the tour,
I like to talk about coach as much as possible.
That was a thing if I was bored was just say that coach
filmed at every single spot.
And there was some clip that I played over where I did it
as coach, it was not coach.
It was a clip of Al Roker or something.
And I'd dub it over.
Hey folks, it's me coach boy.
A lot of fun times filming coach.
27 seasons, I think it was.
Which coach long off the air when you were doing the tour.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Yes, many decades.
But did it come back?
No, they talked about it, but it didn't come to pass.
I was trying to remember, like,
did I see a coach reboot?
It was like NBC or whatever, was it NBC or ABC?
NBC.
They announced it.
They announced it, yeah, yeah.
And it just didn't happen.
And then it didn't happen.
For some reason.
And someone remembered that nobody likes coach.
Right.
Despite it being on TV for a year, a decade.
Was it, or did it switch at one point in time?
It switched networks, yeah.
Okay, that's why.
Because I was just rewatching
the Dana Carvey Show documentary
and the final episode was yanked from its slot
and replaced with a special coach
that I think Troy Aikman was in or something.
Oh, I believe that.
Coach also feels like it started in 1980
and ended in 1998.
Yeah, absolutely.
It started like it bridged two decades.
Many presidents.
I don't even wanna look at it.
Presidents, world events.
I will, but I don't want to.
I don't actually wanna know.
I think that's a nine season.
I feel like that happens more and more nowadays.
Shows switching networks with all the digital outlets
and streaming outlets.
I mean, one day at a time just saved by CBS.
They're putting it on pop TV
because they can't put it on CBS All Access for a while
due to non-compete issues of Netflix shows.
It is a big deal that Netflix is letting the show continue
because of the draconian contracts saying
you cannot move this to another streaming service.
Putting a show on pop TV is saying
we're gonna air the show exclusively in a hole.
We're throwing the show in good news.
It's on pit.
Is that a channel?
No, we're throwing the show into a pit.
But I don't know that CBS All Access is that better.
It may just be there for a couple years
until they can get it to CBS All Access.
Which more people. So pop TV is a safe house.
Yeah, essentially.
We gotta protect the show.
But I just saw Netflix saved Designated Survivor
for third season.
Netflix picked up. Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
Designated Survivor ran two seasons on ABC.
This is Kiefer Sutherland is the cabinet member
who survives a bombing.
He is the Designated Survivor,
the head of housing and urban development
becomes the president due to the line of succession.
Netflix has picked it up for a third season.
These are all-
Less fun King Ralph.
Yeah.
He doesn't do any, no boogie woogie piano
in that line of succession.
But equally idealistic.
But can he stay idealistic in this new position?
These are all just like shell games
that these corporations are playing
where it's like if you move money around here
and get another one of our channels
to take the show, we can then move it into syndication,
which will then give us another 100,
it's all just math.
It's not, some of these things are not based on
even if people like it.
So like coach-
Not like when things were-
Coach was pure.
Yes, yeah.
The demand from the public was so great.
Yeah.
And Deadly Game was pure.
They just wanted to make a great show
and tell a great story about Sebastian Jackle.
Yeah.
This wasn't about finding some weird secret money
in Finland or whatever.
No, this was yes, for the love of the game.
The tale of Jackle.
When Deadly Game got canceled, heaven got another angel.
Can we, when we finally figure out
how to purchase Marvel McFay,
can we also purchase the IP from Deadly Games
so we can own Sebastian Jackle
and license him out in the theme parks?
I think we can.
I think so.
We're slowly amassing,
we're gonna have the best miscellany lineup
of properties outside of Six Flags.
Right.
Because yeah, we'll have Marvel McFay,
what else have we talked about getting, owning?
Oh, the Berry Tales?
We can't just like do a drawing of something we like.
We have to own the-
Yeah, we have to figure-
Character in the song.
I've looked into the Marvel McFay IP.
It's very confusing.
And I think it's just blanket owned by,
well, not Warner Brothers anymore
because they sold Six Flags,
but I think it's just,
it's lumped into all those Six Flags.
Yeah, it's probably in a Warner Brothers vault somewhere.
Yeah, we just gotta get a lawyer-
A fire prone Warner Brothers vault.
Oh no.
We have to find a lawyer
that will look through the documents and see,
and then try to convince someone to negotiate with us.
I mean, do we think Travis Barker has pitched on it?
Was he too young?
I mean, Travis Barker, who did the Astroworld album,
did he ever experience Marvel McFay?
From Blink-182?
Travis Scott, sorry.
Yeah, what?
Travis Scott.
Travis Barker.
I was like, oh fuck, do I not know
there's another Travis Barker?
I am an old, old man.
I love it.
You've been right so many times with modern references.
Now you lose, Jason, I win.
Yeah.
Thrilled.
I mean, whatever makes you happy, Michael.
I don't quite understand the angle on this victory,
but I'll give it to you.
Jason's face turning 8% red, slightly.
Yeah, yeah.
That's your victory.
Travis Scott's Astroworld.
It's possible, yeah, we could look into that.
There were no pictures though of him
with Marvel on stage or anything.
No.
I think he was probably too young.
I think they had shuttered.
I think anyone is too young unless they were like 54.
Wasn't Marvel McFay a long time ago?
Yeah.
Well, yeah, oh yeah.
Maybe like an 80 or whatever.
Did I answer the coach question?
No.
Eight seasons of coach.
Wow.
One less than Seinfeld.
That's true, yeah.
But it does feel like it was there forever.
Mm-hmm.
Wow.
So.
But not, I don't believe included in the medley
of theme songs that you're likely to hear
while you're on the sky, the starway.
Starway.
Starway, not Skyway.
That's a topic we're too scared to cover as well.
Oh yeah.
Starway is now.
So like in both the Billy Bush X's Hollywood era
and the other era, before Billy Bush,
it was a generic radio station
that played exclusively on the starway called KUSH,
which spell that out.
We love it.
What do you get?
One of our favorite, oh it does.
Yeah man.
Kush baby.
Kush radio.
Was that on purpose?
That's a body joke.
I know Universal's the body of the park.
No, I think it didn't occur to them.
Yeah, I don't think they knew.
Yeah, that was a total boardroom.
I think just a lot of Los Angeles stations
used to be K blank, is that correct?
Yeah, yeah, that's K rock.
Well and City Walk had, it was like seven burger,
world's KWB, what was it?
Oh yeah.
Greatest Burgers, KWGB.
Yes, the radio station themed burger restaurant.
I mean folks, we love our fake radio stations,
the one from Twister.
The one from Rockin' Space Mountain?
The one from Rockin' Space Mountain.
Is it like K Star radio?
I don't remember.
Isn't it like Intergalactic radio or something?
Yeah.
And that's on the, what's the platform?
Or am I thinking of a different thing from Tomorrowland?
Oh yes, so I think the radio station gimmick
was used a couple ways in Tomorrowland.
I don't know, we have to go back.
And you can listen in on radio signals today
in Star Wars Galaxy Z.
Yeah, that's true.
And one of them is that you're like picking up music.
You can hear Rex and what's playing in the Cantina
somewhere else in Galaxy Z.
Yes, yeah, yeah, I've heard that.
Why or where?
And then I was in the bathroom
on one of the many Batuu visits.
Oh yeah, that's radio.
And there's a radio and it's like,
there was just somebody was live narrating
some sort of Intergalactic chess game between aliens.
That's fun.
And it was like he wipes his tentacle,
like he wipes his brow with his tentacle.
Like it's a very dry, like jokey alien chess game
they're narrating.
And then also Space Mountain had like a TV station.
That's a whole other theme park exclusive radio stations
and TV stations.
That's a whole excuse for an episode.
Yeah, that's true.
That may be even a Final Four.
Yeah, that's a pretty good one I think.
Yeah.
Best fake theme park radio station or TV station.
Will Kush beat W Chess radio in Batuu?
My chess thing was funny.
Yeah.
It's gonna be hard.
Yeah, yeah.
This, I keep jumping all around here,
but there's a,
did anyone ever catch the other weed reference
on the starway?
No.
During Horror Nights?
Uh-oh.
Horror Nights, they have a whole different narration.
Oh my.
And it's just an aggressive guy like doing this.
Yes.
And then he's like, before he tells everyone the rules,
he goes, shut the hell up.
And then I swear he goes,
and there's no smoking on the starway.
That includes weed.
And I was like, weed?
That's not even.
My bow tie started spinning.
I was spinning.
I've never heard that in a theme park before.
Whoa.
That's history.
That includes weed.
This narration was like the last thing.
And they're like, oh fuck, this is doing half an hour.
Don't write it.
Can you write it with a hammer?
If you have a hammer, everything looks like a nail.
Like just, don't couch it in jokes or,
just say what we talked about.
We'll do it live.
Weed, yeah, we'll do it live.
Don't smoke weed, idiots.
It is all, I don't know if they officially called it this,
but one of the YouTube videos referred
to the Halloween specific starway as Evil Starway.
No.
I don't think Universal actually called it that,
but I could be wrong.
But a lot of it is just,
there is no smoking on the starway.
Yeah.
Please don't sit on the stairs as you descent.
The one-
It's all like friendly info.
Right.
It's red mean.
Mine, the one I was watching,
the video I was watching, it goes,
he's like, don't sit down on the starway
or it'll chew your ass up.
We might've watched it.
Maybe the one I watched is from a year
where they realized they needed to like change the copy.
Cause he also goes like, he goes like,
don't stare straight ahead while you're on the starway.
Don't look to the right and stare at that hot girl
on the opposite escalator.
Don't try to get her phone number
cause you'll look like an idiot.
I get the whole-
What?
He's roasting everybody.
You'll be too scared to do it, you will.
You're gonna pee your pants before you even get a word out.
After the sun goes down, the starway becomes the neg way.
We're negging you all the way to the bottom of the hill.
You've paid a piece of shit.
Your imposter syndrome is correct.
You are a fraud.
Starway is the alpha of this group.
He refers to himself as starway.
Your girlfriends with starway now.
Starway.
You never have a size complex
when you're at a quarter mile long.
Kiss me now on the stairs.
Kiss me, come on, do it.
Get on your knees. Do it for your friends.
I'm giving you special permission
to sit on the stairs for once.
You can kiss him.
Give it a lick.
Do get your tongue stuck in the stairs.
See if anybody cares.
Vice's lid blowing expose
on the universal Hollywood Horror Nights starway.
Okay, so we can't have the little fun
on the escalators anymore, huh?
Thanks a lot, Vice.
I'm the Facebook group of like save evil starway.
Wasn't it better when evil starway was around?
I wrote for evil starway from 2012 to 2018.
I did as well.
Yes, me too.
They had like a 13 person writing staff for some reason.
Yeah, that was, I also, evil starway was in no other way
like an evil escalator.
They didn't do like scary lighting or anything.
No.
But you do pass by the side of the Jurassic Park building.
And I don't know if this was in reference
to a maze or something, or if it was just its own thing.
But in the video I watched, it pans over to the side
and there's a light spinning around and around
and it's like filtered to spell out a word
and it says skulls with a Z.
Skulls, skulls.
Is that a brand of some kind?
I'm not sure, was it a tie in?
You guys weren't such pussies, you would know.
Skulls.
It's my gang.
The skulls, well what's that?
The skulls way, take the skulls way to the lower lot.
The lower lot is still called the lower lot.
Not everything here is evil, but a lot of it is.
We need to keep some stuff the same
for the fire department.
It's a zoning issue more than anything.
Well, skulls way.
Skulls way, yeah.
You were starting to talk about KUSH, the radio station.
KUSH, and it's not what you think Kush radio might play.
They don't play any string cheese incident, unfortunately.
They, you have a host on, before it was Billy Bush,
there was a guy who introduces himself as Clip Jockey Brad.
So they invented a new type, there's disc jockey
and there's video jockey and there's clip jockey.
He kind of sets up, all right, we're gonna do a little,
here's a little Spielberg medley coming at ya.
They present it like he's kicking off a song
and then it's just a big mix of Spielberg scores
and falling home into clever girl.
So that's fun.
They also take fake callers.
They do trivia games and they ask for who,
like the, wait, we're naming title stars director.
They'll play the Back to the Future score
and then somebody calls a really overacting,
hi, my name's Lisa.
I'm a mom and my kids love that movie.
Let me see, Back to the Future, Michael J. Fox,
Christopher Lloyd, famously also Sebastian Jackal
and Roberts and Ekas.
And she wins something, right?
She wins a ride on the Starway
and then she seems really put out.
She seems really like, oh, okay, thanks.
Is that what it is really?
Yeah, that's what happens.
Oh, that's kind of funny.
Yeah, so.
Only valid for Starway, not Skullsway.
Yeah, Starway, yeah, you cannot.
There's also like a.
Oh, come on, let Lisa ride me.
Oh, God.
Come get your prize, Lisa.
Who can escalate her up?
Did you hear the portion of that
that was like a Valley girl calling?
I did not know.
She called, it's like, I think it's this movie
and then the DJ is like, Brad is an asshole.
He's like, oh, like, yeah, I think it is like that.
And it's like, what is this condescending Valley girl bit?
Like.
Geez.
Whatever.
Brad, whatever you make on a clip jockey salary
does not make you some upper tier elite citizen, okay?
Yeah.
You're here in the muck with us, clip jockey Brad.
Don't you forget it.
What an asshole.
Boy, I guess everyone on all the narrate
and then Billy Bush who seemed benign enough.
Right.
We didn't know, you know, he had already participated
in the famous tape, you know, as he recorded this.
Oh yeah, that's true.
In the back of his mind, he knew.
He knew it was coming for him.
Do you think it occurred to him as anything?
Probably not, cause nobody would have thought
he was gonna run for president.
No, and there's probably like a hundred other incidents
similar to that with other celebrities.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That like no one cares about.
Yeah, yeah, there were nobody's seeking the tape.
Right.
Yeah, so nobody cares about the Trump one either.
Yeah, that's true.
I do remember going, oh, this will probably sink him.
Nope.
No one cared.
Yeah, I was on my way to meet you, I think at a desert trip.
Oh, that is the desert trip weekend.
Yeah, yeah.
I get to hang out with Mike and see some good bands
and we can all just celebrate knowing
that the Trump campaign is dead.
It's over cause this came out, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh man, it's gonna be sick.
Most of it was sick.
It was not that bad.
The, what else?
You get a bunch of, hey, you get some retro theme songs.
You get a little bit of Rockford Files and Magnum PI.
And what are both of those?
Mike Post.
Yep.
Two of the great Mike Post themes.
Rockford Files is a funky one.
That one's great.
Yeah.
Yeah, PI, obviously classic.
Also Mike Post, who we realized was involved in Halyx.
I think we can tease some Halyx stuff coming.
Yes.
Coming down the pipe.
And here's confusingly not necessarily from us.
No.
No, yeah.
Let your imagination run wild.
Yeah.
But Halyx is coming back in a big way.
Whatever your guess is, it's not that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, and there's also, and then they do like every type
of like little radio station format.
Like there's a little bit of weather.
Clip Jockey Brad predicts 100% chance of some heavy fun.
I like that.
That's good.
Sure.
He also does, there's also other trivia where he lists
like, now who's the actor who played Frankenstein?
Was it Lon Chaney?
Was it Boris Karloff?
And the answer is none of the above.
Frankenstein is the, it's Frankenstein's monster,
not the doctor.
Oh, right.
That's rough.
I wanna like rule that.
That's one of those edicts I wanna set.
Correcting people and reminding them that Frankenstein
is the doctor, not the monster.
This is done.
We are done with this.
This does not need to happen ever again.
We're all set.
Yeah, we're good.
Well, but in your scenario though,
just do all people realize it is Frankenstein's monster?
And they just call it that?
Or you're saying if somebody calls him Frankenstein,
it's fine.
Let it go.
I think it's, you know what everybody means.
The monster, he is Frankenstein.
Like, come on.
We're here.
The monster, I'm looking at the monster.
The monster is Frankenstein.
I know technically it's Frankenstein's monster,
but hey, we're, come on.
It's more fun to just say that's Frankenstein.
It is more fun.
I didn't know this until a couple of years ago.
Or I didn't realize it.
You didn't read the very boring book?
No, I always liked Frankenstein.
He was my favorite of those monsters.
He seemed fun.
Much more entertaining.
And I like Herman Munster who was a Frankenstein.
If you follow the logic,
a lot of iterations of Frankenstein,
the monster calls Victor Frankenstein father.
So then by that logic, the monster would be his son,
so would be a Frankenstein.
There you go.
And it's like the Holy Trinity
where God and Jesus Christ are one in the same.
We're all the same.
Also societally, we've decided Frankenstein.
That's Frankenstein.
Yes, we get to make the rules
when there's a popular vote here.
That's Frankenstein.
Look, I go to the Frankenstein parking,
which is a similar escalator that goes to it
to the star way.
Right, it doesn't say Frankenstein's monster is parking.
Yeah, it's not Frankenstein parking
in a picture of the doctor.
Right. That's Frankenstein.
New Holy Trinity, Frankenstein,
Frankenstein's monster and Herman Munster.
They are all Frankenstein and they are all one.
And they shot Munsters on this lot.
Yes. Yeah.
Multiple Munsters.
Oh, the new weird one.
The Brian Singer.
Well, the Brian, no, not Brian.
Was it Brian Singer?
No, Brian Fuller.
Wasn't it?
Are you sure on that?
Second mistake.
There is no Brian Singer Munster.
Did he produce it?
Look it up if he produced it.
Fuller made the show.
It was Fuller for sure.
But did Singer produce it?
That's possible, that's true.
But it's Fuller for sure.
I watched an open secret.
They didn't zoom in any frame of a Munsters
where there were pedophiles hiding in the background.
Yeah, Jerry O'Connell.
Everyone is clear in the new Munsters.
I'm sure this is Brian Fuller.
Whatever, it is for sure.
The one that was 1313 Mockingbird Lane.
That's Brian Fuller for sure.
There is a chance he produced it or was involved,
but Fuller was the main guy in charge.
100%.
Yep.
And they built, I was on the tour.
I would put all my money on this on KUSH radio.
If I were live on the air, I'd be willing to do it.
Jerry O'Connell and Eddie Izzard.
Yes.
Okay.
Those are the stars.
Very slowly loading.
Director, Brian Singer.
Brian Singer has made a comfortable living
directing pilots, directed the pilot for House.
What the fuck, really?
He directed 1313 Mockingbird Lane,
written by Brian Fuller.
Oh no.
Jason.
Wow.
Regrettably back on top.
Jason wins again.
No.
He evened it out.
With thanks to Jason's vast wealth
of Brian Singer knowledge.
He's back on top again.
And then ruined the X-Men.
The worst thing he ever did in his life.
Jason stands right now across the world are standing up.
They've knocked over what food or beverage they have.
They're cheering.
The victory, their hero has again thwarted Mike and Scott.
A college professor, this is a lesson
I always remember from college.
They're like the most desirable job in town
is if you can direct the pilot of a TV show
because if it gets picked up,
then you get paid every time an episode is made
because you helped define the vibe, the look of the show.
Yes.
So it's essentially money for nothing.
After a week or two of work, money for nothing
for as long as that show runs for.
Chicks for free.
What?
That's from Dire Straits song.
Oh yeah, okay.
The Dire Straits lyrics do not represent my feelings.
Sure, yeah, yeah.
I was just quoting a song.
Well, so thankfully he did not make money
into the end of time.
No, due to the 1313 Mockingbird Lane.
And probably will not be involved in the newer attempt
to reboot the Munsters that Seth Meyers was attached to.
Oh, is that true?
Is that real?
It's a 2017 Deadline article.
I want a shot at the Munsters.
Right now I'm throwing it out there.
Isn't Grandpa still alive?
No.
Okay.
Why did I think he was alive?
I will empty my bank account right now.
I will prove that's for sure.
He was alive in our lifetime, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Did he run for office or something?
He ran for governor, I think,
when everybody ran for governor.
He was a fucking maniac.
He was on the Howard Stern Show all the time.
I'm saying we could have gotten him back.
If he was alive, we could have gotten him back.
We got Lando back.
He died in 2006.
Okay, okay.
Any new Munsters pilot, I would say,
it has to be like when Carrie Fisher died
or Marlon Brando with Superman.
It all has to be old footage of Grandpa.
We're gonna go to-
No one else can play Grandpa.
Deep fake Grandpa Munster.
We're gonna do some face mapping on whoever,
whatever lucky person out there has a face
closest to Grandpa Al Lewis.
He had a restaurant called Grandpa's.
Yes.
Like in Jersey.
Whoa.
He was just there outside and he didn't own it.
They just called it Grandpa's and he was the mascot.
He was just sleeping, standing up outside it.
Yes, he was just smoking cigars, being rude to people.
It was crazy.
You have to look at it.
Don't come in and see if I care.
Yeah.
Billy West has a lot of good stories about knowing Al Lewis
and going to that restaurant.
Oh, great.
And they're fantastic.
And he's a crazy, Al Lewis was a crazy man.
There's a whole other Munsters called the Munsters Today.
And there's a part where they like do a,
there's like a, they win a music contest.
They're a band and this was a late 80s one.
I've seen some of that, but I don't know it very well.
Yeah.
I want, no, this is, no Munsters has worked
since the first Munsters.
Why?
Yeah.
Although Munsters Today, three seasons.
Really?
Yeah, somehow.
Yeah, everything used to.
Oh, another one of these secret shows.
Boston Common, The Single Guy.
No, I'm just saying like everything used to get
two or three seasons.
It was bad.
It had to be a.
Munsters Today had three seasons?
It had to be like.
How did I not know this?
I just learned about this one season show
called the Hat Squad.
Scott, you must know about the Hat Squad.
I know, I'm sad that I don't.
Oh my God.
Well, I'm going to send you Hat Squad stuff later.
It is a show about three grown orphans.
Okay, it's three, they became orphans.
Their parents were all police officers
who were killed on the line of duty.
Another police officer adopted them all,
trained them all and they became police officers.
And they are in 90s clothing,
except big trench coats and fedoras.
Oh man.
And there's a clip online of them stopping,
villains robbing a convenience store with automatic weapons,
with like Uzis and stuff.
And then they catch, they get all these bad guys
and they stop to get a white guy and they tie him up.
And one of the bad guys looks up and he goes,
oh, are you the Hat Squad?
They're like, yeah.
And they put on the hats.
It's insane.
So that only got one season.
But.
There's still a full season of Hat Squad?
Yeah.
God.
I believe one season.
Everyone I know is pitching five shows a year to no avail.
It's peak TV.
Boy, it's good times.
There's more shows now than ever before.
Nothing ever gets past the first meeting.
Meanwhile, Hat Squad gets an entire season.
Hat Squad reboot.
Some people were posting images of it on Twitter.
The Hat Squad.
Oh, apparently a favorite punching bag
of David Letterman at the time.
Oh, very good.
Okay.
I'm looking at a picture of the cast of Munsters today.
If I showed you a photo and said,
oh, one year my family dressed up as the Munsters,
you'd go, oh, oh yeah, those are pretty good costumes, I guess.
Yeah.
It looks fake.
It was very, very chintzy.
Yeah.
Extremely.
Three years.
Yeah.
The son, Eddie in that one, played by Jason Marsden,
who's a voice in all the Disney stuff and the voice.
It was in all the TJF shows.
He's a Max in a goof troop.
Tying it all together, it'd have been weird.
I've had a thing, and this is a good tip for anybody
trying to get through anything they don't like,
but especially sitting through a boring network notes call.
I developed a secret with my friend Tommy Blotched
that when we were on a notes call
that we were really dreading and it was just going to go and go
and everybody's droning on and it's a bummer because you
don't disagree with the notes.
What we did is we put on the Munsters on mute.
And any time we were bummed out about what they were telling us,
we would then point to the screen
and Herman would run out of a building in fast motion
and his butt would be on fire.
And we could just get a brief.
We'd just look over and like, hi, look at that.
All right, back to this.
So anything similar to that, if you're sitting
on some boring call or like, hey,
if you're going to sit at the DMV for a while
and you can bring a laptop with you, Munsters on mute.
Great.
Any situation go down.
It's like a spoonful of sugar helps the medicine go down.
It is a great tip.
And they were using the they pioneered that fast forwarding
footage that would be used later on Deadly Games.
There would be no Deadly Games at the Munsters.
It's like when Marilyn's boyfriend sees Herman
and he has to run over the he gets scared
and he runs out so fast to his car and they sped that up.
That was an innovation that the Munsters made.
Also deployed by the monkeys to show that they were having fun.
That's true.
And like so much fun.
Hopping around hills and behind trees
and they don't come out the other side.
I guess also Benny Hill did this.
But a little body, a little body, though.
A little body.
So I should know in this uniforms flying off,
revealing cheeky, you would call it, full stocking lingerie
sets underneath.
OK, so I do for again, for listeners
who have never been on the Starway.
It is important in Universal history in that it was Universal.
It connected, you know, expanded the actual theme park in 1991.
When all of this open, when the lower lot open, the Starway opened.
And of course, ET opened down there.
That was Universal's attempt to break out of were more than just a tram tour.
And that that was a stigma that they were trying to break out of.
In more recent years, they've been trying to add attractions and make it
were a full day park.
Will they ever be a multi day park?
Who knows?
Now, that said, 21, 28 years ago, just like right now, all of this OPT,
June, July of 1991, all this stuff.
Lower lot, the ET adventure, the world of Cinemagic,
which was the show where you go from stage to stage and see Hitchcock
and Back to the Future and the Statue of Liberty arm.
That was part of the tour, but they made it something Lucy attribute
to get there. And they started having the studio tour leave from what is now
Jurassic Park. So that moved later.
But you're all of this stuff opened.
Oh, and also full episode AT&T at the movies.
Anyone did you guys ever know you were kids here?
No, no.
I have fond memories of whatever AT&T at the movies was.
I think you like go inside a giant phone.
Really? Sponsored by MCI.
That's not what I thought you were talking about.
So, wow, that sounds great.
Yeah, I got to remember what the hell it was.
But I remember liking it a lot.
I liked all the boring on ride stuff.
Going inside a phone, I would be psyched.
Yeah, I'm sure there was some sort of ET stuff in some sort of AT&T stuff in Florida.
Oh, also the ET toy closet.
Let's not forget.
Oh, yeah, we got so many lower lot episodes to do.
Do you do remember when this all this expansion opened?
I think I had not been before all this because I was six.
So I think my first time, it was probably with a freshly minted starway.
Wow. Great.
It was sparkling.
It was never in better shape.
I found in LA Times article from July 5th, again, 28 years ago this week.
Whoa. As we record this.
That it was mostly about ET opening and they got Spielberg on record
and they were like, yeah, we think ET could be like Universal's Mickey Mouse.
And for a long time, their promotional materials had ET next to the logo or on the logo.
But today, today, they're Mickey Mouse's Vin Diesel hanging off of a helicopter.
Yeah. Helping a minion.
He's holding like a minion fell out of it.
He's trying to catch you.
Sure. The so it's a lot again, a lot about like this is expanding.
We're bringing stuff from Florida back to the future is coming down the line.
This article is one of the oddest leads.
I've ever seen. It's one sentence long.
And it just says, the little bald guy from outer space is back.
What? That is the LA Times, the article and about covering ET
opening the little bald guy from outer space is back.
The little bald like the little bald guy.
It sounds like someone writing in like an Internet joke format,
like that little guy we all know and love.
The little guy from outer space is back like it's so weird.
Well, the bald thing is what I'm the bald guy.
The little bald guy. He's an alien.
I didn't expect him to have a hair like a head full of hair.
Yeah. The little bald guy.
It's how Andrew Dice Clay would roast ET.
Or tell that also Telly Savalas would refer to him as the little bald guy.
Lovingly so. Right. Because he was bald too. Makes sense.
I love it. I stay in the hotel.
They clean up after sloppy telly.
I go see the little bald guy from outer space.
Got an annual pass. I see the little bald guy every day.
Yo, Barkeep, did you hear the little bald guy from outer space is fucking back.
Hey, let me get on the phone with my wife.
Hey, Diane, you heard the little bald guy is back.
Let me tell you something.
I'm going to give you this passport and you're going to you're going to make it
say Telly. It's not going to be Tommy.
It's not going to be Timmy.
I want to. He's going to got to say Telly.
We'll build up to sloppy Telly in one of these days.
If you don't get this right, I will crack your fucking head open.
Have a nice day. Be right in the mouth, you little bald fuck.
He has nightmares back in his hotel room where he's like trying to hit E.T.
Say my name right.
Telly's falls off E.T.
ride, attempting to punch the robot.
I'm going to get you.
So this also this would have been the start of this studio tour being
45 minutes long, which is about the same length it is today.
So you never experience the two and a half hour experience.
No, yeah, I didn't.
Actually way longer if if earthquake broke down or oh, God.
Yeah, you'd get like a 45 minute backup just waiting to go in
earthquake while and then she's having.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I never saw MGM Studios by the time my family went in.
Florida had expanded to, you know, a full park and it wasn't just
a facsimile of a back lot tour.
Mm hmm. A tour of a fake back lot.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, it is weird how Universal evolved and was not really
they very slowly came to being a gated
theme park. Yeah.
The Starway is a big thing that made that possible.
So thank you, Starway. Thank you, Starway.
Thank you, Starway.
I mean, it's crazy to think about MCA's odd like Earl of like,
we're a technology company and also a artist management and tours.
You know, tours were the biggest tour tour, like museums or old house tours.
We do tours like that is such an odd concept, but tour company.
Yeah. Yeah.
But I mean, there are companies that do tours, but like got like
20 minute tours like MCA would design those for places like for other places.
I think so. Yeah.
Really? Like early, early days of like 60s and stuff.
So like a factory. Sure.
Hmm. Hmm. All right.
MCA's other tours, I guess we got to learn about.
Yeah. What else?
What have we missed?
There was an accident in 2008. Uh huh.
The thing snapped and like 20 to 25 people just like shot
like the thing shot backwards, knocking everyone down.
Oh, I think.
Wait, the escalator?
Too much weight on it. It buckled.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, God.
I found this too. Uh huh.
Yeah. So but I think some people went to the hospital.
I think everyone was OK.
Hopefully, or they hit it and we don't know.
There's not really any cast members or team members
guiding you. It's pretty much self guided.
There is one hot dog stand on the second landing.
I'm glad you noticed.
There's a hot dog and snack stand.
The third landing, fucking nothing.
The first landing course has the scenic overlook.
With the Apollo 13 capsule.
Apollo 13 capsule.
And you could take a photo with Hanks and Pax and.
Yeah. And then Bakes.
You know, all of them.
They're all my buds. So I use their nickname.
Sure. Yeah, you're right.
I like that description that, yeah, the first landing is bigger.
It's got a great view.
You can see it's one of the best places to see,
you know, the beautiful city of Burbank.
Yes. The other lots.
You could see Warner Brothers.
You could see Disney.
You could see Lakeside Country Club, a property that Universal
would murder people to get their hands on.
Yes, they want that so bad for a future expansion.
A possible expansion slot.
And then you go down to the second level, hot dog stand, third level,
nothing, fourth level. You're you're down there.
You're down there.
Diminishing returns. Diminishing returns.
Oh, fun fact. A part of that golf course
was or may still be or was.
I don't know if they still the house was on the market again.
I don't know if they were selling this with it.
Bob Hope's house, including a three whole golf course.
Yeah, he had his own golf course.
He had his own golf course adjacent to the countryside.
Country Club. That's a very hard house to sell because how many people
can just buy a 25 million dollar estate?
I've been not fully inside, but I picked up some money there once.
You're at the door.
Essentially, yes.
Drug deal. I honestly I don't think I've ever told the show
told this story on the show and I won't.
I'll do the brief version of it.
When I worked for Catherine Crosby, being Crosby's widow for a little while.
So one time when I was a P.A.,
I got a call from Catherine Crosby on my phone.
And she said and she was she was like, Michael, we're handing out money
at the Hope Estate if you want to come by.
What? Handing it out?
Well, she was just going to pay me for the like what I like.
Basically, she was doing a live show and I was just doing the tech for it.
So she knew she owed me some money.
So she personally called me, left me a message on my cell phone
and then invited me over, which I did not get to go fully in, which was really.
I was like, oh, my God, I'm going over to Bob Hope, Bob Hope's house,
which is five minutes from where I worked.
Yeah. And the Warner Brothers
ranch. So wow.
So Crosby invited you to the whole on a road trip to the
Hope House. What a dream.
And Dolores Hope, his wife is still alive at that point.
I remember. Wow. Wow.
So they had very my family would make a point of
actually my family would do a yearly Christmas trip to City Walk.
And before that, we'd go get an Italian meal
in Toluca Lake and then drive around the houses and we would see the beautiful,
gigantic Nativity scene that they put out at Bob Hope's.
Oh, yeah. State. Mm hmm.
I don't know if I did.
I not say that we did a yearly Christmas City Walk trip.
I don't think so. Walks.
I don't know. Call it to get some Christmas shopping done or just to see it.
Just to see it. Walk around and see the city.
And you'll see the Santa hat on the King Kong.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I think there was some like there was there was some snow
drops and like some foamy snow drops.
And then when we saw the Radio City Rockettes at the amphitheater.
That's fun. Yeah. Gams.
But an Italian restaurant, you want to I guess that's convenient.
So the Nativity scene.
Because McKelley's is right by the other.
No, not. No, we were we're a Barone's family.
Oh, sure. Classic. Yeah.
But I'll say that I'll save that for my Valley Relics
podcast. Yeah. Old school restaurant.
It's amazing. Old school restaurants.
I wonder if we could get in the Hope House now and do an episode about that.
Maybe maybe if we pretended we were going to buy it.
Yeah, we can. We all don't wear like T-shirts.
If we all wear full suit.
You mean I shouldn't wear shorts and a Bucky O'Hare T-shirt
to pretend I'm a multi multi millionaire.
OK, maybe this guy owns Bucky O'Hare.
I will wear a captain's hat and a Navy blazer with gold buttons.
That's all. I'm serious.
And Navy blazers with gold buttons.
What are we captains of? Our own destinies.
And that's why we'd like your estate.
There was a worse tragedy, actually, than people getting
thrown from the starway.
I don't know if you know about this.
There was this other thing where I mean, this this was ongoing.
And I think maybe thousands of people fell victim to this.
The people on the starway were roasted by the Grinch,
who was a big billboard by the 2018 Grinch.
I did hear about this. Yeah.
So, God, I don't even something.
Should we talk about it?
I guess I can get the wherewithal to do it.
But he there was a billboard and he, you know, he was making comments
about Universal Studios and he said, Oh, look, everybody's on the,
you know, on the the funnest ride of all, the escalator.
Well, we have to, dude.
How else are we going to get to Transformers?
Give me a break, Grinch.
There's no other way. There's no elevator.
You think I want to? Yeah, I can't like go.
I can't go sledding down the entire hill like the Hoos.
No, things are different in our world, Grinch.
Yeah, as you stay on your hill, the impolite green creature
from Mount Crumpet is back.
What a headline.
The non bald, very much haired, covered and haired
as unballed as can be.
The unballedest man is back.
Um, uh, what else?
Well, maybe it's time for me to talk about the absolute highlight,
the greatest thing that ever happened on the Starway.
And do you guys know where I'm heading with this?
We may have talked about this at one point in time, but I don't know.
It was a while back.
I would actually hear it. Wait, a couple.
One quick other thing.
You know, you know, it's weird is it's not labeled Starway anymore.
When they put in those extra rows now, it just says lower lot. Right.
But it'll always be the Starway in my heart.
And there and though there have been other signs up in the in the famous
half circle entrance of the Starway, I found pictures of this
that there was something called going on in the lower lot
called Ultimate Marvel Mania.
Do you guys know about Ultimate Marvel Mania?
Oh, it was in like 2003.
It wasn't that long ago. Go on.
And then you keep going down and there's different things on the signs.
You know, there's a bunch of them.
It says superpower celebration.
And then good.
Daredevil Live, Daredevil Live.
What? I was like, what's up with Daredevil Live?
And what Daredevil Live was, was a very brief show where
Daredevil did a flip off of the building.
What? There you go.
Here's a just a man in like a red suit, like the kind you would wear
if you were had to disappear in a green screen.
From here, it could be Magneto without a cape.
Yeah, it's not particularly.
Yeah. Wow.
Really? It's around the time of the Daredevil movie,
but that's not the Daredevil movie costume.
No, it's just a generic unlabeled.
You said 93, right?
2003. Oh, 2003.
Yeah, yeah, I think so.
So the Starway at one point was your path to huh?
To Daredevil Live.
Daredevil Live.
To a one flip stunt show.
I've never seen anything about that.
Yeah, that was news to me.
Thanks to the studio tour.
This is incredible.
But at another another point in time, the if you went up the well,
in an alternate dimension, if you went up the Starway,
that would be your ticket to Sky High Plaza.
Let me explain.
This is all due to a I had to go back.
I found the tweet.
I know the fan listener of the show at C.
Goodman to on Twitter alerted us that after the City Walk Saga,
and I regret that we didn't get this out, that there is an episode of the show.
Slider slider season three, episode 12 called Seasons Greetings.
And this episode, I mean, we might have to do a little more of a dive into this.
But I think a couple sliders, actually, that's true.
Several episodes of sliders filmed on the lot.
I think it all found a lot, but used the theme park and used City Walk, in fact.
But he I'll read his tweet in another episode.
They slide to a world that is basically a mall and they go to one that exists
in the clouds at the top of the universal star way.
Eat at Fallen Brother, Jody Moroni's.
And it's not even called anything different.
There's at Jody Moroni's, Jerry O'Connell's eating hot dogs.
They get jobs at Files Playland in the park.
That's labeled something different.
And then visit City Walk at night.
And he sent some pictures of this.
And I will never forget C.E.
Goodman sending this and just check our Twitter and I'll repost this.
But this shot of an infinite star way going into the clouds.
I remember this. Look at this thing.
Oh, man. It's got some Christmas stripes on it.
And it just like there's the practical ones.
And then it just goes and goes a big tube into a cloud city.
And I watched the episode and that's Sky High Plaza.
It is a world that's totally a mall.
There's scenes on the escalators.
They like there there's a little like, well, not a walk and talk.
Aaron Sorkin couldn't have imagined.
Oh, yeah. Escalade and talk.
Never got one of those into the West Wing.
But Jerry O'Connell, John Rhys Davies are there.
And then they they stop at one of the plazas.
I think the Apollo 13 one.
And they look at a map of Sky High Plaza.
And it is so huge.
There's so many sectors, you'd have to say, of Sky High Plaza.
And they say, since when does a mall have schools, libraries and hospitals?
Because this is a mall that you live in.
And people become essentially indentured servants to the mall.
They're paid. They get jobs at places like Jody Moroni's.
And they're given plaza cards.
So you're paid in money that can only be used there.
And you have to live in Sky High Plaza. Right.
So there's this dystopian mall world.
And the entrance to it is the Starway, an infinite starway.
That's not infinite. Just one that's like a mile longer.
Right. Right. Right. Right.
It's such a good comp.
Like the the the the infinity starway is an amazing moment in television.
Yeah, really.
I know one's used it other than that. Right.
We couldn't we didn't have at least seen it.
Not that I've heard of.
But anybody I'll issue this challenge like a KUSH clip jockey.
Call in if you know any other uses of the starway in media.
But there needn't be another one.
Yeah, that's the ultimate. Yeah.
So excited. That's the best one.
Sliders went up the escalator.
That's great. Yeah. Yeah.
So thanks. Thanks for sliding.
Thanks for and they really predicted the Americana in a way.
A mall that has everything you want. Right.
Yeah. Right. Right.
Mm hmm.
So that will be everywhere, I think.
Yeah. Yeah.
It may already be happening in Northern California in Silicon Valley.
Oh, is that right? You're a different version of it of like tech companies
building apartments and dormitories on the campus like work here, live here.
Right. Sure. Get paid in campus.
But yeah, yeah. Don't go anywhere else.
Yeah. Facebook's. Mm hmm.
Pity the people who only got paid in.
What's Elizabeth Holmes?
Oh, there is a paid in the air.
But yeah, you don't want that.
There are bucks are probably worthless.
I don't look, I don't make a lot of money, but I can get all the blood tests
I could ever need that my children's children could ever need for the rest of time.
I've worked here for three years and I've been paid
one hundred thousand hypothetical blood tests.
There are bucks, there are bucks.
That's the way.
So anyways, have we missed anything?
I'm trying to think the last the only other thing I was going to say is like
the idea with the starway, was it that
it's going to be full of stars?
I mean, I know it's like it's like stairway, not stairway, it's starway.
And seeing Apollo 13 cast there,
you would think maybe the idea was it's going to be full of these type of photo ops.
And like the star, this is a glamorous way to go down a hill.
But it's like there's just a little photo op.
Were there more at a certain point?
I don't recall.
I don't. I can only remember.
I mean, I think they really want to keep people moving.
I think that first.
Oh, yeah, that's a good point.
Is a concession of like, OK, this is a beautiful view.
People want to take pictures, especially tourists not from here.
So we need something.
And they've got some of the binoculars you can put a quarter in. Right.
But then those other two levels are like,
here's an impulse by Snackart.
And then the third one where it's just not kind of get a view of Jurassic Park.
Now Jurassic World.
But I think it's just like her.
Get the get the fuck down there.
Get all. Yeah.
Because they had more photo or attractions on the start.
Yeah. Very few benches, if you notice, on those landings.
Yeah, because they don't want people.
Yeah, I don't think there's any lingering. Yeah.
Yeah, they don't. They want you.
Yeah, because there would be a whole jam.
If they put up a picture of the Lorax on one of these things,
people would stop, I guess.
It wouldn't make any sense.
It wouldn't be practical.
You'd stop and take a photo with the Lorax.
Your friends from Sing.
Sing. All those singing guys. Right.
Coach. Alfred Hitchcock.
That's actually one people would like.
I would like Hitchcock.
Well, if there were, I mean, I would want cutouts of Jerry O'Connell
and John Rhys Davies being
beleaguered at the idea of the Sky High Plaza.
If I could pose with them and go, I know it's insane.
A hospital in a mall.
I would want all the different casts of the Munsters, different shows
to pose with. Sure.
Monster Original, Munsters Today.
Jerry O'Connell. Jerry O'Connell in the Mockingbird Lairn.
Yeah. And then like the guy who wrote that show,
but maybe not the guy who directed it.
So, yeah, I get it.
OK, so we don't want a Bryan Singer cutout.
Yeah. You know what? Let's not do that.
Let's not have that there.
Today, I probably shouldn't have Hitchcock either, let's be honest.
Yeah. Today on KOS Rage Radio, like, OK, Bohemian Rhapsody.
Name the name the stars and director.
OK, let me see.
Rami Malek and the film had no director.
That's correct. Let's not talk about this anymore.
Surviving members of Queen kind of just called the shots, I think.
Wow. They're multitalented.
What about the guy who helped finish it?
Do we need to know? No, don't worry about it.
It just wasn't. It wasn't directed.
It wasn't directed.
You went a ride on Starway.
I'll say as a local, as someone who lives in LA,
this is probably less of a complaint for people visiting from out of town.
Kind of kills the forget about the outside world aspect of theme parks.
I like, you know, sometimes there's none of that already.
Yeah, I mean, it never did.
But when you can see all over the world, like literally as far as the eye can see,
definitely puts that in perspective.
There's no bubble. The bubble effect shattered.
But I mean, it's a creative solution that everywhere in Universal Studios,
you can see the Toyota dealership with lots of creepy mannequins.
Yes.
Crawling all over it.
That is terrifying. Yeah.
Yeah. From like many vantage points.
Can you see that? Yes.
Like when you get there's one, there's whatever you get on the 134
and you pop up and all of a sudden it comes into view.
Do you know what I'm talking about? Yeah.
I think you got off like get on a riverside or something maybe.
And you go up and I like you turn left and like, ah, it's like right there.
Yeah. Anyway, we'll do an episode.
So yeah, we'll cover every mannequin. Yes. Yeah.
Oh, the only the only dry fact I missed three hundred forty five steps.
Interesting. Yeah.
But each as special as the last and each comprise the rich tapestry
that is the Starway.
Thank you, Steps, for your service.
Thank you, Steps. Thank you, Steps.
Thank you for listening, listeners. Yeah.
And if there's any escalators you'd like us to talk about, let us know.
Oh, you know what?
There's also there's a little escalator in Universal Japan
that they named the Starway.
Oh, that's great.
It's not as long as its older brother, and it doesn't have the balls
and the attitude of the evil, the skulls way.
Oh, it's trying its best.
Let's not forget, I've never been in this because you need a cast member
with a key.
There is an elevator to the lower lot.
I don't know. Is there is there one all the way down, though?
I thought you had to like I don't think there's like one
that goes all the way down.
I think for ADA compliance, you have to get in like a truck or something.
Is that right? Yeah.
I could be wrong, but I think I think I was reading that there's not just a single
like one way elevator.
I go down to the fire road.
At one point, you go over a fire road that the trams go in a tram.
Yeah, there's something there.
Some we should know this, honestly.
This sucks.
This is no Starway.
That makes me appreciate the Starway more than ever.
Now, I'm leaving this episode.
Let's get a really long elevator.
appreciation for the Starway.
Have a long elevator already from the Hilton to the Sheraton.
Yeah, we love that elevator.
Yeah. Yeah.
When it works, sometimes it just doesn't work, but it's fun.
It's fun to ride in.
Step it up, Staravator.
Mm hmm.
Are you looking up an elevator piece of info that we have to
not end the episode until you get it?
All right, let's end it now and leave a cliffhanger.
Oh, boy. All right.
Is there an elevator that goes all the way down?
You'd be a cliffhanger if you didn't make it all the way down
the side of the mountain.
Well, you'll find out on Starway to
all right. Starway, Patreon, too.
Stay tuned. The other TV show.
Survive, guys.