Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains
critters moving around in a circle,
a banquet table filled with pie,
Jason interrupting a teenage date,
and a special look at three newish,
recently opened attractions.
It's the Summer Rides Roundup on Podcast The Ride.
["Summer Rides Roundup Theme Song"]
Welcome to Podcast The Ride,
where we have somehow gone months
without telling our audience that we got invited
to a free theme park pie buffet.
I'm Scott Garner, joined by Jason Sheridan and Mike Carlson.
Hi, yes.
How have we not, I mean, we were just looking
for a place to talk about it, I guess.
Yeah.
But how have we possibly sat on this
white hot information for so long?
We were trying to play it cool, I think, you know?
You try to, when you get invited to a cool thing,
when your status rises, you try to be like,
oh, we belong here.
Sure.
I was at the Vanity Fair Oscar after party.
Yeah.
And there was a Knott's unlimited pie table
surrounding the opening of Galico River Rapids.
Yeah, you know, no big, you know, it's just,
you know, I just don't want him to laugh me
out of the room, you know?
Yeah, so just act like you've been here is the phrase,
I think.
So that's what we were trying to do
and that's what we've been doing for months.
But we have to brag about it a little bit,
because that's really, as I said,
at the start of doing this show, I want free stuff.
I want to be invited to places.
That's what I want from this.
Access, sure.
Access, selfish, I just want to go.
Access to boys and berries.
And any other berries that we don't know are delicious
that are coming to us.
Yeah, any berries.
So that still goes.
If you have a berry-based festival or treat or pie
at your theme park or themed area, invite us.
Let us have it for free.
Or Berry Farm.
Or Berry Farm, sure.
If you just do a berry festival.
Is there another berry farm that we could go to like Knott's?
Is there, like, is another berry farm exist?
Well, they need to grow them somewhere.
But is it like fun?
I'm gonna make sure there's hay rides and like, you know.
Well, there's also, there's Knott's,
wherever the berries are actually made today,
which is not Knott's, because it's all a theme park now.
Right.
So we're at an actual farm.
Facilities are, and I don't know,
I don't have a bag of Knott's cookies in front of me
to be able to tell.
Right.
Well, okay, out there, listeners, let us know
if you know of any fun berry farms, real or fake,
if it's just like Knott's in a theme park,
or if it's an actual berry farm
where you can have loads of fun,
please let us know on Twitter.
I'm gonna forget that you asked for that
and one day wake up and go like,
why are people just telling us about assorted berry farms
throughout the country?
We should do a tour of berry farms.
Close enough.
Yeah, close enough.
So yeah, let's, we haven't really said
what we're talking about exactly yet.
Oh yeah, well today, this is a little like,
we're compiling, I realize that you could unite
all of these rides that we're talking about today
and call it the reskins of summer.
Oh yeah.
Sure, that's true.
Three, obviously the big theme park story this summer
is Star Wars Galaxy's Edge, which in its,
is really, I mean, is also a billion dollar reskin
of a goat ranch.
Sure.
Yeah.
Really extensive reskin.
That apparently has the same attendance as the goat ranch.
Yeah, I guess so.
It's not a failure.
It's just a room to graze.
No, aesthetically great, great reviews from people.
Mm-hmm.
Blocked out, too many passes blocked out.
Too many passes blocked out.
It'll be interesting to see that, yeah,
that's a whole other debate.
Is this another one of these Disney Star Wars conspiracies?
But I don't know, I think it does have something to do with,
I'm not sure.
Also, they just jacked up prices,
they jacked prices at least once this year significantly.
Maybe a second time more quietly.
Have they considered lowering prices to get people in?
Lowering?
They're raising them while the attendance is going down.
They have that deal, which I just utilized with my parents.
Oh, yeah.
Which is the $99 park hopper ticket for a day.
Oh, nice.
If you have an annual pass.
I may do the same with my mom.
Do you have to do it in advance
or can you buy it on the day?
How does that work?
You do it on the day.
Okay.
So you just go to the ticket booth in the morning and do it.
Okay, I agree.
So very easy, yeah.
And obviously.
So the talk of the theme park world is,
Galaxy says it's the $99 bring a buddy pass,
but we're gonna manage to step away from this
and talk about some other things.
There is a new Rapids, not a totally new Rapids,
but a redone Rapids ride at Knott's Berry Farm,
Calco River Rapids.
And then the two final missing components of Pixar Pier,
Jesse's Critter, Carousel,
and the inside out emotional whirlwind.
These are, they're, you know,
they're not as big of stories,
but I think worthy of us talking about a little bit.
I'm going to go out on a limb and say
the most successful elements of Pixar Pier in my eyes,
having seen these both now.
You think more than the Incredicoaster, really?
Yeah.
More than the Cookie Num Nums?
No.
The Cookie Num Nums has significant operational issues.
Namely, it's in a weird spot.
It's hard to deliver fresh deep dish cookies that quickly.
Have you had one since we tried them last year?
I don't think I have.
Wow.
And you were a big fan too.
I was a big fan, but like,
I don't get back there that often.
Would you want to try, what do you mean?
We go on the Incredicoaster pretty often.
I guess so.
So you're just breezing right by the cookie cart.
Yeah, because there's like a line with no shade
for like a hot cookie in the middle of summer.
Right.
So would you want it to trade places
maybe with like the churro, the Buzz Churro?
Or maybe the chicken stand.
Like that's supposedly bad, right?
The chicken stand should go.
Yeah.
I mean, aesthetically, I like that.
I actually would disagree.
I don't really like the aesthetic.
I don't like the big box.
Yeah, it looks cheap to me.
I kind of like the box.
Well, you gotta go at night is what you do
where the whole, everything is shaded.
The whole world is shaded.
That's true, yeah.
I mean, it all does look good at night.
Have your hot cookie at night.
Yeah.
Perhaps a better time anyway.
Does Jack Chex close during World of Color?
Good question.
I don't know the answer.
Not sure.
Jesse's Critter Carousel I think does.
I saw a sign.
That's one of, there's not a lot to talk about
with any of these things.
There's like four, so when there's a sign
in front of one of the rides, that's one of the five things.
So that's off my list.
Right.
Yeah, these things are all a lot of fun.
I will say there's another, obviously,
a major, another reskin of summer,
the Jurassic World attraction,
which we have not gotten to do yet.
Yeah.
We're not prepared on that,
so we will hit that at a later date.
We were starting to question,
is this gonna open in a very long time from now,
and then suddenly it just came together,
and we're caught with our pants down.
Yeah.
We're not gonna be there.
Not gonna be there.
I mean, we could.
We could go later today if we wanted.
I guess we could.
Do we want to?
Spend our own money.
We'll pass.
We're waiting on a media invite.
I think we got snubbed for that.
Do you, did it happen?
I think it's...
Is that true?
I believe so.
When?
I think it's end of July.
And there's a, but there is a media preview?
Yeah.
Should I email?
You could try. I'm gonna have to email.
All right, I didn't know.
I'll tell you more off mic.
We'll talk off mic.
Past guests of the show are going.
Like, already heard about it.
Past guests of the show?
What the heck?
And not us?
How many?
Just one that I know of.
One?
Well, that's different.
You added us and asked that all of our guests are going.
You said past guests.
Oh, sorry.
You should have said, a past guest is going.
A past guest is going.
You made it seem like very different.
We're more legitimate.
You made it seem like Sheer was going.
Kyle Mooney's going.
Justin Michael's going.
Jeff Garland's bringing my wife?
How dare he?
Wow, everyone's going.
All right, just the one.
Interesting.
Okay, well, we gotta sort this out then.
We'll figure this out.
Well, one past guest of the show went as a lay person.
Matt Mazzani, who was on our episode
about Jurassic Park, the ride,
went on it this morning, texted me,
really liked it, rave reviews.
Yeah, a lot of people I'm seeing really like it.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Seemingly.
So yeah, that's exciting.
Yeah, we're not gonna talk about that,
that you're maybe like more wanting us to talk about.
Oh, yeah.
We're gonna talk about a carousel with some new critters
and the...
We're gonna talk a lot about critters, honestly, today.
Yeah, a lot of critters.
There's a lot of critter talk.
Yeah.
I'd say I was surprised. Critters of the mind
and inside out. That's true.
Reading about all of these, there's a lot of details.
Like they put a lot of thought into all of these
is the thing that ties them all together.
The Pixar ones you're talking about?
And Calico.
Oh, okay.
And the Rapids.
Where do we wanna start?
Do we wanna start with Calico?
Yeah, where do we wanna start?
Which one has the least thought put into it?
What has almost no thought put in?
I don't know.
A lot of thoughts being put in with inside out,
obviously.
It's all about putting thoughts in places.
I don't know.
Well, you wanna get to this pie?
Maybe that's...
Yeah, let's start with that.
Oh, sure. Let's start with that.
Let's start with the exciting thing.
So we got invited.
I've been begging on this podcast for a long time
for Knots to invite us to something.
We did get to go to that haunt,
but that was through Doug Barnes.
That was through Doug Barnes in season pass,
which was very nice of Doug.
But we had not gotten an official invite via Knots
until this Calico River Rapids opening.
Which, by the way, so that's a ride
that's been in the park for a long time since the 80s,
but it was a relatively unthemed rapids ride.
A very nice rapids ride, good greenery and everything,
but no particular anything to it.
And this was their attempt to do...
It's a spiritual sequel or companion to these rides
that we're very fond of,
the Timber Mountain Log Ride and the Calico Mine Ride,
which have gotten this influx of new animatronics.
Right.
Opened originally in 1987 as the Bigfoot Rapids,
which someone from Knots pointed out,
did not feature Bigfoot in any way.
Yes. And now it does.
And now it does feature Bigfoot.
But it's not called Bigfoot Rapids anymore.
Right.
Which I think they're trying to go with a Calico branding,
which makes sense, but it is funny,
because Bigfoot, you're like, oh cool,
I'm gonna go see Bigfoot.
And now if you were a kid and you heard just Calico Rapids,
you'd be like, oh, that doesn't invoke maybe,
oh my gosh, we're gonna see a monster.
Yeah.
I forget where I got caught with no...
I got caught being a dumbass when I was talking about...
Somebody asked me to explain what the word Calico is,
and it was one of the where I started the sentence
thinking I had an answer and then it collapsed as I went down.
It's the town.
Yeah, but what's that word mean?
You know Calico, it's like one of those,
it's like old, it's when old time,
it's like a spur factory.
I don't know, what does Calico...
Is it a cat?
Is it a type of cat, Calico?
I guess so.
I'm looking it up now.
I did not know the answer to it.
Oh yeah.
Right?
I was talking it up, like adding Calico
to the name of this ride gave it a lot of meaning.
What is that meaning?
Definition of Calico according to Merriam-Webster.
A, cotton cloth imported from India.
B, British, a plain white cotton fabric
that is heavier than muslin.
Is that a fabric?
M-U-S-L-I-N.
Yeah.
Okay.
Any of various cheap cotton fabrics with figured patterns.
And then the second definition is a blotched or spotted animal.
Well then why is everything in the old west called Calico?
Why is every state in America have a Springfield?
Like, I think it was just kind of a go-to.
But Springfield doesn't have like a definition like this.
Springfield is just a name.
This seems to be like either having to deal with
patterns or cloth or an animal.
So maybe just like a fun, it's a fun word.
I guess there was patterned cloth around.
There was underneath the pie, aforementioned.
Does Mike Nesmith have a song called Calico Girlfriend?
Is it a monkey song?
Oh, please look it up.
Jason's disdained for a classic rock.
That seems pretty random to me.
I think you pulled that out of nowhere.
Yeah, it is Mike.
It is.
Really my question was, was it a monkey song?
But it's a Michael Nesmith solo song.
He was one of the monkeys.
Yeah, so I don't know what that means.
It doesn't cloth girlfriend or spotted girlfriend?
What does that mean?
It's about him dating a rag doll.
Or a cat.
Filthy Michael Nesmith or a cat.
Michael Nesmith dating a cat.
None of the answers are good.
Unless the song was somehow fictional.
I can't imagine it was.
I feel like in the old west,
they were just naming stuff because they needed to.
I'm rewatching Deadwood right now.
And like, Deadwood, I don't,
what does that fucking mean?
Deadwood?
This is an odd logic to me.
They were naming stuff because they needed to.
Everything is named because it needs to be.
Was there a higher rate of things
needing to be named in the old west?
I mean, they were just churning stuff out
and claiming stuff and setting up camps and all.
So I don't know that they were,
what I'm saying is Deadwood, Calico,
I don't know that they were putting much thought
into any of the naming.
But Deadwood's also made up.
Or is Deadwood a real place?
No, Deadwood was a real boom town.
Deadwood is, a lot of the show is inspired by real,
while Bill Hillcock was shot dead in Deadwood.
Okay.
Was Deadwood though,
referencing to like just trees that were dead though?
Cause that would make total sense to me.
If it was like they settled a place
where it was like there were just old trees.
Deadwood, you go, great.
I know what that means 100%.
I'm sure there was plenty of splotched animals
wandering around the woods.
So splotched animals.
Plenty.
Yeah.
I guess, okay, so bears,
let me go through the animals on the Calico.
Bears, splotched.
But those are, that's more,
the salmon's included cause it's being caught by a bear.
Yeah.
I'm sure it's not a Calico salmon.
No, not a Calico salmon.
There's a bear.
There's a, what's the thing hanging out above us
on the Calico ride?
What am I, why am I forgetting what it is?
Oh, the mountain line?
The mountain line, yes.
Is he splotched?
Not really.
Not a ton.
Well, so some listener will tell us what we're missing here.
I think there's a piece of the puzzle with Calico.
We're missing a lot.
The fact that I didn't know what Deadwood,
Deadwood was a real place.
Al Swearegin was a real guy.
What's that?
Al Swearegin, the guy,
the main antagonist in the show, Deadwood,
played by, what's that guy's name?
Yeah, he was in.
John Wick and stuff.
I know.
He runs the Continental.
No, we have no information for anyone.
He's the guy who swears on the ice.
He's great.
Really good at cursing.
Why can't I think of this man's name?
I see his face.
Well, I wasn't gonna argue that that.
I haven't even watched the show.
He played Blackbeard.
I wasn't gonna argue that that guy wasn't real.
People are so mad.
I'm not questioning the events of Deadwood in general.
I'm sleepy right now,
and I can't think of this guy's name,
and I know his name.
He was in.
People are so mad at us right now.
We could shave.
No one, they'll look it up themselves.
We owe the listener nothing.
We could talk about anything else.
That's true.
Jason, are you looking his name up?
Why can't I think of his fucking name?
Yeah, I don't.
I love him, and I can't pull.
I have him right here.
His name is, hold on.
Here we go.
I can picture him so vividly.
I have a photo of him right now.
I know him.
Ian McShane.
Oh my god.
That's who we were after was Ian McShane?
So embarrassing.
He kicked his ass.
Okay, well, let's get back to the event.
We were invited to an event at Knott's Berry Farm finally.
At Knott's Berry Farm in the ghost town,
in Calico ghost town,
which is for the sake of Knott's continuity.
Calico is their ghost town where the mine,
yeah, as you said, the mine train is and the log ride
and where the ghost town alive,
you meet the towns folks, you interact.
We met a lot of towns folks.
Yes, so they basically, they had an event
and they had all the actors
who play different roles in the town.
If you've never been to Knott's,
they have a fully immersive land essentially.
What they're talking about with Star Wars land,
where it's like Batuu and they say certain phrases,
and Knott's has been doing this for a little while longer
of like they're fully in character.
The phrase howdy.
Howdy.
You gotta learn all these phrases.
There's like a whole, there's a mayor.
There's a mayor, but then there's like a power structure
in the government, remember?
There's like a vice mayor or something.
I looked this up.
There's a deputy mayor.
Oh, that's right.
That's the one we met.
Yes, yeah, we talked to the deputy mayor for a little bit.
So everyone who was part of this press event
got led in by a specific person from the Calico town.
Yes.
Under the guise of there's a celebration,
but on the way, there's enough time to talk about.
Have you heard rumors of this creature apparently?
Yeah, so that was real fun.
They, and I forget the two brothers.
They're like, oh, have you seen these two brothers
hanging around?
The, well, I wrote these all down.
The brothers are John Potts and John Coulter, two Johns,
and they, like Lewis and Clark, opened up a new path
for expeditions, and that's what this rapid ride is.
And there was a big opening ceremony with a,
what, here, a more unfocused what are words conversation.
What kind of music was that music?
Kinda like little brass band, old Westie.
Oh, yeah, like John Philip Sousa shit.
Like marching band garbage.
Yeah, marching band garbage.
Are you not a Sousa fan?
You don't like the Sousa marches?
I would think you as a child would love the Sousa marches.
I have my limits.
Really, not a Sousa guy.
Scott, you seem like you would be a Sousa fan as a child.
Yo, because I liked history and stuff.
I think I must have written a report about him or something.
I remember looking up that everywhere said
that the great, all the great American music,
the greatest American musician was Aaron Copeland.
Oh, sure.
Made the great stirring American,
and I was never, I did not get into Aaron Copeland.
Which is probably, I think I'd be a hard to relate to
person today.
My favorite musical artist was Aaron Copeland.
I in band.
No offense, I.
Yeah, no, those are all, I was in band my whole,
whenever fifth grade to high school,
so all the band teachers just fuckin'
had a big boner for Sousa and Copeland.
Guys, Sousa.
I gotta go Sousa.
I gotta go Sousa, yeah.
And then other jazz musicians probably.
So I got, I didn't relate to it.
I still thought the best song I've written
was the Ninja Turtles theme by Chuck Lorre.
Did you lobby to play that in the marching band?
No, I never, honestly, I never lobbied.
They would let us play this theme to the Simpsons
once in a while, and I was just fuckin' thrilled.
I don't know why I'm saying the F word so much,
I'm so sorry.
I was so thrilled.
Because you're trying to make it bad ass
that you were playing the Simpsons theme
with your marching band.
Yeah, it was like eighth grade,
and they like, because they would hand out the music,
and you wouldn't know what it was,
so they'd hand out the music, and everyone would just be,
oh, you hear the kids gasp a little bit
as it would go down if it was a cool thing,
which was just a TV or movie theme.
Getting to play the Jurassic Park theme
was just like, oh my God.
We got to play the Jurassic Park theme in a concert,
this is great, and then it would be like a Sousa march,
and I was like, who gives a shit?
Also playing the Simpsons as a marching band song
is, that's transporting you into the opening sequence.
Oh yeah, that's a good point.
That is the diegetic use of it,
and if one girl had gotten up,
played a pretty complex saxophone solo,
and spun out of the room.
That would have been exactly the same thing,
but that didn't happen, nothing fun like that happened.
Interesting, yeah.
There was no one that good, no one as good as Lisa.
Lisa was one of the most gifted musicians,
maybe of all time.
Yeah, at eight years old.
She's seven, and that's the level she played.
Certainly in Springfield.
I always thought eight, I thought Bart was 10.
She was eight.
I think you see Bart turn 10 in the Wally Weasel episode.
Oh yeah, right.
So you do see him turn an age.
But they're not necessarily chronological.
At this point we've seen Bart turn 10,
and won a Nintendo, and then turn 10 again,
and won Google Glass.
And there's also lots of, there's like,
Simpsons multiverses of what their futures are.
Some where Lisa's the president,
and others where Bart sounds different.
He sounds like an old man in one,
but he just sounds like regular Nancy Cartwright in others.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the most complex timelines is the Simpsons verse.
Yeah, I don't wanna get too off track here,
but Jim Hill was floating,
I mean Jim Hill floats a lot of stuff around,
but he was floating the idea that
Disney wants to get Simpsons in the parks perhaps.
So I don't know what the,
he wasn't talking about the legality of that
versus Universal, but it really,
that for whatever reason hit me weirder than
almost any other.
Well the way he was describing it felt craven.
Like we gotta get this in there
to start paying off this Fox purchase.
Well I think a lot of things you could argue were craven
when it comes from the management side.
Yeah, yeah.
They wanna make, yeah.
But I'm saying like even putting any Fox property
like Alien or something,
I'd be like oh that could fit here and there.
But the Simpsons in California Adventure,
I was like that's straight up weird, that's bizarre.
Yeah.
But it will happen,
and we'll also, we'll never not have the Simpsons,
like now that Disney owns them,
it'll, we'll be every,
we'll never not have a new Simpsons in our lifetime.
Oh yeah, if there was ever any chance of it disappearing.
That's what I'm saying, yes.
Yeah, we're heading to season 78.
Oh yeah, for sure.
Should I be the first century long series?
I think that's, I think that's right.
We'll outlive all of us.
Mm-hmm, 120 year old Al Jean is show running.
He's the only one that'll make it, yeah.
But we'll be like, we'll all be,
like one of the last things we see before we die
is we'll be really sad to watch the passing
of Bart number four.
Oh no.
I thought she was gonna make it.
Yeah.
We'll be like, yeah, we'll be 100.
We've seen 200 Lassie's, five Barts.
There's Disney on Iron Man's.
Does Disney own Lassie?
I think Lassie's still the one that's owned
by a weird like other company, like.
Yeah.
There's at least one person at Disney in charge
of like sneaking around, following whoever owns
the copyright and trying to like snipe a Mercyan item.
Where ever any property in the world
is at least one Disney person on it.
Right, there's an assassin that,
or like even just waiting for the person to die.
So there's an heir to the Lassie fortune
and they're like 80 and then there's one person
just stalking them and as soon as they go,
or maybe the play is to like make them fall in love
with them and put Lassie in the will
to be left to that person.
Yes, yeah.
And then they'll sell it to Disney.
There's a lot of Disney agent seductions going on.
Yeah, widows and yeah, whoever owns.
Harvey comics, someone's trying to seduce that person
right now and fall in love with them
so they can sign all the rights to hot stuff,
the little devil.
And just like off the, you know,
whoever owns the copyright of the book Great Expectations,
Disney is planted in the family,
pretending to charm the pants of.
Yeah, yeah, I guess it'd be Dickens, yeah.
I guess you could do Dickens all at once.
Whatever Schmuck wrote.
I have no idea.
It's an unpleasant, in all fairness,
it's an unpleasant book to read.
I always liked it as a kid.
I always thought it was fun, yeah.
I always thought it was such a downer.
It is.
Miss Aversham scared me.
I like, but she turns out to have more
of a heart of gold than you think.
I suppose.
This is why Disney's gotta get their hands on this story.
Yeah, we already have this fan debates.
People are gonna be talking about.
Dickens shared universe does seem like something
that will happen in our lifetime.
I'll be arguing on some movie internet show
about if Maleficent is better than Miss Havisham.
Both played by Angelina Jolie.
Like Havisham, like a movie called Havisham.
Oh, it's just called the last day.
Yeah, Havisham.
Angelina Jolie is Havisham.
The sequel's just called Pip, right?
Yeah, yeah.
That's the kid.
Yeah.
You'll be on movie fights 4.0,
arguing with a robot that's been implanted
with the soul of Nick Mundy.
He's like.
I'm worried it's actually mad at me
because I said that robot's ideas weren't as good.
Like, I know, Mundy robot's mad at me.
It's gonna fire lasers at you from its eyes.
So, Calico Ghost Rapids.
Calico Ghost.
Now, similar to our Deadwood discussion,
the Calico does pull some real life stuff.
Coulter and Potts and Coulter were
on the Lewis and Clark expedition.
What?
That's fun.
They are real life people,
and I think some of the other residents of the town
are inspired by or have the names of real life people.
Gotcha.
I think the deputy mayor we met
is more a commentary on schmoozing politicians.
He's very full of himself.
Very cuts off the mayor a lot and that sort of thing.
The thing in the opening presentation
is that he, in his introduction of the mayor,
ruined everything that the mayor was going to say.
He's like, given the cliff notes of what it's gonna be
and the mayor himself almost doesn't get to talk.
So, for all of you keeping track of character names,
deputy mayor, Milton C. Howell,
and the mayor is Horton Parnell.
But we met Milton C. Howell.
Right, and we have a photo of Jason
and a video of Milton C. Howell with you.
So, we wanted two mayor related people to get together.
Sure.
If you don't know, we've been waging a campaign,
quietly of course, now in the last so many months
for Jason to become mayor of Disneyland.
Doesn't have to happen right away,
but at least in the next 20 years.
But we were given, we asked him for a little bit of advice
about playing the political game
and I don't remember it now.
This was a while back.
Yeah, hey, we have the video.
Well, never spend your own money.
He's right there.
Is that what he said?
Yeah, he said never spend your own money.
Was he talking about making a movie?
Uh-huh.
No, he's like, always spend other people's money
to spend your own.
Dress nice.
Free Knotts event, eating their pies.
Yeah.
Yep, so you're off to a race.
Yeah, we were and I was on good behavior
with a rival mayor, but we were guests,
so you know, you have to have good manners.
Yeah, you gotta be cordial.
Especially in the old west.
I will say what Knotts is doing,
Knotts has had some problems, I think,
identity problems over the last probably decades.
Tony Baxter alluded to them when we interviewed him
because he said that one of his things
that he does with his friends for fun
is to think about how to fix Knotts.
Maybe the greatest moment of the whole interview.
Yeah, yeah, that's pretty cool.
Because they were like, oh yeah, this guy's hardcore.
They're just like, they don't work for Knotts.
They're just imagining how to do.
That's what theme park veterans' Slack channels are talking
about, it's probably not a literal race.
Oh, if those leaked, if only those leaked.
We gotta get on that.
Yeah.
But like, so yeah, so Knotts had,
Knotts was a quaint little ghost town and some rides
and then all of a sudden they just wanted
to catch up to Six Flags.
So most of the park, I guess, is all just big coasters
and kind of a jumbled.
That's like a very 90s 2000s.
I think it still has some of that charm.
We talked about the Berry Tales
and even Legends of the, or Kingdom of the Dinosaurs
is very original IP.
It still had some of that charm for a little bit.
But yeah, then you just, I mean,
it is an aesthetic mishmash at this point.
And you see it as you're approaching the park,
if you're driving up from the outside,
it's just a lot of like coasters
that don't really go together.
Right.
All rising up and out of it.
So yeah, I think they lost their way a little
in terms of what is this place.
Yeah, it reminds me of like, yeah,
driving up to a Six Flags.
It's not bad, I think that some of the coasters are fun.
No, and they made a big move.
They yanked a lot of coasters.
There are at least some of them.
A few, yeah, a few.
When they got bought by Cedar Fair,
they kind of, I think we're given a little more
of a budget to sort of go back to a more classic
Knott's experience.
Yeah, which I was just gonna,
I think I've praised them before,
but it does seem like everyone involved now knows
like what people like and what maybe stands
the test of time a little bit more.
So they're trying to build out the character
and the immersion for this ghost town.
And it's good, I mean, they are on a limited budget
versus Disney, but what they're doing seems like
they're trying to just expand the footprint
of this cool place that's immersive.
And it's just like anything you'd like at Disney
where it's like, you just like, I like being there.
That's really what you like.
The rides are great, but you wanna feel like,
I just wanna be here, which is I think Disneyland's trick,
which you don't even think about necessarily
because you think about rides,
but it's like, I just like sitting here.
I wanna sit here.
Yeah, yeah.
Which is, and look at Batuu under that lens
that I think we've all said,
that's like the main thing is being there.
And not like the ride's cool
and the individual things are cool,
but just, man, I just wanna walk around that place.
Yeah.
It's definitely, I mean, they don't have unlimited money
like Disney, and even with Cedar Fair backing,
there's still a budget to work within,
but everyone seems very passionate and very hungry.
Yeah.
And they hustle, and everyone was,
it seemed like, it feels like a very family environment.
It felt almost like a theater,
like there's all these actors,
the families were all there, everyone,
people were eating in costume.
It felt like a theater company.
Yeah.
And I like that it's a little more chill than,
Disney would lose their minds
if someone sat down at the picnic table
with guests and ate a pork rib dinner like we were,
but there were cow,
we were sitting next to cowboys and stuff,
also eating while they were eating character and stuff.
That was fun.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it was very fun.
So yeah, I think that it feels like what they'll do,
and I don't know this to be a fact,
but it feels like they'll just kinda keep taking money
and expanding out,
and maybe that's the best way you can fix knots,
is just sorta try to expand the lands here
and the narrative and the, I guess the story,
because it's all some interlocked story now
they're trying to tell, which is fun.
Yeah.
Yeah, well and these rides all now tie together.
I love that there's three of these.
Yeah.
The Timber Mountain Calico Mine
and Calico River Rapids are all existing attractions
with just a great overlay of animatronics
all made by, all three of them,
with animatronics by Garner Holt, this amazing studio,
that it doesn't feel like a thing,
an obvious thing for a theme park to do,
but you're putting in a new coaster, that makes sense,
charming up all of these rides with really
very 50s, 60s Disney feeling animatronics, I think,
with all of these, they like, I don't,
it's almost like as Disney gets more modern
and away from what they started as,
it's almost like Knots is trying to occupy
the mental real estate of early,
more limited charming Disneyland.
Yeah, they're at least succeeding in that regard.
Yeah, they're leaning into the quaintness of it
in a way too, where it's like, yeah,
if we can't compete with spectacle,
let's compete with charm and quaintness,
and warmth, I guess too.
And pulling from their own history,
because the actual Knots jam and berry,
the Preserve line is owned by Smuckers now,
the Knots you see in grocery stores are known by Smuckers,
but they have a marketplace line of jams and jellies
they sell at the park, because at some point,
they realize, oh, people are asking us
where they buy the jam, and we haven't sold jam in years
because Smuckers owns the rights,
so we should probably sell boysenberry products.
But also, crazy to me that they would take the time
to put a bunch of robots in the park,
that's a dream for us.
This Knots super loaded park is gonna put in
a ton of great robots every year, that's amazing.
Yeah, I'm impressed with-
Not every year, every other year.
I'm impressed with whoever is in charge of management
approving this, because it feels like they go,
well, the right is there,
is this really gonna be that much better?
So it does feel like a move I'm impressed
that somebody greenlit, because it's still expensive,
it's still probably, what, hundreds of thousands of dollars?
Yeah, and you end up having to refresh logos in everything.
And I think the loading area and the house
that you wander through on the way in,
and a ton of other stuff got redone,
and it feels like those, it's plus ups that are subtle,
but that are akin to what they did to California Adventure,
where now there's so much more charm to the place
than there used to be, it's not as obvious
as putting a big ride in, but I'm really glad they did it.
Yeah, I mean, it feels like they should've used the money
to make one of their roller coasters not kill your neck
when you go on it, but that's, I mean, what is that,
Mesa Manta Sumas revenge?
Or, I mean, I don't know, ghost rider,
I remember being a little rough when I did it,
maybe a lot of them.
There was that, whichever one shoots you up backwards
is the one where I went, oh my, oh my neck, it's horrible.
We rode a Pony Express, though, we rode a lot.
So the event, basically, real quick to sum up,
is we got there, and there was just a spread,
and we were just blown away, we're a bunch of rubes,
we were just like, wow, dinner, holy crap,
and there was beer, it was amazing, this is a press.
Beer and wine, baby.
Oh yeah.
And we were just about, or I think we did a genuine cheers,
we all were like, let's toast,
and then there was a guy with a camera who was like,
hey guys, wanna do that one more time?
And then they put us in the official video,
we'll post this, but I was searching around on YouTube,
and there was a video made of the press event,
and there's a really, it's a very cheesy commercial toast
between the three of us.
Very funny.
We didn't even have to be coached to do it.
Yeah, we knew what they were after.
Sure.
Yeah, I mean, do you guys feel like,
is it almost harder to do the podcast now,
coming in with all the celebrity that we have?
When we started this thing, we were nobodies,
and now we're in an official Knott's internal use video.
Yeah, it is, the fame has skyrocketed.
Just shoveling tamales down my gullet.
I can't, yeah, I've been different since the event,
just in general.
I've just been different to deal with, I think.
I've been a different person.
Which I think is just, it's kinda what the podcast
is gonna be about from now on,
it's just kinda like coping with, you know,
where are we at now that we're not stars?
Yeah, it'll be like an entourage kind of thing.
That's the narrative entourage,
like how does he cope with being this big of a star?
Too many offers, I'm getting pulled every which way,
too many girls, too many offers.
I'm really into sneakers now for some reason.
Like what happened?
Like turtle, yeah, that's what a turtle's thing.
Did you just make yourself turtle?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's sad, oh, that's sad that I had my option
to pick which one I was, and I just went,
oh, I got some turtle.
You gravitated to turtle on your own.
Yeah, there's four of them too.
So we really, yeah, we could've left turtle behind.
Sure.
But I guess you don't wanna be Johnny Drama.
Which one's Edwin?
Hmm, he's E maybe.
Oh, he makes all the money moves?
Yeah, he's just lying right now on the floor,
like a flat pancake.
That one dog that Edwin likes up the street is Sloan.
Oh, his girlfriend.
His girlfriend, he's on it all again.
Sure.
On again, all again girlfriend.
I think your leg is Sloan.
Every time someone comes over, my leg is Sloan for Edwin.
Oh, damn it, my leg's Sloan again.
Edwin's girlfriend is my leg.
Oh, that's cute.
Anyway, I would go.
All right, so yeah, great event,
and as we said, big spread of pies.
Big spread of pies.
I made the same joke I make all the time
when there's a big spread, I was like,
Jason has a garbage bag, he's gonna just fill it up
and take it to his car.
I had gone back for seconds from the regular food,
and every time we'd get off a ride,
you would needle me, like, you gotta get that pie.
And I did eat it, I did not feel terribly good after.
We rode, I was starting to say we rode the Pony Express,
which is a launch coaster that you sit on
as if you were riding a speeding horse.
There were two rides open, the Calico Ride
and then Pony Express, and we rode both five times each.
At least, yeah.
Well, and at one of those events,
you get to just live a 12-year-old's dream
and say, hey, you guys staying on?
Hell yeah, we are.
One more time.
We would change cars, for the Pony Express specifically,
we would change positions.
We tried it from the back, we tried it from the front.
There were like, there's probably.
We mounted it in many different positions.
We mounted the ponies from different positions.
It is an under, it clasps your leg in,
and then the back comes up on you.
One of my least favorite things
is a dangling leg on a theme park ride,
and I felt like my right leg was exposed.
After I got off, I realized I had been tensing my right leg
to try to hold it closer to the pony, to the fake pony.
But we did it, we did a lot.
There was only a couple people on it,
and that ride has the capacity, I'm sure,
for 40 people, something like that.
And there were never more than six of us on it once,
which made it even weirder and cooler.
We got to do it in this bizarre position.
I think we switched both ways,
where it was you guys all the way in the front,
and me all the way in the back.
And I'll post a couple pictures of this,
but it was really unsettling
to be on an otherwise empty coaster vehicle,
also having been shoved in by the back.
Yes, that's also my favorite thing is that happened,
is that we didn't know how it was gonna work,
and you were a little late getting in there.
I was a little bit more in position,
and you sat down next to me,
and I don't think you realized that this...
This HR Geiger sort of device comes up and closes you.
Yeah, traps you in,
it basically traps you in a staple remover.
Basically, yeah.
And all of a sudden this thing comes up,
and you're like, ah!
It crushed you a little bit inside.
It's a little bit of an unwanted touch.
It's a pad on the back,
it's a hug that lasts a little too long.
And this ride goes over the Calico Rapids.
It travels above it.
You go through a shed above the Rapids ride at one point,
which is cool that the rides tie together,
and it has a nice energy.
Yes, absolutely.
Very interweaving and interactive.
So yeah, we had unlimited food, we had...
At some point we were just trying
to make our audience jealous.
I think that is what's happening.
And then...
We're just trying to be honest also.
And then we got to be the stars of a video,
and I had a lot of wine.
We're just trying to tell our truths, our honest truths.
And also, yeah, I'm just thrilled
that Knott's finally acknowledged us.
Sure.
What else about the Rapids ride?
Oh yeah, lots of road rides.
So we haven't really talked about the ride.
You know what's good about it?
It doesn't soak you.
If you're thinking about going to Knott's
and going on this ride,
you have that hard block of like,
I don't want to get on something like that Popeye's ride
where you end up drenched.
You probably won't end up drenched on this thing,
which is nice for Rapids ride to not just
the recce water-wise.
And I just went on the Grizzly River Rapids
a couple days ago.
I haven't been on it in a couple years.
And the robots make a difference.
They really do.
Because there are no robots on Grizzly River Rapids,
and there are bear noises in the caves on that ride.
This is the ride at California Adventure.
There are bear noises trying to make you feel like
there are bears in this part,
but there are no robots.
There are no robot bears.
Give me some Grizzly swiping at me.
Yeah.
Let's have that.
So yeah.
Do you think this makes it a better ride now
than Grizzly Rapids at California Adventure?
I would say that it does.
I think it might.
I think it does.
Certainly there's a fun drop or two
that doesn't exist on this Calico ride,
but drops versus robots.
I guess it all depends on your preference,
and I'll probably take robots.
90% robot animals.
There's a bear, there's a mountain lion.
Very interesting fiberglass animatronics,
presumably so that they can withstand
getting wet over and over.
There's one unhinged human animatronic.
And there's little gags.
That's what's good.
Gags, yeah.
There's little gags.
Yeah, there's a man with a musket that's shooting,
which is fantastic.
Which also I was like, that wasn't here before, right?
Because it feels like, oh, that was a holdover
where a man with a musket shoots at you.
But no, that's new, that's great.
Yeah.
And then it culminates in a Bigfoot,
which is neat, but it's,
I don't think it's meant to be just stared at for a while.
And you don't get to.
This chaos is missed, you're swirling around.
But I think it is a tough area to portray a Bigfoot
in something when you've got the Expedition Everest Yeti
and you've got the Matterhorn, a Bonobo snowman.
Yeah, I think in the promo art,
he looks massive like the Yeti.
Yeah.
And then I think we went by it.
And he's like, yeah, he looks great in the promo.
Yeah, that's not really what they did.
Yeah, that's not accurate.
It's cool, it's just, it's like,
he's probably my height.
Yeah.
He's probably 6'3".
We wrote it so many times, once or twice,
they started doing the please stay in the car
while we unload spiel, right as we hit the Bigfoot.
That didn't happen most times.
It seemed like they were still trying to figure it out.
Yeah, right, right, right.
But then other times, the fog went off
and the Bigfoot screened, and we had lights,
and it was great.
At night, especially, because we wrote it in the day,
we wrote it at night.
It sounds like we were there for 12 hours.
We were just there at dusk.
We were there at sunset, yeah.
Yeah, so in the dark, yeah, I think it looked cooler.
But it is a good animatronic.
I think I was just expecting a massive,
I don't know why I was thinking there was gonna be
a three story Bigfoot.
The concept art, I guess, yeah.
They implied something a little crazier.
But if, I don't know, yeah, if you just wanna go on,
and like, a quaint's a good way to put it,
just a very charming ride that I think now
that it has more character and more of a story
in Grizzly River Rapids.
And boy, would that be a good one, too,
for Disney to add something to.
If there's ever the right property to do an overlay,
and really turn that into something, that'd be great.
Well, obviously the answer, and many people have said,
and it's not my idea, is put some goddamn
country bears on it, for God's sake.
Because those California ones have gotta be somewhere.
Well, yeah, but they have a different skin now, probably.
I think, as we said when the Trump was built,
it's like Big Al from.
They turned him into, yeah.
He turned Big Al into Trump.
Big Al and Oogie Boogie.
Yeah, right.
That's where they went on each ghost.
So yeah, put some new country bear animatronics on this.
The Simpsons, whatever.
That's what it'll be, they'll just jam the Simpsons
in one of the camping episode.
Oh, the Camp Crusty episode.
Episode six of the seven million.
Sure, I mean, fine, I guess.
So I also wanna say they have a fun thing where you can,
what do you call the dynamite box
when you push the lever down?
They have that, you know, where you could shoot water
at people, basically.
It's a calicometer.
A calicometer.
You know, the old.
A detonator.
I guess it's a detonator, yeah.
It's like Wiley Coyote would lay the dynamite
and then the trail of gunpowder.
And then, so you can.
That concept art, very accurate.
Yeah. Sure.
Outside of the right. That is where it is, yes.
So yeah, outside of the ride, you can do that
and you push it down and it shoots water.
And that's very fun.
Very fun to do that.
So I like that a lot.
Yeah. Hey, good job, Knott.
They had to, you know, the odds are stacked against them.
They know people are, they're not gonna steal anyone away
from Galaxy's Edge.
All they can do is hope that while people are
in the theme park resort vicinity,
that maybe they head up the road,
they take a little break from Disney.
And I hope people have.
And I hope people, I tell everybody go to Knott.
If there's like some, you got a random Saturday or Sunday,
burn a hole in your pocket, wanna have a fun day.
No, it's a great place to go.
Yeah. Yeah.
Do it.
Well, is that it?
Do we have any other facts about the Kelico?
Talk about some other critters?
No, I think that, I think we about covered everything.
Then yeehaw, off we go.
Off we go.
And hey, howdy hey.
Let's see.
Another Wild West friend.
It's Jesse from Toy Story.
Jesse the cowboy has our own carousel.
Let's see the cowboy.
Jesse the cowboy?
Jesse the cowgirl.
Jesse the cow person.
Yeah, what is that?
Jesse the rustler, what's that?
The cow person, thank you.
Lindsay's monitoring.
Thank you, Lindsay.
Cow person just rolls off the tongue.
Cow gender is a construct.
So, right, Jesse's critter carousel.
Yeah, this is a reskin of a,
this used to be a King Triton carousel.
This is an opening day attraction at California Adventure.
And it's, you know, it's a ride.
It was there as a people eater.
People were questioning at the time.
So just, there's also a carousel in this park.
There's a Disneyland one and then there's this one,
which by where they put it,
I saw this observation in this complaint
that the King Arthur carousel,
you spin around and you see,
it's a big swirl of everything that there is to see
in Fantasyland.
And then this one, you see,
half for half of it you see the lagoon
and for the other half you see a wall.
A concrete wall that is designed to basically be
like the barrier between Incredicoaster area.
And the bathrooms.
And the, yeah, well then, yeah, the bathrooms as well.
Yes, that's fair.
Because right now what's,
they're doing a meet and greet for the Incredibles
behind that wall.
So I guess they were figuring.
And they made the wall look cool too
with the Incredibles logo.
Yes, the wall does look cool on the Incredicoaster side.
Cool wall.
But the other wall didn't look cool.
So they had to do something with it.
So now they've dressed it up and there's kind of a,
there's a saloon and some art.
And they, I don't know, they,
besides the characters on the carousel being different,
I think they did a little bit more thematic work
and it plays in the kind of 2D vibe
of the original Woody's roundup show
that you find out about in Toy Story 2.
Right.
Which this all made, I don't know,
this was one of the rides they announced
was going into Pixar period where I felt like,
why does this need to happen?
Yeah.
But now that it's open, it's pretty nice and charming.
And it ties things together.
I think they had a carousel already.
Yeah.
But it wasn't a Pixar property.
So I guess they, if it was truly Pixar Pier,
the Little Mermaid wouldn't make sense.
Yeah.
So I guess I admire them for being consistent
with the properties.
So it would have to be this.
Yeah.
And I think they kind of committed to the,
they used the 2D character, the 2D critters
that you see in the Woody's roundup show.
Which are the, I hadn't put it together
that a lot of them are the prizes in Midway Mania.
So that all ties together too.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
That's great.
And it all started to feel more essential to me
when I realized and I saw this name checked
in an official Disney video
that it's all the artwork of Bud Lucky.
Do you guys know about Bud Lucky?
A little bit.
There's a, I mainly know about him
from this really good special feature
on the Incredibles DVD
that he was a guy, he's this long time animator,
a Korean war veteran who went on to be an artist
for commercials for Tony the Tiger and all this stuff
and then did a lot of shorts for Sesame Street
where he did the music and sang it and did all the artwork.
Wow.
What's the Alligator King was the thing on Sesame Street
among others.
But then was hired at Pixar really early on.
Like in the ramp up to Toy Story.
This guy is credited with Woody being a cowboy.
Wow, I guess I didn't know any of this.
But he's sort of a folksy dude.
And if, just to give people the context for him,
yeah, not only was he a behind the scenes person for Pixar,
he's also the voice of Chuckles the Clown in Toy Story 3.
He's got this gravelly, memorable kind of folksy voice.
Right, yes, yes, yes.
He became Eeyore in Winnie the Pooh from 2011.
And he's Rick Dicker,
the head of the superhero relocation program
in The Incredibles.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, he had passed away by the time they did two.
The movie's dedicated to him
and he's replaced by Jonathan Banks,
which is saying something for this guy's vocal performance
that they had to hire this actor
with this incredible voice to fill in.
The gruffest character actor.
So yeah, this guy's super cool.
Oh, the thing about him making,
so like early days of concept art for all these movies,
you know, like in all the options on the table
that they're trying a thousand things,
they knew that it was gonna be
about Buzz Lightyear, a spaceman.
And he was the one who said,
well, just, I don't know,
makes sense that a cowboy would be a good foil for him
because an original plan was for Woody
to be a sarcastic ventriloquist dummy.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I don't like that at all.
And if you've seen Toy Story 4,
there are some very unsettling dummies around,
which I did not realize until now is in a way a nod
to the unpleasant original way that Woody could have been.
Wow.
Yeah, there's early animatics with Woody and Buzz
and Woody is kind of a prick.
Yes, well that's the whole story of it
is that it was like unwatchably caustic
for a long time until,
I wonder at what point did Tom Hanks join?
Did they try story reels with temp voices
and then realize we have to soften this up
and get the most likable person in the world
to play this character or was he already?
Yeah, I don't know how that,
what Lindsey is now answering.
Lindsey knows.
There had been Tom Hanks being a dick, I see.
So that was a revision midway through.
Which is like Tom Hanks playing a dick can be great.
Sure.
Like he's really fun as a villain
or even just like kind of a bunch,
like in a league of their own,
he's kind of curmudgeonly and salty.
Yeah, yeah, but wouldn't have worked for this.
They needed the charm.
So the first ever iteration of Woody being cowboy
was from Bud Lucky and then he really got to go to town
on Toy Story 2 and design all of these critters.
I reminded myself of,
the Woody's roundup sequence at Toy Story 2
was so much fun.
The black and white puppet feel
and especially the critters are great.
These little simple two dimensional cutouts
that just kind of flap around
and make minimal critter sounds.
So I started liking this ride more
and it felt more essential to me,
realizing, oh they're pulling you into the world
of this really charming designer, Bud Lucky.
Yeah, and even just like their design nods
to like the 50s, 60s kind of toys and that sort of thing.
They use the songs from the Woody's roundup show
and then there's a new song, Jesse Saves the Day.
There's six songs total.
Like there's- Oh wow, is that many?
Yeah, Woody's roundup theme, Jesse the Odolin Cowboy,
Prospector Pete, The Ballad of Bullseye, Hey Howdy Hey,
and then the new song, Jesse Saves the Day.
I gotcha.
I love that old Prospector song.
That is great.
Is that Kelsey Grammer?
Is he the old Prospector in that?
Yeah.
The recently Me Too character.
Yes. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
They cut the- This bizarre story.
When they do the fake outtakes,
there's a scene where the old Prospector
is essentially offering like two Barbies.
Yeah, there's a Kingston couch joke.
To be in Toy Story 3, he knows-
They're in his sort of narrow confines box.
That's, I guess, will not be going forward
on any of the Blu-ray or DVD releases.
Do you think that they put that information out there
to sort of like win progressive points,
or was Disney trying to like slide that out
without anybody saying anything,
and then somebody noticed?
That's a good question.
Is it good for them at the end of the day or bad?
I bet Disney put that out.
I'm very, I'm always suspicious
that they're always controlling,
trying to control the narrative.
So I feel like they put that up, but I don't know.
How did someone just discover that?
Because there wasn't like a new Blu-ray release
of Toy Story 2.
I think it's the stream,
I think it's a lot easier to swap in and out masters
on streaming sites and downloads.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
So maybe wherever that's streaming right now, it's gone.
Someone noticed.
I'd like to meet the person if that,
if truly it wasn't Disney,
and they just try to quietly do it,
I'd like to meet the person that was watching it and went,
hey, my favorite of the fake outtakes is gone.
I mean, if I was a film archivist,
I would be losing my mind after the last few months
with like the Dumbo, Dumbo excising stuff for Disney Plus.
Oh.
Like, cause it's just like, oh wait,
well then you have to go find a master cop
just to preserve it, you know, just to have.
If you were like a crazy archivist,
you'd be like driven crazy by this?
I mean like actual professional film archivists
who are like trying to preserve history.
Well, I mean, it exists somewhere.
I don't think general consumers necessarily
have the capacity to put stuff in the context of their times.
Sure.
That's why I understand why they're not like, you know,
Disney Plus featuring Song of the South.
Yeah, no, I think that's probably a bad idea.
But I think for like academic archivists,
I'm sure they're just like, oh God, we gotta make sure.
Someone somewhere should have a copy.
Doesn't mean it, no, this all needs to go.
Yeah.
They don't owe it being on their streaming thing.
Right.
I have Blu-ray of Toy Story 2 from seven years ago.
So I will be the archivist for this casting couch couch joke.
This must be belongs in a museum.
Christopher Lloyd sang an Indiana Jones line.
I don't know why.
You know, let me hear.
I'll tie it back to several things you were talking about
by saying that the the Woody's Roundup theme
and maybe some of these other tracks, I'm not sure,
were done by a band called Riders in the Sky.
They were sort of a little like a little forksy, forksy.
Well, you just got forky on the line.
Your new favorite character.
I always got forky on the line.
Riders in the Sky, a little folksy quartet
that did sort of traditional Gene Autry-esque music.
They did the Woody's Roundup song.
Disney was so happy with that.
They said, would you make an entire album like this?
That album went on to win the best children's album
at the Grammys that year.
And this seems like a family-friendly group
that tours the world.
People seem very fond of them.
And on June 25th, 2019, the New York Times Magazine
listed Riders in the Sky among the hundreds of artists
whose material was destroyed in the 2008 Universal Fire.
No!
Jeez.
They're just a charming bunch of guys.
They made the nice Woody song
and they can never have their masters again.
Oh man.
What a turn.
I know.
Them?
Riders in the Sky also?
Riders in the Sky.
Is there any acts that was not safe?
I gotta check.
Yeah, I was not a recording artist at the time,
but I still feel like I lost something there.
I feel like maybe there was something I recorded
in high school that was stored there.
I don't know what it would be.
My family put, or my baby photo is in there?
Why?
Maybe it was my high school band, Second Level.
Maybe my archives.
Second Level?
I joined it later.
I didn't name the band, but maybe.
You joined it after the,
it became Second Level when you joined.
It was first level before that.
Well, that's what I like to think of it.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Your version of the Simpsons theme song
was a lot more polished.
Yeah, well, we was a punk cover of the Simpsons, probably.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was trying to sing offspring songs.
Is that what Second Level was?
Second Level was a lot of things.
We had a lot of different types of music.
You have a long continuity and backstory,
like Wu Tang and Kohit and Cambria and all that?
Yeah, there were covers, there were originals.
It was all-
What are those, you gotta say a cover.
Well, a cover or an original?
What was it?
Well, I wouldn't know what the originals are,
but what's a cover?
A cover would be like, I'm trying to think of,
we would do Everlong, of course, by the Foo Fighters.
Smooth?
Smooth, no, no, no.
We were much harder than that.
We were a tougher band.
Tougher bunch of high schoolers.
Gone Away by Offspring, one of their intense songs,
not like Pretty Fly for a White Guy.
I'm trying to think what else, maybe-
Crazy taxi theme?
No, not, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Taxilef, right?
Okay.
In Beverly Hills Cup.
We would do a punk cover of All That She Wants
by Ace of Base.
Nice, nice.
That's pretty good.
That was pretty good.
I mean, that's a good idea, conceptually.
Yeah. Yeah.
That was fun.
I'm trying to think of what else.
All I'll say is that an original was called Rock the House,
and it was very Red Hot Chili Peppers influenced.
So that exists.
I'm teasing the audience with that now.
Do you have copies?
Of course.
You have recordings?
Okay.
We did that song at the High School Talent Show.
Wow.
So that is a video of me singing slash rapping Rock the House.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Wow.
Rap rock.
Yeah.
But I am gonna go out on a limb and say there is 0% chance
that you were doing it wearing only a sock.
That is true.
I am not naked as only an attribute
to the Red Hot Chili Peppers.
I am not nude with a sock on at the High School Talent Show.
You remember any lyrics of Rock the House?
I probably remember all of them.
Let me think.
Maybe not all of them.
If Rock the House rhymes with Mickey Mouse.
I think that it truly there were no,
I think it didn't make any sense.
I think the song made no sense,
it was just a collection of words.
Sure.
Chili Peppers ask?
Very Chili Peppers ask.
That was a big influence on us obviously.
I think it was, that's when we rocked the house,
oh wait, we never got out.
That's the sort of manic energy that the critters
on Jesse's Critter Carousel have
because they all got big crazy eyes
because they've all got heat madness.
A detail from one of the Imagineers who worked on it.
What, really?
Yeah, the wacky critters.
Good transition.
The wacky critters have a maniacal look
in their bulging eyes as if they've been out
in the desert heat too long from the Orange County Register.
Interesting.
Wait, they never got out.
They never got out of the desert
even though Jesse came to help.
I think that if we do an episode
where it's my performance of Rock the House
and it's your performance as a Nazi
and when you were 12 in a play,
all on Patreon will be the most successful Patreon
that month of all time.
If there's a video of me reciting the midnight ride
of Paul Revere at my fifth grade graduation ceremony.
It seems like you know there is.
I don't.
I swear I'm not withholding information.
I know that I did it and I recently found
a copy of the script that I had highlighted.
Oh wow.
I think I may have requested to have more of it added.
I wanted to do the second stanza of Paul Revere's ride
and really show off.
Again, little Scott, a little wiener.
Patreon coming soon of humiliating video.
Eventually.
Yeah.
So what else?
Do you guys remember what you've written on there?
What animals?
Mike took a picture of me.
There's a picture of it somewhere.
I don't know where it is.
It's on my phone somewhere.
The backwards skunk is apparently a big hit.
Yeah, Aaron just, we went on again the other day
and Aaron did the backwards skunk.
That's a delight.
Yeah, that's fun.
Yeah, where the tail is really big and high
as a more normal carousel animal's head would be
but it's in reverse.
I like this detail too.
There was an, as they were building it,
there was an Al's Toy Barn pre-order sticker.
Oh yeah, that's fun.
I thought that was a nice attention to detail.
I like that.
I'm looking through my phone and oh, here it is.
I found it.
But the first picture is you wearing a Knott's Berry Farm
poncho holding some pie.
Nice.
But here it is.
I honestly, it doesn't, I've cropped out what I was writing.
You're writing the snake.
Jason's writing the blue snake.
Oh yeah, and Scott's on the bench?
I wrote the blue snake last time.
Oh, and I was on a bench last time?
Or you were on a.
No, no, you were on a thing.
I can't, but you're blocked out too.
I can't see what you're writing on.
I wasn't scared.
I got up on one of the high, high animals.
I'm very brave.
But the benches are like owls
who live in a downed tree trunk.
Even the benches are fun.
Yeah, yeah.
They've all got personality.
It's definitely beyond that it's like
cartoony looking animals.
I like that crazy, that crazed backstory.
That's a lot of fun.
The backdrop, the desert, you can see
as you go around the circle, you see the story
of Jesse going out to help out a miner
who was trapped in a cave, which I believe
is the old prospector who turns out
to be a villain at the end.
But not within, I mean that model of the prospector,
not in the plot of Woody's round up the show.
He's like a hapless, always his butt
getting caught on fire and stuff.
The character fictionally deserves to be rescued.
He's not a Machiavellian schemer.
No.
Could you imagine if Lotso and the prospector teamed up?
Toy Story 5?
Toy Story 5, they all survived.
None of them died I don't think.
No.
One of them ended up on the grill.
Lotso is on a grill.
What I like about this too, at first I was like
well why isn't it just all, why aren't we
sitting on Pixar characters?
Or why aren't we sitting on the Toy Story characters?
And then I was like that doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make sense.
But then when we talk about, or when we were talking about
it's just from the Woody's round up stuff,
I like rides where they try to open up the world
and dig in deeper.
I've said this before, I like Hondo being the guy
on Millennium Falcon and not a famous character.
Give us at least a side character or a new character
because that makes it feel a little more special.
So it does make it fun that you're like digging deeper
into an aspect of Toy Story as opposed to like
sitting on Rex, which would also be awesome.
Which would be fun.
But it should be something where you sit on Rex.
Yeah I agree.
You should sit on Potato Head and Rex and Slinky Dog.
I wanna sit on all of them.
I wanna sit, one of my fantasies was not to play
but to sit on all the toys.
I wanna sit on Rick Dicker from Incredibles.
Yeah let's sit.
On or a bud.
Yeah.
I considered, they talked about having the bullseye
be one of the, but they were concerned like,
oh no, if there's only one bullseye,
people will fight over getting to ride bullseye.
Oh interesting, that makes sense.
Yeah.
It could have been all bullseyes I guess.
I guess it could have, that would have been a little.
Little too much.
Scary.
I guess it's good what they did.
Yeah.
And I think, hey and you know when you think about
how many rides they've now mined Toy Story into.
Four?
Is it that many?
Yeah, yeah I guess yeah Midway Mania and this
and Buzz Lightyear, but Buzz Lightyear is like
an entirely other aspect of just this one franchise.
Yeah it's the same.
Yeah.
The same carousel as.
Yeah same thing I'm talking about.
Slinky Dog Dash and the Little Green Men ride.
Oh yeah where's that?
It's in Toy Story Land in Florida.
Is that the one that's like the major.
Yeah it's like the major one.
Gotcha.
So that's up to five now.
Five I guess?
Yeah.
There's five Toy Story rides.
Wild.
And then that one where you get the drop ride
where you're trapped in the.
In the.
The incinerator.
With the, oh yeah yeah where you're heading down
into the garbage.
No one ever goes on it, it's too terrifying.
They should theme, they should re-theme Tower of Terror
in Florida to the incinerator from Toy Story 3.
Yeah that's a great idea.
Dipped into the incinerator.
Get rid of it just to make it a big industrial,
the hotel turn it into like a big metal.
Like a big metal chute?
A garbage chute?
And then you just go up in the front, up there
and then you just have to, the only way to get out
is you all clutch hands and accept your fate.
But if you fight at all.
If you fight at all it'll ride less longer.
And then just put on like a lot of heat,
like a lot of space heaters on the drop
to make it really feel like you're about to burn up.
Yeah.
And then I guess you get, I guess open the top up
and you get rescued by the aliens, by the claw aliens.
Yeah.
As we all will be, should we, any of us ever face peril.
What we know that's nice is that somebody,
a peripheral friend of ours is gonna suck us up
out of the situation.
Yes.
And that we won't die that time.
Right, exactly.
You get at least one free pass
where your friend rescues you.
That's why we got a flood area 51.
That's why we all gotta show up
and break down the doors with area 51
so the aliens save us.
It is a smart plan.
That is smart, yeah.
Let's do it.
Oh, and one more thing, the dynamite goat.
This is a drawing of a dynamite goat.
Oh, great.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, that's a good little nod
and it's high and together.
I like that.
Yeah, we love when rides reference other rides.
Yeah. That's fun.
It's nice and subtle and it makes sense in the world.
So wonderful, love it.
Does that bring us to the third?
I think it does.
Keep going down Pixar Pier
and head to the Inside Out Emotional Whirlwind.
Itself, it's a new ride
and a place where an old ride was removed,
but it is also a former, a different Pixar ride,
plopped into that other area.
It was Flix Flyers in a Bug's Land
and now it is the Emotional Whirlwind.
So if you were a fan of sitting in an Apple Jack's box,
sorry, no longer.
It's not an Apple, but it is exactly the same.
Yes.
It's not the exact same ride, it's just it looks different.
And you're now, it all makes sense
because they deal with those memory orbs,
so it's like the big ball pieces are those.
And before in the Flix one,
they were like big nuts or something, or like acorns.
Yeah.
Were they big nuts?
Something like that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Something like that.
They're gathering food,
they're just constantly gathering food in Bug's life.
I will first say that I was there a couple days ago
and I was there with my family and I forgot to go on this.
That was something I was doing,
but I was so, I was trying to get in everything
and I totally forgot to go on it.
So I screwed up.
I'm being honest here.
Well then you don't have the copious pages of notes
that I have.
So many notes, I assume.
This episode's gonna be done 35 minutes sooner
because you don't have your thoughts.
I know, I'm sorry.
You dropped the ball, the memory ball.
I have plenty of thoughts.
I just don't have first thoughts.
What good are they?
You don't know what it's like to have that specific wind
rushing through your hair.
I am upset.
I was like, what the hell?
I forgot to do, like,
look, my parents were here for the whole week
and it's, you know, that can be intense.
I think, Jason, it's time to begin the procedure
to impeach Mike from the podcast.
Well, at least someone's doing their job in this country.
Let's be an example by...
I have the video of the POV video.
Unfortunately, I did go on it.
Oh, unfortunately.
Well, no, I went on it, but almost got into some...
Hijinks?
Hijinks, scaring some strangers.
I was there by myself and I got in line
and I got to the front and they put you on a number
and I did not...
What do you mean they did?
Oh, they just like, like any other ride.
They just stand on the number, right.
And it was right across from the pal around,
the Ferris wheel, which we have all been on with me.
I believe I've been on with each of you now separately.
And I thought, oh, well, surely we can all get our...
Oh no, am I riding with this young couple?
Oh, this is gonna be weird.
Cause on the Ferris wheel, they cram people in.
Sure.
So I followed the people in front of me
and sat down in the same car and they were kind of like,
are we, I guess we share on this one?
And then I realized, oh, everyone else had sat in their cars
and there was an empty car.
And I'm like, I am so sorry.
And then went to the car next to us and I went,
I'm so sorry.
I got confused.
How old are the couple?
I would say 20, 19 or 20.
Oh man.
So...
Trying to be a third.
Yeah.
So, yeah.
So that was a little second of weirdness.
I should have just...
That got your emotions up.
That got my emotions up.
Yeah.
You were especially mad when you slinked around
to their side and put your arms around both of them.
I don't know.
And I felt even like more stupid.
When I read the, again, the Orange County Register article
about this ride and they say,
we think this will be a big hit with families
and little kids and hey, we even think it's gonna be
a nice date night ride.
And I'm just like, oh God, a nice date night ride
and Jason is here too.
I always read the OC Register article
before you go on the ride.
Is this a date night ride?
You need to know.
But I also felt extra dumb
because it was like one through eight.
And then you can see there are eight cars
and I am like, oh, I am very stupid.
I am very dumb.
You misunderstood the number system.
It was hot that day.
It was very warm.
It was very hot when I went as well.
It's not the most shaded line.
Not the most shaded line.
Aesthetically very pleasing.
Imagine your site, Mary Blair Influence.
Probably my favorite part, there is a lot of
Raleigh Crump Tower of the Four Winds Whirly gigs.
Oh yeah.
And they were like, that was purposely a reference point
and the sign was a reference point to World's Fair stuff.
Okay, that had not occurred to me.
That makes sense.
These like mobiles where pieces are spinning around.
Oh, that's super cool.
And the one, there's this,
specifically all the posters in the line are really nice,
but the poster for Imagination Land,
this red swirly psychedelic art, it's fantastic.
I'm not sure what, I couldn't even put my finger
on what it's referencing, but that one especially.
But a ton of them are great.
That's I feel like half the reason to bring,
these overlays feel like, they can feel a little perfunctory,
but if you can get the aesthetics of one of these
visually stunning Pixar movies into the parks,
then that's a good thing.
I mean, the orbs, like the sun was going down
as I was going on it and the orbs were all lead up
and everything, the memory orbs,
and that just looked terrific.
I really like Inside Out the movie
and I think it's very nicely designed.
And I got to say the main theme song of the movie,
that piano theme, I think is so great.
And yeah, really adds a nice little vibe to this area.
Yeah, kinetic energy, as they say.
Kinetic energy.
This and the Critter Carousel is interesting
because they're both like the kid rides
and they open later.
Yes.
But they both add the movement
that does make a place feel alive.
For sure.
That does make it feel more fun.
I think this was a dead spot
ever since the Malibuumer was taken out.
For a really long time.
Forever, what is it, seven years ago?
And when it was there, it was maybe sort of
an unpleasant spot because it's just big rocket sounds
and screams.
Yeah.
And they need stuff for little, little kids to go on.
Like under five and all to go on, whatever.
There's a certain height you hit where it's like,
okay, you are free to go on a lot more stuff,
but the younger kids, I mean, once you pre-thrown.
The pre-36 crowd.
Yeah.
What are they left with?
I had a lot of anxiety as a small child
that it's like, I can fit on this, thank God.
Like I cleared.
Was there a lag or was there a time when?
I think I hit the minimum, I did hit the minimum at the age
I started to really get into the parks,
but it's like three foot, four foot,
and I was very nervous at a certain age.
I was like, I'm not gonna be able to be tall enough.
Oh, sure.
It's like if anybody's been to the Newport fun zone
in Newport Beach, there's a ferry.
You can take cars onto the ferry and it takes you back
and forth to this little amusement area.
And I spent a summer down there and I,
that specifically they had an odd system of pricing it
where it was a certain price if you were under 12
and a certain price over 12.
And every time I got on the thing,
because I had just turned 12 and I was proud of it.
I'm an adult now and I would get on this thing
and when they charged me the kid price,
I was more upset than I ever am about anything today.
Wow.
It's like, I've been just pangs of stress.
Like, how dare you, how dare you think
that I am a little child.
I've been on this earth for 12 years, recognize it.
Did your parents do like, hey, if anyone asked today,
you're four.
Oh, for sure, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, that'll do, hey, if I can help save a buck.
But, yeah, but this was a matter of like 10 cents.
That's another weird thing, like 45 cents for an adult.
35 for, it was a really obscure price
and my face would go red when they would say,
oh, one child, huh?
And this is just to get to an amusement area.
It's not a, like, cause we had the Cape.
No, it gets you in general.
You don't have to go to the amusement park to use this.
Oh, okay, yeah, cause we, back East,
there's the Cape Mayfair.
You get on a Jersey and it cuts off like hours from,
it goes from like Jersey to Delaware or Maryland.
It admitted like, it's a shortcut
instead of taking a highway.
This is much more, it's a half hour at most.
At some point we'll cover my beloved ride of mine
from there that's no longer there
called the Scary Dark Ride.
If anyone's listening to this
and knows the Scary Dark Ride,
yeah, I hope you're as fond of it as me.
It's this dual ripoff of Pirates and Haunted Mansion
that said dead men tell no tales over and over again,
even though it was about like skeletons and ghosts.
And today that space is like a dentist's office.
Wow, really?
Cause somebody just works and types in what used to be a.
That's wild.
Yeah, yeah.
Cause it wasn't very big, right?
No, no, it was like.
Yeah, really, it was like a cluster of like.
A couple sheds, essentially.
Yeah, yeah, pretty much, yeah.
In just like kind of like an office parky area, so.
Jeez.
Yeah, wish that was my office.
Is that documented on YouTube?
I think so.
Okay, good.
Yeah, but it's not documented the time
that my friend and I smoked weed in there.
In it?
Yeah, man.
Wow.
For the three month period where I was being bad.
Wow, we gotta do an episode.
Although wait, maybe I just sat while he did it.
That seems more likely.
Secondhand.
So I could like.
Secondhand deadly.
Deny involvement if like somebody stopped us
right on the other side.
In the rare event.
You still got like a thrill from knowing it was bad.
Yeah, you know what I did one time?
You know, it's the craziest thing I've ever done?
I sat next to someone.
Smoking weed on a.
Who took one like scratchy puff of bad weed
on an obscure OC dark red.
God, you, that skeleton who sang
Dead Men Tell No Tales was talking right to you
because that weed could have killed you.
Yeah, well.
That dirt weed.
And now.
The realization dirt weed could have killed you.
Well, and there's, you know, weed is now legal,
but at the time it wasn't.
So really it would be in the,
it'd be okay for the Orange County police
to come up here and arrest me for my misdeeds in 2002.
So I might be.
I might be telling a tale in jail.
Oh no.
Let's get that campaign going.
Hashtag arrest Scott.
Oh no.
Please no.
Lying about his age.
Sitting next to him.
On public transit.
That was also, that was, yeah,
that was in Orange County too.
The many crime.
I like, if there's any way I can make amends
to the city of Newport Beach,
I will now, now I'll happily say I was a minor.
There's a guy.
I'm not embarrassed anymore.
I didn't know what I was doing.
There's like an undercover cop in a car
outside the apartment now that's listening in on this.
And he goes, we got him.
We got him, we got him, we got him.
And then they.
Takes his gun out of his holster,
chambers around, safety off.
They're about to burst through this glass here
and shoot all of us just to get to Scott.
Oh no.
When it's a crime being committed by a now podcaster,
it usually takes them about 110 episodes to fess up.
Let's just bide our time.
Where are they at now?
I don't know.
They've been talking about Liberty Square forever.
I don't think today's our day.
Talking about that poop.
That poop-lush lane.
Got more about the painted sewage lane.
That guy goes home to his wife every day.
How was work today?
This thing always have to be two hours.
Jesus.
I'm gonna be late again.
Sorry, hun.
They're running over.
Well, I guess what else is there to say for this?
My final episode is a free man.
Yeah.
Similar to the carousel, five different songs you can hear.
This one time themed to each emotion.
Yeah.
I got anger.
All the characters speak,
but anger drove it more.
Yeah.
And that was nice.
Yeah, the voices of Amy Poehler, Bill Hader, Mindy Kaling,
and Lewis Black occasionally yell at you on this ride.
If it's them.
If it's them, the Poehler one doesn't quite sound right.
I don't think it's her.
I think it might be Lewis Black.
Is it Amy Poehler's sister we don't know about?
Doesn't Tom Hanks' brother do Woody
when he doesn't wanna do it for the low paycheck?
It's that brother who did the show about Sweden
or whatever that was.
Right.
Oh yeah.
So Amy.
He can perfectly do Amy's voice.
Tom Hanks' brother is doing Amy Poehler's voice.
That's who's doing it.
Yeah, interesting.
I also like the trend and it's the Guardians thing
where it's like six different songs,
like just these little tricks to make you go,
I only had to go on again to get the different song.
Yeah.
Very smart.
You know, Mater's Junkyard Jamboree
was a version of this too.
I think it's a way to make all of these little,
what are essentially still on the cheaper end
a little carnival rides,
like giving it a distinct aesthetic
that is not just the ride vehicles,
but also the murals and everything
and the musical component.
I think like at least bringing you into a world
for the time, from entering the line to leaving the ride.
I don't know, it keeps you coming back more
than if it was just a little spinner or whatever.
So I give these things credit for sure.
Yeah.
The only thing that I would dock it,
and it's not its fault,
but because there's nothing else around it,
it does feel like it doesn't quite belong aesthetically
next to the coaster to me.
Sure.
I feel like everything else,
like I feel like it was placed over by the Critter Carousel
by the treat shop with the games.
It fits better there than in the other room.
Now, Critter Carousel is technically in a section
called the Toy Story Boardwalk,
and I believe this section is called
the Inside Out Headquarters.
Is that right?
I've read this, this was totally news to me.
It's called Headquarters in the movie.
Okay, right, right, right.
But I think the little sections of Picslar Pier
have at least for imagineering references names.
Interesting.
So you could not have the Critter Carousel
anywhere near Inside Out Headquarters.
Or Paradise Gardens Pier Park,
the weird name, the extended name for the restaurant area.
It's still awfully strange.
What part is the Pal-Around in then?
That's a good question.
I don't know what that one is called.
The Picslar Pal-Around.
That's in Pal-Around Park.
Stinkly different than Picslar Pier.
And then.
Lassiter Lagoon.
Nothing's there.
There was never there.
It was there, yeah, I don't know.
The hot, so the angry dogs
are part of Inside Out Headquarters?
Well, that's where it starts to break down
because that's kind of far away
from Inside Out Headquarters. That was my point.
Because that's closer to the Toy Story Miniboy Mania.
Yeah.
So that's a different spot.
There are holes in this.
Or the famously well thought out Picslar Pier,
there are holes.
So the Midway Games and the Bing Bong Treat Shop,
that's Inside Out Headquarters?
I think the Bing Bong Treat Shop is closest to this ride,
but I don't know about the Midway Games.
Well, but that's in between, right?
That would be the Midway.
No, no, wait, is Bing Bong on the opposite?
Am I losing my mind?
Where is Bing Bong's Treat Shop,
the Midway Games and this,
is this to the right of it if I'm staring at it?
How is it possible I don't know this?
How is my brain not retained?
You hit the Midway Games.
Which way left to right?
Why is this weird?
Why am I not knowing this?
This is crazy, I've walked by this a million times.
It's pretty obscure, I don't know.
Yeah.
Bing Bong's across from the Ferris Wheel,
and then you hit the Inside Out emotional whirlwind.
I couldn't think of Ian McShane's name,
I can't think of this.
It's always a good podcast when the phrase hold on
has been said a number of times, followed by silence.
Let me look up just Pixar Pier map.
It's really important, we know left to right.
Well, this is another thing where people
just yelling at us.
West, east, obviously it's a very famous layout,
and these guys, have they all gotten concussions?
How could they not know this?
Yeah, still sort of unclear to me
from looking at this.
Hold on, I got the Disneyland app.
Oh, more hold on's, guys.
I'm looking at the original concept art
for Pixar Pier here, and it looks pretty good,
and now it's fully realized.
It's just the Mickey thing still bothers me
that it's on the wheel.
It doesn't make any sense, why would Mickey be
on the Pixar Pier wheel?
Take it off, put Luxo there.
Because he's their boss, he owns them.
All of the characters are in the ownership of.
Okay, as you go down Pixar Pier,
coming through the entrance by the restaurant
and the Abominable Snowman ice cream,
first you hit the Incredibles area,
then you hit Jesse's Critter Carousel,
then Midway Mania, then Midway Mercantile.
To speed up the pace here.
Sorry, you hit Midway Mercantile first,
then you hit Midway Mania, then around there
you hit an actual Midway.
Okay, so this is on the very end then.
This is on the very end.
Oh God, and now I hit a kid, I'm going to jail.
The Midway itself, the games.
Stir up this map.
The games.
So it goes bing bong, then emotional whirlwind.
Yes.
Got it, okay, so that is the closest thing.
So that's part of it.
The games on Pixar Pier.
That's inside out headquarters,
so we've determined that's right.
I would say that's inside out headquarters.
Okay, gosh.
And then you hit the silly Symphony Swings,
which is not Pixar based.
No, that's a different thing.
Because you're in Paradise Gardens Park.
That's Paradise Gardens Park.
The Incredicoaster runs through all of it.
The Incredicoaster, now we know that at least 30%
of the Incredicoaster traverses inside out headquarters,
and how can that make sense?
That doesn't make any sense,
because that would be, what is the Incredi-
They gotta demolish that part of the coaster.
I do not have an answer for that.
But there is an Incredi-
They have a name for the Incredi-
There's like a little section featuring the Incredicoaster-
Incredi-land?
And Jack Jack's Cookie Num Nums.
Incredi-land.
I don't know what the bathrooms fall under.
Is that, yeah, the Incredible bathrooms,
or are they Jesse bathrooms?
But once you cross to the water side of the pier
when you have senior Buzz Asturos
and the Poultry Palace and the Pal-Around,
is that just the Wild West?
That's well-
I mean, is that part of the Critter Country?
Not Critter, Jesse's Critter Carousel Country.
Oh my God.
And then you got Coco Country,
which consists only of a poster
with the Coco characters on it.
And the Marionette.
There's a man with a Coco Marionette
that walks around once in a while.
Okay.
Right, or is that just an Epcot?
I think it's better to stay by that sign
so that it all happens within Coco Country.
Right.
It doesn't make any sense.
Well, it comes alive for like Day of the Dead
and the Three Kings and that sort of thing.
I want everybody to stay in there.
And it goes away.
Everybody stays in their area.
Yeah, everyone needs to stay in their area.
That's what I'm worried about.
Yeah, Bominable Snow Truwaits, so that's, all right.
Oh, that's the only Monsters Inc. thing there.
Oh yeah, so is that Monsters Inc. Pier
or Monsters Inc. section?
Well, but then the restaurant.
Lamplighter Lounge is over there.
Yeah, Lamplighter Lounge.
So that's Lampland.
Oh, I was gonna call it Animator Alley.
All right, that's fair.
Don't go down Animator Alley.
Yeah, I was gonna say,
don't be careful in Animator Alley.
Yeah, be careful in Animator Alley.
Some say the culture there isn't so great.
And then, yeah.
Bomb Animator Alley.
We'll figure out.
We, you know what?
Maybe we need to do a 19 part section.
Of the Pixar Pier.
Not this year, but at a certain point.
It seems like there's a lot of places.
It seems like the sectors are already created though
for us, which is nice.
Maybe I'd rather go to jail.
I just need to go sit in a cell
and have my meals laid out for me.
Some say this podcast is like jail though.
So you're already there.
You're already there discussing this.
It's a 400 episode sentence.
I'm ticking them off every time.
Well, for this time, we survived podcast The Ride.
Yeah, go check out these new updated rides.
They all have lots of nice attention and detail
and they're all fun.
They're a lot of fun.
Ended up with a lot to talk about with all of them.
And, oh, you know what?
Wait, one more thing.
I like that in the line,
they give the Spanish instructions to Bing Bong.
And he says, soy, Bing Bong.
Oh yeah, that's great.
And that's nice.
That's nice.
There's an Easter egg out front of the ride too.
There's a broccoli plant,
which in Inside Out Riley famously hates eating broccoli.
Oh, really?
Oh, didn't know that one.
Cool.
So you're a fan of Easter eggs.
There's plenty of them.
Go to those places.
And if you're a fan of us,
like failing to get information
or succeeding in getting it many minutes later,
then there's more of that available.
You go to a podcast ride at Twitter,
a podcast ride at Gmail.
If you know any good berry farms that are fun,
remember, send us your berry farms.
We wanna hear about them.
We have live shows coming up.
August 24th in Anaheim, October 24th in Orlando, Florida.
So yeah, get tickets to those.
What else?
Instagram, all that stuff.
Whatever, what else you got?
Nothing?
Patreon?
Oh yeah, we have a second gate.
If you like hearing more of this stuff,
go over to Patreon podcast.
I don't know what the URL is.
Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
There you go.
So yeah, we talk about all this fun stuff.
I'm there for a small fee a month to support.
And kick some money to my bail.
In bail, Scott.
Yeah.
When I am arrested, I assume this,
when I leave this, it's gonna be like to catch a predator
and there's people just waiting on the other side of the door.
I would say.
So I'll just lay down now.
I would say actually, just for that fee,
we should just get you an ISDN line straight into prison.
And you can just do the show live from there.
Boy, that's a way to make us stand out from other.
Yeah, one guy's in prison.
Did you hear that podcast about theme parks
where that one guy's in prison
and does the show live from prison?
Three childless men in their 30s,
one of whom is in prison for a crime
that he committed while a child.
A much better hook, honestly, than what we had.
Yeah.
So yeah, that's good.
You gotta say that hook quick,
but then we'll get a rhythm to it.
Yeah, yeah.
But the concept is great.
And then my soulmate will chip in every once in a while.
He'll for sure be a show character.
No way.
Backdraft sucked.
He's the most popular of the three.
Shut up, Roxo.
He's a prisoner from the 40s.
I was gonna say, yeah, Roxo.
He's been in there since.
He made counterfeit money in the 30s.
He's a Dick Tracy villain.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Roxo's head looks like a rock.
Pray for me, stuck with Roxo.
All right.
He's nice though.
Heart of gold.
So long.
See ya.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
Engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts,
please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.