Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain soup being bowled for, puppets doing G-Funk,
and literal explosions in a place that builds rock-o-fire explosions.
Jamie Loftus joins us for a long-awaited topic.
At last, it's Chuck E. Cheese on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the show where a childless person in their 30s can be a kid.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
Yes, hello.
And Scott Gertner.
Sure can, and always are.
And our special guest today, one of the co-hosts of the Bechtel?
Bechtel.
I knew I should have checked that.
The Bechtel cast, it's Jamie Loftus.
Hi Jamie.
Thanks for having me.
I'm so excited.
I'm a fan.
Oh, thank you.
We appreciate it.
And we're a fan of your work on this topic, on today's topic.
Thanks.
Yes, you've wonderfully condensed all of this maddening history and written some great articles
about it.
You can really identify a span of a couple months where I was very underemployed in 2017
based on the sheer volume of what I wrote about this topic.
And just wandering Chuck E. Cheese's in a blur.
Summer of 2017 was not inner personally my best, but the work was decent.
You made new friends at the Chuck E. Cheese.
I did, yeah.
I love Chuck E. Cheese.
Met some people.
I wish I was like, and now we're married.
That would be sick.
Well, as we know, there's wonderful relationships that came together because of animatronic
robots.
This is dealt with in the documentary, The Rock of Fire Explosion.
They bring people together.
And actually, there's a perfect thing I realize we need to talk to you about before we super
dive into the topic, because it's applicable to your podcast and to today's topic.
So you do the Bechtel cast, which is based around the Bechtel test, which is about measuring
representation of women in media.
And it's mainly due to women in a movie or TV show talk to each other about something
besides a man.
That's sort of the main definition of it.
We stumbled upon something a little while ago.
We have our own sort of theme park version of this that is based not so much in how present
is the character in the narrative, but it's mainly about names.
It's mainly about do female characters in theme park attractions or in themed entertainment
have as interesting of names as the men?
Because that's like a part of for the way we use the Bechtel test.
That's a part of what we use to is like, do the women have names?
Oh, OK.
A lot of time.
That is a component of it.
Oh, for sure.
OK, OK.
Yeah, because ours is specifically like we stumbled upon it during the Waterworld
stunt show because there's like the Deacon and the Mariner.
And then the woman's name is Helen.
Helen.
So we have the Helen test.
And the more we started paying attention, the more and more we realized like, wait,
what's there?
That's Helen.
That character is also named Helen.
And Chuck E. Cheese, obvious famous.
I mean, it is Helen Henney, which is fun.
Helen Henney has a little bit of character.
But Henney makes it fun.
But if you take if you're going pure first names, Helen versus.
Jasper, Pasquale, Munch and Helen.
Helen, all the same.
Yeah, this directly applies to the Helen test.
Right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This was all triangulating.
We had to discuss the Helen test with you.
Chuck E. Cheese is very guilty of like token woman character.
Yes, but I but there were characters that could have I think last.
This is we'll get into it.
But there were characters that were introduced earlier that I feel like could have lasted.
And we could have had an equal representation.
Right.
There should be parity in in animatronics.
Yes.
Yeah, I agree.
But I don't know.
Like it's it's a question of I've thought about this before and I haven't reached a
conclusion.
So there's nothing written on it.
But like whether we as a society are better off with Helen Henney than we would have been
with Mitzi Mozzarella, I don't I don't have the answers.
I feel like maybe if I just dismiss Mitzi Mozzarella as you know, your run of the mill
cheerleader, that's me being a little bit reductive of her.
And I would need to do more research.
And perhaps.
I mean, I hear what you're saying.
But like, don't you think maybe Mitzi Mozzarella would have maybe evolved also past the point
of seeing the characters very simple?
We never know because we never got to see Mitzi Mozzarella in the 90s in 2000.
Because everyone is munch Pasquale.
They've all evolved.
They've all been around now for so many years.
But Mitzi Mozzarella, we should say, was the female character in the Rock of Fire
Explosion, which was the other band that was at Chobas Pizza.
And at some point there was a consolidation and one got turned into the other.
We'll get into it, I'm sure concept unification.
But so there was this alternate.
Imagine a world without the Helen Henney that we know so well, who's so well defined.
But instead, she's a mouse.
What do we know about her?
We we know nothing.
Yes.
I mean, in the famous set of like 1991 era training videos, Helen is at best bumbling.
She cannot figure out the register.
She cannot figure out how to bust the tables.
Yeah, they really frame her as an incompetent.
Yes.
Whereas Pasquale is literally the master of pizza.
And Pasquale is care.
It's weird because now Pasquale is kind of the fumbling.
Have you seen some of the recent videos?
Oh, I watched a lot of them recently.
Yes.
Pasquale now.
I mean, I guess Pasquale, I think he's one of the most well defined characters currently.
Because he now is not just a pizza master and a drummer.
He's also a comedian.
He doesn't stand up at the Lafferoni.
Yes.
He's branched out, too.
He's trying to learn new skills.
He's doing new things.
They're really triple threat.
Yeah, he's he's emerged maybe as the most prominent character of the of the classic.
He's my favorite.
Honestly, I like to pick credit where it's due the Pasquale episode of crashing, whether you like it or not.
Pete, Pasquale, it's classic.
How they land that cameo, biggest names.
I am upset.
I'm a little upset.
I feel like there's some munch stuff, but I feel like munch isn't being explored to its fullest.
No, I don't.
Yeah, I think munch is a little bit slept on.
Yeah.
Same goes for Jasper.
I don't think we know quite enough.
Chuck, he's been rebranded too many times.
I've had it.
You had a million likes.
The bowling for soup guy, who, by the way, will not answer my emails.
Boo.
You're going to voice an iconic character, then you have to be the PR voice of it too.
How busy could he possibly be?
Maybe that's mean, but I wish he would answer.
He should answer.
Yeah, probably one of seven bands on a tour with Sugar Ray.
Yeah, he's doing free summer concerts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's got ships to play.
Death march of eternal free concerts.
Answer my emails.
Be careful what you wish for if you have one hit 20 years ago.
He's going to dox me.
How dare you, Mr. Bowling for Soup.
Jasper is my least favorite, I'll say offhand.
Really?
I don't find a lot to like about Jasper.
He's a country guy, that's all I know.
I think because of country bears and all that, I think a dog in overalls that likes country music,
I can't be mad at that.
I can't have to like him.
A thing that always bothered me was that it's Munch's Make Believe band,
but Chuck E. takes center stage.
Takes the lead.
Well, but Fleetwood Mac, for instance, McFleetwood's the drummer.
Oh wait, no, but Munch is the keyboard player?
Yes.
Yeah.
Uh-huh.
Well, then it's also a little similar to Santana, where Santana doesn't sing.
Right.
So there's actually a fair amount of music.
Right, there's precedent in the rock and roll world.
Wasn't there like a similar focus issue in the Rock Fire Explosion where
Billy Bob is kind of like the central guy, but the band is actually led by someone else?
Am I?
I think you're right.
He's like the free roaming one.
Oh, because Fats Geronimo is like the lead singer.
But like Billy Bob.
He's the musical director.
The music voice is the guy at the keyboard in both bands.
Yeah, but then for some reason, Billy Bob Broccoli, I'm seeing his last name is.
Is it?
Really?
Which is a reference to Robert Brock, the investor that started the pizza wars.
Oh, the turncoat.
Yes.
Interesting.
Billy Bob was the center of attention.
Who knows?
So you end up with the same band dynamics when one is a literally reskinned version of a previous band.
Yes, right.
So yeah, so I always liked Munch the best, I will say that.
I'm coming out as the biggest Munch fan, always.
But I am upset with what they've not done with him lately.
Yeah.
Well, I think there's also some, it's similar to Chuck, there is some voice confusion with Munch
because sometimes he's like a monster.
He's like, like me eat, he's a cookie monster.
And sometimes he's like, I'm just a guy.
Yeah.
I'm Munch.
He's thorough Ravenscroft.
With Munch and Helen, I have like McDonald's land confusion.
Yes.
It's very like Grimace and Birdie.
Yeah, 100%.
It's mainly purple monster and then like, yeah, chicken woman.
Chicken woman who doesn't get a lot to do.
Right.
Like, yeah, underdeveloped chicken woman character.
But at least Birdie we know was into aviation.
She had goggles, she had the cool scarf.
Yes, Birdie.
She wore pants, she wore overalls.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Birdie, I think would be a little bit more in the mix in those commercials.
That's my memory of it.
I don't know if that's true or not.
Because she was introduced because breakfast.
That was like why they made the character.
She's the early bird.
Right.
To your Egg McMuffins.
I didn't realize how much I knew about.
You're in the right place.
Oh, this is good.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Yeah, we're speaking the same language.
In terms of you mentioned the character named after Robert Brock.
I went down the rabbit hole of just like very quickly looking at all the ancillary
Chuck E. Cheese characters over the years.
And my favorites that I came across was the short-lived barbershop quartet,
the four little shavers.
Yeah.
They're named Nolan, O Nolan, Mick Nolan, and Curly.
For Nolan Bushnell.
The Nolan's a nod to Nolan Bushnell.
Yeah.
Co-founder of Atari, founder of Chuck E. Cheese.
Right.
I didn't know that that was their names.
That's cool.
So they only went in a handful of stores that were trying
an ice cream parlor concept in a corner of the store.
So they're like the ice cream parlor, ice cream barbershop quartet,
it's not kind of the stripes, like ferals sort of thing.
I think there's a real lesson with the story of Chuck E. Cheese about homogenization
and refining brands to the point where they're a little bit dull.
Because if you look at the early messy history of Chuck E. Cheese,
the first of which opened in 1977 in San Jose, California,
all the original ones had different showrooms and different acts.
And there was a rotating guest star slot.
And in fact, the first guest star was Helen.
But Helen stuck around and had longevity and became one of the main five.
But.
The middle of second wave feminism.
We can't just rule her out.
We need a woman who's in the workplace, right?
She's a skin gal.
Well, kind of all of the guest stars, they cycled through a lot of women.
I don't think there was ever any talk of there being more than one woman in the band.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, you can't have that.
They have the way they have.
I would sooner have a dog in overalls.
Of course.
Another dog and two dogs.
Second.
As many as possible.
But like, it seems like for the first five years or so,
there'd be these showrooms with these weird bands and this character
who's only in this corner.
Yeah, an ice cream place.
And this one has a lounge singer hippo lady.
Foxy Colleen, the Irish lass.
Well, our Dolly Dimples.
Dolly Dimples.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dolly Dimples should still be a care.
This is what I was saying earlier.
Dolly Dimples, Sally Sachet, where these characters could have stood the test of time.
They could come back now.
Yeah.
Krusty the cat who was originally Chucky's foil.
Yes.
That was back when they were all in frames.
In frames.
Yeah, the original ones were in frames above the restaurant.
Because they didn't have that Aaron Fecter magic.
No.
They didn't have that pneumatic tube magic.
Oh, is that what happened?
Because the characters were initially just the upper halves.
They were very rudimentary animatronics.
And then, I mean, we can tear apart the pizza wars all day.
Yes.
Aaron Fecter, thanks to Robert Brock, was funded to make this full animatronic band.
Because they were more fluid and they were easier to customize because of whatever the
tubing system that he had invented for Whack-a-Mole and then got scammed out of Whack-a-Mole,
even though he kind of stole it himself.
So he had the Tubie system.
And then he made this band called the Wolf Pack 5, which is really fun.
And there's still videos of them on YouTube.
And then Robert Brock funded, saw their Wolf Pack 5, was like, oh, this is cool.
And funded him to make the Rock-a-Fire explosion.
Yes.
Brock worked for the founder Nolan Bush, who was a franchisee.
Brock's a snake.
He's a snake.
Because he's like, oh, shit, this guy's going to blow us out of the water.
I'm getting in business with this guy.
And just copies the Chucky formula, which I always had at the other.
I always thought Showbiz Pizza came first and Chucky copied.
Me too.
And it's the other way around.
Yeah, yeah.
So yeah, Nolan Bushnell found Chucky Cheese with his Atari money,
looking for a way to get arcades going again and to find an excuse for you to be able to drink
in an arcade because that was not a like.
They weren't zoned for that or whatever.
So and for what are the adults doing while the kids are playing games?
Which they will sit and watch an animatronic band, I guess was the idea.
There was like a few examples in early Chucky Cheese's where they had like a mom's room and
a dad's room where they would they were just like small rooms.
I think it was only in a couple of locations, but they would have soap operas just playing
in one room.
And that's where the moms go and sports playing in another small room.
And that's where the dads go.
And so they can stay there for however long while their kids spend all their money.
You can breastfeed in one.
You can stretch your balls in the other.
There's a stag film playing in the dad's room.
Like the parents are separated while their kids play in rooms that their children are not in.
So neither has eyes on their on their children.
No kid check the system to track your child.
In the early days, it was just the I just remember walking in like any restaurant.
It was just the honor system that the child you come with is the child.
Yeah, honor system.
He's just throwing a tantrum.
He's upset.
He lost the game.
He's not mad because I'm abducting him.
That does sound a little dystopian, like a little Fahrenheit 451 of like, well, we come home.
There's father's room and mother's room and child room.
Right.
And if you don't like it, make your own room.
I think that that was like pre animatronic band.
Like while there was not much else to look at, though, like they're just like, oh, we
got to give them something to do.
So give them beer and then turn on a sport.
Right.
Do they have to tape soap operas to play at nine o'clock?
Was that a time when like dad might say like, I don't mind that place that Chuck E.
Cheese's.
That's not such a bad place.
We could go over there.
Like that was a bad like a time when maybe you could have gotten your dad more on board
to go because like it catered to him.
Like the kind of family time where you don't actually have to be together,
which is my family's favorite.
Right.
Yeah.
Everyone gets to kind of do their own thing.
I mean, the early days of family dining does feel like, you know how you hate your fucking
kids, but we all got to eat.
Here's some dark wood and some do dads and some beer like that was that is what I picture
early.
Ben agains and ground rounds and fiddle fat or whatever those fucking places.
I always wonder what the drinking cut off was in early Chuck E.
Cheese days because now it's too, I can say from personal experience.
Yeah.
You can't get more than two.
You get two X's on your hands and if you've got both X's, you're too, you're fucked up.
You know, you can't, you can't drink any more blue moons.
But I wonder, I feel like it might've been open season back then.
Yeah.
I wouldn't be surprised.
Also at the time I found the menu for the original Chuck E.
Cheese pizza time theater.
Soft frozen yogurt.
Enjoy the latest taste sensation.
Toppings include granola, shredded coconut, wheat germ, dates, chopped nuts and shaved
almonds.
So very trendy, I guess at the end of seventies.
We eat your seventies food was really strange in general.
Yeah.
All that weird just gelatin hanging in there is also, they had like a vegetarian pizza and
then a protein pizza where they just kind of doubled the cheese and then put shaved
almonds on top and like beef.
Yeah.
That was like almonds.
I was going to say like this is a weird California pizza kitchen like precursor.
The food has always been pretty gnarly there.
There are some people who will defend the food, but from my experience, it's pretty
indefensible.
The pizza is very sharp.
Like I don't subscribe to like the Shane Dawson conspiracy theories or any garbage like that.
Yeah.
Yes.
It's Shane Dawson Shane Dawson put forth the theory that they recycle their pizza that
they like easy to wrap your head around system of taking uneaten slices and reconstructing
them into a new pizza.
And that is a theory presented by one of YouTube's most popular racists.
A competitive area.
How do you keep track of them?
Yeah.
They have to.
It's the register of the top 10,000.
But I mean, kicking a business while they have been down for 15 years.
So much has fallen.
It actually, I think it did make me mad.
I think I did get to like, don't throw this on them.
It's me.
And there's all these fights happening.
And there's all like horrible fights happening all the time in the Chuck E.
Cheese's and also the misinformation that the robots are going away entirely.
They are.
I mean, they're probably on the way to it, but we've heard it said like I've seen a
lot of the band.
They're gone.
There's no more of them.
The most part, right?
We've asked our listeners send us pictures of the full of give us full munch.
I want to see the full munch.
There's a lot of them out there.
I have the full.
So the way to know whether you're getting the full munch or not is to know when the
Chuck E.
Cheese was opened because they're starting to remove them now.
It's been like two, I think like two years since they said they were going to.
Yeah.
And now they're starting to remove them.
And then the plan is to make it like an open dance space.
And then they're just making that now they're just making those like short sketch
videos with puppets that look like the animatronics sort of.
And I want to know who writes the videos because I want in.
I watched a YouTube video of like the production team.
Really?
I'll send you that.
I'll find it.
Say who the writer was.
They talked to a guy who, I mean, it seems like it's all hands on deck.
I think it's the Muppet Workshop.
I think you're puppeteering in your own and you're directing it.
I'm going to find their LinkedIn and be like, I'll work for free.
I don't care.
If you're willing to move to Irving, Texas.
I'll go.
I'll be like, we need to do some work on Helen.
I'm uniquely qualified.
That's a legitimate angle, I think, to make your way in on.
By any means necessary.
But if the location was open prior to 1998, there should still be a full band there.
Post-98, they start scaling down the animatronics to just a Chucky.
Yes.
Studio C, they call that model.
And that Chucky is designed by Garner Holt, a popular animatronic creator and company.
It's the same company that built all of the robots for the Cars ride.
And all of these really good recent Knott's Berry Farm rides where they've added and refreshed
robots to these sort of ancient attractions.
And the new robots are wonderful.
That's the one good thing you could say about the Studio C Chucks.
He made the new Chuck?
Oh, that's good.
Yeah, good company.
Had a really good exhibit at a museum in San Bernardino recently.
The Studio C Chucks are criminally underused.
They're just sitting there.
No, and look good.
They look great.
Are they taking those out, though?
Slowly they are.
Where are they going?
Do we know where they're going?
I don't know.
I really want to know what they're doing.
If they're being dismantled for parts, I'll lose my mind.
They have to be, right?
I know.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Or they're going in a big unmarked grave.
Like an unmarked robot grave.
Oh my gosh.
Did you know it happened in Nolan Bushnell twice?
They're burning some of the ETs to make room in the grave for Chuckie.
I was saying if you go to a Chuckie Cheese and you walk in and there's just screens and
maybe a little camera that you can be on the green screen and then a single solitary robot,
that is a Studio C.
The one if anyone pre-gamed our dynasty typewriter show at the Chuckie Cheese,
that one is a Studio C and the robot is still there.
The one near the dynasty typewriter?
Yes.
Yeah.
So those are the most at risk is what we're saying.
Of just taking out the one robot.
But if there's five robots, then you've got robot consensus and it's too hard to get rid of all of them.
But they're still going to try?
So I looked up my childhood one in Wilmington, Delaware and that had the full band
up at least into 2012.
I watched a video of the band from 2012.
Then I saw like a walkthrough of it in 2016 and I think it was gone.
But kept the sky tubes, had not yet removed the sky tubes, but the band was gone.
And that was the one I went to growing up.
Usually we would go if we got good report cards, we went.
We were good boys, so we always got good report cards.
And then friends birthdays, at a certain point after a few years, my mom was like,
look, we'll go to Chuckie Cheese, but can we go to a cheaper, better pizza place before?
Can we just eat and then we'll get you tokens, we'll play the games.
But I do not want to eat there, Jace.
I feel like me, my dad and my brother always liked the pizza.
I as a kid always liked eating at the place I was going.
It's like we're staying at the hotel.
Well, I want to check out the hotel restaurant.
I just made it.
It's probably a holdover from Disney of like, well, you're here.
You want to do the stuff that's here.
Yeah, I remember my dad being weirdly defensive of the pizza as well.
I don't really know why.
I don't think he liked being there.
Though my childhood one was closed while I was still a child.
I don't know if it was because it was under attended or it was like kind of like
not the best neighborhood or what it was.
But yeah, that was our good report cards.
We had to end up going to Bugaboo Creek, which is another.
You guys ever heard of Bugaboo Creek?
No.
That was, I think it must have only been in Canada and maybe like New England,
but it's an animatronic restaurant where the theme is Canada.
And there is an animatronic tree at the front that would greet you and be like,
welcome to Bugaboo Creek.
Sit down.
There's a 500 hour wait and would tell jokes.
And then there was like talking moose on the wall.
It was kind of like rainforest.
I think it was they were ripping off Rainforest Cafe.
They're like, what if Rainforest Cafe was Canada?
Right.
And that's where we went.
Was there a Mountie of some kind, like a Mountie robot or something?
No, the waiters were dressed as like all like lumberjack.
OK.
But there was I definitely remember there were a bunch of moose.
There was the talking tree because I used to be really afraid of it.
And there was there was a few different, but I haven't found many people who have been to
Bugaboo Creeks.
That's totally unfamiliar to me.
They're all gone now.
I think I'm wrapping.
I've started to not be afraid of talking trees finally in my 30s because there's a lot.
There's that Sanrio Puroland is very that vibe.
And then I remember being freaked out by them at FAO Schwartz.
There's a lot of talking tree animatronics out there.
Yeah.
I'm trying to think.
I mean, the scary trees on Snow White Scary Adventure, but they didn't do they talk.
I'm talking those.
You're talking about the real.
Hello.
They have kind of like apple cheek.
They have like big like brown cheeks.
There's a wizard laws talking trees to.
Oh, yeah.
Well, they grab.
They grab.
They were violent.
There's also there was a type of fruit snack where in the ad there was a talking tree.
Yeah.
It goes, oh, and he like rains fruit snacks from his branches.
You were afraid of him a little bit.
Yeah.
That's a scary.
There is something scary about a tree like the bark face.
Yeah.
Bark face, whatever reason.
Strange.
The only talking tree I ever really loved was grandmother Willow from Pocahontas.
My mom was great.
She was awesome.
There was like we had a I don't know what kind of tree it was outside when I was little.
And my mom went on it and like put a little smiley face on it and sharpie and was like,
you can go talk to it.
So I would just talk to a tree outside.
But it wasn't grandmother Willow in your mind.
It was just another talking tree.
No, it was grandmother.
Oh, it was.
My mind.
Okay.
I was loving it.
That's great.
Yeah.
I'm teaching you lessons about preserving nature.
She was teaching me about colonialism outside my house.
Wild.
The story of mine you watched is not true.
Not one word of it.
So a friend told me about this place called has anyone encountered this?
They were in the Midwest.
Similarly to Bugaboos, an offshoot.
Major Magic's All-Star Pizza Review.
No.
It is a Chuck E. Cheese like that's Major Magic.
He's a little guy and.
Oh, he's a little guy.
He's a little Captain Crunch.
Little Captain Crunch guy.
Was that a pancake or a burger?
I think that's a drum.
I think that's a drum with a face.
It's a drum.
So.
It's got those apple cheeks I'm talking about.
We looked this up.
Hi, Jane.
The website I found the most of the stuff about on was a man named Dennis Machine Gun Thompson,
who was the drummer in the MC5.
What?
Was involved in this Chuck E. Cheese offshoot.
Yes.
So.
There is a cool.
Oh, I miss being.
Pizza drama.
There is a cool like fox girl in a pink jumpsuit playing guitar too.
Wow.
Yeah.
Here.
She's cool.
Oh, that's like the best of all three.
Whoa.
Wait, what is this band called again?
Major Magic's All-Star Pizza Review.
What's the name of the band?
Of the band.
I'm not sure.
Flash the Drummer is a guy.
I think that's a.
She's red.
That's what the sax player was Sergeant Pepperoni.
Perfect.
Funny.
This guy was had the title vice president of entertainment and then had to recruit people.
Oh, this is a real.
No, no, the guy from the MC5.
Oh, that was his title.
That wasn't a puppet's name.
OK.
No, I mean, the puppets were clearly military ranks.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Sergeant Pepperoni, major.
There's no vice president in the military.
Yeah.
So yeah, major magic's is a whole other rabbit hole.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
Bugaboo.
Bugaboo Creek.
I feel like my mom used to go to like a bugaboo steakhouse.
Yeah, that was it.
Is that it?
Yeah.
Yeah, they might have changed the name.
Maybe they changed it, but I don't remember animal cheese.
Yeah.
That's a whole nother.
So sad.
Major Magic, not enough to keep restaurant open.
The Toledo Blade.
What is it?
Roasted by the Toledo Blade.
This is also like an alternate path for you being the pizza reporter for local newspapers.
If only this was still needed by anyone.
I know.
If there's no longer anything to cover.
It's a beat reporter.
I went to a Chuck E. Cheese in Wisconsin a couple of weeks ago, and it was in pretty good shape.
It was a Studio C model.
But I went to my boyfriend's hometown in Racine, Wisconsin, and we found some good stuff.
This one had to have opened sometime after 1998, but they had the dressing of like,
they'll do like parody posters at Chuck E. Cheese sometimes.
And these were the best ones I'd ever seen.
There's an ER parody.
What is that?
Is it just like a...
It's just Chuck E. and Munch in a surgical room.
It's called ERRR, which I don't know what the joke is.
There'll be these parodies posters, and they did it for albums too.
The one year we were in was TV shows.
It seems like sometimes it's pizza puns, and other times it's about that they're dumb or fat.
So I regard that as like, they aren't smart like doctors.
They're like, errr.
That's what I think of it.
Galaxy range.
It's a very Mad Magazine style.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of like, they're dumb.
You can get the word doofus or clod in there or something.
My favorite one is Chuck Feld.
We'll talk to him at Chuck Feld.
Yeah, Chuck Feld is a classic.
Chuck Feld, which is a poster.
He's...
Okay, so Chuck E. Cheese is in a blazer.
He looks kind of like Jerry, and he's doing standup for,
seemingly, the backs of the heads of human Kramer, George, and Lane.
Yes, he's doing standup for the cast.
Yes, yeah.
It's still the regular...
So these people who know their friend Jerry Seinfeld
today are seeing a different standup show by another guy named Chuck Feld.
Yeah.
Jerry Chuck Feld.
Or is it Chuck E. Chuck Feld?
Yes, that's right.
Charles Entertainment Chuck Feld.
His, yeah, his standup pseudonym is...
Was there...
There's an X files, I think, also?
Yeah, the C files, of course.
Uh-huh.
And then, perhaps the laziest of all, Chuck Trick.
Oh, man.
Jamming together.
Not even like pizza trick or something, which...
Or like the symbol could be in a pizza, not even that.
If we're in the area of the parody posters,
I have a little bit of stuff prepared.
We can keep jumping around the history and whatever,
but so those are the TV posters.
I remember being around ones in...
My childhood one was in Northridge, California,
and they had a lot of classic album covers.
Oh.
They had Yellow Submarine Sandwich,
their insert of Beatles cartoon style,
Saturday Night Retriever.
Is that a night fever?
Oh, do you have these ones that my childhood one too, yeah?
Okay, yes, yeah.
I loved the...
I legitimately have very fond memories of seeing...
I was probably acquainted with, for example,
Braun in the USA.
Braun.
I think I knew that before I had ever seen the cover of Born in the USA.
I think similarly Bad Dog,
where Jasper is presented like Michael Jackson.
Michael Jasper.
That's one joke to it.
That's pretty good.
They wish they thought of that.
But the Flabby Road, another one,
because a lot of the song parodies also,
they'll just talk about being fat and the pizza makes them fat,
which is a strange message in your pizza restaurant.
But the one I legitimately like a lot,
I really like this,
is a...
And it's a deep cut for them to be parodying,
is a parody of Iron Butterfly and Agata da Vita,
and they make it I've agata da pizza,
and the artist's not Iron Butterfly, but Italian pizza guy.
That's thoughtful.
Yeah, that's good.
They really went one step further with it.
And I love these album covers and they've always made me so happy.
And I've always thought they needed to exist in other...
It pains me that they stopped doing this in a certain era,
so you don't get any past 1990,
or there may never be a new one again.
And they stay with albums you might know,
and I always thought it needed to cut deeper.
So this is...
Mike, we just talked about you just resuscitated your Twitter account,
the topical genie from the Aladdin show at California Adventure.
You were doing that in 2010, 2011.
I had this idea about doing new Chuck E. Cheese album covers in 2008.
So I'm gonna show you a Photoshop that I made in 2008,
and I finally have a place for it.
I was just like, how about artsier album covers?
So let me show you this here.
This is Chuck E. Sane.
It's kind of...
It's an Aladdin Sane where he's Chuck E. as the Bowie stripe.
I'll post all this on Twitter.
It's a little scary, isn't it?
I would see a vaguely androgynous Chuck.
And I would have been like, you would have been like,
that was in the restaurant.
I've been like, oh yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I wasn't even trying to go too far beyond
what the kind of thing they would actually have.
This they probably wouldn't have because it's a little too sexualized.
But I was just thinking about the greatest album covers of all time.
There's the Cars, Candio.
And I've turned that into the Hens Pizza O.
We're looking at Helen in kind of a body stocking,
lying on top of a big slice of pizza.
Right, right.
Iconic.
And then this was this one I just made the other day
just to keep this trend going.
But here, because they never went metal.
So what I made is Pasqualica, Master of Pizzas.
And this is a graveyard with many pizzas
and the disembodied hands of the master, Pasquale.
So what I'm saying is I'm going to post these on the Twitter,
but I would there's lots of great artists out there listening to the show.
More of these, please.
I don't have a catchy name or a hashtag for it.
I mean, maybe it's just Chuckie covers, just hashtag Chuckie covers.
But I want to see more.
Like if our feed could be full of classic album covers or TV,
if you have a good Chuck Feld idea as well.
And this isn't a contest.
None of these assets have to be legally clearable.
Just send like, let's all share some Chuckie album covers
since they aren't making these things anymore.
Yeah, I was also going to say like, don't limit this to great artists.
If you suck, let's do it anyway.
Your first day of art.
Yeah, please.
Like we'll see any.
Yeah, actually, I perhaps might prefer the worst or the rough draft.
It doesn't matter.
Oh, yeah.
Let's get these moving.
Let's get a listicle.
Yeah, I recall seeing I recall seeing because they had like,
you know, they had the channels you would watch.
They would have TVs playing and it would just be a loop of entertainment.
Sometimes featuring a character named mouth or.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I remember.
I remember mouth.
Very unpleasant, like fucking rocky horror mouth.
Yeah.
And I remember not caring for that video loop at all.
Because there were games around, there were big robots,
but there was this loop of comedy and then mouth.
A lot of tugging on your mom's leg.
Mommy, it's mouth.
Mommy, you want to go home?
It's mouth.
Did they play at the one I went to when I was a kid,
they played a lot of old Pink Panther cartoons.
That was like.
Interesting.
Something they would play between animatronic shows.
And that was that was probably the first time I would have seen those cartoons.
I guess they played cartoon.
They did play cartoons, but I don't have a memory of what they were.
But they would be breaks.
I remember in between.
Yeah.
Like their spot, their content.
Now it's music videos that they play between their content.
And it's like music videos that they seem to have licensed in the mid to late aughts.
Like at least 10 years ago, because.
Like real music videos.
Yeah, there's one I remember the last time I was there there.
Because they only have like 45 minutes worth of them.
And then it goes back to Vanessa Carlton, A Thousand Miles, which is a song from 2002.
Yeah, very old.
I was going to say Michelle Branch.
Yeah.
Vanessa Carlton.
I was going to say very similar.
Yeah, it was similar at the same time.
Yeah.
Who bestank the reason?
Is that in there?
That would probably line up.
Maybe.
Oh, at the movies?
The fun one?
Well, they did the smooth criminal cover too.
Well, yeah.
I don't remember at the movies.
Movies was the name of the song, I believe.
Oh, OK.
They were dressed like the Ghostbusters at it.
Yeah.
Sweet.
They would talk about going to the movies.
We had the best day dressing up like Ghostbusters.
Boy, being an alien at a farm is a dream.
Maybe they just didn't license music past bowling for soup at their peak.
Maybe they just used all his connections.
He's like, yeah, I know Vanessa Carlton.
I'll hook you up.
That's what you get when you're in business with bowling for soup.
I was watching the Tonys a couple of weeks ago, and they're like,
coming up after the break, David Byrne and Vanessa Carlton.
And I'm like, what?
What is this combination?
And they were presenting an award.
The reason is David Byrne is doing a one-man thing on Broadway,
and Vanessa Carlton is taking over as Carole King in the Carole King music.
Wow, really?
That's kind of cool.
Yeah.
I should like that.
Good for her.
I kind of like A Thousand Miles.
I do too.
Yeah.
I'll also come out.
This is going back to, I shouldn't just be equating them, but Michelle Branch.
I like that.
I want to come out in favor of that Santana song.
The Game of Loves.
I was just about to say I like that song.
Pro Game of Loves.
I'm a big fan of that song as well.
A little bit of this.
Wah wah wah.
I think I'm an everywhere man myself.
Everywhere?
I think that other one is better.
You're into me.
But I'm all right with it.
I'm all right with it.
You guys ever have hit clips?
Wait, the sense familiar?
That's not the thing you got from McDonald's, is it?
They had them at McDonald's at one point,
but it was like a little tiny USB looking thing that you could plug into a fake boom box,
and it would play exactly one minute of a hit song.
It was only a minute.
I remember each one had one song, but I thought it was a full slam.
No, it was just a minute of a song.
And we would get, because my family couldn't afford the current ones,
we would get one minute of ABC by the Jackson 5.
They made vintage ones too.
And then Sugar Ray would be on sale, so we have those ones.
Sure.
Bad news, guys.
We're pricing it down.
They're going down to $149 from $209.
Wow.
These are the things that are going to make us, that already are making us sound old.
And they're so bizarre.
Our parents were pretty clean.
We used to have records.
We would download 45 second real player clips of songs from MTV.com.
You could listen to songs in CD quality.
No, no.
We had to listen to a scratchy clip.
Scratchy Lady Marmalade.
Boy, those are the days.
You were talking about the loops.
Oh yeah, I was just saying, I don't have a good memory of those.
I don't have any fondness for them in my brain.
I think there was just too much stuff I liked better, but a lot of it didn't stick with me.
They are all on YouTube.
There is so much, in talking about tackling a Chuck E. Cheese episode,
I just had to ignore Giant Swaths of Stuff, because it would take full days to watch all
of the material that's been archived on YouTube.
It's a ton, and I would get no pleasure or enjoyment.
That is almost any of it.
Yeah, it's crazy to me how thorough the programming was at the restaurant,
at its peak, where they would make a new hour-long show every single month for a long time.
I guess this would have been post them reskinning the Rock of Fire explosion,
but there was a while where there was a new show every single month,
and then I think it went a seasonal show, and then it just was like eternal,
just the same Vanessa Carlton music video.
But they used to program new stuff all the time where they would play different songs,
and then it was just, and the Rock of Fire explosion was doing the same thing when they
were trying to stay in competition with each other.
So there's all these long ass, it's archived on, I forget what the website is,
but I think it's like a Rock of Fire explosion fan site,
where there's a lot of the hour-long programs archived.
It's that mixed media where this stuff has always been confusing, where sometimes it's puppets,
and sometimes it is people in suits, and then sometimes it's footage of the robots who you're
watching right there, but in other cases it's a robot like the Studio C Chuck doesn't look like
the one that's on the screen, and that doesn't look like the one that's outside, because that's
the Alvin and the Chipmunksified, the bowling for soup one. I swear there are
vantage points you could have in a Chuck E. Cheese where you're looking at five different
iterations of Chuck E. at once.
There's a lot of cognitive dissonance for it. I must be confusing, I remember as a kid being
like, wait a second, Chuck E. is there and moving, and then Chuck E. is also on stage,
and then you just have to reconcile with that. I feel like that doesn't usually happen.
In play, you're only supposed to see one character at a time.
Yeah, Disney is very strict about that.
That's a no-no. If you were taking a photo with Mickey and you saw him walk out of an exit,
that would freak you out.
Yeah, but Chuck E. Cheese, the second you walk in the door, you could be looking at three or four
different media.
He's on the screen as the puppet, he's a walk-around character, but there's a robot of him in the back.
There's art of multiple kinds of him, and he'll be on a machine looking different than he does on
the wall.
He's also sitting in the little car ride nearby. There's so many of him.
They could also show that there's a 40 years of Chuck E. thing they're showing now, which has
all the old clips in it. Can you imagine how confusing that would be for you as a kid?
There is a really good shirt that they were selling. If you get an XL
t-shirt at Chuck E. Cheese, because they don't make them for adults, but that will about fit me.
They had a great line of 40th anniversary merch. I got it all.
Oh, really? Oh my God, I need to look this up. Is this on eBay? Can I look at this now?
My favorite was a red t-shirt that said 40 years of Chuck E. and showed you every iteration of
Chuck E. all the way up to 2017.
So that's like 19 varieties.
Back when he was still a rat, they changed his damn species.
Oh, yeah.
They literally define him as a mouse now.
And that at the very opening of the company, I found this interesting.
It was originally going to be called Coyote Pizza, and then Nolan Bushnell was informed the
costume he bought was a rat, not a coyote. And his pitch for like, okay, we can fix this.
The name now, it's going to be Rick Ratt's Pizza.
Yeah, Rick Ratt.
The company, the board went, no, no, it is not going to be Rick Ratt Pizza.
Rick Ratt is so funny.
He definitely had his eye on a different prize because the quote he says when asked about,
why did you pick pizza to serve? He said, I chose pizza because of the wait time and the build
schedule. Very few components and not too many ways to screw it up. Now that is a man who makes
computer things talking about food.
That's a programmer's approach to a restaurant.
That is a normal way to talk about food.
Little room for error. Very few bugs.
Don't you think hot dogs would have been better?
Well, so they did serve hot dogs for a little while. And in the infamous 1991 training videos,
they show you how to make the hot dog, which is you take a sheet of tin foil, you wrap the
bun in half the tin foil, then you put the hot dog on the other half, and then you put that on a pan
and put it in the pizza oven. I have never seen a baked hot dog before. But then in the video,
they very gingerly then put it in the bun and present it on a plate with one mustard,
one ketchup, one relish, and a bag of Lay's. And it is a beautiful presentation of a hot dog and chips.
Beautiful presentation.
Ray has never uttered until this moment.
Right now they're really pushing their salad bar, which I would not recommend.
I would recommend the lunch buffet. They're trying to basically make it like a Panera bread
with a dance floor where they have solid Wi-Fi now. They have coffee all day. They're putting
in electrical outlets to encourage. I think that's the new soap opera sports room. It's like,
oh, you can come here and do your stuff while your kids are losing their minds on the dance
floor or whatever. But they have a daytime Monday through Friday open buffet for eight bucks.
That's decent. The salad bar, don't touch it. Scary.
Does the buffet have pizza in it then?
Yeah. It's like pizza, cinnamon sticks. There's a couple different options. And then you get a
drink with it and then you just refill until there's too many families there and you start
to get uncomfortable. I shouldn't be here.
But it did seem like on their earnings report or company history, they're trying to get
adults without kids. They're trying to get that arrested development kind of older millennials.
And remove the robots out of their minds?
That's what I don't get.
That's the reason an arrested development person would... Look, there's fucking lines for
four hours to get into a brand new bar with a robot performing called Oga's Cantina. That
should teach him something. Maybe just what they need to do is invest in better robots.
I want to see Chuck and Munch and Pasquale and Helen and Jasper with all of the super hydraulics
of Rex.
So has anyone seen this 30 minute commercial for the endless salad bar?
Yes, the ASMR video.
Yes, it's a yoga ASMR kind of new age thing. And it's 30 minutes long.
I am aghast. My mouth is wide open.
Weird that companies are getting into ASMR now.
Yeah, it's a couple years. So I'll play a couple... I watched a few minutes and honestly,
I was like, well, kind of funny.
It's cute.
Yeah, it's kind of cute.
Are you done crunching?
Chuck E. Cheese.
This is all of us tonight. We have the sound of sleep we've ever had.
Listening to a peaceful voice talk about Chuck E. Cheese.
They just switched the advertising company that they work with. So I think that they're
trying to be like a fun brand now that will like, I don't know, what was the brand that
threatened to commit suicide or something?
Oh, I know what you're talking about.
There was a brand that, yeah, said that they were going to...
Stakehams is very online.
Stakehams did something...
Rebbes was talking to somebody.
I think it was Sonny D.
Sonny D. Yeah, Sonny D was like, I don't know how many more days I'm going to have like this.
Yeah, Sonny D was like extremely depressed.
Yeah, and Hostess was like, no, come on, we're here for you. And Wendy's... It's a dark world.
Darkest timeline.
Oh yeah, Sonny D said, I can't do this anymore.
And Round Table Pizza wrote back, kill yourself.
Pop Tarts replied.
Jackbox replied.
Everything, it's Crest replied.
I hate...
I like to imagine that as two people in the same office just like logging. They're in different
hoot suite windows just tweeting each other.
Just reading passwords.
Uber eats at few occasions.
Having a breakdown through brand accounts.
Moon Pie replied.
That's what I'm thinking of, that Moon Pie's got involved.
Oh God.
What's happening?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I miss when it was robots instead of...
Yeah.
Snarky people.
Bizarre live corporations yelling into our pockets.
I appreciate that Chucky has remained fairly uncool consistently throughout the history.
Yeah. Their attempt at cool was he skateboards and even then has a helmet and pads that restrict.
He's such a nerd.
He's so safe.
Skateboarding in the very flat parking lot, like mile long parking lots that are next to Chucky
Jesus.
The most dangerous version of him was the grifter rat.
The cigar chomping...
The joysy.
The cigar guy.
The joysy rat.
Yeah.
Yeah. Ricky. What's his name?
Rick Rat.
Yeah. That was a scary...
Here I am, Chucky Cheese.
I've realized that the voice of that early Chuck that I do is...
Or that we were both doing...
Is it Jay Leno?
Yes.
Yeah.
Precisely.
But then I was thinking about that and realizing there's some crossover there because think about
it. He's like the entertainer traversing the country. Every little podunk town, he's there.
He's entertaining people. Another guy comes along and it's thought that maybe they can
coexist.
Oh, right, right, right.
And then he crushes the other one.
Right.
Sends him packing. He's not around anymore.
Billy Bob just wasn't selling the pizzas.
That's what it boils down to. He wasn't bringing in the numbers.
Fats just wasn't as good of a bandleader as Munch.
Chucky Cheese hiding in a closet to listen in on the unification talks.
That's the way they had to rebrand him into this little child skateboarder mouse.
He could not be an entertainment sleaze.
But Billy Bob's a family guy. I wish him well. Do you want to put me on the marquee?
I guess. All right, I guess. Okay, I'll do it.
Yeah, I'll do it if you want me to come down. If you want, look, it's not up to me.
I'm around here.
I hadn't thought about it that they're exactly the same.
They're this. Exactly the same.
Equals Chucky.
Real quick, back to the food. My sister was the only one in the family to ever have a birthday
here. And it was a breakfast birthday because I think it was cheaper.
It was a little cheaper because most kids did the same thing.
I think one friend had a McDonald's birthday and it wasn't even at a McDonald's with a play place,
which was insane. So you just went?
Of course. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It was still McDonald's. It's still the best place
other than Chucky Cheese or Discovery Zone. But I was just going to say the breakfast was
just French toast sticks.
That doesn't sound bad. I'd rather, if I'm going to eat there, go with something they can't really
get wrong. But was that just like cut a pizza with syrup on top?
It was just, yeah, no cheese. It was just crust. Crust sugar.
The salad bar prep videos from the 90s. There's a very funny moment in one of them where they're
like, here's how you cut this and here's how long you can leave these out. And they're like,
and don't forget the garnish. Use lots of kale around the containers as the garnish.
It's all these wilted looking vegetables and then giant stalks of kale, a food everyone now knows
and has strong opinions on. But that was the most healthy thing was the garnish.
It's all this kale. No one's eating it. It's just there for decoration.
Love it.
Also that garlic, they would brush everything with this garlic spread and the how to make it.
It's like, take your jug of liquid margarine. If I walked into a friend's house now and was like,
why do you have margarine in the fridge? I don't think I've ever met.
I love the demos of how to put the costume on.
Oh my God.
You just watch a bunch of teenagers struggling with it. They're like, keep the head clean,
which certainly has never happened. Clean with 409.
Yeah, it was 409. I wrote down some of the instructions when we find them.
Oh, great. I'm on the website looking at jobs.
Please, by the end of the episode, you get hired. You do a virtual chat interview while we're talking.
All right, she's a general manager.
Oh, entertainment experience. That's great. Our middle name is entertainment.
To clean Chucky, 409 or similar cleaner should be used on the face, hat or toes.
Any upholstery cleaner like Woolite should be used on the fur. When you put Chucky away at night,
spray a little disinfectant in the head to keep it fresh. Hands, vests and body can be machine
washed in cold water at the lowest setting. Vests can be air dried.
That never once happened. No one kept the head fresh for the next person to wear it.
It was good that most of the stuff was machine washable, except at the very end of one video,
they're like, Helen's dress must be dry clean only. Everything machine washable except this one piece.
Also, like putting a big mascot uniform in a washing machine. Could that keep it looking good?
Like that's not a place for something like that. Yeah, I don't understand like where.
What's a big enough. Whose job is that to do? Do they have them backstage? I'm guessing.
Oh, yeah. Go to the laundromat.
We're taking. I think it's laundromat. Yeah. And sit on top of the machine for a while.
Insane. So in those same videos, in the 90s ones,
the guy hosting them is a guy named Todd Horchner. And I watched a bunch of those.
And then I watched a video from 2007 and I did a double take because the guy in the 2007 video,
it says Todd Horchner. And I'm like, he looks 20 years younger. He looks younger in 2007.
And then I found his LinkedIn. He was the head of training at Chuck E Cheese for 25 years.
So he was a company man. He stuck it out and looked great in the 2000s. Now I think started
his own consulting company. I got a little taste of Todd Horchner and Munch interacting.
Oh, fine. That's that regular guy. Hey, Todd.
Yeah, yeah. Just a loud man.
What do you prefer, do you think, with Munch's character?
I think I like loud man. I think so. I agree.
Like you expect it's the first choice to go me want pizza, but.
And that's still pretty grimacey too. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. You could go the other way where he's like dumb and slow.
But yeah, I kind of like, yes, Todd, more information, please.
You should voice Munch. Yeah, come on.
That would be an achievement. Yes. How do I audition for that? Are you on a part of the
website? Are they hiring for Munch right now? I was looking at jobs in Irving just to see,
if there's any creative positions open. It looks like they're filled right now,
but I'll wait it out. The first time I went to Chekichi, because I originally went
as for a goofy piece I was writing when they first made that kind of tone deaf bizarre
announcement that adults can go alone now. So I was like, all right, I'll go. And I went to
one at the Eagle Rock Mall nearby, and that is a studio C, which I didn't even know what that
meant then. The days of ignorance. I was a fool. But Obama was still president. It was wild. But
I went and I met because I was, you know, like one of the it's mostly like nannies and kids
and then me. And there was a guy there who was troubleshooting the arcade games because it
wasn't super busy. And then he did a little bit of maintenance on the animatronic. And he was like,
an older guy seemed very friendly. And then like spotted me alone. And like, you know, some clock
me. I was like, Oh, what is going to happen? And then he just, he just left a fistful of tokens on
the table. And he was so, and this was like right before they switched from tokens to play passes.
So tokens were still 20 summer 2016. So I guess I was ready about this for a full year anyways.
The the and then I ended up talking to him for a little bit and his job was to to do maintenance
for every animatronic in like the bottom half of California. Like he there's so and he'd been he'd
been working for Chuck E. Cheese for I want to say at least 15 but possibly longer. He had at one
point been the manager of the Chuck E. Cheese in Vegas. And he was just like the stories I could
tell you. And it was like, he is like, it was too much. I like he left the state. It was too much.
And yeah, they allowed gambling at that one. I really want to go to the Chuck E. Cheese in Vegas.
It's a little off the beaten path. So I didn't get to go. They should do like how they have that like
Taco Bell Cantina. They should do a Chuck E. Cheese on the strip. Like with a bunch of fun,
colorful drinks. Margaritas. Margaritas. No kids. And then the class in the classic and then like
Rick Rad in there. Yeah, so fun. Maybe bring Rick Rad back. People would like that. Yeah, if this
brand was smart at all, they would at least in one place like have a destination like old school,
like using original assets, original videos. We know they have all of it. And it's Vegas is the
place I think. Hell yeah. Vegas is the place for you. Taco Bell is like starting a hotel. Yeah, I see.
Yeah, I'm down. Are you trying? I'm gonna try. I signed up for email notifications. How much is
it? It's like a regular hotel reservation, right? Comparable to Palm Springs. It's like $2 a night.
$300 a night or something. Oh, that's a lot. Well, you know, put on a credit card, see what happens.
Yeah, money isn't real. It gets paid for by someone. Actually, but it's in the middle of August.
So that's off season for Palm Springs because it's technically so hot. So I guess you're paying a
little bit of a premium for the pop-up aspect. Right. Yeah, but seeing like really good working
animatronics is unlike Disney Universal is rare. They had, was it last year they had
the Rockafire with Deadpool, which I was conflicted about. Yeah. But it was like, yeah, I mean,
they only had two songs playing, but to see really well, like working, Billy Bob and Mitzi was there
too. Yeah. But like then Deadpool, of course. But it was good. I was like, whoa. Like, so just if you
saw like pristine Chuck E. Cheese characters, classic looking characters, that's going to
trigger something in your child brain. But it's got to be originals and Chuck has to be in the hat.
Bowler hat, vest, red. He has to be shady. You have to be suspicious of him. That's the fun. Cigar.
He's poisoning his lungs. You have to feel unsafe around him. Yes. The Neil Hamburger style tuxedo,
like wrinkled tuxedo. Yes. If he were a human man, you shouldn't trust him. You wouldn't want to
spend time around him. That's the one I want. The Rockafire explosion. Also, they had like another
weird encounter with like a questionable, but they did. They did something with CeeLo like during.
Yeah. CeeLo. Right. Right. Right. Yeah. And they're in Keanu. The. Are they? The Kean
Peele movie. I didn't know that. It's not much of it, but they're like in a warehouse with them.
So. Gotcha. Well, they'll pop up in various things and there's been a couple of music videos,
Mayor Hawthorne, one of my favorite guys, did a video with them. And it's never clear whether.
I guess there's multiple ways you can either participate. You can get Aaron Fector involved,
the inventor, or you can go to one of these places like in Mississippi where a guy is just
keeping a perfect replica of one. Our friend Doug Jones went and had a very bizarre time.
We talked about that in an episode, but. That's so cool. Yeah. So they're around,
but so what's it? Well, maybe we should talk about that copyright thing. A lot of like if you watch
the documentary, if you watch the documentary, the Rockfire Explosion explains all this. And
there was also this really good podcast recently, Slate's Decoder Ring, the name of it. And they
broke down a lot of this stuff. But so the the divide, we were starting to say Brock is the name
of the guy. Robert Brock. Robert Brock, who was like going to he was like a holiday investor and
he was going to open a bunch of Chuck E. Cheese's. Yeah. And Fector started getting
ANSI to like get the contract and maybe have his own original band put in instead of Chuck E.
Cheese because they were more experimental at the time. They'd have Dolly Dimples, the hippo lounge
singer. There'd be weird other stuff. We don't even talk about the king. That's all we'll talk
about. We still have that to get all that stuff to get at least read some descriptions of characters.
Yeah, but yeah, but so the base history, Brock breaks off with Fector, makes a new place,
show biz pizza place as opposed to Chuck E. Cheese pizza time theater. And these places end
up in a bitter competition. Immediately gets sued. Yes. Right. Right. Yes. And it's like over two
years of them in court before it's settled at the peak of both businesses. It's tons of money.
Insane. And they would open down the street from each other. Yeah. It was, it was a war.
And there was a solid two years where both businesses were turning a profit. And then,
you know, that's stopped. Because they wore each other into the ground. They opened at an
unsustainable pace and were suing each other. They both built each other up to just immediately
collapse because there was just hollow cores. So there was, it hit a breaking point where the only
way is to propose a merger of the two businesses that were, that had been suing each other.
So what's so strange is that Chuck E. Cheese was first show biz pizza ripped them off,
but show biz pizza kind of swallowed Chuck E. Cheese. Yeah, they were in the better state
financially when the merger happened. But Chuck E. Cheese had the brand recognition. So keeping
the band made sense. And there was a time, a la Leno Conan, we tried to coexist.
One can do the 10 slot and one could do 1130. And they, so there's ads where it's Billy Bob and
yes. And you would go to the restaurant and not know which you were going to see.
So an unbelievably confusing brand. But what an exciting time. That would have been so cool.
You know, like you, I would be like, oh my God, it's like a different, it would be so,
it would be thrilling. Yeah. Yeah. Would there be just two show biz pizzas, like in the same half
mile from each other? Maybe you went, but one would be Chuck and one would be because ours was show
biz first. And then they obviously rebranded to Chuck E. Cheese. I don't remember. Do you guys know
these yours was showbiz first? Yes. I don't, I don't ever remember the rock fire being in there.
I never saw them. I don't think I ever saw them with them until like a decade ago. Yeah. Mine was
a pizza time theater that had the other rooms. So it also had my, the one I grew up with had the
King, the Elvis, the beach, Bowser's the musical and, and the Beagles, the dog Beatles. They all
at various times were in my childhood. That's unbelievable. Jamie, do you remember? I'm trying
to figure it out. I show, I show biz pizza closed forever a few months before I was born. So I
definitely never went, but I'm trying to figure out if my location was ever, I don't know. Yeah.
I want to, okay. So mine was a show biz pizza in Brockton mass. A show biz pizza was at the
West gate mall. They turned it into a Chuck E. Cheese. Oh, the area grew too violent. No more fun.
Oh, that's what happened. It closes entirely. Yeah. I guess, well there's, yeah, one of my,
like the, another childhood one of mine became part of a dead mall, the fall broke mall, which
now is back together, but became an empty. Oh, thank God the mall is okay. Yeah. Did yours ever
recover or is Brockton? West gate mall is, is yeah, no West gate mall is alive and well. My brother
worked at FYE there until that closed. So my Chuck E. Cheese, I only remember Chuck E. Cheese there.
I never remember show biz pizza, but for a while it was like a real catnip for me because two doors
down was a comic book store. So like good report cards come around. I'm like, like a pig and shit.
And then the comic store closes. Chuck E. Cheese keeps going. When I'm in high school, a different
better comic store opened there. And the day after my senior prom, you know, everyone's still hanging
out. Like we too far away from the beach. We were like, what do we do? And that's some, some that
weekend to the consensus. Let's go to Chuck E. Cheese. So we went to Chuck E. Cheese and this is,
this was how cool I was. I was like, can I sneak away to the comic store for a little while? No,
I probably shouldn't. Should I sneak away from my friends to go look at comic books? No, I'll just
keep hanging out at Chuck E. Cheese. That's fine. So you didn't do it. I didn't do it. No. What a
choice you face. What a choice. Yeah. So I had my eye on the prize. It was really like focused on
high school graduation activities. I'm like, I got my driver's license. I guess I can come back
to the comic store another day. I'm on the retro pizza zone boards right now. And there's someone
who visited a lot of Chuck E. Cheese's in the early 2000s and writes a very depressing description
of my Chuck E. Cheese in its last. This is not how I remembered it, but I'm sure this was an adult and
they had a more objective perspective. But they said, I visited once in October 2002,
Brockton. It was very, it was a part of a mall. It was very tiny. To say the least,
my mom was worried about driving to this particular location because Brockton was not a town she was
familiar with. And she said it was considered a tough city. I visited and was disappointed in the
store size, the condition of the show, a two stage so tiny that the characters were crammed together
literally on top. That is true. Munch was almost dead except for a slow head twitch. Helen's mouth
was shut and her eyes were closed. Jasper's back head was on the stage with his hat dangling off
and Pasquale only moved his mouth. So I guess it died a really slow death.
Pasquale had signed a document saying unplug me if I, my wish is to not be kept alive.
Is there a good resource for all the Chuck E. Cheese's that you're looking at?
I'm just on the retro pizza zone message board. So I don't know if there is like a pizza zone.
I think that that's the website that does most of the archival stuff of the old shows and stuff
like that though. I think that this is about as close as it gets. I think I had searched that site
to find out that the Northridge location was a pizza tie or as they say, like yes, Northridge
was a PTT and it became a phase three. Like there's all this crazy terminology, which I'm
happy to know now. I'm sorry about the decay, but in your mind, none of that's true. They're all
more alive than ever and a child's brain processes trauma in wild ways. And I remember it being,
you know, a little small, but beautiful describing a town in Brockton, Massachusetts as a tough town.
I just imagine like whitey bulger waiting at the city limits. Like you're coming into my town.
I beat up the Chuck E. Cheese. Be careful. Brockton mass rules. People are the haters.
They're just, they're just upset. Yeah. Retro pizza zone is called the city of champions.
Rocky Marciano is from there. Wow. Yeah. We got a 50 foot bronze statue.
The 50 foot Marilamon row and pump spring. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's a long distance relationship,
but they make it work. Yeah. Ups and downs, ups and downs.
So the two chains are coexisting, but at a certain point it comes to a head and there can only be one
and partially because they own the copyright to the Chuck E. Cheese characters, but not to
the rock of fire. And they offer Aaron Fecter a deal, which is let us take, let us take the
characters because there's no other plan and we give, we'll give you nothing for it. And at least
that's how he describes it. And he was, he just thought it was a raw deal and that he was going
to do something else with the characters to keep them alive and that they would have a life in
movies or TV. And so he said no, which just led to that all of the rock of fires were dismantled
and turned into munches make believe band because they, because they were not, they were still the
pizza time players. Right. Right. Right. Phase three as my store was described is when they
became full bodies, no longer in the frames and all of the characters. So like Fats Geronimo is
at the keyboard. He was stripped of his gorilla pair and turned into munch. And Mitzi becomes
Helen, which is a really disturbing one because she's like, she's got like breasts. It's weird.
Like when they, when they strip her down, like, like the skeletal version is really bizarre.
It is very, cause it cuts off after the titties. It just is like titties and then skeleton.
It's very, very jarring to look at. It's somebody's like really bizarre erotic art. I do feel like
there are like nipples too. I think they like for some reason, like, or at least very pointy breasts.
Sure. Yes. You're just like, what, who you can, I have a guess at the gender of the designer.
It is insane. A lot of body horror themes on the show.
Yeah. Will Smith, Jeannie. What is the, what is phase five?
I don't know offhand. Cause I'm, I was phase five. Yeah. I was phase.
You're all about to witness a great becoming.
In phase five, they all like on fire. Yeah. In phase five. I show you my true form.
Yeah. Streamwood was, was the one on Barrington road. Streamwood.
Yeah. That's the town. What a weird town. That sounds like a one season Fox show about a town
with a lot of secrets. Wait, phase five circles of light. Do you know what that means? No,
that sounds like Chuck E. Cheese kills God. Like that sounds like.
Me now. I got the pan. I got to figure this out. What does that mean? Circles of light phase five.
I think I've seen like a lot of light shows that like, I don't know why they think like, yeah,
kids want, want dance floors and light shows. It's like kids always like robot, like robots
haven't gone out of fashion. I don't know. I think the kid that the consensus was with like,
it sounds like they thought that the robots that were there were scary to kids and which is like,
not unreasonable. And that it would have been too expensive to replace them with better robots.
Sure. That's probably right. I was more scared of the walk around characters,
but I'm wondering how much ground did they lose in the late nineties to laser tag slash go kart
places? Oh, that's a good point. I don't know. There's, I've heard Nolan Bush now that he did
an episode of, it was like a business podcast. Oh, is that how I made this? I think it's called
or I don't know why I have a lot of money. No, he's, he's with, he's with us. Okay. I think this
came out like last year, but I think his, if I'm remembering correctly, it was his working theory
that like the business slowed down because they were banking on people coming back to the restaurant
very frequently when people would only come like a few times a year for report cards. And so they
ended up losing money when they weren't making a new show every month. Cause people would be like,
well, I already know what that is. I'm not going to go. And so like when they couldn't like keep up
the hype of like, it's just not a place you would go every week. So then they started to lose steam
or that's his theory. That happened. There was just an article about that. The San Gabriel valley,
where there's a lot of, uh, uh, Chinese, like Chinese food restaurants that have been there
forever. Um, these massive dim sum places could not keep up because they were, it was, it was places
where large, uh, weddings or, or birthday, large parties was the core of their business. But then
like middle of the week, people aren't throwing events of that size. So then having to keep that
much like food and different kinds of meat on stock, like operating costs just add up.
Right. Yeah. It's just an occasion place. So they have not yet cracked having young
professionals go work there on laptops and only get coffee. They'll get there and then they'll
rue the day they got rid of the robots. I'm hoping they're still in Pasadena. I went to the Pasadena
one. They have a beautiful full band still operational. I went on my birthday in 2017,
but I don't know if it's still there. Here's my, I'm not totally sure. My pitch for that is maybe
like if you want to have us go during the day, you change Chuckie's clothes, give him, I know
it's going to be a similar face, but at least give us a bowler hat and a vest and we'll fuck,
we're idiots. We'll go right up there and see it. Why do we like the bowler hat? Uh, it's cause we
saw it when we were kids. That's all it is. I mean, mostly, but I think also it's a more interesting
feeling like old timey choice, which is always, I just respect Laudville. So that's why I like it.
I mean, that's where it all goes back to that. You know, everything's an acceptable answer.
I have phase five here, but that's like really what the newer version is called. So I guess
they're just saying that they're that it's rock and roll Chuckie at my stream would Barrington
road Chuckie cheese. Sorry to hear that. Sorry for your loss. Do we know what were the last place
to have bowler hat Chuck was? I don't think we know that. I don't know. Could there be one
in America that like kind of, they just ignored what they were supposed to do and they forgot
existed that does have bowler hat Chuckie cheese. There's gotta be some like rogue locations that
have just been forgotten even to the company. Why would we throw this out? It works. Why would we
throw it away? Cause that's all these unification, all these training. They were like,
if it's bad, throw it in the garbage. Right. It's a very, very early nineties world of plenty sort
of field. And they're not really thinking about reduce reuse recycle back then. No. At the very
least there would be maybe the old suit lying around somewhere in someone's back of their
restaurant. Yeah. Maybe international. There's, there's a lot of them international in Australia.
His name is Charlie cheese because they did not like the, uh, the, uh, colloquial, uh, version of
vomiting down the Chuck. That's more strongly there. More strongly. So they will throw up cheese.
We'd be remiss if we didn't talk a little about the full name, which is Charles entertainment.
Geez. Right. Uh, facts that apparently people did not really know. And it sort of like caught
internet fire a couple of years ago. Yeah. It was a hashtag viral story,
which they check. He cheese manages to do that every once in a while, which is another thing.
I think they're cluelessness with their own audience and that like all of the interest with
this place is like be semi ironic people in their thirties. Uh, uh, like how most, you know,
fucking marshals doesn't have stories, uh, going viral, uh, once a year, twice a year
in marshals is dreams. They're going to have to start threatening to kill themselves.
Like all the other cool brands every now and then I see a post about marshals and it's like,
look how old these truffles are, like, look how old these perishables are. I love, I love it.
Now it's so bad. Now that it's like, it's just so much exhaustion with like brands trying to be
cool that when you just see them like blowing it, you're like, awesome. Like, great. That's
what you've been doing. You're supposed to do that. Show me a listicle about like bowls. I don't care.
I, um, wait, what does the other middle name too that we haven't, uh, or the full name, uh,
which is even more delightful to me than Charles entertainment cheese, the squally pea pie plate.
Yes. And it's, but then also his origin is that Chuckie discovered him in the kitchen playing
drums on pie plates. So there's both those things. His last name is pie plates, but also
he was playing drums on the pie plates. So it's a little cloudy maybe. Oh, can it be, but also it
could be, but it is both on that has, that is Canon. So it's both, but I forgot this whole thing.
I just found, did you guys catch the pretty recent backstory of Chuckie cheese? Like another, maybe
related to what you talked about, but like I read this whole book that they recently put out
about how Chuckie was an orphan mouse who he lived in an orphanage and he would sing and he was sad
because, because he was an orphan, nobody, he, his favorite song was happy birthday. He was Oliver
twist. No, his own birthday. So nobody could ever say, I did not come across this for him. Uh,
but he taught himself to sing and every birthday was his favorite song. And he moved, he, okay.
Very, very important information. He was very good at singing and also got really good at Pong and
he won $50 in a Pong contest at the orphanage. And that was enough for him to catch a bus to go,
start residing in New York city. Why didn't he just sneak into a pipe in the bus? Because he is
a mouse. I couldn't tell you he knew, but he paid, he's a good boy. He paid the ticket $50. He went
and lived. He also really liked pizza. So he went to live above the squalies, pizzeria, and then
showed up. Like was, he was caught in the kitchen and Pascual was going to like get him, like kill
him. And then he started singing and he thought, Oh, that's well, I shouldn't kill a singing mouse.
So then he, I feel crazy saying, but I swear they put this out. Where is this? Where is this?
What is this book? I'm trying to find it. Chuck E. Cheese Pascualy backstory. I love this.
Also wait, I'm sorry. I missed something big. He grew up at St. Marinara's orphanage.
That's good. I like that. Also this is the business insider, the website where I found this,
makes the point of the book has no author.
Um, well he, he gave it to us. The book has no author. He's just passed down. Yeah. Yeah.
Um, but squalie was so shocked that he dropped his rolling pin. A mouse that can sing in my
restaurant is saved. I'm gonna make you a star. So he set up a restaurant, immediately called it
Chuck E. Cheese's. Right. It was just Pascual's pizza place. He's like, nevermind. It's Chuck E.
Cheese's now. And everybody like big grand opening. Everybody comes see the singing mouse.
He'd never sung in front of a crowd before. So he buckled everybody booed and left.
This is like M and M in eight mile. Yeah. The first time he tries to battle rap.
I mean that, I wish they kept modernizing it because we could have had a post-grips that
Chuck mile. Yeah. Somebody make that please. Um, and it's in his case, it is pizza sauce,
not mom's spaghetti. Right. No, no, I would say it's no spaghetti is available. But anyway,
people started leaving. They changed the name of Pascual. He changed the name of the restaurant
to be his name. Everybody left boo. And then what, and then he like noticed a kid and started
singing happy birthday to him late. And then everybody filed back in. It was like, ah, cool.
Let's stay here. Right. So Chuck fucked up. He didn't do, but this is a whole other.
Chuckie cheese clearly different than Rick rat. Rick rat. Yeah. 200 year old mutant.
Well, yeah. Abuses his talent. This child sweet Chuckie is that's the new,
yeah. That's the new origin of Chuckie essentially. Yeah. That's from like five years ago.
Right. Wow. I like, yeah, that there's some sort of like Chuckie, maybe like Rick rat died in some
like freak accident and Chuckie saw his opportunity to like really sure. He took his name.
John Draper, Dick Whitman. Yeah. Rick rat is the Dick Whitman character.
Or no other way around. Yeah. Yeah. Rick rat is. Oh, we're saying he stole the story of any
invented this bullshits story. The cat or whatever is the brother who's like, it's you,
you're Rick rat. It's like, I don't know. Forget about it. Here's $10,000. Here's $10,000.
Crusty the cat hangs himself in his flop house. That's why he didn't keep being in the band.
Yeah. This is a dark re-imagined. Like if this was a movie, it would be just called Chuck.
Yeah. Why is, and maybe somebody found this and I didn't, has there ever been talk of a real TV
show or movie? Cause there's those that we watch that directed DVD or directed VHS. There's a
couple of those. A Chuck E Cheese in the Galaxy. From like what, from what like years?
There is a movie from 1999. Oh. That is entirely digital environments. That's also about an orphan
and Chuck needs to do a race in outer space to pay for. I'm trying to remember.
I remember. Medicine.
What? Sauce?
This guy is really sick.
We're going to give you a transfusion. Put sauce in your body.
The healthcare system's fucked up. We need to raise money and a race.
But so there, I mean, you're, well, you're proposing here, say what you were saying and I will
ready my material about Chuck and the, your Chuck E Cheese in the Galaxy.
Okay. Yeah. Okay. Good. Good. Yeah. Cause I'm basically like.
Longest episode ever.
There is so much content still being produced and we'll get to that. Maybe that's the last thing.
Sure. Yeah. We'll start driving.
As I found, I'll tease it now. I found a new and maybe you've, there's an album
worth of songs made in the last few years. A full, I have it on, I put on Apple music.
It's a free download off of their YouTube. And there's others, other music videos and stuff
of things that I'm also fascinated with. But for some, for a company that makes so much content
and for a character that so many people know and is easily identifiable, why would they never
have attempted to make a real TV show or a real movie? I mean, it's honestly, you just shit it out
like the Sonic movie or Alvin and the Chipmunks. Like who cares if it's good or not? Like I would,
I'm surprised that it's never happened. I think in the nineties, there was for a very
brief period and even if you could work around it, you get away with it. There was the idea of
shame in children's that are like, well, we can't, it can't be a commercial on the other hands.
So Mac and me. Yeah. Mac and me and Mac tonight. And it's all this fucking annoyed,
like all this fucking kids. Oh yeah. There's video games. Yeah. Right. There's video.
And there's, there's Chucky cheese video games as well. There's a we Chucky cheese game,
which we have to find somewhere and play. I watch a little of it. It's kind of like you're in the
play room. Like, and then there's mini games and like, it's just Chuck and Munch and kind of basic.
Yeah. But fun. They did one. Yeah. Before you pull out the music stuff, there's one thing.
There's like a weird fact about Robert Brock, who we mentioned earlier. So Robert Brock has,
there is a lasting impression that if you drive around any like major area with
office parks, Robert Brock is there present there because as we said, he was a holiday in franchisee.
He was like a business guy. Franchising things was his business. One of his business was the
residence line of hotels that was bought and is now residents in by Marriott. So you see like any
extended stay hotel, like he was one of the first guys doing that. If you see residents in by
Marriott, that's Robert Brock. His body's very nice. I hope he's burning in hell. He started a war.
Well, you're an extended stay, you're an extended stay person. Yes. Exceded stay suites. You don't
like residents by Marriott. Brand loyalty. Yeah. Let me jam through my material on Galaxy 5000.
It's just two quick clips. Really this film is kind of a proto speed racer. It's a race and it's
all digital environments. But with the component of there's some romance in this film. There is,
so all of the characters that we know, except Pasquale is a human being in this very disturbingly,
but the rest are all mascots and their mouths do move. And so- Well, like a human man, no head?
Yeah. He's just a guy with a mustache. Oh, I hate that. He looks like Captain Lu playing Mario.
Right? Exactly. Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. So it's all really strange and disturbing. They're getting
ready for a race and there is, they go to space and find a human woman who wants to mount Chucky
very badly. And there's a lot of weird like, like Chuck and Jasper eyeing this, this woman as, you
know, as she stays away and like, like, you know, she bends over and picks up a handkerchief and
they like, eh. Where is this available? YouTube porn. I think it was a prize. I think is what
how you were originally giving it away. Cool. Yes. It would know we've got enough tickets. You
could watch Jasper awful. A human. It was playing in the dad room.
On Galaxy 5000, uncut in the dad room.
Okay, guys, make sure your dumb wife's not around. There's a tastefully cut one in the mom room.
Yeah. Very fade to black. Yeah. Leave it to the imagination.
It's almost sexier that way. But the Chuck impression that I do is very much from this
and this interaction where the human woman is making Helen very jealous.
Bye, Chuckie. I was going to see if you'd come to the soda shop with me after the
qualifier tomorrow, but I didn't know that you were taken. Oh, you mean Helen?
She's just a friend. You know, she's like one of the guys. Right, Helen?
She hates that. Oh, that is so many different levels of what is that background contacted me.
I really should have prepared you for this. Yeah, she thinks that they're dating. This is
oddly akin to Mickey Minnie Kermit Miss Piggy, though the terms are unclear and the woman seems
to want to be in the relationship much more than the man. But that's like Chuck doesn't even
isn't remotely aware that they're an item. No. And it's just right in front of her like,
yeah, look at that ass. And but then cut to later, I'm doing everyone a favor by only playing these
things. These are kind of the only entertaining things in the Galaxy 5000. But then there's a
song where you get to go to the aforementioned soda shop, which is a giant space dome. And from
there, Helen sings a song venting her frustrations. And here's here's a little taste of that.
Could you say that I'm just one of the guys?
This is her hopelessly devoted to you. Oh, very much. Oh, absolutely. That's totally what it is.
Oh, my God. Could you say that I'm just one of the guys?
Oh, I love that. What is that change? What is that key change?
The phrasing is the phrasing. Let's let's bectal test this.
There's not another woman for her to talk to. Well, I guess there's human women. Yeah, they're
fighting about a man record. Now that I know this exists, I'll do a full watch and report back.
If it does, you know, it's a flawed metric. It's not perfect.
Yes, the pining for and during that song, she's on top of a space dome watching Chuck fix so
strangely proportioned computer car. She doesn't even like come to bed with her or whatever. She's
just like, I got to work in the car. Well, Jay Leno parallels. Oh, no, poor Mavis singing this.
Great. Maybe it's just watching this YouTube video every day. Why does he hang out with Kevin
instead of me? So on board for a Mavis music. I want to touch his tonight show money. He says I
can't. I know as my college commencement speaker. His whole speech was Jay's top 10 Hollywood tips.
It was a list. Oh, flagrant. That's insane. That's so great, though. That's the only way that this
parallel doesn't work is that Chuck didn't like rip off all of his material. But Rockefeller was
the rip off. But you might say they kind of did the more like creative kind of like that's what
the crazier stuff like we are really a fan. We haven't taught. We haven't talked about that,
that there are there's the community that thinks it's blasphemous when we say and I like the
Rockefeller characters, but I have much more affection for Chuck E. Cheese. But I think that
is a really aggressive statement to some fans of Rockefeller who were like there were by far the
better band. Yeah, band wise, people really stand. Yes. Well, I think that that was Aaron
factors fault, though, wasn't it? Because he was he like he had like an opportunity to include them.
But then, like I do remember some this might have been in the documentary, but he said something like
but I saw such potential in that, like he valued the IP over the invention. And that was like his
fatal mistake is these are going to be movies. So he had I do this and then there were no,
no, they just I mean, the reason I value one over the other is just because I know them. I never
get to really see the Rockefeller explosion. Videos don't really tell you everything as Doug
himself tells us. You had to have seen it. You had to be there and he to go see the band had to drive
to Mr. Rural Mississippi. That's amazing, which I guess we all need to do. I guess we need to do it.
Have but I know I think I might I might agree. I might like them more. I just didn't have them
around. They weren't there for me the way Chuck and Pasquale were. Yes, I agree. Yes. And there
wasn't a purple character, which I always like. I do. I do like purple. Although, yeah, fat seems
cool to that was probably cool in this slate podcast that just came out. Aaron Vector himself
is comparing the two and he says something like it's it truly is like, you know, because they're
similar bands. But to me, you'd have to be a just, you know, total dumb, dummy idiot to think that
the Chuck band is better. But I don't know. I guess he's like really he's yeah, he thinks you
are a moron if you like Munch's make a band more. I like that there's a Beatles Stones thing about
them. Yeah, like which it's a very much an individual or reflection of you more so than
and apparently far in the distance, an MC five. Oh, yeah. In its own little ecosystem. Strangely,
like the little cult one. Yeah. That, you know, it's like I'm more off the beaten path. Sure.
Those line up exactly. Yeah. Yeah. What do you got, Mike? Because we're at risk of a three.
Oh, yeah. I mean, there's let me zoom through here because so there's a lot of modern stuff.
We'll post we'll post photos. I do want to talk a little bit more about like Sally Sashay, but
that's OK. I mean, you can look her up and we'll do a full character study of Sally Sashay later.
She's the skunk. You know what? I'll read her bio. I'm not. I'm just saying let's be done before.
Yeah, that's fair. No, I understand. She was often. She was often. She was often called the
beauty from Biloxi and she was also dubbed the disco skunk. The character often
was. Character often poked fun at her perfume and and she was confused at how someone who would
make your ears feel so good but can make your nose feel so bad. Sally was rather sassy and wouldn't
bite back at Chuck E. Cheese's insults and defend her singing. Again, this is what I'm saying. Why
isn't Sally Sashay in the mix now? I was like, I feel like she's the more complex female character.
I completely agree. She sounds like she's got more agency than than Helen. Yes, poor Helen.
How could you say I have no agency? It's more like Mae West kind of like. Yeah, Madame Oink,
the piggy from Paris. She was a guest star. She was sultry and spoke in a thick French accent.
She was in the frame, right? Yes. Yeah. Also apparently Jasper flirted heavily with all of
these. Yes, that's yes. Foxy Colleen, the Irish lassie. The Irish lassie, yeah. She was in multiple
show tapes. She was sweet in nature and was known for singing traditional Irish folk songs.
This is this is so much erasure taking place. All the all the all the male
male band members get to stay. Yes, it's true. I guess that that's a point against the Rockafire
explosion. If they retrofitted everything, it seems like Chuck E. Cheese's had a wealth of female
characters to pull from, but only one robot with titties. Is that why they had to pick Helen?
Oh, maybe it's a practical. It's a practical reason. Yeah. Yeah, maybe because there were not
like female robot bodies. But the original Helen, if you look up on one of these sites,
now I understand the name. Helen Henney was clearly supposed to be a play on Helen Reddy,
because she was a she was a real like folk singer. She was like much like much skinnier and like long
hippie hair. So she may have been like more of a Joan Baez or something. I don't know. I don't know
what she was like and what she sang about, but I think she may have been a little more like thoughtful,
poetic. That was the idea. She was a feel like Joni Mitchell or something. Yeah, I think so.
And there was that one summer where Helen sang the It Don't Worry Me song from the end of Nashville
and everyone's screaming about who fired the gun. God. I would like to, I would love to program.
I will say I do know that reference. I know exactly what you're talking about. I know you do.
I would love to program the Chuck E. Cheese robots to sing the songs from Nash,
from Robert Altman's Nashville. You bought the band. If I bought the band. Side note really fast,
also these are robots that never got built who got left behind. Because clearly Helen,
if Helen Henney was a parody of Helen Reddy, I think they were going to make that more of a
thing that the guest stars would be a play on a character on a real singer that you know, which
always current that CEC and who could be more current in 1977 than Elton John and Glenn Camel.
That's good. I like that. I hear that new Bruce Springsteen record is real heavily Glenn Camel.
Yeah, Glenn Camel. Yeah. Bruce Skunkstein. Yeah, sure. And those there's no pictures of those.
No, those never got built. Those never existed. There was like a PR material saying when Camel
is coming. That's a let down. Imagine going back being like any day now.
Child is calling the restaurant. Like, hey, is Glenn there? The us of 1977. That sounds like it
would be like if they did like one of the live characters that that would be a two person suit
to Glenn Camel. Probably. Yeah, you'd have to one person would have to be his ass.
Gary looked in that hump. Yeah, for sure. So yeah, as I was saying before, the current Chucky
YouTube is very active. Yes. They posted two days ago, five days ago. Five days ago is when that
salad bar thing came out. Wow. Like that's new. And they are very active. There's these cute little
I got push notifications on. There's these cute little puppets they use now. And there's a lot of
there's a lot of first of all, dances. I won't we won't get into them, but they make up a lot of
dances. I think that's just a prep for the for the new stuff. Yeah. Trying to like, I mean, look,
and just the drawing, they're all so much sexier than they used to be. This is like, I mean,
they're like CGI. Yeah, those are the CGI versions. Yeah. Yeah. Current Munch is real creep. I don't
like I don't like Current Munch at all. No, boy. He's got the sonic teeth. Yeah. So let me start.
Munch is sliding into some DMs that he should not be a little too horny. I don't know.
Let me start. Let me start with this. So this is an example of one of my favorite
new Chuck E. Cheese music videos. This is called Rockin' Robot. And Chuck, look at the outfit Chuck
is wearing. Someone describe it. It's like a big it's like an open red hoodie and a chain.
What was there a style equivalent? Yeah, I'm trying to think what how you would describe it.
It's like a sleeveless sweatshirt. I'm ready to get into I mean, I feel like this is almost an
attempt at some sort of hype beast aesthetic for Chuck, which I'm ready for. Yeah, good next
evolution. Yeah. So this is a taste of what they're doing now. He does have that Xan.
This is like some Silicon Valley pro stem bullshit.
This would inspire a young Aaron Fector today.
I'm going to fast forward real quick to when the robot gets built in this video and you'll have
we'll link to this video and there it is. And the robot is terrifying. So I'll fast forward here.
It's playing air guitar or something. Do you think he dabs?
This robot has titties too. He kind of looks like the fish from the shape of water.
Oh, like with a tic tac for a head. I do like the ski board solo.
He said his dad is like twenty five.
Why did this little boy give the robot such a sculpted chest? I don't know. It's again. Yeah tomorrow's
The parents are really proud this Chucky cheese used to encourage you to go into the career of being a dirtbag entertainer
performing for kicks
Yeah, I ran a cabaret. I kind of like the
The Chucky cheese youtube channel, I I like it. I do I like it too
They're churning out content all the damn time. Yeah, it's a fun thing to wake up to
There's a lot of you'll watch new ones as they do like recall any you've seen lately all of them
They're doing some like videos with helen. They'll make comedy videos with pasquale where
Establishing shot the laffaroni
Pasquale is always headlining in hotel pizza buns. I like I mostly watch the pasquale videos
There's uh, there's a rip off of deep thoughts with jack handy with munch
Which I don't love which is a weird reference to be making
Yeah
Well, there's a show loop from a few years ago with the don parto and intro impression introduces pasquale p pizza
Uh hell in any what pie plates I want to make sure you have a new blood in the writing room
So yeah, so there's an l but that is not rock and robot does not appear on the new album, okay
Which is funny because i'm looking at my apple music in the first two it's prince's originals then the munch's make-believe band
songs in the key of
e
Yeah, okay
Yeah, yeah, that's mike in a nutshell if somebody needed to like just found your phone and needed to write a report about you
Yep, oh the third thing is patton's greatest speeches very strange very strange
Patton all right. So
You'll notice like on this. I won't play all the songs, but a lot of the songs are
Parody or inspired by like let me get here
Here
Don't stop so you get enough seemingly and then the chorus is very much like thrillers like it's clearly
Michael jackson is not cancelled in the turkey cheese. No, no, it's too hard to do this song is called. Let's have a party
This is what timberlake does
Now is he still the singer
And then we have me and my friend
Oh, hey, this is familiar
Just
They even do the ding
Just like his name
I mean, this is great. I love this. I'd rather listen to this than uh
Fucking kids bop where they like actually they take the real song right ripping it off, but they have a song by there's some innovation here
Yeah, yeah, helen has still make it its own thing. Yeah, helen has uncle helen's game in time. Oh game in time
Yeah, i've seen that video
High score
Right another yeah
Do
That's it's always a good time by owl city. Yeah
It's always a good time
So they got that so now I like most of this album is there one song I might call problematic
Yes, it wouldn't be this has been a problematic episode in a little ways. It's called dad try to order a third
It's not so bad, but maybe I mean you tell me
You tell me and you'll know
You'll know exactly what
I won't even well, I will say it. It's called another chuckie day. So here we go
That kind of problematic
Here
Head on back down. I won't stay in bed, but I found that I just came dally as my day begins
I got to be a chuckie jesus hanging with my friends
Hop out of bed like a kangaroo. I just make it through all the morning things they got to do
I brush my teeth till I get them both shiny even soaking in the bathtub is where you go
Pizza was the case they gave them
The next thing you know, I got to go because I
The guy from bowling for soups
It's reese really the one he could have gotten in there and said i'm gonna pass on that one
Yeah, I mean it and now try listening to that one bowling for soup song after like hearing any of these chuckie
It's like so him it's wild right? He's barely changing his voice, right? Oh, he was kind of whiny already springsteen
Yeah, that was yeah, uh, that's like a cousin of that boys of summer song
Right, so there is another chuckie day
Lottie dotty chuck likes to party. I have some bad news too chuckie is cancelled pasquale
Unfortunately the famous videos where pasquale teaches you how to make pizza were filmed at the chuckie cheese location
In texas in a town known as white settlement, texas
Did not change that name in the night, I don't know has that been changed maybe yeah, let me look that up
Yeah, i'm gonna roll over to white settlement
Man
Laura ingram just like nodding her head like this good it's tight
No, it's still oh my still a city in texas
Well, we ended on a dark note I guess uh, well so you talk about the fights
We talk about all the fights that happen there. Um, one of my favorite facts about chuckie cheese
I learned uh chuckie only went non-smoking in 1993
Which I guess is about when most restaurants did but in a corporate history it said they did see a drop in business
I guess
I think everywhere was slowly starting to go and everywhere did see a drop in business and then rebounded
But that was also made me laugh because that the same year they went non-smoking was also the year they introduced kid check
Which is the blacklight the hand stamp where they stamp the kid's hands and the parents hands and they have to match
Before you can leave which is there to this day, which is there to this day
Don't worry about it. If you're a lone adult you don't need to get stamped. You just get a stamp for fun. Yeah
Yikes, um, I just I like that if you
type
Chuckie cheese into youtube you get
Current cute puppet videos about building robots that are a little well done. You also get bizarre
Charisma charisma free training videos from 1991 you also get some of the scariest fights
On camera like it's such a wide breadth of content
The one I have so many clips from the fights in march a fight at a pittsburgh chuckie cheese
I don't know what year it was chuckie cheese involved up to 50 people after an argument between a one-year-old's parents escalated
Oh
There's only so many people inside a chuckie cheese at any given time which means the one-year-old could have gotten involved
Don't talk to my parents like that
Motherfucker sprayed milk in my eyes. You're trash you're trash
It's like hair yankings that are so like the fights get
Bonkers and another chuckie cheese in brookfield wisconsin two women were arrested following a mass brawl involving 20 people on july
27th the brawl was sparked according to the police by one child taking too long to choose a toy
I don't know the galaxy 5000 doesn't look good to me. It looks like it might be a problematic
Also, but then you have to with these fights keep in mind that as
Yeah, 50 people are all fighting and deep in the background the trusty munches make-believe band is performing
Like like none of it's happening. They're like
They're bar band veterans they've seen everything they don't care they're not even just especially the vegas ones
Yeah, I don't know that like good wi-fi is gonna help the idea of like
Suburban parents just begrudgingly sitting there with a strong wi-fi connection on instagram
Just like getting mad at their neighbors like I can't believe they got a boat like yeah
Gassed up, but like whatever suburban parents do on the internet. Oh, she said what I gotta go to the next door
I'm gonna do some posts on next door and citizen
There was this is my lab. This is the last one I want to read from there was an abc nightline
Story about it and it said it had become uh chuck e cheese had become a hot spot for violent brawls between adults
And they happen mostly at birthday parties police have been called to one location in pennsylvania 17 times in 18 months
Yet brockton gets the rap as the rough area
Yeah, it's ridiculous bring back the brockton chuck e cheese bring back whitey bulger at least stuff was organized
Yeah, let's bring whitey bulger back to life
Rocky marciano only fought when the bell rang
Uh, well now some towns are asking chuck e cheese to step into the
Ring amid pressure from local politicians some chuck e cheeses have stopped serving alcohol and added security guards who carry pistols
You have to have an armed man or woman holy arm the bots arm the bots
Reach for the sky
You're gonna fight me here i'm gonna give you some lead
Or yeah arm the arm the walk around chuck he's got a little gun
I wonder if they have I wouldn't I okay. How surprised would you be if the walk around chuck had like a knife?
Not at all. I would not be surprised if they had if they had a knife for their own safety
Yeah, what if he used it like to cut pizza also? Yeah. Oh that's cover. Yeah
It says pizza
For pizza for nothing else. Yeah. Yeah, that's a fine
But like walk around chuck e doing that like fake, you know would do the split sometimes do the like almost split
Yeah in those videos just like doing the split and their gun goes off
My favorite part of the walk around chuck e is if you watch, you know
Because he'll come out once every like 15 minutes or something. I'll count down to it in the restaurant
He'll come out he'll do his bit children will chase him around the restaurant and then he'll you know
I like the two seconds that chuck he thinks that he's no longer inside of the people and he drops the act
You see the shoulders fall and you just see someone like go back to just take the head off for 10 minutes
wait
Anytime
Anytime you see like a performer switch. I that's my favorite thing. I'll never forget the the time I saw
Uh in storyland in new hampshire when I was little uh, cinderella on a smoke break and that like
Fucked me up. Oh, yeah, that's yeah
And my mom was like she's just like me like she was really trying to be like she smokes misty menthol 120s as well
Oh, man
Just to give everyone a heads up if you were wondering are there posts of concealed carry advocates may
That chuckie says please no weapons in our store. The answer is yes
A right unexercised is a right denied
Says this one says munch
A right on exercise here's a here's a new story on guns.com
No
Some guys just pumping their fists a decade ago going like yes, I got the I got guns.com. Yes
For more information about my thoughts about freedoms and liberties
Wow, yeah, I don't know what a place what an evolution the pizza wars came and went before any of us were born
and
now we're left with just one hub for
Uh hair pulling and gun violence and inedible food. I wonder do we think there could be another pizza war?
Like very famously like professional wrestling is we used to have monday night wars and now there's a new company that's going to challenge them
Very soon and there's going to be more war like
Wars are great when they're not real wars
Sure, yeah business wars are fantastic fun to watch because the only losers are people who have money anyways
So it doesn't matter low stakes. Yeah, I would love I would love for there to be more pizza wars
I feel like if there was like a very modern version of chuckie cheese. Yes, cool. Like if they made it like a
Not laser taggy, but like they have all those vr experiences now
Yeah, gaming arena is a phrase i've heard a lot lately. I don't i'm afraid to inquire more
Dave and busters has been around for a long time. Obviously, that's the adult version of it, but there's got to be some way
To do a more modern version for aimed more at kids
well if we also it'd be great if there was a re schism and like we start if we
Became chuckie cheese franchisees and switched it back to the bowler hat and he's with rad now
And then that grew and other people were with us and others were against us
But there's another some of the chuckie cheeses all split and all press is good press. Yeah
Could we are you a gun chuckie cheese or not?
Well, we'll have to be a gun chuckie cheese
I think because we just have to get more people in and that'll be at a track that'll be part of it
Bring your gun put it on the table. We don't care. Uh-huh. Yeah rick raps got four of them
And then we will just go against the corporate
Mandate and change all the things and we can bring back the sky. What's her name sachet skunk? Oh sally sachet sally sachet. Thank you
Yeah, absolutely. Yes, we can just start throwing the elven sky each bowser's are back
Yeah, if we round up all the like new the the animatronic people and get let's get factor back on board. You're back in hey
Storm in the country company factors. He's still in florida with the animatronics and now he helps throw he he is a thriving youtube channel
And he has he lets people do birthday parties kids from orlandale can do five nights at freddy's themed birthday parties
The haunted animatronics factory, right? Oh, yes. That was a big resurgence for them was five nights for freddy
Yeah, a big hit. I don't know if that movie is actually going to happen or not
But it would be I feel like the animatronic they would they they will rue the day the animatronics left if that ever worked out
Right. Yeah, they'll be so relevant again
Yeah, and erin's factory is the place to make it
I mean it is pretty much doing fine except when everything exploded because he was inventing a
experimental fuel called
Carbohydrillion
That sounds like um marvel
Throw some words scary words invented carbo carbo hydrillion
Write it down. It's got to be printed an hour ago
There's a lot of there's talk now there's been talk but there's now another article a round of articles about toys of rust coming back
Oh, but there's a little talk. Yeah already. I mean everything is just a big shell game toys of rust basically
bane capital saddled it with
So much debt even though it was making money
It couldn't pay off of its debt and then everybody from bane capital just made a ton of money
Then they still own everything and they just could like it's just they're waiting for the right time to go back
So they didn't lose so much money that it's all just a business. All everyone's a big crook. Anyway
They're talking about so nobody ever lost love or faith in jeffrey
No, people love jeffrey. The only people that got hurt were the employees of toys of rust
Like the people in charge all made a lot of money and then yeah, yeah, it sucks
But anyway, they're talking about bringing toys of rust back, which I think it will
They're they've already rebranded as jeffrey's toy box and there's weird kiosks and croakers
So like what they're just already trying to get some money
So you will come upon I don't think any out here maybe but in the midwest though
You'll just see a kiosk that says jeffrey's toy box and a croaker and there's just some random toys codes for fortnight skin
maybe
but they're talking about like
Bringing stores back now they're gonna I forget there's a decent amount
They're talking like maybe by the end of the year, which I don't know if that'll happen
But they're talking about like more of a kid environment
Play area birthday party thing, which is something they did but feel like more of when we were kids
Yeah, so it's like come on toys of rust if you really want to get back in the game and win us back over let's get a
jeffrey robot and some of his friends that we may never have heard of before
That's what i'm saying
Oh, that would be so great. Yeah, and booze and guns and booze and guns. Let us drink in a toys of rust
Like a whole foods. You can take a glass of wine toys of us on this newsmax article complaining about places that don't allow you guns
Toys are us right above chuckie cheese
All right, no more trampling on liberties
Oh
Oh, yes, thank you and hey
Thanks for like, you know all your articles on it are are great and so fun to talk to you about all this stuff
um, anything that makes it feel worth it
Your dark time the dark days of 2016 17
Yeah now and it results in a very dark podcast
Um, uh, hey, let's exit through the gift shop. Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Oh, uh, you can listen to the bechdel cast. Uh every thursday. That's on iHeartRadio. It's a feminist movie podcast
I host with my friend caitlyn dorante
Um, if you happen to live in scotland, you should come see my show at adan bro fringe this summer
And uh, yeah, that's it
Great. It's gonna be great. You're gonna be a star
Yeah
Awesome, yeah. Well, thanks so much and you can find us go to go to twitter once again hashtag chuckie covers
I really like to see some of those subscribe to the second gate at patreon.com
Podcasts the ride where I can only imagine there will be a lot more chuck content to come. Oh my god
Um, because it's a it's I mean this could be its own podcast the four little shavers episode
alone
No, they each get their own
Uh, uh, and uh, yeah, we got t-shirts on tpublic check us out on instagram and uh follow at topical genie
Follow at topical genie. Um, maybe we can uh, uh, oh I well I set up at if you haven't found it already
I always follow at et. Goodbye and et will say goodbye to you
and uh
Topical g goblin
Yeah, the g is gonna be hard two g's in a row
Yeah, my goal is for us to end up with the longest plug list in all of podcasting like by the end of it
You need to follow 40 things for it to be as dense and confusing as the as showbiz pizza place versus pizza time theater
Um, we're hoping to open the podcast time theater
I've got a bunch of in check out est check out. I I have the rights to nexium now. I'm rebooting nexium, but it's gonna be cool
It's gonna be you're in charge now. Yeah, I'm in charge now. It's gonna be more dance floors issue
It was a leadership issue. Um studio n is coming
You're plenty charismatic i'll get a brand to you any day
It'll be a me animatronic and then quickly a dance floor and puppets
All right, then follow vanguard aka jason sherdon
And
Uh, hey, that's it. Uh, thanks. What a blast see ya
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by mike carlson jason sherryden
scott gerdner brett bowen joe cilio and alex ramsey
engineered and mastered by alex archer
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
And subscribe to our shows on apple podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook