Five, four, three, two, one.
Happy Fourth of July everybody.
That's right, we're here.
I'm Scott Garner with Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
And it's a big one today.
We're talking Liberty Square.
We're talking lanterns and windows.
We're talking oaks that are replicas of other oaks.
Crooked shutters.
I was going, I'm going to say crooked shutters
because I also know this crooked shutters situation.
I don't actually.
Oh.
It's thrilling to be here to talk.
Someone didn't do their research.
Oh man, this is what I live for.
These guys find out about crooked shutters and I get to learn?
Yeah, that's part of the fun of this.
It's thrilling to be here to talk about the beginning of the American experience
at the end of the American experience.
Which is also a joke I may have made last year on Lincoln.
I'm not sure.
Or during the American experience episode.
You mean the American adventure episode?
Oh no, I look like a fool now.
Oh geez.
Some things got to be called the American experience.
That's the great transactions you have when you use an American Express card
is the American experience.
It's true, they're shiny, they're gold, sometimes pink.
A lot of fun.
So we're doing Liberty Square, which is an area, if you don't know, in Orlando.
It's in the Walt Disney World's Magic Kingdom.
And it is a salute to Liberty and our forefathers
and the creation of America.
It's a land based on Colonial.
Colonial.
Colonial times.
And there's a Haunted Mansion there too.
Yes, most importantly the Haunted Mansion is there in Florida.
Where the Declaration of Independence was signed and also there's a spooky house.
Yeah.
So why is this?
I guess it's that there's two things.
So the Haunted Mansion in Disneyland is in New Orleans Square.
They're probably thinking, well, here in Florida we are much closer to the actual New Orleans.
Is it redundant to do a New Orleans themed area so close to New Orleans?
This, of course, decades before a gigantic California theme was built inside California.
But they just weren't ready for that yet.
They weren't ready for the layers of meta to exist, so they had to do something else.
But also it didn't really occur to me that in 1971 we're heading for the long awaited Bicentennial.
America is horned up for the Bicentennial.
America is wild for the Bicentennial.
It's very interesting to me the history that this opened in because 1971 Disney World opens.
Nixon is president.
Vietnam is still happening.
When did Vietnam wind down?
Around then.
But like Vietnam and then soon after that Nixon reelected, but then Watergate.
So people not super jazzed about America at the time, but then the Bicentennial kind of like everyone goes all in for the Bicentennial it feels like.
I guess so.
Yeah, that is a crazy fact that when the Hall of Presidents opened, the current president they were depicting was impeached.
Or not impeached, but was headed for impeachment and resigned.
Like as the Hall of Presidents was open, the current president resigned in shame.
One of Walt's favorites.
One of Walt's favorite guys.
They took a famous monorail ride together.
One of the weird California republics.
California has created Richard Nixon, Ronald Reagan, Walter Knott.
This California streak of Republicans.
Schwarzenegger too.
Knott should have run for president.
There should have been a Walter Knott presidency.
Yeah.
Jam for all.
That would have been ridiculous back then when people had shame, when people experienced shame of like, oh, we can't do this.
That would be shameful behavior.
To vote for Walter Knott?
No, for like a industrialist like that.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Right, but now it's like a TV man.
Yeah, now it's a Huckster.
Yeah.
Now it's a P.T. Barnum kind of guy.
Well, we've come a long way.
That's the thing.
Boy, you know, think of boy, America's divided and people aren't happy about the president.
Sound familiar.
That's the thing I keep seeing places such as in the Laugh-In reunion special that I wrote to you guys about.
Boy, when Laugh-In came on, everybody's met each other, including the president.
Sound familiar at much?
Yeah, you did.
This is your fault, Laugh-In generation.
Yeah.
You did it to us again.
You repeated the abuse of your parents.
A great endorsement for the powerlessness of comedy.
The Laugh-In reunion special.
That is what they're saying though.
Like we healed the nation, right?
Isn't that what Laugh-In is implying?
Well, the special very much was all about that, right?
Yeah, and we were able to, you know, poke fun at ourselves and it.
And then they just proceeded to show a bunch of clips that were just completely racist and homophobic.
Presented as the goes, freeze speech.
Freeze speech and then totally throwing away all of their values during the like go-go 80s during the like rise of Wall Street kind of 80s.
But Goldian made some fun movies.
That's true.
It's true.
Without the Laugh-In people by leaving the fold as quickly as possible.
And not showing up in the special, right?
No, no, no, no.
She said no.
Intelligently so.
Yeah, Rowan and Martin did not have to have a producer credit on every comedy movie or TV show made by alumni of Laugh-In.
Before that system was cracked.
They made a mistake though.
They were rich.
Yeah, I mean, yeah.
Every movie Henry Gibson was in, they would have gotten a big cut of it.
Can you imagine?
Nashville.
Wedding Crashers.
The two movies I could think of that Henry Gibson was in.
That's pretty good.
It's two more than I could do.
He's great, by the way.
I, you know, while we're talking about the Bicentennial a little bit, right on my way out the door, I learned about I was like, what did Disney World really do for the Bicentennial?
And they did a parade, Disney World and Disneyland did a parade called America on Parade in 1976.
And there's a pretty good video of it, like with good, like custom sort of mainstream electrical parade-y music.
And it's pretty well shot despite being a weird old 8 millimeter.
Got kind of that red hue to it.
But it's a fun video and the parade is fun to watch.
It is mostly filled with scary dolls.
Oh my God, they're so scary.
They had them out at D23 four years ago.
Really?
A couple of them.
And I was like, oh my God.
Like human sized costumes that people would wear?
Yeah, but like sort of bigger proportions.
I should find the pictures.
Some were like, some were costumes of big puppet creatures.
It was like giant small world dolls, but with kind of more soulless eyes.
Yeah.
Like the mega pupils.
And it was pretty freaky in general, but there's this one part that I had to pull.
Kind of notable one particular way they paid tribute to America in the bicentennial.
And Jason especially, I think you'll enjoy what I'm going to play here.
Wow.
I've not seen that.
That's like a Dan Wood sandwich.
Yeah.
Oh, that's what I was.
I was trying to think groups mentioned in that sentence, popcorn, candy, hot dogs, ice cream, big sandwiches, rubbing his hands together as he watched that.
Yes, literally true.
Yeah.
I was Dagwood's a good way to put it.
I was thinking it's like the kind of sandwich of like a junkyard cat would be a governing and I have a better photo of it.
And the sandwich also factored into the Disneyland version.
Here it is in front of the Matterhorn.
Look at that thing.
Wow.
Mega sandwich.
If I could describe it for the listeners, it's the 11 layers.
There's like a full egg in it.
Entire olives, pimentos, just dripping lettuce and cheese.
What does this have to do with the bicentennial?
Well, in that justification, it's American food.
This is somehow the most American food.
Giant sandwiches are really American?
I mean, I get hot dogs, ice cream.
That all makes sense.
But do you go to a cookout and get a giant sandwich?
Now, wait a minute.
The official meal of America is a hamburger, fries and a soda pop.
Right.
Like that's the official thing, not represented in this.
But not an 11 layer sandwich.
A really narrow sandwich.
Maybe a very long sandwich, a better way to present a big loaded sandwich
than one that's impossibly tall to bite and it's going to topple over.
What's the most amount of layers you've had in a sandwich?
I think mine is just a club sandwich, bread, some meat and cheese, bread again,
meat and cheese, lettuce, bread, three breads.
And that's it.
That's the highest I think I've ever gone.
I think I've only done a third bread, yes.
Jason's got something about this.
You could not have set me up for this better.
So Dagwood, beloved comics for character Dagwood,
is present in Islands of Adventure.
In the early days of Islands of Adventure, I believe it's still there,
the Dagwood's restaurant.
And when they first opened, they served a big Dagwood, like a sandwich of that size.
Was it 11 piece of bread?
I think it was like six, maybe six layers or something.
And I saw it in the window and we were like walking by.
It's like, oh, we could go here for lunch because everything was still new at Islands of Adventure.
Yeah, you played that real cool.
We could just go here.
I was like, look, the big sandwich.
I was so excited to like the big sandwich, like in the cartoons you get to eat it here.
That's when we were talking about Blue Milk and stuff.
That makes total sense to me that you would have been reading Dagwood your whole life
and you were imagining eating a sandwich.
That makes total sense, unlike the Blue Milk, which I still think is strange.
To immerse yourself in Dagwood's world.
What does a Dagwood taste like?
But like in Looney Tunes and stuff, they would make a sandwich like that and then they crunch it down and shove it all in their mouth.
Joghead. They've all eaten a big sandwich.
So I was like, OK, this is going to be so great.
This is going to be great.
Edwin was startled by the fireplace, which has turned off.
He's fine, folks.
He's fine.
It's not bad, yes.
So I got it and I went to buy it.
Like because you can't eat that.
Like you think it was truly necessary.
You think it was truly a tall sandwich.
What's in there? What's primary ingredients like deli meats?
I don't think there was sardines in it.
I think at one point they did it with the sardine like the fish was sticking out.
And I just remember a couple of bites and I was like, oh, this is bad.
Like this is maybe the worst thing I have ever eaten at a theme park.
Oh, no.
It was so bad.
And I think it was just probably just loaded with onions in the way that like raw onions on the deli sandwich can just overpower everything.
Like it was just a bummer.
And I like I did not finish.
I ate it because it was hot and it was hot.
We're hungry.
The whole sandwich.
No, I didn't finish it.
I like kind of picked it up.
OK, I see what you're saying.
It was like I got a club sandwich once in the famed Carnegie deli now gone, but it was Jewish deli proportion.
So it was like a club sandwich that was the normal look of club sandwich unwieldy.
Yeah.
Like a heart like a quarter thing of lettuce in there and so much bacon and so much Swiss cheese and turkey.
Like you have to it doesn't function as a sandwich.
It's a salad.
You have to pick up a right.
And you don't you can't like choose your own bites and you can't choose.
It's incredibly complicated.
That's why I like the best thing to order is like, well, just pastrami on bread or brisket on bread.
Much much superior.
So maybe that's where the mega sandwich comes from.
Maybe it's more of like an old time deli thing where it was a taller sandwich.
And that's an exaggerated version of it.
Yeah, possibly.
Or just like like, oh, I'm at home.
It's time to make lunch and watch the game.
I'm going to get really indulgent.
Like moving his fingers around.
These kinds of sandwiches we're describing are mainly for sitcom purposes to be like stolen by a mischievous Olsen-esque toddler.
Or dad, dad, dad, if forgets to eat it, it just goes right into his nap.
He doesn't eat the same.
He makes the sandwich.
Yeah.
But then he's such a tuckered out dad.
And then there's like a gerbil or something in the house that he doesn't know is there.
And that steals the same or like if you're say if an alien has recently landed and is starting to live in your house, he might he might steal it.
Or it's for a character that's the best friend of the main character.
And he's trying to eat the sandwich and he goes, come on.
He pulls him. He takes like a bite.
But then he takes a bite of the air and leaves the sandwich behind.
That's good.
Yeah, that could be another situation.
Or just if Jay Wellington Wimpy wants to switch it up one day.
Is his first name Jay or is that just Jay Wellington Wimpy?
No, Jay, period.
Well, I don't know.
I don't know.
I just saw it written down recently next to his picture.
I was like, I forgot his full name is Jay Wellington.
And Wimpy is his last name.
Yeah.
His Christian name.
Oh, his last name is Wimpy?
Yeah.
I thought that was just a nickname.
Wow.
Huh.
So he's called Wimpy like if somebody was just calling you Carlson or.
Right.
Wow.
Well, we got to figure out what the Jay is.
Well, that'll be a whole episode.
Figuring out.
Figuring it out.
The multi-part cereal type.
Does this does the mega sandwich in the parade look appealing to you?
It does.
Yeah, that one looks pretty appealing.
It does have the fish on the top level.
It does have the fish head.
Let me ask.
Let me before we get back on track to Liberty talking about Liberty.
This is Liberty.
Would you be okay if they turned Magic Kingdom Castle into a big sandwich?
Yeah.
Why do you?
How do you even have to ask that?
I'm thinking about I'm just saying like.
How okay would you be is really the.
Cake.
I would be.
Spires are toothpicks with a little colored foils on top.
Okay.
And it'll be a just.
It'll be a bunch of sale.
It'll be different stacks of sandwiches.
Ice cream towers are all fish heads.
Maybe.
Or pickle spears.
Oh, that's better.
This is almost easier than the ice cream cake castle or the cake castle.
You're describing more of a platter.
The castle will be more of a sandwich platter.
It's yeah.
It's a graduation.
It's a high school graduation party sandwich platter.
Can we get Chapek on the phone for the 50th to turn the Magic Kingdom into a sandwich
platter to turn the castle into a sandwich platter?
I mean, they've got art in their archives of like sandwich float.
Right, right.
They know how to build a big sandwich.
This has been accomplished by Disney.
Yeah, they never throw out ideas.
In fact, that's a great transition back to Liberty Square, which was originally going
to be an offshoot of Main Street and Disneyland called Liberty Street.
Yes.
Which ended up in a Liberty Square at the end of Liberty Street was Liberty Square.
So it would have been both.
By the way, I want to go all the way back, but I can't let the big sandwich float pass
without saying that it was trailed by a little tiny mustard jar that followed it around.
That's really great.
That's wonderful.
The little bugs in the Main Street Electrical Parade.
Okay, anyway, back to Liberty Street.
I was just going to say instead of Tinkerbell going to the castle, it's the mustard jar
going toward the sandwich platter.
That's good.
And then dumping out onto it.
There'll be some effect and it'll dump mustard on the sandwich.
Just yellow glitter.
Sure, fine.
Could you dye the lagoon white so that it is like the big sandwich castle is soaking
in mayo?
Yeah, yeah, all right.
Sure.
Delicious.
What if it's mayo with the ketchup mayonnaise so it's reddish and white?
Mayo chip?
Thousand Island.
Thousand Island's fine too.
Spread.
Chipotle mayonnaise?
Chipotle mayonnaise.
That's good.
That has the pesto mayonnaise.
Yeah, you got a lot of options.
Maybe dye it something to change the sauce up once a month.
Yeah, for sure, for the whole year, for that 50th.
You can think of 12 different sauces suitable of the castle sandwich.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
And we, if they don't feel like thinking of them, we'll do it for them.
Yeah, we'll do it.
Bob Chapek needs to let us know.
Do we have to talk about liberty?
Liberty state?
After all that, I'm like, now I'm looking at, now I'm staring at my notes that contain
the phrases one nation under God and Johnny Tremaine.
So let's talk about this real quick.
As children, what were your feelings about America and all of this stuff?
Because Walt was a big American history buff, very proud American, and I think many people
of his generation felt like that.
Not that I don't, I'm very lucky to be living in this time and in America or whatever,
but we don't, I don't think, feel it like that anymore.
And as a kid, I think I was kind of paying attention to American history.
I know the basics, but I wasn't gripped by it.
It wasn't, and it was the sanitized version of it.
It was the exciting one where we were the heroes in most of the stories.
I wasn't being told the nuanced version.
The victors write the textbooks.
Right.
Yeah.
But I think even as a kid, I was just like, yeah, this stuff is okay, but shrank, shrank.
Crank and shredder are more, I combine the two of them, which I think that actually they did
that once in one of the comics, but they didn't call them that.
I was much more like, these stories are interesting.
There's turtles walking around, but I was like not engaged in Paul Revere and Johnny Tremaine.
That's probably the story of generationally is we all, like this whole generation rejected
religion and history in shows, comics and Star Wars.
Yes, it is.
I guess that is part of the downfall, I guess, of America, too.
These are our heroes.
I grew up outside of Philadelphia, so all of this stuff is background noise to me.
Like you just made you less into it because it was just around all the time.
It was just around.
I'm sure it would have been much more novel if you did not live in the Keystone State,
if you did not live in the cradle of liberty.
So because that was the easy class trips into the city is 20 minutes outside the city.
So you kid up the Betsy Ross House, the Ben Franklin House, Independence Hall.
Now the Constitution Center, the Liberty Bell, which you didn't used to be able for a while after 9 11.
A lot of this was locked down.
And now they've kind of opened it a little more open it back up again.
Yeah, I think they were going to like, yeah, we're going to blow up the you could just like push these places over.
Well, for years and years, you couldn't go into the head of the Statue of Liberty.
Just yeah, for a long time.
And so and then we for like shorter trips, we would go to either like Washington, D.C. or New England,
colonial plantation, Plymouth, Massachusetts.
I've been to Plymouth, Massachusetts, colonial Williamsburg.
So I got a lot of it.
I got a growing up.
You're like like like sneak a kiss or like hook up with somebody in one of the monuments.
What do you think?
Was there even like a was there like a high school like a handhold in?
I did. We did do like a four or five day trip when I was a sophomore in high school called Close Up,
which I think a lot of schools have some variation of that either the school individually did it or combined.
A few different schools would go into a Philadelphia trip.
I think people I've talked to grew up in other parts of the country would do like four or five days and hit like New York,
Philadelphia, Amish country, Washington, D.C. would just bang out all of this.
Sure. Yeah.
But I got very little of with the California of like the missions and stuff.
I'm assuming you got a little. Oh boy.
I'm assuming you got missions.
I definitely. Yeah.
I don't know. I don't think I think I have somehow avoided missions better than other.
And I never had to build one.
That was a big thing. That was building missions and like the Michaels type stores around here do just off sell mission kits,
which kind of defeats the purpose of inventively building a mission out of sugar cubes or whatever.
Yeah, I would have been super jealous of you.
I loved all this America shit in middle school.
I was reading this kind. I had like a big coffee table book about Jefferson.
Right. Because the presidents. You love the presidents.
I love the presidents. Yeah.
It's made everything so heartbreaking.
The last few years, it's really, you know, the way the way I revered them.
It's yeah.
I mean, I liked it to a certain extent.
I just got a lot of it. Yeah.
I just got a lot. Right.
A lot. It didn't spark anything because it was always there.
It was around. It was always there.
I did not like classic rock. Yeah.
It was always around. It's a Beatles.
But it wasn't until later that I was like, oh, this is the classic rock I specifically like.
I mean, all of it is very fascinating now.
I find the very like nuanced American history fascinating, I think.
And I was some smart kid who was like, this isn't the right way it went down.
I didn't know. But I mean, it's it is a little homeworky.
Yeah. This section of Disney World is especially Hall of Presidents is homework.
Yeah. Like the American Adventure in Epcot,
I think is a better representative of the American history because it's so weird, because it's so like weird.
As these little scenes, it's not just like it's not a long list of names and some of them sort of forgettable names.
Yeah. I'm just trying to make sure I don't forget anything, because I know I've talked about that.
I cried and cried when the American Adventure was not open because I wanted all this homework stuff.
With the first time I went to Disney World, I was going to say my mom poisoned me,
but she poisoned me with education, with like knowing things.
And then I've, you know, pushed all that out of my brain via beer and wine.
But I was psyched on all this. I was psyched on my Philadelphia trip.
I think I've talked before about when I went to Philadelphia and there was like this movie that played at the museum.
And then my mom looked up what the movie was and got a copy in the gift shop and then sent it to school with me.
Have I told this before? I don't know.
Forgive me if any listeners if I have.
There was a movie that played in the Philadelphia Independence Hall area.
And there was this very dull 70 millimeter thing where the ghosts of the past returned
and John Hancock in a smoky alley is telling you about there was a dispiriting air that day.
And like it was this weird. I've looked it up since it had a lot of the great actors in it.
I don't think the movie was just called Independence or something.
And we really liked it in the museum and my mom bought a copy and sent it to school with me to play in school.
And then it was introduced like and this was brought in by Scott and his mom.
So let's thank them. And I did a little like snooty like you were like, yeah, hell yeah.
I got a shout out from the teacher. Did they go on a Philadelphia trip to the rest of the class?
No, no, no. This was a family trip. No, yes, because I had you see this was sent back to school with me in the fall.
Make sure you have this video played. And it was I don't remember who any of the actors were.
But truly it was like like imagine just imagine all the actors in Amistad like Pete Postle Thwait and like the you know these old guys
in starchy uniforms and speaking poetically about the mists of time.
And this was forcibly played in a classroom and I was proud that I got it.
So you should love Liberty Square. Therefore, I should be jacked up about this episode.
I don't know what happened. I don't know when I turned. I guess I don't know.
I got into things you're supposed to be into.
One more thing, because I did since you set up Dorky, if I'm the one that liked history,
another childhood memory I have is that there was a movie that came out called Jefferson in Paris that was about Jefferson.
Like, I don't know, he took a trip to Paris and he like hooked up with a bunch of women or something.
Yeah, Jefferson and Franklin. That's the stuff they gloss over that they were like whoring around.
Sure. Oh, my God. They also they were wild.
Sally Hemmings was always presented as like and he had child with a one has a worse term.
Yeah, this is not a like coincidentally, a nice relationship.
But what did you like? You're very young. Probably. I would imagine like 13. I don't know.
That's wrong. Maybe I don't know anything. Jefferson in Paris was a film.
Oh, this involves Sally Hemmings. Oh, yes. It's a really sultry cover.
Nick Nolte plays Jefferson. And I remember I was excited that there was a film in theaters that was Thomas Jefferson.
But then I found out it was about his love life. And I remember saying at a family party.
Yeah, I mean, it's cool that it's about Jefferson. But like, who cares about his love life? Oh, my God.
And then a bunch of parents laughed at me. How old were you? Like 10? This is 95. Wow.
This was what I was like at 10. That's so great. I was the biggest wiener in all of America.
I don't know. I was trying to master the Dick Van Dyke falling over an Ottoman.
That's cool. Honestly, that's closer to what I was doing. Probably, too.
Don't forget, I was also imagining scenarios where I became the CEO of where I became Eisner. Oh, wow.
We should get it. If a time machine event was invented, interviewing you at 10 for this episode would be so great.
If there was a way. Oh, can I hear? Can I just say the movie is called Independence?
It was made for this Philadelphia Museum, directed by John Huston, starring Eli Wallach, Pat Hingle.
Whoa. Mayor Gordon. Mayor Gordon, Pat Hingle.
I think what happened is I had all this in the tank for our American Adventure episode and then didn't get to it.
But here you go. Now you can hear my thoughts about how much me at 11 loved seeing James Tolkien,
eventual principal Strickland in Back to the Future playing Thomas Paine.
And E.G. Marshall did a great job narrating. We got to do a Patreon on this.
Look up, if you're listening to this and care, look up Independence 1976 and look at what a dreadful, what a deeply dark, depressing film this is.
I want to do that Jefferson movie, too. Yeah, I never saw it. In looking it up really quick, it has a young Gwyneth Paltrow.
Gwyneth Paltrow, one of her first goals. Wow. Lots to look forward to in Jefferson in Paris.
As a French lady of the evening? I think possibly, yes. Oh my. Man. Of course it's abound.
That's good. Wow. Maybe 10 year old Scott wouldn't have liked it.
It would have turned you off of American history forever if you had seen that scandalous film.
They were good men. They were chased to their wives as they signed important documents.
Another theme park connection to this American history tangent, a place I've been a lot.
Gettysburg, the Gettysburg battlefield visitor center with a essentially circle vision movie in it.
And I believe was getting upgraded. But that was one in the Boy Scouts. I hiked all 13.
There's a trail, a 13 mile trail, and they give you like a big patch at the end if you complete the whole thing.
Also up there, Dwight Eisenhower's farmhouse. That way he didn't.
I guess that was his kind of summer home was a farm in rural Pennsylvania.
Yeah, so that was and there is an Amish farm as well with like where they serve you family style and stuff.
It was Illinois so it was a lot of Lincoln for me. And we saw there was a little, I forget which town it was in,
but there was like a house Lincoln lived in and there was an animatronic Lincoln in the basement.
What? Really? Yeah. So that's like the one memory I have of being like, oh cool.
Lincoln was pretty cool. Look at this fucking robot. We definitely got to cover all the regional present animatronics.
Yeah, I wonder. It would be interesting to see the history of it. My recollection of it was that it was good.
Like it was in a junkie one. Yeah. But who knows? Maybe it was bad. Not as weird as that recent Garner Holt.
Oh, the one with like the overly expressive cartoon face? Yeah, that they made kind of, you know, make as I'll say, kind of an O face.
Yeah, and I also saw that at D23 four years ago. I've seen that in person was like, have we gone too far?
Now, so in the the unbuilt Liberty Street was going to have technically have the Hall of Presidents.
They talked about this in the 1950s. Animatronics did not come along for a while.
So if you can imagine one way to make the Hall of Presidents worse, what if they didn't move at all?
What if they were just haunting wax statues with audio played over them?
I would be like, it was going to be mostly silhouette for sure.
And then there was the second possible attraction. They are one nation under God or no, that was the one that was the show in the Hall of Presidents.
But then there was the other one nation under God, the Hall of Declaration of Independence.
Two of's in a title. No, not the Hall of the Declaration of Independence. Right.
Yeah. So what did we get instead at the end of the 1950s? The Matterhorn, the moderate and the subs.
We got one stuff. Important decision in theme park history.
I'll say this. That really started the course.
Walt was a little indulgent about America. Not as bad as Walter Nott.
Walter Nott came from the movies and I think that helped him realize that you did need to entertain people first.
You got to put butts in the seats. You got to put butts in the seats.
Yeah. And he got to hang out with Nixon as a result of the Mario opening.
And speaking of Walter Nott, you do get kind of a vibe at Knott's Berry Farm of what that original Hall of Presidents might have been like,
because you go, there's a replica Independence Hall weirdly across the street at Knott's Berry Farm.
You go past the TGF right at his and the peanut store.
If you've hit the water park, you've gone too far.
Yes. The water park is right next to the Independence Hall and it is the area is full of terrifying geese.
And you go into a room where you watch an animatronic free Independence Hall show that's where candles light up in the places where all of the people in the
where all the signers, I guess, where the signers would have been.
Is that what it is? Like, I think so. Their position in the in the room.
So if you go, these people shall be three quarters of a person.
I guess that's the Constitution. I guess that's the no, no, no.
Take it down to two fifths. I say I'm getting a call from an unknown number in Anaheim.
Who do you think it could be? Whoa.
Whoa. Chaypeck.
Honda Anaka. Does he have a mission for you? The Lincoln animatronic?
Maybe it could be any of them. I'll see if they leave a message.
Mike, I need your help.
The you know what I did like historically, I like the twists on American.
I like the musical 1776. I did like I guess the book Johnny Tremaine is not much of a twist, but I did think that was an engaging book and I had to read it for summer reading one year.
But in Philadelphia, at some point, they're like, we got to get more people out to these fucking things.
What do they like? Ghosts, the ghosts of the revolution.
So there was nighttime tours, nighttime tours of the houses and stuff and like sightings of ghosts.
So I did a thing like that in Colonial Williamsburg, another play of Cherished Childhood Trip Colonial Williamsburg.
Yeah, there was a yeah, that a ghost tour as well.
I don't remember much that happened, but but you get to watch candles get lit.
Sure. Yeah. Right. A horse with a ghost.
Or Plymouth Plantation. We all got like a cat like a lantern, a metal lantern with a candle inside to walk around the streets holding.
Oh, wow. My mom, that's so much. She bought one of them.
It does feel like if if Walter maybe had combined the Matterhorn with the Hall of Presidents or something like all the presidents are all along the Matterhorn and you get to zoom past all of them.
Like people would like the president like like American history more.
If you combine the thrill ride with some actual facts, Paul Revere's ride like a Paul Revere's nighttime ride ride.
That'd be great. Yeah.
I don't know what would be appropriate housing for the presidents.
Would have to be an American mountain. What's in America?
Good point. Oh, yeah. Like Rocky Mountains or Rocky Mountain.
Rushmore would be oh Rushmore would be great.
A big, big Rushmore. And then it's like you take a roller coaster through their mouths.
Yeah. And you go back in time and see every president along the way.
Yeah, that'd be good. Like, yeah, something like that, I think, could have combined Walt's love of presidents with something much more exciting for the youth of today.
Yeah, because right now the Hall of Presidents is I would say in Orlando, the most homework, homeworky ride.
Right. Now, why do you say that as opposed to American Adventure?
What makes it duller? Is it the fact that it's mainly a list of names?
I think it's a yeah, it's mainly a list of names.
A couple of speeches. I mean, American Adventure has an army of robots that are doing stuff different like different scenes.
Yeah. Climbing stairs. I think it's a better structure, Joe.
It's a tableaus form that's pretty exciting.
Yeah, tableaus. It's fascinating how it works.
Yeah, yeah. Hall of Presidents is just a it's a movie for a while.
Yeah. Right.
And then you and then curtains lift and then you watch a bunch of mainly men staring, old men blinking, nodding, turning slightly, like fiddling with their fingers.
I get that it doesn't sound very exciting.
I think it was better before the current president got to speak because there is no perspective.
You're lumping in a current experience with history where at least a few decades, not a couple hundred years have passed or a hundred years in the case of like.
But you but also, I mean, is it easier to say that with there being a current president robot that we don't like?
Like, wasn't it? I found it to be a pretty neat novelty that the current president was talking and recorded a thing you can only watch in this room at a theme park.
I mean, I wasn't super jazzed to see George W. Bush speak.
No, certainly not. During the war.
And now I know everything that was wrong with Clinton.
But when you're a kid and you just like presidents, obviously, I did you.
Did you guys not think it was neat to hear Bill Clinton talk?
I'm trying to really remember because I don't I don't remember registering that big of a I probably thought it was kind of cool.
But I don't remember. I don't have I can't access that memory if it exists.
Yeah, sure.
I was just like, oh, yeah, there's a president like as a kid, I don't this Liberty Square area didn't register very hard with me to the point where like I didn't remember the geography of it when I went back for the I had been I hadn't been to Disney World since I was 18 and I went at 28.
And I was like, oh, OK. Oh, the honey man is right there.
Yeah, it is.
Like I don't remember where everything was.
And I go, oh, this is like the colonial era. Got it.
OK. Like, it really like.
The diamond horseshoe is technically in Liberty Square.
Not Frontierland.
Yeah, it is interesting.
I was reading about how the edges of Liberty Square, like as you you start to head towards fantasy land like Columbia Harbor House, the restaurant starts to get a little more European in design.
And as you start to head towards Frontierland, it starts to get a little more western.
There's like transitional points from colonial to the American West.
I was trying to realize we've like oddly covered a lot of this area in a way.
You know, you start getting really the closest thing you hit from Liberty Square heading to fantasy land is the tangled toilets.
You right.
And we've talked about the Mike Fink keel boats.
The Mike Fink keel boats.
Haunted Mansion, obviously we're covering slow motion.
We'll hit you with part two in October.
Hall of Presidents, I guess we have and we'll do a full separate Hall of Presidents.
Yeah.
We'll talk about Trump's arrival in there.
But mostly stuff being removed.
The keel boats are gone.
The Admiral Joe Fowler sailing ship is gone.
Yeah.
Was it a sailing?
Was it like a riverboat?
I think they were both Mark Twain.
Yes.
Right.
That's what I read.
Yeah.
There were two Mark Twain's essentially and they were named.
I have it down here.
It was.
They were named after.
As opposed to the beloved author.
Right.
They were named.
These ones were named.
And then there was a former US Navy rear Admiral who was in charge of construction
at both Disneyland and Disney World.
And then who was the other one?
Richard F. Irvine.
A stern wheeler named for a WED executive.
So yeah, not as fun.
That one was renamed then to the current name, which is the Liberty Bell.
Yes.
Yeah.
And there's two things you can do in Liberty Square.
You can see the Liberty Bell, B-E-L-L, which is a bell.
And you can go on the Liberty Bell spelled like Bell the character.
Right.
And that is a boat.
Bell and a boat.
They're both called Bell.
Yeah.
Two Bells.
Did you read what happened in the first one?
The first Mark Twain?
Yes.
Describe it please.
I have it.
This is just from the Wikipedia.
I'm trying to.
I like that you are just referring to riverboats as Mark Twain's Kleenex tissues.
Yeah, it's a brand name.
It's a more effective term.
Hold on, let me see.
Yeah, okay.
It was retired after less than 10 years of operation and it got accidentally destroyed
after falling from a crane onto its dry dock.
So a crane just accidentally dropped this poor ship and broke it.
Fucking owned.
A big like old timey wheel just like crushed like a house of cards.
Jason, are you not more upset about that?
I mean, you know, I think it's...
One of your beloved steam ships.
They got one.
We actually in Florida, they got to the old Fulton's Crab House that is now called Paddlefish.
That is technically a riverboat.
Oh wow, that's true.
Yeah.
So.
I ate there last time.
Is that a docked boat?
I think it might be mostly building.
Yeah, I don't know that it ever sailed.
But very nice.
I had a great meal there last time I was in Florida.
I had a good little...
Yeah, I forget what it was, but I got something good.
Do you have any particular opinions about the Liberty Bell versus the Mark Twain?
I can't...
I'm wondering if it was down for a pair.
I really don't remember.
It was the last time you were on the Liberty Bell.
I was last in Florida, last in Disney World 2012-2014.
I don't know if I got on that.
I definitely will if I go back.
One of those trips I did at Eat at the Infamous Liberty Tree Tavern that conquered Michael.
We've covered that also.
We've covered that quite a bit.
There's little pieces of Liberty Square.
We talked about the Bell Bell.
Did everyone come across the anecdotes about the Liberty Bell they have in Liberty Square?
Yeah, there's a lot of move on from the Bell Boat without saying that you got to go on this thing,
because in 2018 it got a brand new boiler.
So get your ass on the Liberty Bell.
Fuck.
So with that being said, let's talk about the Liberty Bell.
Go ahead.
But not the...
There's a lot of misinformation.
What I found was there's a lot of misinformation about this Liberty Bell.
We're going to clear it up.
So there's been a lot of fucking replica Liberty Bells over the years.
There's so many.
There's one in Wana Park at Nott's by Soak City.
There was a massive influx of them in 1950.
Counterfeit Liberty Bells.
They made a bunch to promote a campaign to buy savings bonds.
That's what it was?
Like Liberty Mutual?
Someone.
I'm not sure if it was a government or a bank.
It's confusing if it wasn't Liberty Mutual.
A bunch were cast in the 50s.
Okay.
Now, the one that I kept seeing on Disney websites, the anecdote I kept seeing was in 1976, for the bicentennial, every state got a replica Liberty Bell.
Pennsylvania famously already had a Liberty Bell.
The first one.
Duh.
And so the others, that one was gifted to Walt Disney World to use.
Is that what you guys came across?
Yeah.
I read a lot of things with a lot of attitude that was like, everywhere got a bell and then Pennsylvania realized, we already got a bell.
Why didn't you guys take the bell?
It's a little too perfect.
I don't think that is what happened.
Yeah, it's not.
It's not, right?
No.
That story's too cutesy.
That story is fake.
What do you mean?
Why would the whole state not want two bells?
Why not?
Right.
You would take two bells if you had them.
Yeah.
What a weird rule.
The bells are fucking everywhere.
They're in state houses.
They're in college campuses.
They're like.
They're giving away.
We could get a bell if we wanted.
I bet we could get a replica Liberty Bell.
From the mold.
End of the week.
By the end of the week?
That's tomorrow.
There's a holiday.
Yeah, the holiday.
Fourth of July.
Yeah, that's going to hold us up.
Everybody's ordering Liberty Bells.
And everyone's horny for Liberty Bells.
That's peak.
That's like, you know, a lot of Jack O'Lantern needs in October.
A lot of Liberty, a lot of full cast iron Liberty Bell needs in the Fourth of July.
We should wait for mid-July.
All right.
Mid-July we'll try to get our hands on a life-size Liberty Bell.
Everyone's ordering Comic-Con stuff.
Okay.
Where are we storing it?
That outside your patio.
Here?
No, I was going to say at the foot of your bed.
I just got a storage out of it that I really like and I really would prefer to keep double
it up.
You're the only person whose place doesn't have stairs unless I'm wrong.
You've got to take a couple stairs up to get to it.
Well, still the least of us.
Probably.
We'll just got to roll the thing.
It's going to get a lot of cracks by the time we get it to its resting place.
Or everyone can sleep in it.
We'll put it on its side and then we can use it as a dog bed.
That sounds nice.
So do you have a real story?
Do you have a real like how the Liberty Bell got to Liberty Square?
I think it's just like they ordered it.
I think it's like not even.
I think that's right.
I don't think it's a fun story.
They ordered, well, in fact, their Liberty Bell was installed on July 4th, 1989.
This very 4th of July, 30 years ago.
So happy 30th anniversary to the Disney World Liberty Bell.
Enjoy that celebration.
Happy 20th anniversary to Carlos Smooth featuring by Carlos Santana featuring Rob Thomas.
20 years.
Really?
20 years this week.
Yeah.
That's something worth celebrating.
Now that's.
I also have that the bell, if you hit it, it's an E flat.
The same key as smooth.
Probably don't look it up.
Yeah, don't look it up.
The oral history of smooth was excellent.
I don't know if you read that.
Oh, where is that?
I forget.
I wish I could credit the place, but look it up.
The oral history of smooth was fantastic.
It really gives you a lot of context for how a hit song is made.
Rob didn't even want to sing it or he was he was just going to write it.
It was going to be a big bolster of the songwriting career and he was suggesting George Michael sing it.
A whole different animal.
That could have been a real comeback for George Michael, right?
Yeah, he didn't really have any hits.
Kind of lying low after the arrest.
Yeah.
He wanted to give that he wanted Mick Jagger to sing that the song disease and Mick said Mick just wrote a verse and said, I don't want to sing it.
Oh, really?
Yeah, he gave it back to him.
Where else would it be?
Rolling Stone, baby.
Rock and roll.
If it happened 20 years ago, Rolling Stone is on the scene.
There's another anniversary that I forgot to say on this particular July 4th.
Another nice clean one.
It was July 4th, 2009 to exactly 10 years ago that animatronic Barack Obama made his debut.
Happy 10.
Barack Hussein Obama.
You always make a point.
I just think I just know you got to.
The robots middle name is that too.
This was back when the current the sitting president recreations were just inaccurate rather than ghastly.
Other than monstrous and Depardieu esque.
I have a question about the Hall of is the Hall of Presidency one attraction.
I feel like we've talked about this in conversation lately off mic, but is that the one attraction they can't get rid of in Florida?
Are they is that just a curse?
No, I think my feeling was that they could get rid of it, but it would have to be like six months before an election.
It has to be strategically timed.
Even now, I think it would feel loaded.
Now would feel loaded.
But I think I think if you do like six months before an election and as long as it's like, well, we don't know who's going to win, then they can just say, you know, wash our hands of it.
I think it would be great publicity for Disney to get gift for free each animatronic to that president's presidential library.
I think that's an easy fix, right?
That's like that's I mean, then they need like a program or they need somebody to maintain it.
But they would get so much shit for like stripping cutting heads off and then putting them as like the luggage checkers on Star Tours.
Yeah, yeah.
Like, hey, did you know, you know, actually, those animatronics, that's Lyndon Johnson's checking our luggage.
Yeah, you know, that war burns voice, but it's in Lyndon Johnson's exoskeleton taft taft.
It becomes Oogie Boogie.
They finally do Nightmare Before Christmas down there.
That's actually not bad.
They should just do that.
Like I should all be stormtroopers on the new rise of the resistance.
Yeah, we can add 45 stormtroopers.
We're just like oddly shaped stormtroopers.
Different heights.
But all nail.
So Carousel of Progress.
Put the president on the Carousel of Progress?
No, no, I think all the presidents Carousel of Progress are the ones that like we can't really get rid of these for different reasons.
But I could see them in a few.
Well, I think this is we didn't talk about this at all really on the show.
There's been some rumors lately about classic attractions being changed or removed.
I think they like soft test out the idea of removing these things every once in a while.
Oh, and I think I yeah, I think I think they sort of try to gauge a reaction.
I do think Carousel of Progress, they can't get rid of anything with the 50th coming up.
I do think right.
I think you've got to keep Carousel there.
But I think at a certain point they would love to get rid of all of these things.
They would love to get rid of Tiki Room, Country Bears, Carousel of Progress because they don't people.
They're not packed.
If you ever go in there, probably hard to maintain, hard to maintain, old time robots.
Yeah.
And it's like, why do we even do that?
I guess history and they're not as popular as pirates and on a mansion.
Sure. So they see the idea of what if we removed it?
They give it to a website which goes on several bizarre rants and threatens and blocks everyone on Twitter.
The most volatile website.
Yeah.
Yeah, to test the water, see what happens.
But you know, that said, that website has assured us that their regular column, like here's some shit that's broken.
Here's some pictures of shit that's not working is coming back.
I'm also poking fun because like, yeah, somebody probably told them that rumor and there was some truth to it and whatever.
Just be like, hey, I post rumors. It's OK.
Yeah.
I post rumors when once in a while the rumors, they change because stuff changes.
A little too crusade, a little too Woodward Bernstein.
Yeah, it's fine.
The truth, you know.
If you didn't know about the story, this website like posted, they got so defensive because Disney specifically said there's been some unscrupulous websites issuing rumors.
That's fantastic. I would love it if Disney blasted us.
No.
Sure.
Wait, all press is good press, right?
You know, how often does a fan site get fucking owned by the company that they cover?
If Disney were to put on their blog that they will not be turning the Magic Kingdom's Castle into a sandwich platter.
That is a rumor that was started on a Patreon only podcast called Podcasts The Ride.
That is not true.
I would we would be thrilled.
Yeah. So let's say here now that we were playing around with like, what if we invented that idea?
We have we have totally 100% confirmed Disney will be turning.
We'll never be proven wrong.
That's fine. One of our inside sources knows Bob Chapek and they were eating a sandwich with him and he goes, hey, here's a little bit of inside info.
We're going to turn the Magic Kingdom into a sandwich platter.
We turn the castle into a sandwich platter.
And people don't like it.
Fuck them. It's a sandwich castle now.
That's true. Yeah.
I hate my fucking fans, said Bob Chapek.
The only thing I hate more is these dreadful parks.
We're going to burn them all to the ground one day.
Build condos and smelting refineries.
Coal mines pollute the air.
That's well, that's what Bob Chapek says.
I wish he would respond to us.
So a couple of little design features of Liberty Square.
One, a friend literally what I said we were doing this told me this an hour and a half ago and I had it made total sense as soon as they said it.
But I was still surprised.
There is a replica sewage trough like in the street.
There's a brown sort of divot as a nod to history when people would throw their feces out the window into the streets and would drain through down this trough.
And there's only one bathroom in the land, technically.
There is one at the Harbor House as well.
The street?
Yeah, you could have to shit in the street.
You're allowed. You can just go take a crap in the middle of Liberty Square.
Liberty Square, in case you didn't know, the only land in any Disney park where you're allowed to shit in the street.
Again, totally true.
Totally true.
Disney themselves told us this is fine.
Bring it on, blog. Deny it if it's true, if it's false.
So yeah, the only restroom is in Liberty Tree Tavern because you have to legally have a restroom in there.
Because it's a sit down restaurant.
And the Harbor House is on the outskirts of, even though it's technically part of Liberty Square, it's on the outskirts.
So they were trying to be accurate and not have a restroom.
Weird. Who cares? They also have coke slushes.
Like none of it's accurate.
Yeah, I had to diet coke with my too much meal that I ate at the Liberty Tree Tavern.
Columbia Harbor House, usually one of the better reviewed restaurants.
I feel like my family liked it. It's a fish house. Fried fish and chowder and stuff.
I haven't had that.
Switch up from the burgers and fries that kind of everywhere in Florida.
I really like Sleepy Hollow. It's a waffle themed stand.
Oh yes, we had a waffle.
Waffle sandwiches. Delicious.
Yeah, and I'm looking at the menu. They have something called a hot dog pretzel pocket.
They shove a hot dog into sort of a pretzel roll.
That's American ingenuity at its best.
But Franklin himself would be proud.
I don't want to just backtrack entirely, but I really, I don't know if we stated enough the fact that it is a big brown stripe that is ebbing and flowing throughout the land.
It just looks like a regular ground pattern, but discovering that it is representing...
It's sewage. It's early sewage.
That in colonial America with this charming architecture and with Thomas Payton walking around, that there would have just been shit flowing in the streets and then raining down from windows up above you.
You'd just be walking around and somebody would dump their shit on you.
Anyone who romanticizes this era is insane.
Ten year old me, somebody should have told me back then, keep in mind there was shit in the street, human shit everywhere.
If you traveled back in time to that, you would just be immediately vomiting because of the smell, because of the awful smell.
Yes, and none of them would be because that's normal to them.
Yeah, so yes, your first move. Would you like to see colonial times come with me?
That's what any time some weirdo far right maniac is like, well, we should take a lesson from Percy Thompson of the Massachusetts colony.
It's like, these motherfuckers, how much soap did these motherfuckers ever touch in their lifetime?
Like, really? Like, how many lessons should we take from these people who didn't know about medicine?
Yes, yeah, and the gun debate, certainly.
Let's remember what those guys said who walked around in their own shit and their friends shit and family shit.
Yeah, everyone died at 50. Everyone had like a knife on them at all times.
Except for like the founding fathers. They all lived in their 70s because they were doing well.
A lot of them did.
Because they were like landed gentry. They sat inside reading and just like coughing up blood all day.
Was it like a taboo though if you were like sitting in like Ben Franklin's house and you're talking to him and he like had a shit bucket full of shit?
Would you like, would you keep it in another room or would he say, I must excuse myself for a moment to clean or to throw the shit bucket into the street?
Like how do they deal with it? Was that something that was just, well we know that's around and that's not a big thing or would it be like they...
I mean he was such a hedonist. I have no, he would probably just do whatever he felt like.
Well I mean not Ben specifically, but I mean like in common courtesy of others, was the shit bucket held somewhere?
Was the shit immediately thrown out when it was made?
I think that there were a couple things going on. I looked into this a little bit.
Okay, thank you. Good. Because I just was thinking of these questions now.
It never occurred to me that there was not sewage and the colonial times were full of shit.
I can actually tell you specifically about Benjamin Franklin.
Because if you go to Benjamin Franklin's home in Philadelphia, as you did many times, there is a hole in the ground called his privy spot.
And it's marked and called that. And so that, yeah, he had a shit pit.
So he had a shit pit in his house.
It was outside. And then there's another pit marked off right next to like a couple feet, just like six feet away, not even a person's length away.
And that was the well. That's where he got his drinkable water from. Look at a picture of it. They were so close.
He was a notorious drinker too. There has to be a...
He definitely got the mixed up.
No, no, I'm saying he was a little out of his mind and he took a shit in the well.
That's what I'm saying. Most likely or had no choice in the way if you're really sick, maybe you like, oh no, I threw up in the sink.
Right. The well was closer and he threw up. He'd vomit in the well and then drink water from the well.
Did he ever comically stumble and fall into either? Had to. 100%.
He had to. 100%.
Upside down and got stuck like Winnie the Pooh.
Oh yeah. What was there every time when he fell maybe?
Thomas Jefferson had to come draw a face on it.
Thomas Jefferson is like a rabbit in this instance.
Yes. Oh dear. Oh, you've done it again, Ben.
Franklin tumbling into the well drunk, gets up, cleaning himself off, trips, falls backwards into the shit pit. Has to have happened.
Pops out and goes a penny saved, is a penny earned.
The leaders of my almanac would love to hear about this amusing tale.
Wait until they hear about this in the almanac offices.
I will say something about Ben Franklin. I think as a kid I was amused by him in general. I felt like he was a fun character.
He was fun.
Whether he was full of VD or whatever. I didn't know that at the time. The book, Ben and Me, I liked.
Oh, and the movie. The Disney cartoon.
Yeah, yeah, with him and the mouse, little mouse friend.
Yeah, voiced by Sterling Holloway.
Yes.
So he sounded like Winnie the Pooh.
How about that?
Sterling Holloway is one voice that was all of our favorite character. All of my favorite characters.
Yeah.
Fitch, Hitcher Cat.
So, so yeah, Franklin.
We thought of him as like, he was like America's Santa Claus.
Yes, I think that is probably right. I thought I was like, oh, I like him.
Bumbling, robust man with a lot of inventive ideas.
Right.
Who talked like this for sure.
Well, I have to give him credit because I'm sure other people back in colonial times had servants or when you crossed the Mason Dixon line, slaves to just clear out their chamber pots. So like took care of that.
Sure.
Oh, so you give him credit for not making a slave take his shit somewhere.
I.
Lindsay is questioning the Mason Dixon line.
Yeah, they all had slaves.
Oh, in his era.
No, no, no, they still did. I think they abolished. They stopped having slaves.
But that was later.
It was much later.
I was not a history major. I was a television major.
So I can tell you that at one point, Dick Van Dyke had a opening credit sequence where he it seems like he's not going to trip over the Hasek.
The Ottoman.
Oh, I see. That's your recovery on this.
That's my recovery.
I see. There's a line in his house that he was hoping to not trip.
Anyway, he trips over something else.
I see.
Yeah. Well, you know, he stubs. There's a couple versions. Actually, I know the answer to this too.
There's one where he like side steps and then like trips on the carpeting.
And then there's one where he doesn't do that.
I believe there's one where he survives fine and it kind of plays on your expectation.
Like seasons went on.
And then there is one where he sidesteps it and falls right into someone's shit pit.
He's covered in shit.
Yeah.
Splash.
And Rosemary has to pull him out.
Still in the 60s. Even if you were a successful television writer, you probably had a shit.
Yeah.
Right in your living room.
You know, in fact, I was also it also made me think what was going on in the White House and the White House.
OK, George Washington did not live in the White House.
John Adams in John Adams is time he would he had to go to an outhouse.
The first sitting president had to go outside in the yard to an outhouse to poop.
Thomas Jefferson was the first to say, how about water closets where we can fill up the pans and then throw those out?
And there were two of those.
Right. And there were not there was likely no running water until Andrew Jackson and no flush toilet until Millard Fillmore.
Wow. What was film or how many presidents in his hey, you know, 1516 something.
No, Lincoln 16.
Lindsay knows.
A divider between slave states and free states as of 1781.
1781 was the Mason Dixon line.
Franklin alive.
Franklin still alive.
It existed.
There was a line, but it wasn't have slaves above it.
Right.
OK.
Well, I will read the thousand page Thomas Pynchon novel Mason Dixon to get caught up on by Mason Dixon.
I was look, I was in the history as a kid and then not for a long time until yesterday when I learned about President Toilets.
And President Toilets is who I'm throwing my support behind.
2020 the heir to the toilets.
Fortune.
Yeah.
President Toilets.
Jason Sheridan is President Toilets.
President Toilets has a weird has the swoop.
He's got the classic presidential coiffed hair.
And like the debate is just like somebody's talking for like five minutes and then they go in President Toilets.
How would you like to respond?
And he just flushes himself.
People cheer.
People going nuts for President Toilets.
Better than what Biden was in.
This is that is a laugh in sketch.
There's a debate with Nixon and Nixon toilet.
Toilet sense familiar.
Goldie Hawn flushes it and then they all start dancing.
Yeah.
They were the first to push the envelope.
There was never a flushing toilet shown on television until then.
So it faded.
It faded to black.
It panned to the wall as if somebody was going to get shot.
Oh boy.
Where were we?
Hey after all that talk about shit let's keep talking about food because there is a lot of that's really the main thing about Liberty Square.
There's a lot of restaurants.
There's more restaurants than attractions.
Yes.
The Liberty Tree Tavern.
Where Mike you had your your incident.
I forget when we talked about that.
That is on.
There's a Pirates Dinner Adventure episode right after my birthday last year.
And that's when I come back from the Florida trip.
Yeah.
There's basically like an all you can eat American style food thing.
And I did it alone which was a big mistake because I had to get on a plane like so many times.
I had to get on a plane like soon.
It was like the last thing I did at Magic Kingdom.
It's the last time I was in Orlando and the last thing I did was eat an all you can eat family style buffet alone.
All of those items available as individual platters.
Yeah.
But I think I was looking at the menu and I was trying to figure out what to do because people had said that was a good place to eat.
And it was like everything I saw was like well this is the thing to get.
This is you have to get the all you can eat.
I forget. I don't know if it's all you can eat if that's what they call it on the menu too.
So I wasn't like thinking it was.
I think it has a I think they dress it up in a sort of like old timey.
They say like all you wish to partake in.
Yeah.
The current branding I believe instead of all you can eat during the like obesity crisis I believe a lot of changes place a lot of places changed the phrasing to all you care to eat.
Is this one of those things Trump has dismantled and made right?
We're going to be saying all you can eat again.
We'll be so you folks.
You will be saying eat until you're not hungry anymore.
It's not that hard.
Those hungry boys those hungry football boys wanted their Burger King.
They were little Burger King boys hungry boys.
Well if he hasn't done it I know president who will president toilet.
If the more you eat the more toilets get fed across the street.
Come see me afterwards.
Wink.
The ball of course is opening and closing is the wink.
It doesn't work so well but I would think the jiggling the handle might be enough for a wink.
Because he has one eye.
President Toilets has one eye.
Yeah so I had that and the first I knew I was in trouble when they brought the cornbread to start and it was clearly for a family of four.
Yeah.
It wasn't just a little piece for me it was like a skillet of four giant pieces and I was like oh shit.
They're not changing this for a single man because I think I said on the episode I was waiting for a while and they do a whole little song and dance when it starts.
It's like Smith family party of five right this way Smith family and they keep it's all family all families and then they're like Carlson party.
Right.
You want right this way and I was like yeah and I'm like the Carlson man Carlson single man in his 30s.
I was the only person that was alone.
Everyone else was a family so they were not going to be like oh shit there's like a guy alone.
What are we going to do here.
I don't know.
Just give him the four pieces of cornbread.
We don't know.
We don't have a way to deal with this.
So they just gave me the amount they would give a family conversation.
Oh for sure.
We're talking about me.
I think it was he ordered this.
Let's put that out.
Fair enough.
Maybe that's true but I don't think.
Well is he a large man?
Is he a big fella?
No he's very lean.
He's tall and lean.
I made a mistake.
Maybe his children are hiding or lost.
But they should have just given me one piece and then the full they shouldn't have given me so much macaroni and cheese.
But you ordered it.
I know but I'm saying since it's since it's family style they should have proportionally given me smaller amounts because they were using the same serving trays.
They use for the full family that all digs in and gets it.
There's a procedure.
You paid for items that then you were given and you're complaining about it.
I'm just.
Over a year later.
I'm not complaining.
I'm just saying I don't think they have a procedure in place for a single man to order all you can.
The procedure is you order one thing.
You order a skid.
The skid comes.
But four pieces of cornbread for a single man isn't good.
They're losing money quite frankly because I didn't eat all four of those pieces.
They aren't losing money because nobody does this.
Margins dictate that they're the amount of money they're charging for that all you can eat.
They're already making.
But if you have a family of four if I had a family of four and we all ordered the same thing and it was all the same amount of money.
Now they're bringing a skillet of four cornbreads each having one.
It's a giant piece.
They're not having to pay for that for a single.
You know what I'm saying.
OK.
I guess everyone gets charged.
Everyone gets charged.
So they're making the full amount of money with a family.
They should have an option where there's just one little tiny skillet with one piece of cornbread for when I show up.
That's what I'm saying.
They need to make.
They just need to make a hungry single man in a rush because I would have.
Have it thine way.
Because I just wasted food and I don't like doing that.
It's plagued you ever since.
Why don't you just the food you made a mistake and then the food goes away.
I made a mistake for sure and I won't.
I won't make the mistake twice but I'm just saying if maybe Orlando becomes more of a destination where a man can wander around alone and come into a restaurant Disneyland I think they wouldn't make the mistake because they're much more used to people like me.
Roaming.
We've all done it.
The three of us have all been single men of roaming Disneyland.
So not single.
Not single.
Okay you can go to the how about you go to a place that serves a full pizza and then eight pieces come out and you're like what's this different.
Well you can expect to leave you can box it up.
All you can yeah you can box it up.
It's going to be fresher if you order the whole pie if you want extra meals.
You could box up the cornbread and they don't know you're on your way to the airport.
It's complicated with all you can eat stuff.
It's a little complicated with family style stuff.
It's tougher because that's.
Because they don't want you they don't want it to become a thing that people hear about that they can take stuff to leave.
Right because then you could take a whole like three person.
Now you're taking three servings of the cornbread home and it becomes a problem for them if they have it happen a lot.
Maybe they wouldn't.
It's not a problem.
They have the money the desired.
Well it's not a problem because they're a very rich corporation and I'm not worried about them.
I'm just saying.
I don't think they've been crunching the numbers on this for 13 months.
To say my family ate there last time we were there and we each got individual plot like I had a pork sandwich someone I'd write love someone I'd and we were so full and then we had foolishly scheduled a dinner at Calif like a late dinner at the California Grill on top of the contemporary that night.
And we were just all sitting down going like I don't I don't want to eat.
We're here.
This was a pain to get this reservation during the fire because that's the restaurant where everything stops when the fireworks start.
Everyone goes out on patio.
They stop dinner service so the food doesn't get cold and then you come back in and sit down.
So everyone's like what is light like what has getting the waiters.
So what is the lightest thing you would recommend.
You poor poor guys you had too much delicious food.
On your vacation too much food on your fun trip to Florida.
I've been better.
Yummy.
It's a very sympathetic tales.
The day before I think we had dinner to at least celly a another big portion place and that morning had had the breakfast buffet at the Hard Rock Hotel.
Oh my god did not.
We're trying to ambitious with our eating plans that trip way too ambitious.
Jason I'm so sorry this happened to you.
Thank you.
I mean I understand Mike's quandary.
I get it.
I know you would come around.
You understood the buffet situation and it's because it's different.
It's also this is the last thing I'll say.
It is not a traditional buffet like a hometown.
I am allowed to come and take the portions that I want.
They give it a certain.
I almost sounded like Craig.
They give it a certain food.
They give you a certain plate that is full of the portion they normally do for a full family.
There wasn't a sampler.
There wasn't like a best of the best of the in option like the taste of Italy at Olive Garden where you get one and one and one.
I missed it.
OK.
What was the name of the item?
I should look it up because if you're picturing a buffet and then that's not what if it's called a buffet that's one thing.
Hold a buffet.
Well then you don't have then that buffet argument is out the window my friend.
I mean I would have loved to see you eating with a fork out of a styrofoam container on like a Delta flight back to Los Angeles.
I mean it's the Patriots platter because it's turkey.
It's a lot of food.
Mm hmm.
But it doesn't.
Well this hold on.
I have to find the actual menu.
I'm on the official menu the official Disney.
All you care to enjoy.
So you got the Patriots platter.
Patriots.
But all you care to enjoy.
I would think they bring you a piece of cornbread.
And I say my good man I'd like another piece of cornbread please.
And they go of course.
It's a theme park.
They're not going to.
OK.
So next interaction.
Sir how many would you wait.
What are you picturing.
What bizarre restructure.
Oh wait a minute.
It's like no other restaurant on earth.
As I'm thinking this if there's eight people doing it they have to bring out.
They would have to bring out more cornbread.
So there should be a smaller and now as I look at this.
There should be more.
Entree items are you can get your pot roast is lunch weight.
The pilgrims feast is turkey breast.
Turkey pot pot.
So there is no sampler if you want to try everything.
Right.
Take me through.
You sit down.
What is supposed to happen when you order.
Hold on.
Their lobster roll is lobster salad and fried clams on it.
That's fucked up.
That is very weird.
That's another 30 minutes.
We still have to finish.
OK.
So all all Mike.
My only complaint is is that the Patriots platter is all you care to enjoy for a family and they come out.
They bring you a big four piece four pieces of cornbread big pieces in a big skillet.
Great.
And it's great because most of the people there are families that makes total sense family of four or five or whatever.
And then you have the ability to say I'd like more cornbread please because it's all you care to eat.
So you could order more of anything.
That's what they told me.
More of anything you'd want.
Right.
But they don't have smaller portions for one even two people.
Four pieces is too much.
Even if they had just brought a platter of two that I would say I would have felt much less guilty not eating.
There's somebody else out there who does want the whole all the cornbread for himself and they don't bring it all to him and he's like what the fuck.
Well but then he just says oh can I have more cornbread and they bring him more cornbread.
Yeah.
They're the starting amount separately.
100 percent.
They have to do this.
They don't have to do it.
They have to invent a system for only the patriot platter.
There's no system.
They just have to say there's one guy there.
Let's give him one piece or two pieces.
One to eat while you wait for your meal and then one to have with the meal for scooping and dipping.
To palate cleanse.
To palate no scooping and dipping.
You guys this is the most complicated restaurant math.
I think everyone is going to understand exactly what I'm saying.
I just wanted smaller plates because I was a single man and not with a family.
I didn't know your family's not in the bathroom.
Because I made it very clear I was alone.
I've come around because it says all you care to enjoy Bill of Fair and it is like that as like one menu item.
It's not saying necessarily.
Right so it didn't say.
It didn't say.
Okay all you can care to eat Bill of Fair.
You start with a declaration salad.
Mix greens with house made dressing.
Then you get the patriot platter.
Roasted turkey breast.
Pot roast.
Oven roasted pork.
Mashed potatoes.
Seasonal vegetables.
Herb stuffing.
Mac and cheese.
You're fucking insane already for having ordered this.
I am.
That's a long list.
It's a long list.
I agree.
And then hold on.
Hold on.
Ooey gooey toffee cake for dessert.
And it was like a serving of ooey gooey toffee cake for three or four people.
That actually.
As it is supposed to be.
You are not for a single man.
Well wait ooey gooey toffee cake is on here as an a la carte item dessert for eight dollars.
That was probably you got that included in whatever you paid.
You probably did financially rather than ordering all of this stuff a la carte.
You probably made the correct financial decision.
I agree with you.
I'm not actually upset about my financial decision.
That has nothing to do with what I'm talking about here.
The value is fine.
I'm actually concerned about the restaurant.
That's what I'm concerned about.
You're concerned about a bulk food restaurant at a theme park that due to this one interaction
that they wasted two rolls.
Now hold on.
The game has changed.
Because now I'm looking at the dinner version.
At a dinner you have the choice of dessert of ooey gooey toffee cake, warm banana cake,
or apple fritters.
Or.
Could you order all three?
Now I bet you're paying a premium for dinner.
I bet you're paying a premium for dinner.
I mean obviously yes you should be able to.
If the menu said you will be brought out a platter for four people of all of these.
Every item is for four people and that's what you're getting.
Once again what menu has specific instructions.
You want a fucking book to go with this one.
This lead.
This does not say serves a family.
This is an all you care.
Right.
It doesn't say serve a family.
All you care to enjoy Bill of Fair.
Right.
If it was a regular buffet I would feel much more comfortable going oh I'll have a little
scoop of this.
I'll try all of the items and that's what that indicates.
It doesn't say we're going to bring you out.
It doesn't say the word buffet.
So much.
But all you care to enjoy is I'm saying like if it was.
I gotta say it's also leading on this menu.
Like it's the top item.
So it's what they're leading with.
That's what they're leading with.
That is the item you should get.
So in all you can eat you order an all you can eat thing and then lots of food comes
out and you are upset about it to this day.
I'm not upset but it's not something I'm dwelling on.
We're talking about Liberty Square but now I'm reliving it and I'm saying they put all
of this food in front of me and I felt an urgency to eat it.
So they didn't do anything wrong.
And they didn't book the flight that close.
No of course they didn't.
You did this to yourself.
So you've added that stress.
Yes 100 percent.
It's four hours.
Yes that's true.
Yeah.
Wait a second.
Very important.
The Liberty Tree Tavern did not book your flight.
They did not book my flight but they did put four large pieces of cornbread to start.
How dare they.
I'm in trouble.
These monsters.
Lock them up.
But then I wasted food and I felt bad about it.
I think we haven't touched on this.
This is a popular restaurant.
Good word of mouth.
Yes.
So for now.
But when the word gets out of it.
It's a wasted cornbread.
But I think they may have brought out a large portions so they didn't have to keep coming
back.
So they're like there's no way I will have to I'm going to take care of this.
Who knows how many.
It's always.
Yes that is probably the situation is that they brought they just they don't want to
have to keep coming back more.
They would rather go big the first time and not have me go another piece please.
Like they don't want to do with that.
That is the thinking behind it.
Funny story in my family about this restaurant.
My uncle Joey was down there with his wife and there was a guy one table over and they
started up a conversation.
Both parties had the Disney dining plan where you are allocated like certain meals you're
allocated to me like you get a meal and a drink and dessert and sometimes an appetite
and like the guy at the other table is like hey do you guys want our dessert.
I can't.
I'm a big guy.
I can't eat this much.
They give you so much food on this dining plan and as he's saying this my uncle looks
down and realize the guy is wearing a Super Bowl ring.
So this is a professional football player who has won the Super Bowl.
I don't remember who it was.
It was for sure a Super Bowl.
It was a Super Bowl because then he asked him about it.
He's like oh yeah I played for a few years for blah blah blah for the Bills or whatever
you know.
And it's so like he was still a tank of a man and even he was like this fucking this
restaurant's dining plan.
They give you so much food on these things.
Wow.
It wasn't just a guy wearing a souvenir ring doing stolen stolen Super Bowl valor.
So now so yeah so heavy Porsche I mean is his failed professional football players award
winning professional football players.
We'll see.
People will rule I think on this issue if I have a point here.
I know they're going to rule against me but I know how these things go but I'm just saying
the the the sorted tale where four roles are brought to you.
It's not a tragedy.
I'm not trying to say I'm some persecuted individual.
I'm just saying that that for a man trying to try it out go with a smaller plate.
All I'm saying is a smaller plate.
That's all I'm trying to say.
I'm not going to commit us anything but should the nation should something arise where all
of us are in Orlando could you imagine.
I think we got a think we got a save.
I think we have to do it with an hour before our flight.
Yeah we have to do a less time than I have to reproduce the conditions.
Yeah that's true.
Palpitations.
Here's what we have to do.
What we have to do.
We have to make separate reservations.
We will not sit at the same table.
Yeah we will each make single reservations and then each go and deal with the amount
of food they give each.
I don't like to be looked in the eye while I eat like a street dog.
Yes.
All right.
So that's that's for sure.
If we go to Orlando.
Wow.
Each get one of these.
Can we talk about so this is totally unrelated.
Mike Mike you I mentioned this very briefly before the show Scott I don't think this you
would come upon this one the crooked shutters another design element the crooked shutters.
We said the beginning I don't know what's up with crooked shutters.
Yeah.
Do you know it's basically in the like the shutters are crooked in the area because in
the old times they needed to they needed metal.
Yeah there was not a lot of metal being shipped during the Revolutionary War.
There was a shortage of metal.
Right.
So they would take the metal pieces out of whatever were they just those were the things
that held the shutters in I think.
Yeah they were melting it down for bullets and they would do it.
They would turn it into the government to turn into bullets and then they would use
leather straps to fix the shutters to the house or whatever.
OK.
And so they did they made them going to be crooked because that wasn't the best way to
put shutters on leather.
Leather softens as it starts to age.
So the shutters would shutters are crooked.
There is a tribute to this real life thing that happened.
Yeah.
So how about that.
Just as the Liberty just as the tall oak next to the Liberty tree tavern is a tribute to
the real Liberty tree that used to be near Boston Common.
There were acts of rebellion until some loyalist scumbag chopped it down in 1775.
Oh really.
It got.
Oh yes.
Nathaniel J.
Coffin chopped it down.
Bastard.
He's in a coffin now.
Thank God.
Your trees are safe every one.
Liberty tree.
I didn't even know there was a Liberty tree I think.
Here's how much I veered from knowing about history is that when I heard about the Liberty
tree I didn't think about the history.
I don't think I knew much of anything about it.
What I thought of was is something that I do know the full history of which is football
player wraps.
Obviously everybody knows the Super Bowl shuffle but people might not know the many other
football wraps that occurred including that.
So the Super Bowl shuffle was made in 1870.
So the Super Bowl shuffle was made in 1985 before the Super Bowl that was the Bears
versus the Patriots and they hadn't won the Super Bowl.
It wasn't a song celebrating that they won.
It was that they're going to win and the Patriots were like fuck this we got to get a song
out too and their song was so much worse and the song is called New England the Patriots
and We.
It is markedly worse.
The Patriots lost the Super Bowl and they deserve to purely for their terrible song
and let me tie it all together and tell you to show you why I think of that with this
topic.
Here's a little taste of New England Patriots and We.
That's that's that.
I don't know who that player is but that very flat will hang a bell from the Liberty tree.
That is not as fun as the Super Bowl shuffle.
It is much worse.
It's even less qualified rappers.
I think another one is here's a V for Victor Rhee.
Crap song.
I will I'll just say if you I don't know how far we can stretch the confines of this podcast
but if there is any interest in a full history of football raps this is a if that somehow
counts this is a topic I can speak to at length.
There is either on it there are like 20 of those.
I was going to say how many do you know off the top of your head?
Super Bowl shuffle Patriots and We, Ram It, Buddy's Watching You, Philadelphia Eagles
won.
There's got to be some baseball ones in there.
I can only name four.
There's definitely more.
Okay.
Well, then I mean we'll do it.
Yes.
Great.
Football raps coming at you.
What did we miss?
Very few additions over the years.
Memento Mori the Haunted Mansion shop added in the last few years.
For years there was not a Haunted Mansion shop just a little cart.
The Liberty Square pillory.
The stocks.
Yeah, that's fun.
That's real fun.
Yeah.
At some point you kids would be deemed sons and daughters of Liberty and hand it declarations
of independence and a ceremony.
Is that true?
Yeah, I saw it.
There's footage of like a 1970s.
They don't do that anymore, do they?
I don't know.
We got to get you that certificate.
There's still a town crier.
I mean you met the restaurant crier but there is a town crier who shows up.
JJ who shows up in the Muppets.
Oh yeah.
Present great moments in Muppet history.
We didn't even touch on that.
That's probably worth its own episode.
That is worth its own episode but we've talked a little bit about it and I, you have not,
oh yeah, I've not really seen it.
I saw a little video clips.
It's the greatest.
It's very fun.
It's really great.
Money.
Real puppets, real puppeteers.
Real puppets.
There's a couple different shows.
I think so many yelled at me for saying there were too many like four maybe.
There's at least two.
There's two.
Paul of Vier and Declaration of Independence.
And then like they're in the different spots in different buildings like Sam Eagle's over
in the Hall of Presidents one time.
Oh so you don't know where they're going to appear.
Yeah and they're real puppets and it's, and it's also, it's probably the only thing that's
like self-referential about American history because in the main song it's like we're singing
about American history or singing about great moments in history but only the American parts.
And there's like a nice, there's you know like Muppets joking about Sam Eagle.
Just that little bit of subversiveness.
Yeah.
That's great.
There was, I'm trying to think there was something like they apologized to the British people
in the audience for like the take on something like whatever they were like because they're
basically they're just reenacting famous moments in history and they fuck it up because they're
the Muppets.
Yeah.
And it's great.
And the real voices in it.
Yeah.
I believe so.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Yeah it seemed like Steve Whitmire pre, they're not seeing Steve Whitmire.
Right.
Before the incidents.
Or incident whatever we, yeah.
Yeah.
So yeah that's really great and is so fun.
Well that's, it seems like they finally figured out a way to if we're filling this area is
too homeworky.
Yeah.
Give us some of our friends.
Give us some of our beloved characters.
I want a little, I want it a little coarser.
I want the all of Howard Zinn's A People's History of the United States.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
The book they hand you with your dorm keys at every liberal arts college in America.
Uh huh.
And who's in there?
Oliver Stone and Michael Moore and.
Sure it's a little more dry.
It's a little more dry.
The history of the indigenous people and working people and stuff.
Yeah.
It's more just like a lot of this.
It's not just like a quick sound bite.
It's like 15 minutes of somebody saying how they were subjugated.
Yes.
Or add Noam Chomsky into the Hall of Presidents and have him like after every dialogue like
here's why that's bullshit.
Well they should close it out.
Like the last show of the night should run like an hour and a half and should have addendums.
Oh yeah.
Like their THO Martin.
Hall of Presidents after dark.
And now for the Hall of Presidents rebuttal.
It's like a little.
It's body.
Yeah.
More fun.
Well then it's the big, it's the Hall of Mistresses.
Oh yeah.
There's not enough room in that building for all the mistresses.
Yeah.
I really wonder if you added every extramarital affair with the 45 presidents.
If you are in the performing arts community in Orlando and you have not done the Hall
of Mistresses at the Orlando Fringe yet, what are you doing?
Get on that.
What are you waiting for?
What?
Yeah.
They, that would be, they would have to shut.
What if they shut Carousel Progress and Country Bears down and just put the mistresses in
there?
They would need both campuses.
Yeah, do both of them.
Now for part two.
Yeah.
It's 1901 so head over to the.
The post-industrial mistresses.
I think that's fine.
Sure.
Hey, just grab back what we missed.
The parasol cart.
Oh yeah.
The pretty squares where you get yourself a pretty parasol.
Which is probably something we should do when we, let's see if they'll customize.
Let's see if they'll, because they got purple parasols.
They do.
Let's get a parasol.
It says podcast the ride.
Yeah.
Ye olde Christmas shop.
Mm-hmm.
Or it's Christmas all year round.
Yeah.
Yes.
That's, we have a Christmas shop here too now.
Kind of, there's a little section.
Right.
But it's, yeah, that is, I was shocked.
I was like, oh wow.
What's this doing here?
When I was there in Florida.
Yeah.
I mean, America is very instrumental in the history of the way Christmas is celebrated.
Like it was very celebrated very differently over the years and stuff.
And the version we have of Christmas now did not come about until like 20, early 20th century.
Those Coke ads.
Coke ads were a big part of it.
And Coke is readily available.
Late 19th century.
I mean, British, Charles Dickens and Christmas Carol was a big part of it.
You know?
Interesting.
Yeah.
But I make sense they have Christmas thing there because sometimes you go once a year
and you want a couple of Christmas things.
Oh yeah.
They're not like crazy like we are.
We go all the time.
Hey, hanging on the tree.
You remember your nice trip?
You went on one.
Yeah.
It's not so crazy.
It's fine.
That's why we think Christmas presents are okay.
Yeah.
So Liberty Square, we did it.
We missed the Columbia Harbor house.
Oh yeah.
We talked a little bit.
Yeah.
Oh, the fish house.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, there's also a weird thing about it where the it's supposed to tie into the Columbia.
Like it was like where that was like, oh yeah, supplies are kept or like, you know, if you're
working the Columbia, that's where you sleep.
That's the cottage that goes along with the Columbia.
Right.
But then they didn't build a Columbia.
So it's weird.
I didn't realize that was supposed to be a tie into a ship that never got built because
they did two Mark Twain's instead.
Two Mark Twain's.
I had to rush that fact in.
Yeah.
Well, that was the episode.
People were like, oh my God, I'm canceling this Patreon unless they get to the Columbia
effect.
Well, the other thing we haven't talked about is the haunted mansion.
But I guess that I think it's assumed.
That gets this whole thing.
Yeah.
It's a nice looking haunted mansion.
Yeah, it's a great haunted mansion.
My mom still claims that's the better looking outside one.
I'm still not so sure.
I go back and forth.
Because it is creepier.
It's a creepier thing.
And we'll talk about it on.
It reminded me as growing up of where Corella DeVille lived.
Because it is set back, which is nice.
It's got a cool like setback thing and like that makes it feel creepier.
And they reproduced it in Tokyo.
They chose that as the Tokyo haunted mansion as well.
So that speaks to its quality.
I'm not sure.
I think they're both good in their own ways.
Yeah, that I think there was I read some stuff, but it was a little too complicated to try.
The architecture of the land, if you add 17 or 18 in front of the address of some of the
buildings, it gives you an idea of what year you're kind of looking at.
And the haunted mansion is older.
There's two numbers on the door.
And if you put 18 in front of them, it says what year.
You would have seen that style.
Something like that.
Yeah.
I think the haunted mansion is actually earlier.
Hmm.
It is what is interesting about Haunted Mansion being there is like because it's Liberty Square.
You're like almost celebrating an idea in an era more than with New Orleans Square,
which makes more sense where it's like, OK, it's an area and there's like the fun part
of it.
But then there's like kind of the setback creepy mansion.
The reason it feels like it's because Liberty Square, it's so tied to like American history.
And like that's what's kind of weird about it being there.
Yeah.
And there's nothing else patriotic about nothing.
The Hall of Presidents.
Because it makes sense.
I'm sorry about the Haunted Mansion.
It's not there's not like ghosts of presidents or congressmen.
Right.
Which would be maybe cool if they had done that.
They should have just made them all.
Yeah.
Every character is.
Well, maybe that's the way you just put all the presidents into it.
Because most of the presidents are dead.
So right.
They would be in the Haunted Mansion.
Yeah, sure.
Sure.
Or Hall of I mean, more criminals in the Hall of Presidents and Pirates of the Caribbean.
It's a scurvier bunch of scoundrels.
For sure is.
Yeah.
I know we're heading to the end, but if I say this bizarre facts, then we can save it
in Haunted Mansion Part III down the road.
Sure.
And since we're talking about architecturally, this Haunted Mansion, if you've never been
there, it doesn't look like it's not the pillars.
It's not the new like southern style plantation kind of house like it is in California.
It is a style that you describe as colonial Dutch Gothic.
And it's supposed to look like a place called the Harry Packer Mansion, which is in Pennsylvania.
Basically, it's in the town of Jim Thorpe, Pennsylvania.
Do you know about Jim Thorpe, Pennsylvania?
I think I've been camping in Jim Thorpe, Pennsylvania.
I think there's a state park or something.
It's a place you can camp.
Yeah.
I just got on my way out the door.
I got curious about that.
Quick tangent.
Jim Thorpe, Pennsylvania, named after the famous Olympian and football player and assuredly
the town named after him because that was his beloved hometown and where he resided.
Right?
Yes.
He's from Oklahoma and he never stepped foot in this town.
This guy died in the 50s and people were talking about, well, do we build a park in Oklahoma?
What do we do?
Meanwhile, his third wife sold his remains to this town, which was called Motch Chunk.
Motch Chunk, Pennsylvania, bought Jim Thorpe's body.
You can do that?
Like a widow can sell a body and it's still where his remains are.
That's what Casey Kasem's wife did.
Really?
Well, remember, she was dragging his corpse all over the place so it wouldn't be in the
ground to keep it from the kids, to keep the kids from getting his money.
It was a whole thing.
I'm not sure I knew he died.
Casey Kasem?
Yeah.
It was like five years ago, I think.
Oh yeah, it was a big scandal.
Soikes!
There it goes!
She was taking his corpse around the world to keep it from being buried.
Anyway, that's a whole other...
That's a Patreon episode.
We'll get into that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Casey Kasem's body.
Anyway, yeah, this town needed a tourism element so we'll name ourselves Jim Thorpe and put
this guy's body in the town.
And then in 2010, one of Jim Thorpe's sons sued the town to get his father's remains
back and then he died a year later and then four years later the case was overturned by
the Supreme Court and they didn't get the remains back.
So this guy was trying to get his dad to be buried where he wanted to be buried, died
and the Supreme Court said no.
So hooray.
And also it has a house that looks like the haunted mansion.
God, what a ghoulish.
That was my initial point.
It's a ghoulish tale.
What a ghoulish tale.
Surrounding the ghoulish home where the ghosts reside.
That is an American tale if I have ever heard one.
That's what I was...
Yeah, as I said that.
The third wife sold the corpse, the son tried to get it back but then he died.
Honestly, this is not dissimilar to the Gene Kasem situation.
Really?
Yeah.
The kids were just like put him, bury him.
We need to bury him.
The kids wanted it stopped and the wife...
She kept the kids from seeing him toward the end.
It's a whole situation.
I mean, I might have some details wrong but that's the gist of it.
And then like he wasn't in the...
Like months after, it took months for him to get buried finally because it was such a
dispute over his money and everything.
Geez, wow.
And his wife was an evil carnival owner.
I don't think he was...
She didn't sell his corpse to a town, Casey Kasem, Pennsylvania.
So I guess that's where it's different.
Right next door.
Which by the way sounds fun.
Yeah.
Loving Casey Kasem, Pennsylvania.
Sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It has a ring to it.
Yeah, but no, what an odd little encapsulation of...
Yeah, that's the way an Olympic athlete is treated, a Native American Olympic athlete.
Right.
Wow.
Yeah.
Got to know anything about that.
Attuate.
Yeah, great stuff.
Lordy Square.
Well, yeah, how fitting I suppose for...
Yeah, Olympic corpses being trotted around against their will, shit in the streets.
Sandwoods, platter castles.
Food arguments.
A literal food fight.
I mean, that was...
Yeah, I enjoyed that and I hope any listeners who have been determined that the Liberty
Tree Tavern situation was left as a cliffhanger.
Well, yeah.
I'm glad we got back into it.
Well, you can see the coming glory, all the coming, all the glory.
I mean, if we go to Orlando, if we go, I think that we'll do a full Liberty Tree episode,
main feed, two hours.
Is there something that you would like to...
What would be the lesson that I would need to learn?
I think if you just said much like the episode where you said that three days you needed
at least three days to talk to...
If you said the plates aren't too big for one man, I think that would be...
I'll say that right now.
No, no, I don't want it like this.
I don't want it like this.
Not like this.
We'll hash it out in the two, maybe two and a half hour main feed episode about Liberty
Tree Tavern if we go to Orlando.
All right then.
You survived podcasts, right?
There'll be many more things to survive in the future.
Yeah, good luck.
Happy Fourth of July.
Oh, and here, well, here's a little quote from Walt Disney about America and his feelings
about America to send us out.
If you could see close in my eyes, the American flag is waving in both of them and up my spine
is growing this red, white and blue stripe.
And that's what killed him.
All right, goodbye.
Goodbye.