Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains messy clots, drug humor, scary wooden flats, a tasteless
candy gag gift that threatens to derail the entire episode with its vulgarity, and a far
out look man at the Alice in Wonderland ride.
We're through the looking glass.
It's Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, hosted by three very good boys who immediately leave the Alice
in Wonderland ride and narc on the hookah smoking caterpillar.
I'm Scott Gertner, joined by Mike Carlson.
Yeah, Mike Carlson here.
Jason Sheridan.
Jason, yeah, I don't like it.
I don't care for it.
It's clearly like some funny stuff in there.
You're not supposed to do that inside.
In fact, you're not supposed to do it in the parks at all anymore.
So security, they've been actually they've been looking into it and they've taken a lot
of the smoking areas away.
So I find it a little offensive that on the ride, there's somebody smoking, not only smoking,
but smoking and making vows with his smoke.
I'm offended by his language.
He's flaunting it.
He's being flashy about his brazen breaking of the rules.
And I don't care for it.
It's only going to lead to more of that kind of thing.
Yeah. And it's not tobacco.
It can't be tobacco.
Yeah, it's it's a what is it?
What is it? What is it?
Hookah is traditionally a kind of tobacco.
Yeah, but but I'm saying with this caterpillar, this is not.
Oh, who knows? It's probably opium.
Yeah, OK, that actually makes a lot more sense.
We're mixed in with tobacco.
And we're dealing with the twisted mind of Lewis Carroll.
The twisted mind of Lewis Carroll.
What's the Sean William Scott and Ashton Kutcher?
Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
That's good. Yeah, actually, I like to see that.
That's good. Rachel Lee.
Rachel Lee Cook is Alice.
Man, this is great casting with like the she's all that era.
You're putting this in 2001.
D.J. Qualls, D.J. Qualls.
I was like, oh, shit, who's D.J. Qualls?
Seth Green is the king of hearts.
Oh, yes. But they kind of like shrunken down with bad CGI.
Like, yeah, it doesn't look good.
And the queen is already laying in drag.
Oh, my God. Oh, yeah.
That's outrageous.
I don't know if he would have gotten that part.
I don't know. Maybe.
I don't know. He was in some movies here and there.
Yeah. Yeah.
It would have been like there was like six months where he could have gotten that.
Yes. Like if he was on his best behavior in the quick little window.
Like Norm Show season two.
There's a six month window where Artie Lang would have been cast.
Yes. As the queen.
And Norm's the mad hatter.
No, no one was a mad hatter.
They're the mad hatter.
That's an impression of shitty Norm Impressions is what it is.
Hey, well, you know, before we get into
today's topic, this ride, one of the Disneyland dark rides,
you know, in the the Alice tale
kicks off with her, you know, trying these potions, these little,
you know, the eat me and the drink me. Right.
And I realize that's maybe that's a fun way
to start our little journey, to try a little experimental spirit.
As it were. Yes, indeed.
You're giving me weird looks here, but allow me to explain.
I've not that long ago, I was in Las Vegas.
Right. Real real life wonderland.
Huh? Just you have things in this bag.
What's that? Do you have things for?
I do. I do have things in the bag and I can explain.
So I was I was on my way to to the Bally's Resort, which, by the way,
I mean, I'll say this separately.
I was going to the Twilight Zone mini golf course by made by Monster mini golf,
the same place that made the Kiss mini golf.
Right. Anybody's been on that.
I have been to that. And yeah, yeah.
I think that was that was really great.
I think it's moved. It's it's at one of the casinos now.
I forget which was across the street from Hard Rock Hotel.
Yes, I believe it is not anymore.
I think it's part of a casino complex now.
And now Bally's has a second one, the Twilight Zone, which I would highly recommend.
It's a lot of fun. This place does good stuff.
Some great, great characters and great black light, much like today's attraction as well.
So and and and relatively cheap, I will say, for it being a strip attraction.
Right. You get out of there without spending a ton.
Anybody looking for weird stuff to do in Vegas?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm not.
They do take your ball at the end.
You know, you don't get to take that home.
You're not buying a ball for that price.
But so I was on my way into Bally's.
And what should I see?
Jump out of me in the shopping center in front of Bally's.
But one of our beloved city walk stores, it's sugar.
It's sugar. Oh, yes.
Now in front of the Bally's hotel.
And I didn't realize till I got home.
That is a brand new Bally's or not.
Bally's is not new brand, brand new.
It's sugar only opened in June.
It is now they consider it a flagship location.
Only the second location on the strip, there's already one at the Venetian.
But now there's this new gigantic, it's sugar,
which is very theme parky in general when you end up going to Vegas again.
I mean, I guess maybe I shouldn't spoil everything, but you can see
gigantic nerds made of nerds.
Yes, that got a gasp out of you.
I was hoping it would.
You can get a picture with a big jelly belly on a bench.
That's good. Yeah, there's tons of like big theme parky figures and stuff.
But there was something that jumped out at me and something that I haven't seen
in the city walk. It's sugar.
Maybe it's a new thing. Maybe they do have it.
But I was like, I have to bring this home to the guys and we have to
we have to give this a try.
And here, give me a sec. Let me pull it out.
What I have with me.
What what a treat.
Get ready for urine. Yeah.
Have you seen urine before?
And just a few minutes ago, in fact,
your own urine.
This is clinical looking.
Yes. It the urine comes in a sample jar.
It looks like you would do a copy.
Yes. And on the back, a little form of name reason, time date
and a sterile sticker, sterile interior if the seal is not broken.
But this is a jar of some strange yellow liquid of candy piss.
Candy piss is what I hold in my hands.
Tag candy piss.
The the official name of this product is urine for a treat.
Whoa. And this was also this is one of the eye popping displays
of the new Vegas at Sugar.
There was one.
This is one of 50 that were all overflowing out of a urinal
attached to the wall.
Wait, a full a regular sized urinal or a novelty sized urinal?
I would call it more novelty.
OK, although the urinals can be large and they go down to the floor.
But this was a mounted one, not a floor length one.
So they're all in on selling candy piss.
This isn't just like we're trying it out for a while.
Yeah, this is like a permanent part.
It's a load bearing urinal.
Jeff, on the pillar of the store, I feel like
Mike and I were talking about Vegas recently and I was pulling up pictures
of the it was Vince Neal's Tatuado
each drink party where they briefly served drinks in plastic toilet cups.
Or maybe it was each drink party and Tatuado is the current
Vince Neal restaurant at Circus Circus.
Well, I mean, that's a question of how do we how do we consume this urine?
I mean, it's I also if we just want to dip forks, I have forks with me.
I mean, how is it thick here?
You see it turning? Not really.
I know what you mean by forks, though.
But like I feel like you need to be like honey.
You could like it could be the you think it's viscous.
Maybe we should do it like it should be.
Let's do let's do it like it's heroin with a spoon.
Yeah, that's good.
That's what we dip a little bit into a spoon.
Like, yeah, maybe, maybe it's I should have warned you.
I'm sorry, but I wanted to spring this year and you're all.
So now you can hear me cracking the seal.
So, you know that this urine has not been contaminated.
It has not been.
It is it is still sterilized in as much as.
But yeah, apparently the toilet cups were briefly popular.
And for a while, they had a version where you would drink out of the bowl
or your food would be in the bowl and then the.
Yes, you're going to have your drink down.
OK.
OK, here now they're breaking the seal, no longer sterile and quick.
OK, great.
So yeah, maybe you stay standing and you can hand this to.
Carol and Jason not have predicted this level.
And I mean, he was perverted, but OK, let me take a little dip here.
Hmm. I mean, it feels like it looks like medicine or it looks like a honey.
We'll document this in some way here.
No, you're you take and then take it to Jason.
I'll take a picture. Oh, yes. Yeah.
Take a picture of this process.
And at home, if you're in Las Vegas already, get your own piss.
Edwin is lined up to get it.
So yeah, this is going to be a bit.
Yeah, you're going to have to.
All right, Scott, you take yours.
Mike, take the cup and the spoon. OK.
And he's locked in and staring daggers.
Maybe maybe just put it in Jason's mouth.
Maybe just feed Jason.
Wait, wait, wait. Let me let me take a photo of this, too.
Sorry, listener.
I we should have walked in on a candy piss again.
Thank you. Thank you, my boy.
Hang on. Here we go. OK.
A photo and Edwin's in there, too.
That's fantastic.
OK, let's hear it.
And you do it, too, Mike. So there's not too much of a delay.
I'm going to take a big spoonful of this. Here we go.
Hey, let me say officially, Mike, Jason, eat my piss.
You want to say it?
Because finally.
Oof. Oh, it tastes like medicine.
So it stays like a yellow medicine.
I did have to drink out of a bottle like that is awful.
That is really sour.
Oh, Mike is very unhappy.
Like you left lemon heads in the car and they melted.
And you like took it.
Mike is eating an actual lemon now for relief.
That's not a joke.
Yeah. From like an old Dunkin Donuts.
Oh, I crave the smooth taste of lemon.
Should I go back?
You want more? You want more?
I think I need another to like get your full.
We'll get up.
I think that I don't because my I think I think my teeth are rotting already.
It's a candy that rots your teeth instantly.
I will say I have a canker sore in my mouth.
Oh, no. And it really inflamed it.
The it's like medicine, except it fucks up your mouth problems more.
Yeah, it's an awesome.
Also, too.
Uh, not great.
Less better because I used the end of the spoon, so I got very little.
I sometimes sometimes some people say like,
I don't like this food because of the texture.
And sometimes I'm like, I guess a real asshole and I'm skeptical.
And I'm like, well, the texture doesn't really bother me.
I will say that's maybe the most unpleasant texture I've ever put in my mouth.
Because it's somewhere between is not as thick as maple syrup or something.
And though it is a little more solid and it is certainly not just pure water or soda.
Right. It's a really uncanny valley of liquid consistency.
At first, I thought, oh, it's going to be like gelatin.
And it's not. It is like syrup.
Yeah. From a distance, it looked very watery.
And then when I got up close, I was like, oh, this is syrup.
It has the same color as like some.
Like very intense medicine I had to take when I was like very ill in high school.
Like I had to go to the hospital and get fluids and like that sort of thing.
And they're like, you have to take this for a week.
And it's just like, oh, it tastes bad.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
I mean, kind of thing you would only eat for survival.
Yeah. Not dying.
That's going to go on our earthquake kit unless you guys want to take it.
Did you just buy? Is that what that is?
Is that a backpack?
We've had that earthquake thing for a while.
We just had an earthquake a couple of weeks ago.
Two weeks. You know, things are bad when you're subsisting on that urine.
You're drinking candy piss.
Before you get to your own.
Would you maybe would you choose your own piss over this fake piss?
I do think my own piss would be more pleasant than this candy piss.
I think so, too.
You know what it is?
Yeah, it's it's the liquid.
It's just like liquid, at least not this bizarre in between
that you're dealing with here.
Yeah, I would.
You know, I think the hotness of this would be the trouble for me.
But maybe I kind of pre do it, let it cool down a little.
Well, you would piss into a glass with ice.
Yeah. Assuming that in this
like emergency scenario, ice is still available.
Aren't there those things where you like break it open and it turns icy?
Am I making something up?
Yeah, for like pain relief, not for eating.
Yeah, there you go. Yeah.
It's for like your back. Yeah, yeah.
But you could use it to cool your piss in a disaster.
I suppose. Yeah.
Oh, you could.
Yeah, there are like refreezeable, like liquid things that you can put
in your or something because there's a thing like for my there's a back thing
that we have where you like snap it and it like turns things on.
And it heats. Sure.
So if you use one of those, not to relieve an injury, but wrapped
a cup of your piss, that would that I think that what I'm describing
would taste better than what we just. Yeah.
I mean, thanks for thinking of us.
Thank you. That is nice.
I want you to know when I saw that you're full of these samples.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
In the hot in a hot desert.
You also talked about like bringing back like Italian meat,
delicious Italian meats and cheese.
Oh, yes, that's true.
I went to Italy and then I and I and then I had a flight that day
and I didn't have to do the full security screening.
So, yes, in my bag was both.
Yeah, like fantastic prosciutto de parma
and the sealed sealed candy piss.
That's Vegas, baby.
That's Vegas.
I know. I know it's supposed to stay there, but hey, I'm talking about it.
I brought it home with me.
My last question about the candy piss is, is it
was their intention to like obviously make it look gross,
but then you'd have and you go, oh, this is delicious.
Or is the idea that it's going to be like, oh, we're all eating a gross thing.
And it's like a little bit unpleasant.
Of course, it's just sugar.
Because it's also not like so vile.
It's not like it's not like a joke, like fart flavor.
Right. Yeah.
Have you we had any in any of our sugar wanderings?
Did we ever have some nobody had like one of the poop candies or something?
No, I've had the jelly belly like the birdie bots, the Harry Potter jelly beans.
And every now and then there's like grass or booger or like.
Mm hmm. Yeah, those are.
Those are unpleasant, but won't kill you.
But this is just that just felt like this is I don't even know.
Like how are you meant to consume?
Like, I feel like if I took a sip, I'd be really upset.
Like, it seems like a thing you would you would open the lid and then sip from it.
But like, it doesn't dripping.
Yeah, down. Yeah.
Is there with you both with facial hair?
Thank God you didn't just dive in.
Then you've got piss in your. Yeah.
I also wonder, like, why couldn't it just be like a yellow soda?
Sure. Is it just look right into in the container?
Maybe like, you never see better.
Hmm. Yeah, I think the fact that because any like sodas
usually contain in such a way that you can't like quite see the flavor inside.
You know, the bottles are dark like vitamin water.
Yellow vitamin water looks like that, doesn't it?
Yeah, that's true.
Is it that I don't know if it's that thick piss yellow.
I guess that's why it just has to be thicker because piss is thicker than vitamin water.
This is thicker than water.
That was very unpleasant.
I wasn't. Yeah, I wasn't sure it was going to go that way.
It seemed possible to me that like, oh, and then it's kind of a fun little lemon treat.
But that was very unpleasant and I was unpleasant to listen to.
We said the word piss a lot.
Yeah. Sorry about that. If you're piss sensitive
or any piss, it's really going down the rabbit hole or any listeners
who enjoy drinking piss and are offended that we've spoken a little bit.
Mm hmm. So yeah, either way, it's an acquired taste and a flavor that we apologize.
Either way, enjoy.
I apologize to you guys, I suppose,
but I would still recommend a trip to the flagship, it's sugar for fine products like that.
I just want to know what else they're working on.
Is there like a do they have blood? They sell candy blood already, right?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I think so.
So what other what other fluids?
No, never mind.
There's only so many.
Let's just talk about Alice in Wonderland.
Let's now talk about Alice in Wonderland.
Let's open the big door.
Do you guys feel like anything's happening to you?
Do you feel like you do?
Do you feel like you're growing 10 feet tall from that consumption of urine? No.
Is your mind open now?
That's yeah, I feel like I'm coming off of a lot of number opium.
I feel like I've got the shakes and I'm sweating.
I do have a weird feeling in my I think that could have provoked a headache.
I'm not sure.
The lemon I really is a as if I did a shot of tequila.
I took the lemon afterwards.
I would rather my palate. Yeah.
You want that alcohol aftertaste without the taste?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Give me some rubbing alcohol, please.
I need something here.
Oh, boy. Well, yeah.
Let's swing from that to what I think is a pretty fun and pleasant ride.
Alice in Wonderland Disneyland and at no other parks.
Interestingly, Disneyland, Disneyland, Dark Ride exclusive.
One of the only dark rides. It's only one park. Yeah.
Fifty one years old.
Opened June 14th, 1958.
Same day as the sailing ship Columbia.
Important day for you. An important day for me.
Fun fact, when it opened, the sailing ship Columbia cost three hundred
thousand dollars, which in today's
money would be over two million dollars.
That's still pretty cheap.
That's still they could.
That's one one hundredth of Galaxy's.
Yeah, that is true.
Yeah, not even more.
Wait, I'm no, I'm not even close.
They're both a billion dollars.
Both galaxies.
I think that's what Jim Hill said or over a bit.
That's what he always says.
Like, that's what they admit they've spent on both parts.
Part of both parts.
So like it's possible it's over a billion dollars.
When you factor in like movie budgets are like, oh, and then there's
marketing on top of that.
Yeah. And then then the I assume to fix rise of the resistance,
which we haven't even talked about as opening next year,
which is just here.
Insane. Yeah.
But it's not without precedent, of course.
But still, I just want to go on the goddamn right.
Yeah, I know.
When the Disney world gets it before us and yet after we've been there
for our live show tickets available now, maybe hopefully.
Or they're not. They're not.
Go get them fast.
That was Mike's theory.
Your theory was that like you maybe they would let you know,
that would be a surprise for people going to the parks panel.
Well, that's supposedly what you get a wristband to go on.
Rise of the resistance.
They usually do that kind of fun thing at D23.
And like you one time I got a world of color fast pass for the new show
for that night. And they do fun stuff like that.
And Jim Hill was saying that they wanted it open just at least for D23 weekend.
So people would go on it, whether they were going to do that,
if like kind of fun event or not.
But no, instead of that, six months later.
Yeah. So there's only one fun choice for D23 weekend,
which is to come see the podcast, the ride gang at the Anaheim Hotel.
The night before. Don't do it after the parks panel.
Come do it the night before. That's when that's when we're actually there.
Do it. Do it when we're doing it.
Hit up the pizza press beforehand.
Design your own pizza. It's very fun.
That pizza press. I feel like you are. You love the designer on pizza.
I like that. Well, pizza press.
I like the concept.
I do think pizza press is one of the better ones.
If you remember at City Walk, I really beefed it with Blaze. OK.
And I'm still not quite sure how much of that was them and how much was me.
But you've been working it out with your therapist.
I still try to figure it out. You'll crack it one day.
So this Alice in Wonderland.
Well, you know, I was going to say, did they ever do you think they looked
at the numbers for Galaxy's Edge and thought, maybe we should just build
200 more Columbia's?
Like for this price. Yeah.
I think that more ships
crammed all over every bit of empty space, crammed ships.
Bob Chapek now is crunching the numbers on the ships.
This ride is this is kind of a creeper for me in that
not in the Lewis Carroll way in the it's a creeper on my list of
favorite dark rides.
It's depending on the day.
I could even maybe list this as my as my number one of the Disneyland.
Of the Disneyland, you said that, OK, like, OK, I guess that's how you feel.
Oh, I didn't intend to.
I think I'm still processing the thing.
My mouth still feels bad.
Oh, yeah, that's going to be a subject.
I guess we are still. Yeah.
I would not disagree with that.
I have always been a big Mr.
Toad kid, and I was so delighted when I came out here and found it was still here
after it had been tragically closed in Florida.
I might still have to call it that, but I think it's those two are vying for one.
I mean, this has so many unique elements to it, too, that kind of set it apart.
Yeah, I it the location of it for whatever reason.
I don't go on it that much, but it's not fair to it.
Like because it is really good.
Yeah, it is one of the best ones.
Well, I yeah, I never feel like waiting in that line, but that's a great one.
If you're there in that last hour and it's sort of thinning out
because those quitter kids have all left. Yes.
And I ended up doing this was actually the first thing that I went to
in this bizarre night that I told you guys about, but I didn't go.
I didn't talk about on the show that I ended up at.
I was like that was a Disneyland solo.
And I was like kind of looking forward to like, yeah, you know,
I'll take off early and, you know, just like that was a good, quick little trip.
That was nice. I got to Mickey and friends.
It was full to the brim because there was an accident.
Two exits up the five.
And I was looking at the map and the freeway was mostly fine.
It was mainly affecting Mickey and friends.
Yeah, it was like that.
It was like a degree of traffic that would have been OK
where they're not, you know, like thousands and thousands of people
leaving one location with only one way out at the same.
So I got to Mickey and friends, saw the crowd.
Nope, never mind.
Went straight back on the tram.
And I went straight to Alice in Wonderland, which probably put this in my brain.
And I thought we should talk about this thing.
What was the weight? 15, maybe less, maybe like 10.
Wow. Yeah.
And I think it's a nice area to hang, especially at night.
Like that's an area that you maybe don't want to do in a hot summer sun.
But at night with those mad tea party lanterns
and the Matterhorn looks cool at night, I think that's and that's another thing
real estate wise that you get in the shadow of the of the Matterhorn.
And when you come out on that second layer, you get them at the Matterhorn
off in the distance.
It's a cool little pocket over there.
Yeah, it is. I went on this a couple of weeks ago with friend of the show,
Andrew Grissom, and then we went on that on the teacups right after.
This was like the last 15 minutes.
So we crammed we were like, can we do teacups right at the end?
And we got it like two minutes before. Nice.
And yeah, hell yeah.
What a hell yeah.
Rock and roll. Right.
Midnight teacup ride.
Too bad, Espros.
Too cool boys.
Yeah, I think I yeah, that night.
This is one of those I like.
It looks OK during the day, but at night it looks amazing.
I kind of I kind of feel like the outside of the ride looks OK
during the day. It's not my favorite visually of like the queue
and like of the exterior.
But at night, it's awesome. I don't know.
Well, you know, that might be a point in Mr.
Toad's favor that that the little like
the little outdoor courtyard part of that line is very neat.
And then you get inside and that that wooden toad statue and you're
you know, you're looking at the bookcase, the entry area.
Yeah. So that might be an argument that notches it over to Toad.
But right, because the area about round Alice doesn't beckon me until the night.
Night, I feel beckoned by it, but not during the day.
Not that I just go, oh, there's that like cramped little line and like,
oh, yeah, yeah, the outside looks OK.
And then I then I remember, oh, it's a great ride.
It's a great dark ride.
You know what? I think you got to give it some credit for is that
I think I think you're correct today, you're saying.
But I think the that in 58 when it opened,
think about how this was not the new fantasy land that Tony Baxter oversaw
in the 80s when the fantasy land opened, it was much more of these
these flat carnival exteriors.
And then this thing joins three years after.
And it's a much more dynamic
exterior than all of them with the with the caterpillars
coming down that big vine.
You call it a vine or a leaf trail or what you call it.
But I think it was a super dynamic exterior compared to the other ones in.
Right at the time, for sure.
And it's two stories.
Yeah, coming out on the top.
The majority of the ride is the takes place over top of Mr.
Toad. Yeah, which I never knew.
You were above Mr. Toad.
And then the strange is where the duplex of attractions.
That's a good did.
I didn't see this when I was looking up.
But is it a situation where if like a fire alarm gets pulled on Toad,
they have to shut Alice down? I would think because that's the
that's the problem they're having with Avatar is that the river
ride and flight of passage are in the same building.
So if a fire alarm gets pulled in one of them, they have to shut both rides down,
which just destroys capacity for the land for an hour.
The whole part, I'm sure.
So I wonder if that's the same situation or maybe it just rarely happens.
It's interesting this guy ride got built at all
because the Alice movie was considered a flop on its first release in 1951.
Disney himself thought the problem was it didn't have a lot of heart.
The movie has multiple directors, I believe, five credited directors.
Really? Yeah.
And so like he threw it on like this,
an early episode of the Disneyland TV show, he like tossed it on there.
They cut it down to an hour.
Cut it down to an hour.
Well, I mean, then the the re releases is when it got successful,
especially during the psychedelic 60s.
Oh, yes. And they re released it with that in mind.
Yeah. Nodded to like for Disney, oddly cheeky to nod to the Jefferson
airplane, White Rabbit song.
I watched a video, a yesterworld video that was talking about a lot of this stuff.
And there's like clips of Alice Wonderland.
And let me this is a realization I had as I was looking all this stuff up.
I love Alice in Wonderland.
And I didn't remember if you asked me last week, I would have said,
oh, yeah, I like some of it.
I like to I apparently love Alice in Wonderland, the movie, the Disney movie.
Because as I was watching this, then I went and just watched clips from the movie.
I went, oh, yeah.
Like, I guess I haven't watched this in 25 years.
But so many that just like the shot of Alice looking through
the handles on the teak on the teapots.
I was like, oh, my God.
Like, I just started like getting child memories of like, oh, awesome.
Awesome. All like her in the room shrinking, growing big with a doorknob.
I remember just being fascinated by this.
And it was dormant in me up until hours, like days ago.
I rewatched when Netflix very first started
streaming a lot of the old, old Disney movies, like six or seven years ago.
I rewatched a bunch and I was shocked at how similarly how much I enjoyed Alice.
The characters are fantastic.
The design is great. The colors are amazing.
And then I was shocked how short it is.
It's only 75 minutes long.
But it moves and everything like it's all great voice actors.
All the character designs are specific.
All the sequences are very, very imaginative, very imaginative.
Sorry to correct myself.
There were three credited directors, but 13 people had the story by credit.
Wow. Wow. Yes. Yeah.
So that that was another criticism of the time of like, oh, is it to just join in?
Are there too many cooks on this one?
I guess the fact that it is all of these little like disconnected sequences.
Yeah. Way. Maybe that was the the Waltz
like insecurity at the time was is like there's not this
big story that you feel this emotion about.
But I think maybe I liked it for that reason, because I yeah, I you know,
my favorite things as a kid were specials and whatever.
And Sesame Street, which is a new thing every two minutes.
And I liked it for that reason that it was like a lot of like
just choppy little.
I think that's the source material is is split up.
And Alice's adventures in Wonderland and through the looking glass
is kind of split up into chunks. Sure. Yeah.
So I yeah, I read the Queen of which playing croquet.
I was like, I love this. Yeah.
I forgot I loved this.
The painting of the roses has just a real I just have some like baby brain.
Yeah. I meant to I just think that's neat. Yeah.
Somehow, for sure.
I think all of that stuff and I honestly going on this
the ride a couple of weeks ago, it didn't necessarily unlock
what I felt watching the clips of the movie.
So I still really like the ride.
I just didn't quite I didn't remember yet
that I loved Alice in Wonderland.
So I so it's official.
I love Alice in Wonderland, the Disney movie. Sure.
And you adore the two Tim Burton ones, right?
No, I didn't say that.
Twisted. I did not say that.
Hugely popular internationally.
Oh, yeah. Very successful.
Second one. Second one, I don't think as much, but probably not as much.
But there's like a walkthrough garden at the Shanghai Disney.
Like, oh, yes. In Shanghai, the attraction is the gigantic
Helena Bonham Carter head. Yes.
Which is a rare case of the live action
remake getting the parks treatment over the cartoon.
Yeah. I walked by a Lion King Cart at California Adventure, and I was like,
why is it stupid old simple Simba
and not the fully dimensionalized, the photo real lion that I love?
Why is this my dad's Simba?
Yeah, I want this real lion that can't really open its mouth.
I don't want the one voice by James Earl Jones.
I want the one voice by James Earl Jones.
I guess we are wrong.
The second one only made 300 million and the first one made a billion.
Yikes. Wow. So I mean, a lot of money, but like that's one Star Wars land.
Yeah. One is a massive hit and the other is like great drop offs.
And who would ever blame them for making a sequel? Right.
They'd be like, this is slam dunk.
Yeah. What what does that is that one of those people
that didn't actually like it as much as they thought?
Yeah, it might be the Johnny Depp syndrome.
They were saying that was that internationally.
I don't think I though the Fantastic Beasts had a very similar.
Yeah, but this is years before that.
Yeah. I don't.
And I think especially I don't know who was keeping.
I don't know why.
That's why the latest Hollywood vampires
see the as opposed to the first one sold 1200 copies.
This one only sold the nine and nine hundred fifty. Yeah.
So Johnny Depp, precipitous.
Depth effect.
Let's let's say is personally just more like I think people are a little
that coincides with people being burned out.
I mean, yes, that's like it's going to be him.
He's going to be doing a voice doesn't have the same effects that it used to.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
People have been let down by those a number of times.
Remember when we all watched the Kevin Smith film in which you.
Yoga hosers. Yes.
Started fast forwarding through it.
Almighty listener might not have heard those words.
They might not know that Johnny Depp is in this film and you might watch it
and you might not even see him.
But keep an eye on a certain plastic looking man.
Your favorite character from Tusk might make a reappearance.
Is it the same character?
It's the same private detective character.
What? This is another this is a second view of skewniverse.
There is a second view of skewniverse that has the Tusk
yoga hosers and then isn't there one more or or did it not get made?
I don't think the third one got me.
Red State is not in this second view of skewniverse.
No, I think Red State stands alone.
OK, I forgot about Red State.
I watched Red State, too.
Mm hmm. And it's not.
Why am I having the Johnny Depp detective movie?
Oh, Mordecai. The one you love.
Yes. It's not Mordecai.
He's not playing Mordecai in these either.
That's a different universe.
I would you also believe that these,
you know, Red State and yoga hosers also not represented in the Disney park.
Shopping. Did they buy?
Did Disney buy those?
Do they own some of it via Miramax?
I know Miramax doesn't some Miramax isn't really them anymore.
Yeah, right. They sold that.
So that's a whole but then, yeah,
we'll have to look into that. Don't know.
Yes. Candy, you're an update.
My teeth are starting to hurt.
Yeah, I've got a bad feeling in the back of my throat.
I'm feeling my molars. Are we sick now?
I drugged you unknowingly.
I'm sorry.
But maybe but maybe we don't even realize how good and crazy this episode is.
And people tell us you didn't even know you were you were tripping
and you just thought that your teeth hurt.
But really, you are on the right of your lives.
One pill makes you a larger one pill makes you small.
You know, I'm going to set my next your throat taste like shit.
The urine now is sitting on this
this table I have next to the couch right by Dexter Jekster,
my Dexter Jekster toy from Attack of the Clones,
diner owner from Attack of the Clones.
And as soon as I see him start moving,
oh, no, it's kick time.
You know, looking at it earlier, I did get the feeling of when like
the Ghostbusters are trepidatiously standing around the ooze.
And then Ray makes the toaster dance Ghostbusters to.
OK, yeah, that's right.
They realize it can be be positive as well.
But right now, still at the negative feeling towards it.
If Dexter starts scooping up that urine and using it in some recipes.
So if I play higher and higher,
Jackie Wilson, Jackie Wilson's higher and higher than maybe pure.
Something good will happen.
Something good, something pure.
Am I quoting that correctly?
That is correct.
Yeah.
Nobody says this line like get a gunpoint way.
You can tell he's kind of like, I don't think I like the narrative
thrust of this movie as much.
He's checked out already.
I think so, yeah.
But he will be in the new one.
You think he's now like just when they all do whatever you want.
I mean, you'd probably be like tilted two days on it.
He's not going to be in it.
I mean, he was in the other one, too.
He did the other one.
He did the press for the other one.
Mm hmm. Oh, yeah, that's right.
Right. Yeah.
So like, I don't know, he he probably needs money.
Yeah, that's right.
Now, he owns a minor like baseball team.
That's one of those things that you would think like
like, because like, you know, Bill Murray press on the Internet is so.
Oh, my God.
Jesus Christ have through have risen again.
Bill fucking Murray.
And then like, oh, my God, he's going to be in the new one.
And he was nobody care.
And then it'll be like, yeah, right.
The new one again.
People go, holy shit, stop the fucking presses.
Bill. And then he will be in no one like that either.
And only the same thing.
And yeah, I know the mist.
That's another my mistake.
There might be the Bill Murray effect is what you're referring to
where there's diminishing returns.
I think, yes, similar to the Johnny Depp effect.
Yes, there's a bill Murray effects.
And but there will never, never be a diminishing amount of blog
articles about Bill Murray doing anything and bothering people at parties and
being annoying. Yeah.
Running around being annoying and getting away with it.
Well, I guess I'm so polite.
Look, hey, we like things he used to do.
This is nothing to do with the.
I'm not trying to form an anti Bill Murray stance.
No, but it's an anti Bill Murray culture stance.
I think that's it.
I guess the culture, that's the problem.
Wandering 60 something year old man.
But you kind of liked him as blue live.
I did like him as blue.
I'm just I'm not as big of a fan of him.
I seem like roaming from town to town.
Touching people like and saying, you'll never believe that I was here.
But that's the story.
If Baloo the bear walked in and said, you never believe I was here.
Amazing.
You'll never believe what a terrible father I was in real life.
Baloo saying that.
Yeah, you regret his time with Mowgli.
Didn't do a good job.
My little buddy boy.
Great pilot, though. Great pilot.
Kept on carnage and check.
So Alice and Wonderland.
Always happy to see
an Ed Wynn vehicle.
Ed Wynn, of course, and Alice is a Mad Hatter.
Yeah. Which was a newer edition during the 1980s.
Re-update.
Oh, so they didn't talk before.
Well, they did. It was like a nightmare.
OK, so the original version of this was a nightmare.
That's the revelation of the Yesterworld video, which I didn't know because
old Claude Coats Claude Coats was involved.
Wanted to make it creepy.
And Claude Coats was the person responsible for
Snow White's scary adventures in Florida being so scary.
Yeah. And the scarier part of the Haunted Mansion.
Haunted Mansion, the earlier stuff.
OK, OK. Yeah, because it was Mark Davis and Claude Coats
who ultimately both had the biggest influence on when they finally decided
on what they were doing with Haunted Mansion and Claude wanted it scary.
Mark wanted it whimsical. OK, OK.
And Claude was a real creep.
I mean, I'm just saying like a fun crew.
Yeah, I know. I don't know anything about him personally.
Well, because you got to, you know, I mean, because I was looking up Claude Coats
stuff in relation to this, and it is very impressive that he was like
he was a background painter on so many of the early animated films.
And then he, you know, one of those that we talk about where Walt says,
all right, you're going here now.
And he just without missing a beat does it.
I read an interview where he talked about how
it's basically like with Disneyland set to open in a couple of months.
Walt says, hey, we've come down and maybe do some painting and stuff.
And then the story changes to, hey, that that professional scenic
painting company that I hired, they only have time to do Peter Pan and Snow White.
So you got to paint Mr. Toad.
And he's he says, well, so I was going from a medium
that was 20 inches to 18 feet.
He's completely shifting the kind of painting he's doing.
Did incredible job.
And he worked on all the other ones, too.
So he worked on the first three dark rides.
And then this was his chance to go to town and design it all.
Yeah. Ken Anderson also in a similar boat
where like worked on the original movies, painting the original movies.
And then he's painting the rides, you know, weird.
And that it's some of the same people from like he paint
that he did backgrounds on Snow White and then is, you know,
a couple of decades later doing the same
going taking you back into that world, but in a whole other medium.
Pretty. Yeah.
But it's to where like this guy, it's all him.
The exterior is him, the way it plays out.
The story is him.
The track layout is him.
And the vehicle is him.
Like the sketches are Claude Coates. Right.
And I found a story about that where he wanted the right vehicles
to be playing cards.
He showed that to Walt.
Walt said, I don't like it. Do a caterpillar.
And then he sketched up a caterpillar by the end of the day.
And that was that.
And then they somebody came around and said, we need you to fill out a form
to because we have to patent this vehicle.
And he said, I wouldn't feel right patenting it.
It was Walt's idea.
Wow. They said they actually said, no, no, no.
You will be on the patent.
And for that, he got an extra ten dollars from the company.
Wow. Wow.
But in but the patent office has, you know, like a very clinical drawing of,
you can't make your own caterpillar vehicle.
That's cool. Yeah. Yeah.
Stuff. It does seem like because Snow White, scary adventure
is the one everyone talks about as being really scary.
And I obviously didn't go on this original version.
I was not alive, nor did I visit Disneyland till the 2000s.
But it does have a similar vibe from the pictures
that are in that yesterworld video of like of like
a little twisted in relation to actually what the character designs were.
Like he was going for something like a little surreal and a little scarier.
Because the Cheshire cat is like a warped version of the Cheshire cat.
And I think it seems like it's on purpose.
With like gigantic pupils.
Yeah. Like what? Like super dilated.
Like what's happening to us is this urine kicks in. Right.
You guys look crazy.
If you looked in a mirror lately.
And it seems like it's focused like much like Snow White.
It focuses on like the scary stuff versus the fun stuff.
Yeah. Yeah. Like the Mad Tea Party.
There's no fun element of it.
It's just big cutouts of the March of the March hair and the man.
They're giant heads and smiling demonic smiles.
Yeah. Noise unsettling noises supposedly.
And just like there's the flowers look creepy as hell.
Like jump out at you.
If there's there's spinning teapots
or teacups in this ride, there are any more original version.
And they're spinning wildly.
And it kind of looks like they're going to slam into your vehicle.
Which I like. I think they should have put that in still.
That's kind of cool.
That's one of the things I was like,
I get why this can't be like weird and surreal anymore.
But I was like, those teacups sound fun.
Yeah. Because there's something similar.
Like it reminded me a little bit of the Pooh's Honey Hunt
with the trackless vehicles.
Yeah. That shoot a character car at you.
And I was yeah, I was thinking of that when I watched a different video.
And forgive me, I don't have the credit for it.
But some some other videos said that in the early days, the Mad Tea Party,
that the characters might come in and like join you in their car.
Like Jason tried to do with a couple on the inside out emotional whirlwind.
I went on my own emotional whirlwind.
Step one shame.
But this was a ride I forgot to mention when we talked about emotional whirlwind.
When they rethemed that, they flew it to Italy to be redesigned,
because that where the manufacturer was. Really?
This ride they were able to do in Anaheim.
But there's been, you know, Jim and Len were talking recently about how long
it takes Imagineering to announce something and then get it built and opened.
Maybe it's the flying stuff to Italy is slowing stuff down.
I feel like they did the new fantasy land in the 80s reasonably quickly.
They just banged it out. The grand scheme of things.
Yeah. Yeah. We blew it up.
They blew a big hole. Yeah, they blew a big hole.
Speaking of that big hole,
I saw pictures in that yester yesterworld video.
I had never seen what it actually looked like when they were redoing everything.
Me neither. Yeah. And boy, it's chaos.
It's scary. Yeah.
Because like they got it, those dark rides in fantasy land
when they were making new fantasy land.
And there is just a big chunk taken out of the castle.
I don't know where he got these photos because I've never seen them before.
But they're just it's terrified.
It's like what everyone imagines, like the post apocalyptic theme park looks like.
And it's just a castle pieces of the castle gutted, just empty thing,
because they took everything out of those dark rides to redo them.
Which is what Tony Baxter has talked about, that he like when it was in that state,
he was looking around like, what have I done?
And I can totally I mean, I knew it in the abstract, but now seeing the pictures,
I would if I was standing in there, I'd go, oh, my God.
Yeah, that would be traumatic. That's traumatic.
Well, imagine if like a kid somehow got a view of that
because the park never closed.
But in but to redo fantasy land in the 80s, they did close all of fantasy land
and they lifted the drawbridge so nobody could go into fantasy land.
And if a kid had somehow like snuck in there and gotten a view and like, oh, my God.
Could you see it on the skyway?
Oh, I don't know what they did on the skyway.
Because if that's a good question. Oh, yeah.
Because maybe you would just see just holes punched
into the side of fantasy land in the castle.
Yeah, I had stomped around like the Jack and the Beanstalk giant
just kicked doors in was just like the pirate ship.
They were going to try to save the Peter Pan pirate ship.
And when they tried to move it, it was just too many years of wear and tear.
And it just started collapsing. Right.
It's funny that there were guests stomping around on that all day, every day.
And they tried to move it once and it fell apart. Yeah. Yeah.
Like like a slight nudge.
I found another related thing from Tony Baxter.
But I'm pulling a lot of stuff from the the ticket magazine.
I went and found my issue of that about Alice in Wonderland magazine in the
I think it's in there that Tony Baxter is quoted as saying that he would like
he he like especially fell in love with the Alice in Wonderland ride
while like looking down on it from Holiday Hill.
Oh, what a holiday.
Oh, what the make out pill is this?
Yeah. Yeah. This weird like I forgot about that part of it.
It was a matter of it was my matter of runs, right?
Yeah. Just kind of a big mountain.
We're better than that.
And teens would go up in neck.
Oh, boy. Not Tony, not our Tony.
No, Tony wouldn't disrespect the park like that.
But I other teens went and looked at at track layout.
And that's why he is where he is today.
I do like the idea of like just so many teens making out and Tony's
like sitting in between just like ignoring all of them,
but like sketching the track layout of a drafting paper.
And yeah, well, you like that idea because that's
what I would do. Three of us.
Yeah. Yeah, really.
But so yeah, but he you know, it's interesting that he said that he like
yeah, he loved looking down on the way the vehicles moved and slinked around
from the second floor down to the first on that big vine piece.
But then when he went on the ride, he always felt like and that's it.
And that's that childhood feeling of like it's not as good as what I want it to be
when I'm looking at it from afar.
He got to go in and like make it right in his head
and give you this bang at the end of with the the unbirthday scene
and the big, yeah, little extra room that they had because I was not there until 83.
No, that sequence was upstairs where the Queen of Hearts is.
And they were able to move in and of course, redo it
and add all the animatronics
in the 80s redo.
And that opened up the space for that Queen of Hearts sequence.
And the King of Hearts is there, too.
He's real little and he's behind the Queen.
He's a little short king, but he's not a short king in our current definition of it.
But what do you mean?
He's a little short king, but not in the common, not in the common,
not in the way the kids say short kings, where it's like shorter, confident people.
Oh, it's like me.
I was going to say, I've seen people online refer to you as a short.
Yeah.
So I think that's what you're getting.
I have. Yeah. Yeah.
Probably on our Facebook group, but
people are saying, but people are saying people are talking with the short kings.
Yeah. So this one.
Yeah. So, yeah, it would just end.
I haven't actually seen the video of it.
I think it was just the vine would wrap around back to the loading.
Right. Vine kind of was the ending.
Yeah. And then originally, too, like all the other fantasy land rides,
this was just your first person like you were supposed to be Alice initially.
Yes, correct. Alice was not visible anywhere.
And Alice didn't even speak as she does today because in 83,
they added narration when you're going down the rabbit hole.
And they got the original voice actress, Catherine Beaumont,
who was also the voice of Wendy.
Oh, and it's still alive.
Wow. And like was still doing voice, like still like
adding voice stuff, apparently up until 10 years ago or something.
I don't know the actual amount of time, but still sounded enough like,
yeah, like your young self.
That's amazing. So that's fun.
You know, it's the thing I want to give this ride credit for is
somebody somebody correct me if I'm wrong, but is this is this the first
Disneyland or Disney theme park indoor outdoor attraction?
Oh, that's interesting.
I cannot think about that of what else that might be.
You may have to people who are tunnel.
And that wasn't there yet.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
You may have to take tunnels out of this definition.
Train counts as an indoor outdoor ride. Huh?
Dude, our tunnels do tunnels count is question one.
What was mine train?
When was mine train through nature's wonderland?
There was some version of that, but I'm not sure that it had indoor scenes.
Yeah, yeah.
And count. I could be wrong about that one, but I couldn't.
I don't know. Yeah, you're probably right.
Because it's 58. So it's like it's not.
There haven't been too many.
I haven't been too many rides in general.
Many attractions. Yeah.
I mean, it's certainly unique, especially under the crop of Disneyland,
Fantasyland rides and the building alone.
Like you were saying, the facades all used to just be kind of tense
before they they gussied them up in the 80s.
But this was always, you know, the sort of castly looking thing, wasn't it?
Let's see. I think I like that.
It's that it's castle that it feels like an extension of the castle.
It's like ties everything together.
Yeah, I see. Yeah.
I also like that little bathroom nook over.
That's one of the bathrooms.
I'm most fond of, you know, with the Cheshire cat
poking out nearby and isn't that great?
Isn't the men's sign is the is the short.
That's a great photo spot is the Cheshire cat.
The bathrooms. Yeah.
Oh, the bathrooms. Yes. OK.
All bathrooms are great.
He's like just above head like your head.
That's fun. Like you can get some fun pics there.
I think I have several over the years.
Fake rocks. Fake rocks.
Yeah. Good point.
I think they recently had to redo the outdoor squiggly part of the track
because of what?
Safety safety regulations.
And that part is my own like that part could look maybe a little better,
but that's sort of we're not happy about how wide.
Yeah. That track became.
Yeah, I get it.
And there's like there's no other way to do it.
It is what it is. Yeah.
But the other the everything else I like.
But you know, it's you know, it's the thing I really like is how,
you know, it's right.
So the car goes outdoors.
So you're waiting and you can see the path.
You can see what it's going to do.
But not until you come out of those doors and are actually on the ride.
You see the other side of that open book and see the little
the little shoes left behind. Oh, yeah.
On top of that toast.
I like how that's a little like that's a little secret.
And you don't get to find out about it unless you actually
brave enough to go on the ride.
The mushroom. Yeah.
On top of the mushroom. That used to be the ticket booth.
That's a nod.
That's a nod because it was in the yesterday world video where there's
like a people thought that the caterpillar was in the ticket booth.
Well, the idea I believe what I read was that
it's a nod that the caterpillar turned into a like pitter
pattered away. I see.
Off of that mushroom or turn it to a butterfly.
This is coming back into my head.
Something weird.
I was feeling OK.
And then like some weird taste started hitting me in the mouth a little bit.
We shouldn't say we all had.
I mean, I don't know how to say the amount, but it was like less than
a few spoons. You gave us a spoonful of piss.
Mm hmm. A real mild
of spoonful of piss and just a spoonful of piss.
In the least delightful way.
Yeah. As an aftertie.
Yeah. Yeah.
Aperty for.
We'll keep giving you progress reports, but I don't think it's going anywhere
good for any. No, it's not.
The let's see.
Where was I?
I think. Oh, yeah.
The initial plans for this was a walkthrough.
OK. It was not going to be a dark ride.
They eventually did a walkthrough in Paris,
mostly just of the Queen of Hearts stuff.
Right. You did it right.
I don't know if I don't think I ended up going into it.
OK. I like the idea of that.
And there's a restaurant in Tokyo.
There's Queen of Hearts.
Oh, yeah, there is. Yeah.
That was unbelievably crowded when I was passing by.
It's very popular.
Yeah. And but it was going to be a walkthrough.
There's I think this is all from that yesterworld thing, I think.
And there was a land.
It was going to be a thing called Anything Can Happen land,
which is I think not a good thing to say.
No rules, no laws.
Yeah. Maybe that's not good.
I mean, I guess if that was still the case, like then we wouldn't be upset
with the caterpillar smoking his opium.
Because anything can happen.
Yeah. Yeah.
Anything can go down.
It's a good thing Holiday Hill was not at Anything Can Happen land.
Oh, boy.
Because then it would have been, you know, babies could happen.
Morgy on Holiday Hill.
But it was going to be a walkthrough.
And this is going to be the only only ride I see
where I almost see the value in it being a walkthrough as opposed to
a ride vehicle. Yeah.
Because like Pirates was going to be a walkthrough upon a mansion walkthrough.
And then they became right.
And I'm like, I don't know.
I mean, a haunted mansion would be really cool to walk through it, too.
But this one especially, because like they were going to have a scene
like Alice in the room where she doesn't know how to get out
and the door handle and talking.
And I was like that proportions of that in my mind seem very cool
to be able to walk into that room that is all fucked up.
Like it's the scene in The Simpsons where they rebuild Ned's house.
And it's like that would be fun to like, yeah, do that.
And it's Willy Wonka.
Same thing where it's like the proportions are weird. Right.
And maybe that's just too hard to like
people would trip over, like angles and things.
Probably hard to do.
But walking is an inherent part of Alice in Wonderland.
She's like wandering through trying to find a way out from this.
Let's call it a nightmare world, like a whimsical, but then frustrating
dream place.
Because the ride as it is now is a very good, very good dark ride of Alice.
But I do think you're missing some of like the trippy stuff,
which maybe you got a little more from the original version of it being like
kind of this hallucinogenic thing.
But I was like, if you're walking through a couple of those things
where the proportions are all weird and you're sort of like,
I don't know, you're questioning how big you are versus something else.
I don't know that did.
I when I was watching that, I was like, oh, this would be real cool
if they could have done something that would have given you a little bit
of a taste of of that movie or feeling like.
Well, I think I think walkthroughs as a genre just never really took off for them.
Right. Yeah. They're rare at this point in time.
One of those in Disney Paris and a cool one, this 20,000 leagues
thing in Discoveryland.
But besides that, they don't frequently.
I think it was on Jim and Len.
And I didn't even realize this in Hong Kong.
They do Halloween mazes.
Really? Walk through mazes behind Main Street.
Whoa. Or like maybe alongside, like behind the shops on Main Street.
I'm unclear of where it is.
But in general, yeah, Disney doesn't do that.
That has become a thing with Universal and Nats and everything
with the Halloween stuff.
But in general, I guess, I guess, I don't know.
It's easier to control people if they're an old vehicle.
Yeah. Maybe that's why.
But it does feel like certain things would be real cool.
Well, the walkthrough Sleeping Beauty Castle, I guess.
It's true. It's a walk through.
Nobody's ever up there.
Yeah, we walked up there.
I was there with my family not too long ago.
My mom likes it. It looks great, honestly.
It's real great. That's nice.
There's a couple of really great scenes.
The one where you look down into the. Yeah.
Castle is really cool.
Like, it's very cool.
It's obviously like low scale.
The scale isn't too big, but there was briefly a walk through
in Tomorrowland of sets and props from 20,000 leagues under the sea.
I think we talked about on that episode.
Like, that's where the Oregon first was before they used it for the Haunted Mansion.
And that was surprisingly a big hit.
Yeah.
So we walk through the cool thing.
I don't think about a walk through Disney.
That's all I'm saying.
It's not the worst way, especially to like, you know,
if you think of them as daytime haunt mazes.
Yeah, it's not the worst.
And if they have a bunch of props from something,
sooner, they do do this temporarily sometimes.
Yeah.
What do you mean?
Like like like maybe Universal has done this a tiny bit.
I think there was some like they I think they may have had like a Casper
walk through. Oh, really?
Around when Casper came out.
Did you was it a scare?
I mean, was it like lightly fun, scary or I don't think I don't know if I did it.
Was I too scared to go into a Casper walk through?
He was a ghost.
You got to give him that.
Certainly might have been a little boy, but he was a little ghost.
I do know what you mean of like short run, like
lightly set dress rooms and props and stuff is very popular.
Comic con too of like pop up.
Oh, yeah.
They did. I mean, they did do that Ninja Turtle one out here.
Yeah. They had it in the parking garage.
Oh, yeah.
And you would get a toy at the end.
I didn't do it. I've heard about it.
And I'm insanely jealous.
I can't believe I didn't do that.
It's why in the world was I not told my friend who had like one all the time
said you just get a toy every time.
I think it was one of the six core first line.
It wasn't like, yeah, it wasn't like you were getting man Ray or Mountie Moose.
I don't know those.
But I'm saying like it was a core like four turtles and maybe splinter
April shredder. But you get a toy.
Yeah. It's wild.
So you go through the sewer and then get a toy.
It's my dream. Walkthroughs are great.
You get toys. Yeah.
So I guess, yeah, they've they've been doing things here and there.
But yeah, this one, I mean, it makes sense now that they've done
like two versions of an Alice in Wonderland, because so much of it
lends itself to being something you should walk through.
Mm hmm. Yeah.
So many of the scenes.
But like the rides are popular, like Waterworld, like Waterworld.
First Waterworld. Yes.
Yeah, I guess so.
And it has in like Waterworld as a smoker.
The cat. Yeah, it has.
Yeah.
So anyway, I was a they owe some money to Disney.
Yeah, they do.
They owe money to a lot of people still.
Yeah.
So yeah, I mean, I think it's a lot of people.
Yeah, they do.
They owe money to a lot of people still.
Well, for that fire.
I think I think I heard something crazy, like five years ago,
once you factored in DVD sales, Waterworld had made back its budget.
Really? Something like that.
It was like so expensive.
Ended up being a hit, though.
Well, not a hit. A breakeven. A breakeven. Yeah.
Would they count, though, the revenue brought in by the Waterworld show
at Universal? Does that go into its official?
I don't know that.
How do you section off that revenue as?
That's what Jim Hill was talking about, though, with the Fox properties,
where it's like Disney wants to recoup the money.
So they're going to put the properties in the parks.
So they do like in their minds figure that being a way to offset the cost,
I guess. Yeah.
Because if you're going to come for a new thing or a show you like,
you're going to come and see the Ice Age characters
take over half of Animal Kingdom, which is what he's rumored.
Which still seems crazy.
But he says it more than one.
He says it so often that somebody had to have told him that.
So there has to be some chatter about Ice Age.
It's crazy.
Who knows what sort of mischiefs Skitter and Scrat and
I could not even think of one character and all of those characters we love.
Are those real names?
I think Scrat is real.
But do you go to Scribler?
Scribler.
I don't I confuse Ice Age and Madagascar.
Yeah. Well, you won't soon.
I won't know after they're there every park.
And we get full Ice Age Kingdom, the fifth gate in Disneyland.
Disney World.
Oh, yeah. What did I say?
You said fifth gate in Disneyland.
OK, yeah.
It'll be the fifth gate in Disneyland as well.
OK, so there'll be a hundred years from now.
Yeah.
There'll be two other Fox properties that are the third and fourth gate.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. They'll do full.
Seth McFarland Park.
Yeah. Yeah.
McFarland Park.
Sethi land.
Sethi land is the best.
You go to Kohog.
You ride on the Orville.
You go to the Pentagon with Stan from American Dad.
And then the old million ways to die in the Westland.
Oh, million ways down the West.
And of course, Ted Ted talk like Turtletalk.
Yeah. Watch out.
Ted talk.
We're not.
Ted's not leaving his paws off of you.
Mm hmm.
And then, yeah, there's like a teenager playing Ted
behind a screen like Turtletalk.
Mm hmm. Great.
And then shall add a nice and when you head to the croon in kingdom.
Oh, my gosh. That's most of the park.
Seth has a lot to say.
He's the one who designed it.
So, yeah, that's seven.
He personally hired all of the crooners.
They all are doing.
They all look like him, though.
It's the reverse of Oga's Cantina, where that when everyone wants to get
into this small bar.
But crooner kingdom is like a supper club that seats five hundred
and is never full.
Come on, it's just rude.
Come on in.
Go on.
There's human beings in here.
Oh, it's possible.
Makes you so big.
All of this is possible, honestly.
Yeah. Anything is possible in the blue sky.
My God. That's true.
See you in Sethi land.
Sethi land. So what else?
The original and now it still has not to it.
Goofy is on this ride.
What? Yeah.
Goofy has the original had three goofy screams.
Yeah.
But you're like leaving out every door.
Yeah. When you go out the doors to the second level,
it's like you're being like tossed out there
kind of as the blinding light of day hits you.
And now there still is the one is the Yahoo.
Right. The famous old screen.
But there's three goofy screams for whatever reason.
They I guess they thought it was a little nod to goofy.
So strange. I don't know why.
Very strange.
There's not a scream in Alice in Wonderland.
But but then it sort of gets into the Wilhelm scream territory.
Like that's the Disney scream.
Right. Which I sort of like.
Yeah. I know. I don't hate that.
Yeah. Yeah.
I like I mean, I really like when you go outside,
as you were saying, like a night.
The view of the Matterhorn is great.
And especially now that so many years have passed, that big tree in front of the ride,
he looks that the scale of just because it's so huge now.
And it's almost cut to me.
It almost looks like a a large bush.
Like you were looking up at a massive like bush, like in the polo scenes.
Yeah, I see what you're saying.
I had not thought of that.
Wow. It's like a big bush.
Like a big bush.
But it adds to the feeling of smallness that you've been shrunk down.
I thought that too.
Tree looks like a bush. All right.
No, I'm saying people are like us.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
Another into it. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's it's now just like I mean, it is just like, what do you what do you like?
Because I like a lot.
Yeah. And I don't know.
All these episodes don't have to be snark fest.
No. And I like stuff we drink.
Remember, we drank piss at the start of the journey.
And getting this by drinking your own.
So we were allowed to be a little.
I like that these animatronics more statuesque animatronics
do have movement to them.
Like they sort of look in the vein of the Pixar fear statues.
Sure. That statue pier, the old statue pier.
These guys move. They like move a little like that.
That's what happened in 83.
Was that you got more dimensional figures and they weren't all
two dimensional cutouts.
The other thing is, according to Tony Baxter,
the the original ride was it was super blacklight.
They were really leaning on the blacklight for the for the surrealism
and almost like it was like the point of it was how much blacklight there was.
And that also, I think I think I'm right.
Like that gave it like a 3D effect a little bit.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Flats mostly.
And that would kind of give it a little bit of dimension.
Very novel at the time.
It was a way to I think maybe
it was Claude Coates pointing this out himself in some movies about how
a giant space you wouldn't you wouldn't want to use blacklight.
It's too hard to fill.
Like pirates doesn't need it because they have so much space.
They can make it look super huge.
But in a narrow space, these tricks like blacklight are very important
to make it seem like a bigger Vistas than it is. Right.
But by the time like,
you know, hey, this was not there.
There weren't, you know,
bong shops and such place and, you know, Bill Graham posters
that was made with blacklight.
This was not as common before the 60s and 70s.
So they could, you know, this was a neat style and aesthetic for 1958.
By the time the 80s rolls around, it seems like kind of a cheap chintzy trick,
which is why there was a discussion Tony had was like, that's still part of it.
That's the spirit of it.
And that's all of the dark rides will always have that.
But we have to fold in some different.
It's just an aspect rather than the main aspect.
Yeah. Right. Sorry, blacklight.
So, yeah, blacklight.
Blacklight on the Knights and White Saturn ride a lot, too.
Yeah, with that, we're back to that's the point of it.
Is looking at blacklight for a while. Right.
Because it's a rock and roll experience.
They do you guys get worried when you go on any of these rides
with the blacklight that you will look to, you know, because you look down
at your clothing and you see bizarre stains and such.
Do you ever wonder like, is this is this going to reveal something
I didn't even know was there?
Some like just full pants covering your car.
Like, did I did I pee myself and not realize it?
Some we were selling a lot of bodily fluids on this episode.
I am not I'm more worried that there's some sort of like food or drink.
Yeah, because that would show up the same way.
Anything like I don't want everybody to look around.
Oh, look, you can see things on our clothes.
Oh, my God. What is that?
Yeah, I am pretty sure as far as fluids, I'm good.
But like at lunch, did I spill a fuzzy tauntaun on my leg?
Yes, I perhaps did.
And will like the color or whatever artificial color that's in that
will that show up on my pants? Perhaps.
So that is a concern. Right.
But I think, yeah, other than that, I'm not too worried.
That being said, I could be surprised. I don't know.
Who knows, Jason? What about?
I think that's the reason why I'd have to agree with you.
Yeah. Does fudge show up on a blacklight?
That's a good question.
I don't know. Glow in the dark fudge.
Yeah. Does fudge glow in the dark?
Does anyone know the listeners?
If you have a blacklight and you can run to a cracker barrel,
if a forensics team were to go into your bedroom,
would they see fudge everywhere?
Yeah, it's stacked up to the ceiling.
So this is where that fudge supply went missing.
We found we got him.
Ladies and gentlemen, we got him.
Famous fudge heist.
If you took some of that jar of urine,
if we poured that on our pants and then went on a ride,
I think it would start talking to us.
Oh, my God. That's how that's how crazy the chemical.
And it would have Edwin's voice.
Which is what Edwin?
Oh, Edwin. Not your dog.
Not your dog. No, no, no. Edwin.
That was confused. Edwin's voice. Edwin's voice is Edwin.
That's what I do when Lindsay and I are together.
OK, kind of a wheezy.
Yeah. But Edwin is Edwin's voice.
Mm hmm. OK. So the piss would sound like that, I think. Sure. Sure.
It might sound different to everybody.
Mine might sound like like Edwin the dog. That's true.
I'm urine.
That was creepier than what you did.
Yeah. That's my.
What would your piss voice sound like?
Sorry to put you on the spot here, but I know.
You can come back. You can come back to it.
Yeah, let's circle back.
Circle back. I'm going to think on it.
We'll tease that for the very end of the episode.
Is that you'll debut your piss voice.
You know, you got it.
No, no, no. Save it for the end. Save it for the end.
We need a reason the listeners are going to want to keep listening to this.
Yeah. Yeah. Like the final little surprise, like the unbirthday ring.
Yeah. So if you want to go upstairs and workshop it, too.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Add in old clips of you another episode going, yeah, this is good.
This ride. I like it.
So they updated this.
They've updated a few times.
Twenty fourteen was last big.
Yes. And that was what Jason Glip.
He's not here.
I like it.
Sounds good. Sounds good.
It definitely improved things.
I ate some fudge.
So I forgot all about like all the digital stuff that they added to the ride,
which is great, like legit great.
I think it's my favorite of the recently added fantasy land.
Digital plus ups.
And it's the most I think the most obvious ones, I think.
It reminded me of like because in Pooh's Honey Hunt, they do a lot of that, too.
So I wonder if I don't know.
I'm sure the same people worked on it.
But there's so much they do so much stuff and they do it in such a good way.
And some of it's like subtle.
Some of it's like the subtle stuff works really well.
Just augment the scene, the stuff that's a little more in your face.
Like there's like there's just a little like the rabbit moving and stuff.
That's fun. It's just a little scene.
And then there's like they add like trippier things in the hallway
with the door and stuff.
It's great as soon as you go in.
Yeah, that big swirling.
That's it's like a super dynamic introduction.
Like it's really it really like makes it.
That's you could probably argue it's the best ride now,
even though I still think Peter Pan is I'm still on Team Pan.
But I do think like it feels the most modern of that and walk around
to the team because there's a big art.
We had, of course, that drag knockout drag down argument.
Toad or Pan is best dark red.
But I guess you really should throw Alice in there as well.
Yeah, I think it's in the conversation.
I think it has to be because, yes, it does.
I'm imagining the Civil War,
kept the Captain America Civil War poster with like J.M.
Barry staring down Lewis Carroll in terms of, you know,
the creators, the original creators of these
rides, the original two British weirdos made Pan and Alice
clash of the British British weirdos, British opium weirdos.
The scene with the cards, I can't like
there's mirrors in there, right?
Like they're to make it look more.
Or I mean, there used to be or is the effect changed?
I don't know. I don't know.
I went through and I was like, oh, there's so many of them.
Some point in time, there were mirrors.
I forget what it is now, but I love that.
I love the fact that you what you were saying about how it could be walked
through the fact that there are these like funhouse optical illusion
elements of it here and there is great.
And then all of the cards
shooting out from behind the Queen. Yes.
Oh, that's super dynamic.
Queen's face is projection now, too. Is that right?
That looks good.
I really like to learn in the in the 80s plus up, they color
match the flowers to Mary Blair's original colors in the film.
Oh, wow. I really like that attention.
I feel like it's it's of all the ones in fantasy land.
It's maybe the one that I would go on and think, oh, they recently built this.
Yeah, sure. Like with the other one, like Toad feels older and Pan,
like the thing that feels the oldest on Pan, of course, is that the track above you.
There's a couple of times when you lurch down and he feels like the things
about to come off the ceiling. Yeah.
Like that was fun until it slammed into the wall when we were on it.
Like it's slammed into the bumper.
Yeah. Yeah. When it comes back into docking, we were on it
and it just jammed in there and we're like, ah.
But there's a part where you're like, just going because it's such a pleasant,
beautiful ride.
And then there's a part where it kind of dips down. Yeah.
And it feels like it has to catch itself from like letting you swing.
There's something on the track there that's I guess.
Let me swing is my feeling as well.
But there's there's aspects of all of the rides.
And I know Pinocchio was newer, but this one feels the newest.
I mean, maybe they did put the most care into to updating it or the most money.
But I do think you could put me on this.
I go, oh, yeah, this is like newer, right?
Yeah. All the effects feel really modern.
And they've taken what was there and yeah, really made it feel new.
I think that's a credit to the movie, the source material, like aging
the best a little bit.
I mean, I yeah, I see what you're saying, because I think that the references are
people love that Lewis Carroll shit.
I even just like the 51, the original animated movie.
I mean, I feel like I was saying earlier holds up so well.
And people still like to do drugs.
So that's still sad. That's true.
Yes. Yes, I don't.
I don't care to.
But some people do.
So they they like it.
You're hooked on the most addictive drug at all.
Sugar, all those brightly colored candy drinks.
And I guess you're right.
Just been you've had a crazy straw into that cup of piss.
You've been you've been lying.
You've been like slurping it up.
You pulled out your own cup, your own one.
You had already bought yourself.
Yeah, I had a different a different company makes a different kind of candy.
Piss drinking it secretly.
You're disgusted because it's not as good as it is.
Not as good as my company.
Pepsi versus Coke.
Wonka Pepsi challenge wonka.
Mexico.
I was going to say Wonka makes a piss as well.
Yeah, Nestle makes a piss.
Now, that would have been a more unpleasant river for Augustus
gloop to fall into.
Oh, yeah. Oh, my boy.
My boy. Oh, no.
He is blinded by urine.
What if there should be a national pastime?
You're making a mockery of a national pastime.
A pretty good sketch would be a wonka candy factory,
but all novelty dirty candy.
River of candy piss.
Everlasting.
I don't know. You take it from there.
My boy is choking on a choking on a candy thong.
I was going to walk into the candy thong closet.
Now I can't breathe.
OK, a candy kidney stone.
Never left at everlasting kidney stone.
That is not, by the way, that's patented to me.
No one has gotten that yet.
No one has thought of that.
It's pretty good.
Make sure to offload this audio file and then mail it to yourself
and seal the envelope so you have it.
If he does it before it comes out.
A gray piece of candy.
That's a candy kidney stone.
Fucking I'm a genius.
The most desirable.
And so it's you have to suck on it to make it be small enough to pass.
Yes, exactly.
That's the whole point of it.
And by the time you're done, you probably will start forming real kidney stones.
Yeah, it is made of calcium.
Ingredient number one, calcium.
It's good for you.
Calcium and sugar.
It's also your build ups for a growing boy.
It's good for the elderly.
Yeah, they need that calcium supplement to supplement their bones.
Novelty gift for like look who it's nifty or 50 part.
Like you get like here's your jar of candy kidney stones.
You don't get them. Drink lots of water.
But do we eat these?
Do we think I know the logic for your bones, which are also aging?
Well, you can.
Yeah, you could bring it out at a party and say, like,
if there's a jar of 80 of them and like, hey, that's all.
That's how many old Mike has passed.
Guess the kidney stones in the jar, too.
That would be fun.
Get like a gust of gumballs. Sure.
There's a lot of things you could do with this. Great idea.
Unfortunately, if you look close enough in the Alice in Wonderland
ride at the man tea party on birthday scene,
they're offering like tea, crumpets, candy, kidney stones.
Got to get rid of these.
Some got to get rid of these candy kidney stones.
Yeah, that's good.
I don't know. This is real good.
I mean, it's you're right that there are we're talking about.
Are there other bodily fluids and we were avoiding certain ones, probably.
But what else can your body make?
You thought of one more. Bile. Yeah.
Oh, bile is good. Bile is great.
Bile is good. Bile is good. A bile drink.
You get a little cinnamon or a little pop rock.
So it's like, ah, it's corrosive. Right.
You know, that's good.
I think careful with cinnamon, folks.
Cinnamon can really fuck you up.
They really fuck up your life.
There's got to be rest stop water that's like
liberal tears or something for conservative people making a stop.
Right. And you're good at this.
This is another good one.
That's a good one. Right. Yeah.
It's just got to be like the sunny water.
Diminish our fine highway rest stops.
Sure. I'm well, they usually with these rest stop gift shops,
they, of course, are equal opportunity offenders.
You'll see the toilet, the Hillary toilet paper and the Trump toilet paper.
I suppose that's so they might have a different thing to roast the other side.
But the liberal tears water.
This is good. I should really leave this out because I probably would make a million dollars.
You are now the head of Flying J International.
Flying J is like the truck stop.
The rest stop.
She stopped at one in Barstow once.
OK. Yeah.
So that's good.
What's the so what's the conservative?
The equivalent is like
what comes out of your body?
You're so mad at what Cortez
tweeted that you pee yourself.
I'm not sure what.
Oh, I would just my first pitch, honestly, was gun water.
Doesn't make sense.
Why not?
Yeah, I don't know.
Or that you it's vomit.
That's it. It's vomit because what
Alexandria Casio Cortez said made you throw up in your mouth a little bit.
Right. Oh, that's still slamming liberals.
So that's still.
That doesn't read to you as like they're so like you could sell
candy panties in a bunch because your your panties are in a bunch.
You're so mad at what Cortez said.
OK, that's not bad.
Like candy, you make like, oh, make it
AOC, making America puke again.
Like you're not making America great again.
That one's back on her.
That's yeah, that's kind of back on her.
It needs to be something that like the conservatives do
that you could spin off into a candy or a drink.
They're like salivating because they want to fuck Trump.
Maybe that's a stretch.
How do you candy a brain aneurysm because you're just terminally online?
OK, headbandage.
Like, is that a candy head?
Oh, it's like fruit roll ups.
It's a headband.
It's a white mystery like airhead.
Like why?
Yeah, why does that old man have a bandage?
Yeah, that's good.
It's all a bottle of raindrops from our our perfect,
most beloved Fourth of July celebration of America.
That's going off.
Fracking water.
That's good.
Delicious fracking water oil, too, because, you know, like National Park
oil, because because more conservatives want to drill like national parks
and off the grill, drill that of Teddy Roosevelt's head.
And yeah, so it's like, yeah, like National Park oil,
Yellowstone oil.
Still not as it doesn't read quite as good as the T.
Liberal tears.
Joe Cicis, liberal tears.
The real tears is sort of the gold standard for this type of thing.
I think it's still in vibe.
It's va about its Pence.
This is Mike Pence's vomit because he saw a gay person smiling
or was in the room with a woman.
He was in the not his wife.
Well, then you could say that could be an assorted set
because he relieved himself in every way he threw.
Oh, yeah.
Shit because he was in the room with another woman and sweat.
All of them.
Uh, uh, that's a grab bag.
There could be like a pen that you flip over that a woman's clothes comes off.
And it's just like says like Mike Pence is a worst nightmare or something.
Or no, no, it wouldn't even be new.
No more.
We go on. Yes, yes, yes.
It was just like you turn the pen over and she would just say, hello,
we're in the room together.
And that would be it.
There wouldn't be any nudity.
The pen novelty pen where the clothes don't come off, the clothes don't come up.
She just says hello.
And then that's the worst.
Yeah, yeah, that's the worst it could be.
Oh, oh, thank God.
It was just a joke pen.
She thank you.
This has been a wonderful birthday.
She's like a full suit and turns it up and she's got like a winter coat on.
She says hello.
And his fantasy would just be a big candy Garfield
because he loves Garfield.
Is that true? Yeah.
Have you seen he there's a bizarre him like taking some time out of
like a congressional session or whatever to say that it's Jim Davis's birthday?
Oh, I have seen that.
I have a daughtering.
He's been making us laugh for 50 years.
He may not be perfect.
He doesn't care much for Mondays.
But the spirit of this cat is like the spirit of our nation.
Why they get Garfield's name out of your mouth.
Mr. Sir, Mr. Pence, sir.
Do we know?
Funnier than you.
But do we know Jim Davis's politics?
I believe he's pretty apolitical.
I believe that that seems right.
That's what's great about him.
Everybody who is just on another planet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who we have taken some turns on this one.
It's a kooky world of fouls and wonderland.
You know what? I like that there's a little dandelion projections flying around.
Yeah, that might be it.
That might be all I have.
I don't know. I'm running out.
It is one of those ones who is just good.
It's good.
And there's not a ton of like lore.
It's nice to just like rides.
But then you do then.
And we're just saying this thing's good and that thing's good.
I have some background on the manufacturer.
Oh, please.
Now we're getting to the good shit.
Arrow development.
Later, followed by Arrow dynamics.
They were involved in a lot of the early rides of Disneyland,
in fact, six opening day Disneyland rides,
Manatee Party, King Arthur Carousel, Mr.
Toad Dumbo, Casey Jr. and Snow White Scary Adventures.
Hmm. Yes.
And still around in Virginia, the state around in a different form, I believe.
I believe the one company went under and then reformed something like that.
But they helped out a lot of Disney rides through the year.
Alice, the Matterhorn, Flying Saucers,
the Mark four redesign of the Autopia cars.
Yeah. Good for them.
Good for them. Thanks, Arrow.
We salute you.
I will also say that the caterpillar cars were ultimately sculpted
by Blaine Gibson, which is weird because Blaine Gibson made a lot of the famous,
you know, like a lot of the great humanesque animatronics
like Abraham Lincoln, like all of the Hall of Presidents,
all the way up through George W.
Bush, when there was a new president, he would come out of retirement
and make the new president. Wow.
And and the the partners statue
was this guy, Waltz and Mickey holding hands.
But it's weird that you're in a ride vehicle that he merely he at least made
the mold and they made, you know, 16.
That's 16 of them total.
But yeah, which is that's the thing you got to give it credit for.
That it's a it's a cool ride vehicle.
And I think it's one of the one of the best of those darker red vehicles,
maybe one of the best in one of the most
one of the oddest, most specific ride vehicles in all of the. Yeah. Sure.
And it's a character, which is fun and different colors.
Always fun. Yeah.
And not dissimilar to the leaked Nintendo art or model.
Did you see that the leaked Nintendo land model where apparently,
yeah, it's not we're not getting it.
I hope Japan is getting it.
I guess because of space is that there seems to be a Yoshi Omnimover type.
Wow. Hell, yeah.
And they're just different colored Yoshi's.
I don't know how.
I don't know if it's one per Yoshi or like it's a little thing on his back.
Whatever it looks like, there's a cool outdoor indoor Yoshi Omnimover,
which reminded me of this because it's like all the same character,
but different colors. Yeah.
Which, God, I hope I hope that's in Japan because people are saying that's so bad.
Yeah. People were saying that like maybe this is like an initial model.
So we don't know. We don't have confirmation yet
that that is going somewhere, hopefully at least Florida,
because that's going to be the biggest one, supposedly.
And if the ride breaks, then every every Yoshi just scurries
in multiple directions until it falls into a pit.
Unless you can jump on top of it.
Yes. And they hurry.
They scream at you to get back on.
It's going to die.
I had such panic as a kid when I would get hit
and Yoshi would run around because I would say it was
it was traumatizing to seem like run off a cliff. Yeah.
Because like you'd hit and he would run around and you'd have to get him
before he hit off of a cliff.
And I would just feel such pressure.
And sometimes it wouldn't happen. And I'd feel depressed.
There's a lot of characters being murdered at all times in the Mario games.
Oh, yeah. Most of them are villains. Right.
And some of them are you and that's on you.
And you know, you'll be back watching your pal, somebody you bonded with
and flown the skies with, watching him just jump into a
jump into a pit because he was scared.
That's what's the worst part about it.
He's scared and he just throws himself off a cliff.
He's not.
No, there's always extremely relatable.
Very relatable. Better do this.
Getting scared and throwing yourself off a cliff. Yeah.
It's what we're all it's what we're all thinking about doing.
Every time we check Twitter.
I'm scared now.
Oh, maybe a Trump's Twitter candy of some kind or a drink like, hmm,
something like that.
It's going to keep you up at night.
It is. Yeah, I got to crack it. I'll crack it.
Well, just yeah.
Well, if you get it and do a conference call, patch us in,
wake us up at three in the morning, record it and put it on podcasts.
The right way. Well, I'll do it.
Yeah. The last you content at all times, even as we sleep.
I'm looking through the last bit of my notes here and I'm trying to.
I'm like, I guess he's talked about everything.
And then I looked at this and I said, what is this note?
And it says clock jam.
And then I remember I wanted to make a note because my favorite part,
I think of Alice in Wonderland, the movie is where the mad hatter
and the March hair try to fix the clock by putting jam on it.
And you remember this? Yeah.
And then they just smash it. Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that's one of those lodged memories.
I haven't watched them forever.
You should watch it because my goodness, did it bring up.
I was like, oh, oh, man, I love this.
This is so good.
I don't know what it was about.
I don't know if I like I guess I was a fan of jams and jellies.
I think it's so silly as a kid.
Like, you know, you don't know a lot.
You can't get complex humor, but you know that condiments don't belong on a clock.
Yeah. And I think it's also like a mix of like I didn't like
they were breaking the clock, but I also liked what they were doing.
I was just a bunch of emotions at once.
And seeing what's in a clock, seeing all those crazy doodads.
Yes. And I that's another one.
Oh, shit. I think this is the best scene in the movie.
That's a snack they should sell is an edible clock.
Oh, yeah. They should.
Oh, that'd be great.
Yeah, that's great.
Like cakey piece or it's like a chocolate shell thing that crumbles.
Yeah. Oh, man, that's great.
Yeah. A lot of good ideas on this episode with marshmallow gears inside.
Jason, what do you think is the expert?
Do you want to hear my piss voice?
You're just going to I asked you a question.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was asking you, what do you think about the treat?
I'm into it. I think they could even they're always
they're fussing around with churros so much nowadays.
I bet you could reverse and you could figure out how to do it in churro form.
Or it's a wide churro instead of a long churro that looks like a clock.
And you spread the jam on top.
Wide churro sounds fantastic.
Wide churro sounds good, right?
Were you just sitting thinking of your piss voice?
Yeah, I was kind of.
All right. Well, let's hear it.
Let's hear it.
Hey, it's Jason's piss.
It's one of two voices, Jason.
Put me in a toilet. Whoa.
Wow. Wow.
And applause for it.
Wow. It's a very specific area.
What's your piss voice?
Sure. There's only so many.
Yeah, yeah. The answers there could be.
But don't let that
a, you know, a rousing voice.
Don't let that incredible voice performance overshadow.
A rousing voice.
You say a rousing voice. Rousing.
Oh, I've been seeing a lot of people online
are saying that Jason is a short king and that his voice is a rousing.
Let's not let it all overshadow wide churro.
My idea that I am copyrighting.
Wide churro. There's so many good ideas.
We're all copywriting. Yeah.
Who? I don't know.
I got nothing else.
What's it? Wait, so can I copy?
I guess I would take I guess the deadable jam clocks was my idea.
You brought up jam clocks, but me making a snack was my idea.
It was. Yes. OK.
OK, great. So we don't have to sue each other.
I have kidney stone candy.
I'm still liberal.
Which I bet I bet already you can buy liberal tears somewhere.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that's not.
But I do believe I invented kidney stone candy because liberal tear.
That's the thing. That's not like a new
that could have been sold 20 years ago.
Just would have been a more niche. Yeah. Market.
There's got to be like a liberal snowflake, snowflake cookie or something
where you like a snowflake and you eat it, an edible snowflake.
The most fragile. Yeah.
Right. The most fragile candy.
The console immediately.
My friend Avery Monson briefly sold a coffee mug online that instead of
tear, he removed the R from the phrase liberal tears.
So it just said liberal tease.
And everyone from every side of the aisle got mad at him
because they read it too quickly.
And he's like, what? It's just tea.
It's just a mug for tea.
That's good.
Well, here I'm looking I looked up candy.
There may not be candy necessarily, actually, but there's mugs.
Liberal tears and melted snowflakes is on a mug. Right.
So that's that covers both of them.
There's a coffee mug that says I lubricate my AR 15 with liberal tears.
Which is nice to hear because that probably makes it less
lubricated and less likely to hurt people.
So keep on doing it, sir.
And how can you possibly procure enough to lubricate the firearms?
Go deal with saltwater. Great.
Handle it very well.
Yeah, I'm sure.
There are three useless things in this world.
A dull knife, an unloaded gun and liberals.
I didn't know that didn't say tears until I got to the end.
Liberals is real much bigger than the rest.
That's why I shouted it.
So that's all great stuff.
You can. Oh, wait, I'm seeing maybe as a zazzle tin you can buy.
Oh, OK. Yeah.
And it's yeah, there's a little snowflake on it and it says from the salt mines.
I'm sure what that part's about. Yeah, that's a leap.
Yeah, I don't get it.
It's a reach. Are tears salty?
I suppose.
Hmm. All right.
Well, the point is, if you want liberal tears, there's many ways to get them.
I looked up candy kidney stones. Uh huh.
It doesn't appear. Great.
The first thing that comes up is sugar kidney stones.
So maybe there's kidney stones that are sugar,
which honestly would lend itself better.
So we just saw it as like a real thing.
And Disney could market these also because, as we discussed with Big
Thunder Mountain, there was a study about how that ride is effective
for passing kidney stones.
So they go specifically.
You could sell this idea to Disney and give and they sell it in gift shops
outside of Big Thunder.
Kind of lacking for Big Thunder merch. That's true.
That's a good point. Yeah.
Very good. So you sell them in a in a tin that looks like the train,
like those popcorn tins are becoming popular.
So Big Thunder train full of kidney stones. Right.
Big Thunder mining company.
We hit a bonanza. We hit a jackpot.
Look at all these stones.
All these kidney stones.
Of all the trains over the years that have been going through the mines
and just shooting kidney stones off, ripping straight through the pants,
banging around the innards of the cave.
And they all land in a big pile.
That's what's being portrayed here.
It is unpleasant.
There's been a lot of, well, it's all, you know,
by kicking it off with the urine, I was guaranteeing
that we would it would be an unpleasant episode and that we would feel unpleasant.
Do how do we feel? OK, now do we ride the wave?
Do we feel all right?
That's what happens when you record a show through the looking glass, man.
And. Yeah, everyone like that.
Everyone. Yes, I found it very arising. Great.
Very erosive.
Well, I guess in that case, everyone has survived.
We survived podcast the ride.
Disgusting edition.
Disgusting. Our gross out humor today.
Our nanny, our au pair is shaking us awake under a tree.
Wake up. Get up.
Oh, right. It was a dream.
Right. Stupid idiot.
Stupid opium addicted idiot.
Is that what inspired like was somebody yelling that to Lewis Carroll?
Probably. Yeah.
Many times in his life.
He was asleep down at the dock, almost rolled into the water.
Candy opium another.
Yeah, that's good.
With kind of steampunky design.
Yeah, that would be really out there, though, because that opium isn't legal.
Yes, true.
All right. Well, like a lot of merch ideas and presumably on our tea
public eventually will be able to sell all of these candies.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And we'll start.
You know what? We'll start selling liberal tears.
Yeah. Why don't we? Yeah.
Let's just sell out entirely.
Yeah. Liberal tears.
It's our tea public is your place for Disney.
Theme park adjacent comedy shirts.
And also, yeah,
I use liberal tears to power my gas guzzling,
rolling coal SUV.
I use liberal tears instead of gas.
It's also a clean, which is also clean energy.
Yeah, that's a way to trick people into supporting clean energy.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
We'll probably sell more conservative
shirts and merch than we do our own podcast.
Honestly, it's half about Sonia clips and stuff and half about all tears.
Yeah. Sonia clips with a gun is outselling all of our other shirts.
Just unrelated.
Like I drink liberal tears for breakfast and it's a picture of Sonia clips.
He's straight. Yeah, he's drinking it.
And he's also saluting.
It's unclear what he's saluting this tie together like Pepe the Frog.
Why would these things be?
But he's a backwards man.
So he he salutes the ground.
He salutes the ground and he drinks libtabular liars.
Anyway, OK, what else?
Live shows coming up, as we mentioned.
Yeah, check it out.
August 24th, Anaheim, October 24th, Orlando. Yeah.
Yeah. And follow us on Twitter and on Instagram and the second gate at Patreon.
And thanks for listening.
Go to Vegas, pick up your own urine and urine for a treat.
Bye. Forever.
Oh, this has been a forever dog production executive
produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Bowen, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.