Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains talking trash can secrets, the sugar substitute stevia,
non-specific smuggling, and a well rehearsed half speed knock down drag out dissection of
the A-Team and Miami Vice stunt shows with special guest Matt Gourley.
I love it when a podcast comes together.
It's Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, hosted by three guys who never get starstruck unless they are
meeting the voice of a theme park trash can.
I'm Scott Gertner, Jason Sheridan, Mike Carlson are here.
Hi, yes.
Yes, and that is what's happening today among other things.
We're happily joined by a luminary of both podcasting and theme parks from Super Ego,
from James Bond, and from Colonel O'Brien Needs a Friend.
Matt Gourley is here.
Hi guys, I feel like this is a long time coming.
Yeah.
I mean, if ever there are two wheelhouses for me, I'm excited to be here.
No kidding.
The list seems to rival your podcast list is the theme park list.
Sadly, yeah.
No, these are the most excited, the funnest of areas.
I'm so glad we could talk about it.
People have tweeted us a lot of like, you got to have Gourley on.
You got to have Gourley on.
Yeah, I've seen a lot of those.
Yeah, we will.
Yeah.
Well, and we got sort of like, I feel like we were almost like set up on a podcast blind
date by a listener who approached you somewhere and said, when are you going to do Podcast
The Ride?
Yeah, I was thankful to hear about, which I think when, and I heard the response there
was that you were, you were curious about Waterworld, but Jordan Morris dove in and
got there first.
Yeah, I saw that and that immediately hit me hard.
That's real good.
Oh, the podcast war started new.
Yeah.
That was the real sea war.
But I understood it.
And I thought maybe that's an invitation for me to go one, maybe even two levels deeper.
Yes, yes, both.
And these are, this is really the bones of the, like there could be no Waterworld alive,
Sea War Spectacular without the essential building blocks of Miami Vice and A-Team.
Which are the burial ground, like the Poltergeist Native American stunt show Spectacular burial
ground on which Waterworld is on top of.
Yes.
Sure, sure.
And any problems that they encounter, if anyone were to get hurt, it is probably stemming
from that they would dare to exile all the crock-it-and-tubbs.
Yeah, all the ghosts of the stunts that happened.
The bones of the poor man's B.A.
Baracus will come out of the Waterworld lake because they were literally on the same grounds.
I guess that's clear, but maybe some people don't know that.
Yeah, yeah.
Waterworld's from around 95, 96, I think is when they made that switch.
I don't want to say 95.
But yeah, Miami Vice before that and A-Team before that, that's always been the sectioned-off
stunt area for, for the most part, properties that go longer than the thing that it is based
on.
Well longer, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, because Miami Vice is still going in 94 when it's been off the air for four years.
Four years, I think.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, both of them ran until after their show had gone off the air.
The show went till 1990?
Yeah.
Oh my God, what did they do with their fashions?
Did they update them or?
I don't know.
Yeah, I don't know where they land.
And, and well, and seemingly the, in the live show, they started to get a little looser.
Like they were like sort of like ponytail crockets.
That's right.
They let them hang a little bit, at least the ones you can see on YouTube.
So I guess they weren't being held to the, you know, the proper style standards.
There's no Crockett style standards.
But in 1995, like children watching the Miami Vice stunt show were just like, well, this is cool.
I don't know what it is.
Yeah.
It's just neat.
And Waterworld's now like many generations deep.
Oh, no idea.
Yeah.
Before we get into all these excellent topics that you got into, we got to ask you about the history.
The, I mean, there's a number of things.
Push among them, the soap opera, Beast.
I'm not, I'm not sure where to start.
I think more than any guest we've had, you've been, you've logged a lot of time in the parks.
Yeah, I guess so.
So I think it all began in 2001.
I can't remember.
I think it was right, right after 9-11.
Would you say that's why you got into food parks?
Because of the transformation that happened?
It was an inside job.
I got this job doing this thing called the Soap Opera Beast, Disney's California Adventure,
which was a soap opera themed restaurant based on the ABC soap opera.
So every room of the restaurant was a different set, like a mansion, a war for surgery room.
And so there was this group of improvisers and we were all, we all came from the same circle.
So it was like my best friends.
We were all doing this thing where you'd go in once an hour for about 10 minutes,
improvise a soap opera scene while people are eating.
You'd put your hand on the shoulders of some woman and go like, my wife, Monrovia here, left me.
And the people just ate it up.
You're wearing doctor's scrubs all day.
It was the easiest job I will ever have.
It was a union performers job.
And then also the park was doing so poorly that we'd come in for like a 10 o'clock shift
and they go, we're not going to open until five, so just go ride some rides.
And it was a union job, so you'd be paid for it.
And I mean, this is really how Super Ego started because we, I had already had like my friend Jeremy,
that I do Super Ego with, we were already friends, but Mark, we all kind of would just have so much downtime
that we would just goof off with each other and straight man each other for bits and things like that.
And we all became fast, close friends.
And then soap opera brister didn't last that long.
I was going to say, I don't even know how that's like really that's opening day California Adventure early, early.
Did you last till the end of it?
Yeah, well, well beyond, well beyond because that closed fairly early.
And then basically everybody who was doing that job transitioned to a new show called Department of Untapped Hilarity.
Duh. Duh.
For short.
Yeah.
So I have questions about duh.
And actually that first was something called the, I think it was called the Wrong Brothers instead of the Right Brothers,
which took place in the aviation area.
And we were like airplane mechanics doing improv on the street.
Yeah.
I'm just remembering a lot of his notes.
What a narrow area.
I know.
Like an Aaron Hayes from all kinds of TV.
She was part of it.
Wow.
Chris Tallman, Jeremy Mark from Super Ego.
I'm trying to think of other people that some people took off.
I forget.
Was this a random, was it like sort of random auditioning for this or were they aware of your pocket of people as we should reach out to them?
It was random auditioning, but the guy who was basically running it all, Frank Maciel, was a friend of ours.
So it was kind of like he pulled from the talent pool that I think he knew.
Okay, sure, sure.
And then that turned into Department of Untapped Hilarity, which was the big stage show in California Adventure where we dressed like Mormons on a mission and rode bicycles to set each set.
It was so strange.
But then we did like a Whose Line Is It Anyway type show for about 20 minutes.
And that was really fun and did fairly well.
But then they shut that down too.
And then I moved to like I did Laughingstock.
I did Billy Hill and the Hillbillies briefly.
I did push the Talking Trashcan for years.
And then I taught improv workshops through their entertainment program and education program.
And that was basically my run.
Wow, wow. Oh, geez.
So you like facilitated anything that was the improv-y around the party, which there is a lot of stuff when you add all that up and even like down to the like the characters or the walk around characters.
It's improv. Star Wars.
There's so much improv going on.
It is a you forget what a big hub of.
Yeah, it's like it's one of the maybe the only in a way like real world applications of here's a place where improv is needed.
And one of the few you get paid to improvise.
Yeah, right.
And it was a great job because I was in my 20s when I started.
And I think it was like I want to say it was like 20 or 25 dollars an hour.
And you got full benefits.
Pretty good. Yeah.
Geez. Wow. Yeah.
And much better, by the way, than I will get to.
There were some labor disputes in the A-Team stunt show.
That's one of the only Google results.
There's not a ton online for the A-Team stunt show, but they were they would have been more than happy with those rates.
And they were like doing like they were like hurting themselves.
They were risking their lives every day.
And maybe Universal, I could I could speak to this as a tour guide.
I think maybe the Disney pay is for performers is superior to Universal potentially.
Because there's also wasn't there a guy at least in the Wild West on show and there were two incarnations of that.
That one guy fell off the zip line and broke his neck.
Oh, geez. I remember that happening, too.
Really? Oh, man. I don't know that one.
Wow. Wow. Yeah.
No injuries on the job for you.
Just like emotional, I guess.
No, actually, that was a really good time of life because it was it was like the first time I felt truly independent, had some disposable income.
I was with my best friends.
We would go get a beer after every time.
And, you know, it was great.
Was there a hangout spot you would have after getting off the job?
You mean in the park? Yeah.
Well, anywhere, really.
Well, around, we would go to the block at Orange, which, by the way, you take a street called Shop Pertainment to get into and go to this place called I think it was Alcatraz Brewery.
Because a few of us lived in Long Beach.
Most of us lived in L.A.
I lived in Long Beach, and this is a place where we could go while we're all down there.
And we know traffic, which is considerable.
We're pretty trapped down there for sure.
Wow. Well, block at Orange, solid.
They got the sagebrush cantina now.
Oh, the creepy mannequins outside.
Excellent alter-ito.
You know, the massive alter-ito.
Have we been in that alter-ito?
I don't believe so.
We went to one by water.
We went to one by the John Wayne.
Okay, we've been to a different alter-ito down in Orange County.
Well, you got to hit them all because they're just vastly nuanced.
They're like the Fry's electronic store.
They're just way different.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, stay tuned for that one.
I can't build up our eventual Fry's episode.
We're doing a Fry's episode.
Are you?
Oh, for sure.
It's themes.
That's the theme.
That's true.
There's a radical amount of theming in all of them.
They're all totally different.
Like Roman space.
There's like, yeah, there's island ones.
There's like Alice in Wonderland.
What? Where?
The valley.
Down the note.
Oh my God.
Kenoga Park is the...
Yeah, yeah.
But like scratchy Lewis Carroll era illustration, Alice in Wonderland.
Oh my God.
So it's a little horrific.
That is so specific and strange for an electronic superstore.
Really specific and really intense.
Like they put more attention into theming than they do into their stock.
The new having stuff in stock.
Yes.
There's so much missing.
Everything I've ever bought from their breaks.
It's like not a good store, but theming.
But a surprising selection of snacks.
Yes.
A very well stocked convenience store, a not great stocked electronics store.
Yeah.
And every time I've been in there on display on the big TVs is always like the four woman
electronic violin ensemble playing like live concert DVD.
Wow.
I think they're called Bond actually.
Oh really?
Yeah.
But nothing to do with Bond.
I don't think.
Right.
Oh weird.
But like one of those, are they like the piano guys?
Like all the guys who like together play piano and like deconstructed.
Yeah.
Piano guys like play Trump's inauguration I think.
Oh boy.
They were one of the ones real, but like something around it is real.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But they're not political.
That's a thing.
Like they would do any president.
They're apolitical.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank God.
I think politics haven't gotten the four piano guys.
Yeah.
They're harking back to a better time.
Bipartisanship ruled.
Well, so Push.
Let's talk Push a little bit.
I feel like I'm mainly aware of Push because of your association with that.
I don't think I ever met Push when I was in the party.
Do you guys interact with Push ever?
Push was only out here.
No, it was pretty much every park.
I feel like I met, maybe I did meet Push.
What years were it?
I forget.
Well into like the, I think late 90s into the 2010s.
I remember a moving trash can, but not necessarily a talking trash can.
Well, I bet that was it, but the intercom was broken because it was always breaking
down.
Okay.
So perhaps in Florida, there was a moving trash can.
Yeah.
I mean, it was a lot of frequency issues all the time.
Where were you, where were you do it from?
Where were you stationed?
They moved it around a lot.
So it was at one point in Tomorrowland, then it was in California Adventure in a few different
places.
It would move a lot and it was frequently moving because of frequency issues, like with
all their radios and stuff.
And there was two, there was one called Push and one called Shove and they looked identical,
but you know, one always worked better than the other, but even that.
Also, even though it might've been working, there was some push operators, I'm not saying
I'm one of them, who would like milk that it wasn't working to get off their sets a
little early.
Oh, how would you just be like, I'm trying and it just doesn't, it's not going.
Yeah.
And again, it was definitely not me.
But if you did it.
I'm not saying it was not me.
Fair, fair.
But when I did do that.
And were you far away in a room where you were watching a camera or were you close by?
No, you're very close by.
You got to wear your own.
Oh, this is a great thing.
So this is another union job and you got to wear your own clothes and then they had to
pay you for wearing your own clothes.
So you got an extra bonus.
Oh, wow.
You get a bump.
Sure.
So you'd wear like a ball cap and you just wore like a lavalier mic, but instead of
putting it on your lapel, it would run down your sleeve, like under a watch into your
hand like this.
Like you just kind of have a semi-closed fist and then a duffel bag over your shoulder with
the controller on your right hand.
And so I just kind of put my hand up to my mouth like this.
And then I would only have to talk like this and it would modulate my voice up.
And I was usually about, I could get as far away as I wanted, but if you get really far
away, you can't hear what the people talking to push are saying because push had no like
two way microphone.
Oh, you had nothing in your ear.
No.
So I had to be close to hear them live.
And so I would usually just, whoever it was talking to, I'd stand somewhat behind them
and they couldn't hear me because the microphone or the speaker was louder.
But the parents all knew, you know, most people would, I didn't try to hide that much.
Yeah.
You looked like Serpica.
You looked like a plain clothes cop wearing a wire.
Definitely.
Yeah.
I mean, it definitely must have looked creepy with a guy in his hand in his bag.
Maybe that's why they stopped doing it because it was probably like, oh God, who's this?
Watch out for Push's friend.
Yeah.
I wondered because they have now we all were in Galaxy's at the same time.
Yes.
Oh yes.
Day one.
And we had interacted with R2D2 and I wonder was there a guy?
I didn't see R2D2.
He's in the Droid Depot and I was just going.
He's available for purchase, but they also like turn him on and he'll like beep at you.
And he can tell if your intonation is a question or.
Wait, you can buy a full sized R2D2?
$25,000.
Wait, they're selling something for $25,000?
Yeah.
Got some weird press in that like there was almost like a weird, like a novelty bragging
point of the place that if you really want to throw it down, there's a $25,000.
Yeah.
I think I saw him.
I saw the control.
I saw the guy.
Oh, because that's what I was wondering.
Was there a person behind me?
Because I believe so.
I think he was fully in like a cast member garb.
Because that's a tiny room.
It's in like a tiny room where you I bought Rex sitting over there.
There he is.
Oh, yeah.
He was bad.
He's in the corner looking at the wall.
Oh, my God.
He's Blair Witching it.
Yeah.
The dog doesn't like him either.
Oh, that's too bad.
He wheels around.
Oh, yeah.
I haven't done a lot of interacting with I have carpet too.
So Rex can't get far.
But yeah, Rex is really a pre or not a pre push is similar to push.
You need a BB8 for carpet, right?
Oh, I guess so.
That's a good point.
Oh, yeah.
Because there's no part with wheels.
Like it's all I don't know how they work.
Really.
Did you do a droid?
Did you get a droid?
No, I couldn't even get in.
I couldn't get into the cantina.
Couldn't get into the lightsaber thing.
I had a pretty bad experience at Galaxy's.
That was all right.
Yeah, yeah.
That makes sense.
Well, you were part of you were the second group, right?
You were staggered.
So like now you're competing with every but like you're that was the first time that group
one and group two were all mission.
And yes, we fighting in your we were bad boys and caught in line with someone to get into
the cantina.
Good for you.
We joined an existing party.
We were in the same group.
I just want to acknowledge it.
So if we had been if we had been more in communication, we may have been able to tell you what the
whole situation is, which is regrettable.
I'm sorry.
You can just walk in now.
It's wide open.
You can make a reservation for the bar whenever you want.
The thing that killed me was that when we went to go into the cantina, there was this
young just as most Disney employees are just full of fear.
Guy saying, you know, I'm going to go into the cantina.
Bright Suns offworlder.
You can't you can't even you can't even get in line.
And so he had to continue talking in this vernacular that they make them talk.
But I'm sure they've given them a limited vocabulary of things to memorize.
So he didn't have the words to deal with people going, wait, why can't we at least get in
line?
Like, it's our choice if we want to get in line offworlder.
I regret to inform you.
The First Order has a.
Oh, God.
I'm sorry.
I regret to inform you.
The First Order has a.
Oh, God.
And he was like near tears and I felt horrible.
We backed off for his sake.
But it was really strange.
You know, the word they what do they call lines or buzzers or apps?
Right.
The cosmic cue that you get, the galactic cue is evolved at capacity.
Oh, God.
And he was just like imploding and everybody was so stressed.
Language, please.
Yes, I'm stuck.
Yeah.
I'm going to turn to the universal translator on.
Oh, please.
OK.
Turn it off.
My job.
They're watching me.
You don't understand.
It's not the First Order.
It's the middle managers.
They're over there and chinos and bled shirts and straw hats.
They're after me.
An upsetting amount of casual middle managers there that day.
There is more of them than workers at Disney.
It is.
That's the unsettling thing about Galaxy's Edge.
When you work there and I'm not doing that thing where I'm like likening Disney to a
fascist regime.
However, they they do have a culture of fear and like cult there for their workers who
go there thinking like this is a dream job because it's paradise.
And everybody's so kind of afraid of messing up that nobody makes a decision.
So getting an answer from someone has to go way up the chain.
Right.
Yeah.
It's a strange place to work.
We were always separated as the union performers, but watching it happen.
And my wife was a princess there, too.
And she.
Wow.
She.
Yeah.
And Tokyo Disney, too.
God, you guys should have her.
Oh, wow.
Yeah.
She worked in Tokyo.
For six months.
Wow.
Did she start here and get like was offered?
Yeah.
She was a Ariel, Mary Poppins and a Cinderella and I think a Sleeping Beauty, I think.
Wow.
Did she have to learn the same Japanese to do this?
No, I guess not.
I don't think so.
And there is a they do hire white people to portray the princesses.
Right.
Well, like in Japan.
Yeah.
Because, yeah, you do not see Japanese.
Right.
They want to.
Yeah.
They want them to look American.
I got be American.
Not look American.
Be American.
All the princesses are American.
Yeah.
Well, yeah.
Right.
A Little Mermaid lives in the sea next to America.
Yeah.
Mulan is from Chinatown, San Francisco.
America.
She speaks English.
Oh, I listen to her.
We know they want American performers because I was trying to get Jason years ago to apply
to play Austin Powers at Universal Japan.
A British band.
Yeah.
Yes.
I was like, come on, let's go do it.
We're not doing anything here.
We didn't have a podcast yet.
Yeah.
In retrospect, I should have.
I should have gone.
Were you working there?
No, no.
I just saw it online and I go, hey, Jason, go do this.
It'll be funny if you go to Japan and play Austin Powers.
Yeah.
You're just checking job listings for Jason.
Anytime you have ever sent me a job listing, it's not like, hey, this would be a good job.
This would be good pay.
It's like, this would be funny if you did this.
Yeah, sure.
And you have yet to apply to one of them.
I know.
Yeah.
Your current one is like, you should apply to be artist director at UCB.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Ladies and gentlemen, if you're listening to this now, support Jason Sheridan to be
the artistic director of UCB.
I support you.
We've had a great few years.
Everything's going good.
I want you to be there as soon as the ship goes down.
I want you to get revenge on all of our enemies.
I want it to all happen.
I support this.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's do it.
Anyway, back to it.
And do it all dressed as Austin Powers.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Like go in there for the interview going, I get comedy very, very.
Yeah.
Do I make you horny is not a question that any artistic director should be asking.
But it will replace don't think as the official phrase of the UCB theater.
Yeah.
Where were we?
What were we saying?
Japanese princess.
Oh my God.
So wait, so okay.
But because you were you were governed by the union, so you were outside of the you're
not saying Gestapo like tactics of the rest of the Disney.
Yeah, we were managed by them still, but they they didn't quite treat us like the characters
and the and the like ride operators and the regular employees.
I see.
Was it equity?
No, it is in Florida, but it was AGVA, the American Guild of Variety Artists, which was
a useless union.
It has a no strike clause.
Literally, like there's no power in this union.
We couldn't strike.
So negotiations were always like, oh, we got an extra vending machine for you.
You know, and I think like Phyllis Diller was the president for a long time.
Really?
So it was like a reader.
No, it was like a holdover from Vaudeville, I believe.
Literally the union.
Yeah.
Wow.
Well, we've had past.
I think if you pass guest, if he was talking about how there were different like clicks,
essentially, depending on what department you were like princesses.
Do you remember this?
And there's like a whole social structure in the park.
Did you experience that or were you just doing your own thing?
I guess, yeah, I know that the face characters, because my wife, Amanda has told me this,
were kind of the top of the food chain in terms of characters.
And then the like the you know, like the fuzzy characters were below that.
And then we were disconnected from it all.
But I'm imagining we were higher on the food chain because I know all those people
wanted to be agvats like the goal was always to be an agvah.
That's what you're called an agvah because you got good pay and you got, you know,
respect.
And I say that loosely.
Respecting your aviator stained overalls.
Yes, riding a bicycle.
Playing up.
Was there any job in the park that you were like gunning forever or was it just not in
the realm of it?
Well, were you even just like, I want to do a day of Haunted Mansion or something,
because that always seemed like fun?
No, I think it was the reason I think back on it so fondly is that it was the easiest
job. It required nothing like the job that you truly left behind the minute you clocked
out. And if anything, if you carried it with you, it was something like you're still
hanging out with your friends.
There was no pressure, no high stakes.
It was so breezy and like the stakes were so low because you I guess some people that
don't do improv, it would make them tense.
But anybody that does, it was the lowest stakes improv.
You were often reusing a lot of the same theme park jokes.
It was not high art in any way, but it worked so well that the people love like push
alone. People just ate it up.
I don't know why they still don't do push.
It's so it's one person on a job and it gets so much for its, you know, like
investment and like pulls people out of lines and crowds for a while.
Yeah, like this will eat up 50 people for this run of time and delight them.
And I would get these huge crowds and circles just surrounding this trash can.
And like the kids were in awe.
The parents were laughing.
I probably couldn't do a lot of the things I was doing at the time, because like I would
make the trash can like flirt with people or bump into the other trash can and go like,
Sheila, why did you divorce me?
You know, and like hound people for their churros.
I was like, you know, like to borderline harassment, throw your dish.
God dang.
So push would have been canceled.
Yes, I would have been fired today.
I would have been fired.
Push the problematic trash.
Yeah, yeah.
And I would like someone would throw away a beer and I would just do a whole set drunk
as push, you know.
Yeah.
Were they poor, beerian me?
And I would just like go bump into things and then like roll up to women and go, hi,
how you doing?
It was horrible.
It feels like that would be you could get away with that now.
Like horror nights.
Yeah.
They should push trash can and horror.
Yeah, they should.
And then he could say what it would on the Sweden episode.
I guess it's actually coming out the star way.
And like they can mention weed on the announcements.
They can be like, don't smoke on the star way, even weed or something like they can
say weed, which is crazy.
So bold faced.
I know there were times where like kids would a lot of kids would kick it like preteens
would kick it.
And sometimes their parents were there and I would just flat up roll up to the parents
go, why aren't you doing something about your child?
Do something about your child.
And then I would get the rest of the crowd to shame those parents.
Wow.
Sometimes it got tense.
People like a little comedy.
Like people like a little especially when it goes against the Disney type.
Yeah.
They're relaxed.
They're on vacation.
They're like, oh, OK, yeah, I'm into this.
A lot of jokes about how expensive things were.
Mm hmm.
Yeah.
I think I was sort of like part of me wanted to get fired because part of me at that point
pushes is a solitary job and my friends were gone and I would break with like a lot of
the characters and there was a handful of them that I broke with regularly that I loved.
They were like my family.
But then there were these others that would come in and just like eat a banana with their
mouth open the whole time next to you.
And it was just I was and they'd always like put on a Disney movie on your break in the
break room and you couldn't escape it.
And I started to go a little crazy.
And so there was part of me that was like, I want to get fired.
Sure.
Yeah.
But it was like being in a like bad relationship where you sabotage it rather than have the
balls to break up.
I was like the money is too good.
You know, so I was just kind of daring them to fire me and they never did.
When in the unlikely event that you're being supervised to such an extent that you like
that you actually you slip up and say something like they would have to line up, you know,
that would require like three different things to happen as opposed to you quitting, which
you'd have to like go do that.
You have to arrange a meeting.
Well, a lot of the middle managers were kind of afraid of the agvas for some reason.
I think because they knew the agvas didn't care.
So they didn't have the unspoken discipline of fear over them.
And I remember there's, you know, we would get away with saying weird things.
I remember there's a guy on the Laughing Stock show that got a little kid to come and volunteer
and he was talking to this character, Clem, and he's like, this kid's the only one with
nuts enough to challenge you, Clem.
I'm full Mike.
You know, I'm like, I remember another guy was like, Jesus Christ.
They never meant to do it, but it would come out or like we were doing an improvised song
about Aladdin and my friend Gail, she's like, I want you to come into my cave of wonders.
Like all this sexual, like we do a lot of sexual innuendo and it was funny.
We had so many regulars, like I hesitate to call them stalkers, but they were like anywhere
from just super Disney fans that would come to every show every day to like special needs
people that were dropped off as a cheaper way of care.
We'd see this at Universal as well, where special needs people were dropped off often
in groups of two and they were just given annual passes because it was cheaper to have
them be at the park all day than to have specialized care.
And they were lovely, wonderful, but you'd see them every day and they'd volunteer every
time and like or yell your jokes out before you could get them out.
But that was more my fault or our fault for reusing the same jokes.
We found a pattern.
Yeah.
But this can also be rare in comedy is like an audience who's happy to be there or like
an audience who really wants to be because it's like, well, I already paid for that.
This is free.
I can sit down.
That's true.
At the very least.
And they actually somehow liked repetition.
They almost didn't like new things.
You could imagine your everyday Disney guest who comes every day is probably into things
not changing.
Like they like the stability.
The Internet makes that very clear.
Just move a plant or something.
Just peruse the mice chat message boards.
I can't imagine if we were working there in the days of Reddit because there was burgeoning
message boards and we had seen some of them.
I had an issue with a stalker there and she would post on some things.
By the way, she was in her seventies and she was a strange stalker that admitted to me
she thought I was sending her coded messages on stage and stuff like that.
Oh no.
Yeah.
So retire those jokes, I guess, if you know what the code is.
She found my email and it was strange.
She would come with her middle-aged son who would wear cataract glasses and sit separate
from her, but they both would come to every show every day.
Whoa.
Yeah.
She was very sweet, but something was off.
What's the procedure for dealing with that?
That's a good question.
I'm sure there's a super protocol for that now.
I just walked up to her and she, because at one point she emailed me going, oh, I don't
like when you hug and kiss Gail on stage.
She came up to me after the show and I was like, I just want to clarify, A, that's just
an act and B, that's kind of not something you should say.
She's like, well, aren't you sending me these messages?
You're throwing references my way.
I went, I'm sorry, I'm not.
Then she reached in her bag and I hunkered down.
Oh my God.
This is it.
Then she just said, I guess I'm just going a little crazy.
Then pulled her hand out of her bag and nothing was in it.
I was just like, what is happening here?
Oh my gosh.
You didn't ask for, well, by virtue of me being a performer, I'm putting myself out
there for things like this.
You should expect this kind of thing to happen.
It was really, really strange.
Oh my God.
Which is a little microcosm of if you were a very famous person, the kind of insanity
you would deal with that all the time.
I can't imagine.
That's the only time anything like that's ever happened to me.
I think even that was totally harmless.
She didn't have anything in her bag, but it's the first time that it gave you cause to ever
consider that kind of thing.
It was really strange.
Yikes.
I remember that happened when I was, I taught for many years.
The last couple of years was the first time I was aware of troubled students and the
surroundings of my classroom and thinking, I've never had to consider that something
tragic could happen here.
It kind of took the joy out of teaching.
It was horrible.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Oh God.
Well, that's a rough area, but if you're listening and you think you've been hearing coded messages
from us, you're absolutely right.
We're talking to you.
Please murder us.
That's me.
I've been hearing coded messages and I'm here to murder you.
We invited you.
We let the wolf into the hen house.
I developed Super Ego and podcast to get to this point.
Wow.
You built up your own podcast.
Long game.
The Heath Ledger Joker is such a long con.
Such a long con to talented Mr. Ripley.
That's a longer one.
That's a better example.
I admire the strategy.
Matt, what did you, I have a guess, but what did you do with Universal?
Oh, I'm curious to hear what your guess is.
Were you a working class Brooklyn man who yelled from the windows?
Close.
I was the spinoff of that, the short-lived spinoff of that, the British yelling person
up on a balcony on the British street.
So you should have been Austin Powers in Japan.
No.
Yeah.
Yeah, because there's this thing, the people up in the Brooklyn window just yell down at
the park guests.
They thought, let's do that with the English street.
And this was, I guess, I think this was 2011 and it was summer and I had come out of a
fairly long relationship and I was feeling like a lot of my friends lived in LA and I'm
like, I should get social again because I'm kind of like, I skew towards the reclusive
home body.
And so I decided I'll go, my friends are doing this.
Maybe it'll be a rehash of Disney where you're seeing your friends and you're doing improv.
And then I went that day and auditioned and then for the first day of orientation, we
all had to stand up and introduce ourselves and my wife stood up and I just, I remember
literally saying, uh-oh, like who is that?
And we hit it off that day, we hit it off and we're basically like, she's like, it was
crazy.
It was one of those true, like, not only say like love it for a site, but we both were
all in somehow.
I don't know how it happened or what.
And so we worked that summer together and we were the first ones to open that show the
first day together.
And just as soon as we were like officially a couple, I quit because I didn't really want
to do that job. And I'm like, my God, not only did I get to see my friends, but I think
I met my wife. And so like, I don't need this job anymore.
Wow.
Got out of there. She worked there a little while longer.
And then she also did the special effects show and the Jurassic Park dino expert or
whatever it is that walks around.
Yeah.
Wait, what was it? Was it were you with a dinosaur for that or?
I think there was like a cart that you had like animatronic puppet.
Oh, the egg. I think it was like the egg.
Yeah. The puppet hand puppet.
Hey, yes. Yeah, that's right.
And now it's much more advanced.
I like to say all the full sized raptor, full sized triceratops.
Yeah. I want to say it was called Dino Chasers, but is that something else?
That sounds like something else.
But maybe, you know, that's a cartoon I watched as a kid, I think.
Maybe you watched all three seasons and yet don't remember a drop of it.
I don't know. Yeah, anyway.
But anyway, there's a movie coming out, I'm sure.
I am the gateway to so many people if you want them like Mark, Jeremy, Amanda.
They all had so many jobs at theme parks like.
We were the mayor's of of Disney.
Disney. Yeah, probably.
We also all did a bunch of special events.
That was the other thing, like corporate special events, improv things.
I was also a thing called a swing, which if you did enough shows,
you would just come in for the day and in case they needed you.
So you'd sit around all day and maybe you'd do a couple of shows to keep fresh.
That was the greatest.
Wow. Wow. Did you guys then like sort of fall in love wearing like
monogles and bowler hats and she's got missing teeth?
And that. Yeah.
So originally, yes, it was like a tweety upper class British man and a posh woman.
But they for some reason wanted to do away with that.
So she was dressed like a Spice Girl and I was dressed like Keith Richards.
It was awful. It was truly awful.
How did it compare like work like I universal?
I don't think it's union. It was union.
It was. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't. I they do have a small union section.
I was thinking when you were talking about the Disney Union,
that there was some I remember there's a lot of grumbling when I was a tour guide
of that at one point in time, like before 1995 or something,
the tour guides and the drivers were in the same union.
And then and then the guides were like, we need to be our own union.
And that caused the rates to go to like half of what the drivers make.
So there hadn't been the split because the drivers do great.
And they should, because that's real work.
Yeah, they're doing because if they aren't doing the tram,
they're like driving equipment around for the studio.
Real there. They should be good.
But for some reason, the like union happily walked off a cliff
and cut their wages in half.
I don't know. That sounds about right.
I bet you it was Agva.
Yeah, it could have been. Yeah.
Forget what I forget what I was then.
What were my tiny paychecks?
What TV legend was your head of your organization?
Well, there while there was, I don't know if I should say that.
Oh, I was just trying to.
Well, no, he was not a union person,
but they're like one of the higher ups at the in the tour
that program was the youngest son on the nanny.
Oh, really?
Still there. He was at the Jurassic World.
Oh, I didn't say hi. Oh, my gosh.
You've been keeping the secret from us for years now.
We didn't know this. But he's not he's not a union.
He's not a person causing right.
He's not the man causing the wages to stay low.
So let me make that very clear. He was very nice.
He's not some some agvacrony.
But so this is insane.
The way specific Spice Girl or the general?
No, not. And no, it was never even you are a Spice Girls just modeled that.
And like I wasn't a Rolling Stone. It was just that kind of thing.
And Eric. Yeah.
So it was like a UK shirt, maybe like a flag.
I have a picture I'll show you.
Actually, I think in the picture, it was our first day working, I think.
I actually think she might have still been the posh lady,
but I was the rocker for some reason.
So I had like a wig with a headband and scarves and like a tight
shirt and tight leather pants. It was awful.
I'm tempted to ask, is there a chance you remember how the voice sounded?
I think it went a little bit like this.
Yeah. What are you doing down there on a street?
I go around, get me popping corn.
I mean, that's great.
I would enjoy it. Yeah.
Walked by today.
Would you make harmlessly make fun of people's clothing or hats?
Yeah, I think so.
Because that's blazing hot.
It was summer and we were in the direct sunlight.
Sure. Everything is entirely polyester.
Yeah. Nothing great. Yeah.
Yeah. It was happening to get them to the Greek mania.
Yes. Yeah.
Definitely had that feeling.
Yeah, I know.
That's one of my favorite theme park tropes is the look of rock
and roll entirely divorced from music.
It's like, all right, headband,
surly, cockney, British, emaciated guy.
No music, no music, but just that vibe.
Yeah, we know that to be rock and roll.
Semiotic said that's the symbol that communicates rock and roll.
And who's been that for a long time?
Who's been the big rock star who is British and shirtless?
You know, you know what the vibe you're describing is like Tom Cruise in
Rock of Ages. Yeah.
Like, yeah, Johnny Rock that or that or that Dennis Leary show.
Yeah. What name a new star since Oasis?
Who is of this nature?
That child band who sounds like Led Zeppelin.
What are they called? Oh, yeah.
Red Van Fleet.
Yeah. The child.
I hate it. I thought I thought he was a teenage girl.
No, yeah. Yeah.
So Red Van Fleet was like Joanna Newsome type.
Right. Oh, yeah.
I mean, it's like, yeah.
Yeah. And they're like in their early 20s.
And the little singer, he's adorable.
And he's just just so fresh faced.
He's like Annie. He's like orphan.
Yeah. Yeah.
The black smoke rises.
The death of.
And then I like that song is so goddamn catchy, too.
Well, I saw them on Saturday Night Live and I remember seeing feeling the same way
when I saw Future Islands on Letterman going, what is happening?
And I will I will investigate this hours for hours.
And I did.
I went down such a Future Islands rabbit hole after seeing that.
Do you have you seen that when he was on Letterman?
Yes. And he's doing that like speed skating dance and like this
and looks like Brando in the 50s, but not, you know, as well put together.
And I love him. Yeah.
I did a similar shorter research on Red Van Fleet.
The first article was like
Grandin and Fleet says they do not like to be compared to Led Zeppelin.
That's every article.
Yeah. And that's their own fault. Yeah.
I don't like to go to the grocery store, but look, some things are
can't avoid it. Yeah.
What do you want?
I get me. I'm like, I eat all the food.
I guess I got to find it. God damn it.
People know me as the grocery store guy.
Shake it.
If I'm at one, yeah, I can't avoid the.
Garen does not want to be known as the grocery store guy.
I don't know. I don't know. Why did I say that even?
I don't mind going to the grocery store.
You know, I hate the grocery store. I hate it. I hate it. I hate it.
I don't know why. Parking crowds.
Sure. Well, if you're dealing if it's if it's Trader Joe's.
Oh, yeah. I don't know why, because I'm also someone that like I won't eat.
I'll forget to eat.
So going to the grocery store is like
going to do something that I may forget to use anyway later.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll go.
I'll be like, I should go to the grocery store and then I'll just go to McDonald's.
Yeah. Which is next to the sprouts over here.
Yeah. And then I'll just come home.
I understand. I understand that.
So I'm like, well, I took care of the immediate need.
Yeah. Let's put it off.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'll go. And there's a very short window where it's all like in the fridge
and the cupboards and I feel great. Yeah.
And then after I've eaten a little bit of it, I'm like, oh no, it's going to be gone.
So I go back.
Oh, no. You have exactly how many of you guys live here?
Just me and my girlfriend, Lindsey. Yeah.
Lindsey Kate. I know. Yeah, of course.
Oh, my God. Well, I'm curious.
I want to see your refrigerator after.
Oh, I don't think it's in good shape.
No, I'm just kidding. You can't.
You can't see it. No.
You want to see it live on Mike?
Let's see.
Does it stretch that far?
I guess it's like strangely intimate.
You know, yeah.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Even even if mine is clean and there's people over, it still feels like I don't.
Yeah, it's like looking in your closet or something. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, we can peek in Mike's and see what fruit flavored soda he has this week.
So I don't look a new artificial sweetener is out.
No, I'm not. I'm more of a stevia man in general.
But I don't have any Ziva, which is what you're referring to.
Yeah. No, but I think there's going to be a hyper stevia.
There's going to be stevia, too.
You think I'm going to go all in on a new crazy stevia?
Maybe there's stevia in that kombucha that I like that I drink. Oh, right.
Yeah, I am a big stevia fan, but sometimes I drink too much and I get a stomach ache.
Mike does not want to be known as the stevia guy. Incorrect.
Fire away, he says.
Mike starting a podcast about stevia soon headline.
Mike loves being called stevia.
Wait, that's stevia. No, it's stevia. Yeah.
OK. Stevia artificial sweeteners.
The thing that killed Lydia on Breaking Bad.
Spoiler. Yeah. Stevia killed her.
Yeah. Well, yeah, yeah.
I guess not. Oh, you're right. Yeah.
Other contents in a packet.
OK. Yeah. Anyway.
But you know, you don't have to worry about going to the grocery store with Hello Fresh,
which I imagine we'll be having to read an ad for soon.
Does this count? Do we not have to read one if we do this now?
I don't think we hit the talking point, so I don't think it counts.
Ah, shit. All right.
We can cover both if you have one to read anytime soon.
Sure, Blue Apron does.
Yeah. I think this counts if you do it here. Yeah.
Well, Miami Vice, I guess we should we could start.
But we can make our way from Little Britain or whatever you call that.
Yeah. Mostly unused UK zone over there.
Yeah. Let's keep walking down to the down to the stunt zone, but also into the past.
Oh, man. OK. So I grew up in Southern California in Whittier,
which was fairly close to Disney, a little farther from Universal.
So for my birthday, I always had my dad take me to Universal.
I was more interested in that because also we got to go to Disney
through his work once a year, like have the park just for the gas company.
And that was cool.
And I would end up at Disney probably two or three times a year.
But Universal to me was like the movies.
It was it was so exciting.
It felt it felt more grown up in a little bit.
Yeah. I talk about this.
We thought it seemed like cooler, edgier up there. Yeah.
And maybe more at the time, certainly in Miami Vice included more recent properties.
You feel like you're, you know, going into your favorite show of right now,
as opposed to like a fairy tale from the 50s.
Yeah, there was no characters really.
They didn't have like the Marvel.
Well, they used to have the Marvel things and then the like of the Shrek.
None of that.
The only people they had walking around was Frankenstein, Dracula, Charlie Chaplin.
I think there might have been a Maryland, a Lucio Ball.
Yeah. Yeah.
And there was a chaplain who would do warm up for the stunt shows.
Camille Cassoon, I think, was his name, and he was like the lifetime
chaplain impersonator. Wow.
Yeah. Down in like especially the Western stunt show.
God, there's also the Conan one.
Yeah. At one time, there was five shows and the tram tour.
And that's what you could go see at Universal.
Oh, yeah. Oh, wait, let me see if I can name them.
Yeah. Because it was the Wild West stunt show, the Conan stunt show,
the animal actor stage, the special effects show, I think.
Yeah. Yeah. Like when I remember it is like it was heavily based on like
an airplane tragedy crash movie.
Cool. And they would use people in the audience
and then you could buy a videotape of it afterwards.
Like you had to jump into water at one point. Yeah. Oh, wow. And then.
Well, Miami Vice.
Oh, yeah. Miami Vice.
Yeah. Our A team. OK, yeah.
So also we covered it recently.
There's another thing where you could buy a video.
Oh, yeah. And it didn't take it home.
Do you recall the the Star Trek?
Was it the Star Trek adventure?
Was it called the Star Trek adventure?
Yeah, it was like they remember that they would put you in like
starfleet uniforms or a Klingon off.
I forget what Starfleet is.
Yeah, that does sound vaguely familiar. Yeah.
And like it would be DeForest Kelly doing
like they had done parts and then they would just cut it in poorly.
So it's great. Yeah. Live shot on stage.
But yeah, you're a Klingon.
Yeah, it was all shows at a point. Yeah.
No rides, no separate rides from the tram until ET.
Yeah, I believe I think that was the first one.
Yeah. So Miami Vice was my favorite of the three.
And and don't get me wrong, I love all three.
Well, a team isn't fair because I'll talk about it in a minute.
But it was a weird version I saw.
But Miami Vice, the set,
just all the pains they took to preplace pyrotechnics,
reloadable pyrotechnics, the feel of the fire,
the smell of that heavily dyed water, you know.
Yeah, for sure. Oh, yeah.
And it gets splashed around and those bullets get shot up.
Yeah. Big jets of it.
And it kind of missed onto you. Yeah.
Yeah. Smell of pyro, smell of water.
God, I loved it. A lot of boats.
There was a speedboat and multiple jet skis and a fan, but like miniature.
Yes. Of all these things.
Yeah, it was incredible.
And I wasn't even a Miami Vice fan.
Like I'd seen the show.
Same thing with Waterworld. I did love A-Team, but
those just something about the amazing technical achievement
of those stunt shows, but also the cheesiness of the scripts
and the the like you've got a shelf life once those stunts go in
of about maybe three months.
And then after three months, every actor is phoning it in completely.
There's no energy in the punches.
The delivery is like, get up there. You've got to save them.
And then there's always like a stage manager and cut.
This is a real Hollywood set, you know, and I just love that artifice of it.
That's not in the Waterworld one. I wish there would have been.
No, Waterworld kind of condenses the story into like 20 minutes.
And then Miami Vice, a guy in a tucked in polo shirt comes out
and it's like, I'm the director and we're going to walk you through this.
And the stunt guys don't really talk besides doing bits.
They do some. They do a lot of wacky, wacky and wholesome bits.
That wasn't a thing on Miami Vice, the TV show.
No, it wasn't stopped by the director.
I know that that wasn't.
Miami has some cool meta show.
It was hard boiled.
Jones does it, too.
There's a stage manager that interrupts the action.
Yeah. Yeah. And all under the guise of we're shooting a real Hollywood action film.
And I just oh, God, I love that.
Which is so like, why?
Why would they be doing it here now with an audience
with one direction that you can't see?
I know. And the Indiana Jones one goes so far as to have fake cameras
on Dolly tracks and a crew.
Yeah. Yeah. That's the last one hanging on like that with like,
you know, there's it's just them now.
Like they they're the emcee.
They move the action along and then the stunts happen.
Yes. Waterwell.
I mean, a lot of that dialogue is like queued from the booth.
Yeah. And they have to hit every mark.
Yeah. And then there's always the thing at the end now where they
give the credits of the stunt workers.
Who's like from CSI Miami.
And it's just done some stunt work on there. Right.
So like we do these series of stunt spectacular sketches on Super Ego.
And they're all based on on just stopping the action
and narrating it through the stage manager.
That is just the most needless role.
And there's they have that cadence to like in a Hollywood show.
You've got to get ready for some action.
There's danger abound.
And it's just this weird cadence that must not be taught,
but is somehow assumed.
And I can't understand why.
It's like the same thing as like modern prayer cadence of Father God,
we just want to thank you.
We only want to praise you.
We just merely want to thank you.
And it's the same vernacular.
And it's like an unspoken dialect.
And I'm fascinated by those like miniature subsets of society
that speak in the same way, but no one ever acknowledges it.
We're like one person genuinely talks that way, like 70 years ago.
And everything's been an imitation of that person ever since.
It exists in medical waiting room.
People when they come in for Matthew.
Right this way for for Jonathan or like hotel concierges, like,
I'm sorry, we're fully committed.
They don't say we're full, but like there's these weird
vocabulary usages that just get set into it.
And I know that's what you had me on here to talk about.
Anthropology. Yeah.
Bizarre. Seen Park talk is very fascinating.
Yes. And and yeah, I think you're right that like,
yes, someone early on was like, let's try it this way.
And they're like, well, we did this way long enough.
I guess we do the next one.
Yeah, it's all come full circle.
Actually, there is a reason to talk about it with with Galaxy's Edge,
because they have a literal like list of things they're supposed to use,
like Bright Sun's offworlder and how hello traveler or whatever.
Yeah. Yeah.
Maybe the first instance of a specific set of language and terminology.
Only for the part. Yeah.
They tried it a little bit with Pandora.
Oh, really? But I think they gave it up very quickly.
Yeah, I bet they do at this one, too.
Yeah. Well, appear the first day there was already like a lady in the droid
depot who was just like, all right, this is thirty dollars.
Yeah. OK, here you go.
She didn't say anything. Yeah.
She like was like kind of trying to figure out what was even happening.
I feel like so I feel like with my friend, he got the blue milk,
which was the highlight of Galaxy's Edge for me.
I thought it was amazing. It is good.
Yeah. But they were like because I think someone in their party had
dietary restrictions and so they're like, what's what's in this?
Well, that's the blue milk of the bantha.
Yeah. But what's in it?
Well, it's the milk from the bantha.
No, no, I need you to tell me or I will die.
Yeah. And finally, the person because it's just rice milk with the fruit additive.
I'm sorry. I don't mean to get us back off Miami Vice.
They have no poisoning on this planet.
Is that a thing you have?
They have foaming at the mouth and you go to the hospital.
We call that the Sith's revenge.
Do you have the Sith's revenge?
Come on. The middle managers all like I asked one for directions.
They're like, the refreshers, the bathrooms are that way.
Like they said it.
And then they're just like, no, I just want you to just go.
I have to go somewhere else. Yeah.
The refreshers, the refreshers, the bathrooms are called.
Really? Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Yeah. Clearly not a fan of any of this.
There's no but Batoovian magic
coursing through your veins.
I like that stuff when it's done tongue in cheek, but I don't know.
I've said this before on a podcast or two.
I don't even I don't want to get negative.
Let's talk about Miami Vice.
That's a show set in our world, set in the grindy world.
They care of being drug smugglers.
Here's the quality that you could compare.
Oh, God. Have you guys watched it on YouTube or did you ever see it live?
I watched it. The whole thing is available on YouTube.
And this is one of my favorite
things to pick up on of like when home video cameras caught on.
Because that's really helpful for us doing research like, OK,
I could see the whole Miami Vice show. Yeah.
There is but a team little too early.
There is 15 seconds of footage on YouTube of the show.
Yeah. But there are multiple full versions of the Miami Vice one.
And the footage is silent.
Yeah, there's no audio.
A pretty good sizzle reel. Yeah.
But Miami Vice, you can see the whole thing from multiple years.
I saw the 18 one in person and it was in its last days.
And I I've told this story before, too, but it's really pertinent here.
So we my dad and I went for I think I'm sure for my birthday again.
And by the way, I also remember a merchandise booth outside the stunt show.
And you could buy all of the 18 action figures.
And they were the heads of the four 18 guys, but they had paramilitary
primary color bodies that were pure ripoffs from first series GI Joe.
Like the bodies were and they were cheaper plastic.
And I bought those and you could also buy an AK 47 toy gun.
That was really cool.
But also, I remember in the show, they didn't have a K-47.
They had M-14s with banana clips.
I'm getting so nerdy here.
But everybody at school was like, they got AK 47s like any gun with a banana clip.
And I was, you know, junior high, Matt Gorley, like, pardon me.
OK, hold on. I don't know.
And so we go into the stunt show and it was like near its.
It was already, I think, announced that it was closing soon.
It was a rainy day and outcome
B.A. Barakas and Hannibal in the 18 band.
They do a little opening stunt thing.
And so only those two characters come out.
And then Hannibal excuses himself, goes back in the van,
and the same guy comes out dressed as Murdoch and you never saw face.
He was never in the show.
What? And it was just like clearly they weren't putting money into it.
They didn't want to hire all the people.
People are sick or it was raining.
The whole thing was so lackluster.
It's like an Avengers with only Hawkeye. Yeah.
And then so then when I came back to see Miami Vice, my mind was blown
because it was probably newer and they were into it.
And like it was a real step up.
There was suddenly a lagoon and boats and explosions.
And then the like helicopter comes up. It was incredible.
I think there was a helicopter in the 1812
because it then sold that to Magic Mountain for their Batman and Robin stunt show.
I remember seeing the same helicopter.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, I think I'm pretty sure.
I mean, that's only going off my own recognition of that.
But I think you can take that to the back.
I think you're right. I wouldn't dare.
That's fact. Well, that is a fact.
The Batman and Robin stunt shows at Six Flags would do for like three weeks a year.
And then it would be like, oh, it's closed. Sorry.
Yeah. It was a busy period.
It was just done on the street.
There was no real set except the helicopter was above a facade.
So that would come up.
But like the rest of it was just kind of like gymnasts on mats dancing.
We're not dancing, fighting.
And that's the other thing.
They never they never seem to regiment stuff at Six Flags
because I saw Batman's stunt show.
And I think we talked about this on like the second or third episode.
But that was in a whole amphitheater.
What? Whoa. And then there was another there's another one
where it's like the Batman stunt show was on the body of water.
Yeah, there was a water show.
And it looked like it just opened up into a swamp.
Yeah. Like it just looked like there was a big body of water and there were boats.
But there was no like like backing or anything.
That's where the woods was behind it.
Great Adventure in New Jersey had the lethal weapons
stunt show, which was where that's where I got the bullet.
Like at the end, they're like giving away the blank, the casings to kids.
Like they were giving them out.
Wait, was there a stage manager in that one, like a cut guy who would yell cut?
I know. I think that one was more like water was more like story based.
It was. It didn't break the fourth wall.
These guys. Yeah, I like my realistic.
It definitely was a lot of drug dealers getting shot.
Like it was like a Miami Vice one.
Like, well, this would never fly nowadays.
I guess there's some gunplay in water world.
But before like the Internet knew so much about people
thought they knew so much about movies and announcements or movies.
Were there people that probably went and were like, wow, they're shooting a movie today.
I bet. Probably. Right.
Some like, you know, international travelers of like, this is a big deal.
Yeah, they must really be shooting.
I feel like you were like, hey, honey, what happened?
We saw that Indiana Jones movie shooting two years ago.
That would come out. I think we're in it.
I think, yeah. Like remember the guy next to us, he went down and he did a stunt.
Like, when did that movie come out?
My favorite thing was that you would see these stunts shows pop up on other TV shows quite a bit.
So like if there was especially like a kind of low budget,
syndicated show that shot on the universe a lot, they invariably did an episode
where one of the characters would end up on the Miami Vice stunt show set, like
out of this world. Do you remember that show?
Oh, yeah. She one time was on that set.
There was another one where they end up on it and they would just be like cheap
sets and they would like use some of the pyrotechnics.
If you're shooting on that lot, you'll find a way to use Flash Flood.
Yes. You'll find a way to use even like something from a movie.
Like I want to say Knight Rider went to the Psycho House twice.
I'm sure. I'm sure.
At least once. But there is a picture.
There is an 18 episode where a fish man
gets on the trolley that used to be up by where Seawalk is now.
A guy in a fish costume.
Like clearly like that sort of thing.
Was it Hannibal in disguise?
I couldn't. I just saw still pictures.
It might have been one of them in disguise, but you can see Womp
Hoppers in the background, the the long gone restaurant Womp
Hoppers we talked about before.
The two letters P something L Womp Hoppers.
What used to be Sagebrush Cantina, the second Sagebrush mentioned today.
There was this weird, like old timey restaurant called Womp Hoppers.
There was a restaurant themed after a it was supposed to be a wagon
wheel factory and a guy walked around.
It was very much like a dream finder and literally played by the same guy
who played Dream Finder, a guy in a beard like I'm H.L. Womp Hopper.
Was that so that wasn't in the park that was outside the park?
It was right outside the park.
The picture of it somewhere online.
We'll pull it up.
It was right where Saddle Ranch was, right? Yeah. Yeah.
It was like a big, honestly, a building I was thinking not.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
From the Miami Vice set.
But it looks like it's rusted out warehouse kind of early, you know,
like tin roofs and kind of collapse and sort of vibe.
C.L. Womp Hoppers.
Yeah, there you go.
Wow. And we'd like to get the rights to that character so we can do things.
We can make a movie.
We're trying to collect all the unused IP.
It isn't like nobody's doing anything with.
How many rights can we hold at the end of this park?
Yes, I hope we have yet to get one, though.
So no, no, no. Or look into how to do it.
Yeah. Well, I asked a friend once casually and he said, I don't know.
So that's a very thrilling conclusion.
Old friend.
Well, he knows things.
You know, he's into like looking up things.
So that's as far as I went.
That's as close to a lawyer.
I asked about there's a character named Marvel McFay,
who was a Six Flags character and he was also an old tiny beard.
Like a Sherman.
We love old timey beard cartoon character men in top hats.
All three of these things we would describe.
Dream Finder, Wampumper and and I said, hey, where do you think?
You think where would like where would we even go about this?
And he goes, that's probably like in the Warner Brothers vault.
Probably you'd have to like find a lawyer to find it in Warner Brothers.
Oh, my God. Because like they bought.
Well, they know they owned it already when it was Marvel and Fay,
but then they just got rid of him and then they just made it a Six Flags.
Like a standard. Wow.
That was Astroworld.
And so we got to break in in an Ethan Hunt.
We have to get it.
It's like the Indiana Jones warehouse where the Ark of Covenant is.
There's like all of these.
There's like shells of like cartoon characters, comma racist,
cartoon characters, comma not racist.
I'd like to be in on this. Yeah.
Join the heist. Please.
Large bearded fantastical cartoon men.
Yeah. And we'll only get chased out of this warehouse if we enter,
not because they're hiding secrets,
but because if we start poking around, they have to do work.
Yes, right.
I'm going to take the crew.
We're going to take the crane.
I got to put the gloves on if you have to.
Oh, God, I saw something on YouTube.
I was watching like a Disney history thing, and they had like the original print
of the illustration of the Disneyland Park and a woman at the archive.
This thing was handling it for him and she had white gloves on.
But they had those three dashes like Mickey Mouse has.
And I was just fuck off. Are you kidding?
You have to theme your fancy archivist gloves.
I might have been for the camera.
I don't care. It's too much.
If you're a Disney archivist, you're probably gung ho on that.
I know I have a complicated relationship with Disney.
How did it change working there versus?
I never had a reverence for Disney.
I loved going to Disneyland, but we're similar.
It's not like we're so we don't love.
But like, oh, you guys want to watch So Dear to My Heart, the 40s lamb movie.
We know like we like the rise and stuff.
Maybe the deepest reference I could have pulled.
It's some weird old live action.
It's like a family raising a lamb or something.
That's not Lambert, the sheepish lion.
No, because that's a cartoon.
Yeah. I think So Dear to My Heart is a boring old.
I've never seen So Dear to My Heart.
Wow. I don't know where I've never heard of.
That's a good quote, though. Yeah.
As long as it exists.
Let me look that up.
If it's not real, it wasn't a good pull.
And if so, I had a really specific dream.
Oh, here we go. It's from 1948.
The war combines animation and live action.
And it looks incredibly boring.
The war has been won.
A generation comes home to the homeland,
and this is what they're rewarded with for entertainment.
Family raises a lamb.
Now relax and watch.
Now relax. Yeah.
Jeremiah names do not address your PTSD.
Watch the lamb.
Watch the lives as Uncle Hiram.
Oh, no, I mean, I mean, I know.
I didn't realize fans.
OK, so let me alter my previous statement.
We didn't care about the movies until we found out about So Dear to My Heart.
Yeah. You were you were a right person more than a Disney historian.
Yeah. Yeah.
And like I said, I think I was more into
Universal.
And then when I was a teenager, Magic Mountain was the place to be
because it was hip.
And I'd gone to Knott's a ton because I lived pretty close to Knott's,
like 10, 15 minutes away from Whittier.
Yeah. It's neighbors to Buena Park, basically.
Do you still go? We love talking of Knott's as much as I haven't been in a while.
I would love to go to Knott's again and not for I don't want to go.
I don't want anything to do with the Halloween horror.
And I know. Sure. Sure. Yeah.
All right. I like that.
This guy defected and started liking haunts.
We went we went for the their their what's it called?
Not scary farm. Yeah.
And I got it. I'm into the mazes now.
But we were all scared when we started this podcast.
Yeah. I'm an excitable person and it scares me.
But my friend Jeremy works at Knott's from Super Ego.
He currently does. He does that Ghost Town alive thing.
And then he does the Hanging show and all that.
Oh, it's part of the hang. Yeah.
And my friend Ken, I believe I can't remember if he's still
directing and writing those.
I'm telling you, I'm your connection.
My ex-girlfriend was in the Waterworld stunt show.
Wow. Helen.
She was a Helen. Yeah.
Wow. Yeah.
Do we interact? We talk to Ghost Town alive people.
We met a deputy mayor.
We went to the opening of the new the reskinned rapid drive.
Oh, my God. Oh, it's been reskinned.
They they rethemed and they like incorporated into the Calico ghost town.
OK, that's not so terribly nice.
You got a crazy old lunatic on a porch with a musket.
Is that animatronic? Yeah.
Like not crazy. It just rocks back and forth.
But you get a little bit of movement.
You go to go check out all those robot rides,
whether or not you do coasters, do that if you want or not.
But we're just all about these charming robots
and that Knott's Chicken Dinner restaurant, which they like hippified a little.
And now it's like a little bit more like a gastropub or something.
Should we just go straight there after this?
Oh, my God. That boysenberry juice, too.
Yeah. Yeah.
For one very year.
They got all the boysenberry beer.
Yeah. Well, they have a whole boysenberry festival.
That's right. In March.
My dad went to high school with the Knott's, the Knott brothers.
Also, he worked as an ice cream scooper at Disneyland early on and met Walt Disney.
He was backstage and he and his Walt Disney, his wife came by
and were like, how they treating you here?
Why? Wow. Oh, crazy.
I don't think so.
I think Tony Baxter only met Walt once as a or did not meet Walt as a.
I don't remember.
I'm a second generation Disney employee.
I just realized that.
That is your grand.
Your granddaughter better go to work there.
You will work at Disney.
You will. You will do the family line.
You've a lady. It's the G-pop.
You know what? I we talked to we were talking about knots about this new,
you know, they did a lot of work on that rapids ride.
And I think I forgot to bring up a fact I had found out about knots.
Buena Park, in terms of an entity as like a town or a city,
has only existed for like a couple of decades before that.
It was kind of an unincorporated area.
And as such, the knots security team was deputized
like to assist with the was was deputized,
was sis the Orange County Sheriff's Office.
That makes sense.
I also have a friend who was a dispatcher at knots for security.
Yeah. So they would talk about that sometimes get
dispatched to help with situations and stuff.
And the head of the security for a long time was a knot, was a knot.
A knot. So I thought you were going to say something else.
Yeah. Keep that word going.
It was a knot.
Yeah, not.
That's true.
Is it myth or true that no one can be pronounced dead on Disney grounds?
And so if someone dies, which they have, I think that's kind of urban.
There's no record saying much. Yeah.
But as soon as their soul leaves their body, that's technically not.
Then it's a fairy land and it goes right to the haunted mansion.
You're happy.
Now, if you die on Disney grounds, they give you the option of
when do you like to go to work as a grim grinning ghost?
How's your baritone?
Yeah, we don't say they passed away.
We say they're now a happy haunt.
Gone to a happier hauntier place.
Oh, I.
I OK.
So does that mean that technically like a ghost town sheriff could?
That's what my question was going to be.
Arrest somebody. Oh, too.
Yeah. And as a ghost town like bandit, breaking the law.
Mm hmm. The knot stunt show.
Oh, God. That was one that didn't change for years and years.
It's different now. But I had that thing memorized.
I loved that thing so much.
Is it a Western one? Yeah.
I wanted to be in it so bad.
And I went and tried out when I was in college.
I was I was a really little guy in high school
and really wiry thin in college.
And it was just like no way I could pass for a man.
And I even wore like a plaid vest to kind of like butch myself up.
But that doesn't do that.
And I think I generally got laughed out of there.
They didn't have like a nerd or a dorky barber who they could pull
his pants down or something.
Oh, they had an audience plant in Hawaiian shirt.
But even that guy was like a bearded.
They were all men.
Like they were like the Beaumont Bear was like a big Hollywood stunt man
that came down to the Berry Pick and Knots Berry Farm.
And like the main guy was like a real fancy dude.
And the Beaumont Bear was a Hollywood stunt man who would come bully him around.
And then there was just those two guys in the audience plant
who would like come on stage in a Hawaiian shirt.
And the main dude was like, I'm going to throw a Hollywood punch to you.
He's like, hold on. I just had a taco.
You know, and you think he's really a plant because he's also got a wife
he's sitting with.
And then he's the one that ends up getting shot and doing a high fall at the end.
And you're like, whoa, that's great.
I miss that one, because now it's kind of like there's like a big Gatling gun.
And it's just like trying to be a little bit more blockbuster like Waterworld.
But it's somewhere in the middle and it doesn't work.
There was something really quaint about just the three person stunt man.
Yeah, we saw one a couple of years ago, which I think is the bigger scope.
Probably one, I think so.
Knots is getting back, I think, to the charm, though, with the ghost.
I got to get out to that.
It's slowly like trying to charmify the park again.
I thought I think is my friend Ken, who went to work there, Ken Parks,
who used to work at Disney and is responsible for a lot of that stuff
because he's great.
And he brought, I think, some of that Disney style stuff over.
Yeah. Yeah.
Geez. Well, yeah, mission accomplished.
It is. It just get more and more charming by the year.
That's what we want. Charm. Yeah. Same. Same here.
We love charm. Charm.
Chicken and charm. Tear down the coasters.
Yeah. Bring up the charm.
That's the main thing that this stunt show happened under the shadow
of a roller coaster that just every 10 seconds. Right.
Yeah. So that was that was not the case originally,
because that's one of the fairly newer ones.
I see. Yeah. Right. Right.
Oh, I miss that stunt show.
Oh, geez. My advice, though, I, you know, well, you know,
you were also talking about you were talking about the set being cool.
I want to give a little shout out to the I think.
I think this I think the main thing was landscaped beautifully.
So beautiful. Yes. Yeah.
Lush vegetation looks like you're in the
because you're supposed to be you're on some sort of like all drug smuggling island.
Yeah. But do they ever mention drugs?
You know what? I saw like copy in.
Oh, wait, hang on. Smugglers and arms traders. Yeah.
So smugglers could be it could be like rare exotic bananas.
It could be just definitely that. Yeah.
Yeah. I have the phrase, he says Caribbean crime boss
and his gang of sleazy smugglers.
I saw that. And action.
So they're smuggling like gold teeth.
Also, the sound systems on these things were amazing, too,
because we can the music blares when they start and you get that like,
what are they called? Timmons drums.
I always get it wrong. Simmons or Timmons drums with those like,
oh, yeah. Yeah.
And those in the arena.
Oh, God. He's sort of like tinny speak.
It's like music.
The Miami Vice theme is perfectly suited to be played on those kind of like.
Yeah. Like not great car speak.
It's cassette rock. Yeah. I think.
And if I remember correctly, like Waterworld, they do use blanks in.
They do use blanks. Yeah.
In Miami Vice, it was sound effects and they had dummy guns.
And they were doing the like recoil because I remember like there's a
Crockett and Tubbs, especially maybe one or two of the goons
have blanks at some point. Yeah.
Crockett and Tubbs have like the same guns.
They just keep tossing. Yeah.
The whole time. And the sound doesn't know.
It's not always 100 percent.
It's either dead on or it's a little off.
And the best part, again, is like you get into the zone
where they're phoning it in.
So even the recoil of the gun is just this like lackluster.
You know, there was a thing where they pull back, shoot one guy with a shotgun
and he's hooked up to an elastic cord and he gets like drawn back
through these main two doors.
And it's so slow and elastic.
But it's so funny, like you shoot someone with a shotgun
and then they fly back at like a medium pace through the air.
It's so strange. And I just I just love the artificialness of it.
I don't know what it was.
How could you possibly go through those motions and not just get limper
and limper? I don't know.
As time goes on.
I mean, I have that question about any.
I've never been in a play or anything that ran for a long time. Yeah.
I've done any performance more than once ever.
So I don't know how anybody like gives it their all.
Like, yeah, I imagine like doing Shakespeare 300 nights in a row.
But I still want my theme park employees to, you know, give it all you got. Yeah.
There's some like like
Crockett does a flip at some someone does a flip.
Someone kicks someone else in the face.
Those are those seem like they're the fun ones to do because they they give it.
They're all. Yeah, they have to to literally like get over to flip.
And also not land on their head.
But the faces are still dead.
That's the crazy thing. They're doing all this stuff and their faces are dead.
I will say this, and I worked at Disneyland for
10, 12 years. I don't know.
I never found it in that improv stuff.
Even so, Papa Beast, or like I would give it my all because I think I was.
I think it just came from doing theater in college.
They're like, it's embarrassing if you're not convincing, you know.
Yeah. Yeah. Stunt man.
You're not really trained in acting.
And so I and I guess there would be a drudgery to it, though.
At the same time, I've heard the other complaint about stuntmen
that they go so like I've heard people who have to say like,
he does not be like what would a real person do?
Not just like huge swing back and like, oh, right.
Like like hammy deaths can be.
I think maybe some men have a hard time like finding that.
Yeah. That middle. Yeah.
I went I remember taking a whole roll of film once of like, you know,
Kodak film, just shooting pictures of the stunt show.
And then I went home and tried to build a G.I. Joe stunt show.
So I would like I had like as a young age, pretty much learned
how to do like blood pack squibs.
And so I'd set up these little model rocket igniters to batteries and put little
I would drain Piccolo Pete powder out of Piccolo Pete's,
put him in these like toothpaste caps and made this little diorama.
And then I'd made like a little brass tube that I had my neighbor drill with like
some holes that got smaller and hooked a little rubber tube up to like a big
lighter and hid that so there could be like a line of flames that would come up
and then hit the button.
And they're like a little explosion.
And I made little mattresses for my G.I. Joe.
Whoa. Let them fall safely.
Yeah. Yeah.
And it was just like I wanted to play the stunt show, not the real,
not the reality. Yeah.
You're speaking our language.
Oh, boy. And not even like I'm going to fuck up my toys and throw them hard at the ground.
Like what they got to be because they got to do the show.
Yeah. Yeah. They got to they got to redo it.
And I'd have to clean the like white powder burns off them each time.
But even so, on the set, I liked the powder burns because the Miami Vice thing
was covered in white powder burns, you know.
Oh, yeah. They reuse like any like time like there was a bullet hit on the walls.
It was just like a little plug cap they put in there.
And so I would sit there in the beginning of the show and go like,
oh, that's a bullet hit.
That's a bullet hit because it was just stained white from all the powder.
You know. Oh, yeah.
Which causes this set that's supposed to be rustic to begin with.
Yeah. Age up as it goes, bearing the scars of its many performances.
Yeah. Pretty cool.
Would you watch movies as a kid and be like just kind of fascinated
by the process more than the movie itself? Yeah.
And any time I could take a peek behind the curtain, like in Die Hard,
when they go up to the roof and the helicopters coming and John McClain
shoots his gun up in the air to get the people to go back downstairs
and then the helicopters shoot the roof.
There's two shots where you can see the whole web of wires
for the squibs on the ground, like they didn't even bother to hide them.
They're just laid out.
Well, bare wires with little squibs.
I'm trying to remember. Oh, in Platoon, when
Willem Dafoe's character is running out in that huge moment,
he's wired with tons of squibs, but they didn't work.
And there are so many it was such a major shot with so many cameras,
helicopters and explosions that they kept going.
And there's a couple of shots where you can see him pressing the button
in his hand. Nothing's happening.
And then he lets go.
And then later the wires just dangling from his hand and like wide open
shots. He's just you just a wire hanging from his hand.
And did you notice that as a kid? Yeah. Yeah. Wow.
Yeah. So you were really just paying attention to that.
You're so into squibs. Well, I had this podcast called I Was There Too.
And I would always ask these guests, have you ever been squibbed?
And then on the 50th episode, I had asked so much that this special effects
house reached out to me and I was going to be in New York for Super Ego.
And we did a whole documentary on me getting squibbed.
It's called The Squibbening.
And I finally got to realize my dream.
We did one individual squib.
And then we did a shot of four machine gun squibs on me.
And it was so fun. Wow. How did it look?
It looked great. Yeah.
I mean, you can just Google the squibbening and it's a documentary online.
You can watch it. Were you happy with your your own performance?
Do you think you rode the stunt man line?
I don't think I did it well because I was too well.
A, it was too new an experience and B, I was too relishing the moment to act.
Oh, sure. Yeah. Yeah.
You can't compare. You can't tame that smile down.
No, I couldn't. I couldn't. I was too happy to get shot.
Well, well, are there moments like that?
Because you're a big James Bond guy. Yeah. Right.
You have a James Bond podcast as well. That's right. Yeah.
Are there any moments you ever caught like in the classic Bond movies?
Like, well, there's I can see that.
Oh, good question. I'm sure there is.
Let me think, especially around those 80s ones.
You also design.
Did you design a hypothetical James Bond park or stunt show?
I did. OK, so, yeah, this is slightly embarrassing.
I did three.
I've done three prints of James Bond theme park stunt spectaculars.
So I did the Thunderball Aquatic Extravaganza, which is like in a big tank.
And then I did Live and Let Die Stunt Spectacular and
Honor Majesty Secret Service.
And they all take place at fictional like Six Flags over Squaw Valley
Snow Resort, Six Flags over over
Baton Rouge.
And then there was one in Florida.
And if you go to MacWheely.com, you can see those or purchase them.
Like, yeah.
And I'm thinking about doing some other movies, you know, like
like Friday the 13th or, you know, like stunt spectaculars or something.
And wow. Wow. And what is that art?
What's what's in? How do you convey what?
I treated it like a poster from the time.
So it's not like a drawing of what it would actually look like.
But I remember the like newspaper ads for Miami Vice.
And so you would see the elements of the actual set as they were.
But it was still movie posterized where everything's kind of coming at you.
And it was like kind of fictional looking and explosions.
Like it's it's not meant to be linear.
So it incorporates all the elements of the movie that would be in that stunt show.
Yeah. Yeah. That's a great idea.
Wow. Wow. So like there's sharks in the in the Thunderball one and a jet pack.
And, you know, and then they're like this
honor majesty secret service one has like a bobsled track and because also.
Oh, sure. Did you all of you guys ever covered this?
You probably know about this at Six Flags Magic Mountain in 1984
when the Olympics were big and not the Los Angeles Olympics,
but the Sarajevo, Yugoslavia Olympics.
There was a ride called Sarajevo bobsleds at Magic Mountain.
No never come across this.
Based on the Olympics. Oh, my God.
It's funny you say that because I was at
Busch Gardens Williamsburg during the 96 94, which was the 90s Olympics.
They was 96.
And then Izzy, you remember Izzy, the little mascot.
They had built a small wildcat roller coaster that was themed to Izzy.
Really? So is he coaster?
Yeah. Magic Mountain was big on just buying prefab
roller coasters and loosely theming them. Yeah.
But I believe they shut the bobsleds one down because it was dangerous
because it was loose bobsleds in a like regular bobsled with wheels instead of
blades blades. Yeah.
And it was just in a U shaped like a water slide track.
Whoa. Yeah. Which is the kind of ride that feels very action point,
like the kind of thing where they would totally fuck you up
and skin your knees if you fell off it.
Yeah. Yeah. Jeez, that's a dangerous thing.
You know, the Miami Vice Stunt Show was written and put together by
the guy Phil Hedema, who's come up on the show before part of the Star Trek thing
we talked about a little while back.
But he got into theme park world after having designed the opening
and closing ceremony of the 84 L.A. Olympics, which is totally insane
where a UFO lands and a spaceman comes out and like, you know, he
essentially it's not this.
It's some message about like why I've seen you humans now, like your finest
and your most harmony.
And does that imply that he was like going to kill us?
Right. And the Olympics convinced him not to.
I did not remember that until you said that stuff, because I went to some of the
84 Olympics as a kid. Oh, really?
I didn't go to the opening ceremonies, but now I want to rewatch that.
That sounds nuts.
I only barely did it out the door.
I got to sit and watch the whole thing.
But also Lionel Richie killer all night long performance.
80 for those. Those are.
Yeah, I come in for solid. Yeah.
Yes. Will it be as fun this time?
It's like the destroy the city.
Well, it may be. Yeah.
No longer possible.
Yeah, that feels like that Super Bowl halftime show before they would just get
like an old rock act. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. When they when they had skits.
I want skits in my sports entertainment.
Start doing stunt shows at halftime, because actually, that's a lot more
football based than, you know, putting like Justin Timberlake in.
Like, imagine you do it.
Action stunt spectacular at the halftime.
Do you know about? Yeah.
We all we're all challenged to tell you.
We can't wait to tell you.
Sorry, I got to go.
No, please. All right. I'll write you a letter about it.
There was a there was an Indiana Jones halftime show promoting
the Indiana Jones adventure opening at Disneyland.
And it was so the star of the stunt show is just a man you've never seen before
as Indiana Jones.
And it is it's stunts, it's passing of the Super Bowl trophy back and forth
like Marion, it's Marion to amazing in between performances from
Tony Bennett, Tony Bennett.
Tony Bennett sings Can You Feel the Love Tonight?
I believe the Lion King song and Patti LaBelle.
Yeah, I think that's right.
Yeah. Yeah. With a big shock and hair.
Capsa in there singing Anything Goes.
Oh, yeah.
That's what it's kind of that vibe.
It's a little bit of like the 40s cabaret club or whatever.
I got to check that out.
Indiana Jones falls from the sky.
He skydives into the arena.
Yeah, I got to see that.
Oh, it's it's so nuts.
And I think and that like I think it was for everything you read about it.
It was a disaster. It like barely came together.
And I think people did maybe get hurt.
So there was some weird thing where like, or at least during the one run
through, they had the Patti LaBelle's high heel got caught in a grate
or something, and she almost tripped and fell down the stairs.
Really insane.
But it's like all the stuff like spikes coming up from the ground
and India avoiding it, but live during the Super Bowl.
Did you guys ever see the miniature stunt show they did in Disneyland
for Indiana Jones?
It was kind of in the like a jungle area.
Bizarre. Oh, we talked about that.
As a woman. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
We never heard of it till we looked into. Yeah.
Go to hell.
I don't think he says go to hell.
But if she possesses, he possessed.
She's possessed. I saw it. So it's fine. Yeah. Yeah.
He's really punching the devil via this woman's body.
He doesn't want the devil.
Then he throws her into the Cave of Wonders.
Right.
It's like a slightly disguised the old Cave of Wonders set.
He does. He does kill her eventually. Yeah.
Yeah. It's OK. He kills her.
Killings fine. Punching.
And he puts her out of her misery.
Yeah. The humane thing.
Right. Were you working there when that happened?
I might have been, but I don't remember.
That seems like that could have crossed over.
I forget. What am I missing from?
Miami Vice is a very I mean, there's some very impressive.
The helicopters are impressive.
I do wonder if the helicopter what worked more often,
the helicopter or the water world Balsa wood plane?
Yeah, Balsa wood plane gets canceled if there's too high a wind.
Is that what it is? Yeah.
Yeah. They don't do it, which would be a real bummer.
What do they do? They just they just saw it once.
They just set off all the fireworks, I think. Right.
But I think, yeah, I think so.
But then there's a weird thing, at least when I saw it when I was much younger.
There's a weird part where the deacon goes.
There's a crash. He hears a crash and he looks back where you can't see and says,
Oh, no, my plane. Oh, yeah.
No, I love I think I love.
I don't know.
Maybe it's not a theme park stunt show unless there's stuff that doesn't work.
Acclaimed stuff.
The other cool thing in Miami Vice was when they ride in that mine car.
That's the mine. And it explodes and they go flying out.
That just blew my mind. That's a crazy stunt.
I don't know how they do that.
That is like you can't half ass that.
They get seems so whiplashy.
They get just suddenly hard stops and they go flying out.
And they do like a full flip, I believe.
Yes. Both of them.
That's what's also impressive to me is that they both flip out of it.
Yeah. And you'd think they would like their heads would collide regularly.
It would happen all the time.
But maybe it did. I don't know. Yeah.
They the articles when this was opening in the L.A.
Times, the MCA's corporate safety program director,
because MCA owned Universal at this time, said our industry quote,
our industry gets a lot of publicity when things go wrong, said Paul Holhouse.
I love it.
I love it. All the whole house.
I'm the director of the MCA's corporate safety program.
But what are what are all the Miami Vice, at least like the water
and the landscaping looks pleasant.
It's aesthetically appealing to look at.
The 18 look like a dirty field, like a dirty demolition,
derby, monster truck show.
Yeah, it was it was like a Mexican villa or something.
Or I can't remember. I think it's the border.
I think you're at the relevant US Mexico border and the like it's so it's
and you're you're watching it through like there's a fence in front of you
with barbed wire that like bends.
That's like that feels like it's trapping in the performer side of things.
So that was like a safety thing.
There was like a chain link fence or it was theming or safety or maybe all together.
I don't know. But it's so dreary.
You're watching like a very depressing pen essentially.
Footage of that has to exist, like archive footage of that thing.
I wish they would release that.
How could it only be?
Yeah, definitely made it hard to find much about.
But yeah, I saw a couple of photos that were really miserable.
And then I read about this sort of miserable
like union organizing situation.
They there was a successful walkout by the A team.
I guess not successful in the A team.
By the A team. They did it.
They banded together.
Doesn't fight their way out.
I love it when a plan comes together.
I love when a union comes to collective bargaining.
You don't got to solve everything with punches.
By the way, I rewatched some of the A team originally in the first season.
His catchphrase or at least the first few episodes that would just be the pilot
because they actually recast face, I think, and did some recasting.
His his catchphrase was not I love it when a plan comes together.
It was Hannibal's on the jazz.
Well, it's like I'm on the jazz.
That was his way of saying, like, I'm I'm in the like the rhythm I'm in.
I'm on the prowl.
I'm making it happen in the pocket.
I don't know what. But it's my catchphrase now.
That's what I was thinking.
It's on the jazz.
We will we will find a proper moment to say it later on.
Yeah, that was another IP that we can buy up because nobody's using it.
They never made T-shirts of on the jazz.
So it's ours now.
So the yeah, they were like they seem to perform.
They're very unhappy with what they were making on the thing.
And they even quoted them like somebody says,
we don't feel we should risk our lives for a lousy two hundred fifty dollars a week
when I could go dump trash and get paid more.
Gee, we assume that's a five day work week.
So that's fifty dollars a day for stunt work.
That's crazy.
Is it around what I got paid as a tour guide?
These guys are but this is but then, yeah, an eighty five and it's stunt people.
Yeah, that's really shitty.
They proposed to Universal a five dollar per performance raise.
That's and Universal said, how about a fifteen dollar per performance cut?
They like just they got the request and just said, fine,
we're drastically cutting your salary.
So they all walked out.
And but the universe was like fine.
And they just put up a newspaper ad for more, which maybe is what happened
when you saw it. Maybe they were just like, well, we found three of the guys,
but not all of them.
You got to go back and forth.
You're Murdoch to stunt scabs scabs.
The lowest form of life.
That's what Haim Saban did at the Power Rangers.
Right. Yeah. Right.
They're like, hey, we want some money because this is so popular.
And he was like, no, I will replace you.
And he did. And like as a kid, I was just like, oh, that sucks.
I like them. Anyway, I'll keep watching.
Weird that that cool doesn't like Bernie Sanders or Elizabeth Warren.
That's weird. Yes, it is weird. I agree.
They also released a statement, another bizarrely named universal person,
Patty Casino.
Whole house and casino are on the job.
Another whole house casino production.
Patty Casino took to the papers to say, you know, the stuntmen say that
it's what this is.
They choose one of our most popular shows, but actually, it's not as popular
as the Western show or the animal show or kind of the barbarian.
She went out of her way to say it's not doing well for us.
So that's like when Disney was like, you know, Lord Miller,
we're doing a very good job making this solo movie.
That's why we fired them.
Yeah. Yeah.
I sent them away in disgrace.
They must have had ghostwriters on all their other mega successes.
Yeah. These guys were really shit in the bed on the set.
It does seem a little claustrophobic to me, the idea of going to Universal
and doing the tram and then five shows like that.
Yeah. A lot of sitting.
Yeah, because there was no lower like lot theme park area at that point.
Yeah. Yeah.
Until they installed the star way.
Upcoming topic, the star way.
The escalator. Yes. Yeah.
We did. We got an episode in the can about the escalator.
We had a lot to say. Oh, yeah.
Who is that out yet?
Not known in our world.
That's familiar to me.
Yes. Similarly, Monday.
Earlier in the episode, I think.
Probably.
Although I think it will be up by the time this comes out.
Now that I'm thinking about it, I'm doing the math in my head.
The world will know.
The world will have changed.
It sounds familiar because of all the awards it won.
You're getting like a future future flash.
I think it's happening.
That's the 84 Olympic ceremony.
Yeah.
One day you will have the world's greatest escalator.
I believe in you, humanity.
The same quote from the guy who does doesn't like his
two hundred fifty dollars salary for some reason.
He is the guy who plays Mr.
T in the beginning of his his quote to the press.
He says, I pity the fool who takes my money.
Oh, my God.
He did his newspaper quote in character that
that helps his case a little bit.
He should be out of here.
He should be enjoying his fight.
Or maybe he should.
He's showing how good he is.
Yeah, that's true.
The probably unspeaking role in the show.
Right. There was a Mr.
T who worked for Universal until he died.
There was a Baracus who could walk around character.
Well, he became a tram driver after the show.
That name on the studio tour, JJ.
I don't specifically remember that person, but it does sound familiar.
I'm going to head to the stronger union, I guess.
He worked for Universal until he died in 2014.
Oh, geez. That's nice.
Lifer. Huh?
Um, the what have I what have I missed?
The there's sorry, I was going to say Miami Vice.
Yeah, I have there was I watched it behind the scenes,
which is like it was billed as like a making of.
It's like two minutes long.
I just see that there's a Conan one that's kind of our Conan.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
There's super tech going on with that, because if people don't know that show,
there's a dragon that rises up from the lasers.
Yeah. Yeah. And laser is the highest tech thing of all.
Rain curtain.
So somebody in the video is like, you know, there's 50 stunts in 18 minutes
and it will be radical.
I wrote that down, too.
And I can tell you it was radical.
Yeah, it certainly was.
And I wrote that guy who says that kind of looks like Randy Johnson.
A little bit. Oh, yeah.
Mustachioed baseball.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that is a great moment.
My other favorite part of that video is a guy practicing doing
practicing taking shots from like a zip line.
So he's there choreographing when the shots would take place
and watching a man slide down a zip line and go, what do you think?
Really, really fun.
Yes, that is good. Yeah. Yeah.
Good video. Good video.
It's a short one, though.
They also then there's a part where a guy says, yeah,
you got to be careful and choreograph these things, right?
Because if not, this can happen.
And he raises his arm and it's in a full cast like that.
I had a crazy angle.
And then the narrator says, but when it all works right,
which is almost all the time
in a casino whole house production, no
spared no expense.
Put the money on the screen.
There is a way there is an odd joke in Miami Vice.
The one joke where I'm like, well, that really wouldn't fly nowadays is the
the director, MC guy picks up a rifle and he's like, of course,
everything is the sound.
These are fake guns.
We never use live ammo.
And then he points it at the ground.
A bunch of squibs go off in the water.
And he's like, whoa, I guess this thing loaded.
And I'm like, 1995, when did Brandon Lee happen?
Like, I was just like, oh, I don't this seems I don't know about this one.
Yeah, right. That's right.
The Crowe stunt show was not ultimately, you know,
did not get off the ground.
That's the thing with the show in general that I do.
I think today, if a new theme park stunt show was put together,
I don't think it would just be guns.
It is a show all about guns and nothing but guns.
And in the case of Miami Vice, like,
you know, we're ignoring all of the like moral complexity
and ambiguity of the show and all of that.
That is mainly a show where people like talk very soberly and like, no, it's guns.
They shoot each other. Big guns.
I say bring it back, but 2006 Miami Vice.
So it's a lot of like, I love that.
Can you get the encore? Do you want more?
And like, there's the weird Colin Farrell, weird haircut.
They keep saying go fast boats.
Get in the go fast boats.
Yeah, get in the go fast.
It's just the boats and a lot of lighting and digital video from the time
and the Jay-Z, Linkin Park mashups. Yeah.
Oh, right. That's what you get to see.
I've never watched it. Just sound pretty crazy.
I like it a lot, actually.
I know I'm in the minority, but I think there's a growing appreciation
for that movie again.
It's come up a lot lately.
And I'm like, I can rewatch that.
Yeah, like I don't I don't think it's better.
I think Collateral is still a better movie.
But like that, it's we it's interesting to see what expensive digital
film looked like at the time.
What I remember about that movie is that somebody came to speak to my film school
who was working in the post department of that movie and who's in.
They said that during editing, Michael Mann would come in
and watch the full movie every day.
He would not just do a part of it when he got there.
I love the thing.
I'm not just me. I'm a fan.
Look how cool that light looks.
Crack of Dawn. Public enemies is dog shit.
Don't watch public enemies.
Oh, no. No.
Dillinger one. Right. Too bad.
I I should also say the
you know, it's weird is that Universal Florida had this show
that was on their lagoon.
They had a stunt show for a long time that was not Miami Vice,
but it starred like two Miami vicey dudes.
And they played the Miami vice music
through the whole show was all scored by Miami vice music.
But it was not specifically the Miami vice stunt.
It was called Dynamite Nights Stuntacular.
Did you guys ever see to stay around for at night and watch Dynamite?
Never. I miss that show.
A non brand.
If there's any way to make this better, making it a little less brand.
Yeah. Yeah. Miami vice stunt.
Spectator generica sizing it up a bit.
I never remember seeing that.
I probably saw it from a bad viewpoint only when I went in like 2012 or 2014
where it like happened to be eating at dinner at Lombards,
the seafood place on the water.
And they're like, oh, you can go out on the patio and just watch.
And at that time, it was Morgan Freeman telling you about the importance of movies
like the magic of 100 years of movies.
OK, that was less spectacular.
Extremely dull. Yes. Yeah.
But I guess like I should mention this with a gun thing to her as this question,
like saying when there was this new Miami vice
that sort of got back to the roots of what it was going to be like.
I don't know the show unbelievably well.
I have not watched the full run of the show, but it does not seem like
I feel like I know so much more the the theme park version of it.
But it does not seem like it was a show that was all ass kicking all the time.
You know what I mean?
Like and I even saw YouTube comment that said this is more like Rambo to me
than Miami vice.
So which I don't mind.
I think it's cool that it just like takes all the top moments of the show
and boils it down, but does not necessarily reflect its source material.
Not at all.
Yeah. Yeah. It was way more Rambo.
Yeah. Yeah.
Tango and cash kind of thing or so. Oh, sure. Sure.
Yeah. Yeah. Which apparently in the same guy, I mentioned Phil Hedema
who planned the things he said in the newspaper article.
The tour had been planning a new live action edition to the studio since last fall.
But the executives didn't decide on a Miami vice theme until February.
And this article is from July.
So wow.
They were like they were building a stunt show without knowing.
Oh, right. It was going to be.
They probably knew it's it's guns and it's boats.
They maybe they're building the lagoon, but not which maybe it was some other
problem. They were toying around or keeping it generic in case the Rambo rights
came through or something.
Yeah, I know that there was concept work done for a James Bond stunt show
for I believe Universal.
In fact, Ralph McQuarrie did the artwork.
You can see it online.
And it's the volcano set from You Only Live Twice.
I mean, yeah, that's yeah, that seems awesome.
Is James Bond reflected in theme park world anywhere?
I don't believe so. Yes.
Oh, yes.
Briefly at Kings Dominion, when it was in the Paramount parks,
they had a motion simulator theater for the longest time.
It was Days of Thunder and it was slightly more movement than
D box or 40 X.
You kind of sat in chairs like that and it would be like the NASCAR race.
And then in the mid 90s, they flipped it to Pierce Brosnan and James Bond.
Oh, wow. I never got to see it.
And that only lasted a year or two.
And then they flipped it to like Stan Lee presents the age of heroes,
like one of those generic superhero things that like they slapped Stan Lee's name on.
Oh, no heroes you'd recognize.
No. Oh, no, no, no, no.
All new. It's the new universe of heroes like there's colors.
Just blue man, yellow man.
I feel like Stan made up as many character
or had involvement with as many characters in Marvel as he did outside.
Like he has 300 characters you never heard of.
Yeah. Yes. Like just trying.
There's some audible thing right now.
Yeah. Yeah. There's all these different ways.
I was I just when I was a comic and I was like,
is Stan's most popular creation outside of Marvel strip orella?
It is for me now.
And at a TV show, there was a Pamela Anderson voice TV show on TV.
It's recognizable. Right.
So like that might be it outside of anything he did at Marvel. OK.
And final, final thoughts in Miami Vice related stuff, as you're saying,
hearing that hearing that score blare through those speakers.
Fantastic. The Jan Hamer Jan Hamer.
Do you do you use I mean, your temptation is to say Jan Hamer.
But I think it's I think you're right.
I think it is. I think I got it right the first time.
It just felt I felt pretentious saying it or something.
Yeah. I was looking up the rest of the of the the Jan Hamer discography.
I discovered that he was keyboard magazines,
best studio synthesis for two years in a row.
Jesus Christ.
I'm surprised you had to look that up, because I assume you know that.
I've got four years of synthesizer.
Yeah, yeah, I've got him loaded up.
Yeah, he took the reins from Greg Fillinggain.
And so, you know, obviously the guy to beat.
But, you know, I'm reading all the, you know, the the odds and ends about
Jan Hamer, and then I get to the end of the most recent thing on June 25th,
2019, the New York Times magazine listed Jan Hamer among the hundreds of artists
whose material was reportedly destroyed in the 2008 year.
Fire. We this is how it's been a couple of times now.
We talked about that with that crazy fire that burned up
the music masters a little while ago.
And then who was it? It was like some it was like the gentle band
that does the Woody's roundup music like the night.
These nice guys who play their fiddles,
all their all their masters were destroyed in the universal fire.
And now this is going to have to be like copy pasted for every episode.
For any time we talk about a musician.
Tragic. Deal with that fire.
You know, anyway, horrible.
But his music lives on in the best quality that you can find it,
which is on camcorder videos of a stunt show.
That is that's what probably if you're like programming drums,
it's how you want it to sound.
It's coming through several mediums at once.
Yes. That crunch.
It also has the music as like that pan.
What is it like a flute of some kind? Right.
Synthesize like a pan flute or synth flute or something.
It's like it's like the intro to Thunder in Paradise, which I love.
Oh, yeah. Syndicated show.
Also, if there could have been a stunt show of any that.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Thunder and paradise properties that jump out to you.
If you I mean, Rambo, you mentioned Rambo would be amazing stunt show.
I mean, they made a kids cartoon out of it.
Was there really? Yeah, there was. Yeah.
Well, how did they like handle all the Rambo enos of it?
He was just it basically was a team format where he would go help some village
every time, I think.
And it was like a general villain that was after him or something.
He was in like
Tierra Libre was the the country he was in.
I don't know how I remember this.
They were the Robocop cartoon.
Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Yeah.
Robocop show. That'd be good. Yeah.
Oh, my God. That would be the best.
Some of these might have existed in like Germany or Australia.
Because there was a stray police academy stunt show in a couple of odd places.
But Star Wars stunt show, an actual like stunt spectacular was amazing.
They've never really done that.
There's always some twist to it, like a Jedi academy or something that just shits it.
Yeah, there are there.
I feel like that the promise of some of Galaxy's Edge was like,
and there's going to be like flash mob scenes and like,
I don't know if they're going to roll that out eventually.
But you would feel like they could do a full, cool, awesome, like, yeah.
Within the land stunt show somehow. Mm hmm.
And it's a it's a property we're getting.
Violent is not so it's fine. It's great.
We have it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
No, it's a laser. Right now. Bullets. That's great.
Oh, yeah. True. Yeah. And they're they're aliens.
We don't have any attachment to the aliens or robots. Stormtroopers. Yeah.
I wish they'd just do full on adult franchise themes
like theme parks, stunts shows like a Saving Private Ryan stunts show.
Platoon die hard, die hard stunts show.
The series.
You watch the guy getting his finger.
Michael Clayton. Yeah, Michael.
And that's a guy just fixing all the problems after the stunt show. Yeah.
Yeah. Good. The car explodes in that car.
Sure. Building that happened before the show. Oh, OK. Yeah.
You just seem to go through everything.
The theme park having to buy the property to have a full size,
an accurate size Normandy like to get the scale of the beach. Correct.
They have to close down their adjoining water park.
So it all becomes a much sadder beach.
And then how do you handle the German soldiers or Nazis?
Because wasn't didn't they used to have swastikas in the Indiana Jones
stunt show and they took them all out.
Now it's just kind of generally red and black. Yeah.
That's just like, yeah,
they're jerks. It's the jerk patrol. Yeah.
Well, we're we might be on the the precipice
of a new generation of stunt shows with those Marvel robots.
Have you seen those, the stunt robots? Oh, yes. Yeah.
These crazy things that fly through the air that like can make a super heroic pose.
Yeah. So like we.
I mean, they're obviously going to kill us eventually, but it's.
The least they could do is do some stunt shows in the meantime.
Do a little stunt show for us and then murder us in a couple of years.
Get our defenses down. Right.
Full sense of security. Warm our hearts.
So just here to do stunts, spectacular.
It doesn't matter that they're multiplying.
They found a way to mate.
It just means more stunt shows.
There's more than today because that just means more stunts for us.
Yeah. Right.
Everybody gets a personal stunt team in their house now. Yeah.
And they keep talking about two weeks to go time.
It must be a stunt language.
I don't know.
Wouldn't it be very like apropos if we were all killed by a bunch of superheroes?
Yeah. Like they took over our cinema.
Now they're in our homes and like Spider-Man is just choking us all out.
Like, yeah, we deserve it.
I guess we just make me breakfast or something.
Yeah. Some dweeb like his life being choked out of him going,
Oh, who watches the watchman?
See, so leave his body. Yeah.
That's the way I want to go.
I mean, for one, I welcome our robot stunts eventual overlords,
but they would not exist without the the brave stuntman
who literally did break their arms to make the Miami boys show what it was.
Thank you for coming and talking to us about it for a while.
Matt Gorley Survive podcast.
I do it all over again.
I feel like there's more to talk about.
Yeah, there's probably.
Send us a send us like just send us like a voice memo addendum.
If you're leaving here, just, you know, call me, leave me a message.
Well, we'll just add it to the end.
Sounds good. Should make that an option for all.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Yeah. On the way home, if you just want to talk on your phone.
Yeah, I forgot.
Sometimes Tubbs would wear like a orange suit that looked cool.
All right. That's it. Bye.
Yeah. Hey, thanks so much for being here.
And let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Oh, gosh, I guess not.
I mean, I said MacGorley.com so you can find everything there.
Yeah, whatever social media.
I know that now.
Yeah. Any podcast I'm doing, I think Suprigo is coming back later this year.
And so all that's there.
Yeah. Thank you guys. Absolutely.
And show from your days at the way.
Which one? Wait, what did you all do to get soap with some of it with soap?
I think most of it. Yeah, we started in soap opera bistro
and then around that transition period, I think is when it happened.
I'm sure it's saying, can we play parts that are not doctors or?
Yeah, it was like we were doing such straightforward mainstream improv.
We wanted to start.
We get off stage and just start denying each other as a like venting thing.
And so we wanted to just break the rules of improv.
And that's how Suprigo was born, basically.
Geez. Wow. It's like math related to the theme park experience.
That's pretty crazy. Is there like an oral history of this yet?
I'm like imagining like the Tom Shales SNL book where you're like talking about
the soap opera bistro and like you guys are all there together and like
people have asked us to do like this group of people to do a podcast about it.
Like just the stories behind.
I remember some middle manager
took a picture of me with my shirt off in the dressing room and emailed it to me.
It was a weird place.
Yeah. He was a creepy Disney guy who'd come in every day
with a giant Cheshire cat smile on his face going,
are we all having a Disney day?
Yeah, he was gross.
That exists. That's like what you show in a movie about working.
We used to have this running joke.
We won't say I won't say his name here, but let's say his name was like
Leonard Baratso, and we'd always go Leonard Baratso for a county molester.
Vote Leonard Baratso for a county molester.
Leonard Baratso, I think, first of these robots who are eventually going to kill us.
Yeah, it was an early prototype.
Oh, he was. Yeah, yeah. That makes sense.
You know, gentlemen, what else we got?
Live show tickets still available for Anaheim.
August 24th, Anaheim, October 24th, Orlando.
Where are you doing the show at the Anaheim Hotel near D23?
You Disney conventions. Yeah. Yeah.
During that convention? Yes.
Yeah. Not affiliated.
You know, legally not affiliated.
And what's the subject?
I don't think we know.
We were just running ideas around yesterday, but we know.
Yeah, we don't. We're not ready to say yet.
I don't know. It's very.
Yeah. Yeah.
But if you're not if you're not all paneled out by the end of D23,
please, please come to a different ballroom, a different sweaty ballroom.
OK, that's good.
I said yes to them having a person there with their cash bar.
We don't get any money from it, but enjoy.
But if I get booze from it, then I'm all set.
And yes, it's good as money.
Yeah, sure. Sure.
And check us to check us out on the second gate on Patreon,
our Twitter, our Facebook.
He probably like all of that.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, the things.
Yeah. Thanks for thanks for listening, everybody.
It's been radical.
It has been radical.
Jason was on that jazz.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner,
Brett Bowen, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.