Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
They put up screens.
They put up a tiki bar with fun drinks.
They were so preoccupied with whether or not they could do an overlay of an old attraction,
they never stopped to think if they should.
Charles Rogers from Search Party joins us to question those who would play God.
It's Jurassic World on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast hosted by three guys who wish they were all Owen Grady's,
but in reality are all Lowry Crothers.
I'm Mike Carlson.
Joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Is Lowry Crothers BD Wong's character?
No, that's not right.
Also Scott Garner with me.
Lowry Crothers.
Oh, I know who it is.
Can I guess that Lowry Crothers hosts the auction in Fallen Kingdom?
No, incorrect.
We saw a toy of Lowry Crothers.
You know him as a co-creator of Search Party and from the podcast The Problem with Charles
and Casey.
Ladies and gentlemen, it's Charles Rogers.
Thank you for being here.
Can you answer the question?
To me, Lowry Crothers is Scatman Crothers.
And you're just talking about The Shining.
That's what I wish I was talking about.
Crothers is mental real estate for you.
I think I have it.
I think I know because you apologize for this joke.
Is that the lawyer who gets eaten on the toilet?
Not correct.
What?
It's got to be Jurassic World 3.
It's Jurassic World specific.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Lowry Crothers.
And not Fallen Kingdom.
No, no.
First one, Lowry Crothers.
It's who Judy Greer is divorcing.
No, that is all three of us though.
We are that type of gentleman.
Or her lawyer.
No, no, no, no.
Uh-huh.
Is it, do we see a toy of it?
Is there a toy of it?
Oh, is it Jake Johnson?
Yes, there it is.
Okay.
He has a last name.
Yeah, Lowry Crothers.
By the way, it took me four websites to find the full name.
Not even the IMDB had it.
Yes, it does.
That's correct.
It said Lowry.
And then I finally found it was Lowry Crothers.
In a fan fiction site probably.
It might have been fan fiction.
He was having sex with other famous characters.
So yeah, that is who it was.
I think, I don't know if it's spelled the same, but there's a character, Mrs. Crothers, who is a teacher played by Marshall Wallace on Full House, who is after Uncle Joey.
Uh-huh.
Like she's, you know, kind of like a tacky woman who really wants to-
Oh, I remember that.
Grab Joey's ass essentially.
Tacky, sounds like she's horny.
I just mean like style-wise, she's very gaudy.
I see, I see.
And so maybe Mrs. Crothers from Full House is related to, is an aunt or something to Lowry Crothers, eventual operations employee of Jurassic World.
I think that's a good possibility.
I think so.
Full House really disrespected Uncle Joey's life.
Like he never had a real like job or he was always like available to be like playing the piano while the kids danced or something.
He was just the character that, it doesn't matter, no one's talking about this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know what you're saying.
Well, he'll hold it down and it's a showbiz career, which look, are not steady.
Yeah, that's right.
You know, it's a good lesson.
He's struggling.
You know, it should have been a lesson to all of us, just in case, like, hey, know that you could have a life like Joey where you're-
It's a cautionary tale.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe you win Star Search one day, but are a, you know, a kids show puppet host the next or just a drive time DJ.
All these are great jobs as I described them.
Yeah, that's true.
Even if he only holds them briefly.
I do think putting him in the basement sort of made Joey like lesser than.
Completely. They silenced the lambs, Tim.
Yeah, they locked him away.
They locked him away.
Did he move up to the attic later on?
That's Jesse. No, no, no.
Oh, Jesse.
And Becky.
Oh, Joey is the, yeah, he's the com- Yeah.
Yeah, they sort of made, they sort of made the house bigger.
Imagine, like, looking at that strip of houses in San Francisco and being like that many people, like that world is inside that house.
Like, there's like multiple levels of like marriages in this one house.
Yes, three entire families, lots of children, many, many children live in there.
And a point I'm always making.
Multiple generations.
Yeah, yeah.
And now today, if you include Fuller House, even more.
And the point I'm always making is how all of San Francisco's major media figures all live in that home.
It's true.
The two hosts of the most popular morning show, this Joey, a titan of various medias, and the, and Jesse, the singer of the most major band in San Francisco, and a nightclub owner.
Like how, in what it'd be like, I don't know what's an equivalent.
Like, you know, finding out that Al Roker lived in the same house as who's a big New York stand up.
Bill, Bill Bird.
Yeah, it's basically a Bohemian Grove or something.
It's just a summit of powerful people.
Well, but on Fuller House, like the whole family is getting evicted by like some tech sociopath who really wants to tell you about fasting.
Really?
No, I don't know.
I would assume.
I also felt like bringing up Full House, we all apparently really wanted to talk about Full House.
I just was the other night.
I'm confident in that conversation from two days ago.
Oh, so you just did this.
I've just been in a Full House run.
Yeah, I try to be as much as possible.
But what were you saying?
I was just saying it felt like Full House was brought up when you all like, we're like, yeah, let's talk about Full House.
Yeah, I'm happy to talk about that instead.
We got a letter from the government saying, hey, you've had a podcast for a little while now.
We noticed you hadn't talked about Full House much with your age and Democrat.
You really you have to.
Sure.
Where our tax money goes.
Yes. Yeah, yeah.
We'd have to pay the penalty if we didn't talk about it.
I'm working on a think piece about why Kellyanne Conway is kind of like the Kimmy Gibbler of the Trump administration.
I think that's a good point.
Oh, mine is just called Stinky Feet.
Mine is called We're All Lori Laughlin.
Slash Lori Laughlin Innocent.
You're a Lori Truth or somebody.
Well, there'll be a Patreon episode of some kind, I guess about the Smash Club.
I think that's a place.
That was Jesse's club where the Ripper would play.
That's where his evil cousin Stavros stole the money, which is maybe my favorite episode of television.
That's a good call.
Evil cousins always a good thing.
And also a nightclub that is always children's entertainment.
It's always elementary school fundraisers.
Right.
Little Richard and then those three cowgirl singing ladies.
Remember the three cowgirl singing ladies vaguely?
Yes.
They were on like peewee specials.
Oh, right. Yeah.
That's if I forget their names.
I know I have looked up the names of the three girls singing ladies before.
Sure.
If anyone's yelling at their phone about this one.
Tell yourself.
Yeah, come on.
Useless info.
So, yeah, let's get out of the Full House talk.
Let's just get back into theme parks.
The topic of the show.
Yeah.
So, Charles, you contacted me a little while ago.
It seems like you're into this stuff.
We don't really we haven't talked too much, but let's like let's how how hard do you go in this theme park world?
You know, I have shame.
So the shame holds me back.
So we're here.
All aspects of life, but particularly here.
This is a place don't know shame here.
No shame.
Yeah, finally.
I'm finally free.
Open place.
Talk to me.
We are. Yeah, we roll in our own slop every episode.
That is what this is.
I think we're all filled with shame, but not about theme parks.
Yeah.
The only area we're confident in.
I mean, I love I love theme parks like I don't love all.
I don't like I wouldn't go to like Busch Gardens or something and like but I love like Disney and Universal.
Those are like I've always loved.
Right. So you like more the higher more highly themed experience maybe versus just roller coasters.
Yeah, I think so.
I think so.
And I like how Disney is.
I mean, I like the window into the past.
The Disney is like I think the best thing about it is like pirates or like haunted mansion.
Just being like, so this is what people wanted is entertainment in like the 50s and 60s.
And I get to still live through that like point of view.
It's so weird that that like nothing else is still intact like that in America where you can like enter a point of view about fantasy besides like watching movies or hearing music or something.
But like, yeah, it's still intact, which is cool.
But the past is racist, too.
So it's not it's not a purely good like nostalgia to have.
Things have happened in pirates.
But they've had is there's nothing racist going on.
Haunted Mansion is there.
I think there's I think they're fine.
Yes, unless it's true.
Ghost racism.
Yeah.
The lack of diversity, I guess.
It's all white.
They're all translucent.
Yeah.
So it's like a nice you have you ever been to Knott's?
Because that's scary.
It's not scary.
Oh, nice.
Because like Knott's is older stuff even.
Yeah.
It is interesting to be like, yeah, everyone like this is basically the same as it was certain parts of it, the same as it was 50 years ago or 100.
Not this case, 7500 years ago.
Take your way.
It's hard for me to to like going to I just went to Universal on Sunday to a week ago to do the Jurassic World.
Right. And it's like hard for me to like accept changes in theme parks.
Like I don't care about like any new IP like Fast and Furious.
I'm like, this is bad for the world.
Like Transformers is bad for the world.
Like so many things that I'm like, this is not like the right side of history culturally.
And I don't want that.
I don't know.
I have a hard time with like what's like the newest ride that you like.
I really liked I mean, I guess Jurassic World was a revamp, but I really I did really like it.
Yeah.
I liked it.
I like. Yeah, I like a lot, too.
I thought they did a lot of great stuff with it.
Yeah.
We'll get into.
I find I've said before how right like even if I don't like the franchise that a ride comes from so much, it's still like it can transcend property that I don't particularly love.
Fast and Furious, I don't think does.
It's bizarre.
Yeah.
Ride is bizarre.
Like there's that party.
Yes.
It starts with like a like a spring break party and then like the FBI is like, get out.
And then they like talk to you and they're like, you just witnessed something.
You're a witness.
And then you drive really fast and you're like, I have no idea what just happened.
Better synopsis than I could have done.
I have no idea.
I've done it twice and I'm trying to figure out what happens.
It's really over scripted.
I haven't done the version in Florida, but they adapted it for a standalone ride in Florida.
But I think it's the same.
It's just the same.
Does it make more sense?
I don't think so.
I'm not sure.
More elaborate.
Yeah, I'm not really sure.
I don't know why they weren't just like, oh yeah, this garage is usually just storage
for the part.
There's a party going on.
Like they set up throughout the tour that like we've got a secret agent on the ride.
There's a lot of like, you're just being talked to in a pre video that you're in.
You're just like, I can't, I'm trying to listen, but I just can't.
Like everything is just washing over me.
I can't hear you.
There's a lot of modern rides that have a little too much plot.
That's probably the worst example of one.
Yeah.
Like of like, just like I'm zoning out.
I don't know.
The Avatar ride in Florida, which is fantastic.
I haven't done that.
It's fantastic.
That being said, we're going to do it in October.
The plot.
Ooh.
Try to follow it.
Like explaining like we're going into a lab now.
We're going to take your like heat signature and what's going to happen now is you're going
to be scanned.
When you're going to be scanned, then you're going to put your body into an Avatar.
You're going to ride on the back of it.
And it's like just that's like a 10th of what it is.
And you're just like, I don't know what I'm so am I riding in the back of a monster?
Great.
That's all you need to know.
Back of a monster.
Great.
And I'm having fun.
Fantastic.
But like it's yeah, there's a need.
I think people want to like really like give them the experience.
Like most people are zoning out.
Right.
They're tired.
It's hot.
They're drunk.
Who knows?
Yeah.
I like Harry Potter.
I think the Harry Potter ride is great too.
Yeah.
It's really simple.
Open house day at the school.
Come in.
See everything.
Yeah.
Get changed.
And there's like when I just redid it and like Dumbledore tells you you're brave at the
end and you're like, I am brave.
And then I did the what's the other right.
The Transformers, which I have no like feelings about that franchise.
Yeah.
And at the end they're like, you're bravery.
And I'm like, fuck you.
Like I wasn't brave.
Like you don't know me.
It's like a totally different.
I didn't earn this compliment.
Talk about this.
Mike loves this.
I love.
Yes.
I love when a character.
Doesn't matter if I like the character or not.
It tells me I did a good job.
Yeah.
It just feels good.
It feels good.
Because Optimus Prime, which you're talking about on that Transformers ride.
And I as a kid, I was Ninja Turtles Ghostbuster kid.
Didn't care about Transformers.
But when he leans over and he goes, thank you for your bravery or whatever he says, I'm
like, it touches you.
It does.
It's like a nice.
I hear him telling me like who to vote for.
And I'm like, no, no.
Control this narrative.
I have agency in this story.
I can do shit.
I just said R.
90% of your budget came from the Defense Department.
This makes me feel weird.
I mean, Michael Bay is my father is like really what he said.
Like I am.
I have a certain set of values.
That is the right to me.
But I overlook that when he just says, I just feel good, you know, whatever makes me feel
good, whatever makes me feel good.
Yeah.
But yeah, they got to pair these plots down.
It's got to be a little more.
You need a thing or no story.
Sort of there.
Yeah, it is to be like, you know, your big thunder mountain railroad is just like, it's
a wild ride.
Here you go.
It doesn't matter.
We don't need like justifications to be on rides.
It's like, yeah, the ride is the ride.
Like we don't need at some point the ride to change into another type of ride.
Yeah.
Jurassic world.
Pretty simple.
What they did with this ride, honestly, for me, squared the circle of the logic of the
Jurassic Park for it because that one you get knocked off course by a dinosaur and the
parks out.
This one you're just, oh no, the super smart killer dinosaur broke out.
You were on your path.
And then all of the warnings and everything are done in theme park style.
Like the Owen, Owen, hold on.
I wrote this, these names down and I think Scott, I saw you too.
Of course I got him.
Owen Grady and Claire Dearing, the characters we all know and love.
I said Owen at the top of the show.
But the full names, I can never remember the full one.
You did.
Yeah.
Okay.
Because who would ever miss an opportunity to say Owen Grady?
I say it all the time.
Just the thing I say.
So it's just like boy name, girl name, those two names.
Pretty much.
I don't like that.
Now, why is that?
Why do we think like, what's an example of a better, like why do we remember Dr. Grant
or whatever?
What's Dr. Grant's first name?
Alan.
Thank you.
Why does Alan Grant feel better than Owen Grady?
I trust the point of view of the people behind it more.
Like it's just like Jurassic Park deserves such a better franchise than it's gotten like
from the first movie on.
And that's always like, I'm really flawed history past the number one.
Yeah.
Well, I kind of like the sequel.
Like, I kind of like the lost world.
I think that there's still like Spielberg in it and you can feel like you can feel like
the Spielberg glowing unconscious brain, like channeling in it.
But then like the third one is just like a comic book.
Like it's so paper thin.
And then the new ones are like so gendery and like, like he's, he's macho and she's
like an uptight high heel.
It's just like, what is the, like, yeah, she's a scientist who runs in heels.
Yeah.
Doesn't want to get, yeah.
She's like a bad aunt is the lesson she has to learn.
It's like, who cares if you're a bad aunt?
Like you like, that's not a real thing.
Like no one has ever like Aunt Claire isn't paying attention to it.
That's not an issue to overcome.
Expectations are pretty low.
It's like, yeah, she's like a very successful person running a theme park.
And she got you in for free.
Like in this, in, in falling kingdom, they very, those kids are gone.
Boys are gone.
There is a kid which gets very complicated in it, but I did, I liked falling kingdom
just cause it pretty quickly became a haunted house movie.
And I think it was just a better director.
It's just the first thing, new thing that franchise has done too.
It's like, oh, now it's going to be in a house and there's an auction.
And I was like, okay, cool.
Like it's inventive again.
And I think Jurassic, the Jurassic franchises share like DNA with like men in black where
it's like, I like the world.
I like the reoccurring aesthetics.
Yeah.
Frank the pug, the dinosaurs, the neuro, the neuralyser, like I like all that stuff, but
sometimes the execution doesn't always nail it.
You can just really feel the studio first feeling and like the new ones where it's just
like a board of people making decisions and then sending people off to write.
And there's none of that like coming from an artist first version that the original
was.
Yeah.
I think stuff in there, like I think like the updated color schemes, which you see in
the ride, the blue and kind of silver and stuff that makes sense.
Yeah.
The ride makes a touches on a little of like the one, one of the things I did like for
Jurassic world of just like the idea of the park is open.
Yeah.
Like the part, the people come to the park and they have to worry about attendance and
new attractions.
Yeah.
Right.
Like an attraction at a theme park that starts to break down.
They do a pretty good job of like, of not dismissing the originals too.
Like they, they'll like keep little like novelty things in the movies.
And like, I liked how they had like the old Raptor and then like the new Raptor, like
in some of the old animatronics in the ride, they were like slightly cleaned up, but like
still are kind of janky.
It's nice.
It's nice to like not eclipse the past completely.
It makes me like believe it's not all money.
Yeah.
Well, universal is like a little less.
We've said this many times, I think like universal less precious with their classics ride wise.
Like they will burn a ride down.
They'll burn ET down.
I know.
Like ET is like a magical iconic.
I mean, that's the only one where I'm really like just leave ET.
Why?
Is anybody that fond of revenge of the mummy?
Yeah, right.
It's like you didn't replace it with a really unpleasant.
Well, and it's like, I totally agree.
It's really caustic.
It's like not the full experience.
Right.
Yeah.
The Florida one is great.
And then this is so like blacklight in a like fun house way.
That's like, well, this doesn't really remind me of the movie at all.
And it's like short.
It's like a minute short.
It's like a short version.
Like you're like, you go all in there.
I think I've said this before.
It like shoves my extremities inside them.
Like the seats are unpleasant.
Like I go inside of myself.
I'm not trying to be too graphic here, but it's horrible.
I'm a tall man and I'm saying in the seats, I have to like adjust so much.
Yeah.
And then I'm like freaked out because I'm already in there and that's yelling at me.
A mummy's yelling at me.
Yeah.
And it's very, that are really close, but not in like, oh, I feel the heat.
It's like, I don't know.
That hurts.
I'm trying to get outside already.
I can't even.
I can't even adjust my pants as like those skeletons come down.
I'm like, I'm not ready.
And that's good to get another minute.
I will say if we're rebooting everything, bring back Brendan Fraser mummy.
I agree.
It's so good.
I just rewatched the original mummy and I think it's great.
Yeah.
First one's great.
Second one has its moments.
I don't remember.
CGI doesn't hold up a lot of stuff.
And that doesn't hold up as well, but the first one's really fun.
Yeah, I love any movie where like they just like, like everyone in the original mummy
is just like, you know, the lost city of Hamunatra.
And it's like, why do you, why is that something everyone knows about?
Like, yeah, we all know in this world.
Do you know how to get there?
That was my favorite search party episode too, where they go to the lost city.
Everyone knows what you're talking about.
Everyone in Brooklyn knows.
Turns out universal doesn't own Turner.
Who can keep track now?
Yeah, who owns what?
In a couple of years though, it'll all work itself out.
We all work for the company.
It's Coke.
We're all laughing, ha ha ha, cut to 20 years and that's a reality.
Yeah, that's true.
They should just lengthen.
Let's just lengthen the mummy, right?
Just give it the rest of it.
Yeah.
You know, don't take it because I think they would need to build a second sound.
I think they fit into whatever sound stage.
Build a bigger one.
Well, they make it like you go to the end of the track and then you switch on to another
track and go in reverse and they try and convince you that you're still on the same track going
in reverse, right?
Because by the time you go back to the beginning, it's not like you're literally on the same
track the whole time.
I think that you go to the end of the ride.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We're just trying to figure out what you're saying.
We are fascinated by tracks.
I was thinking about this.
I'm like, you go to the end of the track and then you stop and then you actually like switch
on to another track and go in reverse.
Right, right.
They convince you that it's the same track because it's all the same black light.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You're trying to make you feel like you're going backwards because you're seeing the
same signage.
But of course it's a different.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Which I feel is like a waste of space.
Like I would have rather done just going.
Yeah.
If they had twice as much track to play room to play with.
I see what you're saying.
You could have been a longer thing.
Yeah, that truly went just backwards.
The whole I'm sure it's a capacity only.
It's probably a capacity thing because they probably can write run to it once.
And this way they'd have to only you can only do one.
Yeah. But I see what you're saying.
Because it would be double different place.
That right. Like how do you have to end up in a different ending location?
Right. You need a different track to write.
You guys work for that.
You guys work for the money.
I wasn't trying to argue.
We're we're two kinds of people.
They would burn money for a few years of like when you got off,
there's all these mummies and one of them would be a person who would jump out at you.
Oh, well, like that's an actor you have to pay and rotate in and out in the exit.
There's like the mummies on pedestals and there's one or two empty pedestals
where like scare actors would be there.
That's fun.
Yeah, that's a real like final frontier of rides that isn't like like the human
participation on rides.
I feel like they've tried it at various times.
They was on Haunted Mansion, apparently.
Yeah. Oh, people would scare you.
Yeah. There would be like a person that would just like like in the suit of armor
or somebody else who would just like lunge in front of the cars.
And apparently I think somebody got punched.
And I think that's when they stopped.
I think a lot of people gotten punched that were scare actors.
That's probably a tradition among them.
A rite of passage, probably like some dad.
It's like, oh, I was working with somebody who told me a story
of being in like a Iowa corn maze or something where a guy jumped out
and then he really clocked him like to the hospital.
Oh, yeah. And then he's like immediately.
I didn't mean to. I don't.
It was just an impulse.
I'm not like trying to hurt anybody.
He was severely traumatized.
Every year at Halloween season, there's a new story.
This happened like so much.
I've been especially the smaller haunts where like people are just doing it
skin to their teeth, like just figuring it out.
They don't have the rules and regulations that Disney and Universal do.
I did a haunted house when I was like 15 and all of the performers took my pants off.
They pinned me to the ground.
What took my pants off?
What? I swear.
OK, I know.
I always tell this story and people are like, are you OK?
And I'm like, I think I'm fine.
I've been working through it.
I got back on and ran out.
That was the end of that.
Hmm. Was that a thing they probably did a lot?
I think that they were just like all other like 18 year olds
and like just were like trying new things every night.
Sure. Like they just got bored.
Where was it?
In Brownsville, Texas, on the border.
That is a common prank.
It's a high school prank. Right.
Removing pants, pants or pantsing, whatever you'd call it.
Sure. I'm scared already to be in a haunted house.
And that happens. Yeah.
Have you got let me ask a question.
Have you been pantsed or deep pantsed ever in high school?
No, no, no.
No, I don't. Yes.
Oh, no. What happened?
Gym class.
I believe Tony Young sang his name.
I think Tony Young, who I liked,
ran up to me and pulled my pants down, my gym shorts down.
And I believe it was he pulled everything as well.
I remember I'm just on the track.
It was gym class.
So for whatever reason, the stakes felt less.
Yeah, it wasn't like in the hallway or anything.
But I was like pantsless for two seconds.
I couldn't pull them up.
My hands are floppy.
They won't pull the pants back up.
So yeah, it happened.
Closeted high school.
That would have been like my Christmas day.
Getting to see another point deep pants.
That would have been like forever remembering that.
Mine was it was not.
I'm sure I just like looking like struggled.
And it was very unpleasant.
Yeah, nothing good about it.
You from Texas? Yeah.
What was the where the theme parks growing up?
Well, six flags over Texas.
Exactly. I went to that a lot.
And my mom went to that as a kid.
And that was the first six flags.
And first of all, the first of all, because like,
I mean, you guys probably know this, but like six flags is because there were six
flags of Texas, like they're different.
OK, like ruling one of the ruling empires of ruling and conquered
different kingdoms.
Confederate.
Probably. I think.
Yeah, it is.
Yes.
And and so like she went to it before it was like this national six flags chain.
It was just like six flags over Texas.
And then Fiesta, Texas is the other one I went to a lot.
And Schlitterbahn. You guys know what Schlitterbahn?
Yes. Yeah.
Schlitterbahn was a great in my memory.
You buy that like you're by the Bomega one, like the really great.
I mean, I traveled for it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
But then they open one up in where I grew up at South Padre Island,
which was like a beach destination.
And there was like the beachy one.
Yeah, it was jankier than it wasn't the magical like
the fully the you think you're actually in Austria or whatever.
Yeah. And it wasn't the criminal one in the Midwest.
Yeah. Someday I'll make it to the homeland.
So so yeah, it was like a kid like so you were going to these places,
but it was like, were you roller coaster?
Were you more like as a kid?
I was a Tilt-A-Whirl kid, but not a roller coaster kid.
Oh, that's rough. Tilt-A-Whirl is intense now.
I can't do spinning now.
Spinning and dropping are like, I can't do it.
But I was I think I was a roller coaster kid because I felt like I had
like in the same way that like my friends like I was like a part of like
a group of like boy, like skater boys from like through junior high
until like freshman year of high school.
It was a college until my mid 30s.
And and then like I started to be like, actually, this isn't my vibe.
And like, I kind of want to be friends with everybody and like the other
closeted kids who just were like kind of drawn to each other.
But like I so I felt like they all like slipknot and shit.
And I like and so I was just like, yeah, me too.
You know, and I didn't even know what I was saying.
So in the same way, we're like, yeah, we're going to ride roller coasters.
Like, I think I convinced myself that I love that.
But in my heart, I'm like, I mean, honestly, like I'm I'm like
like, what the fuck?
The people of tomorrow, what's the like the it's a great big.
So progress.
So progress. That's that's what I love.
Like, I love psychosis.
Like, I love the like the crazy like propaganda aspect of like Disneyland
that feels like Cold War and like in it.
So it's like, why is it still here?
And then in order to get all this stuff built, they have to include corporate
messaging, which can be sort of odd and nefarious.
And yeah, totally.
And like invisible to a lot of people who mostly are like,
that's a nice song and everything.
Yeah. Yeah.
Weird G.
Yeah, but by Pepsident and like. Right.
But then in an odd bit of postmodernism, a lot of those rides still around
with no sponsors or different sponsors. Right.
But like the heart of the way. Yeah, I know.
Or Epcot. I loved Epcot.
Like, I just loved anything that was like, this has a vision to it.
And I don't know why we're doing it, but like it's here.
And so it's just take advantage of it.
Really specific. Yeah.
No other theme park is nothing like, you know, we should do is gigantic
like steel pavilions about like the very general themes.
Right. And then the nations of the world.
We'll give it the worst title for a theme park ever
that no one even knows what it means.
Like no one can remember the environmental protection agency or whatever it is.
You can't.
Protection.
Yeah, it would.
I was going to say, though, because it's so it became it comes
around to being the best, though, in my mind, Epcot becomes the best title
because of. Yeah, right. Right.
Because it's just so specific.
It's funny, like because all that stuff in Epcot and everything, it's like
you're talking about like a comedian as a voice and like a show or what?
A Quentin Tarantino is a voice or whatever.
But it's like Epcot does have a voice.
There's a voice of classic Epcot that like that is what I feel like.
If you like it, that's what you're responding to.
You're like, I know this is so odd and specific and why the 80s?
Like, yeah, and all like this bizarre educational thing.
Edutainment, Edutainment.
Yeah, which is strange.
In a conflict that has hit all times.
Yeah, I mean, struggling with like that message being like, well, we decided
it's that's what it is. Yeah.
It'll be gone in five.
Like that vibe, I think for the most part will be any education contained.
And spaceship. Yeah, that's what I mean.
Spatial birth will still be that I think will still be.
That'll be probably the last.
Yeah. Vestige of old Epcot.
And everything else is going to be like some corporate sponsored,
like new computer thing.
This is where the living sees as Dr.
Strange's laboratory, Dr.
Strange's fish tank.
You're looking at his personal fish collection.
Yeah. Well, the Guardians' Coaster,
there's a building at Guardians of the Galaxy Coaster,
but it's supposed to be a nod to classic Epcot and at least in the line.
So you'll get a little of it.
But that to me is a sign.
It's like they are acknowledging lately that there is a voice like they're like,
not getting in touch with its roots again.
That is like they are.
And like putting little like Easter egg, like, like,
oh, you can kind of see those those ride emblems, like what our logo is based on.
Like they're incorporating those again, a little more.
That's true. And the color scheme.
Well, they're acknowledging it in ways that don't cost them a lot of money.
They're not building new rides to it, but they'll do a nighttime show about it.
They'll put it in cues.
They'll sell merchandise theme to it.
Yeah, we're suckers who will buy that stuff and we will buy it.
Yeah, yeah. Yes, absolutely.
So, yeah, there's there's yeah, it won't be gone completely.
I shouldn't say that, but it'll be it'll be a little hidden areas.
Well, how do you I mean, do you guys feel maybe you're not allowed to talk about this
because you're you're being treated so well by these companies?
Oh, no, but it's not doing great.
But like I just like I went to Disneyland, like maybe it was like a month ago.
Or like the Star Wars right had just opened in this land.
But I was like there's no way I was going to get in.
I didn't do any of the preparation for it.
I was like, I'm actually just going to Disneyland.
And but I just I feel like that should be in California.
Like it doesn't it feels sacrilegious to like all in California venture.
Yeah, I see.
It just feels like like I guess we just come to accept Disney as an ever changing
concept. But like, yeah, it's like, why are you like,
like just piecing in this like very new like financial feeling?
It just feels like a property that's like stuck on.
And it's like, oh, I feel like it should have just been like California
adventure should be like where you can just like throw whatever into and like
less precious and they can just which I think is what it is.
Like with with everything else, like all the Pixar stuff goes there.
Marvel goes there and it doesn't have to be as congruous.
Yeah, you're just saying.
And maybe in another world where they had more room over there.
That's what they would do.
Yeah, I mean, I could see maybe my justification would be, well,
if this is where the great tales live,
fairy tales, a bigger, it's a bigger property. Yeah.
It like like it's, you know, really one of the greats like, you know,
like modern stories.
So it does belong there or like that there already is Star Tours in Indiana
Jones. Yeah, that's true.
If we're talking about Lucas is the new Walt Disney.
Yeah, sure. Maybe.
And that of course, and that JJ and Rian Johnson are the new Walt Disney.
And a bunch of all those Trevor.
Trevor almost made it.
I don't know.
I have mixed feelings about him.
Walt Disney 3.0.
Colin Trevorrow.
Yeah, so serious.
I mean, we'll probably all meet him one day, but like he like.
We just look so serious from a distance.
We all we were hoping to ride the ride with him because we went to the press
event, but we thought him.
I should. I guess we should.
The three of us went to the opening event for it.
Yes. Yes.
Yes, we said we we were not originally invited.
We said I complain and I complained on this show, right?
I think. Yes.
Is that why you guys got?
No, I don't believe so.
No, I don't think anyone wants to hear us talk about anything.
A politely worded email.
I would be very impressed if any anyone's PR department is like
listening to us every week.
But maybe the main question of Edwin the dog.
Yeah, we're talking about Edwin.
What do they think? Do they like the plus ups or not?
Jason's hot dog eating like. Sure.
That's really what they're listening for.
Do they think the price point at Island New Bar is acceptable?
Very hard fish. Very hard.
Mahi Mahi.
There was a little hard as a rusty frost.
That guys didn't get sick, but not tender.
I like the pork. I had the pork pork.
The pork was good. Yeah, they were very happy.
Everybody there was like had the like new opening happiness to it.
Yeah. Although the Jurassic Park people felt happy to be.
The whole Jurassic World area, like redo area looks great.
Yeah. Yeah.
Elan New Bar is great.
We yeah, we we can't we didn't get a good like
regular person view of it because it was a it was a open bar.
We got to dinner.
So it was very nice.
By the skin of our teeth.
Oh, really? We're moving a little.
We took our time.
You did it at night, right? Yeah.
What was that like? That was probably fun.
It looks great at night.
I have to say the ride.
I've never been on the previous ride at night.
So yeah, yeah.
No iteration had I is pretty cool.
I got soaked. You guys get I was like I did it three times.
And what rose what rose the first and the last first last first.
That's why.
Oh, first I think you get soaked a little bit.
But the Moses like right off the bat, the like Moses oris just like soaks you.
It's like, all right.
Yes. Yes.
This is the first second I've been on this ride.
Yeah. Universal does not hold mind.
Yeah. The only thing that Disney does that's crazy is that second to last
splash mountain drop in the dark.
Yeah. In the dark.
That one, because the big one doesn't get you that crazy wet.
But that second to last one just literally slowly dumps 10 gallons into the log.
Yeah. And water in the dark is different than water in the light.
It feels different.
I mean, I want to argue with that.
Yeah. Like more nefarious.
You're in a flood or something.
But it's in what insects you're circling around the toilet.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
The splash mountain one, though, feels like because everything else is just like
a giant splash and oh, no, I'm really soaked.
And that one just feels like you're there's you're immediately wet.
You're immediately just like you fell into a bathtub.
That's totally different.
It comes over the side.
Yeah. It's your pants and universal.
Yeah. Universal in general, just more aggressive with their water.
Yeah. And I will give them credit.
I mean, we'll go we'll go back real quick to the press event, but that that first
effect that the Mosasaur like shoot, that is cool.
I will say I didn't see it coming like that.
Yeah, I didn't see it coming. Very impressive.
They kept like pushing the crack being a spray on the inside.
I was like, that's the thing.
And then I liked that. Yeah.
But you see it's like three elements and you see the Mosasaur pop up.
There's a music sting.
There is like the big the song, the Giacchino.
Jurassic World song.
And then you get hit by the water like simultaneously.
And I watched a bunch of ride throughs and it happens every time.
It's great. Yeah, I loved it.
And I love seeing those like big doors.
Like I didn't mind that it wasn't the Jurassic Park doors, that it was just
the like Jurassic World doors that have.
Sure.
Yes.
So great.
Or significant.
You're not.
Every level.
Yeah, emotions aren't.
And just like the wind dinosaurs ruled like everything about the very beginning.
I was like, oh, like I'm I'm I'm transcending.
I love this.
I think this is this is nice.
It's neat.
It looks good.
It's enclosed a little more so you see less of parking garages and hotels.
And that must have been some of the strategy that so that like that the grand reveal and
some people a lot of people don't like this redo.
And there's some of their point is like we used to get this big vista and the
Brontosaurus is there.
So I but you're right.
You also get parking garages and stuff that doesn't belong.
Well, and those dinosaur animatronics, the tall ones, the Ultra Sword age, they are
hit by sun and occasional rain and the elements.
They aged a lot over the years.
So tough for maybe some of the toughest theme park to keep up.
It was like welcome to Jurassic Park.
All of our dinosaurs are sick.
They're all dying.
The lysine issue that they have.
Welcome to.
But in terms of screen and screen, then you get hit by water.
This the Mosasaur aquarium is is great.
Yeah, so great.
The crack at the end is legitimately unnerving to me.
It's a real like you got to figure that out.
Jurassic World, if your Moses horse is cracking your tanks.
Yeah, that fast.
This is an indominus created situation.
It's just poor parking.
And then the problem becomes the indominus.
But wait a minute.
It's like there are problems.
We get a lot going on.
That's happening today.
Yeah, Carly Weisel in her write up, a past guest of the show,
said like this ride is is much more meta now of like the theme park
within a theme park element of it and like the ride breaking.
Stuff is going wrong.
Right.
This theme park.
Yeah, that's true.
Down to like the mural, the murals in Eastland or whatever the restaurants.
Is it the restaurant?
Is the Jurassic Cafe?
I think it's the restaurant.
The murals are like the T-Rex fighting the indominus.
And it's like, so your murals are like of the worst day your park has ever had.
Like you're just like immortalizing this 9-11 of theme parks.
Everyone died is forever on our cafe wall.
OK, the logic on that's a little not.
Not as bad.
No one.
Yeah, but it is worth the store eight, the indomitant.
Then how much money did it cost to make the indomitant?
So that's that's so much down like stocks.
Yeah, that's a disaster.
In the original narrative of the ride area, I would assume it's like the park is good.
It works like they're not trying to remind you of any disaster until you're on the ride,
which in the narrative is like you're experiencing for the first time the park going crazy.
Whereas like Jurassic World, it's like the park goes crazy all the time.
Yeah, you know what the drill is.
Like, yeah, they're going to chomp at you.
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah.
Are we where are we in the timeline in dress?
It's sort of the experience of Jurassic World, I think.
Yeah.
The endominus is it like you're saying is it what we're experiencing to the events of the film?
In the first film, they are about to open up the endominus.
OK, I believe sponsored by Verizon, which is a funny theme park gag.
Sure.
But I'm saying is the ride the ride is taking place at that time?
I think, yeah, because I mean the same day that that happens.
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
I mean, the park is open for a while in the movie for at least a few years.
Right.
Claire and Owen are there.
They've had a thing.
Right.
A brief thing.
They've had their thing.
Right.
Yeah.
Where are we in the timeline of their thing?
It's sort of in an alternate timeline universe to the to the Jurassic World.
Like it's kind of like somewhere in the movies.
Yeah.
BD Wong is in the Q video.
Which I didn't see.
We got on the ride at the press event and we were given ponchos so we didn't get super wet.
And then we went to like use the bathroom and then get more drinks and I made a dessert plate.
And then we went to try to get back on the ride and they had already shut it down for the night.
So we got on by the skin of our teeth.
And then we were just hanging out in matching ponchos.
Just hanging out in ponchos.
They made us take a picture.
Right.
Because we look embarrassing.
You guys are just having drinks in ponchos.
Right.
There wasn't like what are you doing?
Why are you wearing that?
And we're like we just got off the ride.
We just got off.
I felt a little sick.
This is what you do.
Yeah.
We saw Colton Dunn, Superstars Colton Dunn who we know from UCB.
He was there.
And then we met some of the dinosaurs.
Oh yeah.
Blue was walking around.
Julie had the Triceratops.
Did you meet the blue or triceratops?
No.
There's a Triceratops?
Yeah.
I didn't know that.
Very impressive.
The walks around.
I've seen blue like I went to Universal like a year ago and I feel like there was already
maybe it wasn't blue but I saw Willow Smith watching blue last time I was there.
Whoa.
That's great.
Wow.
That's really good.
Was there like a promotional?
Jaden.
I saw Jaden.
Jaden Smith.
Oh.
And now we all lose.
We're all like oh.
No.
Only Jaden.
All right.
She's got the better song that I like.
That's yeah.
Yeah.
That's the only reason.
That's where I land.
I'm not against Jaden.
Yeah.
And yet look at the feel the energy drop.
It sucked.
Yeah.
We sucked.
Goodnight everybody.
Oh man.
Let's think about Willow some more.
Jaden has the cartoon.
The Netflix.
Yes.
Jaden has a cartoon.
He's a character.
He's got the water company.
The water company.
Right.
Oh right.
The water company.
Box water?
Is that him?
I didn't know he had a cartoon.
I don't know if it's box water.
It might be box water.
It might be something else.
There's a Jaden Smith cartoon.
It's him and Vampire Weekend.
What?
Keening.
Is that right?
Keening and Jaden Smith are like.
What are you talking about?
Oh I know what you're talking about.
It's like set in the future right?
Yeah.
It's actually good right?
It's supposed to be good.
Yeah.
Neo-Yokio.
I just went from being against it to liking it.
Oh yeah.
Huh.
All right.
Let me find this water company.
I'm so sorry.
I just need to do this.
No.
Yeah somebody was.
Is there something like hoaxy about it that's funny?
Just water is the company.
Oh okay.
Not box water.
Not box.
That's right.
You get sprayed exclusively by just water on this ride.
Drink it up.
Sponsorship.
Yeah.
When that mosa sort of splashes you.
I love the idea of a water ride that you're supposed to like drink as much of as you go through.
Go.
Hurry.
Get electrolytes.
Wow it's flavored water too so.
All right.
Look at this.
I like honestly.
I like the look of this.
Uh huh.
Yeah I've seen that.
That's very pleasing.
I've seen that water.
Go to just water.com.
Know what Mike's excited about.
You won't be disappointed.
No.
But yeah.
Wait wait dinosaurs.
You saw blue.
I saw like I thought I saw blue.
I think it's.
Blue's been walking around.
They've had the blue puppet for a while.
I don't have a huge allegiance to blue.
Okay.
But I liked the animatronic a lot in the in the like when you go up to the like the last part.
I thought that was I don't know if you want to not skip to the end or what.
We can jump around.
I'm sorry if and around.
The running animal.
There's a running raptor in it.
That is blue right.
Yeah I think it's supposed to be blue.
Yeah.
It's kind of far from a distance.
I mean that was one of the big the mosasaur and the new entry and then the within the building
the t-rex habitat that all just used to be pipes and barrels and now it's filled with vegetation
and moving animatronics.
I love it.
It's great.
It was a good that I didn't know anything about so it was like such a big good surprise to like
go up in there and be like oh like this should have been like it would the original was so 90.
It was that like I remember there was like a video a sega version of Jurassic Park where like
so much happened in like a pipes world and like there was that side of the 90s that was always
trying to like put us in pipes world all the time and it's like it's just like that no one
really wanted ever be in pipes world.
That was the game where you could play as a raptor killing humans or you could play as
Alan Grant with a gun.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Walking around.
And dying was always like ah, like fall.
Do you know that in pipes worlds that there was a big I watched I did a ride through of
the original ride and there's a pipe that says steam supply.
Does what?
The point of it was to corral their steam.
Why do you need steam?
The most generic like like anyone who has never thought of pipes just makes steam supply.
Yeah.
That's the first yeah.
Why do they why are all these pipes around?
What are they Gary?
That's also one of those things though depending on the intention I either love it or I'm very
confused by like.
If it's like meta joke.
Right.
I love it.
Steam supply is great but if it was just like I don't know pipe and steam supply you're like
what is it?
Yeah, it's a genius joke.
Drip storage.
It's where we keep all our drips.
That's good too though.
That's a funny.
Yeah.
If that was the intention.
There's some hydroelectric engineer listening to this going like you need steam you fools.
You fools that was authentic.
That's the one authentic.
So we supply.
Yeah.
If Jurassic Park had a full enough steam supply they wouldn't have any problems.
Beat it to those dinos.
I do as like I don't really have like Jurassic World is like all it kind of does is like
make me think of what I'd rather see like whenever like what I'd rather the movies be you
know like but I agree I liked Fallen Kingdom more but like there just isn't like enough
soul to Jurassic World but.
It's not this so the story of being a good aunt doesn't pull you in.
Yeah.
Well none of the moments are like really lived in in the way that I want like in Jurassic
Park like when they see the dinosaurs for the first time you're so with them and they're
like emotional head space and it's like so you want to cry.
It's so powerful.
Well I think they tried to do that because remember they like and there was a lot of
like stuff firing in my brain when they get on a monorail to go to Jurassic World and I'm like
yes I like this and then the reveal right but it's so like CGI.
It's to CGI and it's to all at once like you know you it's not through like all CGI shit now is so
like I let's just see everything now and it's like but I want to see it through the character
and those kids don't care like the kid the larger kid is like yeah bored it's like well that's I'm
going to be bored like if your characters are bored I'll be bored like that's also a weird thing in
the movie where it's like the one kid who's bored and it's like well there aren't dinosaur theme
parks in every state.
I know I know it's not like $15,000 to go.
Yeah this is a high end thing where I think somebody would be at least like not on their
phone when a giant water dinosaur eats another thing like yeah it's yeah it's like I don't know
if the lot that was my thing with the movie was like just the logic of how everyone's acting
makes sense like no yeah it's kind of like skipping ahead to a future that doesn't exist
either in like I like that I like the idea of the gyrosphere but it's like that but that doesn't
exist like you can't convince me that that exists.
Like it's a gyrosphere and it's like no but what is that like unless we get the rumor of like
an eventual gyrosphere ride yeah maybe maybe like that's a good thing.
Imitate art.
That has been there's a big announcement big announcement coming this week.
Oh yeah that's right.
Universal doing a press release at the Orlando Convention Center.
It'll probably but this will probably be out by the time that happens.
There's a big announcement Universal Orlando coming.
Oh really?
So we'll see if it's involved.
What do you think it's going to be?
Their new theme park.
Oh we'll see if we're right or wrong.
The fourth people will know.
And like theme park inside Islands of Adventure or?
No inside.
Full another one.
The next one after Islands of Adventure.
It's called Fantastic.
Third one.
Their water park.
I hate calling Volcano Bay the third park.
I hate it.
It is not the third park.
Scott Hollis we ask that's the only thing we've asked you to ever play ball on.
What if I do this?
What I get at this is I like I just have an emotional breakdown.
Don't put me in a box.
I really I basically like honestly and I feel like you guys do buy into the brand.
You were like every time call it the fourth.
Well it's because they.
Fuck that child.
All right.
He didn't know.
Charles didn't know what we were talking about.
I was lost as hell.
A whole new gate.
A whole new gate at Universal Florida.
That's the that's the big thing.
What do you think it's going to be?
Well there's a lot of.
Well a lot of it's like half confirmed.
We've got like there's articles for it.
There's articles.
Real quick in case listeners I'm sure I've said this before.
Universal Monster Classic Monsterland.
New like Crimes of Grindelwald land probably.
Some bricks.
How to Train Your Dragon I believe.
Yeah how to train your dragon.
And then.
There's where you see Claire Dearing's penthouse apartments back in the mainland.
It's just like Claire Dearing's life.
You know there's a book that you like there's a like how I did it by Claire Dearing.
There's a book.
What?
It's a paperback book.
That is a thing because there's the book in the Ghostbusters.
How to Answer Your Call the paranormal book.
They made one.
They made it for one.
Wow I'd rather buy that like.
Yeah like I saw like Bryce Dallas Howard's Instagram like a year and a half ago was just
like her posing with the book being like so proud to be playing a scientist.
Who is this for?
An entire book of the Claire Dearing bed story.
Wow.
Oh I can't wait.
That's it.
I'm gonna buy copies for you guys.
We're gonna do a Patreon episode about it for sure.
That's our first book club book is the Claire Dearing.
Yeah.
Claire Dearing.
That should be the new land.
I think that's a great idea.
Yeah yeah.
I love the idea of the monster land but it won't be that.
But I love that.
That's still I'm optimistic about that being the case because it survived so many rumor cycles.
So I would I wouldn't put a ton of money on it but I put some.
But I'm disappointed in how I was so happy to see a Frankenstein and Universal Studios
like walking around and I'm yeah I'm disappointed that they've kind of like
like gotten rid of that.
That's like I love like the old hot.
I just feel like the park should feel like a continuum of like old to new not like just.
Like Disney.
Yeah like more so.
Right.
I think because the dark universe movies didn't work out the it could lead to the if the universal
monsters are in this new Orlando park it could lead to it being better because the stock is so
low.
Yeah right.
So they let Universal Creative have more fun with it.
There's I mean there's promo art and I think like for sure the whole thing is whether or not they
green light it the whole thing is designed there's like promo art of what looks like
a Dracula's castle like e-ticket with all the monsters in it.
I'm so excited.
So there's a good chance.
Because they all live in one castle together.
I believe that's the case.
I believe there is a.
It's full house.
Like full house.
I knew we talked about it for a reason.
All the major monster personalities all live in one house.
Okay which one is the exhausting ventriloquist uncle.
Oh was there.
Which is it the invisible man.
He's got a little mummy.
Yeah it's a mummy.
So supposedly like maybe a kooka arm Harry Potter ride vehicle through Dracula's castle.
And it could be like legit like pretty scary but well again I'm not.
So fun.
That sounds like the greatest.
But yeah we'll see.
I'm hoping because they are supposed to be four worlds and the last one is.
What am I forgetting Nintendo it's Nintendo.
Oh it's not Jurassic World.
There's rumors Jurassic World but there's also rumors that they're just going to
expand out on building a new Jurassic Park coaster in Orlando now.
Right.
Blue.
It's a coaster coaster though.
It's a coaster it's not a job but there but there was a patent for that
vehicle for the Jurassic World vehicle a while ago so.
I don't understand coasters that are still supposed to be like within like the Hagrid
or not but the hippogriff one and like I know it's like for kids but I don't understand like
coasters that are like semi in that like I'd rather.
Oh that was there for years and they kind of retro.
Oh really.
Yeah okay.
What is it to them to the Harry Potter.
I know where does it land in their brains.
This is like a roller coaster next to their school.
It's a hippo it's the flight of the hippogriff.
That was that was called.
And you see the flying it.
Can you fly that in the movies.
I forget.
You're supposed to respect it.
They do at some point right.
I don't remember.
Is it like the mighty Akron.
Well you see it you go by the animatronic and it bows to you.
They're constantly bowing to the hippogriff.
Hippogriff is the character I know is the hippogriff that you see which is a great robot.
Anyway we'll look into that.
You're a great robot.
That's what I say.
You're very brave.
I try to pay it back now sometimes.
So when I see you're a great robot and you make me very happy.
Try to bow to robots.
This is the future when we all work for the company or have to compliment the robots.
We will have to.
Yes won't be a choice anymore.
We all have to talk to Optimus Prime and see what a good robot is.
But we started all this by saying by being at this premiere that we got to be in close
proximity to Mr. Trevorrow Walt Disney 3.0 as I call him.
What did you think.
I just I felt I felt more creative having been in his having walked behind him creepily for 20
steps.
I felt I felt imbued by his really.
Man he's a guy.
We thought he was getting on the boat and we're like we got to get it.
We were like trying to say that we rode dress.
Yeah.
We would buy the picture.
But he was just leaving.
I just feel like anytime I've seen it and if he ever hears this I'm really sorry.
But like anytime I've seen him on it's like Spielberg has such levity and life and
Trevor is so serious so self serious about Jurassic World and it's like this is Jurassic
World like be fun like you're making a fun movie and like his smile like he only closed
mouth smiles and pictures and and like he and it's it's like he's like everyone knows I'm King.
Right.
Like that's the vibe.
I don't know.
I'm like it makes me sad that that's like the owner of this franchise.
You got to watch the making of book in Book of Henry feature to really understand.
The joyful Trevor.
It does explain so much.
It explains.
It is more yeah.
Yeah.
That's yeah.
When you're dealing with a character like Sickleman and you can really.
That's that's an exciting.
Henry right.
Yeah.
The villain is the bad character is named Sickleman.
Is that Dean Norris?
That's that is who wants to like touch kids and his brother is in charge of child services
so he can get away.
All right.
That's really got to see it.
I can't believe I haven't seen it.
You have to everyone listening Book of Henry.
We put those Twitter claps in between a Book of Henry.
Is that supposed to say the Twitter claps out loud or are they not meant to be said out loud?
No I think you have to clap.
Is it on the word book?
No it's after the word.
It's after book of Henry.
It's like what is now say it with me.
But Henry it's like every Brooklyn comedian's trick now.
No punch lines just claps.
It's like and what is that book?
It's always Book of Henry.
What was this year's what was that one with McConaughey and Anne Hathaway that you're
like you got us.
Oh is it Serenity.
Serenity.
Yeah.
Movie called Serenity.
It's an exciting time because you don't get like most bad movies are pretty boring and
it's rare that you get like holy shit that is fun front to back.
Yeah.
That is such a balls out nutso movie and Book of Henry was the one Serenity.
Serenity.
Yeah.
Good stuff.
Was a good bad movie.
It's the best.
Yeah.
It's so like oh you can get so tricked and any weird like you know every
every sharkasaurus offshoot kind of movie it's usually so fucking boring or they know
it's campy.
Well that is the problem usually is like you know we're like we're just making a bad thing
and it'll be funny because it's bad but it's like no no no no you want a sincere effort.
Yeah.
That's what makes it good.
Right.
Yeah.
I thought Rampage would be a good like wind down like oh this would be a dumb action movie
and I was just like oh no this is so.
Like not even trying.
This is yeah I was like oh this is bumming me out.
What's the gorilla is it or an ape what's the monkey's name.
Yeah I forget.
George.
I forget.
Yeah I like George.
George was good.
I liked him but I I mean I just wanted to see the monsters from my friends from the old arcade
game the old monsters we used to destroy the cities together.
Hey folks podcast the rides live show is one week away.
August 24th at the Anaheim Hotel in Anaheim during D23 weekend.
But not affiliated with it in any way and thank God because we don't want their baggage
we don't want all the crap they're bringing to the table we're putting on our own show
it's going to be bigger and better than whatever they're doing I don't know what it is but ours
is going to be better.
And also they denied us press passes so we will not be going to the convention unless some magical
savior whisks free passes in our way because now the convention is sold out so we're not going to
be at that convention but we will be at the Anaheim Hotel August 24th and we have a very
special announcement.
Jenny Nicholson will be joining us she's the very special guest we're still talking about topics
but she's going to be there we're going to be having a lot of fun.
It's going to be great whatever it is and way greater than what those stiff shirts over at the
big convention center doing what they have to prove.
What is who yeah what are they going to show us a movie another Nutcracker movie that they're
debuting.
No more realms I'm not going to any more realms that being said I would again if there's free
passes that someone has give them to me I will sit in the room and watch the new Nutcracker
trailer.
Hear about the realms but in this current situation fuck them but not fuck us because
we're going to put on a great show and more tickets are available due to demand we moved to a bigger
room at the Anaheim Hotel right so take that D23 yeah and you guys take yourselves down to the
Anaheim Hotel it's going to be a blast tickets still available check our Twitter and hey if
you're in Orlando come see us there as well that's coming up that's at the end of the month.
That's October 24th.
Another 24th October 24th we will be in Orlando and we're so excited and tickets still available
it's going to be a great time.
We got to see a speech from Conchrevere because we was part of the press event there was a big
presentation and he there was this odd assertion by a couple people that like the feat that you
know people who grew up on Jurassic Park the ride will now get to bring their children to
Jurassic World the ride and I which I don't is anyone going to I mean people will literally do
that that is really like like son this was very important to me.
It's also assuming we're going to start flume ride children at like 24 or two it's like yeah
that's a little like scary yeah and we're in Los Angeles people take their time
nobody's getting right through grandchildren ride.
They also thanked two people well first off they shot Pyro off really close like that was great
that way it was great but then they also thanked two people who could not be here tonight one of
which is Steven Spielberg he's off making West Side Story right now and the other is Michael
Crichton Michael he's away a few years ago.
Yeah the dead one first he did the dead one first.
Oh yeah yeah and then Spielberg he closed with the not deceased yes which made us feel when
they said Spielberg you go is this is this how we're finding out that Spielberg died right.
Trevor gives a ride opening yeah and like what he did when I was also like kind of surprised they
brought up Crichton because I feel like they don't bring him up a lot and I feel like at the
end of his life he was starting to get a little yeah became such a like a truth about like the
truth about global warming right yeah yeah yeah yeah I just read Jurassic Park for that I never
read any Crichton books and I never read Jurassic Park and I just read it like two or three months
ago and it was and I was like oh this is Crichton that's interesting like he's like ideas it's so
different from the movie and that like it's full of like all the ideas and the philosophy that gets
spouted in the movie which I think makes the movie so good because by the time the dinosaurs
attack you felt the weight of all the morality and stuff because they've just yeah right to death
you're like oh I get it but then in the book it's sort of like the characters like emotional lives
don't like work half and like there's this sub story about how like there's they know that there's
raptors on a boat going to Costa Rica and like they need to get back to control to stop that
boat yeah yeah and it's like no you're like fighting for your life and they like they would
like almost die and then Dr. Grant would be like and we have to get back because we know that that
boat has raptors and it's like um like I'm sure that like when they wrote the script there the
first thing they were like let's cut the boat thing like that was confusing there's just a lot
of like oh you wouldn't actually act that way like moments like in the book that every he was a
strange guy characters die too right and stuff the lawyer is like a jacked up guy that survives in
the book right and he's a cowardly man who gets eaten on the toilet but but I think Malcolm dies
in the book he does it was such a hit they're like uh he survived he's back for lost world yeah and
then in the boat and like lost world I think it's literally just like Malcolm comes in with a cane
and he goes like rumors of my demise were greatly exaggerated yeah that's all they do and you're
like okay it's an old adventure serial gag like the emperor that's what they're gonna do in
and rise of skywalker
yeah everyone I feel like everyone was unpleasant in the Jurassic Park book completely like there's
so because you with so many great characters even Dr. Grant is like a lovable curmudgeon who
doesn't like kids but of course he does like kids but everyone's just like mean and yeah like it's
weird and Ellie's and I don't know Lex is like I don't like a kill Lex in the book like she's just
always like I'm hungry yeah every day and then it was clearly like when they adapted it like
I forget that guy's name that adapted it but David Kep is his name but he was like I wanted to not
make Lex be like a bad role model for young girls like she is like they gave her the computer savvy
and like right agency they made her smart they swapped ages I believe too I believe the boy was
older in the book and then Hammond is a real piece of shit like a super capitalist yeah like
a real asshole and they made him he's like reaming people out and he's BD Wong's character out at a
certain point yeah and especially by the end of Fallen Kingdom they've elevated him as like the
moral core yeah of it so much and later we find out about his business partner James Cromwell who's
just strange I think it's strange there's cloning starts to get involved and like they definitely
would in the movie the first movie they were like Hammond is like Walt Disney right because or was
he Santa no he was Santa Claus already right from now that was after what what year is it at 95 yeah
that was post wait wait I do define when he becomes Santa Claus when he was in the movie
Miracle on 34th Street
I went to go to Jurassic World
in the universe
the ascendancy level
the straight to TV special Christmas on Jurassic Park
we went to Gandhi before all of this
oh yeah right yeah and Chaplin
right
oh it's that right the same Attenborough
Richard Attenborough
and then how is he related to the brothers
it's brothers the earth
David Attenborough
is there a director who's in close encounters
oh that's um uh uh the French New Wave
is it John Huston
oh no no no is Truffaut
yeah it's Truffaut yeah wow wow
oh yeah okay uh yeah so big Spielberg history of great directors
you can see in like behind the scenes stuff of Jurassic Park like Spielberg loved having Richard Attenborough there
because he like respected him and he was always like he would like talk you can like tell he's like
like they're actors that you have to like kind of like just keep happy and like just get along too
yeah and then like and then he's like but you old dog like there's this like relationship between them
sure yeah you know it's funny that how Jurassic Park I don't there probably was never a movie that had more
how it was made interest surrounding it and that was sort of a peak era for Universal Studios
like now people just don't care about how movies are made and it's all kind of like yeah it's green screen computers
but like I feel like every scene that we know some detail or have seen some footage or some cool photo
I think it makes sense that like if that was a height of people come to this place because they want to see how movies are made
because you truly don't it's so confusing how Jurassic Park could have been made so complicated
I miss those like lights camera magic shows that used to be on TV
Discovery Channel kind of stuff yeah yeah yeah and they would get Hocus Pocus one yeah they was always in Twister
Twister and Hocus Pocus were like and and Terminator 2 too was oh yeah yeah all of them and they all involved
the abyss was always like those water globs oh yeah right right remember like doesn't it make you nostalgic for that time
I know yeah movies are made oh yeah there's less love in things now like there's just less passion and less love and like every like
movies don't even exist anymore it's really sad like well got easier it got easier yeah and everything is so corporately funded now
that like I always was but like there was more like a Tori's like feeling in Blockbusters like in the 90s like yeah and they're so original
and concept and there's everything is like really derivative now it's like it's like it's upsetting to me and that but the nice thing about Jurassic World
Ride was that I felt like I could appreciate what was new about the series and then like still have like an assurance that they didn't like
forget why this whole series exists at the same time and there's still like Jurassic Park in its DNA it's the only thing keeping Jurassic World tethered
and not the worst thing you've ever seen that there is yeah they are building on the core idea and there's respect for the original yeah film even as
messy and strange as these movies are yeah and the ride doesn't stray from that you're dealing with like I think like these I don't know what
Universal creative and then Imagineers like maybe you people didn't like the new Star Wars very much but like you can feel like in that land I do think like
you're like all these people really give a shit about the history of it and they're like real fans and like I feel you can feel that on the ride sometimes more you can feel it in the movies
right for things so you can tell just from the pictures of the Star Wars land that it like brings you back to the thing you love that feeling yeah like so for sure and tells a new story
takes you to a new place that they got to invent from whole cloth and you can tell how much love they did it with and one of the few subsects of the entertainment industry were like
yeah Imagineering Universal creative has to think people are going to go on this for a decade plus it's not like a movie they live in for two hours the movie comes out in theaters it terminates on Blu-ray and streaming and at best we can hope people see it in the movies and on Blu-ray but like we have we're committing to an attraction or a land or something for probably 15 to 20 years
yeah yeah it's like a movie that's always playing in a theater somewhere yeah yeah so it has to they have to think about the long sustainability long game a little more than like when that T-Rex flings out at you at the end I was so overjoyed like I really was like oh I'm seven again like I'm so happy to be seven again
last trip it was like oh yes this I really felt like I think they like updated how the T-Rex comes out at you it's like more impressive now so you mentioned this to me a week ago and I heard this again on another podcast and this I think it was one of Jim Hill's podcast yeah the final scene is not supposedly the real final scene it's a temporary scene wait in the ride in the ride oh and they're going to do something new so that it's going to be a little bit of a
different story and that other dinosaur is in like is not the real animatronic because it's kind of limited movement it's just really moving its head and even in like the early rumors of this ride it was that you're supposed to get attacked by the
and then the T-Rex comes out like it always does and like in the movies the T-Rex kind of states them yeah so I should I because so I what my first thought was like wow T-Rex is out early did you have the same experience the timing was perfect on the first perfect on the first one and then it was like off the second and then back on the first okay so he did come out like in a similar way that the initial original ride he kind of pops out right as you're going down yeah but I feel like he used to come down more and now
he swings out but maybe I'm just imagining that I think he always had correctly I think he's had this wing out a little bit like this but then I think he would kind of dip down a little bit to be attached to see flying it's a good question his feet are on platforms I saw like the whole so like the whole body is like on some sort of like platform okay it's just that they're so far back that it kind of drops in a shot yeah he's standing on a pipe it's one of these I think I've said a front
row though like last time I went on this front road like he pops out and it is scary it's so good it's great I mean it's great and he pops out so I'm always impressed by that but when we went on it correct me if I'm wrong it felt like T-Rex was outer ready and we were still 20 seconds from going down the hill I think that's right I thought his complaint was like so he had the same thing shock isn't there because he's out they have to get him out to have him interact with the indominus
we held the second time we got held like there for like 10 seconds or something like and so then but it was like all off by the time we went right so it feels like right now what they're running is the indominus is like poking his like be mode head out but he's not getting close to you and then T-Rex has to come out earlier because he would technically eat you you know what I mean he has to come out earlier to stop whatever is going to happen before you get to
the raft whereas I think what was at least pitched to what I've seen online was the idea is like you're going along you're pretty close to the end this giant thing comes out to get you and T-Rex comes out to save you where you get close to the other dinosaur and then T-Rex comes out and I don't know I assume they're not going to touch that would be insane.
Oh yeah.
I see me just.
And if he doesn't show up the robot eats the raft.
Right that's not going to be good.
Everyone gets even on good but you're saying that there's some like bigger effects that we might say different robot is what I heard.
So the indominus like attacks you.
And yes you're one so in a future one supposedly it's a totally different indominus robot that is like bigger and can do and can reach out farther.
Yeah come into the sea which makes a lot more sense because I saw that last scene I was like this is very cool I go but it sort of takes away that kind of scary thing.
Yeah because it's set up earlier in the ride that and this I thought was very cool because you used to be going towards hadris or cove and then get knocked off course this one the heightening you're just full on going to predator cove which is very funny.
Predator in 2019 2019.
No.
Yes they had to put predator cove and be mode to after some court proceedings came up recently that kind of delayed it.
But yeah all that whole scene it's just now covered in blood.
I will say I like.
The right.
There was rumors of this thing being scarier which I think maybe the ending in the way it eventually will be will be scarier because I could see if it was as dark as the old one was and also flashed like a strobe dinosaur attacks you and then another dinosaur that would freak you out of on the first try.
Yeah this was well lit and I was like oh I like the scene but here we go like.
Right.
It wasn't as shocking but I will say the there wasn't blood on the last ride so I give him credit for that.
Yeah there was what do you mean.
There's a like there's like a wall covered in blood like a whole wall covered in blood.
But you know what I did see that.
Wait you didn't see that.
We know I'm seeing the old ride like a horror.
But then I'm off in a corner you can kind of miss the blood.
Yeah I did the second time but that Pteranodon or Pterodactyl.
Yeah there's a there's a corpse of a Pterodactyl in that scene too.
That just makes you like oh I can't wait to see him.
Yes.
Yeah.
And it doesn't look very good.
It's the one and it's like it looks really foamy like one like I like the idea of it but I was like I want this to look a little better.
I think I think that I think that the aquarium scene is fantastic.
Yeah we all agree on that and that gets you going like oh this is like oh this is a whole new thing.
This this fucking rules.
And then the set design of everything is really cool like in Predator Cove.
But then you start to feel like I want to see more robots though.
Right.
Where they all go.
We I don't think he would mind us saying this Colton had a good plus up now we didn't ask him for it.
But even there's that spot around Predator Cove where it feels a little quiet.
It used to be where the truck or the Jeep would fall.
Which hadn't worked for years.
And like he was like he goes there should be a guy that like and there's an open and ominous Rex cage.
He goes should be like a guy that runs out and he's like bloody and he's like oh god or whatever.
I'm like that's pretty pretty good.
Like humans on the rise if they could pull it off.
Norman Bates run out to the tram every time.
Right.
We have a hot Norman Bates.
Really.
I hope he keeps booking because you have to get like I imagine they have to get a type because of the Anthony
Perkins face and like he was you have to get a very specific like neat taken care of man.
I assume you could go a couple ways.
You could because he's a handsome guy but you could go into very just like pasty odd guy.
But like.
Right.
Like two Crispin Glover or.
If you don't consider Crispin Glover a hot guy.
Do I?
Someone does.
Mrs.
Glover.
If there is one I wonder if there is one.
I stan Willard.
I stan the Rat King.
Yeah there's something hot about Willard in a hot topic kind of way.
Is Willard his hottest role?
George McFly is a dream role for me.
I would love to.
Oh.
Confrontation.
Yeah.
Fantastic.
I thought there was some good timing plus up like coming after.
I mean the lift hill has a lot more going on the glitching TVs and stuff.
They kept the one Raptor that comes through the ceiling.
But that splashdown at least when I when we did it and then some of the videos I saw like the splashdown of that little hill the lights come on and a spitter gets you right as you drop.
Like I thought that was a good fun reveal.
And then also just all the vegetation.
And I thought the T-Rex coming through the ceiling was working really well too.
Some of this stuff they may have just like spruced up cleaned up make sure it was running at top capacity.
Yeah.
I wonder if there's there was a little like on the same.
All my sources are from Jim Hill's podcast.
This was in his Inside Universal podcast.
I think there also was a chance there's more stuff too.
Like maybe there is something else they add along that little.
Yeah.
It felt like.
Pulling up I kind of wanted like something to happen.
Because I feel like there was a rap there was something before.
Well the Raptor comes down there was a rapper that comes down like holding to.
Wires.
It was a second one of those.
It is goofy.
Yeah.
But I do like the 90s.
I like that.
If you're going to have blue then can you also do a 90s like.
I don't know.
Yeah it is good.
It is campy.
Have a human's head in your mouth or something like do something scary.
Yeah.
But was did was there was spitter there.
I forget what was there was.
I think there was a second ceiling Raptor on that hill.
Right.
That they replaced with the TV.
Now it's.
Yeah.
This is what he said.
This is Owen Grady.
What.
Why am I so obsessed with these names.
The fact that they say them.
Listen this is Claire Dearing.
I need you to stay.
The ridiculous.
Board game names.
Yeah.
Like a really thin like why a mystery novel.
And why if you were OK if you were really in the shades.
Actually.
Yeah.
And it's just so like if you were on a Disney ride and then there was a problem like in
reality.
Right.
Like.
You know a real gorilla was loose on expedition Everest or something.
And then all and then on the loudspeakers somebody's like attention this is Sharon
Brown.
Why are you telling me your name.
I know it's so true.
You're a Disney person.
And you're going to help me.
Or it was like Bob Chapek.
Attention this is head of parks and resorts Bob Chapek telling you please.
Sorry.
Parks.
Yeah.
As soon as I said it I know products and experience.
That's his real insane title.
I got it wrong.
Full credit as you're about to die.
I know.
And then he has like nothing to offer.
He's just like just hold tight.
You're fucking Jets.
Breathe.
Good thing.
How much do they pay you.
This is his second appearance on a ride.
He is now I have two has two rides.
You will have three when the coaster opens up in Florida.
Oh well you don't have the same character.
It'll be the same Peter Quill character.
Yeah it's sort of actually oddly similar scenario where it's a plus up of an
existing ride plus up to have screens and Chris Pratt is on the screens and they
are not 3D screens but they're very good screens.
Screens.
Yes.
On both.
They're being guardians.
I was going to throw this trivia question everybody's way.
Can you think of anyone else who at the same time was appearing in both a Disney
attraction and a universal attraction.
Oh I can only think of one that was ever.
Hold on.
I can I can hint if you think.
I think I know it.
So whoopie Goldberg.
Whoopie Goldberg.
You got it.
On the host of the studio tour when I did a studio tour in 2006 and at the same
time was still appearing as Khalifa the spirit of California in golden dreams.
The very sleepy film.
It's a California which is now Little Mermaid in California Adventure or that
that building.
I said yeah.
Yeah.
It's not into the woods last night at the Hollywood Bowl.
Oh I saw that.
Yeah I saw that Friday.
You saw that Friday.
Yeah it was great.
I loved it.
Yeah.
And whoopie is the voice of the giant and it's so you didn't know that I didn't
pick up on that.
Gosh that giant effect was cool but I had read the kid.
Is she credited in the official can.
Yeah.
I think on the billboards it's like and it's like on the force of whoopie.
You can't like tell that you're not going to be there.
Yeah.
Oh right.
Wait to buy a ticket and like overlook that she's just recorded.
Yeah.
I want to see whoopie Goldberg with my own eyes 3000 feet away.
Yeah that is that I had eye strain by the end of the night from like looking so far
down.
Oh I know.
Going between the stage and the videos.
It's hard.
And I didn't have my glasses either.
Everything was black.
The sound was amazing.
I mean it sounded great.
The acoustics are great.
That's such a great show.
Yeah.
Well is it over now.
I think tonight's last night was a concert of a yeah yeah.
Yeah.
Worth it.
You got nothing to do.
I have something to do.
Oh my God.
Maybe.
Yeah maybe.
I will.
Bring them there.
Have your general there.
Have a Sunday night general.
Are you guys watching Sunday night generals.
Great show.
That's a spectrum exclusive right.
One of those weird shows where it's like I can only watch this if I have spectrum
cable.
It's like 15 minutes on the like the direct TV.
It's like oh but there's only half a show time.
Yeah yeah.
This is what Johnny Lee Miller's been up to.
Yeah.
Christian Slater's in his prime again.
Killing it.
Mark Harmon.
Somehow boost mobile.
Thank you.
You got other characters also in.
I watched the pre show.
We weren't able to do it.
We had no line.
Unfortunately we just got on the thing so we can get to watch all the pre show
videos which I watched a really blurry copy of and you get to see like a live
Jurassic Park Jurassic World news show.
Jurassic Network.
Yeah you're watching Jurassic Network.
Is that like the in room channel though like at Disney because we all love the
in room a little bit.
So I kind of like that gives me that vibe a little bit and I like that it says
live from Jurassic Studios down in the park.
I like that.
I'm thinking like who am I who what friend do I have who's going to be in
this like it was just like sure.
And so I was like there are obviously groundlings that they're being like a
little smaller.
Like that day rate that single day rate buyout for 30 years when they got a one
day buyout.
Six million still emailing about their season pass discounts.
They show my face in the park.
But you get to meet the Jurassic News anchor Monica Bayer.
We were saying it the whole day.
And she also says it so many times.
What is this world.
I know.
Like she plays it so straight as like what it is too.
It's like I love like the the like fan fiction like it just lowers the rent of
the universe of Jurassic World so much to see Monica Bayer interviewing Owen
Grady.
Yeah.
And why it's also from a perspective of like the way she's talking about it.
Like she's talking about it.
She thinks it.
Yeah.
And why it's also from a perspective of well you the theme park visitor know
assuredly who Owen Grady is.
You know who I am.
Monica Baird is.
You'll see Claire Dearing later.
Obviously you know her.
There's no besides us dorks who know the people who work there.
Who you would know it.
In the world of Jurassic World is real.
We'd be dying on a Disney ride like Jay Pack.
And we yeah if Jurassic World were real we'd be doing like little bits in every
episode to like we want to get Monica Baird on the show.
So tweeted a hashtag BTR Monica Baird.
But to the normies yeah why do we care about Monica Baird.
And she'd like been banned Owen can't keep his own flirting a little bit.
I know he is.
Yeah he's a he's a cheater.
Claire is right there Owen.
Monica Baird's desk is like like huge studio space like in a tower with like
views of the park like the best view of the park.
It's like elevated above the park.
It's like clearly from it's like a still of like like the shot when they show like
the whole park.
But then it's like these like it feels like something on a Mars attacks like it's
like this beautiful like groovy white like all white 60s mod feeling room and
like the light like window like groovy looking mod windows are not this way.
It's like a huge facility and it's just Monica Baird like dead center.
It feels very Dr.
Strangelove.
Yeah.
Like what is this like.
Sorry.
Wait what.
It's a little like black like if black mirror shows TV show or something.
Yeah it's really it's odd.
Yeah.
I also think it's funny for years they had standard deaf TVs and now they've
upgraded to the widest ultra HD TVs I have ever seen.
The widest wide screen.
Yeah.
It's true.
And like not normal aspect ratio screen.
Well I think it's those ones that curve a little.
Oh OK.
Maybe that's why it's why the tagline for the road is it just got wide.
You can see in the billboards.
Yeah sure.
Wide billboards.
They also interview BD Wong's character too.
Yeah.
He just like continues this Dr.
Wu who is my favorite Jurassic Park universe character because he has the same
name as a Steely Dance song.
Number one in my book.
And they turned him is he in the last one BD Wong.
Thank you.
Yes.
They turned him evil in the Jurassic World.
They did.
And he was just like a nice like.
Yeah.
He's a scientist hiding his sexuality at Jurassic Park and now he's a full
fruity evil mastermind.
He's just a nice man.
Which is nice to be able to have that permission because they've had to like.
You feel like in Lion King they had to like tame Scar down.
Yeah.
Does the feel like well we can't have a villain who's kind of like that's the
subtext but it's more fun.
It's always more fun.
Yeah.
It's like we think but they can't have that fun.
I get they're too scared to have.
So I guess with BD Wong.
Yeah.
You get your kind of like.
Well did you guys see Aladdin.
Yes we did.
Fascinating.
Yes.
There's a real like right into someone's the duality around someone's sexuality
is really interesting.
Wait wait wait explain your your specific your thoughts.
It was just really interesting to see Will Smith grapple with how to finally
express his femininity.
That field felt very like truthful to him but under the caveat of like I'm but I'm
doing this as a joke and then but then also starting out like this like hyper
straight boring stripped down genie.
Genie as a human at the beginning was just like it was the worst acting will
Smith's ever done.
Like it was really like bad.
And then when he got into the genie he got to finally be like the.
Oh sure.
He is deep down.
That was really still not as because Robin Williams in the songs gets like very
like I he wouldn't will Smith would not dare go.
Yeah yeah it was a weird it was like a weird it was just like I felt like
struggle and release like the entire time.
So you're saying when he was like human and when he was blue is sort of the
switch.
Yeah when he's well when he when he's on the kind of like at the cold open you
have already got the whole open and you're right.
Yeah.
I totally forgot about the book.
I see.
He plays it really different so that you're like is he the right.
Right.
Just like him being like I'm straight.
It's really very pasted on beard.
He's literally wearing a beard.
Right.
Yeah.
That does not match.
It is not a kind of beard that Smith would grow.
Is that a nod to the Robin Williams character at the start of the cartoon
which has a beard and he's technically the genie.
Is that I don't know ambiguous.
It's very ambiguous.
The casting of Nassim Pedrad who I think is very funny but the casting of Nassim Pedrad
and Will Smith as a couple is surreal and everyone just accepted it.
Yeah.
It's literally like I can't even think what it's like.
It's like Casey Wilson and Brad Pitt or like Kyle Mooney and like Angelina Jolie as a couple.
Like it's just like what's going on.
One of these days.
Yeah.
And they don't there's no like sparks between them.
They may have any kind like do they ever they don't kiss do they.
It's just like I don't know separately they imply they like each other together.
Yeah.
It's definitely a tell don't show thing.
Right.
I know they did scenes together but it also feels like if somebody went you know they just
sort of added that in post I'd be like oh yeah.
The whole movie.
They will you will.
Yeah.
80 percent of it wasn't there until a month.
No one set foot on us.
They just have a technology to move people's mouths differently and then a voice actor came
in and they'll just face timed and then they got.
Yeah I love you.
Yeah.
We're gonna have kids.
There it's gonna be really interesting to watch.
I mean some podcast will clean up with the like five year anniversary of all of the live action.
Oh yeah.
It is completely like no one will want to talk about them already.
Beauty and the Beast live action feels like just don't know they're all being buried immediately
in like Dumbo.
I don't even know if that comes out in three years or came out a year ago.
I don't even know.
This is like kind of you were saying earlier like the movies can don't necessarily have a heart and
you know I like some reboots and some franchises and stuff but you know when it's all said and
done and everything just goes on Netflix or Hulu and it's like Citizen Kane is next to
a sitcom that ran for a season is next to Planet Earth is next to Netflix original.
You're like only we saw billboards for because Netflix buys the same billboards in Los Angeles
every week.
It kind of there's a strange flattening of culture where everything is the same everything's
equivalent everything's just or stuff is impossible to find it's like hey that show that got good
reviews but only lasted like 10 episodes where do I find it.
I know like true and there's like shows that are like 15 minutes long on Netflix and then
there's like like oh like Scorsese is doing a nice movie.
Yes it's crazy it's just like none of us are going to be remembered like that's the bottom line.
Like well that's true there's no more there's no more archetypal genius brains to like root
for.
It's pretty scary I talk about how like when I worked at Funny or Die with a lot of people
have been guests on the show and there was always a lot of jockeying for the front position
like if we don't get main player then we're sunk we're not going to get our 20,000 views
or whatever and now that is Netflix and film entire you could like then now the funny or die
main player is a film you worked on for 40 years like but they didn't it's on Netflix
and they paid for it but they didn't show that it existed.
Just put it in that big stripe that goes by I know my life is ruined.
Yeah yeah it's it's not so it's a weird time yeah just lying down the toilet.
This is what you're doing to us.
Oh man as someone who is not created or co-created a television show it's great hearing to people
who have be so optimistic.
Get out there.
Joey stay at it.
Anyway the Disney plus is coming soon and Disney plus it's Netflix HBO Max like they're all these
titans and I'm sure they're all going to want to do lots of new original stories that are not
and not just you know the Rocketeer the show which is something we all know happening.
I mean camp crustaceans I'm losing my mind.
It's a restaurant.
That sounds fun though honestly.
I'm working on camp crustaceans that's all crabs and lobsters.
I also watched a food tour.
I also watched on Netflix actually a Lego Jurassic World and it's kind of fun.
I kind of liked it.
Oh yeah the Lego all sort of like slowly getting the inoculation.
Yeah we're getting slowly desensitized.
That's what I saw it wasn't so bad.
This is the Lego the Lego movies are good.
And this is part of it honestly that like that we don't think any of us love the Jurassic
World films but now we've we kind of like this ride we're getting used to the vibe
we're like apologizing for things about the movies because the ride is all right.
It's true.
I like J.A. Biona too.
I liked that movie the orphanage he made and it was really good and then I like him like when
he talks he's like yeah it's like gonna be amazing and you're like yeah he cares like it's like
yeah sure yeah his passion is what we're saying.
Now he should have been there yeah.
We did get to see Chris Brett team blue live.
I mean that's what you want to say.
Power of Christ.
All that is real.
Blue's yeah that's really these movies like Jurassic Park is Jewish and Jurassic World's
Christian like I don't it's weird like how did that happen.
That's my theory.
Explain explain about that.
Jurassic Park Spielberg like I don't care about your 4000 years old earth there were dinosaurs
like right yeah but it's like they say the word science a lot.
That's true yeah but it's mega church Christian it's like righteous gemstone it's Christian.
That's true but that's kind of it's about the folly of that so I would argue that yeah
but then Jurassic World feels like it's bright and shiny and like oh it's like no come on in
take a seat we're all friends here and you're like I don't know if I believe that.
I mean honestly I'll be honest I've never thought about that before.
I know that your mom just into this show so I'm sorry if this is a cultural problem.
We were apologizing for religious stuff in the other episode.
Yeah we recorded an earlier one today and I was apologizing honestly I think though she'll
she'll like that because she's half Jewish.
Okay good all right.
So she'll kind of like that it's been balanced out.
Yeah yeah so she's somewhere she's a Jurassic Park three head.
Yeah she was.
She likes the end of three in the beginning of the world.
He gets his hat back at the end of three that's a little nod to Steven and yeah.
Laura Dern and Sam Neill are divorced and Laura Dern's married to another man and she calls the
like the army or something.
The SWAT team to like oh yeah.
How did that happen?
The end of the movie is like her showing up on the beach with the army.
And he's like huh Ellie.
How though?
It is I've never made it this far in this film.
Yeah the Navy Seals.
It's only like 70 minutes so you can get there.
I mean I do one in the third Jurassic where I want all of them back like the Malcolm
that was a big disappointing thing in Fallen Kingdom was like yeah totally.
They clearly had Goldblum for a day his entire scene is sitting at a table in a
Senate subcommittee.
So weird.
I want him and Laura Dern and Sam Neill for the next one.
They are they're all coming back.
All right I'm on board.
They weren't saying it and then Laura Dern and her passionate mania was like I'm doing
it and then like tweeted it and they were like oh yeah we're doing it.
I love the Dern Renaissance we're getting now.
I am jazzed about how much Laura Dern is.
To the point now that I don't know if you watch Big Little Lies too but it's just Laura
Dern fan fiction at this point.
Like it's just like jokes of what you want to see Laura Dern doing the show.
I'm finishing up the second season of Deadwood so I got to I will swing to something.
You'll get to it in about 25 years.
Yeah I'm taking my time.
You have to get through the whole HBO.
Big Little Lies is pretty quick and then I'll finally do the full Twin Peaks run.
Oh cool.
Because I've only done half.
Well if you get high and watch the original like I well I guess you could just watch it
without being high but I was really high and I was watching Laura Dern and every scene
and she is like it's an underwritten character and you don't feel that because she's delivering
the most presence of anyone in the movie and she's just like buried like she's like
holding a leaf and just like immersed in like what the leaf is like and she's got no lines
in the scene and she and it's like you're stealing the show like you are really doing
such an endearing character.
Yeah.
So maybe they could overlay this when the next one comes out and give us a little Dern
on the screen.
Yeah.
Once in a while give us a.
Well they should trade it.
She's gonna turn it into like a piece of.
She's not gonna I feel like there's no way she's gonna be like serving a greater story
like she's gonna be like doing a like now for some reason Ellie Sattler is like emotionally
unstable.
It's gonna be it's gonna it's like there's no way she's gonna chill out for this.
I mean that's good though.
Yeah it's good.
Yeah I don't want to just sit on that lift hill and watch this Ellie Sattler break down
on the monitors.
Well you know there's gonna be a scene where Owen Grady and Claire Dearing are sizing up
Alan Grant and Ellie stat like what's this.
Yeah very much so yeah.
Yeah that Seinfeld episode with the like new friends and the old friends.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Yeah yeah.
Here's a question I guess is because we kind of wind it down.
Do you do we think this is worth doing at the other parks or is this because it feels to
me like all right well Star Wars is opening down the freeway.
We got to do something for the summer that feels like what motivated all of this happening.
But was this successful enough that they should go to Orlando Orlando and Osaka.
And I well I'm obviously they love Claire Dearing in Osaka in Japan.
They'll be out with the book.
Right.
Children have to read it in school.
It's how they learn English in Japan now.
I I'm always a fan of two versions of rides so.
I like the guardians.
That's what I think like I like guardians a lot.
It's one of my favorites but please keep my beloved Florida Tower of Terror safe.
I like two different versions.
I like the idea that I can go do the classic in Orlando.
That's nice.
I'm not against them doing it or do this version in Orlando but I like that.
Let's keep them if we can.
I guess like if I wasn't thinking about what's realistic I would just want there to be like a
new ride that has stuff I want to see like and just let there be like two different new rides.
But I know that's not going to happen.
Years and the concept art of this is pretty easy to find online.
There was like a Jeep ride.
Oh right.
Adventure ride that they always talked about building in Florida.
I think there's still space available to build it.
Well that's where people were like at Islands Adventure.
Right.
Yeah yeah yeah.
And like because that's what I think then the new idea was for the gyrosphere thing which
if they can make a big ball roll and have a Jimmy Fallon on the screen in there I'm all like let's do it.
When that was in the movie I will say no the only other thing that I've ever went well that's made
for a theme park is the drivers fear and then in the one Hobbit movie when they get in the barrels
and they go through the rapid.
I'm sure that's fun too.
But that Jeep thing like you could make like the scariest ride of all time
if you can have like the T-Rex chomping down like the scene in the first Jurassic Park
which I don't even know if they could do it because of how freaked out any child that went on it
because as a kid I was traumatized by that scene.
I love Jurassic Park but I would watch that and I was just freaked out because of how good it is.
But like yeah that that Jeep ride that would be awesome.
Yeah.
But I would be I'd be scarred if I.
It'd be the gyros if they were going to do it it would be a gyrosphere.
Yeah and you couldn't like break that open.
I feel like you could get a Jeep and you could somehow like make it feel like it was squeezing
in a little bit.
Like a piece of glass comes down within.
Oh no it would be so.
Yeah.
I would contend with the fact that gyrospheres don't exist finally.
That's true.
They have to finally admit that that's not real.
But they don't want to do that.
But there was a drawing on a patent I saw it.
And it's real that means it's real.
I should support imagination.
The only reason I could see them doing this overlay in Florida for a couple of reasons
whether they should or not is up up for discussion.
But because Islands of Adventure is hitting the 20 year mark and stuff is like start they are
starting to freshen up stuff.
Also depending on how they're going to theme that Raptor roller coaster if they flip it all
to Jurassic will that cause them to go like we should make it all Jurassic World.
I think they're going to see how this one is received.
They're going to listen to this podcast specifically and see.
We do have to remember Jurassic World was insanely successful.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Super.
In the top 10 movies of all time in terms of box office crews.
Every movie that comes out is in the top 10 movies of all time.
I guess.
That is true.
10 movies are refreshed every single year now.
Yeah.
Everyone wants to see dinosaurs.
And also it's like.
No matter what.
Yeah no matter what.
Right.
No matter how many assistants get strangled to death.
How long the way.
And also what bothers me is that none of these movies Gone with the Wind is the number one
movie.
Will always be.
Where's that ride?
Yeah.
Yeah right.
That's like if you.
In the burning.
Yeah.
If the inflation if inflation were taken into account most of these movies are not in the top 10.
That's true.
So like.
Titanic.
Yeah.
That would be a good ride.
But again only the theme park divisions are thinking about the long game.
Everyone else is thinking about the next financial quarter or two.
I just want to see pterodactyls.
Like I think that's.
Yes.
Would just be so fun.
As a kid I was reading the book I was like there were pterodactyls in that first book
and they were not in the movie.
I know it's.
Because that was my favorite dinosaur.
Because they go through an aviary where there's a there was supposed to be a hotel
inside the aviary and then they were immediately like oh that was a terrible idea because it's
all boarded up and apparently all the workmen died.
It's like well obviously.
And then all the pterodactyls do is just like kamikaze dive bomb the kids and try to
knock them unconscious and it's fun like that would be cool.
Yeah.
They should do that.
I'm looking at it.
It's Gone with the Wind Star Wars Sound of Music E.T.
Titanic.
Wow.
That's the top five.
Which feels like in terms of impact that feels correct.
Yeah.
Right.
Although Dr.
Zhivago is eight.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
It's Ten Commandments Jaws Dr.
Zhivago Exorcist Snow White.
Oh.
And then you start getting into the territory.
Eleven is Force Awakens.
Okay.
So.
Guys these are going to have the biggest corners of that academy museum that's coming
to Wilshire Boulevard.
I am so excited for that.
Are you.
The technodrome.
No I'm interested.
It seems like a misuse of money in the current state of Los Angeles.
The current state of Los Angeles is it feels like a misuse of money.
But the one piece of concept art with the one giant room is just columns.
It's just an empty room with massive columns and Spielberg paid a million dollars for a
column.
Jason Blum paid a million dollars for a column.
It's just people buying columns for a million dollars and I think it's called the Heim
Saban Room that I've talked about.
When you say column just like a blank column.
Just columns.
And it has their name on it or.
Yeah.
Oh okay.
I think so.
It's like they're the donors but it's just the concept art.
It's like this just a room with a lot of lighting.
It's just an empty room with columns.
This is so odd.
Yeah.
Are you saying we should buy a column.
I mean it would be very funny to buy a column as a.
Like if someone.
Pull a million altogether.
If we could pull money for a column and then made it say like Pee Pee Poo Poo.
That would be very funny.
That would be the choice.
So and then people would be like I actually love Pee Pee Poo Poo's films.
I've seen all of them actually.
I know what it is.
Yeah.
I think it'll be it will be an interesting museum but it just seems like it's it's going
to be the most expensive museum of all time and it feels a little decadent.
It definitely looks decadent but in the way that the promise of L.A.
Seems like it's supposed to be like there's like a room that's like close encounters in Star Wars.
It's just like sci fi room and it looks really I just want to get high.
I mean to look at like.
Scarlett O'Hara and DT and like the exercise.
Sure.
It sounds fun.
I just want to see the columns.
Jason's really actually built the columns up in my mind.
I'm excited for these columns now.
Is that more of a rose?
I just like the idea of someone buying a ceremonial column in an empty room for a million dollars.
Sure.
Well we'll get one.
Oh and Iger Bob Iger was the big of course the big pitchman for like come on buy these columns.
Someday we'll have column money.
Yeah.
I'm looking through OK.
One of the things we didn't talk about.
This is not confirmed and somebody tell me if they came across this.
The ride is slower than Jurassic Park.
Don't know that.
If you look up this is I think another Jim Hill source thing.
If you look at the videos when they're both together it seems like the Jurassic World
moves slower.
It's just longer ride.
I don't know.
We have yet to see what the duration is on like Wikipedia or something.
Get your stopwatches out everybody.
Let's find out.
Let's figure that out.
And they turn the jets on a little slower.
Opening is probably the Mosasaurus probably is where I would say I feel like being slower.
Maybe.
Yeah.
I don't know.
You're in there for a while.
Yeah.
So but the whole thing maybe overall.
I don't know.
That's about it.
What a way to end the show.
You know what I'd like to say is I forgot to acknowledge at the beginning that I went on
the ride.
I'm afraid of cat.
I said the whole Jurassic Park ride episode.
Like I've only done it once.
I don't want to do it again.
But it's been a courageous year for me.
I've done a lot and just like SplashMath.
Thank you.
That's what I wanted.
It was a half hour.
I was.
I stopped because you weren't done.
And I will applaud fully.
I was all it.
Here is the column room.
Oh I have seen that picture.
And I did.
I had no idea what I was looking at.
Wow.
All right.
Very good.
But you know I just like as with everything in my
courageous writing your Splash Mountain and Criticoaster Tower of Terror and Guardians.
I had help from a little friend called Liquor.
And if I could just you know anybody listening out there I can't say enough.
If there's something you're scared of doing drink a bunch and then do it.
If I could give apart any message.
Yeah.
And we could.
Drink a bunch then do it.
Clap for points.
Island New Bar what do we think?
Oh that was great.
I mean I didn't get a drink.
It's hard.
Look it's hard to not like it when you're at a press event.
Yeah.
So I tried a lot of the.
Blended ones and I thought they were pretty good for like machine blended drinks.
Do we have a picture of the menu?
I forget.
It's my tie.
Sorry.
No no no.
You say no Tiki.
I don't think I think that if they're collectible why are they not dressing world.
Like I don't get the like they're just like a bamboo stick that you don't want to take home.
More of like a dinosaur shape.
Yeah or just something that's like Jurassic World.
I don't know I thought that was kind of like it looked cheap too.
I don't know.
I like yeah I like the idea of like a Tiki theme but it would make more sense if it was a dinosaur
glass.
Yeah.
Yeah that makes sense.
Collectible.
Yeah and also I've seen the complaint now that it's like not like a you know it's not
in the summer of Oga's Cantina the incredible bar in Star Wars land this is just a stand.
Yeah.
I was hoping for a little more because when we I believe we got that scoop live while
we were recording that there was going to be a Tiki bar and I was imagining maybe on the top
of the restaurant there'd be this cool theme.
I thought that too.
But unfortunately yeah it's just a little stand not that it's not bad I think it gives it the
area a little like energy but it's not the fully emer we want even we know what we want.
We want a dinosaur in the robot on the restaurant.
I want to be able to sit and look at the splash down.
We want to sit and look at the splash down.
Tropical margarita.
We want to feel Costa Rica like when you're there.
Costa Rica we want like a dinosaur with a lay on or something like a hat like a sun hat.
The food is a real step up for the lower the chicken and the pork and rice and stuff was
a real step up for the lower lot.
I think the issue with now though is like oh cool new land we plus everything up in this area.
It's like you got to get a move on on the rest of the other parts of the park because it makes
them work worse by comparison.
Right.
I think the restaurant still could be like cooler though.
There's something so like it's still it's always felt like a hospital or something like.
There's a clinical.
I like the original mural like there were these like painted they were kind of janky and small
but they were just like painted photo realist like murals of dinosaurs like it loving life
and it was like out in the open and I liked that that was like a choice that felt weird
and like and also like that's how Jurassic Park is like in the like in the cafeteria and stuff.
Like they have these like murals like that.
But then this felt the murals this aesthetic felt clean and nice but like a like a half
assed lunch children's lunch box of Jurassic Park.
You know like it didn't have anything like really immersive like.
Yeah there's no personality really.
Yeah but it's nicer than like a lot of stuff at a theme park so.
Yes and it's new it's newish now so that's great.
Yeah it's clean right now.
But if there could be a drink where what about a drink where like this little like
you get a little Mr. DNA with it and those are a little.
Yes that's a perfect.
Yeah I mean that's.
You drop into the drink you like disconnect him.
Eating DNA.
Yeah yeah yeah.
This is where Disney is just kicking Universal's ass is in the Instagrammable
food and drink departments.
Right on.
With whether it's mugs whether it's the Hatbox Ghost Tiki mugs like they know what nerds want
to buy and they know like what's going to like be an Instagram like there's a big donut that's
in the shape of Donald Duck's ass like it's like his.
His little bottom.
His bottom I should have said bottom I'm so sorry mom.
Ass.
I don't know why I said ass.
Donald Duck's thick ass.
This is Duck Butt and it's but it's like people take a picture of it.
There's a wizard hat like smoothie that looks like the sorcerer like why wouldn't they do that.
Like Mr. D is you just literally that's a multi-million dollar idea.
That they will they won't do it they won't listen to us.
Yeah they're kind of boring I don't know.
I drink it's like a spitter you squeeze it and it squeezes.
Oh yeah.
Bits alcohol India.
Great.
Or like just rip off.
New ways to be an alcoholic now.
Yeah faster.
New discovery.
The Joe's Crab Shack drink the Shark Bite where you pour in.
My favorite drink.
A little blood and then it makes the water it's like a little shark sheen.
We didn't do it this year at Comic Con though.
We didn't do it at Comic Con it just never worked out.
It's a tradition usually of it's like a big like chalice glass chalice that's probably
not what the term is and it's blue and then you put red in it and it's a whole they do
the whole show for you.
Do a little show like that feels like a given.
Yeah they don't do that.
Joe's Crab Shack part of the appeal is also it's usually very cold inside and quiet.
And it's relatively quiet.
And the food is acceptable.
It's fine.
But it's on the water which is nice.
It's on the water.
It's behind the convention center.
Yeah.
There is something about the restaurant that feels like designed by execs or something.
Like it's like for meetings or something like you're supposed to like take meetings
at Jurassic Park Cafe like it's just like clean and inoffensive.
It's not like making any choices.
It's like it's like you'll like it.
There's something for everyone.
I mean the food just used to be so dour looking so like getting some mojo pork and the the
crisp a repas.
Is that what the crispy cornbread stuff looks like?
And crispy plantain.
It's like well this is this is nice.
This feels nice.
Yeah.
It is night and day.
Fred theme.
So that's good.
But also I want to have one more.
I get a drink that comes in a shaving cream can.
Yeah.
Oh.
It's so fun.
I mean how how.
Yeah.
I mean truly that would like make them so much more money.
And for like Harry Potter which they're doing it in another part of the park.
It's crazy they don't.
Yeah.
Like just make it make a dinosaur mug and make them limited edition.
And idiots like me will buy them.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
They're going to be gone soon and I need it now.
Even Springfield even Springfield has kooky like some kooky food.
Yeah.
And the Duff and the big donuts.
The flaming mo at least.
Yeah.
Hard on your body.
They are delicious but you gotta share.
Yeah they are good.
But you gotta share them.
Well we ate the Grinch donut.
Yeah we ate the Grinch's face and donut for him.
And then about a week later I ate another Grinch donut.
Oh my god.
Wow.
Now you gotta have your weekly Grinch donut.
Yeah now I'm hooked.
Which is I'm really hungry now.
They're not too bready.
That was my I looked and I was like I bet this is like tricks you and it's actually really bready.
That was my theory.
Well the Grinch since I haven't actually had a maybe the Springfield one is bready
but there's so much frosting on the Grinch's face.
Yeah.
It's a perfect ratio.
Maybe too much frostings.
So now frosting breakfast every day and.
I have to do it.
And a shark bite to go with it.
An 11 a.m. shark bite every morning.
Any closing thoughts anything I don't know.
It's just fun.
I dug it.
Thanks for coming to do it.
Yeah thank you.
Thank you guys.
Jumping on the ride and get this is one of the quickest from opening to episode topics
I think we've had.
That's what I intended yeah.
Break a record.
Break a speed record.
Yeah hey hey Charles Radjasek survived podcast.
Thank you guys.
Thank you.
Thank you for being a big fan.
I very much appreciate it.
Okay thank you.
Thanks for doing it much appreciated.
You all move a little differently in person than I had imagined.
Each one in your own way.
Could you say what you thought I moved like.
You smile more with your eyes than I expected.
Interesting.
Wow.
Because I think my delivery.
My delivery might be flat.
Pretty flat so I could imagine I'm trying to imagine what I would look like with just
my voice so I didn't make that make sense.
Wow.
And then.
More heart.
Jason you're more like your body is more like loose and fluid than I imagined.
Hey I like that.
And then.
And then you.
I'm sorry I just fucked up your name.
Oh no hey we're in a group of three.
I know I know.
No no no.
Jason you.
I was on this podcast I don't know who the fuck that was.
I can't believe anyone knows the names.
Horrible.
So no no no.
I'm being on a podcast.
Why?
And then I was like am I gonna.
Am I gonna like somehow like trick my way back into fixing this and then I did it.
No Jason you.
You like or think you're always thinking and that's something you can't hear on on air.
You know.
Oh thank you.
The gears are turning.
I'm looser.
I think you're looser.
Physicality.
I'm stiff as a board.
No no.
Thank you I appreciate it.
We did take some pictures and video at the the open we took a bunch and there's like one or
two where I was like hey I look pretty good at that there's one where I was like oh no
what happened.
Isn't that what we all go through.
Yeah I didn't know I should have got my angle.
I didn't know my angle in them.
We gotta know your angles.
I didn't mean to somehow inspire that type of thinking in you.
Oh yeah that's.
I was gonna show you and get a compliment and that's what we all do.
I appreciate your compliment.
Comedians are the worst.
Just like like this ride it's so this one really is that when you get off the ride they say
you survive Jurassic Park the ride and then you exit through the gift shop.
Charles would you like to plug anything by exiting through the gift shop.
Oh I mean you got a couple more months listening to a podcast that I made that's on earwulf
before it goes on to Stitcher premium.
Okay okay.
And then you have to pay for it which no one will.
Classic earwulf the clock is ticking.
I know.
It's called the problem with Charles and Casey and I'm sitting on a lot of search party news that I
will soon be able to reveal when corporate powers allow.
Very exciting.
Oh they control all of the information.
Because you want to make a big splash then when it is revealable.
Did you tell them that you were going on a theme park podcast and it might be perfect timing.
Perfect timing.
And the perfect audience.
Yeah it's such a direct line.
Are you releasing a new ride anytime soon.
Oh man I got a couple rides in me.
Okay all right.
Is there like you have a good where would these announcements be.
I mean I'll put it on my Instagram.
Instagram what's that name?
G Charles Rogers.
Okay.
And it's the French spelling R-O-G-E-R-S.
Let me ask so you're not a victim of the flattening of culture.
Where can people stream the first two seasons of search party.
You can stream I mean it's on iTunes it's on the TBS app.
But iTunes you can watch the extended versions which are better and a little longer and funny.
And have some.
Oh you don't have to condense it to the airing stand.
Oh wow.
We have two extra minutes on the extended one.
So that's great.
Interesting.
And then its second season is also on Hulu but not the first season.
And then soon everything is going to be easier to find and it's going to be great.
And we shot the third season and we're waiting to release that.
Oh great great.
Cool.
Congrats on everything that's good.
That's great.
Cool.
And as for us we are always buying to pay well on Patreon.
Our second gauge.
Yeah check out our T public our Twitter our Facebook.
I guess write a Gmail if you want to send us an email.
We never tell people to write the reviews.
I know we got to do it anymore.
How about one with those Twitter claps.
Make a point make a real point a good point about the show.
And put those Twitter claps in there.
Yeah please.
So yeah dude let's get like they've been stagnant.
People say that matters getting those reviews.
So we hear.
Let's hear.
I mean I don't know that that's actually real.
I'd like to see the way that it benefits us.
I think the idea is that when we get a review on Twitter and it's like five stars that shoots
us up in those charts.
But I don't know who looks at those charts of like the top 20.
Anyway that's what people say.
So we have to follow.
We'd like to listen.
So we like to follow orders.
So to please help us get out of the six hundreds.
I don't know maybe is that we're in.
That's pretty good.
We're very lucky.
But for inflation we're more our podcast is more popular than Dr. Shabak.
Well that's a fact.
Yeah.
All right.
Hey I'll do it.
Thanks for listening.
Like we'll find a way.
And yeah yeah yeah.
Yeah goodbye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Brett Boehm Joe Sillio and Alex
Ramsey engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts dot com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple podcast Spotify or wherever you get your podcast.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.