Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
hosted by three guys who have finally recovered
from their T23 weekend hangovers.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
And Mike Carlson.
Yep.
Oh, wild.
Oh my God, I'll never forget having a beer and a half,
you know, 100 feet away from who might've been Joe Roady.
Friggin' wild, dude.
I didn't have any alcohol on Saturday, I realized.
I should have, I guess, but I should have loosened up,
because I felt like I was really wound up.
But that being said, I was still having a wild ass time.
Driving around Anaheim, went to Burger King before the show.
Damn, oh man, I hit up CPK, yo.
Yeah.
I went to Pizza Press, connected to the hotel.
You had.
It was crazy, man.
I thought, I ordered a six ounce pour,
but then the waiter, because it was coming a little late,
he just gave me the nine for free.
Whoa, free nine.
Yeah, yeah.
Wow.
And then I cut it off after six,
because we had a show to do, and I gave Aaron the other three.
But nonetheless, I could've gotten three ounces more of wild.
Whoa, that is wild.
I wasn't drinking, because I was still getting over a case
of the Phase Four Heebie-Jeebies.
The Marvel Phase Four?
The Marvel Phase Four.
Oh, I see.
The Willys, the Gooseys.
From Comic-Con Phase Four?
No, they were talking about Phase Four at D23.
But they didn't have one division.
No, but they had it on the big screen, it said Phase Four.
I saw, so you were like.
Just seeing the words gave you Heebie-Jeebies.
Yes.
So you didn't get a flare up at Comic-Con when it was announced,
you just had it happen when it was D23.
No, I was dealing with damp bedding at Comic-Con.
Oh, right, right, right.
Yeah, you had your whole other thing.
Different problem.
Yeah.
I mean, it was a weekend just full of amazing timeline charts.
I mean, just to finally understand how Star Wars works.
Yeah.
That there was the age of Darth Maul,
there was the age of the Plagueis and the age of, you know,
the Han looking cool and the age of whatever it is now,
the age of the Hinged Lightsaber.
Did you see that?
There was some like chart because they had to explain
where Mandalorian lands.
Right.
I mean, it's a little helpful,
but it's so funny that we're in,
well, it's between Return of the Jedi and Force Awakens.
Oh, okay.
It bridges those.
Yes, that's an era that hasn't been bridged yet.
It's explored except in like three dozen novels
that are not canon.
But are also now being canon again slowly.
Because people like them and pay for them.
Maybe they shouldn't have been so mean to all that stuff
because it really put the pressure on the new ones.
Yeah, yes, I did see that.
They couldn't fit it all into one picture.
So it looked like there was like these branches
coming off of it.
I, as a comic fan, I'm used to stuff like that
on a page maybe listed.
There's the current X-Men comic.
Jonathan Hickman has like maybe 10 charts per issue
of like what happened in the timeline.
And I won't spoil it.
But it is funny to feel like you have to show that
and to feel like that even reads well in an arena
or wherever they're showing it.
In the X-Men comic, it's good.
And X-Men famously convoluted continuity.
So like I would actually feel okay giving these to someone
because they are kind of self-contained
and self-explanatory.
I'm a fan of charts.
I always said Back to the Future 2 is my favorite movie
because it gets so confusing.
A character has to make a chart for you in the middle.
But I do think it's funny where like now we gather
in arenas to cheer for charts
and brand alliance announcements.
What we're doing here today, by the way,
so we have our own confusing timeline.
We're doing this, having recorded our live episode
this past Saturday night near D23 with Jenny Nicholson
and you the listener who weren't there,
we'll be hearing that this upcoming Friday.
And it was a great time.
It was a weird time I might say, but a lot of fun.
We made some earth shattering announcements
about our own show and some extremely incorrect predictions
about D23.
I don't think we were that incorrect.
I was incorrect about one major thing.
I guess I can reveal that's not that such a spoiler
to feel like people are gonna go,
oh, what was he incorrect about?
I can't wait till Friday.
The only thing I was incorrect, I think about was Avengers.
Yeah, that they wouldn't announce the Avengers ride.
The bulk of this episode will be
about the parks announcements.
Yes, which we recorded our live show before that.
We were just guessing, but now it's happened.
And Scott and I were awake and live tweeting it
as people were live streaming it.
We got to watch it from the comfort of our own homes.
Mike, you woke up with about half an hour.
I actually woke up,
Lizzy took the dog out in the morning on the Sunday.
So I got to sleep in, which was nice.
Yeah, cause I had to catch up.
But so yeah, I came in halfway
and then I was scrubbing through the live stream.
And like I saw Bob Chapek talking about
Runaway Railway and stuff.
You didn't feel the electricity emanating from like
Gizmo Gerald's live stream
when Bullseye the Target Dog came out.
Was that the actual name of the man?
No, I forget the name.
The name wasn't that bad.
It's rare you get to be part of an in-mass experience,
like the finale of MASH or the Super Bowl
or the finale of Breaking Bad or something.
And that's how, I know you watched Bullseye
the Target Dog come out later,
but it just wasn't the same as having watched it
20 minutes prior as it happened live.
Yeah, I know, I hear that.
You're always gonna be at a little bit of a deficit.
Yeah, no, that's true.
There'll be a little piece of my life
that's not as complete as yours.
Yeah, it's also a little sad we weren't there
to get the $10 gift card.
That was my big regret.
Right, yeah, I assure you.
We could have, oof, we could have cleaned up with that.
Cleaned up.
So I don't wanna get too ahead of myself or ourselves,
but why was that at the Parks panel?
Okay, I will tell you why.
Because Parks falls under consumer products now.
Oh, so the, oh, oh man.
Consumer products and experiences,
including the experience of tiny little Disney stores
coming to Target's throughout the country.
You know what, fine with that,
but I just don't want it in my Parks panel.
It was oddly corporate for something that you're turning,
you're tuning in to see if they're gonna build a panel
or if they're gonna build a pavilion of Brazil
or Disneyland India, some of the crazy things.
That was a rumor, yes.
Rumored about and then you instead get,
and now ladies and gentlemen, the CEO of Target.
It's like, why wasn't that just a press release?
Who was excited, who was so jacked up about that?
I marked out when the dog came out.
Sure. I will say.
Because it was, Bullseye had the red, yeah, the red.
They painted a real dog with the Bullseye.
They did, they defaced a dog.
Ladies and gentlemen, a defaced dog.
And because I will say before that, it was a lot,
besides some new footage from within Rise of the Resistance,
which I feel like is just different footage
from a different angle,
similar footage from a different angle,
it was a lot of stuff of them saying,
here's some stuff that already opened.
I did see, I saw a little bit of that trailer
and I had to turn it off because I did see a scene in there
that I didn't know was in there.
Yep, I didn't wanna know, I didn't look at it.
Good, that's good, because there was a thing that happened
and I was like, oh shit, that's awesome.
I didn't know that was in there.
And then I turned it off so I didn't see anything else.
I kind of forgot a lot of it.
I was still, I was awake but kind of grounded.
I was still tired from the show.
That's the cool effect that I think they're gonna do.
Yeah, I agree.
Carly Weisel tweeting today,
she went to a Star Wars thing
in some press event in Florida
and she, I think, got a walkthrough of Rise of the Resistance
and said, this will absolutely change
your perception of Galaxy's Edge.
Sure. She seems to be supporting
that any odd deflation or disappointment
that anybody's feeling will be corrected
by Rise of the Resistance.
Did she go through the whole thing this time?
Because when we were interviewing her,
she said she just walked through the first part of it.
Did it seem like she's actually walked the whole thing now?
I don't know that, can't tell you.
They were a little further along on it in Florida
because they didn't have to rip out the sensors.
Right, they didn't have to, yeah.
So I wonder if she got to,
because I think before she got to go
into the main hangar area with the loading,
I think she got up to the loading
when their actual trackless ride begins.
So I wonder, we'll ask her.
She's at the opening right now
for Galaxy's Edge in Orlando.
We hope they can get this thing working.
That's the main issue, I would say, yes.
Well, why don't we, while we're talking Star,
let's bang out all the Star Wars crap first.
Sure.
Rise of the Resistance coming,
showed a little extra footage,
showed kind of a too long montage of people saying
they like Galaxy's Edge.
Yeah.
Which, yeah, people do like it.
There was a lot of, this is,
we shouldn't get into other parts of it,
but the Star Wars, they showed a minute of Star Wars,
you reference the double lightsaber with Rey,
evil Rey or whatever.
But they show like a minute and a half of the old Star Wars
and you're like, yeah, okay.
But, I guess we know.
But it's all like, hey, remember this, you like this.
It also really illustrates how these are not one story
because they're just so aesthetically,
radically aesthetically different.
So putting Samuel L. Jackson next to Princess Leia
next to the new stuff next to the Hugs,
it's just not one thing at all.
I'm just saying it feels a little,
both of these moves feel a little bit insecure
with Galaxy's Edge.
We love Galaxy's Edge.
It's like, yeah, fine, just show us the ride.
It's fine.
I'm excited you and McGregor's coming back.
Yes. Sure.
Yeah.
I'm on board for that.
Okay, yeah, me too.
What, what other, oh, the Galactic Star Cruiser.
Oh yes, we gotta talk about it.
The inclusive hotel.
Galactic Cruiser, there's no star in that title.
Are you sure?
You seem very thrown by this.
Yeah, well.
It's not, it wouldn't be called
Star Wars Galactic Star Cruiser.
That's too many stars.
I think it might be.
Oh boy, all right, it's on.
But is it called, is that the official name
that Disney's calling it?
And then in the canon, it's a Star Cruiser?
I'm proud potentially.
Cause the Star Cruiser in Star Wars is real, I think.
So basically what it is, what I understand,
it's like now they're like presenting it
as like it's a cruise ship in space.
Yes, apparently.
Yes.
Which I do think is better
than what I was thinking where it was like
a very cold transport that you were just on for two days.
Like a cold, like alien, you were on the ship from Alien.
And you're meant to imagine that every time.
In this world, every time.
In fact, that is the headline of CNN Travels articles.
Is a cruise ship in space.
Disney Star Wars Hotel is a cruise ship in space.
Right.
It's pretty fun.
I like that.
It's a really fun idea.
I still am worried people are gonna freak out
and have like madness from not being able
to see a window for two days.
That was my concern, yeah.
Can they give you the option to step outside of?
That would be a thing.
A port day at Galaxy's Edge.
Right, so you do leave for a little bit,
but it's a two day experience.
But I mean, can the screen,
like can you have a space or not?
That's an ops question.
Yeah.
Where they must,
cause I don't think the screen though
is a window behind it.
You know what I mean?
I don't think, unless they're gonna have the option
where it turns off.
Disneyworld.go.com,
Star Wars colon galactic star cruiser
at Disney World Resort.
Really?
A two night all inclusive.
Ah, all right.
Yeah.
You know what?
I copied it from something that was wrong then.
Galactic cruiser.
I kind of read a bunch of articles
just cause every now and then one would mention a detail
that another one missed.
Like I was trying to find this off this topic,
but like Mary Poppins, the attraction,
I think you go through the front door of the bank's house,
which I only saw one place mention that,
but I think was in the presentation.
That I think could be.
Nothing about the ride isn't.
No, nothing at all.
No one knows anything.
That is called, that's called galactic umbrella cruiser.
We do know that.
Yes.
That's true.
There's a consistency.
Yes.
Like, God, everything's named the same way now.
Well, hey, congrats to you.
Apologies for either.
Oh, that's okay.
A victory for Jason.
I don't, so I was on Blue Loop,
the themed entertainment industry kind of trade magazine.
They were quoting our past guest, Lynn Testa,
as this for a family of four,
this two night experience will cost $2,500.
Which if that includes.
All of, for everyone?
Yeah, which I was trying to break down.
If that includes food and lodging and the experiences
and a park ticket.
Why do we think it's food?
It's not bad.
What's the indication of food?
Because they said,
because they were saying the buffet,
like breakfast, lunch, and sit down dinners,
if it's all inclusive, like a cruise ship,
food is included.
Okay.
So maybe.
Again, I'm sure like liquor is probably an add on.
That's how it works on cruise.
Again, if this is being the cruise ship model on land,
stuff is included and then there's plus up add ons.
Do you get bands past their prime?
Do you get a modal nodes tribute bands
of like sadder fatter?
Well, like a, but like a max,
yeah, max Rebo band tribute.
Yeah.
Dressed as max Rebo.
But the max Rebo experience.
Oh, I know it's a female max Rebo tribute band
called max Shebo.
Pretty good.
Yeah. I don't know.
They haven't mentioned the bands yet in the press release.
And it's not a true cruise ship experience to me,
unless you got a zip line
and you got and all you can eat Ronto.
If it should be like a gross pile of Ronto that's right.
Like the little miss colored, like, I don't know.
This isn't prime Ronto.
Right. And then like for certain weeks,
it'll be like a singles cruise.
And like you can't have families there.
It's a hookup.
It's a hookup on the spaceship type of a situation.
There's a rumor that the velvet sessions,
which are the intimate performances by bands done
in the hard rock hotel lobby at Universal
will be moving to collect.
That's a lot of info in one sentence.
I actually didn't know.
I have been there.
So I was, I must've told this story.
Well, I was there like when I was in college,
but like under 21, too young to go and the fix played.
And my dad's like, Oh, tutoring center.
I'm going to go to this.
You guys just go to the park.
And then when I was there two years ago in 2017,
the velvet session that night was the fix.
So. And your dad was a member.
Yeah.
He joined the band without you knowing.
This guy seems cool.
Does indeed lead to another.
The first time I was there was around the time
Grand Theft Auto of like city was big.
And that song is in that nonstop.
Oh, sure.
Very exciting.
Yeah.
Some good go West in there too.
Stan go West.
There's a, on the star cruise, the star cruiser,
they have like, I saw it.
So they have like a room for kids to play in,
but it looks like just sort of a cargo bay area.
Okay.
Where they crawl in vents.
Oh yeah.
Which like on one hand, I'm like, that's cool.
But also like, it doesn't look that big.
We'll see.
I don't, we don't know what it looks like for real.
Mom, I want to go back to the boiler room.
It does look, actually that's a better way to describe it.
It does look like the boiler room.
And it looks like kids are like climbing in the vents,
which I guess I liked the idea of climbing in the vents
as a kid.
And then there's a room where you go in the captain,
you go in the bridge and like, I guess an attack happens
and you got to like go and press buttons or something,
which is cool.
My, my, here's my two concerns.
Number one, somebody's-
People think it's weird if when you go by yourself
and without children.
That's way down the list of concerns, honestly,
for this specifically.
Yeah, I don't think you're the only one with this problem.
This will be less down like to 15 or 16 concern.
Is that the, first of all, somebody will go mad
from not seeing the sun.
Space madness.
Yeah.
And then two is that like the families are not gonna
want to do it.
Families, if they do it, they're gonna hate it
because they're like stuck in this weird building
and there's too many themed experiences.
And it doesn't look like this is,
this is a controversial thing.
I think I said a day or two ago, I said,
I think that an Avatar hotel would be a more sure bet
than a Star Wars hotel, not because of the IP,
but because Avatar aesthetically is so pleasing.
People like the hallelujah mountains.
They like the colors.
If you could see.
I love being in a screensaver.
Yes.
If I could just live in a screensaver
for two days straight.
I think a sure bet is like, if you could see
the mountains outside the window
and you were sort of being taken care of by the Navi
and it's a very like a spa kind of a thing,
that to me, I was like, mom and dad who don't care maybe
about the IP as much, that would be a slam dunk.
I think the Star Wars is a little cold.
What percentage do I disagree with you?
120%?
No, I think that I'm just saying like,
if you look at it without the IP,
what are mom and dad gonna like better?
The one where it's like this kind of earthy thing,
very beautiful or this kind of cold spacecraft
with some kiddy, like fun kid stuff
when they can't see out the window and there's no sunlight.
I think I agree with both of you.
Scott, I don't think you're wrong.
I think Mike, there is some truth in what you were saying
because just comparing like what they've done
with what I've seen of Avatar and Animal
Kingdom, it's a lot of lush greenery, a lot of foliage.
More like a resort is already.
Yeah, but just seeing pictures of that,
I find it pleasing in the same way that like a lot
of the new Epcot landscape architecture,
multi-level parks, I'm like, if you just fill this
with like a glut of green space, I'm into that.
I'm actually into that.
I guess I am too.
As I'm parsing what Mike was saying,
maybe where I depart is being taken care of by the Navi.
Well, that's just a fun.
Are they craving you like a baby?
That's just a fun extra little add on.
They don't have to necessarily take care of it.
I mean, I don't need a massage from a Navi.
I picture these berries.
I like that.
I mean, I like them telling me they have berries for me.
Do the employees have to be?
There could be some humans,
but there has to be some sort of Navi experience.
I'm just saying.
A tuck-in experience?
The big like banana leaf blanket.
Can they even, are they even?
They're so tall, aren't they?
I was gonna say they're so tall.
Is it gonna be hard for them to get in the room?
Well, then maybe they're gonna build all the rooms
like 11 feet high.
Yeah.
Or how big are they?
15 feet?
How tall are they?
I'm not sure.
I'm just saying, yeah, maybe the, look,
it doesn't have to be fully everyone's dressed up as a Navi.
I'm just saying, I think that my concern is,
is that if you just take the,
if you took the Star Wars out of it,
all these experiences better be like crazy cool.
They better be so next level cool.
Because kids are gonna break down,
like I wanna go to the Magic Kingdom.
It's like, well, no, we're on the Galactic Star Cruise.
Yeah, cause it's like.
For another.
But you can't, they're not gonna make you stay,
just you're paying for it.
Yeah.
But will there be bus service?
Well, it's weird, cause it's a whole.
I think so.
I mean, you're wearing clothes.
They give you clothes.
Like Star Wars clothes.
It's a whole narrative thing.
They say like you get in with, it's like a cruise.
You get in with the same group of people
and then you all leave at the same time.
And then they take.
You have to coordinate?
That's what it sounds like.
All guests will, again, cruise ship rules apply.
So all guests will board at the same time.
It's a little claustrophobic.
I assume there has to be a way to get out.
There has to be.
They wouldn't do that to you.
But.
It's not a Logan's Run scenario.
You don't get like electrocuted upon your attempt to exit.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
I don't think.
We have a runner.
It's possible.
It's possible you get electrocuted if you leave.
One of my sons got sniped.
Stormtroopers like leave that turkey like at the door.
Sith trooper.
I'm just saying all of that stuff to me sounds
a little bit like you're a little bit too regimented.
And then the experience itself better be.
You're in a war.
You're in a literal.
Yeah.
I think, well, I think it's people will put it
at the start or end of their.
Right.
Disney World stay.
It won't be in lieu of it.
It'll be at the end of their lives when they go insane
and kill their entire family.
But like parents who don't like Star Wars
aren't gonna wanna go back.
Cause like dad at night is just gonna be,
can we go to the beach?
Can I sit on the beach with a drink?
Well, they said different levels,
different levels of commitment or immersion.
Sure.
So you'll be able to customize that.
Right onto the beach with a beer.
Like again, at a cruise ship,
you pick what restaurant on board.
You want to be your dinner restaurant
or you pick whether you drink or not.
If it was that enterprise hotel,
I think that's a different story.
The Star Trek thing that we're gonna build in Vegas.
Cause the enterprise I think is a much warmer situation,
much warmer place.
And then going on that bridge, that's an iconic bridge.
That's a little bit more fun.
There's a little bit more like recognition there.
So I'm just saying that might be a little bit
of a different story.
But I'm still-
So you wouldn't have wanted to leave the Star Trek bridge.
Well, as a child,
I fantasized about living on the enterprise D.
So no, I would not have wanted to leave.
As long as all these experiences line up to your taste,
which is very Avatar centric.
This Star Cruiser does,
your experience does end with Admiral Hodo
suicide lightspeed into a-
You're yelling at her, what is your plan?
And she's like, yeah, I don't need to tell you.
And then she kills, she kills herself on the ship.
You're the finest actress of your generation.
You're wasted standing behind consoles.
She goes on to blaze of glory.
Yeah.
That was cool.
Sure.
So we'll see, I wanna do it.
Don't get me wrong.
I wanna do it.
I'm just interested to see what happens.
Cause they want, this is expensive and-
Very, they're heading into Westworld territory.
Yeah.
With the costumes.
So yeah, I'm just interested to see what happens.
And those are my two main concerns.
Yeah.
Space madness.
And it's a little bit not fun.
There's gonna be shinings happening every day.
Yes.
Many, many dads going and talking to ghost bartenders,
force ghost bartenders.
Yeah.
I think that's possible.
Paintings on the wall and it'll be nothing but out of time.
Frozen in the painting now.
A hundred insane dads in this tableau.
The Imagineers are actually designing the hotel.
So when you look at furniture,
look away and look back, it's moved slightly.
Little drones unsettlingly in every room,
moving chairs just a little bit.
But for a nod, there is a lot of Minotaur imagery
everywhere.
That they didn't change.
That they're just like, this is for Stanley.
We love Stanley.
An incredible technology to clean up
elevator blood hourly.
Blue elevator blood.
Just don't stay in room 237 on this cruise ship
is what we're saying.
Just avoid that room.
Okay.
Should we go on to the thing
that we all probably care about the most?
Epcot?
Sure.
Yeah, all right.
You think that's what we all care about the most?
It is.
And yet nothing in this block of news super excited me.
Except that I love the sort of new, old Epcot aesthetic
that they're playing with.
They're embracing those awesome little emblems
that our logo is based on.
I like the new logo of the park in general.
I like it because it points the way to a Tomorrowland
that just is 80s future.
Because why have we overshot it?
That was the future.
It always was.
And Epcot seems to be embracing it.
Well, so Epcot, someone pointed out online,
it kind of made me sad.
It's like, well, we lost Future World.
So they're dividing Future World into three neighborhoods.
World Nature, World Discovery, World Celebration,
World Showcase stays the same.
And in fact, that's what inspired
these new namings clearly.
Now we were, Jason, you and I were talking yesterday,
this naming device gives me a headache
because World Showcase is because you go
and visit places in the world.
Yes, and World Fair was copyrighted probably.
Sure. They couldn't use it.
But then World Nature is where, it's like, okay,
World Showcase, the theme part is the first word.
Right.
World Nature, the theme park is the,
the theme word is the second word.
So Showcase, what does Showcase have to do
with seeing Germany and Canada?
Right.
It's retroactively made the original name make no sense.
You know, right? Yes.
Well, I mean, it's kind of like how it doesn't make sense.
Pixar Pier has a Ferris wheel with a giant Mickey on it.
Sure.
But people like that and they don't want that to change.
Yeah.
So that just stays as is.
It's just like a complication that you just have to deal with.
I think I'd just rather be Discovery World,
Celebration World, Nature World.
Yeah, list, okay, list them again.
World Nature?
Huh? World Nature.
List them again for me.
World Nature.
I'll break it down to World Nature
is the land and the seas.
Right.
Pavilions.
World Discovery is test track mission space
and Guardians of the Galaxy, colon, cosmic rewind.
World Celebration is new.
It's the entryway and spaceship earth
and that three tiered park sort of thing.
I like that.
There's a park, yeah, there's a park on top of a building now.
And there's like a beer garden on top of it or something.
Something like that.
I think that's where they'll have a lot of the festival stuff,
but like green space and you'll be able,
it'll give you views of the park.
Yeah, the green space is in World Celebration,
not World Nature, get out of here with your green space.
That does not, that has no place in World Nature.
The content art of the Play Pavilion
has a lot of greenery around the entrance.
I'm for all this greenery
because it's better than beige clay or beige cement.
Now Play sounds like celebrating to me.
Is that in World Celebration?
No, it's in World Discovery, idiot.
Play is discovery.
Get it through your thick skull.
The world thing also just makes everything like,
it doesn't differentiate the two parts anymore.
No.
What it does is it makes it so Future World
does not have to try to outrace the actual impending future.
Right, I get why Future is gone.
I agree with Sky, it's weird that everything
is branded World.
World Celebration, where a big space orb is.
It still is Futuri.
They haven't, it's not like they've lost that.
Well, but yeah, it is Futuri,
they're changing Spaceship Earth, I just read.
Yeah.
Yes, it is no longer about the history of communication,
it's about the history of storytelling.
Does Disney like storytelling?
I say throwing my head against a wall.
Yeah, but they're gonna keep some scenes.
By the way, whatever we're about to goof on,
I'm sure it'll be great.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
It's an original IP ride, at least.
But there might be characters.
Oh, is that what they're saying?
In the storytelling, yeah, there might be some characters
in there.
And the spirit of storytelling will guide you.
There's a great character, the spirit of storytelling.
There's a little.
Who is a light.
Right, right, right, right.
Who you follow.
There's a little light.
I think there's something, there's like some kind of like,
weird like color bat.
There's like a, is the spirit just an abstract light?
I remember seeing some footage that had some like,
more winged creature.
Almost like a little more avatar-y.
I didn't see that.
I could see the spirit of storytelling transformed
just as it transformed throughout the ages.
Ah, good, yes, and took different forms
to inspire different storytellers.
Now, I think the majority of the forms will be like,
when a regional theater, a community theater,
does Peter Pan and puts a kind of rigged up camping lantern
to be Tinker Bell hanging from the ceiling.
A slightly expanding and compressing light.
The most technologically advanced Tinker Bell light dot
will guide you through Spaceship Earth now.
So it's.
And Josh Gad is replacing Judi Dench.
So we'll all off be on this ride too.
We're floating on a spaceship.
We're little floaty boys.
It's called, it's called Spaceship Earth still.
Press and roll around the hot dog for a dinner
everyone will enjoy.
Is that the Pillsbury Dole Boy?
Yeah, that's the Pillsbury.
Nothing.
He's also the Pillsbury Dole Boy.
I'm also the Dole Boy.
So, but it's still called,
it's not called Storyship Earth.
No, it's still called Spaceship Earth.
Still called Spaceship Earth.
Yes, it's Spaceship Earth,
which is always about the history of communication.
Space-ship Earth, the communication ride.
Now it's the story ride.
It's very easy.
I mean, I guess, I guess that didn't make any sense either.
It's probably fine.
They're clearly keeping like the,
thank the Phoenicians and like something else.
But is that the storytelling?
You call that scene, thank the Phoenicians.
Thank the Phoenicians.
That's the thing I just say.
They sell a lot of merchandise that says,
thank the Phoenicians.
When I'm relieved.
I'm not kidding.
Really?
Wait, yeah.
That scene where it's like,
if you can read, thank the Phoenician.
That's a phoenician.
That scene.
Oh, okay.
They have started branding that.
Branding that, yeah, merchandising that.
I don't know if the like Steve Jobs garage
will still be there.
You know, that was a newer edition.
Wanna get beat up when you go back to school?
Wear a thank the Phoenicians t-shirt.
I'm looking up, thank the Phoenicians t-shirt.
I wanna find it.
This is crazy.
I see a, okay, so thank the Phoenicians t-shirt.
Oh, it's Phoenicians, not Phoenicians.
No, it's pH, right?
Don't you pronounce that?
Phoenicians?
Phoenicians.
Okay, yeah, okay.
So P-H-E-I'm out of it.
I do not have a spaceship.
Oh, not people of Venice.
Oh, I was confused.
I was confused.
Phoenicians.
I see.
It's where phonetic.
Right, right, I know that.
I thought you meant Venetians.
Do you like phonetic language?
Yeah.
Thank the Phoenicians.
I see like a lot of teespring, T-Public things.
Is it official merch?
I think they, I mean, there's definitely unofficial merch,
but I feel like I saw at Disney official merch.
I see like Redbubble, I see Etsy,
but I don't see an official one.
Wow.
All right, well, we'll get to, we'll really.
People have an affection for that.
Can we steal it?
Can we make our own?
Yeah.
Yeah, why not?
Yeah, whatever.
So Michelangelo painting the Sistine Chapel,
that was, is that storytelling?
Probably, yeah.
It counts as both communication and storytelling.
So at a certain point,
it's just gonna switch over though to like, and then.
Some narration changes, probably some projection effects.
And then it'll just be.
Maybe Moana shows up.
That's what I was gonna say,
like is Moana to show up or something?
Cause like, it's gonna be a hard split
between old ass animatronics
that we're talking about communication
versus all of a sudden now we're talking about Disney.
Well, Captain Jack Sparrow's been.
They'll move Captain Jack Sparrow in there
and they'll build robots of, you know,
people who've told stories for Disney,
like the lost guys, like Carlton.
Cruise.
Cruise, there'll be a robot of Carlton Cruise.
Oh, okay.
Is he the legend Jack Kirby?
Yes, yeah.
A person who had never worked for Disney, Jack Kirby,
will be in Spaceship Earth.
Yeah, that was a weird one.
Is it gonna dismay,
are they just gonna project the characters
on the, at the end of the.
The ending is kind of like going back to Earth,
quote unquote.
That is kind of just a room with like,
pink gong ball lights in it.
Which is fun, but I mean like,
is that gonna be the time when,
cause there's the big glorious finale to Spaceship Earth,
which is like both cool and underwhelming.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, it's like.
They pump in cool music to make you,
it's like cool at first,
and then you got like six minutes to go.
Yeah, because.
Winding down.
Cause you can see then,
you're finally, you're at the top of the, of the ball,
and you can see how big it is,
and you're inside it,
and it's really cool, and the music's cool,
and there's some cool like lasers,
but then it's like, there's not much going on.
So now is it gonna be like,
Will Smith Genie projected on the inside of the ball,
or something.
Genie.
A montage of all your favorite IP.
That seems like the room that could easily be plused up.
Yeah, I think I read somewhere that that was a big,
yeah, they're gonna really,
that's gonna be a lot different.
It'll be Jon Favreau explaining
why the photorealistic animals.
Just a junket interview.
Right.
For four minutes.
And they can sub out different junkets
with different movies he's remade.
Oh.
So that'll be good.
It can always tribute Favreau's newest realistic film.
Yeah, so that'll be nice.
I love Space Your Birth,
so I'm excited for a little refresh.
Yeah, I'm sad it'll be closed for a while
to get all this stuff in.
Cause I like it.
We'll get to go on it though, right?
We'll go on it.
Before?
I hope so.
Yeah, and we'll get to see that Epcot Forever show.
Epcot Forever, I'm psyched to see that.
That's gonna be a short-lived show,
but it's got all the classic music in it.
Oh, that's cool.
And then they're gonna replace it with.
And the logos, like projected.
And that's over the lagoon.
Over the lagoon.
I'll wait for this show.
This is a show I will watch.
That's like the only show.
Yeah.
We might have a day, when we're in Orlando,
we might have a day we're at Epcot
for like 16 hours or something.
Yeah, I was thinking about our upcoming trip.
Like, what do I need?
What are the big new attractions I need to see?
And Epcot doesn't even really have one,
but I'm like, but I need to.
What's, oh, Frozen.
Frozen.
Oh, true, I'm not frozen yet.
Yeah.
Cause you haven't seen Diagon yet, have you?
Nope.
No.
And I haven't seen Avatar.
Yeah.
We both haven't seen Avatar.
Right, right.
I'm gonna be kind.
I feel like it's gonna be a speed run.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we're gonna have to jam a lot.
I can only stay like six days.
You guys should stay two weeks.
I've been many times in the last two years.
Sorry, we haven't done our homework.
I'm just saying for your fun.
I'm not chastising you.
My stay is dependent on how aggressive
Dunkin' Donuts is marketing their SIPPEO Win contest.
Well, let's put that out to the listeners.
They tell Dunkin' you love this contest
and you wanna see more of the commercials.
Keep this contest going.
Jason's in an ad is what we're talking about.
Yeah.
Yay, it's good.
It's a funny ad.
Well, what won't be there
and we'll have to make a return trip just for this
is to visit the most exciting new area, Dreamers Point.
Well, overlooking the lagoon where you get to sit
maybe next to a new statue of Walt
who is casually sitting and looking.
Yes, Casual Walt is what he's referring to.
Casual Walt is really the biggest takeaway
from the panel.
It was fun watching a feed of that
streaming live on YouTube in here
and with a new Walt statue and somebody going, yeah.
There was one yeah like that.
What about me?
There was one yeah like that for a lot of the announcements.
Single, yeah.
One single, but different people.
Like it struck a chord with one person in the audience.
It was like, yeah.
Someone collated all the tweets where someone said
like they searched the term Walt statue crying
and just people going new Walt statue, I'm crying.
And I'm like, oh, I don't know.
I think he's a lot more complicated of a figure than that.
I think it was an interesting man who did a lot of good.
But there was some weird stuff.
Well, but also regardless of that, it's a statue.
Yeah, it's a statue.
Yeah, yeah.
They bring him back to life.
You don't have to like relitigate his past sins.
It's a statue.
Yeah, yeah.
It's an odd thing to make you cry.
I think you're like ready to cry at almost anything
if you're crying.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
These aren't people who are,
this is their only cry in 10 years.
Yeah.
I think I think there's maybe a lot of tears.
They also, it's a good point.
They also, it's definitely like,
it's the most made for a photo op statue they've ever done.
It's a really Instagramable.
Cause I assume it looks like you can go sit next to him.
You can chill with Walt.
I would assume that is the idea.
So like they'll, it's like a tribute to him,
but also like it's going to be great for our Instagram.
It's going to be great for promoting Epcot.
People with like used car dealerships,
they're going to be trying to get the t-shirt logo,
like get a t-shirt on it, like take a picture,
take a picture with the logo.
Walt statues wear the logo for my used boat dealership.
No, but with this, you can like, you can put a hat on him.
Good point.
You can dress him.
If you have a watch brand you're promoting.
If you have a knockoff fit bit that you're hogging.
You can get it on him.
You can't get his arms, his statue arms
through this shirt though.
Well, that's tough.
Well, you could, anything that zips up from the back.
Cause then you could put a vest.
You could put like a vest on him,
but you could put a vest on the one in California Adventure.
That's true.
Should we try to put a vest on him?
Yeah, no, we've never tried in all our times there.
We've never tried to put clothes on Walt.
Cause you can walk right up to that thing.
It's not like the one in Disneyland.
Yes.
That's guarded by an armada of characters.
Right.
He's got attack, he's got his attack dog, Pluto
and his attack chip, monks, Chippendale.
I'm just saying people are bringing props.
Maybe.
People like space mountain people
or splash mountain for the picture.
People will bring props.
You're announcing this is a new like meme area.
This will be memed.
Yeah.
That's interesting.
I'm calling it now.
I like it.
Yeah.
We're wristbands.
You could put like, I guess you probably
can't get under the legs.
I was going to say leg warmers,
but you could put like kind of aerobics arm bands on him.
Yeah.
What if you give him like a Ninja turtle mask
and the belt and the weapons.
We could do that to the California Adventure one too.
Yeah.
We should do it.
We should go to Oogie Boogie's bash,
get a little drunk and then start putting
the Ninja turtle outfit onto Walt in the statue.
The wildest night of Mike's life.
Yeah.
This is what I'm talking about.
This is me being bad.
Cause it'll be Halloween though.
Cause it'll be fun.
Yeah.
You know, cause Walt's dressed up too.
You know who would endorse that idea?
Oogie Boogie.
He likes mischiefs.
He loves chaos.
He's made of bugs.
So I'll say this.
New dress up Walt.
Or do we, I was just going to say this Epcot picture I love.
Yeah.
There's some great concept art.
Very like, yeah.
The spaceship earth has new colors on it.
There's a prism of colors.
There's a lot of sparkles.
The new fountain looks cool.
And new olds, the, the, the embracing of that old,
like updating that new Epcot.
It's painted in the seventies, early eighties,
like marketing style.
Yes.
Which all that concept art is nuts.
For sure. Epcot is going to look nice.
It was a little low on announcements of like crazy new, big,
like, Oh, a mission space that doesn't hurt you.
Like they didn't announce that that's still going to be there.
I guess.
A lot of word salad, story telling,
harmonious night time.
Yeah.
Like harmonious hurt my head.
Moana the journey of water,
like a water conservation sort of exhibit with splash pads.
I think Carly thought I was making fun of her saying,
are the dancing water by journey into imagination,
is that one of the most positively reviewed things at Epcot?
But I was being sincere.
Cause when I was a kid,
I would spend hours playing in those like jumping fountains.
Hours?
Like over the course of a trip,
I'd always want to go on journey to imagination and then go
like, well, can we, are we going back to the hotel soon?
Can I get a little wet at the dancing fountain?
Like, and so kids like splashing
in those a whole Moana themed one with like living water,
dancing water.
It's sort of misty.
And it's kind of misty.
Yeah. I like that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I would agree.
And we're getting a new movie at the land.
Awesome planet.
Awesome planet. Right.
I saw that.
Not to be confused with new park, epic universe,
awesome planet and epic universe.
Totally different things.
And that's going to be a fun look at our awesome planet.
Yeah.
Which I don't know in that space.
I don't know about the word fun.
I think those movies need to be as boring as possible.
Yeah, that's true.
In the history of symbiosis.
Well, Canada foreign wide 360 is coming.
Hell yeah.
How many Canada movies?
Wondrous China.
That one creeps me out.
I for one welcome our new Chinese overlords.
This is a good thing to say on the, on public record.
Sure. Yeah.
You're matching your bets.
I think we should take those, all the tariffs away.
And frankly.
Wondrous China is followed up by horrible,
misbehaving Hong Kong.
Oh yeah.
You watch a three minute film about how Hong Kong sucks.
Are they tore down our beloved facial recognition poles?
That was something.
The pride of wondrous China.
They blitz through the castle of magical dreams.
The new Hong Kong castle and like their frozen land.
They blitz through Hong Kong.
I want to hear more.
On this presentation.
I want, wait, what's the castle called?
Castle of magical dreams?
I believe so.
Yes.
The castle of magical dreams,
themed to 13 different Disney heroines.
You look cool.
It does look cool.
It looks less psychotic than the first concept art
looked so.
They should have just made it a cake.
One of these castles will be a permit cake.
Should be a cake.
Yeah. They ripped through that.
That's someone with a frozen roller coaster too.
Yes.
Which looks like a snow white.
Snow white roller coaster now.
What's that name?
Wandering Oaken's sliding sleigh.
Yes.
Wonderful.
What's supposed to be trackless originally?
They switched to the coaster.
Interesting.
Little coasters are,
they've been pretty successful in that area.
I didn't get to go on the little crush coaster
in Disney Studios Paris,
but that seemed like a lot of fun.
Yeah.
Seven dwarfs mine train's great.
I think it's a good little like, you know,
D to Z genre.
Yeah.
I don't know if you've ever been on any coaster.
Remy's Ratatouille Adventure.
Yeah. When is that open?
Coming next summer.
Next summer.
2020.
I am kind of charmed by like,
they're putting a recreation of Cherry Tree Lane
from Mary Poppins.
Yeah, that's great.
In the British Pavilion.
Total surprise.
That's probably the one that came out of nowhere.
That in the England Pavilion in Epcot,
there'll be a new Mary Poppins attraction.
Yeah. There was a rumor for a while.
People were downplaying that rumor.
I feel like some people were like,
it's going to be like nothing of a ride,
but I don't know if that's what this is.
It's unclear.
Like it'll be in a show building.
So probably more than just a carousel.
Cause that's the rumor.
That was a rumor.
It was going to be a little Mary Poppins mini-land,
but it just have like a carousel.
So hopefully this is a little bit of a step up from that.
Hopefully it's that Tony Baxter drawing
that he made in the 60s or 70s.
Also, I really liked Emily Blunt in that movie.
It was Emily Blunt, right?
Am I fucking that up?
Yeah.
However, it was Mary Poppins.
I liked Tick Van Dyke.
They wheeled that Tick Van Dyke.
So you want to ride with Emily Blunt and Dick Van Dyke.
And Dick Van Dyke.
And that's all.
You don't want Julie Andrews and you don't want Lynn.
I don't think Julie Andrews like already didn't come back
for the sequel.
I don't know that she would come back for the movie.
You don't want a portrayal.
Right, I was just saying like a portrayal.
I would love Julie Andrews.
No, I would love Julie Andrews,
but I feel like she is like,
I feel like she has kind of been like, I mean,
Well, she, I think she.
Her voice is shot.
Sorry.
Whoa, the truth is coming out of your ears
about Julie Andrews.
No, but like medically,
like she had an issue with her voice.
Isn't that right?
She can't really sing.
Yeah, she had an issue with her voice.
I'm not saying she's like washed up.
I'm saying like she has like a condition.
I didn't mean not knowing the medical issue.
It sounded like, whoa.
She cannot sing anymore.
She's very sad, but the way you said it was very funny,
especially when you're now,
you feel like you're on trial for not liking Julie Andrews.
No, I love Julie Andrews.
No, I just don't need,
I don't need Lynn telling me to have a good morning.
Like, I don't need that.
I do.
I'm so fucking sad.
And the only thing that makes me feel
is the announcement of a new Walt statue.
And I maybe won't get out of bed
unless Lynn tells me to get out of bed.
So I want the ride to be,
I start in a bed and then Lynn tells me, get up, get up.
Good morning.
Go inspire him, stunner.
You're a number one stunner today.
Kiss, kiss.
Okay, so you want Lynn and Julie Andrews on the ride.
Yes, let's do, there should be competing.
Wait.
Lynn and Julie Andrews,
Jason wants Dick Van Dyke and Emily Blunt.
I want the opposite of Jason.
This is like the Civil, Captain America Civil War poster
with half the Avengers on one side and one the other.
Two brothers, one wants Lynn and one wants Blunt.
And I want just Lynn and Dick Van Dyke.
No Mary Poppins on the ride.
I don't care for the character.
Hey, two charming chaps.
Yeah, and I want them not to be a portrayal.
I want them to record new stuff
so it's 93 year old Dick Van Dyke and 40 year old Lynn.
I mean, in reality, I just want the Admiral.
I just want.
Oh yeah, hell yeah.
Yeah, that is in the concept art.
Really realistic robot.
Oh yeah, are they gonna do the cannon?
Are they gonna do the cannon every hour?
Holy shit.
Or every 10 minutes?
I would love the cannon.
That would be incredible.
That'd be great.
I mean, I would like an animatronic Ben Wishaw
like saying, let's go fly a kite.
Like he was cocking a shotgun in a zombie movie.
Yeah.
Cocking a string, tightening it,
which makes a big loud sound.
Emily Mortimer also kind of underutilized in that movie.
Yeah, it doesn't have a lot to do.
A wonderful actress.
I never saw the new movie,
but a couple of people sent me the clip of Lin-Manuel
singing like, I'm such a lucky guy.
Look, the song is good.
It's still, he has a breakdown.
It's like a British music hall song.
I don't know.
Mark Shaman writes a new song every hour of the day.
I want.
I want Paul.
I want Ed Wynn to be in the ride.
Love to laugh sequence.
That would be great.
That would be good.
But will we have the newer version of the character?
Topsy?
Meryl Streep's famous character, Topsy.
Oof.
I'm unfamiliar.
From maybe the worst scene in the movie.
Jason is laughing more than a third.
This might be the hardest ever to last on the show.
Remembering Meryl Streep's character named Topsy.
And what scene?
The song is called Turning Turtle.
Yeah, it's just like another, they're just trying.
I see it.
Can we get a little snippet of it?
Well, I honestly, I don't remember the tune at all.
Lucky turtle.
I don't remember the tune at all.
It's just, I actually enjoy the movie,
but there's like a lot of,
there's too many callbacks to things.
And then this is clearly like turning things upside down,
which is very similar to being on the ceiling.
Is Topsy the uncle's widow or something?
It's unclear.
It's not really, it's kind of.
Let me play.
It's a spiritual heir.
It's kind of like.
His friend from the crazy house.
Right, I don't think that's at all referenced,
but I can't remember.
It's confusing on the level of the Ghostbusters
answer the call cameos.
Yeah, who is, why is there another Dan Aykroyd
in this world?
Was there another Bill Murray?
Only Sigourney Weaver one,
to me was really satisfying in terms of cameos.
This is a foreign version of turning turtle.
Here's the real version.
What exactly does that mean?
It means my whole world.
That's Meryl Streep.
Goes flippity flop like a turtle on its back.
And I don't know, my up from my down,
my east from my vest, my topsy from my bottomsy.
If you ring me something broken on a Thursday.
She's doing the voice of any time a fortune teller
character shows up on The Simpsons.
This is going to be based on a song, I think.
Children's Saturday, Sunday, Monday.
Does she deserve an Oscar for this?
Of course, always.
Do I like it?
Maybe not.
Every second Wednesday.
Easy.
I mean, you get the gist of it.
I sure do.
Anyway, so Topsy is on the ride, I think.
You know what else?
I really like the girl from that movie
who played Ben Wishaw's daughter.
I thought she was good.
If we're going to bring classic Disney musical numbers
to life, I think they should honor in the parks
the newest best Disney musical number,
The Simpsons Squad versus Trump.
Oh my God.
You should get out of America.
If anyone didn't see this.
Disney?
Congratulations on your bye.
We know the history of that, but we can't say it on the air.
So ask us after.
Oh, good.
Oh, no.
How am I supposed to finish the episode now?
Just remember, I'll let her know to myself.
It's the Democratic candidates.
That's a better Trump than.
Yeah.
One last Epcot thing.
Le Creperie de Paris in the France Pavilion from Chef
Jerome Bocou, son of Paul Bocou, who made Chef Paul,
the restaurant in the France Pavilion.
He has passed away.
He was a famous French chef.
Yeah, so that's kind of a cute little nod to the history.
Could I real quick, Cosmic Rewind?
Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind?
Which honestly, I hope the name, I think,
is going to be double meaning name because it's Rewind.
You start it's a backwards launch, which is fun.
And the coaster spins.
But I do think Rewind maybe suggests
that we're going to get some classic Epcot stuff.
But you think they would have shown some of it,
but they didn't.
So I'm worried.
I'm worried.
But also the name suggests to me Rewind means like retro.
Because they love their cassette tape.
Yes.
Rewind is like a cassette tape.
So it's like a cassette tape, but hopefully also
is like retro-y and we'll get Figmen in there.
Also no mention of what happens to Figmen.
There's a Figmen sized hole in the Epcot presentation.
Yeah.
Which means he's going away because they
didn't want to say anything.
Wait, what?
You just think he's going away?
Well, he's not mentioned in one of the neighborhoods.
I mean, we're going away from the ride.
That's what I meant.
And you'll hear on.
You think?
Yeah, because Jenny Nicholson pointed out,
obviously you'll hear what she has
to say on the live show on Friday.
But the rumor is like there'll be like a show maybe
or a video that you'll get to watch,
but that the journey will be turned into Inside Out.
Really?
That's been the rumor for a long time.
OK.
And I'm worried that they're going
to move Figmen to something else.
Yeah, but maybe not.
I mean, there's a theater right there.
Yeah, they'll put him in the theater
and you'll see a little movie with him.
I guess that at least he'll still be there.
If there's something of Figmen, then fine.
Because I don't think anybody's winning with him
his current iteration.
No.
I wouldn't be sad if that went away.
If he is like.
No, that's true.
A playful antagonist for Peter Quill.
Like if he's like if he was like
messing with the Guardians in a fun way.
Sure, that would be good.
But I don't know if they're going to go that hard.
No, I doubt that.
My hands don't scan.
Anything scans with your imagination.
They haven't.
That's the one thing they haven't explained
about Cosmic Rewind.
What's the hand scan situation?
Yeah, are they going to need us or this time
will Rockets hands be able to scan?
It's a different place.
Yeah, it's a different place.
We know his hands don't scan in the Collector's Mansion,
but in Cosmic Rewind Fortress,
do his hands scan or don't they scan?
We don't know.
They haven't announced it yet.
Well, Topsy.
That's actually where Topsy will show up.
Topsy's going to be on Cosmic Rewind?
She's in the Guardians.
Guardians of the Galaxy has had a very large roster of members.
It's Gamora, Peter Quill, Drax, Star-Lord Groot and Topsy.
Topsy.
I don't know my Topsy from my bottomsy.
Oh, Topsy.
Surprise Topsy hasn't come up yet.
Yeah.
I talk about Topsy a lot.
It's being something that delighted Jason so thoroughly.
Yeah, I talk about Topsy a lot in my personal life.
So that's what's surprising.
Congratulations to Lindsay.
Yeah.
She loves a good Topsy reference.
You just, you ask her.
Hey, Lindsay.
There's a space restaurant.
I mean, we knew about that.
Oh, yeah.
That's opening soon.
Space 220.
220 referring to the amount of miles up it is.
Is that right?
Above Epcot.
Above.
It's like you're going into space.
Oh.
And then you come back down to Earth on Epcot.
That's cute.
In a crazy elevator like the Disney Quest one?
Oh, I don't know.
I think something like that.
I do think they're going to do something like that.
Then they're testing it out for the Star Wars hotel.
Like, that's what Jim Hillis said.
They're testing out the screens and how it looks.
And the transport ahead of the Star Wars hotel.
OK.
Restaurant run by the Patina Group.
Hell yeah.
Hell yes.
Yeah, I went, yeah, for Patina.
We're going to be talking about Patina a lot in the Denta
and Disney ordeal, that's for sure.
So I'll save my Patina.
Hey, we didn't talk about the thing
they said in the Play Pavilion.
Oh, yeah.
You'll have the chance to help legendary fashion icon Edna
Mode on her quest to rid the world of uninspired style
or make a splash competing in a water balloon fight hosted
by Huey, Dewey, Louie, and Webby.
You get to visit DuckTales water balloon fight.
That's the kind of thing that's in play.
Sure.
And is it the real water balloons?
No.
I bet it's digital magic.
It has to be digital.
Do you get to float?
Maybe you get to do the ultimate float
near the ceiling experience hosted by Topsy.
Very possible.
Topsy could be going in every new direction.
Could be in Mary Poppins ride.
Could be in play.
Could be storytelling.
She tells a story of not knowing her Topsy from her bottoms.
Right.
And then that new Epcot logo, the T in it
was much more whimsical than the rest of the letters.
Was that a clue?
It was upside down.
Wait a minute.
Analyze that.
Who is Topsy?
That's a T that doesn't know it's Topsy from its bottom.
I'm going to say, well, I feel compelled
to say this phrase 12 more times.
We've barely covered anything yet.
So you'll get a lot more chances.
Well, you want to leave Epcot behind.
And we saw art for Mickey and Minnie's Runaway Railway
in 2022, at least the version here.
Which is like in Florida.
It's inside the Chinese theater recreation.
Here we'll be in a new building, the El Capitoon.
Capitoon.
Very cute.
I do like that.
It's got a little marquee, as if it
was a movie theater in Toontown.
I think Toontown's getting a little bit of a facelift,
so it looks nice.
I hope so.
Man, just paint it.
Having been in that Tokyo Toontown, oh my god,
the difference is so clear.
We got to catch up.
Or they'll get it.
Maybe.
Yeah, maybe they'll do the same thing.
I saw a picture of the ride, or I saw a little maquette
of the ride vehicle on the show floor, a picture of it
from the show floor.
Looks real cool.
Little train.
Big cartoon train.
Yeah.
And I think track was right?
Yep.
Yeah, great.
Yeah, this feels like it's going to be a sleeper.
It's just going to, without the hype of something
like Smuggler's Run, it's going to just sneak up and be like,
man, that is a delightful little ride.
I think message board rumors for years have said,
oh, this is going to be amazing.
People are going to really be blown away by this technology.
I think this is another one where it's like,
they just got to get it to work.
But the technology of it, the screens flipping and switching
around to different scenes, I think people are going to love it.
That's what it sounds like.
Oh, with you different technology,
we didn't talk about in this Star Wars Star Cruiser,
the you can do lightsaber training.
Oh, yeah.
Training like Luke did in A New Hope.
That's fun.
3D glasses, probably.
Maybe.
Because you got to shoot.
There's a copy.
There was like a trademark for it.
Right.
I mean, they've tried.
They've been trying to do it without it.
But I would distill some maybe 3D.
We were acting as if like we've barely gotten through anything.
But I'm looking at my list is not a lot left.
I mean, I guess we do have to talk about the new island that the cruise
ship goes to, Elu Thera.
Well, the Marvel stuff, there's all the.
Yeah, there's more.
There's more Disneyland stuff.
Oh, sure, sure.
Well, but hang on, because I can't unseat Elu Thera and your landing
point lighthouse point different than Dreamers Point Lighthouse.
Right.
But the main headline with this is that this is a new.
This is Disney's second island.
Yeah, and it will be designed by famed Imagineer Joe Rody.
Yeah, this is Rody Island.
Rody has been given an island to design.
And they brought Rody out to just make sure everyone knew that they were not
going to just destroy the Bahamas.
Yeah, like they were like, go out there and make people not think
we're just taking or not just taking over, which they are, I think.
But he's going to do it with care.
Successful than when the fire app took over the Bahamas.
Yeah, he will probably have a better plan in place.
Yes.
They this was all before this was after they talked about the new cruise ship,
which they ended the presentation with all this stuff.
Yes, they ended with Make-A-Wish and cruise ship stuff, which I Carly and I
were talking and she's like, that was kind of a weird ending.
Right. Do you think it seemed like something got pulled like because
they usually you want to end on a bang.
Yeah. And there's already there's been a big musical number in Dick Van Dyke.
And then we're then they're talking about Ellu Thera and that Rapunzel
is on the Disney Wish on the stern on the stern permanently.
Rapunzel's on the stern.
Goodbye, everybody.
Yeah. Validate parking. See you.
It was so odd because I was watching it going and there, you know, we've heard
and I think, yeah, I was saying that there won't be any sort of fun
Tomorrowland announcement.
There was a Tomorrowland and figment sized holes.
But I was thinking, oh, man, they've been doing this dry stuff,
which, yeah, this dry stuff for 10 minutes now.
Got to be a big thing to go out on.
Yeah. Because like you'd go out with the Avengers ticket or something.
You'd go out with something where it's like, you know, people like the ride.
They want a big ride announcement.
That's what they want.
Especially if it's Anaheim, even better.
Like our show people you'll hear if anyone who wasn't there,
you will hear what we go out on for shattering news.
Yeah. So let me build that up as much.
I you will not believe it.
You will. You will not believe what Michael did.
No, no, no, no. Yeah. Yeah. No, you're right.
Yeah. You will not believe what Michael did.
Yeah. What a clue.
What Michael did. Yeah.
Which Michael? I don't know. I don't know.
Could be any Michael.
So you're right. We're on the risk of saying too much.
So yeah, look, we know we're showmen.
You go out with a go out with a bang.
These guys doing I would you would.
It was structured weird, like Epcot should have been at the end.
Or yeah, like you're saying Avengers, that's all the Marvel stuff.
Sure. They're down the street.
They're in Anaheim. Right.
And people like it like, yeah.
So it's very odd that they did that.
It does feel like something outpolled.
I'm assuming that in a world where Galaxy's Edge broke records all summer,
we have a big thing at the end of this presentation.
I do think that chain because that historically happens
when something in the company isn't performing as well.
Records of most angry YouTube videos ever made.
Yes. Seampark topic.
But Disney, but that's not something that they're after.
Yeah, they can't monetize that as well. No.
So, yeah, so it does feel like something got pulled.
Who knows how last second.
There's always rumors or word of like, oh, yeah, and then this got pulled
right at the last second for this and this got pulled.
And there's probably 50 other, probably more, probably like 100 projects
at various parks, and they're deciding what to put in and what to pull out.
People being spotted in the parks, you know, but still move something around.
I mean, Chaypeck's not great with that teleprompter.
So maybe he had been rehearsing and they were like, he goes, no, no,
if you change things around, I don't know.
There's an order in my head and I can cut stuff like we can just cut the end,
but I cannot move something around.
Yeah, the incredible stage presence of Bob Chaypeck.
Yeah, I was I went back to the beginning just to see where he started from.
Do we have any parks fans here today?
I knew it. Well, and then just so much like because the parks have always been
about the magic of dreamers and about dreaming up new magic.
And what makes good dreams?
Excellent storytelling and all of us together.
Storytellers have always been the ultimate dream tellers
and imbued each story they tell with magic.
Don't change course in midstream.
I was impressed.
We were watching.
Lindsay was watching some of it with me.
And then Rody comes out and Rody is just like a great public speaker.
He's great. I'm going to see him.
The day this comes out.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speaking at the Getty.
You're seeing him today. Oh, really?
Yeah. How fun.
Yeah, these are the Getty.
Yeah. So I was like, oh, the contrast here.
Yeah. So who knows?
Who knows what it was supposed to be or wasn't supposed to be at the end of that presentation?
We can go out with a bang.
What with Marvel, we're doing the order that they should have done.
Right. Yeah, I forgot about all of that.
Well, let's not forget, magic happens.
The new daytime parade.
Magic happens celebrating the stories of dreamers.
Right. Dreamers, wishes.
I love when they announced the cruise ship.
They're like, and the new name.
It's like there's literally seven words you guys use.
No, there's seven different words.
And it was a wish.
Dream, wish.
Wonder, please let it be wonder.
Magic, wonder, wish, dream.
I what I like about that picture, the promo art for the
the parade is that Mickey isn't a very like Tokyo Disney looking robe to me
because I love the costumes in Tokyo Disney for the characters.
For some reason, there's there's so much better.
I don't know why they're more interesting.
But the art there looks cool.
I liked his little colorful robe.
So that's what I'm looking forward to.
Robe. I'm looking forward to an outfit.
Or Mickey. Mickey's got new clothes.
But that's not that's not a new thing for me.
I like his clothes.
You've always been on the record liking his clothes.
But you like the classic to red shorts, two buttons.
Can't go wrong with the classic.
Yeah, no classic look.
Always in style.
But Marvel. Yeah, I totally forgot.
I was like scribbling notes and it's not on my notes stupidly.
But yes, we do know more about although none of it is really different
than anything we. Yeah.
Names were clarified.
Pim's Pim's Test Kitchen.
Pim's Test Kitchen seems to be implying shrunken foods and enlarged foods.
Right. Pim and Webb are coming to DCA.
The Worldwide Engineering Brigade.
I will say the art look, the full art they reveal looks a little bit more
promising as far as an interesting thing to look at than initially it did.
Because I am going to hear like you're going to YouTube Space LA.
Yeah, I was goofing on it in the hear me goof on in the live show.
And I'm still goofing on a little bit.
But like it does, like with the Avengers headquarters with the Quinjen.
OK, I like that a lot.
So that is going to be cool.
I was pretty confused by what the Avengers attraction is, but it is.
He took it. I have some speculation on that, and I have not seen anyone else
with this speculation, too.
So let's go. Well, let's go through the rest of the not as cool stuff.
Pim's Test Kitchen, a Dr.
Strange little sanctum show kind of like in the.
OK, good.
That that would probably be cool.
The Spider-Man ride an open house at the Worldwide Engineering Brigade.
Web goes wrong.
The folks, they love it when open houses go wrong.
So I think God, look, my mom is a teacher for a long time.
If there had been any hijinks at her open houses, I would have been horrified.
But in the realm of magic and dreams and storytelling.
Well, that's what you know, to make an open house go right, you need
an itinerary, you need some wristbands and you need a bottle of Chardonnay.
Am I right, folks?
I just remember Disney Genie.
Oh, fuck.
No, no, hold on.
We'll go through Marvel.
Disney Genie, real quick, is just I don't care for it
because it's a computer that plans your trip for you and checks for you.
And I can do a better job than you're like, John Henry. Yeah.
I'll show you.
I'll check faster than that machine ever could.
Me versus Disney Genie.
No contest for come on.
Yeah. All right. Anyway, back to Marvel.
And you can do more celebrity impressions, too. Yeah.
You got good ones. Yeah.
You got Jeff Garland, Pillsbury Doughboy.
Jeff Goldblum, finding out all sorts of facts about the world.
You could do that, isn't it, Fresh?
I could, but it's not one of the ones I do. OK.
We're all going to be doing it soon with our new favorite show.
That's true.
Friggin Goldblum.
All right. Yeah. We're going to go.
Blum, that's a friggin random.
Goldberg, Goldberg, I called him.
Jesus, I was in my mind where he's approaching like the Bill Murray.
Yes, we're being we're fighting.
Yeah, it's inherently funny to reference him and add nothing.
Yeah. To the reference.
Yeah, it's it's that that's this is the Chuck Norris rule.
You're right. Yes. Say the name.
And I'm laughing already. Right.
You're like this guy, real character.
This cage kind of cross that.
Yeah, that's true.
Mm hmm. Different flavors.
But yeah, same deal. Mm hmm.
What were you saying? You were saying microbrewery.
Well, it was originally plugged as a microbrewery,
like promote as a microbrewery.
And now they're going more with test kitchen.
Yeah, I guess a little more family friendly. Right.
This all sounds like they if especially if he gets evicted,
this seems like a good place for Dr.
Nigel Channing to work. Oh, yeah.
Now as his test experiments shrinking.
Yeah, yeah.
Shrinking experiments.
Spider bots, spider bots out of control.
This is the premise of the ride that you have to help him.
The spider bots start replicating.
You have to help him gather them like no one gets hurt.
You get to shoot webs at Dr.
Octopus, though. Oh, no, no.
This is what we got to round up his like failed experiments.
There's robots that roaming around.
We got to shoot him.
We'll probably be in mask the whole time.
Yeah, fine. With the Sony stuff.
We have to capture Spider Man's sperms.
There's robot sperms, genetic outcasts and.
Geez. Yep.
Maybe Spider Man splooged all over the lab.
It's his friends.
So I'm hoping Ned and MJ like are around.
They're not going to pay those people.
I guess. Yeah.
I think Zendaya's quote is probably very high.
He's going to be friend.
His friend is going to be Bob Chapec or something.
It's going to be just like.
No, they're not going to get him either.
Maybe they'll get Favreau.
Maybe. But MCU now, is that a problem?
Maybe that'll be resolved in like a month.
Oh, you think so? Yeah, it's just a play.
There's already like a counter offer.
I read. Oh, I don't know about that.
Well, I've talked about that off air, too.
Maybe you have insight. Insight.
Anyway, I don't. I was just clicking around.
All right. Great.
So we're going to.
WGA and the agents be able to break bread at Pym's Test Kitchen.
Will that be resolved?
What's your inside information there?
Do you. Well, my information there is that I was a gog when I learned that
someone running for WGA office is the son of Elia Kazan,
the rat, Elia Kazan, who named names.
So he definitely should have input on a labor union.
He definitely seems above board.
Yeah. That family.
Very regular.
Do not have a tight up Elia Kazan in the 50s.
That's the right I want to do.
That would be great.
Like how like Captain America punching Hitler.
Yeah.
So OK, so it's robots, Spider-Man.
We have to get his robots.
Whirling in the webs.
Spider-Man.
Robots. Why can't we shoot them at his villains?
Why can't I already a ride?
But we're not shooting at them in there and they use different villains.
Give me other villains.
Yeah, there's a lot more, it seems like.
There's tons.
So no villains on the ride, just spider robots.
And we don't know that.
We don't know that.
We'll see. Maybe there is a villain behind all of it.
And yeah, who knows?
Your theory about the Avengers attraction.
OK, so the Avengers attraction, they announced it.
There's been a lot of rumors for years now that first it was, I believe,
Captain America, E-Ticket Ride.
That was originally what I always read was the first thing.
Then it was Avengers E-Ticket.
They've supposedly redesigned, designed different concepts
that would be like crazy E-Ticket roller coasters.
They wanted it to be like a teen, teen boy thing, which means, I don't know, fast.
I guess that's what I've read.
That means you got to go fast.
And it's been a big problem.
And obviously, there's no work being done on it right now.
They're just working on that little land.
So it's been very mysterious as to what this big ride is going to be.
So I thought it was not going to be announced.
They did announce it.
It's going to go like they they have the promo art of that
Avengers area with the Quinjet.
And then all of a sudden, they the big building appears behind it
during the presentation.
Like, so they're just going to be building it sort of behind Guardians,
which is the rumor for forever.
What's there right now? Nothing. Parking parking. Yeah.
So they'll just build this big building behind it.
And now it's going to be flight to Wakanda.
Essentially, you're going to be on a Quinjet.
But you go to Wakanda. Right. Yeah.
And you know, Black Panther is going to be on the Avengers.
He's been on the Avengers before.
Rumor I read there is difficulty maybe putting Wakanda in Orlando
because on one of those single paintings at Islands of Adventure,
Black Panther is represented on a pillar.
So he technically exists in Universal.
Someone just to face it. Cross.
We'll see. We'll go do that.
We'll go spray paint over it.
So then we get a Wakanda.
He could be they could put Wakanda in, but Black Panther is not here.
So you can use like Shuri and Dora Milage.
Yeah, you can use all the claw.
You can use them all except Black Panther.
So anyway, so they showed a picture, which I don't have right here,
of like guests in the cockpit, which is first like honestly,
is a person who's been waiting for an e-ticket Avengers ride.
I rolled my eyes at it because I went, oh, it's like a simulator ride.
This sucks.
But then they I saw this art they released also.
And it's this. And I don't know if you saw it.
I've already shown given Jason my theory via text.
I figured I'd do this to you live, Scott.
So you didn't get to.
Heroes are all running around and punching and throwing other characters.
Yeah. So it's a big battle scene.
And it's just like, OK, this feels like, oh, that'll be like one of the scenes
you'll see when you're like flying around or whatever.
But take a look at these three characters.
Can you see them from where you're sitting?
Oh, these people, these are people in flying machines with their legs dangling.
OK, jetpack chairs.
So no one again, I have not seen this.
I'm sure somebody has speculated about this.
My speculation is if there's a photo of people in the Quinjet and then here
that this could be some sort of ride where maybe you start out in the Quinjet.
It's simulated for the first part.
Then the bottom drops out, dropping everybody into maybe a circle vision, 3D theater.
This is a guess, obviously, with, you know, you have 3D glasses on or whatever.
And then you're spinning around maybe in a circle,
being directed at the action on the 3D screens.
Are you in rows with people still?
Is it a Soren? I don't know any of that.
But that's I'm just trying to figure out where you would be able to figure
like navigate that scene being in the plane and then being out here in the action.
This looks very thinking about being in a chair like that
and seeing the kind of intense action you're seeing.
Yeah, this like that's I see.
That's a screen right. I can get behind.
Yeah. If you get like a lot of you aren't just in some big car like Star Tours,
because we've seen this many times.
Right. I'm I don't think we're opposed to screen rides, but no, should be innovative.
I mean, if it was like, well, like an war, if you could look in all directions
and you're surrounded, you're in the middle of a giant superhero fight.
I mean, that would be most I mean, most directions.
Obviously, there's going to you're going to have to have like a cord and stuff.
So like they could put something over your head so you can't look up up.
You think we're maybe in
like a helmet void kind of territory, potentially?
I don't know.
It's still not a quick way to get those helmets on.
Yeah. And also, like the size of the building to me from this picture
they showed, like the size of it suggests a big ride.
Yeah. So I would they don't need that much space if it's a void thing.
But if you could imagine a soaring, you could look down.
Yeah. There was stuff and people were maybe a little further apart from you.
I mean, yeah, even even even with a limited range of motion, like
if you imagine there was a row of people and they were all kind of being
dropped down by a cord and then turned around, like you can still direct
people's view.
So it's like it's it's honestly kind of more like the next flight of
like the next logical step from flight of passage or soaring.
Yeah. And it lets you be feel like a hero who's flying around in a suit,
which is there's there hasn't really been a ride that gives you that sensation
like your Iron Man or whatever.
Yeah, that's true, too. Yes.
This is also a regular device in comic books, the Quinjet or the Blackbird
or the Batwing blows up and the character is like flying in midair
or like falling in midair or something.
Yeah. And it does it does sort of solve the problem because I want a lot of robots
on the ride. But you can't really have a bunch of robots
fighting at the level of the Marvel superheroes in the movie.
So this does solve the problem of putting you in the middle of the action
and getting to see like a really fluid, insane battle
that you're taking part in in some way.
I like your guess.
Thank you for analyzing that photo. I think you're right on.
I mean, I hope. Yeah, because like it'll I would assume they would know
that just being in a plane with a simulator isn't that interesting.
Yeah, I would say this steps a bit.
It's like not unlike a rise to the resistance.
It's like a multi stage.
Yeah, I mean, I would hope. Yeah.
And yeah, because I guess if you really think about it, it's like Soren flight
of passage, tower of terror.
Like it's a dry could be a drop right potentially to drop into
because like that would be awesome.
Like you're doing we're going to drop because that makes a lot of sense to like,
OK, you're all recruits. We need help.
We're going to drop you in the middle of the action.
The bottom drops out.
You shoot into the battle and then you shoot up and down as stuff happens.
And like, you know, giant man tries to grab you and then lifts you up.
Like there are the possibilities of that are endless.
We're kind of in
Harry Potter land a little bit to like the ability to bob up and down.
Yeah, with like a kooka arm.
I mean, it could be that, too.
It could be maybe like the kooka arm basically is like in the ride
and pulls you down and flips.
Who knows? So it could be anything.
Oh, hey, I'm excited now.
Yeah, it sounds like they will maybe deliver on
what I hope is the promise of this type of ride.
Also interesting that it seems like they I mean, this was probably always the plan
for this Marvel stuff in DCA, but they're kind of
spinning it of like, well, like Galaxy's Edge,
where the big ride is coming in the second part of it, you know.
Yeah, they are. And they didn't announce a date for this.
No. What's the date for the first leg of it next year?
Twenty twenty. Yeah. Oh, so like it is quick.
But I I have a feeling that this will be twenty twenty three.
Yes, that's because Runaway Railway is in 20 is until 2022.
And I can't imagine that like they've already built most of that one.
So they're just cloning it.
And this is going to be a totally new ride.
I can't imagine this opens before Runaway Railway.
That's a nice piece of a few years of big new attractions in Anaheim.
Sure. Yeah. And the new Tomorrowland and then to 35.
Sure. That is the I mean, I was so hoping I was wrong about that prediction
and that we would get a big announcement.
But yeah, that feels like that's now another world away.
Yeah. I feel like the cast of Tomorrowland
looking into that future seeing device where they see only disappointment.
Yeah. Just about Tomorrowland.
Just all this other stuff seems cool.
As relatable of a reference as Topsy.
Yes. Same thing. Yeah.
Topsy. Yeah. Yeah.
They yeah. And there's.
They yeah, when they say Marvel phase two, also, like
I was hoping that they would announce like and we're ripping out
the rest of Hollywoodland to make it.
Yes. A notable thing about the concept art Hollywood stays.
I mean, for now, and they just built a new marquee for Philhar Magic.
That's opening soon. That's cool. It looks cool.
It's right next to Ward Wieners.
And it looks nice. A timeless marquee.
Timeless marquee. And also, like, you can be able to they can change the thing out here.
So I don't think I don't think they're doing anything to any of that anytime soon.
I think there might be a plus up or redo of the Hollywoodland stuff coming.
Really? I guess all that rumored some one website
that I'm not going to name was dropping unconfirmed rumors
all weekend, along with breaking official rumors.
And that was a little. Yeah. Confusing.
You can name them.
We all know what I'm talking about. OK, I got it.
I got the one. The one. The one.
Got a controversial one.
They did know that Ron John surf shop was coming.
Anybody else did.
It's very funny tweet to very funny tweet about like.
We know we told you about Ron John.
Remember Ron John?
You support Bob J.
Beck, you support the destruction of Ron John.
Oh, that. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
What was that? Yeah, there was a lot of it.
You were if you were applauding Mr.
J. Beck and you are applauding the end of original ideas.
And he lands plane hotel rooms, hotel rooms.
I feel like Disney has kind of upped the game on their hotel rooms
this in the last few years.
Like, well, yeah, they were in the dumps for a little while.
A little while. Yeah.
I mean, the deluxe ones were always nice, but they've kind of adjusted to like,
well, people want places to put their luggage out of the way
and they want a lot of outlets to charge devices.
Murphy beds are back.
Hey, I love the return of Murphy bed.
They only sleep one in Florida. Who knows?
If you're lucky, if I was so lucky. Yeah.
Does he remember clapping for Bob J.
Beck is clapping for all of this?
An alien and droid list.
Galaxy's Edge. Not true.
Plane hotel rooms and resort parking fees.
You are plotting a war criminal, sir.
What a crazy. Oh, my God.
You could tell, you know, you know, I you know, my life is in a good place
where I was out to dinner with friends talking about this particular
news site and their recent tweets.
And then I checked my phone and you had texted me something different about this
particular.
I got double news coming at me, but angry, angry
Disney tweeters.
Yeah. Yeah.
Anyway, hopefully some tomorrowland news coming soon.
And the Avengers ride looks great.
Trying to end on a positive. Oh, I see.
Look, I can end on a positive because we look we covered this a little bit earlier,
but I wanted to read just relive my absolute favorite part of the power.
Fifty one panel, which is the the introduction of
target CEO Brian Cornell.
Imagine like the day before they got to see the rock come out in a jungle cruise
boat. They saw Emily Blunt and Julia Louis Dreyfus and Jamie Foxx and Tina Fey.
But the next day you got to see Brian friggin Cornell.
It right. Right.
It led not to say nothing of bullseye.
But my my absolute favorite part of this panel was the the introduction of Brian
Cornell and tears. I have it queued up.
And to tell you more, I'd like to welcome the CEO of Target, Brian
Cornell.
The giant Target logo on screen.
Brian Cornell's walkout music.
His name is Brian Cornell.
He's the man with the Target plan.
Brian Cornell, every idea he has is a big old bullseye.
Brian Cornell.
He is here.
Got to tell us all about it.
His blood runs red and white with circles.
He's Brian Cornell.
I wish they'd allowed me.
We stand. We stand.
We stand. Brian Cornell.
I think you could tweet a version of that, Adam.
Yes, I could sample that.
Maybe I'll record the song later.
I mean, do a song, Brian.
I mean, I didn't invent your walkout music, which is very for that's Johnny's
theme. Dan and Dan Dan.
Right. Johnny's theme and Brian's theme are the most iconic instrumentals.
But who's to say some lyrics couldn't help out.
Yeah, I think that is he on Twitter?
We can find out.
Roll out the red and white circle carpet.
Brian Cornell.
And then you just list that on your resume as you wrote the words to Brian
Cornell's entrance music.
Yeah.
If that weren't enough, he's going to show you bullseye Brian Cornell.
It is also like almost like his SNL sketch music,
like a character who just like a Brian Fellows or something.
He's the massive head wound Harry.
Right. His jingle for his sketch.
He's what I'm looking for.
Yeah.
The game of the sketch beforehand.
Yeah. Yeah.
Debbie Downer had what?
Yeah. Yeah. It's very much that that spirit.
And the game of Brian Cornell is he's the greatest guy.
He's going to blow our minds, telling us about Instagrammable Disney
moments coming to our local target.
If it's one of the 20 that was chosen, right.
The game 20 out of five.
The scene Brian Cornell being awesome.
Hell, yeah. You got it.
Thank you for always having Nature Valley granola bars on sale, Brian.
Yeah, you're making this joke.
But Jason's thinking he is awesome.
It was a great target.
I look. Target has good clothes.
Target has groceries now.
They have affordable prices, especially if you're buying food in bulk for his
shoot or some such thing.
It's true. I think the aesthetics are good.
Great. The best prices on canned goods, dry goods, you know, really good.
My mom is not as good.
Yeah. My mom loves Target.
It's where you get your soup, cereal, peanut butter.
It's great. Some of them, the recently built ones are like pretty cool looking.
Some of some there's architecture of Target.
Yeah. Yeah. It is all right.
They redid the Glendale one just recently.
Mm hmm. It's very interesting.
It's where it's recently redone.
Yeah. Really?
In the last month.
Already very cool.
The multiple the three story Target.
Yeah. Shopping cart escalators.
I was a little bummed when CVS took over their pharmacies because Target had those
crazy like proprietary bought those crazy upside down bottles
and then they stopped having them.
Oh, I don't know what you're talking about, but that's I'm sorry.
People will know the bottle upside down bottles.
Who thought of this topsy?
Wow. I wasn't even.
Wow. Magic relief is all around us.
I don't know the topsy from the bottomsy.
Well, I think you survived podcast the ride on that note.
Check Twitter for my anthem to my
friend of devotion.
You got a quick turnaround time on that.
Yeah, I know. Boy, I got to go home and knock that out, I guess.
Hey, did I?
Hey, I think I'll I think I'll nail it.
I'll hit the bullseye.
Just like Brian always does.
Yes. And just remember, folks, dreams are wishes you make with storytelling.
Check out our check out the D23 show coming on on Friday.
Thanks, everybody.