Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate, where if you like speculation with a side of
Florida transportation infrastructure talk, this is the episode for you.
Folks, as we record this mere hours ago, Universal announced Universal's Epic Universe.
I'm Jason Sheridan here with Mike Carlson.
Yeah, I'm here.
And Scott Gerrider.
An epic day.
We can feel it.
I think we're all exhausted from all of the epicness, but we're forcing ourselves to stay
up and process all of this.
You joke, but I have been up since 730 AM reading live tweets and drinking coffee.
The dog woke me up at 7 AM, which he's been doing lately, and I saw you just texting furiously.
And then I was a little underwhelmed by the announcements and I went back to bed sort
of like disappointed, but you seemed like you were riled and ready to go.
I was ready to go.
You seemed very genuinely psyched.
I mean, I'm excited about it.
I'm not saying I'm not excited.
I think also this is the 20 years we just passed the 20 year anniversary of Islands
of Adventure, the last park built in Orlando.
And this is the first major park built since then.
New theme park with Disney or Universal.
Or Universal.
Yeah.
Except the theme water park, Volcano Bay.
But for the sake of today, we will not.
It's going to grind my ears.
I know.
There's blood coming out of your ear.
Can we get a quick comic con recap from you?
Oh, OK.
You want to do?
I wasn't sure if this was the chaser.
That's where this is an epic episode.
There's a little bit of an anecdote I wanted the listeners to hear.
And this let's let's just do it real quick here.
I think we're not too far out from Comic Con.
You guys went to go.
Yeah.
A story has been saved for me to hear.
So here's the set up.
I go down to Comic Con every year.
Jason usually goes for a couple of days.
I stay at Lindsay's mom's place to save a little money.
It's only like 10 minute lift from the convention center.
So I was trying to get Jason to go down.
I'm like, I'm sure you can find an Airbnb that'll be good.
And I send him some links.
He's looking up stuff himself.
And we actually I'm checking a lot.
And finally you land on a place that looks pretty good.
Price is good.
Looks like it's a nice location and like a nice, you know, look.
It's a scenic.
It's nice.
Yeah.
Tenth floor of a high rise looking down like first J Street.
Right.
Beautiful view.
That was the second one I booked.
Yes, that's right.
I was condensing.
And you found a nicer looking one.
Yeah.
So I switched.
I switched to that one.
Also, Mike now living his dream, booking fun experiences for other people.
Yeah, which I do do fairly often.
If you give me the rope, I will.
I will lasso a hotel for you or an Airbnb.
You were helpful.
And in the long run, this part of this worked out in that like it seemed like there was
like two or three people I could have potentially shared this room with.
Yeah.
And that didn't end up happening, which thank God.
So so this is what this is the important part to the setup.
So you said to me, you said, you know what?
I'm just going to do it myself.
I'm not going to stay with anyone.
I'm going to have a nice night in this nice Airbnb stretch out.
Was there a pool?
There was a pool.
You're like, I'm going to go to the pool.
I'm just going to have a nice, you know, 48 hours in San Diego with the convention.
This is going to be a time when I get to treat myself.
This is going to be a really nice 48 hour little mini trip for myself.
So you were very excited about it.
It sounds like the first act of a sitcom.
It certainly anyone else saying any of this.
Maybe you can trust it would go OK.
But it's a hapless character.
So I it was on Saturday and I had just found my way into Hall H.
And I well, is this when I started texting about what was going down?
So because for me, it started a little earlier.
You'll be able to tell that part of it.
I receive a text in the middle of Hall H from our friend, Anthony Geo, friend of the show.
My savior.
It is so it is such a great text.
And it's not great for you, but it's such a ridiculous text.
And now I will let you take it from here.
OK, unless you want me to say no, no, work backwards.
We'll catch up to the text.
Got it. Got it.
If you want to.
I'm going to find the text.
So my trouble began when we all went to lunch.
We went to this Greek place.
And I started the host, the Airbnb host starts calling me.
And he goes, hey, man, wanted to check in, wanted to see when we could meet up
so I could give you the keys.
And I was like, that's not great, because the listing said pick up at concierge,
pick up at front desk.
I was like, oh, this is an apartment building with a front desk.
So and he's like, yeah, I just checked.
I can't do that.
Sorry, it's my first weekend hosting.
So a couple of flags never asked.
Oh, my God. Never asked.
But it felt OK putting it on his list.
So I was like, OK.
And he's like, can you meet up?
Do you want to hop in a quick lift?
Come over and get them.
And I'm like, I don't want to hop in a quick lift and come over and get them at all.
Because I was like going to scarf food down and run back to go to an X-Men panel
at the Convention Center, which also all weekend, any panel I tried to go to,
I did not get to.
I did not either get in or I just fucked up the timing.
It did not make it to.
So eventually we set a time to meet up to exchange the keys.
He pushes his back 15 minutes.
I then I get there right at like 345 or whatever.
I'm standing on a street corner.
Five minutes past, 10 minutes past, 15 minutes past.
And finally, I'm like texting.
Hey, man, where are you?
About 10 minutes later, he finally calls and he's like, OK, I'm coming up.
Man, a lot of traffic today.
It's like, yeah, it's comic.
Anything going on in town?
Anything going on?
Text, I have the text.
Yes. And so I I had found a street corner.
I actively found a street corner that was not blocked off from traffic.
So eventually he pulls up and he gives me the keys.
And I'm like, OK, great.
So just leave them on the kitchen table when I like check out or leave them on,
you know, a hook or something.
He's like, oh, no, they're my only set of keys.
Can you just leave them under the mat when you check out?
I'm like, yes, sure, man.
I'll leave them under the. OK.
And at this point, he's like, all right, I'm out.
See you. Have a good time.
And so I'm like, well, at this point, I'm like three blocks from the place.
So I don't just go put my bag down and check it out.
So I walk over and I go up to it and it's very nice and very clean.
The sun is setting and I go to just
just as a habit in the last five, ten years,
I've gotten to when I go to stay at a hotel or a rental place.
I check the sheets for bed bugs.
Can I read the text now?
So yes. So this is when my troubles really began.
So here's the text.
A little update from.
So this is Anthony texting me a little update from the convention floor.
Jason will be staying with me because this Airbnb bed was wet.
So I. Oh, I.
I pulled the sheets back on the bed and I am like, these are damp
and it is not cold because the windows are all open.
He did not leave the air.
Are they let the windows up?
I think just to get some fresh air in there.
Like this is wet.
And I'm like, how wet is it?
And then I touch the comfort.
I'm like, oh, the comforter is more wet.
The comforter is the source of the wetness.
This is the fire festival scenario, despite there not having been a flood.
Or I'm sorry. I would like a, you know, a storm that rained down on a
very thin tent. How did this happen in a?
How did this or apartment complex?
So I pull I was like, well, maybe I'm OK.
Let me see how wet.
So I check all the quarters and they are all wet.
And so I text, hey, man, just got to the apartment.
The bedding is wet.
And then the guy promptly calls.
He's like, I'm so sorry.
The person who stayed last night checked out late, which may push the cleaning
lady back. And like I was racing to pull the bedding out of the,
you know, the comforter out of the dryer so I could put it on the bed.
And I guess I didn't check.
I didn't notice. And I'm like, I don't know if you would not be able to check.
Yeah. And so I'm like, all right.
Well, that's you know, if it's in your hands, you know, if it is wet or dry.
That's true. So I'm going to say Airbnb hosting tip by two shed
sets of bedding by two, just maybe ask your building if you can do this.
And do that. Yes. And I had to give it.
He was very polite. He was very nice.
And that's you for keeping it. Hey, man.
You kept it. I kept it.
Cash, you know, therapy and meditation.
And also I had a look.
I was just low key stoned all weekend.
And so I was pretty chill.
And I'm like, I don't want to yell at this guy
because he's very tall and I think could easily kick my ass.
Throw you just throw me
into a muscly, sleeved, tattoo sleeved arms.
I'll make you wet.
And he was like, I'm so sorry.
But then and thankfully, this only went on for like a minute.
He was like, you know what?
I'm really sorry. I'll give you 20 bucks back.
And I'm like, no.
He went, OK, OK, 50.
And I was like, I'm not not really cool with that.
I don't want to sleep on the couch.
He's like, no, no, I don't want you to sleep on the couch.
What if I came back and put the comforter in the dryer?
Or you could put it in the dry.
I'm like, I am on vacation.
I don't want to do launch.
So what if you slept on my warm back?
I'll cradle you to sleep.
And I had already before I called the guy, I called Anthony Gia,
who had offered he last minute got a hotel room that had a sofa bed in it.
He's like, if you want it, it's available.
And I was like, is that still available?
And he's like, yes.
And I'm like, OK, I'm going to play.
And I was like, hey, man, I think I just really want to refi.
I'm not going to stay here tonight.
I want to refund. I'll leave the key under the.
I'm not going to stay. I'm going to stay with a friend.
And after a split second of him going like, well, not a lot of places to stay.
You know, San Diego is pretty busy right now.
And I'm like, you miss you did not hear.
I got a place to I'm good.
So just he and he's like, OK, all right, no problem.
I'll call you. Airbnb.
And to his credit, he did promptly call Airbnb and said
they would give a refund and they called me like 10, 15 minutes later.
And they call you the next day as well.
They called me the next day just to make sure, you know,
if I had any other questions.
They knew you were like a travel influencer, probably.
Sure. You would be talking about this experience.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
They're going to lose points.
So bad review on that second gate.
The good karma, the Spring Hill suites.
Wonderful buffet breakfast.
Great customer service.
That's where I stay at the Spring Hill suites.
If I do an overnight at Disneyland, if I if I want to, you know,
be able to be able to very sleek.
Yeah. Very modern fan of the brand from my one experience.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's a they have a Anaheim one as a social hour, they call it.
There's a big pile of hamburgers.
None of it's it's he all seems inedible, but I like the idea of it.
So this had a sunset toast and also a beautiful terrace
that overlook the one the
God, I forget what it's called.
I don't know if it's the harbor at that point, but we were looking down
at an aircraft carrier.
OK, and it was really beautiful.
And they're like sunset toast.
And I was like, I was like, well, I have to kill time for the train.
The next day back, I'll just hang out here for the sunset toast.
And I was like, I'd like the sunset toast, please.
And they're like, well, it's brought to you by Cut Water Spirits,
which is the canned cocktails that are so popular.
And they poured me two sips of a whiskey lemonade.
And that was it.
And I was like, oh, right.
OK, so enough in the glass to make a toast.
So whiskey of pre combined whiskey, pre combined whiskey.
Other than that, that was but it was the funniest note to to end on.
I mean, better than what you had better than what I had in the spring.
Sweets, the most important thing, they give you the option of
do you want a dry or a wet comforter?
They ask you when you check in, would you like it damp or soaked?
There's a gray area in between.
How wet you want it?
Jason, depending on his mood, does sometimes want a very wet bed.
But he just wasn't feeling it that weekend.
I wasn't feeling it.
Some days he likes it sloshing around in a hotel bed or an Airbnb bed.
But not this weekend.
This was a relaxing.
We get humid real quickly.
Yeah. So anyway, like a frog on a lily pad.
Yeah. Splashing around the swamp.
So anyway, that's the continuing saga of Jason vacationing.
You get another wrinkle.
Yeah, but we took the the surf liner back like in business class
and they give you a snack box, a little bottle of wine.
Very nice. Very nice. Yeah.
Yeah. All right.
So epic. That was epic.
Yeah, that was epic.
Step one of a very epic episode.
Yeah. And it's an episode of surprises for me because you guys saved that info.
Yeah. Thank you for telling it to me.
And then this epic universe announcement, the info about the
fourth gate at Universal Studios.
We we can call apart.
We can just call it the new part.
You don't have to worry about the to leave numbers out of it.
If we could.
Maybe I don't like to play these companies games.
Maybe that's what's going on.
But anyway, you know, this announcement was made this morning.
Unlike you, I was not up at six a.m.
I wanted to discover all of this information live on the air.
I wanted you to feel the emotion as I saw epic universe for the first time.
Slash, I did not have time to look at it earlier.
That's so that's fair.
So you're going to get three like
real world job stuff, things go hitting you at once as I'm sitting there going,
oh, interesting, that's a lot of parking spots.
I had a scenario in which a
I was on the I was on a phone call with like a like an agency
in another country while a right at the moment that a
1800s era costume with big like man capes was being delivered to my door.
These these are two types of things that don't happen to me every day.
So why would they both happen within the same 15 minutes?
Another epic epic.
Oh, fuck me.
I don't know. Epic happening.
Now you're thinking about having to call it the fourth gate.
Yeah, that too.
Make this running gag run.
I put the picture behind you in a funny way.
Oh, oh, boy.
I have the whole problem.
I had you. Well, I got to spin around.
This is the concept art.
OK, here we go. Take a look.
I'm going to veer from my usual podcast.
This is called Epic.
What is it called?
Universal's epic universe.
A lot of universe.
And it is OK.
Now it's not the Disney California venture.
They are still using the apostrophe and the S.
Is that right? Universal's universal.
You know, this is very important.
It's very important to have this out because we don't know anything else
because they didn't announce the IP.
And I like how you're holding the mic stand like a stick.
Steven Tyler holds.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm rocking out. I got aero Smith.
I got energy.
So now for briefly speculated, leaked last year.
Fantastic World seemed like there was some trademark
funny business with Warner Brothers, who they need to keep on good terms
with because they have the Harry Potter stuff.
Yeah. So this is so the way.
Yeah, the name for for a long time rumored was Fantastic Worlds.
Now you think or have you read that that was a Warner Brothers problem or
I believe supposedly there was a trademark dispute, but they did
register both Fantastic Worlds and Epic Universe around right off the bat.
I will say Fantastic World's better name than Epic Universe.
Better name epic sort of ties it to right now or maybe to like seven years ago.
When did people start calling things seven years ago?
I think is right. So, yeah, that feels a little bit more.
Ties it to 20 or 20 surfers.
Yes. I mean, they're friggin epic.
I would I would think with the vibe of this,
they would be reaching for the traditional version of the word epic.
Grant, you know, grand in scope.
Sure. I would think so, too.
It's a word that hasn't been used in a theme park title before.
I'll give you that. Yeah.
They didn't go with the third choice.
Awesome Acres.
Awesome Acres sounds good.
I should say what I'm looking at here.
I just said wow, as if it was interesting to say, wow, OK.
So it's in processing this for the first time.
I mean, it's very yellow and very green.
I think it feels very city of Oz to me.
It feels like does it remind you of something else in the theme parks here recently?
Because it reminded me of something.
Really? I'm not sure what you're getting at.
Well, in the dead center is an extremely discovery mountain looking building.
It looks like it's like a dome ish structure that is very space
mountainy with a glow coming out of it, but a little more ornate.
And I don't know what I'm looking at there.
Well, we don't.
My thing was that it looks not dissimilar to the Epcot
redo. Yeah, the Epcot redo concept art that's already they've already moved past
just for the abundance of greens and black and purple.
Right. There's a lot of yeah, like plant life and trees.
So basically a lot of this stuff is kind of confirmed from rumor.
Basically, you'll be able to supposedly and Jason, correct me if I'm wrong.
And the park for free in the middle of the hub, we get to that hotel for free.
So basically, there's a new city walk.
What we're looking at in the middle is new city walk.
What the shops, I don't know if they're going to call it that.
They should.
But that's a new city walk.
So like that thing with the light shining out the top of it is maybe a restaurant
of some kind.
Wait, there's going to be.
Wait, I'm confused.
That entirely new shopping area.
Yes. And this is the whole park is about what, two miles away from the other two
parks. Sure.
Let me show off. So it's maps its own.
It is its own.
Twelve minutes away down I for.
And it's because this is the former site of Wet n Wild.
No water part. No, it's not.
This is this is actually maybe my favorite fact I learned today.
This is a site that Universal originally bought in 1998
to expand into.
Unfortunately, that site was previously owned by Lockheed Martin.
So after they cleaned up the landfills and toxic sludge left behind.
Whoa. They got to about the point of
2001 when the theme park industry took a very sharp dive in business
due to the September 11th attacks in 2003.
Vivendi Universal sold this plot of land.
And in the mid like around 2015, thereabouts, they started buying it back
piece by piece.
Would they sell it to?
Do we know that?
Oh, I don't know. I don't know that.
That's a good question to find out.
So, yeah, this is where sludge used to be.
It was going to be low income housing.
And then they were like, yeah, let's get let's get that back.
This is what they're making. Yeah, let's make it a fancy park.
So, yeah. So there's a former sludge depot sludge deep formally the sludge depot.
So, yeah. So this is about the whole site is almost as big as the entire
Islands of Adventure, Universal and City Walk site.
Yes. That's right.
Yeah. Equals the two existing parks.
And you can see three.
And then, yes, so no tells.
Is there a that here are the numbers that I could find the number they threw out
today is that the whole site is seven hundred and fifty acres.
A previous public filing had a picture to to show five hundred and forty one
point five acres.
The park itself being one hundred thirty five acres.
To put that in perspective, Islands of Adventure, one hundred and ten acres.
Universal, Florida, one hundred twenty five acres.
Magic Kingdom, one forty two, Epcot, three hundred.
Hollywood Studios, one fifty four.
Animal Kingdom, five hundred acres.
And I'll say those are estimates because I was having a real tough time
finding numbers that everyone could agree on.
It seems like there's a lot of different numbers floating around out there.
I see. Yeah. This will the park itself will be bigger than the other two
universal parks.
A large portion of this land will be dedicated to five thousand and eighty
nine parking spaces, which is speculated to possibly be a surface lot.
That's the comparison. Now we're talking parking lots.
So you see how like that's the green is the universal existing property.
It looks like it's like Indiana or something.
And then Louisiana down on the bottom right is new epic universe.
And they're comparable in size.
Yes. I think it's pretty crazy to they ran out of room like they they did stuff.
How does it come? Do we know you didn't look this up if we had to guess
Tokyo Disney property? Oh, that's a good question.
Pretty sprawl. Oh, that's a good question.
Yeah. Those numbers are out there.
I just wrote down the Orlando once Disney sees one seventy six.
So this is and to use in one fifteen.
Yeah, this is massive. Right.
I mean, this this amount of size is epic. Yeah.
So now factoring in the epicness of it, though, you can see on the art.
And they haven't said anything.
We're going to get into what we think these these little lands are, because
they look exactly even deconstructed in a matter of hours.
Yeah, yeah. But there are like, as you can see, there are big plots
of undeveloped land spokes in the
various slots between the other lands.
So like there's still room for, you know, who knows, four different
I don't know how many tons of expansion, tons of expansion.
So as much as that site is very big, it's not going to be all developed
on right away, seemingly.
Universal's map where they showed like here's the current property
and here's where the expansion is going to be kind of conveniently
erases the rest of the world.
I pulled up with the map looks like with the rest of the world, including I for
if you can see.
So this little spot right here and we'll post all these pictures
on the Twitter account.
So this little red dot is where the property is over here.
This little red dot is the Orlando Convention Center.
So that's a huge convention center.
And right in the middle of the Kisiby St.
Clement, right in the middle.
Further up, you can see the giant Ferris wheel, the wheel at Icon Park,
kind of like the big one in Vegas or the London Eye.
Fun Spot America also on the way to the original universal.
So they've got to carry you over other theme park.
Yes.
Site properties. Yes.
And how do you get from this property to the original mainland universal park?
Well, I think the answer for now is probably going to be buses,
although on a few.
I'm disappointed by that answer.
Well, Jim Hill has been speculating that there are alternative
transportation methods being considered like what I some sort of large birds,
some sort of gondola system, or I don't think they can extend waterways.
Yeah. Fantastic.
Epic catapult. Yeah.
Just individual universal employees driving you in their car.
You got to like move Taco Bell rappers out of the way.
Hey, buddy.
In the back.
You just have to say, hey, buddy, can I get a ride?
And then it's the right you say it in the right way.
I get an epic ride.
Now you may enter.
Ask gas or grass.
No one rides for free to this epic universe.
One of your famous phrases.
I'm looking at this art, too.
Are you still talking about something?
No, I mean, it is it is not going to be self-contained
in the way that Disney World is, obviously, because you start hitting
ponds and neighborhoods and other theme parks and ferris wheels
and major highways cutting right through the center of Orlando.
Or I guess the outskirts.
I don't know where the center of Orlando is, but it would be.
It's interesting to me to see how this will all play out
because Universal's original property is not dissimilar
to Disneyland's of the two parks kind of adjacent to each other.
Hotels and shopping area all connected.
And this kind of breaks that.
And if Disneyland never gets a third gate, they're going to need to do
something similar.
So they might have to be universal, might have to be the guinea pig
in the scenario of theme parks that are related,
but not literally right next to each other and where there's public space in between.
Right. It's Disney World.
The parks are all very spread out, but they own it all.
This will be the first time you're dealing with how do you get people
down the street in a convenient manner? Right.
Do we know where the land they own is on that map?
Has somebody put that together?
It's this right corner, right?
No, but I'm saying what else do they own?
Oh, like, like I would assume really sure I would assume they're
I think I think I've said this on the show before.
I assume Disney has some sort of plan over here in Anaheim
where if they could maybe choke all these businesses out,
they can start buying stuff up so cheap.
And I would imagine that in 20 years, they would want Anaheim
to resemble Orlando if they could do it.
Yeah. If they can get there won't even be roads anymore.
Herb Boulevard's gone. They filled all that in. Right.
Well, yeah. Or it's just private roads somehow.
Like I would assume Universal has it because Universal is very aggressive.
Universal wants to, as Jim Hill has said, flip the script on the Orlando vacation
and make or and make the Universal your number one destination.
And then you'll go, oh, maybe we'll do a couple of days at Disney,
which, of course, would be unprecedented, which they are slowly colonizing
down the road there.
You can see the endless summer resort already kind of breaking.
This is the best word pattern colonization. Yeah. Yeah.
That's sort of what's going on.
These are these kind of what do they call James Tan like encampments?
Essentially. Oh, oh, I know. Yeah.
Settlements. Yeah. Settlements.
Probably a good word. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
This is like original America, except cooler, because they everywhere
has roller coasters. Yeah.
And I feel like I've heard rumors that like universal
like fun, oh, was fun spot was going to go on the market, like Fun Spot America.
Like they had their eyes on that.
What's fun spot America?
Fun Spot America is just kind of like a collection of rides.
It's kind of like a carnival.
Generic generic. I don't know.
Blow it up. Kill it.
Phil, that's what leaks sludge into the land surrounding it.
Make them have to get foreclosed.
And then we get more universal sea world every now and then.
It's like, well, universal just by the sea world property.
Well, that's been a rumor forever, too.
Or like, are they just going to sell all of them off and maybe?
I mean, they've already stopped the Shamu show.
So what's the point of this sea world anyway?
Like, who cares? They no longer have a thing that I just found out about.
A Baywatch stunt show that.
Yeah, they had a Baywatch. Wow.
I know that kind of show, which I knew about because it factored into an episode
like the Baywatch stunt show exists in the world of Baywatch.
Whoa. The lifeguard.
So Mitch Buchanan goes to watch the Baywatch stunt show
in which he's done a voice.
You hear him over the loudspeaker.
This is Mitch Buchanan from Bay.
You're like in this world, you're a lifeguard.
Right. Not a famous person.
Why would you this Baywatch is in a universe
where lifeguards are the most famous people on Earth.
It's similar to now you see me.
One of my favorite franchises in that that's a film where
magicians are the center of everyone's universe.
We're thinking about magicians.
I mean, the horsemen certainly are.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
It would it be that way in our world if there were magicians as good as the horsemen.
But but but there are not, sadly, only in the now you see me universe.
Love those fucking movies.
You got to join up next time.
I haven't seen them.
I don't think I knew you were in the club, the Nicem Club and YSM.
Is there going to be a third one? Yeah, I believe so.
Oh, wow. Yes.
And it's one of those where they're drastically expanding the role of
a Chinese side character to make it do better in China, where it secretly did well.
Oh, no, that's a separate.
Yeah, separate as a spin off.
Well, because a lot of the second one takes place in Macau.
Was there going to be a theme park attraction somewhere in like the Lions
Gate line? Yes, in the Lions Gate.
I'm sorry. So sorry, then that that's not going to.
Well, but it could still have.
So now the Lions Gate stuff again, we call that we call that
would never happen in Times Square.
Very early on, we are. Yeah.
Yeah. But we will call the Quibi will be a smash.
We're going to be a smash hit.
We're putting all of our eggs in that basket.
Yeah. You want to.
So let's just can we direct deposit the Patreon money straight into Quibi stock?
Can we just so there's no middle.
It goes straight into shares of Quibi.
Sure. Yeah, let's do it.
I think we're all agree.
A guy in the train to Comic Con said, don't sleep on Quibi.
And I never did. I haven't yet.
Were you going to like pass out on a dog or something on the train?
It was his dog, Quibi.
Yes, that's what he's talking about.
He was a hobo with a dog named Quibi.
Similarly, a few summers ago, I was at an audition
and I heard a guy in the waiting room go, well, you know,
biggest name of comedy right now, see. So.
And I had just shot something for see.
So and been told, hey, it's going up.
But then see, so shutting down.
So it was great to hear your thing was up for it was like in that
if you turned on see, so in the minute before, like from eleven fifty
nine to midnight, you could watch the flu philanthropy
starring Flula Borg, Ed Helms and me.
And you are the I've seen this.
It's great. And you're the third.
No, no, you're the second lead of the show.
Essentially. Yes.
Yeah. This is a thing the world doesn't get to see.
Yeah, it was up for one for 60 seconds and then.
Yeah. Maybe you'll get a quibby pickup.
Maybe maybe, you know, why not?
We'll see. But did you shoot it in two formats?
Oh, shit. Long ways.
Oh, shit.
Yeah. Yeah. That's going to be hard.
I kill you, unfortunately.
All right. Well, it's all the next one.
You know, they're on it.
It'll air on Epic.
The epic universe only
streaming site that you can only watch it
while you're in epic universe.
Probably not far off, honestly.
It'll be epic how they will somehow pay me even less.
Yeah. Which is which would be
I don't know how they would be able to do that unless they paid me
in the company's script.
Yeah. They'll be able to figure it out, I think.
Yeah. They have people working on the chairs from our office.
You need it. Do you need an office chair?
No. If you can imagine, we don't need it anymore.
We don't need any of these push pins or sticky notes.
Well, it turns out I do need all of those things.
So I'm taking those. Thank you.
All right. So back to this map
with all these lights shooting into the air.
Yeah. So walk us.
You beautiful glowing lights.
It's a very glowy.
Yeah. So we're indicating.
I mean, it needs its own hotel in city walk because it's so far away
from everything else. Right.
Own city. You think they'll call it city walk?
I don't know.
And maybe probably like the marketplace.
That's probably right about that.
It's probably not going to be called city walk.
As this looks like a village, maybe maybe.
I'm going for epic walk.
And maybe I should trademark that word.
Epic Square, maybe.
Epic Square, like it does feel like this is going to be like a classier overall.
They're like, oh, they're going for a Disney sea from at least the look of this art.
We'll see if it actually looks like that detail wise when they build it.
It's kind of an architectural style that isn't specific to it.
It's not emulating a current place.
It feels very future.
It's the future of the Middle East.
I feel maybe like Dubai.
Yeah, sort of.
Yes, I agree with that.
Money is what you're looking at.
That's what you're feeling.
Yes. Yeah.
But it's very but a lot of domes, a lot of domes, atriums.
I'm a fan of that stuff.
I heard there was a rumor that there would be like a couple like mild rides for free.
Now, I'm looking at this thing.
Does this seem like a Ferris wheel?
Perhaps someone's guessing Carousel Carousel.
That's what I meant. I'm sorry.
So maybe they have like a couple little kiddie kind of rides that you can ride for free.
Get you get you a little taste of those rides and then very generous.
You get a ticket.
I mean, where does this where does the park start?
Well, but now that's the thing.
So a big credit to theme park university because it they they called what.
Yeah, so it seems like it was going to be the art.
So the art of this confirms all these rumors for the most part.
Now, I will say Universal is saying basically we're not going to announce any of the lands yet.
We're not announcing when it's opening.
This is still art.
We're not announcing the cost.
Well, yeah. Yeah.
But this is subject to change.
But I would imagine this is going to look pretty similar if they're releasing it.
But yes, theme park university basically called it that you enter here at the bottom here on the bottom.
And that's probably free to enter.
They haven't confirmed that.
And then this is all walkable, free shops, restaurants, maybe a few rides.
You're showing me most of the place.
Right. And this is the hotel, which is found at the opposite side of the park.
Yeah. So supposedly all that is going to be able to be gone into for free.
And then these four sections are the actual park.
So that's the park.
That's the park.
Strange.
And this is the park.
And they won't. You will have to go in and out and leave to get to the other parts.
So you will not be able to get to the other worlds.
Constant going in and out of admission gates.
Yes. That's weird.
It's all I get the idea of it.
I'm I'm of two minds about it, honestly.
Yeah. I mean, they've experimented with a little because to ride that you have not been to Diagon Alley yet.
So if you're going to take the Hogwarts Express while both parks are open, you need to card
in because you are entering a second park.
Yeah. I mean, it's like Disney.
It's like Disneyland, the California adventure.
It's not like that's not it's not like that has no precedent.
I've had four of them.
But is that why that all four of those are like as sizable as a well, that's what's the theme.
I think that could you only buy admission for one or two?
That's a question that I has not been answered.
I'm guessing no, I'm guessing that's going to be too complicated because somebody is going to get
confused and they'd rather just sell a day pass to all of them.
But it's possible. I mean, yeah, I don't know.
I'm confused.
It's possible that you could just buy in.
But I think the rumors are that it's a one day pass and then you can go anywhere you want.
And right now, the rumor was there'll be four different lands when it opens.
And that's what we see on this map and this piece of art.
And now we should really clarify here that we are dissecting a label free map.
Yes, no piece of IP is clear whatsoever.
And that's the big thing from today.
We don't know what the lands are, but we do also if we're going off of this, I think, because it looks well, because it looks OK.
So people have already identified we're late to the start in the lower left and let's just go clockwise.
The one over that's my dog.
That's not so OK.
So here. So people have already named these online.
We're slow to get here.
This, to me, is Nintendo.
This looks just like it.
And someone on a YouTube video points out like this looks so they've decolored
a lot of it to make it a little more generic for whatever, because I guess they just don't want us to know, even though it's pretty clear, like it's boxy and blocky.
And then somebody pointed out this is identical to the Donkey Kong land art that's been released.
And you can see like the little like Tiki, Hutter, Towers or whatever you call them.
And like there's a track there that would be the mine cart coaster.
I think you're right. So it's pretty and Nintendo is not going into islands or main universal.
So I think this is maybe this is the most safe bet of all four.
This for sure is going to be Nintendo.
I think you're correct. And yeah.
And from the look of it, they'll be this is probably the Mario Kart show building right here.
There's a massive show building.
Yeah. And it's a big black box.
So I guess everybody will freak the fuck out like that Guardians thing.
Yes. Everybody cool it about the black.
What else are you going to put up?
It was tall, I guess.
Well, it means you get a big old ride.
Yeah, I don't know.
Where do people are?
Here's a little.
I might say, am I talking to anyone who is like, am I is anyone on the other side of this argument?
And be like, I will choose to stay mad about the black box.
I don't know. Are you guys mad about the big box?
I mean, I'm sure it's also not done.
I don't know. I mean, the universe.
Is it a blue is in a big blue box?
Is it blue? I mean, but it's still how many years from open?
Like I have to think to put something on it like.
I don't know. I mean, I was just like, OK, I don't know.
I didn't really think that much.
Spray paint. Sorry, it's a box.
Yeah. Then then that's OK.
Star Lord, like he wrote it.
And that's a reverent and people like that in one of the public filings.
The site's maximum allowed building height is 400 feet,
which is about 37 stories, just under 37 stories.
I remember that when my grandparents were alive,
their neighbors were mad at them because they built a like a little
like outdoor house on their deck and they couldn't see the boring road
that was passed because they used to be able to see the road
through my grandparents here and they had a big fight about it.
I remember this now.
So I think it's a similar thing.
It's just like a thing goes up and people get mad
because they're used to being able to see where they used to be able to see.
Same thing as my grandparents.
They weren't building a third.
It wasn't a 37 story.
My grandparents did not build a 37 story roller coaster in the back.
It would have been unbelievable.
We have had the finest.
Wait, but what are you missing out on a view of now that there's a box?
No, nothing. I'm just saying it's the idea that you're being deprived
of something, even if it's nothing.
Just the feeling of it is like you're taking something away from certain people.
Sure. Now, I will agree that
when I was in Disney, see, there's a big there's a big old theater.
I didn't see a show in the theater, but then a big old theater has to be in a big box.
But they took the time to theme it and make it bricks that looked nice.
And I appreciated that because that's your view coming into the park.
So I look, I want things to be a city.
I don't want a box, I guess.
But I think people are very mad about this.
I haven't. I mean, I've seen a little of it.
Well, let's make our judgment when we go there.
Maybe we will hate the box and it be agreeing with everyone.
We may yet. Maybe so.
I share with you. We'll see how mad we get.
It might be balanced out that all my friends from Guardians of the Galaxy are inside.
Yeah, think about that.
Yeah, sure. All your buds are there.
Stuber's in there. Stuber is in there.
I don't know which one's Stuber.
I think Kumail is Stuber, but Kumail is not there.
Kumail is joining the Marvel Universe.
So he will be able to reteam with. Is he?
Dave Batista. Yeah, he's in the new.
Was that one of the announcements?
One of the. Yes, it was.
OK. And he's jacked now.
He's getting jacked.
So he's going to be as big as Dave Batista.
Wow. So, yeah.
Stuber will be. People are getting the call that they want.
Like we've chosen you to get jacked.
Yeah. So maybe when they do Stuber too, they'll both be the same size.
Wow. There's a decent chance of that.
Stuber's not going to take your shit anymore.
He says. The whole new dynamic.
Stuber is jacked now.
Super Stuber. That's the tagline.
Oh, Stuber. Super Stuber is a good.
That's a good title. Yeah.
I mean, it's the format of that.
There was a Mario Brothers game and then a Super Mario Brothers.
Some franchise has to go from regular to why not?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
From a date night to super date night.
Good boys to super good boys.
I mean, which but we have.
Well, that's us. Yeah.
Yeah.
We are super good boys today.
And clean our plates.
All right. Anyway, there's another land here.
So this is now bottom right when you're looking at it.
And people are saying because these are the four that were rumored.
And this is the one I would be least sure of.
But how to train your dragon land is probably this bottom right.
There's a big, long dual launch coaster.
And really all nice and very big, huge, very huge.
Looks fun.
I honestly I don't see anything else that would make me think it's
how to train your dragon land.
Other than just reasonably certain that land will be.
But that's what the strong rumor is.
So I'm assuming that it's some sort of dragon coaster.
I think those are like little like places like little like, I don't know.
Like it looks like houses from the movie.
I've never seen it.
I think little like huts and stuff from the movie.
I've never scolded about needing to see these.
Zach did.
These are.
Yeah, I believe people like these a lot.
I haven't done it yet.
I haven't.
Three of them now.
I like to start.
You know, I got to start at the beginning.
Although I saw now you see me too before one and I was so taken with it.
I like immediately ran home and when it was spoiled.
Oh, that's it.
I had already.
You knew the horseman.
Yeah.
I still got a lot of wrestling to catch up on.
So I can't watch it.
Although I did watch Hello.
I did watch Hellraiser.
Lindsay and I watch Hellraiser.
Oh, you went to a world beyond pleasure and pain.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah.
If you think because I was thinking like, you know, I'm in a haunts and I was saying,
well, but like I never wanted to watch horror movies and as a kid, I went into blockbuster
and I would see Hellraiser and I would think, why would you ever?
Yeah.
Why would you ever scared by the very idea, the idea of pinhead and the thing sticking
into his face?
And I was like, I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know what's sticking into his face.
And I was like, well, and she was like, yeah, I felt the same when I go, well, let's see
what I go because I have no concept of what it's like.
I really don't.
So I was like, all right.
And it is gross as shit.
It's so gross.
And then pinhead doesn't show.
This spoiler alert from a movie came out in 1987.
Pinhead and his cronies don't show up until like an hour into it.
And he and his cronies are great.
He's like an English guy and they're like maybe all English and they have cool designs.
And then when they show up, you're like, oh, that's cool.
They come out of this weird box.
The lament configuration.
You've seen it.
I haven't seen it.
It's just been a running thing on Twitter lately.
Like everyone keeps seeing hell raiser jokes.
I've just like you have just most.
I've watched Hellraiser because people because I'm not.
What do they say in that?
Like I have such wonderful things to show you or like something like that.
Something like that.
The plot is insane.
The plot is a woman wants starts killing people to help resurrect her dead ex-boyfriend that
she used to have like hot sex with.
And she's like so in love with him still.
She starts killing people.
And then the daughter of her current husband like meet Pinhead and his cronies and they
want to like take the other guy's soul back.
So she gets mixed in with all of it.
But then I was like once Pinhead showed up, I was like, OK, I like this.
Before that, it is a lot of like hooks going into fake skin and ripping the skin and blood
everywhere.
And there's tons of these movies.
I think there was just a direct to Netflix.
There's like 10 hell raisers and I think they're all bad except maybe the first two.
Yeah.
But anyway, so now I'm Fred Durst has directed like three of them that we don't know.
All right.
So this is the Hellblazer portal.
This is the next one is Hellblazer.
You have to solve a puzzle box to get into it.
There's 30 pictures of Edwin.
Well, he does.
He gets his own.
My phone is, of course, like overheated now and it doesn't want to.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
There's a lot of pressure on your phone.
So thanks for bouncing your phone to the TV to give us an epic view.
Also, I'm glad the park will always have fireworks.
Yeah.
Going just all hours of the day.
Just once an hour.
Eight hours.
Oh, yeah. Maybe it just never stops.
I hope so.
It's just. Yeah.
That's where all the money goes.
So we go up here and the fantastic beasts and where to find them.
The Harry Potter spin off.
I would think this is that was a rumored land.
And this looks like fantastic beasts because it looks like old time New York City.
And what I like about is that right?
No, I zoom in a little.
I think it's supposed to be Paris.
Oh, is that right?
See the blue and the yet potentially.
Where is that? Where am I looking at?
The old time New York.
Zoom in on just like the windows.
No, to the right.
I can only zoom so far here.
The people were speculating, I think, just because the tan, those blue roofs are kind of all over Paris.
Sure.
OK.
I think you're right.
So where's that movie set?
This is in place in Paris.
OK, because the original was in New York.
So now it's who knows?
Subject to change city.
What I do like about this is that it appears to be the whole land is in a show building from the look of this, maybe past the fireworks.
But that means you can do a lot, obviously, of like, you know, setting a scene and a mood if you can control the sky.
Sure.
So they can control the sky.
Do you feel at all, though, now with Fantastic Beasts and How to Train Your Dragon, we're pretty specific to franchises?
Well, this is and this is, yeah, people have been talking about Star Wars and people were upset that such a big thing was was devoted to an IP,
which, you know, we all like Cars Land and I think we kind of aren't too hard saying, agreeing with those people.
But I think with Dragon and especially Fantastic Beasts, the bloom is a little bit off the rose on the Fantastic Beasts at this point,
unless this next movie like resuscitates it.
So it is, you know, this thing will open in two years, three years, probably, probably three years at least.
Yeah, at least.
If not, but Universal does build fast and then half of it doesn't work, but they do get it open.
So, yeah, Fantastic Beasts is done.
The next movie eats shit.
And there's a whole one of the quarter of the park is devoted to it.
It is a little weird.
I do wonder if they didn't announce all the lands because they're wondering if they could just maybe generically call this Harry Potter three version three or something.
You know what I mean?
There might be a chance that like if they had developed a magic based attraction, just call it Harry Potter or call it like Harry Potter's Paris or whatever.
Well, like, you know, even Star Wars.
Yeah, it's a land based on the biggest IP of all time.
And the fact that it is, you know, it's probably largely episode seven through nine, but, you know, it's sort of mendable.
Flexible.
Star Wars in general and its own thing.
And yeah, but yeah, I mean, you're right that Cars is not a pro.
I don't know why I'm bringing this up with them that these feel a little less like, well, classic or like, will they all matter in five years or?
I think a couple of that one universal has always been ride the movies.
So it's movies people know I have to think they focus group like tested enough of that.
These are things people have a positive association with and like I mean, Nintendo feels like a slam dunk.
Well, that's why I like of all four and we'll get to the last one of all four Nintendo slam dunk.
How the Train Your Dragon sustained three movies, I think pretty well reviewed universally.
Like not like my Edwin is having a nightmare.
If that's the noise you're hearing on the mics, it sounds like he's underwater when he has a bad dream.
But yeah, so Nintendo, obviously, that's going to be around forever, seemingly forever.
Like, there's no slowing down. All the games are still great.
But yeah, I don't know.
I wonder because because for a while it was this was going to be called Fantastic Worlds, which was fantastic, similar to Fantastic Beasts.
Like maybe they were like, oh, this is the anchor that his nightmare is getting worse.
Yeah. Wow. Oh, boy.
Edwin, who's who's good? Edwin.
So many yips. Edwin.
Oh, gosh. Wow.
I wonder if the listener can hear.
Is this a common thing on a podcast where the hostess to apologize for his dog having a loud underwater nightmare?
You know, we really haven't apologized for technical difficulties, maybe ever.
So, yeah, we got a good track record with that, but that is a very distracting sound.
I think he's out of it right now.
See, what's is he having a nightmare about there being another giant deaf robot in the park world?
Yeah, he doesn't like this.
A Grindelwald. He specifically he likes Jack.
OK, but Grindelwald, he hates Grindelwald is the mascot for the whole park.
Grindelwald walking around.
It's a nightmare, but I for traffic.
You want to get stuck on it? Look, there's a bunch that's closed right now.
You can't even take that off.
Well, they are going to have to fix that.
They're going to have to fix. I do wonder.
Oh, it went off the screen.
I do wonder if it's just like, yeah, Harry Potter's New York or whatever.
You call me Paris.
Magical, the magical world, the Wizarding World.
There I guess that.
I guess that's true.
Wizarding City.
But the last quadrant is classic.
Well, so the last quadrant, it was the rumor and we talked about it a little bit,
but it's on the map and it looks to be the smallest of the four,
potentially, maybe Fantastic Beasts.
But it looks like Universal Classic Monster Land is here,
which is the most exciting of all four and me.
And maybe just I mean, Nintendo, very exciting, too.
But the idea of like probably having more leeway, honestly, of all four.
Yeah, because these are like they're supposedly based again on the classic
monster movies, so probably they can do whatever they want.
So you're looking at like what appears to be like a castle and like a small town,
like a creepy town that I'm sure they'll do, like a flash mob of like Frankenstern
chasing Frankenstein's monster with pitchforks.
Like that would be fun.
And every like at nine o'clock at night,
you get to grab a pitchfork and chase a monster out of town.
That's my kind of interactive experience.
You'll you'll be I'll be I'll be a pig.
We'll be part of chasing him away.
Yeah, well, I guess that's no, no, no.
Oh, I'll be the one who like gets in front of the mob and is like, no,
you don't understand.
He's he has feelings.
We are the monsters. Right.
I love him. I love him.
I'm in love with him.
So they'll pick somebody out of the crowd to do that.
And it'll be me.
I mean, I think I feel like maybe pitchforks,
but I don't think Universal's going to willingly have a torch wielding mob.
Yeah.
2019. That's true.
A tiki torch mob.
That would be a bad optics, maybe.
Yeah. Or may our regular or honest to God torches.
It's still in vogue.
Are they still? Yeah, that's a good.
Societal with classic monster movies.
Or they'll sell like a kiddie version of a torch with like a light up fire.
So they'll make like thirty dollars per torch.
Pretty good idea, I think.
And then like there's there's like monsters that will interact with in the land.
So you wave. It's like the Harry Potter ones.
You wave your child's torch at like a Frankenstein robot and he goes,
and like that'll be fun for the kids.
Because they can sell RFID crosses to like word off.
That would be a poor taste. Yeah.
Mm hmm. But they can sell garlic.
Oh, that's better. That's yeah, that is good.
So there'll be different things.
You can buy that a Bluetooth in them to ward off the monsters.
Met a Dracula monster.
Yeah, I don't know how the Dracula a Dracula, you know, a Dracula monster.
I didn't think a second thought of when you said it.
I think we're all agreed in the way we like to say these monster names.
And you're with a hunchback.
You can also see there's like an empathy.
No one's quite sure what the do you have a guess of what the empathy or is?
Just his graveyard review.
A giant beetle juices graveyard.
Finally, the 5000 seats that he's been asking for.
Yeah, the capacity, because it's always sold out.
You can never get in finally.
Or just a permanent Bill and Ted show.
Oh, my God.
An epic Bill and Ted show, maybe rewritten topical every night.
Yeah. You can go to the warm up.
You can watch them rehearse at three thirty.
They're doing it more casually in plain clothes, throwing cards out. Right.
John Hickenlooper.
John Delaney.
Jay Inslee.
Yeah. But what was the one?
Biden 3033.
Oh, yeah.
Was this be all by the time this comes out?
But what was Biden three?
Was Joe 303?
So he fucked that up.
I believe he said it was a website.
And what he was supposed to say is if you text Biden
to that sequence of numbers, all right.
He also fucked up deductibles and copays.
Kind of an important distinction for a health care debate to have.
Sort of big this year.
Sort of big.
Might not have the stamina for this. Yeah.
Anyway, yeah. Go to 303.
What do you mean? Go to it.
Is it a physical place?
You talk about a box I have to find.
Walk to the box. Walk to the area.
All right.
It's going to be a lot now. That's going to be a lot of traffic.
Everybody going to three or three.
Oh, it once had you think Biden has ever taken the Hogwarts Express?
He loves trains. He loves trains.
I mean, he goes to Universal.
That's all he does. Yeah.
He has the Hogwarts.
Well, we can circle back around to closing thoughts on this.
But I since you bring up trains.
Oh, I cannot help this segue.
Do you guys know about Virgin Trains USA?
Yeah. So no reason to go into it.
I know all about it.
I'm covered.
No, I don't know. What's this?
So this is currently the United States is only privately owned
and operated intercity passenger railroad.
Virgin Virgin Richard Branson owned Richard Branson.
Trains. Yeah, they took over.
I think it was called Brightline previously.
And he owns it unlike because he sold Virgin Airlines to Alaska Airlines.
Right. He still owns this.
He still owns some Virgin stuff.
So this is a line connecting
the downtowns of Fort Lauderdale, West Palm Beach and Miami.
And they are expanding to Orlando,
to a terminal at the Orlando International Airport.
The what is it called?
I believe it's the Intermodal Terminal.
An Intermodal Terminal uses multiple forms of transportation.
In this case, the train probably in the future, a regional rail,
people movers to get you to the main, of course, the famous Orlando Airport
people movers, the main airport terminal is about a mile away
from this intermodal terminal that's still being built.
It reuses the plans for the former Florida High Speed Rail,
which Florida scumbag Rick Scott, the former
Florida governor, said he would not take federal funding for that project.
Right.
Current Florida scumbag governor
Rick DeSantis was at this announcement today at the convention center.
He didn't really say anything.
But he's OK with he's OK with intermodal intermodality.
I look well, I think because private industry is paying for it.
Oh, I see that changes. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. So no skin off his back. So no skin off his back.
So this so this is connecting Miami to Orlando,
which is a big deal. It's connecting at the airport.
There's rumors that they've been talking to Disney to have a stop at Disney World.
And at this event today, you know,
Universal had said, like, you know, with every bit of strength we've got,
we're trying to get a stop at the convention center,
which is right across from where this new park will be.
OK, so high speed rail, a privately owned rail,
which in Japan, there's hundreds of rail.
Yeah, it's everywhere.
It's everywhere. Sure.
And a convenient way to get to the parks, among other things.
So this that would be nice because it's like it's hard.
You have to get a long list to get to these places from the airport.
Yeah, we know that's always a bummer.
And you get like, wow, I'm in Orlando.
And it's really if it's five p.m., it's like 45 minutes to an hour drive sometimes.
Yeah. If it's like in the middle of rush hour. Yeah.
So, yeah, high speed rail. Great.
Richard Branson save us, I say. Yeah.
He seems like we love him among the lesser of the evils of well, mega billionaires.
Yeah. I mean, just search like Richard Branson picking up women.
And it's strange.
You'll see like 30 different pictures of him, like forcibly holding a woman
in his arms, like at a photo op.
And you're like, oh, something going on there. Yeah.
But even but something going on is better than like specifically
a utter piece of trash specifically.
Yeah. I mean, I think wasn't he accused of something to a couple of months ago?
Probably. Probably. Yeah.
Yeah. But I guess in the scheme of cues is better than if you're still at large.
If you're comparing him to Cosby, 100 percent better than.
Oh, you didn't say you said mogul.
So I would not take Cosby's high speed rail line.
Steve Wynn, I guess, has been he's pretty bad.
You know, he's not so good as the president of Trump enterprises.
Donald Trump. I don't believe that.
Yeah. I've heard some not so good things about him.
I don't believe it.
He seems like a nice guy.
I like when he's on TV. He's very dynamic. Yes.
Tom Williams, chairman and CEO getting back to the park now.
So Tom Williams, chairman and CEO of Universal Parks and Resorts says
today at this event, a universe is bigger than a world,
which I feel like is a line that I am shocked we did not hear
in the Democratic debate.
So congratulations to Tom Williams for throwing his hat in.
I'm sure him and his people thought that was a slam dunk line.
Yeah. So that's like the other shots fired shot fired world
here. So, yeah, I mean, we're looking I mean, we'll just anything.
Like, I'm fascinated by what this Epcot looking building is.
Looks a lot like mission space. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, the thing with any concept movie concept art, especially,
like, well, it could be.
There's no specifics, but it gives an impression.
It gives a vibe. Right.
Here's the hall of presidents over here. Sure.
They're just going to do their own. Yeah.
Universal presidents.
So like was Harrison Ford in Air Force One?
Was he was he a universal movie?
Oh, that's a good question. Yeah.
Any anyone who was ever in a universal movie?
Yeah. Was the my fellow Americans?
Was Dave Universal?
No, it's in universal films.
We got any Google results for that?
They're all like from the past.
There's an old movie.
No, that's just that Ronald Reagan was in a movie called Law and Order.
That counts. Put him in. Yeah.
OK, great. From 1953, he stopped at an all time high.
Yes. This very week.
Yeah. Anything horrible.
But let's go. Let's think about those better days when he played
a character named Frame Johnson.
What? Frame.
Know what he was called? Frame?
Not even in 1953. That's fake. That's madness.
It'll be the hall of current universal executives.
The hall of C-suite in the hall of VP executive VPs.
Dwight Cain's co-president domestic marketing.
Cobbcast CEO Brian Roberts.
Rowan Kahn.
Some more numbers.
Fourteen thousand jobs.
They're saying this will bring to the area at fifteen dollars an hour,
which the current universal rate is twelve dollar base salary.
They said what they're going to pay.
They're saying well, because I think it makes it tries to get them some goodwill.
But people, I mean, you know, there's a lot of the fight for 15 now,
which is great.
But even by this year, fifteen dollars is not enough.
Like the people already talking about like twenty.
It should be a twenty dollar minimum wage to keep up with.
Well, it's cost of living and inflation and that sort of thing.
So right now is a great time for them to say and fifteen dollars.
And also the park will be opening twenty twenty nine. Bye, everybody.
Yeah. And then we'll put two and two together.
Florida minimum wage currently is eight forty six.
Is it really? Yeah.
So they do pay more than minimum wage.
But as people who live down there and travel down there regularly have told us,
like it is getting like everywhere else, it's getting more expensive.
Sure. So, yeah, that's kind of a transparent move.
Like we're going to pay everyone fifteen dollars and five years, three to five years.
Yeah.
There's yeah. So I'm just looking if there's anything else interesting on this map.
I like the intro.
The intro, like the little there's like a little like thing you have to enter.
Oh, you can't see it there. No, there it is.
There's like a little like creepy looking like mouth.
Oh, to get into this universal classic monsters.
That's the one where I wish that I had a higher, even higher res
to see into it, because it looks very, very cool.
Yeah. It's just like an old timey town square.
Yeah. Like they all live in one place.
And the rumor is, yeah, you ticket maybe Kuka arm.
Dracula's castle ride with all the monsters. Wow.
Which would be great.
And I think I've said before, like they make so much money off of scary stuff
at horror nights.
It is surprising to me it would be it's taken this long to like just get
something like kind of scary into one of the parks, like at a high level,
not like just a walk through maze.
But you would think, yeah, that's so much of their business that.
Yeah. So that that's good.
Like, let's do that. That's fun.
They should. They also a plus up I have already.
Throw the Munsters house on that place.
Yeah. In that area, too.
Absolutely. That would be great.
I have a fun one. Scary one.
Bachelor pad have his first beer with him.
Yeah. And it's you can get a big sandwich there, too, like Dagwood.
Oh, well, I mean, Dagwood should be in every park.
Yeah, there should be a whole Dagwood land.
You're all this thing epic.
And it's not even you can't even buy one lousy Dagwood in here.
Well, there's still as we said, there's there's room for expansion.
So maybe the Blondie expansion will happen in a couple of years.
Well, I mean, will Disney, though, fight this now that they own
the rights to 20 20th Century Fox's epic
featuring Nimgaloo, our beloved character, Nimgaloo.
I wanted to be Nimgaloo.
I can't even wish I forget how much we've
did we have people have people seen the video.
Did we play the video?
I think people are talking about it.
Yeah, I felt a little bit of resonating.
We tweeted people know about Nimgaloo.
Nimgaloo, Nimgaloo, who talks to like some snails, eyes bang together.
Uh huh.
It's something like here.
Anything's possible.
Anything you can imagine is possible.
And then they make a silly face and go, even this.
He says, yes, even this.
They make a sillier face.
Yes. It's a real it's a remarkable scene.
And then he does like, and you know, I had to do a song for this movie.
Let's get a bit of a diva diva diva diva diva diva diva diva diva diva diva.
My name is Galu.
Is Nimgaloo in the song?
I don't I'm not sure about that.
We've got to look that up.
Yeah, we'll do a whole name.
Galu, I think they were character episode, the Tyler.
That's another we've been talking a lot about these voices like, yeah,
the acting voice of Steven Tyler, right?
Who I guess was on The Simpsons, but playing the less challenging role
of Steven Tyler.
Yeah.
Hmm.
Well, maybe, yeah, maybe if did if you were Jason's proposing
that Disney will fight back with its own epic expansion, literally epic,
the movie that will be more Steven Tyler acting and much more Nimgaloo.
Is there a way that they can like put a really tiny
semicolon or something in there to make it epic universe?
And then they technically like built they build that name first.
Like it's is that little colon is the key to separating it.
That would be they should do that.
We'll give you the Marvel characters back.
OK, you can doom in Orlando.
Just let us have a Nimgaloo.
Let us have this company.
Fantastic piece, three, eight shit.
That's the thing.
Maybe it maybe that's with how to train your dragon.
It's like it was consistent.
It was solid. It was well reviewed.
It it doesn't have like the baggage of like
secret life of pets to or crimes of Grindelwald, where it's like, oh, no.
That's right. You're saying the perception is actually important.
I'm just going all this with three movies that we liked and not like, oh, no,
that thing, that thing ain't shit.
Yeah. I mean, it's like that rumor that was going around a few years ago.
It's probably a Jim Hill thing or a guest on his podcast said like
people like Shrek.
People fondly think of Shrek and the Shrek universe.
Yeah, they do not necessarily want any more of this current run of Shrek.
Well, that is for sure.
I mean, there's going to be new Shrek movies for sure.
They got to spice them up.
They got to redesign them.
We well, the rumor I think was live act like Disney live action Shrek
with CGI Shrek.
That's what I heard. At least really different, though.
It's barely different, but they'll have like real humans.
Maybe Farquaad could be played by a real man.
Yeah, that's right.
And then like it's in a lot of prosthetics.
Yeah. And then the same voices for Shrek and Fiona and Donkey.
Sure. Malibu Stacey has a new hat.
Yeah, they would keep all the same people.
That's what I've heard. I mean, this is a real.
This hasn't been been.
There was also rumors that one of these worlds was going to be the swamp
was going to be Shrek's.
Well, the swamp real quick.
We'll talk about some rumors I've heard over the years was there was going to be a full
one of the hubs was going to be Shrek and it was going to be a take on Disney.
So you'd walk down like a weird main street, but it was Shrek.
So it was a little bit
a little ribald, a little ribald, a little bit irreverent, you know.
They would have dared to make a joke about it's a small world being an annoying.
We went there.
Yeah. Edgy. That's if the park was edgy.
Yeah. Yeah.
But I mean, maybe one of the extra lands will be edgier.
Other rumors, Jurassic World, which we don't see any evidence of that.
So maybe they will just totally because for a while it was like,
maybe they'll just do Jurassic Park and Jurassic World in two different parks.
And there's the rumor that the second gate to begin with was going to be all
Jurassic Park. Yeah.
It was an interesting alternate universe, but probably would have been limited.
I think it's probably worked out that it's one of five.
And yeah, that would have been interesting.
But yeah, I don't know how long that would have how long that would have sustained.
Yeah. Rumors of Star Trek land.
Yeah. But I think they don't like that's still paramount.
So I don't know if you know, well, no, Universal doesn't own Nintendo
and doesn't own Harry Potter.
So they're still working with things.
I think when they partner with people, they want to make sure it's safe bets.
Like Harry Potter or Nintendo after Picard comes out and it's a smash.
Then maybe we'll see a Picard land.
Did you guys see the wine, the official Picard wine? No, but I will.
I will have a really. Yeah, I am excited.
I think a red a red and white ones is Infidel.
I love that. The other is a Bordeaux.
Oh, because Picard has been now on his winery for 20 years.
That's the premise of the show.
Something bad happened.
And he went back to France where he has his winery, where he and that's
that's in canon.
He fought with his brother at the winery on Next Generation
in one of the early seasons.
So I thought the show was about boring spaceships or something.
Now that I know it's about it's about property disputes on wineries.
Yeah, I think they like literally were in the mud in front of the grapes.
I believe on the episode.
Oh, boy. Star Trek, as I said, I think there is an in for you somewhere
because of how old TV it is. Next Gen specifically.
Yeah, there's some old TV and like good boring stuff on it.
Yeah, I know. There's got to be there's got to be an angle.
I'd like to figure it out. An alien.
So, yeah, put heart.
Maybe that will be the land.
It'll just be a big winery.
Wine always a good wine's been my in for scary roller coasters.
So it might be my in for the show.
Cool bottles. Whoa, it is.
Oh, yeah. Well, I mean, more so the red on the left.
If that is a red jeez, that's a that's a space angled bottle.
That's cool. I think it's made by a company called
is it called Rockstar Wines?
Is that what it's called?
Yeah, stock sinking fast.
But we'll try to get a hold of of those.
Yeah, we'll review that on the show.
Total totally bad ass wine.
Lord of the Rings rumored.
Yeah, for a long time.
Not sure that they've worked even the deal out with having the rights to that.
But there's a big Amazon, like
five hundred million dollar TV show Lord of the Rings coming.
So you would think that might end up somewhere.
Your questions are finally answered.
Yeah, we had a lot of questions after with the three Hobbits,
three Hobbits, three Lord of the Rings with extended editions.
Four books.
That's the scenario.
Yeah. Now we're getting like 60 episodes of television.
It's not like that. Something crazy.
It's not good. Oh, really?
Oh, well, well, that was I've only heard that replacing Marvel Superhero Island.
It's a really Jim Hillie rumor.
That's a Jim Hill rumor.
And he's heard him say it multiple times is that they'll re theme
the whole coaster to the Wicked Witch coaster.
Seems a bit implausible to me because it's green.
I guess because it's green.
Yeah. Well, you would have to paint.
And they're supposed the Wicked Movie eventually is coming.
I don't know when.
So you're in a the canon that transformed her into a witch.
I guess. Yeah.
So when you would be transformed into the Hulk, you'd be transformed into the Wicked
Witch. Maybe that's what it is.
Which would feel like you're shot out of a cannon.
Yeah. Yeah.
If riding around on a road.
That's it. Exactly.
So you take the Hulk's head off and you put the witch on in the statue
below the coaster.
And then Spider-Man, I don't know what you do to it.
Dr. Glinda's fear fall.
I mean, Lord and Lord of the Rings and all rumor to replace every island.
I think. Yeah.
Hold on. I have one more joke.
Sorry. Wicked and Marvel.
They all come out on ATVs every 45 minutes.
Which and. Well, he got the ATVs.
Yeah, they repaint them green and they all come out in ATVs every 45 minutes.
Yeah. And also, well, and the other rumor that is not for this one, but is
Zelda replacing Lost Continent.
Yes. So there's more Nintendo on the way potentially.
OK. So that's what we know now.
That's what we know to speculate.
It's fun to imagine.
The one question I have and I saw this a couple of days ago and I swear
I booked Mark the tweet and I could not find it.
If anyone who is looking at the logo for Epic Universe can tell me,
tweet at me, what is this thing called?
It's a star finder.
It's a navigational tool.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Is it like a centuries old navigational tool?
It's not a compass, not a compass.
OK. It's kind of like a compass.
Not a compass or a compass.
OK. Neither of them.
All right.
Well, I've been trying to be better.
I've let like two mispronunciations go.
I know it'll go lately too.
It's fine. It's the three of us and I feel like it wouldn't derail.
No, no, it's fine.
Now I've got to go back and listen to see all these ones you let go.
No, I don't even remember them.
Can you spot them? Yes.
Yeah. If someone could tell me what that's called, because I had it
a few days ago and I cannot find out what the name is.
Chloe Goldring.
Ball. Gold ball.
So, yeah, that's your in depth analysis of no information.
One picture and the information.
Thing to do on a podcast and the information, all that we sort of knew already.
And you could have found easily three weeks ago on various websites.
I do think that people are not.
I mean, I'm one of the hosts.
I wasn't looking at these rumors.
That's true.
So at least some people won't be disappointed by the information they already know.
I was surprised by all of it today.
That's good.
This has taught me a lesson, which is don't prepare ever.
Yeah, it does. It doesn't matter.
Honestly, the quality of the show probably doesn't suffer at all.
If any of us are prepared or not.
I don't think so either.
Because people like when we, you know, go on tangents and do, you know,
the comedy bits and I end up stressing about like,
well, I need to make sure I know when the when they went to the council
to get the proper zoning in 1962.
So far, people are like, oh, this episode's real dry.
Oh, man, Jason said compass again.
Hell, yeah, this is funny.
They're good.
His ass.
Get him.
Maybe the one thing.
And then they'll talk to me.
If they do have a friend that listens, which they don't, they'll say.
And that's not a slight against them.
I'm just saying how would there be no way that multiple people subscribe
to this Patreon, right, that know each other?
Yeah.
For from separate means and then talk to each other about it.
And sanity, if you subscribe to the Patreon, obviously you're very shameful,
shame, shameful feeling about it.
Every time that five dollars.
Are you?
What I'm just saying, you know,
oh, I'm paid another five dollars to hear these idiots.
But now that they know that they're
they're helping us get in on the ground floor of the future of entertainment.
Yeah, would be. Yeah.
Right. Yes.
So, yeah, they're helping the we're going to be the next Richard Branson's.
Mm hmm.
Off of our Quibi earnings.
And we're going to be so much better.
We're not going to pick up a woman or whatever it was.
I was actually about to pledge that in five years we will pick up
a lot of women at press events.
So I was going to go the other way with it.
I'll stick to desserts.
Thank you very much.
Google Jason Sheridan picking up desserts.
Fifty different things of you like holding a dessert.
The dessert seems like it doesn't want to be picked up,
but you're holding it over your head on a plate.
I wouldn't seem like it. It's melting.
Yeah, it's trying to escape from the bowl. Right.
Well, because it doesn't want to get eaten.
Yeah, that's true. But too bad.
Don't make this nice new park tawdry.
I don't know that we really tawdried it up that bad, but
I do by saying that ice cream will be melted or wasted.
My love of ice cream is pure.
Yeah. Well, we'll do a full another speculation episode about like
what types of ice cream each land will have. Oh, green.
You know, flavor dragon berry ice cream.
Oh, oh, tour or berry ice torch cone torch.
Orange cream, orange cream and a black black or brown
cone, darker brown little strawberry drizzle like blood.
Yeah, that's good.
And Frankenstein sees that and is like fire. Good.
I think we can't top that.
Let's get out of here now.
And that's so folks at the universe.