Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain treacherous tales of photoventury, secret log
sock exchanges, and the stonifying of Usumate.
Mary Holland takes us to a bear-themed land containing no bears.
It's Grizzly River Run on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men who have not signed
up for Disney Plus yet, but would do it immediately if they announced a show based on an anthropomorphic
river rapid that lives in Grizzly River Run.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
So wait, if a rapid is anthropomorphic, that's just like a splash?
Yeah, well, it's a piece of the river in my mind.
So it's like it has a face and two eyeballs.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
A rapid.
A single rapid, yes.
A single rapid.
All right.
So you're a friend of the rapid, and you root for him.
And he's friends or enemies, or enemies maybe with a different rapid, with the other many
rapids, I guess.
Yeah, obviously, like we're going to explore his relationship with the other rapids.
That's Scott Garner talking.
Do extreme sports in me, but don't film me with garbage.
That's how that's you.
By the way, you do the voice for the show.
What's his name?
Like, Rivy or something?
It was your pitch.
Yeah.
Well, I'm just saying we're all working on it now.
We're all in this together.
Actually, future guest of the show, Danny Jelenek and I were working on an idea about
a bunch of alive waves called wavies.
Really?
So it's the same idea.
We haven't picked that idea up in a while, but...
Wow, it's the same idea.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We can ship that over to being rapidies.
Yeah, well, let's bring our guest in to pitch on this great idea.
You know, well, she's from coming into...
The show is coming out on Comedy Central.
You know what?
She's coming.
It's coming out on TV soon.
It's a Comedy Central show called Robbie.
She's here to talk about bears and water.
It's Mary Holland.
Hello.
You know me from the future.
I always say, you know me from, and then I was like, no, it's a future credit.
Wow.
Horses, UCB.
That's true.
Yes, yes.
I'm around, folks.
Yeah.
You didn't just step off the bus this week?
No, no, no, no.
Like 11 years ago, like...
Oh, boy.
Yeah.
Oh, I've been just chugging along for a long time.
In a minute.
And so many Google results in the meantime.
That's right.
Everyone can check it out.
I love this writer's room that I'm stepping into.
Yeah.
We're pitching on this idea.
What do you think the rapids name should be?
I think it should be Grizzly.
Okay, Grizzly the rapid.
Yeah.
But is Grizzly sort of playing against the type?
Because I feel like it's maybe a meek rapid.
Yeah, yeah.
You know what I mean?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it's not like a crazy, you know...
No, it's not like white water rapid, you know.
Right.
It's like when a little character is called...
Yeah, or like Joe or something.
Yeah, it's a teeny tiny...
Yeah, it's a tiny little rapid.
It's making up for the lack of aggression.
Yeah, when he was in the rapid high school
and like the jocks would be like, come on, Grizzly.
And they would say it all sarcastic,
but now he sort of wears it as a badge of honor.
That's right.
He's embraced it.
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
I like that.
Take the power back.
So we would sign up for Disney Plus if the show would exist.
So just throwing it out.
Does a rapid...
Does it have to be like...
So I picture it sort of like mid peak, like it's bubbling.
It's like in the middle of it's foaming up and at its height.
So how can a rapid exist when it's not in the middle of a splash?
It's a very good question.
It's a question we're facing on wavies as well.
So I'm just...
Should we outsource this question to your listeners?
How we would be able to like this,
the distinction between just the normal water
and the characters that are water.
Because the water itself might not be.
It's a rapid is...
Right.
The rapid is a talking, thinking thing,
but the water is what the rapid lives in,
even though they are both water.
Yeah.
Sometimes there's a little rapid.
Like sometimes that's what like the ones that surprise people.
Like you went past the waterfall and then there's a little splash
and that's when you actually get wet.
But it's like a little trick.
So it's a little trick.
It's a little trick.
So the character is a little trick.
Rapids are water tricks.
So that I guess that makes them all mischievous.
Yes.
They're all...
They're up to hijinks.
A lot are sneaking behind,
like they're trying to hide in a place where you wouldn't know a big splash was coming.
Maybe it's just that they're like darker blue.
The water is lighter blue and they're darker blue.
Or they're lighter because they're like white.
They're white water rapids.
Oh, good point.
Yeah.
They might have to be light.
That might set them apart from the blue color.
And so this room, we're here for eight hours.
Is that right?
Yes.
We got a crowd going today.
This room is lasting.
Okay.
Yeah.
You've signed a free contract to develop a Disney series.
That is the future for sure.
Like the podcast and they're just like, well, we own everything you said today.
Yeah.
That's true.
Oh, God.
Yes, you're right.
I keep all my brilliant ideas to myself.
That's why you haven't heard any brilliant ideas yet is because I'm just aware that you guys will claim ownership.
Oh, yeah.
Keep it flat.
You can say stuff, but just, you know.
Keep it super mundane and flat.
The rapids ride exists.
That's your observation today.
Don't ascend to brilliance.
Any joke you were to say today, you would catch like you would hear from somebody else.
Like we were using them like out on the town.
Out on the town.
We were just to entertain in a bar.
If anybody uses any more of my jokes out on the town, I'm going to flip my lid.
Yeah.
People are just out on the town all the time using my jokes.
That's so funny.
Walking across a bridge, hailing a cab.
Yeah.
Hailing a cab with one of your jokes.
Just running errands with my jokes.
They're for fun and not for commerce.
I don't like the thought of it.
All right.
Well, we're going to talk about Grizzly River Run today.
You were talking about California Adventure in general.
Let's just get your feelings in the theme parks, Disney, all of it.
Where do you start with all this stuff?
I am pro all of it.
Good.
You passed the first test.
I love them so much.
I remember my first Disney experience when I was four years old.
I had severe asthma.
My mother had to stay in the hotel with me for the most part.
There were a few days when I was in good enough health where I could go out into the park with the rest of my family.
I had never experienced anything like it.
It was life changing, truly.
It was magical.
I remember I had a real breakdown heading into it's a small world after all.
I still like I can almost remember the smell of the building that I don't even know if it's a building actually.
The line going into where you get into the boats that then go into this dark tunnel.
I remember I saw people getting in boats and going into darkness and I lost my damn mind.
I really like it's like the worst tantrum you can imagine a child having.
I was like flailing my body around.
I was screaming.
I was crying.
My poor mother.
I don't know how they didn't were just like let's get the hell out of here.
We got onto the boat.
I was freaking out.
We went into the darkness and then I was like this is great.
I was having the best time.
Anyway.
That could have been a cave.
They could have been just like a big knife slicing you up.
You didn't know what that was.
Exactly.
This was in Florida, right?
Yes.
The small world where you get in in Florida is an enclosed building but it's kind of outside.
It's got very high ceilings and it does kind of trap that deep water smell.
Yes.
I remember the smell of it for sure.
That's why.
That is a very distinct first memory I have of an amusement park.
I love them all so much.
I try to go at least once a year more if I can swing it.
I just think it's perfect.
I think everything about it is perfect except for the prices and except for the line.
I'm sure you guys have talked about that.
Sometimes the food is very good but sometimes you got to pick right.
You got to do your research.
That's a perk of California Adventure I think is that good food.
You can get drinks.
It's like I think California Adventure is a nice sweet spot where it's still Disney feeling.
There's still like Disney-esque-ness to it but it's also got an adult tinge to it that's like,
oh, this is sort of an in-between of like we're just out in the world and we're at a theme park.
You know what I mean?
It's got a leisurely pit.
There's not a million rides.
I mean there was hardly any when it first opened.
This Grizzly River Run was an opening day attraction February 8, 2001.
Thank you.
I've seen it over the years though.
There's really this ride I think is the first thing that worked really well.
It's like the thing that's had the least changes that like that whole this whole area I think was off to the races.
The Rapids Zone and Soarin' right by it.
Separate but relate and now like part of the same district.
But if you went to California Adventure and just went off to the right and did all that and then had to leave,
you would think this is a great park.
I love that they've embraced the sort of national park feel to it all.
They have that Rambler out there which is I think my favorite car I've ever seen.
Do you guys know what I'm talking about?
The car that's like parked outside.
Of Soarin'.
Of Soarin', yeah.
It's like a cross.
It's like geared up for like a camping road trip or whatever in the 70s.
And it's got like a canoe on it and it's got all this like binoculars and cameras and maps and everything inside the car.
It's just it evokes this like, oh, we're like we're in a national park.
It's just got that feel to it.
Sure.
It's really special.
And it smells different in there.
We're only talking about smells.
But I feel like California Adventure smells different than Disneyland even though they're like they share the same like.
Is there a specific area of smell that you think is the best in California Adventure?
I would, I mean honestly all around that area.
Yeah.
It's like pine.
Pine, yes.
They're pumping like pine in.
It smells like woods.
It smells like the forest.
Right.
It's like aged so well because the trees have all grown out.
They were all saplings when they were planted.
Now it's been 18 years.
So they're starting to fill out.
Right.
And with the hotel in the background, the hotel always looked good.
But like as they've like gussied up this area, it just looks nicer and nicer.
Have you guys ever been in that hotel?
I've stayed a couple of times.
You have?
Yeah.
I'm so jealous.
I've only been in the lobby and have just salivated over it.
Or just that.
I think it's in that lobby for, you could do it any time you want.
Just go down there.
Just go down to that lobby because it is special.
Yeah, yeah.
A couple of us may have done some work in there, that lobby, like writing.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, you may have, huh?
That's how weird we are.
That's so great.
It's so, yeah, it's a really warm inviting space.
Yeah, it's very tall.
It's meant to, like they're going for like an indoor tree vibe, I think.
That's what it feels like.
It's like being at the bottom of a redwood forest.
I love the Tiffany lamps too, the sort of like, those lamps, great choice by whoever designed that interior.
Yeah, that is a very strong component.
I got a Tiffany lamp at home.
I'm very proud of my Tiffany lamp.
We have Tiffany lamp night lamps.
Night lamps, you know.
For night, when light is needed.
Lamps you only use at night.
Yeah, not night yet.
Turn it off.
I love them too.
I love them.
It's just such a nice glow.
Yeah, what is so, and those thick little frames you're putting on about Tiffany lamps.
There's a husk in here.
I'm attracted to them, I guess.
Yeah, I know.
I'm attracted to them.
The most amorous voice I've ever heard.
Yeah, I've never been so breathy on the show.
The arts and crafts style of all of this.
Right.
The arts and crafts style in that whole area has, again, aged so well.
I feel like that never really goes out of fashion.
I agree.
They say on the tram from Mickey and Friends, they're always like, it's based on the arts and crafts movement of California.
Which I always thought, what is that?
What is the arts and crafts movement?
I never heard of that.
Arts and crafts movement in the early 20th century, I believe.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Craftsman style goods?
Craftsman houses.
I always pictured it like people with popsicle sticks and glue.
Like arts and crafts is what I think of in a child's project.
That's what the modern terms mean.
But it came about as a response to machine produced goods.
It was a response to that, of people making stuff more by hand.
That's information.
Now that's information.
Yeah. Now that I like.
Maybe that's the thing with the Tiffany lamps is that they're clearly like hand set and the patterns are random.
They aren't pumped out by some lamp machine.
Right.
That's why the breathiness.
That's why I'm attracted to them.
People made them with their hands.
You see. Lovingly caressed.
I don't think we've ever talked about Tiffany lamps on here before.
I know what you're talking about.
I don't think we have. We don't have any, but I like them.
I don't know that it's the same style, but also I was always very fond of the lamp work in any 80s Pizza Hut.
Yes. And those are Tiffany lamps.
They are Tiffany lamps.
Because it's like stained glass basically is what it looks like with a.
Ice cream parlors too.
Yes.
Well that Feral's style, the original Feral's.
Not the weird like failed comeback Feral's.
Yeah. TGI Fridays I think had a cool vibe as well.
Mary, did you ever have a Pizza Hut buffet where you came from?
Where you're hometown?
Yeah, we had a Pizza Hut.
Buffet though specifically.
Is that a different chain?
No, it's the same chain.
It's just they have a buffet.
It's just at lunch they would just set a bunch of pizzas out.
Yes, we did have that.
Okay.
Because we've talked a little bit about that and I want to get deeper into that eventually on the show.
Yeah.
That's a topic I'd like to.
You got to do a deep dive on it.
Pizza spin-off podcast deep dish.
Pizza Hut did used to be kind of a themed experience.
I do remember it going.
I remember that too.
And it was like a thing to do.
Yeah.
And you can still see those huts.
They're usually banks now.
They're banks.
There's those big, those odd tall roofs spotting this country and no longer delivering pizza anymore.
Yeah.
It's a bummer.
It is a real bummer.
What's happened to this nation of ours?
See?
We're falling apart.
First the Pizza Hut.
Go vote 2020.
I'll vote for any primary candidate who vows to bring back the Pizza Hut buffet.
Sit down, Pizza Hut.
Tiffany Lamps.
Pro-Lamp, pro-Tiffany Lamp candidate.
Yeah.
So you were a Disney, you were, you were East Coast, so you were a Disney World.
Yes.
A kid.
That's right.
You know what?
Really quickly, but this is a tangent, but this is a themed thing.
You worked in my hometown.
I did.
Is my recollection.
That's right.
At a very highly themed place called Medieval Times.
Oh baby.
Oh, Ocasianburg had a Medieval Times.
Yes.
It still does.
Okay.
I worked there.
Yeah.
Whoa.
So could we do a little side, slide, Joanne, to make no idea.
I was thrilled to dig in to that.
Yeah.
Because we, well then we also, four dough boys, we all went on a little group call a little
while ago, of like a year ago, and you knew someone who was working there.
I knew, get this, the Lord Chancellor.
Oh man.
Hold on to your pants.
Hold on to your shoes.
He was the Lord Chancellor at the Schoenberg.
Right.
And he transferred to Braena Park.
And he, yes.
And he transferred there and was working, was wanting to, I feel like he was living
in, when I talked to him years and years ago, when he first started working at the one down
here, he was saying that he lived in West Hollywood.
And I was like, wow, that's a commute.
But nothing compared to the commute I did in Illinois.
What was that?
Were you living in Rockford or something?
I was living in DeKalb.
DeKalb, yeah.
It was 100 miles round trip.
And I did that commute because, and this is how much I love medieval times.
I did that commute every Friday, Saturday and Sunday and for $6.50 an hour to get paid
$6.50 an hour.
Plus commissions, which I never made.
How do you make commissions?
Well, I was a photography wench.
Whoa.
And you have to sell.
I feel like the one here in California has like, or what park is it in?
Not Anaheim.
Buena Park.
Yes.
I feel like they do it a little bit different, but how it was in Schomburg at the time I
worked there, what we did was people would come in and they would be like, okay, get
in front of this backdrop and hold up your table number.
And that was truly just so we could, once the pictures were printed, find them in the
arena and then try to sell them the picture.
But the pictures were so bad.
It was like, it would be like you come in, we would get the top of your shoulders, your
head, a picture of your table number, which is like, why do you want a memory of that?
And then seven feet of backdrop above you.
Like it was of just blue sky.
Like it was, uh, that's all it is.
It's not like some more Nate's, uh, tapestry.
No, no, um, sky.
Yeah.
Fake sky.
I mean, there was stuff on the edges, but like, like no one knew, no one was a professional
photographer.
Um, I say that maybe someone was, but, uh, I was definitely not.
And so I would like, uh, you know, and they, we were encouraged to sort of have, you know,
British accents.
And so, uh, you know, I embrace that.
So I was like, my Lords, my ladies, I'd like lead people in and, and like have them take
their picture and then right this way, enjoy your turn.
Some sort of weird accent.
And then they would all go into the arena and we would go up to the, to the, like our
lab or whatever, and they would print out all the pictures and they'd print like one
that we'd put in the frames and then print one we put in the key chain and, and you'd
make a little packet and then you'd get loaded up with packets.
And then over the course of the show, you would like, uh, like you'd have a little
flashlight and I'd be like, oh, okay, I'm looking for this guy.
He's wearing a red shirt and they're in the blue section row three.
And so I just sort of walk along.
Like you see the, you know, the people working there sort of weaving their way in, in and
So we, I just looked to find that person and then I'd come up to them and be like $20 for
this.
And some people would buy it.
But if they didn't buy, would you then just throw all these printed pictures in the
garbage?
Yeah.
Well, well, if they didn't buy it in the arena, they have one more chance after the show
is over, we, we like had a booth or a little section set up where we displayed all the
pictures and then they could come by them after the show on their way out if they decided
to.
But, um, but yeah.
Uh, and so I would do that commute 50 miles each way and I would not take any of the freeways
in Illinois.
I would only take state roads like through the back because, and I would listen to the
Lord of the Rings soundtrack.
Every time I was deep in it every time, cause it like got me in the mode of like, Oh, I'm
medieval.
You know, it was really crazy to get into character.
Wow.
We're saying is your picture.
Yes.
I, well, I just loved the whole vibe of it so much.
I'm very into atmosphere.
Like I'm really into that.
And that's, I think why I love amusement parks so much is that you, you get to just walk
into, you can believe that you're in a whole other world.
And you're like, you just entrenched in this atmosphere.
Um, and also Illinois is quite beautiful.
So you didn't mind taking these routes.
You chose to take these routes.
I did.
I chose.
It was fun.
Yeah.
I liked it.
How often, how many people on average would buy the photo?
Like pretty percentage wise.
From me?
Sure.
Yeah.
Well, the thing is, is I think like, because we worked on commissions, I remember there
was one guy who was in the, in the, in like our department who every night would sell
like $300.
He would get $300 in commission or something.
He was, he would go out with a massive armful of packets and would sell them all.
And I would maybe sell one on average.
I feel like my, my success rate was, uh, maybe I would get two or three a night and he would
just sell hundreds.
I don't know.
I think I also, I didn't, I sort of didn't believe in the pictures.
Like I was like, I was like, this is.
Well, you were just a simple scullery made.
You were not committed.
I was not committed.
And I also felt like consumption.
I wanted to advise the person don't buy this.
Why are you spending your money on this terrible picture?
I'll take a picture of you right now.
That's like much better and like more dynamic than this.
Check the dumpster in an hour and you can get it for free.
Exactly.
Did you ever do another job or were you just the photography wench?
I was just a photography wench.
I just did it for a summer.
Cause then, uh, I had to go back.
College started again into Calvin.
I couldn't do that commute when I was once that started.
It was over the summer that I worked there.
But, uh, do you ever buy a picture of yourself?
I think we bought the one when we, when we went with doughboys, I think, uh,
I think we bought that one.
Maybe, um, nod, nod to your past.
Yeah.
But my dream was to be in the show.
My dream was to be at the time, the princess, but now they have a
whole bunch of, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh,
at the time, the princess, but now they have a queen. Yes. Oh yeah. That's good.
So do you think you would make the, it's less, it's a less of a commute for you.
Honestly, it takes everything. If they offered me the role of queen,
I would drop everything. Let's see. I mean, including my current relationship.
Just kidding, Matt. Just kidding.
For any excuse. It sounds like I got a job. I can't offer me something.
If they offer me something, a pirate's dinner adventure, I'll take it too.
I've never been there. I hear that's very fun.
Uh, yes, it is fun. So listeners, if anyone has a connection to medieval times,
email us, offer the job to Mary and we'll see what happens.
We'll see what happens. You are offer only at this point.
Exactly. I am offer only.
When it comes to medieval times, I'm offer only.
I do like the idea of them putting out offers like a movie or show.
I think it would be smart for like, if you know,
pirates dinner adventure is like, we want Paul of Tompkins for seven weeks.
We want like, we need like a novelty. Like, let's, let's get a star in here.
Phoenix. Oh man. Whoa.
Who would have to like commit and be a method.
Chancellor for gravelly talking about,
bring out the shrimp kebabs. Like,
exactly.
Kind of unhinged pretty quill, the master like sort of voice.
Like,
yeah,
this is going to, but he's going to like,
this is going to be bad for all the medieval incels out there.
They're all going to.
And hacked up.
Yeah.
This performance.
Tuned in.
I am a polling a master reference when this,
this is a,
I'm not counting a master reference when this podcast will come out right around
the Joker movie.
Oh yeah.
The Joker move.
Yes.
Perfect.
Time to that beautifully.
We'll all know.
We'll know when it happens.
Yeah. Any, any final,
like was the,
was there a great day at medieval times?
Was there a weird day or was it always the same pictures and.
Yeah.
I mean it was, but I, I guess my whole vibe that I didn't really hang out with anybody
because I had to drive 50 miles.
I didn't really get to know anybody really that I worked with.
I sort of was like on my own journey with medieval times.
Like I'd show up and then once the show started and I was selling the pictures,
I was really just enjoying the show.
And again, the smell, I love the smell of medieval times.
And just being in that world and, and like the lights and the sound,
I just sort of, I almost treated it like I was,
I was getting to go to medieval times every night was how it felt to me.
That's fun.
And then, and that's probably why I didn't sell any pictures.
Did you ever get any local Illinois,
like the Rob Blagojevich and family ever come in or something?
I bet he did.
I know, not that I know of, but I also, I didn't have the finger on the pulse.
Nobody really talked to me.
Honestly.
Yeah.
It was like Dennis Rodman didn't come in one day.
He did.
No, he didn't.
Not that I know of.
Must have fortune gambling on the rock and not you.
Yeah.
But it was a great, it was, it was great.
I really loved it.
Yeah.
That's wild.
So like Schomburg, you, did you go a lot?
You were there.
I honestly think I went once or twice in the whole time I was living there,
which was many years of my life.
I also saw an independent wrestling show at medieval times.
They just set up.
They held a separate thing at medieval times.
What?
In the dirt?
That's a pretty big venue.
Wow.
I saw Tatanka wrestle, a former WWE 90s wrestler, Tatanka.
Wow, that's cool.
Wrestling obviously is cooler, but I like it when,
my dream is that they hold like a religious service in there,
that there's a mass at medieval times.
Honestly, I don't, it felt like they were renting it out so that it may have happened.
I don't know that to be a fact, but it may have happened.
It's a big space with seats.
So you got to do something with it when they're on it.
That being said, it's actually real close to a mega church called Willow Creek.
Okay.
Which honestly we should do on the show too, because it has like a massive,
In Schomburg?
Yeah.
It's a massive budgeted, like big production Christmas show type place.
Oh, wow.
Really?
Animals?
Oh, I don't know about animals.
In Lancaster, there's a place called the Sight and Sound Theater,
and they would do the Christmas like story with live animals.
Wow.
This is, yeah, Willow Creek is like a mega church,
and it's looked right by medieval times.
So maybe that, maybe they didn't want to infringe on Willow Creek.
But anyway, we'll look into that.
And other medieval times could consider religious services.
Yes.
Sure.
We could rent the Buena Park medieval times out for a religious service.
We should.
Yeah.
We have so many religious services we've been wanting to do.
So many ideas, so many mass ideas, so many Psalms we will never get rid of.
Podcasters are the new gods.
Mm-hmm.
We are the prophets now.
Jason says he's rubbing his hands together.
I know, he's truly literally rubbing his hands together like an evil genius.
Yeah, weird.
What were you doing there?
Were you putting cream on or something?
No.
Cream.
I don't know, hand cream.
He put cream.
He creams up before the show.
Definitely creaming while recording.
Oh, Jesus.
Creaming out.
Look, even Edwin's sick of this.
Edwin does look like he's rolling his eyes a lot of the time.
He gets it.
All right, so let's go back to the forest.
Let's jump.
We're back in the forest.
To the west.
Are you a fan of national parks?
I was wondering, like, does that make you, did that make you, like, especially have affinity for this area?
I am a fan of national parks.
Yeah, I love Yosemite.
I've only been a handful of times, but I really, I just love that sort of immersion in nature that's so overwhelmingly big.
Like, there's something about California national parks in particular.
I guess I haven't been to that many outside of California, but like I'm thinking of the Redwoods and the Sequoias, like, where there's like, it's just so massive and overwhelming and all these, like, the big boulders and the big waterfalls.
All of that is just very soothing to me.
Yeah, I feel like intimate.
That's not the word.
Infinite.
Yes.
It feels like it goes like a Joshua tree or something.
It's like it goes on literally forever, it feels like.
Yes, and it always changes my perspective.
Like it always, and there's something about stepping into that area of California adventure that gives me a little bit of that where I'm like, oh yeah, there's this whole other world out there.
Sure, yeah.
In this theme park.
Well, and there's this weird, in talking about this being the first area that worked with California Adventure, the idea of like encapsulating the California experience in one little place.
Some of that is inherently silly because Hollywood, you can go to real Hollywood up the road and that's all kind of stupid, like Hollywood tourism's all cheesy and shouldn't be recreated really.
And then like a seaside amusement park, like that area has gotten a lot more charm and it feels more like the 20s, 30s now, but when it opened, it was just kind of like chintzy carnival.
So the national parks felt like the only thing that they were like recreating that felt elevated and where they did it justice, like they actually did get some of the national park vibe.
That's how I feel about it.
And even the Route 66, like over by Cars Land and everything, like the Radiator Springs and all of that, like it, I feel like they really did it right where you, it does feel very California.
That like ties it all together in a nice way.
Now there's multiple types of national parks.
There's the more Kenyan-y, red rock type and then the more pine tree, redwood sort of vibe.
And a large hotel in the background.
Like I haven't really gone to any of the California state or national parks, but I do like the appeal of like, and there's a really nice hotel in the middle of it.
These crazy old lodges.
The lodges, yeah, because we didn't really have those in Pennsylvania.
Like the state parks were perfectly nice and we would camp in them and all, but there wasn't like an 80 year old like, you know, luxury hotel.
Sure.
Places are nuts.
Like the Shining Hotel, but not scary.
You would like, from what you were saying, I was thinking you wanted like a hotel just right in the middle of Joshua Tree National Park.
Like a massive full lodge.
Just in dead center.
Oh yeah, there's not really any lodge.
The desert landscape, all the hotels and stuff are pretty flat.
Like three or four stories maximum.
But like where the trees are taller, where the cliffs are taller, you make the buildings taller.
Joshua Tree, though, should be like a rock, a fake rock hotel.
That's a great idea.
We talk a lot about on the show about fake rocks, how much we love fake rocks.
I love fake rocks.
What is that?
We're not exactly sure.
We did a whole bracket, a tournament to determine what the best fake rocks were.
Tournament.
Sadly, Grizzly Peak did not win.
Sorry to tell you.
Grizzly Peak didn't win.
Very cool fake rocks though.
Radiator Springs area, Ornament Valley won.
Incredible.
So, but yeah, so there should be like a big fake rock hotel that looks like they just sort of carved the hotel out of a bunch of big rocks.
Yeah.
That'd be great.
Maybe that's a land, upcoming land.
To actually stay in fake rocks.
To stay in fake rocks.
That's actually the next level of our fake rock love.
Yeah.
To actually sleep inside one.
In the Madonna Inn.
I was just going to say Madonna Inn.
Madonna Inn, yes.
There's a lot of rock work.
I'm not even sure.
They're fake.
I think there's a lot of real rocks around.
Yeah, maybe they have real rocks.
But you can go, at least in the men's restroom, you can go just pee into rocks.
Oh yeah, we did that.
Yeah, your dream.
We did that around the same time, like at the same time, I think, when we were there.
We were there for a wedding.
Oh, okay, yeah.
And it was weird.
That whole, I'll be honest with you, I didn't care for it.
You didn't care for Madonna Inn?
The Madonna Inn was weird?
No, no, not the Madonna Inn.
For what?
No, the bathroom, specifically just the bathroom.
Oh, I see.
It was weird.
It felt like peeing into an open shower or something.
Yes, that's true.
It didn't feel like a lush waterfall.
It felt like a leaky pipe.
It felt like there was a big shower in a high school gym and we were just pissing in it.
Yeah.
And it was like light rocks.
And look, I love doing everything around fake rocks.
You love a round of grab ass and locker room.
If you know me, I love a round of grab ass.
You love a round of grab ass.
That's the thing.
A real towel snapper.
Grab ass.
Jason also has been working as a high school gym coach on the weekend.
Oh yeah.
That's why he's got that terminology in his head.
I love it.
I love telling everyone to try their best.
I love picking the scrawniest nerds out there.
I love picking the scrawniest nerdiest guys and saying, come on.
Come on.
Pick it up.
God, that's all you say?
I'm just doing what I learned.
You can't compliment them on being stronger fast.
I can't.
Because they're not.
That's true.
You don't want to lie.
Yeah.
A good coach doesn't lie.
So that's a no on the drip drop of Madonna.
Yeah.
Well, I'm sorry to tell you, Grizzly Peak didn't fare that well in the final four.
I understand.
One of the issues, at least that I had, I might have poisoned the water, is that I've
felt a lot of confusion about whether the, even though we, if you know it's called Grizzly
Peak, then you know that the big rock is supposed to be a bear.
Yes.
But I've heard confusion over is it in fact supposed to be a coyote or a wolf or a wolf.
Interesting.
And this is compounded further by the story behind Grizzly Peak, the mountain.
Right on.
Amazing.
Amazing transition.
That was a story time.
That was gorgeous, Jason.
The legend of Grizzly Peak.
Long ago, Ah-ha-lay, the coyote, met Oosu-ma-tee, the grizzly bear on top of the mountain.
Seeing the grizzly was powerful.
The coyote asked him to watch over and protect the land.
Then one day people came and tried to chase Oosu-ma-tee from the mountain.
But grizzly was strong and held his ground.
When the coyote saw the brave bear standing alone against so many, he turned Oosu-ma-tee
into stone so that he could never be driven away.
That almost made me cry.
Yes.
When you said when you saw the brave bear, I'm gonna cry.
The idea of a brave bear is great.
I don't know why that's making me so emotional.
I think brave applied to an animal.
It's just really nice.
I know.
Brave dog.
We can take a minute if you need.
I need a second.
No, that is beautiful.
I mean, what a, it's kind of a strange way to force a creature to stay.
Yeah, that's my, that's why I'm not tearing up about it is that I have my concerns about
freezing a bear in stone state, petrifying him forever so he can't move.
Right.
This is what Putin did to that one guy.
He turned that guy to stone.
Remember?
Yeah, there's a guy, there's like an enemy of Putin who he injected with some drug and
then his face popped up.
A bark bench in London?
Ew.
Oh, God.
No, man, I don't, it's a little too exaggerated to say Putin turned someone to stone, but
that's a more fun way to put it.
But a guy got like a, he got like a big craggy face.
Oh my God.
He got poisoned.
I mean, he claims he didn't do it, but, and I, you know, I should, I should like our president
choose to believe him, but I tell you, he didn't do the stone thing.
But I don't know, he said he didn't do it.
But I don't know, I think there's something a little malicious about a coyote turning
a bear to stone.
Well, and that the bear was frozen in a position that I associate more with wolves than coyote,
which is howling upwards at the sky.
Right.
Maybe perhaps howling, don't turn me to stone.
Please, please don't do this.
Right.
It's like the Vesuvius.
I do sort of feel like, though, coyote dogs and bears are similar looking in their snout.
In their snout, for sure.
I could see, I see a semblance there where, you know, if you're not seeing the rest of
the body, you know what I mean?
We're just going off face.
Which we are.
We don't see a big old bear butt.
No, there's no bear butt.
And there's no coyote tits.
You know, what are you going to go off of?
You got to go off the face.
No big jiggly coyote tits.
Jiggly.
I think those are two, we usually do like a plus up at the end, but for this area, those
are two plus ups I wouldn't mind.
Yeah.
The butt and the tits.
Yeah, some coyote tits.
Teeths, I should say.
Teeths, yeah, yeah.
We shouldn't be so crude.
So proud of the brave bear that the coyote raised their tits in celebration.
And that to the legend.
Yeah, it is.
It's a good, like, if you know what you're looking at, it's a very cool rock structure
thing, but I can see, yeah, it's a little bit obscured, which I like.
I think I made the point that I kind of liked that there was mystery surrounding it.
I like that too.
So then you can, and you can see it more when you're on the actual ride.
It's always sort of in the distance, which I like, which is cool.
It's like not such a visible thing.
Well, some articles have pointed out, as Jason said, the trees have grown very much in the
20 years that California Adventure has been open.
So you could see the bear a lot better upon opening, but now those trees have climbed
and climbed.
And I haven't said, I think it was on this website, Yesterland, that somebody said that
it looks like, they think it looks like a bear drowning in a sea of trees.
I'm not sure I agree with.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I think he's doing OK.
I think it's a proud, brave yell, but that was their take.
Also, the presence, you get a whimsical bear next to this attraction too at the entrance.
Oh, he's funny.
This is fun.
This is the best.
Now, this is him in his present state with more, leaning more towards the national parks
vibe.
You can see he's got a wooden oar.
A number of years ago, he was a little more of an extreme sports bear.
That's a very modern aluminum wood.
He's got a cool logo, 90s logo.
Wow.
Yeah.
He also, this bear, sports bear.
This bear is fantastic.
First of all, I just want to say that on record.
He's about what we say, 30 feet tall.
He's very large.
Is he 20 or 25?
He's very tall.
He's a big boy.
I do appreciate that he's wearing a life jacket because I think that's a good message.
Even a bear.
Yeah.
Needs a flotation device.
Even a bear.
I mean, you see some of those nature shows and they eat it in the rivers a lot.
They're fine, but they're swatting for fish and they'll fall in sometimes.
Yeah.
They need a life jacket.
Safety first.
That bear right now is holding a Halloween bucket.
What?
Is he?
I saw a picture of it last night.
He's holding a little trick or treat bucket.
And then at Christmas, they take the vest off and put a Christmas sweater on him.
And this is the greatest bear other than the country bears in the Disney parks.
Does this bear have a name?
I looked for it and we couldn't.
I don't believe so.
They haven't given him any backstory.
It's odd that Disney names everything.
Why does this bear not have a name?
He has no backstory.
He must have a name.
I Googled pretty thoroughly.
Is he supposed to be the bear from Grin and Barrett?
The goofy?
Is that Donald or Goofy?
That's Humphrey.
That bear is portrayed elsewhere.
That's Humphrey the bear and he's in those like drying stations that they put out sometimes.
Oh, yes.
He wasn't always.
He is now.
He's not always.
Yeah.
So this is a nameless bear.
We could name the bear on the episode, I guess, today.
I want to name the bear.
Okay, Mary.
Oh, I don't.
This is an idea for a name.
We can debate.
We should all throw out names.
I'm willing to let you just do it.
The first one that came to my mind, Canoe.
Canoe the bear.
Is it spelled like canoe or is it like kind of like a K-A-N-U?
Closer to Keanu.
Oh, yeah.
I guess in my head it was spelled like canoe.
Okay.
What do you guys think?
What's a good name?
Canoe.
Ansel?
In honor of Ansel Adams, nature photographer?
No.
You don't want to call him Ansel?
That's a great name.
Or John.
John or Muir.
John or Muir?
There's John Muir references everywhere.
That's cute.
We call the bear Muir.
Muir.
Okay, so far in the pile is Muir and Canoe.
Those are the two ideas we have.
Scott, do you have an idea?
What about, would you be spelled different, but like the star of the show you're on, Rory.
Rory.
You could be Rory.
That's cute.
You could maybe put an A in there.
Oh, that's good.
Well, this is a little inside reference.
When we first got Edwin, I would call him Edwin and then when he was bad, I would call
him Rory.
And as I'm saying this, he's hawking up a hairball.
Mic by him.
Are you okay, pal?
I guess he's okay.
Whoa.
Wait, sorry.
You.
I'll wait.
That's the anecdote again.
Yes.
Yeah.
Because it was so good.
Edwin, I used to call Edwin Rory when he was bad when we first got him.
He had two personalities.
Really?
No.
He was Rory when he was bad.
So my cat Brenda is usually a little bit feisty, a little bit of a, we call her a moody teen
because she usually wants to be by herself and to try to pet and she bites.
But if she decides to be affectionate, then she is frienda.
So I also have a dual pet nature and a naming system to acknowledge this.
Mary dual pet naming structure at all.
Oh, nope.
Just in one name.
All right.
Whatever.
Because that one name, well then whatever.
That one name just, pets are complicated and just like humans and just like my name, Mary,
encompasses all sides of me, the dark and the light.
So too do my pet's names.
We contain multitudes.
Yeah.
It's nice to have a sort of like clear, okay, now she's frienda and now she's safe to approach.
It's like, I consider it almost, it's like the plus, it's like a, like a different state
of Mario, like Tanooki suit.
Now you're super Mario, right?
Right, right.
Yeah, that makes sense.
That's funny.
Yeah.
The treat to meet frienda.
My name for the bear would be Michael.
Well wait a minute.
My God.
Awfully selfish.
This is no, no, no.
I will not let this stand.
Wait, okay, did I want to name the bear Mary?
Okay.
No.
This is what you were bound to unleash.
Now I gotta throw Scott in the mix.
Do I want it to be named Scott?
I don't know, but Jason still wants Ansel.
I'm doubling down on Ansel.
Jason's going to win just because we all got split up.
Yeah.
You also though want us to call you Ansel in real life.
Yeah, it's not catching on.
I'm like cousin Greg on Succession going, I'm Greg right now.
No one listens to him.
So that bear is fantastic.
Yeah, like I take a photo of that bear every time I walk by.
Yeah, and that Christmas sweater is great.
That's a great idea.
I love that.
Jason, you brought up Humphrey the bear.
So this is a really specific like these like 50s era Disney cartoons set in national parks
where there was a bear who was like it would not be a bear.
It's the Pluto goofy rules where it's more of an animal than a Humphrey doesn't really
talk, right?
Right.
Humphrey is more animal than anthropomorphized.
And I always liked these things.
And they featured another guy who's in the parks, who's featured now as the narration
on the Grizzly River Run ride.
This fellow, this park ranger.
Oh, yeah.
See Ring a Bell?
He's seen this dude and his name.
He's very rarely named, but only in one thing is he named Jay Audubon Woodlore.
He rocks.
Great name.
Yeah, I really like him.
It really takes you a bit.
Like there was this era of like, I think we've talked about like the domestic Disney characters.
You have a little statue in your home of domestic Mickey with a yellow polo shirt.
Like when he became a homeowner, he said he wasn't like struggling and working little
odd jobs anymore.
He bought a house, he settled down and like Chip and Dale are causing problems in his
house, but he's mellow.
Right.
This was filled with like, you know, goofy's taking all these trips and trying out sports.
I think Donald's version of it was going to these national parks.
I really liked all these commercials, all these commercials, all these, all these shorts.
But there was this one, there's one moment with Jay Audubon Woodlore.
Does anybody know this offhand?
When I Googled him, there's this one moment that stands out and it's on YouTube and hopefully
it's queued up correctly.
But he's giving Donald the rules of his visits to the national park.
And here is this.
Welcome to Brownstone National Park.
Now a few rules.
No hunting, no fishing, no swimming, no drinking, no fires, no going over the end bed if you
don't do that.
And remember, don't molest the bears.
Don't molest the bears.
I think a more common everyday word back then.
We just say bother.
Like molest star, like the Spanish for molestar.
Yeah, yeah.
It just today really stands out and really jumped out of me in the Google imaging for
Jay Audubon Woodlore.
But just as true today.
Don't molest the bears.
Don't molest anyone.
Yeah.
Or anything.
Yes.
That rule applies to all species and maybe especially bears.
Not especially bears, it's all legal.
But bears will retaliate in a way that maybe.
Yes.
Yeah, you're really asking for a mauling if you.
You're asking for a mauling.
That character was ahead of his time, maybe.
Yes.
I like to think that.
Like just getting out of, yeah, getting out in front of it.
Wait, I don't recognize him though from the ride.
When does he come up?
Will you hear his voice now?
If you've gone recently, he does the safety instructions.
Oh, OK.
Apparently it used to be.
This is wild.
This is what?
Extreme sports guy.
I don't know.
What was he?
He was a rafting safety.
He was a rafting instructor.
Named Bumper McFerrin.
What?
This might be the bear does it.
The bear, whoever one takes pictures of, doesn't have a name, but they named an unseen voice
Bumper McFerrin.
Bumper is a great name.
So pretty good.
Think to 2001 as this park is opening, the X Games still popular.
They did X Games stuff in the park.
In the park.
And so the queue had a lot of like extreme sports kind of paraphernalia, even as it's
surrounded by like giant trees and like a craftsman style hotel.
Yeah, weird.
That was Bumper McFerrin.
Bumper McFerrin.
And why sounds like that?
Like he had that kind of.
Yeah.
Why McFerrin?
Are they trying to reference Bobby McFerrin?
Don't worry.
Be happy.
That seems like that sort of writer's room kind of like create.
It's the name, the uncanny valley of names.
You're like, you come up with the first name, like, what do we call this guy?
Like, yeah, Bumper.
Yeah.
OK.
Bumper Johnson.
Well, and Mick is very comedy.
That's like very comedy.
Like Mick's silly face.
That's like a random naming mechanism.
Yeah.
But McFerrin's pretty specific.
They were probably all Bobby McFerrin fans.
I mean, aren't we all?
Sure.
They like the message.
So that's probably it.
Yeah.
Will, you know, like how they've put Rex on something else, will Bumper McFerrin ever come
back in the parks?
Because like they've taken now in Star Wars land there used to be the pilot of Star
Tours Rex.
That's a toy of him.
He's now DJing in the Cantina.
Will Bumper.
Oh, that's cool.
Really nice reference to an old thing.
Will.
But like maybe it'll take 20 years for Bumper to come back.
But like he'll show up in a new ride eventually.
I hope so.
Yeah.
Seems like he'd be a good DJ.
DJ for the Rapids ride.
Yeah.
When they do the DJ, the Rapids club.
When you get on it, you are on a big turntable.
Oh, it's so cool.
I love it.
Those things weird you out though.
The like when you step on and off, it's like that like ghostly.
Yeah.
Like getting on an escalator that's not moving.
I think it's super.
I think I almost think that's part of the ride is like getting on that turntable and
timing it perfectly so that you get into your raft.
You have a little like job that you step off the stairs and then you got to like scurry
over and not let the weird motion sickness get to you.
Yeah.
And you got to get on your in your raft efficiently before it like goes.
Like you have a lot to do.
You got to stuff everything into that little space in the middle.
Yeah.
And like eight people's worth of stuff and purses and bags and backpacks don't necessarily
fit.
Yeah.
It's a little stressful I think getting on these things.
But you like it.
I like the interaction with it.
Like I feel the same way about food.
Like I like interacting with food.
I love crab legs.
I love Korean barbecue.
I like I like working with the food.
Oh, sure.
And and I feel the same way about rides where I like have a job to do.
I like that.
I love a moving platform.
Like I think that is my natural state of being is stepping onto a moving platform or like
at an airport.
Natural state.
Oh, the moving sidewalks.
I'm like, oh, moving.
I got to get on the moving sidewalk.
Never miss it.
He's calling to me.
It's man wants to be near flowing water, which I do.
But also I want to be by those moving walkways.
Yeah.
I got to get on motion.
You want the floor to be taking you where you have to go at all times.
I given me a little extra boosts, like a little a little help along the way.
It's like having bionic implants.
Like you feel like you're 10 percent robot when you're on a moving sidewalk.
Feels great.
I mean, I probably just have positive childhood memories of like you usually was at an airport
or a theme park.
I'm going to somewhere I like.
I'm excited to go to.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
It has positive.
And also there's something we were drawn to, like kinetic energy, like movement is like
very it's it's I don't know.
It's exciting.
It gets you like, oh, we're moving like it's that's I think one of the appeals of this
area is there's a lot of greenery.
I think like a lot of green space goes a long way.
Yeah, I agree.
A lot of kinetic energy from the rafts and the flowing water.
I mean, there's lots of look at there's multiple lookout points where you can just watch the
ride.
You can watch the river.
So far, a big conveyor belt and the windmill.
And yeah, the milk.
There's a beautiful I mean, there's that little trail.
I don't know what if they call it Grizzly River Trail, Grizzly.
There's a big sign that says Grizzly Peak Pass, but you can go behind the ride and follow
this trail.
That's the best secret.
That's one of the best places to go in California Adventure.
And I say secret just because I feel like nobody goes back there.
Right.
Because it's like added more and more details and stuff over the years.
Carts and quiet.
It's quiet.
Quietest part, I feel like of the whole place.
And then at night, it's like you can just sit out on that or you can like stand on a
little like plat.
There's a couple different like little bridge type platforms.
I, my best friend and I went to Disneyland and we spent the whole day there.
And it was like, I think California Adventure was closing at like 10 or something.
And we had gotten dinner in California Adventure.
We had some more.
And we it was like nine o'clock and we were like, oh, the rides are still open.
That's my favorite time to do rides at Disneyland or California Adventure because they're
definitely not as crowded and they're they're a whole different experience.
Like like Big Thunder Road at night is like the best.
The best returns in Grizzly River runs the same way.
It was empty.
It was just me and Catherine and we just like it was so fun, like weaving our way through
the line and then there are the like where the line is and you're like in this canoe
shack or whatever as you're going through to get to the platform.
And then we got in the raft and we went around.
It was just us in the raft.
There was no one else in the raft in front or behind us.
And then when we came around to like get off, we were like, can we just stay?
And the guy was like, yeah.
And so we just did the ride over and over and over.
Yeah.
It was either Catherine took a picture of me once from it and it's the happiest I've ever lived.
It was the most fun.
Do you know how many times you went on total like three or was it more?
I feel like five.
Wow.
Because you just like, why not?
And it's like normally the line during the day, especially during a hot day, it's like two hours or something.
It can be really bad.
And there's like not a lot going on in that line.
It's super boring.
So to feel like you're getting that for you don't even have to do it.
You don't even have to get out.
You don't have to walk.
Wonderful.
It was fun.
Rapids are one of the easiest ones to like, can we go again?
Yes.
Because it's such work getting in and out.
Totally.
It's really rewarding.
But it's also like pretty easy.
Like you're not going to hit like, no, you can't stay in the pass a steel beam before it gets loaded again.
Right.
It just is.
Yes.
It's a cycle.
So yeah, you couldn't just stay on the Haunted Mansion.
I don't know what happens between the unload and the load.
I don't know.
Decapitating machine.
Yeah.
That's where they get the ghosts.
There's no stove.
It's a ghost maker.
Oh my gosh.
That's so funny.
Do you think they get all those ghosts?
Yeah.
Do you do poncho or no poncho?
What do you feel about a poncho?
No poncho.
Do you think that's a sign of weakness if you need a poncho on a ride like that?
Honestly, no.
No, I don't.
Because I get it if you're wearing something like, or if you got like a
expensive camera or whatever.
I understand that.
But I think that's part of the, for me, I definitely don't judge other people if they're
doing it.
But for me, I'm like, I'm no poncho because that's the experience of it.
That's the fun of it is getting wet and then getting dry after by being out in the park.
So you don't have the germ concern.
There is the-
Love germs.
I'm here to welcome them here.
Yeah, I have zero germ concern, maybe to a not great degree.
But I'm not even worried even a little bit.
And part of me is like, why not strengthen my immune system?
Like I'm sort of-
You drink a little of the water too every time?
Yeah, I drink a little bit.
Some of that's getting in your mouth.
Some of that water is probably going in your mouth.
100%.
If you're laughing, you're having a good time.
If you're laughing, you're drinking.
If you are on the Dower Rapids ride, if someone's like, imagine someone upset looking on a water
ride.
I don't just have my mouth open the whole ride.
I would if I could.
But I've never caught a stray drop in my mouth.
But even if I did, I don't know.
You've gotten mist though, probably in your mouth because the mist is all over the place.
Sure, sure.
That's still some water.
I'll take it.
I'm fine with it.
I love it.
I mean, I'm good with it.
I have to say one of my other natural states is being soaking wet in full clothing.
So I don't mind walking around.
These are natural states.
Just from being, I feel very serene just from going to so many theme parks.
If I took you out on the balcony here and soaked you with the hose, would you be upset?
Soaked you?
If it came without warning.
But if I was prepared, I would just come back in and continue the show.
The image of you hosing down jazz.
Oh, I know.
There's a hose right there.
It's so tempting.
Yeah, we can hose them down right now.
I mean, I have some errands to run after this.
So you'll be wet for them.
You'll be in your natural state.
I know, but other people might be surprised.
Like, you can get away with it on property.
I don't want to unnerve people.
I mean, context, context is king.
You think people might be scared.
Oh, a wet man like a soaking wet man in a CVS.
Like, I don't know. I might be a little concerned.
I saw that. I would be a little.
Because what if it's gasoline?
Well, yeah, I don't know.
Now you're writing.
What if he looks like you're writing falling down to like,
I don't know what's as a crazy gassed up guy
walking in every store.
I think the CVS employees would be like,
oh, my God, there's a soaking wet man here.
But he looks like he's the happiest a man could be.
Yeah, he's either having a great day or a bad day.
So serene.
Hi, everybody.
Just throwing water everywhere.
This is all why Jason voluntarily did the ice bucket challenge
hundreds of times.
I didn't record it.
Yeah, yeah, not all for camera.
Record it.
Stop challenging more people.
Just for fun.
I challenge Jason.
And it's himself back infinite loop of ice bucket challenge.
Oh, man.
What else is part of this experience?
You know, what doesn't happen on this particular rabbit ride
is the thing where people like pay a little bit of money and then like blast
you like fire cannons or make geysers go off.
Like sometimes water rapids rise.
Or other flu.
Dudley Do-Right does that in Orlando, an Islands of Adventure.
And then you could sort of do it on the new way.
I'm blanking on what the knots right now.
Calico Calico River Rapids and Knotsberry Farm.
Very fun. If you're looking for even more.
I've never been to Knotsberry Farm.
Oh, we got to go.
Big recommends.
And same manufacturer as this ride Intamin
Oh, really?
Constructed both of these rides.
The Collie River Rapids in that Disney's Animal Kingdom.
And California Screamin and a ton. Yes.
Yeah, they've constructed a lot of stuff.
But they made the first rapids ride at Astro World.
Oh, yeah.
I think they may have made all rapids rides like I've always been like,
oh, rapids rides have this and this and this.
And that may partially be because one manufacturer makes the ball.
But I find I don't get super wet on this ride a lot of times.
Yeah, I go through.
I have gotten very wet.
Yeah. And then I have also escaped unscathed.
They can turn it up if they want.
That's the that's the secret.
Is it? Yeah.
And the hot in the hot days.
Also, it's not that much of a secret.
In the hot days, they can crank the water level up so it'll soak everybody more.
And if it's colder, they can turn it down.
I think Splash Mountain does that, too. Right.
It does. Yeah.
It's the same. Like there's levels of how wet they will get everybody.
I think in California, especially they they scale it back when it
because it does get colder out here.
All of them. All water. Jurassic World, too.
My question about Splash Mountain would be
that like they turn it up and down, like on the last big drop.
But the real place you get soaked is that like second to last drop
because it just a gallons of water slowly enters.
It's like a soup into the.
Yeah, it soaps in and soaks your pants like crazy.
And I feel like they can't.
I feel like they can't turn that off.
Yeah, I feel like that's not a setting.
I think that's just like a thing.
That's just where water has gathered.
And you're going to just go to displacement and volume like.
Yeah, exactly. A tennis ball in a bucket.
Yeah. So like the end is like they can change it.
But I feel like that souping of your pants, that's going to be forever.
Mike. Hmm.
Be honest. Did you soup your pants?
It's not the right.
Is it? I guess I will admit I did soup my pants.
Soup my pants is such a.
The drop is scary.
Is it scary? Is souped them?
I end up souping.
Mom, I souped my pants again.
Michael, it's every day.
I we don't know what to do.
We're going to have to send you somewhere.
We've talked to every psychologist in the Schaumburg area.
He won't stop souping his pants and we're at our wits end.
Oh, that's the way you got to have a T-shirt, I guess, about the longs in the toilet.
Soot my pants.
Hashtag soup my pants.
Have you souped your pants?
Tweeted us with a hashtag.
My pants. I'm a super hashtag.
I'm a super.
I think, OK, if you're talking getting wet,
if you're talking soupings, the I think the most.
Unpleasant. OK, there's all right.
This poncho is right. And that that helps.
I've done these rides with ponchos.
I'm not dying to get wet on these things.
But really, the big problem enters with the feet.
I think if there was an easier way to prevent your because wet socks,
I think it's nobody.
Yeah, nobody likes that.
And I can maintain.
You just said he likes wet socks and shoes.
Is that that's not true.
I don't mind.
I don't mind is different than like if we hook you up to a lie detector,
would you pass?
I might.
I don't want to walk around with it.
You know, this is a contrarian opinion.
Maybe because I have some contrarian opinions, but I don't like wet socks,
which is why I mean, if a sudden rainstorm comes in that I wasn't expecting.
But again, if I know I'm going on a water ride and I had fun,
it's a nice memory that I had fun.
But you can have a memory without your
you don't have to wear a memory.
Can I get at least?
You've got like 20 memories.
You have family albums of pictures of your wet socks from going on rides.
Like, oh, remember on his mantle, just different socks that are wet.
Oh, you they've just crusted over 15 years.
They dry.
It takes forever for your socks to dry.
It does. Yeah, it takes a lot longer.
Sort of the thickest, potentially thickest fabric you're wearing.
I and I don't know if I've revealed this on the show before,
but there's a bit of a confession.
So on Splash Mountain, I say the last five times I've gone on,
I will covertly take my socks off in the log.
You sneaky.
Oh, my gosh, that's so smart.
This is the end of the ride.
I'm furious about this confession secretly when he's going like,
I'm taking my socks off.
I'll do it low key.
I will just kind of go and then I put one in the pocket
and I put the other two so no one notices his sock off song.
But I'm wanting to throw people off.
You know, they're they don't know this guy's just obviously he's having a nice day.
My shoes, they're still on.
I'm going to go like this sock over here.
You narrated.
Mm hmm. You announce it that you're doing.
You're like, because it's a little trick.
You mean I've been in the log with you.
Yeah, I let you in on all the weird shit I do.
Why do you keep that secret?
What's the problem with that?
Because I feel like if I feel like people are weird with bare feet in general.
Got it. Oh, you take you take care of it.
I guess in my head, what I was of course, that makes more sense.
And my head, what I was picturing was you have you like slip your shoes off,
take your socks off, put your shoes back on.
Yes, you do.
But then you put your shoes back on.
I put the shoes back on on the ride.
Yeah, I'm not bare feet in the log. Right.
So but then you're just you got a rubber.
Barefoot exposure weirds people out.
Yeah. So I feel like it, especially sometimes you're in the log with strangers.
You know, sometimes you're like, this guy taking his shoes off.
You're solo and sometimes you're all it's otherwise children.
Sometimes you're behind a bunch of children.
That is happening a couple times.
Although I don't think I was doing the shoe trick then, but I was with.
It's a hack. I like to call it a shoe hack.
Did you know shoes come off?
Shoes can come off and your socks also can come off and go into your pockets.
Mom, the man behind me in the right started taking his gloves off.
No, that's not what happened.
The shoes are fine, but he started telling it to me like it was a little trick.
Then he sang and then I asked him why and he said, I don't want to get souped.
Hello, boys. Did you know that your shoes can come off?
Oh, God.
Take your shoes off if you don't want to soup it.
Yeah, I'm a cool adult.
I like that hack. I think that's a good hack.
Yeah, you can wear a slip on.
I don't I don't do that at Disney yet, but that's a good idea to wear slip on,
slip on off and then your shoes dry a lot easier.
And then you go to the bathroom, you put your socks.
I think the pre putting on the flip flops is maybe the way to.
That's good. You did.
So that means you have to throw them into knots.
Flop. Yes, unfortunately.
Yeah, but listen, they're I mean, they're flipping the floppy.
You know, you flip and flop them.
They fold up. You're not careful.
Flip flop right away.
That's right. You got to keep your flip on.
But when they flip a flop and you just fold them up and put them somewhere
like they're not like regular shoes.
I saw. Yeah.
There's no dimensionality.
Easy. Yeah.
So that's my hack.
I shove flip flops in between.
Yeah. Under my belt.
All these hacks.
Maybe I could I leave them like dangling on like a belt loop.
Yeah, like get a little chain.
Yeah, like a chain wallet.
But they're chain flip flops.
That would be the strangest thing.
Or I go to downtown Disney Sandal Store, Sanuk.
Of course, you know, Sanuk.
I've been learning about anticipation of the downtown Disney ordeal coming soon.
You go to Sanuk by your flip flops.
Then as soon as you're off the ride, return them.
And hopefully they don't care that they're soaking wet.
Sneaky. I like that.
It's not the plastic act that doesn't work.
Yeah, I would imagine it doesn't work.
But if you put them into the drying station
and Humphreys dry, you know, hold the shoes right up to the hottest part.
Now, this is a lot of work.
You really got to you're really engaging.
And I'm spending a lot of money because the drying station costs five dollars.
It does. It costs. It's a very.
Their ponchos are pretty prohibitively expensive as well,
because I thought about doing it late at night one time.
And my wife would only do it if we got ponchos and the ponchos were like
$15, $15.
Ridiculous. It's just plastic that's been gathered.
Yes, that's like two cents worth.
And you end up wet anyway because you are sweating
because of the sheet of unbreathable plastic you're wearing.
Good point.
Also, the plastic we got, we, Lindsey and I got a poncho in Animal Kingdom.
And the fumes from the plastic were toxic.
Yeah, we were getting headaches from it wearing it for 25 minutes.
So I don't know if they're the same ponchos as the California Adventure ones.
But we were like it was pouring rain and we just took them off.
And we're like, we can't do this.
It's crazy. I don't know why.
Who knows? We somebody chime in on what kind of plastic they use.
Somebody out there knows.
Question just occurred to me, why don't you take your socks off
before you get on the ride?
Uh, nobody's looking at your feet.
Yeah, I feel like that's.
People are all like ringing stuff out.
No, people are there's benches like by the entrance and actually people.
Oh, you're right.
But that's actually that feels more, I guess.
OK, I could probably do the bathroom.
But because I don't want to be in a bench.
Clothes essentially on a ride
and having to sneak and sing your song.
I guess probably the answer is I like doing it on the ride.
I think the answer is I get some sort of enjoyment on it.
Oh, God. Here we go.
Now this is the confession part.
Now Mike's the weird one. Yes.
Well, no longer the image of me on a moving platform soaking wet.
I didn't. I don't forget about your love of wet socks.
Yeah, that's the weirdest thing.
We've moved on entirely. Squash, baby.
That's the way.
The bathroom is the only other place I think you could do it.
And I think just sometimes, well, you got the fast pass,
you're running a splash and I'm not going to hold everyone up
when I know I can do it in the log.
And that I hold everyone up.
I mean, I go to the bathroom.
There's also you got to go past for help for because also there's not.
You pulled everyone up every time you go to the bathroom.
Plus changing shoes in a bathroom like is not ideal.
Yes, it is. There's no where to sit.
And let's like to put the toilet down and sit on the toilet.
Yeah. Yes. No, I don't want to do that.
Many bathrooms have chairs. They're called toilets.
I don't care for that. Honestly.
And you refuse to do it on a bench
because you don't want the general public to peep your feet.
Who are also doing that, who are already there doing that.
The general public is already doing what you're doing.
Yeah, I guess you do it in the log.
Let him do it in the log.
Just say you don't want to end up on wiki feet, Michael.
I know you already are.
I guarantee all of you guys are on wiki.
I know I am.
I would be honored if somebody would put me on there, honestly.
I'd like on wiki feet.
Change in your shoes from the I mean, a security camera has to have it.
And there used to be the website called Flash Mountain,
where they collected every time somebody flashed their boobs
going down the road.
That was a very like early internet and the site still exists.
And there's honestly like, you know, six photos on it.
Like it never really happened.
So this, I think, is the new thing.
Log feet, log feet.
So maybe I should like put my feet in the air on the photo part.
Like I should. That would be an.
I would be worried about you.
What would happen to your body?
Maybe they're like even just hitting the splash.
What would you like?
Crunch your lumbar or something like that?
I wouldn't seem safe because there's no belt.
It's a reason why. That's right.
You could you just tumble right out, but you'd land feet first
and you'd slide down the railing like, whoa, which would be really fun, honestly.
Flipping out of the car, flipped up
and out of the car on Splash Mountain and slid down.
And then and then like
and then like through your hands up in a shocker was like tubular.
I would definitely use some beach slaying, some beach
surfers slaying on the way down. You have to.
And then you and then you're being loaded into the ambulance after all this.
And they ask, are you OK?
And you say, I'm more than OK.
I'm I'm coming to wiki feet.
Please, please do not get us kicked off
Patreon for your weird wiki feet.
It's flat around wiki feet business.
You think that'll happen?
Spatial would ban us.
They're going to kick us off because because of Mike's adult activities.
Adult activities.
As Mike's adult,
all the head adult pervert business, the nun who runs the school is here
to give me rules.
I'd like to start an adult pervert business, please.
You know, Patreon is like porn.
Yeah, it was paid.
But then it's like hidden, like your page gets hidden.
Then for if you market explicit.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, so it's not searchable.
I'm making a joke that you're you're doing like pervert feet stuff.
Pervert feet stuff.
I guess I am. No joke.
He likes it. That's what we've determined.
We've discussed the dirty foot on pirates.
Yeah, doing it in the log.
Dear Pet House Forum, you'll never guess what happened to me in a log.
It's the thrill.
It's like getting a quickie in like, like, yeah, like, hey,
can we do we have sex really fast, like in this public space?
You're like trying to see how quickly you can.
It's exactly the same thing.
Yeah, it's exactly.
Yeah, totally the same.
Yeah, yeah, completely.
And our Patreon is fucked.
It's yeah, our Patreon is screwed now because I take my socks off.
And our log.
We are pervert content.
This has been let's put the warning.
It will use the real warning at the top of the adult content.
It's all.
You have to use it at the top of every episode of every show.
It always goes there.
It is your fault.
I know. This is sort of your fault.
Actually, it is. Yeah.
But I would not take my socks off like that on the rapids
because it's so visible.
I would not on Grizzly River Rapids.
The fact that people would see you do.
Because they got to pay, right?
I'm not putting on my show.
You don't work for free.
I'm not putting on my pervert foot show unless I get paid for it.
Oh, man.
Gee whiz.
Jason's laughing.
I don't think he's going to be able to get himself back here.
We got to cover.
We got to cover him.
Yeah, what else?
Talk about the signage.
I don't know. I don't know where else.
I don't know where to go from there.
Let's talk about this.
We've thrown this out and I want Mary's opinion on it.
Sometimes we've said, and I'm wearing the shirt kind of accidentally,
but we've said the country bears are no longer in Disneyland.
They took them out.
The bear is there now.
We've thrown the idea out of throwing some country bear robots on this ride.
Do you think that would be blasphemous?
Do you think that would ruin the ride?
Do you like it pure like this or are you open to?
Oh, I'm open to it.
I mean, absolutely open.
Because that line, you sort of weave your eye.
I actually love this line because you're like,
it feels like you're like going through like canoe sheds and like you're seeing like it.
It feels very like camp esque to me, which I really like.
But it's true that there's not much going on besides getting to look at old coffee tins and that kind of thing.
So I think putting up putting some of those country bears along the way couldn't hurt.
I think that'd be really fun.
And I don't feel like there's it's enough of a specific.
There's not a narrative to it.
You know what I mean?
Like you're you're just like you're in Grizzly River Rapids and that's the story.
Right. So I don't think there's any clashing of stories that's happening.
Right. There's nothing necessarily that like the country where it doesn't belong in this story.
It doesn't really matter. Yeah.
Well, and that's been one of our complaints about the ride is for a ride with a bear at the entry,
a bear mountain in the distance.
There's no bears. There's no bear.
Yeah, we're the bears. Yeah, that's true.
You go through a cave. There's a roar.
There's a roar. So it's a just bear.
That's fun.
That's that's said to possibly be the ghost of Usiwawi.
What's the name of the bear? The stoned bear.
I go back and get the name.
Ozzy Mada Ozzy Mada.
Usumati or Matei.
Usumati. OK, great.
OK, so that's his roar, but it's a ghost bear.
Yeah, I think I saw somewhere referring to that.
It's a ghost bear, which is cool.
Yeah, it would be fun, though, to have them like along the ride.
That would be fun, like in like in Splash Mountain, where you see all those characters.
Yeah, right. That's really fun.
At the very least, like more like ghost bear or have like a hitchhiking ghost bear
or something like Haunted Mansion.
Hitchhiking ghost bear.
That's a nice thing.
Well,
getting to see them.
I mean, we've talked about this, putting the country bears there, but why are they there?
Are they on vacation?
Is that where we like witnessing little like their like, is it little vacation
tableaus because one of those country bear shows was the vacation hoedown?
And it's still in Tokyo.
So are we seeing that's this is what it's like when the bears are not
where because they or should they be singing to you?
They could be the spokes bears
for like conservation or the park for whatever.
REI. I feel like that seems a little less fun than them having like a hootenanny.
But well, like like they're no, they can still have a hootenanny.
But they're also explaining park rules as well.
Like they're doing.
What do they call it? Like influencer spawn con?
They're doing like sponsored content for the.
Oh, I know you a little.
They tell you a little about the parks in line and then they do the show
like the ride is the show.
So they're not explaining stuff in the ride or they are.
Well, maybe Henry can.
So Henry's zooming past these characters.
You can't really like listen to him talk for more than.
No, you can get a little music.
Music, but they can't explain. That's what I mean.
I'm saying in line, they can tell you about the parks a little.
Which is what, like square footage?
What? Like what are they?
What are they telling you?
The way all the conservation.
I love the defensive.
Well, they could still have a hootenanny.
I don't know.
Just that tone with that word is just very funny.
It's a little mix.
I still have a hootenanny.
The songs with a message going by.
I think that they should all be.
They should be having a woman.
No more rules.
No stats, no rules.
Hootenanny.
They should be on vacation.
Step one, Hootenanny.
Number two, no statistics, no rules, no explanations.
Like the X games before them, no rules.
OK, wait, never mind.
No Hootenanny.
Country Bears performing X games.
Oh, we found it.
Now I like this.
I like where this is going.
Together. OK.
So so Henry is snowboarding.
Liver Lips McGraw is, I don't know,
skateboarding, skateboarding with a sword or something.
That's an X games thing, I assume.
The three sisters are all like they're all on separate motorcycles
spinning endlessly around a scared tourist.
Yes. Not letting them go.
I'm trying to think.
Trixie is or no.
Why am I having a brain fart about her name?
Teddy Swingin.
Swingin Teddy Bear.
Swingin Teddy Bear on the right there.
And she's, of course, in being lowered from a helicopter.
Wow. Yeah.
It's in its very dangerous.
She's there to rescue a hiker who got trapped under rocks.
And then to seduce him as well.
Oh, cool. Yeah, that's fun.
She's like the Mae West Bear.
Yeah. So, yeah.
We always need a Mae West Bear.
All of the bears, all of the female bears are
like Mae West types, honestly.
They're just different ages.
Yes. Yeah.
There's like teenager Mae West types, the Sun Bonnet Trio.
There's Teddy Bear, who's crying.
And then there's no, no, there's Trixie who's crying
and then Swingin Teddy Bear who comes out from the ceiling.
They're all kind of like handkerchief blowers.
Hello. Right.
I wish we had a video.
Oh, there's a GIF of you doing hello.
Hello.
I'll happily recreate it and I'll put a foot up too.
I'll put it on WikiFace.
I'll wave a handkerchief with my foot.
We are getting on that goddamn site now because we've talked about it so much.
You sure are.
Our dream.
Hi, Edwin.
So, yeah, there.
I think we'd be the first men on it.
And that might be. No way.
No, I'm sure it is, man.
I feel like the ratio is going to be like 99.5 percent.
The Monty Python foot is probably on there.
You think they just put up like classic foots of lore?
Yeah.
Any Giants foot from.
Yeah. So so like Knott's just recently put on all put all these like they did
a very nice job of putting on all these different like woodland creatures
on their raft ride, at least they didn't do like a crazy.
Except for there's an old man with a musket, which is great.
But everything else is just sort of like animal robots.
Cool. So. I love robots.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think all we want out of this ride is get some robots on the.
Get some robots. Yeah.
I like going through the.
Coyote.
Oh, yeah.
Hello. Hello.
To Mills, Eureka Gold and Timber Company.
There's a very intensive back story about Eureka
Gold and Timber that the Imagineers have.
The Bears could tell you that the Bears could tell you about Jacob Probst,
who discovered their gold there.
The fictional gold prospector.
Oh, that's fun.
Yeah. Related to an ancestor of Mark Probst or Jeff Probst.
Jeff Brass. That's what I meant.
TV. Not Mark. Best host on TV.
Sorry, I got his name wrong.
Is there a Mark Probst somewhere?
I don't know.
I think I might have just fucked that up anyway.
You were thinking of Mark Summers.
Yeah. I mean, always.
Yes. Your favorite host.
Mark Summers. Jeff Probst is survivor though.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think Mark Probst is he on what we do in the shadows.
The actor Mark Proche is what I'm.
Yes. Yeah.
From the from the Dickerverse.
Mary, best animatronic at any theme park.
What's your opinion?
Boof.
Favorites, just some favorites.
Some favorites. Let's see.
Oh, I love the hippos on Jungle Cruise.
I like the hippos.
I like the elephant on Jungle Cruise.
Some of the OGs. Some of the first era.
Those are some favorites. Let's see.
I'm trying to think of what.
I might need reminding of what all the animatronics are.
I mean, there's a go down Big Thunder and there's.
There's like the dancing animals and splash, you know.
Yes, of course, those guys.
The riverboat animals.
Yeah. The.
Yeah, that's the geese or the ladies who are dancing.
A little like kick line. Yeah.
Yeah. Are they geese that kick line?
People are yelling at us now.
They're listening in their cars.
Are there geese that kick line?
Oh, come on.
You know what they are.
Stay away from the.
What does that lady sing?
Yeah. She's a awesome. Right.
She's like a pod. Yeah.
She's a possum. Possum mom.
Yeah. That's my favorite part.
The laughing place. That's right.
That gets so serious.
From the laughing place.
It really is so scary.
That's one of my favorites, too.
And all the all the little ones are like, oh, oh.
You're auditioning for.
It seems like you're auditioning right now for playing that character
on a Disney plus show.
Mm hmm. And also hurry back.
Oh, yeah.
Back. That's good.
Thank you so much. And also and also.
Uh. Um.
Uh.
The hesitant robot.
Can't think of a single.
I'm so sure.
Jay Audubon Woodlore when he's at a loss for words.
Bumper McFerrin.
Oh, he's never at a loss for words.
No, no, no. He's always he's.
He knows just what to say.
A lot of 1950s like cartoon characters had that kind of voice.
Well, like a droopy dog.
Though this person.
Wait, let me get the name right, because I was looking at I was like,
why is that voice familiar?
But that voice of that of Jay Audubon Woodlore,
it was not always, but most of the time droopy.
One of the original group and then and also the White Rabbit and Smee.
Yes, I believe that's me.
That's a do be more.
Did I?
I don't know if I talked about this on the show, but when I saw Once Upon
a Time in the Hollywood at the Vista, which is like a one screen,
an old one screen movie theater here in Hollywood.
And they played a droopy dog short before it that killed.
Well, people were laughing.
They applauded at the like it played better than some UCB shows
I've seen in the last five years.
I don't believe that.
So, yeah, droopy dogs still got it.
Still got it. Still got it.
Still laughing after all these years.
You got to love droopy. Yeah.
We were in the clip that I showed earlier where the signed
Don't Molest the Bears, then it cuts to Donald,
who is a really funny expression on his face,
almost as if he wanted to molest the bears.
It's kind of like, well, and I it was making us.
I'm sure that is not why, but I was making us
my wife, I just fleshed to like, yeah, Donald's funny.
You forget these characters are just around and they exist
mainly as like photo opportunities and theme parks.
And you go back at some of these shorts and forget
they are like really super funny.
Yeah, they're funny.
Yeah, Donald is funny. Don't forget it.
And it sounds like droopy is too.
I'm trying to think there's an old I got this
IDW collection of old Mickey cartoons and they are,
you know, problematic in some ways.
But Mickey is a maniac and he says crazy stuff like constantly.
Like he threatens like to he hopes somebody dies in one of them.
Really? Yeah.
And then like he says something really not like cancelable to many.
He says like many are I'm trying to think.
Oh, yeah. Many are a peach for looks, but you've got applesauce for brains.
Which is like crazy.
Like these characters used to be insane.
These characters.
This you've got apples famously
superior to apples.
Yeah. So looking like a peach, you want these characters like an apple.
Hell no.
They used to have these characters say crazy shit.
Yeah. All the time.
Yeah. Because why why why not?
Sure. I mean, I guess also over the time, it was like that was just a normal thing
for a man to say to a woman.
That was just a turn of phrase that everyone was saying out on the town.
Right. Right.
And when you were out on the town, you're always talking about
who was a peach for looks, who had applesauce for brains.
And she's great, but she's got that fucking applesauce for brains.
Oh, boy. That applesauce for brains.
Oh, jeez.
If you got sick, you'd say you've got an applesauce.
You've got applesauce for an immune system.
Mm hmm. Yeah. Any negative quality.
Right. Which luckily that's changed.
And applesauce is good.
And the because it's delicious.
And the greatest compliment you could get is you're a peach for looks
and you have brains for brains.
No higher praise. Yeah.
Both. Imagine that. Yeah.
What about like you're a peach for looks and you've got a peach for a brain?
I don't. That's hmm.
Sounds a little bit. Sounds pretty soft.
Pretty quickly.
They get more.
You want to look like a peach, but not think like one.
Yeah. Right.
That's so crazy.
All right. I'm going to go through all the fruits now.
What is the smartest fruit?
You have to think of a lot of stuff.
We have to still crack that show idea at the start of the episode.
We have to figure this out.
There's a lot of work we have to still do.
Add it to the whiteboard. Yeah.
Better start that hose up.
I'm thinking I got a natural state.
Very well. Put a hose on.
All right. What else?
So what else do we have not talked about here?
There's a logistical thing I never knew about this ride.
So apparently when rapids rides are not in operation and in California
and I think even in Orlando for there's a few months of the
colder months of the year, they shut it down to do work on it.
Usually like this pride is usually closed like what?
January to like March or so.
A little refurbished a little refurbished.
But regardless, they need somewhere even when it's running.
But when it's not pumping, like at night, when the ride's not running,
they need somewhere to put the water.
So they were trying to figure out what to do with that.
And they were going to build an underground basin to do it,
which would have been very expensive. Basin.
Basin. Yeah. OK.
And so they realized that there was a large body of water
they were going to build at the at the wharf area, the other part of the park.
So that's where the water drains to sometimes,
which they wanted that to be like a tidal basin to simulate
like rising and falling water anyway.
So they needed a place to sometimes store water from this ride.
So I guess they connected the two underground.
They are genius. Yeah.
So all of the California Adventure bodies of water connect.
Not all of them, but those do.
And that's why I don't mind having it in my mouth.
Yeah. It's been all over that park.
And it's taken care of. They take care of the water.
And I know they take care of that water.
They put thought into that water.
I think. I love it.
We should take a cup, an empty cup, when we go on these rides
and have a little scoop of a little drink.
Have a little scoop. Have a little scoop of water.
Yeah, we should see.
You should get a little scoop and then go get it water tested.
See, see how dangerous it actually is.
Although you probably would get sued for that. Right.
I don't know. I think it's OK.
I mean, how? Like, if I don't know, how would they sue you?
What would be illegal of it?
That you. That you.
You did it and we didn't say you could.
You didn't ask. Yeah.
I think if you do it, as long as you don't publish like a lid blower,
as long as you're not like.
Because they're not claiming that that water is drinkable.
So there's nothing that you would. Yeah.
It's probably on the warning signs, too.
Yes. Don't drink. Yes. I think you're right.
Don't drink this water, idiot.
Yeah. Don't drink this water. Why would you? You suck.
Yeah. What you need the country bears around to mourn about.
Right. And one of the country bear the river in that version, they would stop
the rap. The actual raft would stop in front of a bear for a couple of minutes.
Well, explain why the water wasn't drinkable.
We had it tested recently. Right.
Let me get into this.
Alkali level.
The pH specific, the pH specifics.
Swipe didn't go well.
Jason's dream ride.
All right.
Hillbilly bears talking about pH. Yeah.
What else you got?
You know, what's the fact about the thing we haven't talked about is this is one of the best.
This region, the Grizzly Peak Recreation Area is one of the best places to see
Disneyland feral cats in and around.
Oh, yeah. Like in and around the brushes.
At least that's one of the spots that I have seen the cats.
And especially a shout out to Francisco, a long haired tortoise shell.
Say hello to Francisco if you're there, because the cats all have names.
Do you know any of this about?
There's an Instagram account, I believe, that tracks the Disneyland cats
and knows who all of them are.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's there's consistent characters.
So this is one of the places because they want to be near
nature or a simulation thereof.
And it's still there's quiet parts of this area.
So it's not necessarily quiet parts.
So trafficked so they can have a little break.
A cat would not want to hang out in Radiator Springs because every five seconds.
Oh, my gosh. Yeah.
And all that.
Not a place for a cat to hang out.
All that rock and roll music.
Cats hate rock and roll. Yeah.
Yeah, it's a fact.
That's a fact.
Cats love jazz.
They love the acoustics.
Flucking. Yeah.
Yeah. They love bright bass.
They love Spanish guitar.
Right. Which is California.
Spanish guitar. Tons of California flamenco.
Guitar is everywhere at California Adventure. Yeah.
Yeah. And to well Puss in Boots
loves flamenco guitar.
Oh, right. He's but he's not an Antonio Banderas puts in boots.
Mm hmm. Yeah, that's true.
Yeah. Dreamworks. Yeah.
I know. You can't be in the park.
I'm just saying. No, I'm just saying.
If he sets one foot in that park.
The train set him on fire.
I will personally tie some fake rocks to his little kitty legs.
You go into the bottom of that tidal basin.
Oh, too hard, Jason.
We don't have to.
I was setting them on fire, but I would never do that.
OK, all right. No, my drowning is more in.
You know what would be the simulation of the rising and falling tides
when the water drains into there, you know, you don't want it draining.
And then like, what is that? Right.
You know, exactly.
Then got to bury it.
You got to draw some in the castle, the castle moat.
That's all that's deep and dark.
Nobody ever goes into the castle. Don't drain that.
Don't drain that.
Yeah. I don't even want to know what you'd find.
Enemies from from the 50s.
Yeah, he kept them all communists.
It's just full of communists.
Communists.
He built Disneyland as a place to hide the body of communists.
Communist. Yeah.
Anyway, the police can't come looking if it's my own the lake.
That's true.
Former Disney head E.
Card Walker got up to some real shady business in the 70s.
Nixon, Disney, let Nixon hide some of his enemies.
Sure. Well, Orange County buddies.
Got to. Got to.
Why they built the submarines.
That's why he was there overlooking it.
So here's where you can hide them in the reef. OK.
God's cut this monorail ribbon.
So what have we missed?
We've missed that there's a big drop and the drops pretty fun.
You're not 20 feet. 22 feet, I think.
Wow. Is it? I've heard 21.
Word on the street is there are different numbers around 20.
We know that for sure.
So it's not a complete fact yet.
And the rafts, this is unique to this ride.
I feel that they spin as they go down that track.
Raph spin. Yes, that's fun.
Designed by that.
Not every like a lot of rapids rides have that sort of drop,
but they don't all spin.
They found a new thing in this genre.
If you look at the list of all the rapids rides that there ever were,
it's a weird genre of ride that existed outside of the major.
But there wasn't they didn't have them at Disney, didn't have them at Universal.
And they were all like mostly Six Flags and Hershey Park
and those kind of places.
But once Disney finally got on board this trend, they reinvented the wheel.
Yeah. Added a big mill wheel.
I love it. Twirl. Yeah. Yeah.
It's so fun. The twirl.
It's really fun. It's so fun.
Because then you get to be on all sides of it.
You get to be facing down and then you get to be backwards going down.
It's really fun. Yeah.
I love that moment, too, like
right before you go down the drop, you can see where you just were.
Yeah. And like it's like a little bridge going over.
I like that, too. Yeah.
It's really, really great.
It's also like a ride like every other ride.
It positions you in a certain spot in a certain direction.
So it is like if you went on, you'd have a different experience,
technically a different experience every time.
Sometimes you go over backwards.
Like imagine sometimes you went backwards on Big Thunder.
That would be amazing.
But it's impossible, unfortunately.
I mean, it's not impossible, but you get in trouble.
You just whip your head around a lot.
One time I rode Big Thunder Mountain and
me and my friend were in the last seat.
Right. It's two, two at a time. Right.
Yeah. And the woman in the little cart in front of us
had hair that went that like truly was like skimming the gears.
Like it was like this long gray hair that was.
Oh, my God. Truly when she got off the ride, it was like down to her
like knees or something.
And I was like she it was almost like she wanted something to happen.
Like she was like just like waving her hair around like it.
Catherine and I were both like clutching the sides of the cart the entire time.
I mean, are we going to are we going to see a head come off?
Are we going to see a head come off?
But the workers were like not worried, didn't tell her to tie her hair up or anything.
But I was like, why on earth would you even toy with it?
If you had hair that long and great have hair that long.
I love it. But but why would you even want to even play with the idea
that it could get caught in something like, oh, it's so scary.
Yeah, that's very scary.
I also to lesser degree, I don't really want to be touched by strangers hair.
So yeah, that long. Yes, it didn't.
It wasn't blowing into our face.
OK, that's good. It was just sort of waving down like below.
It's like giving the track clean, giving a little sweep.
It was so crazy. Wild.
Because you I'm sure like I guess it's probably just something
they don't come in contact with ever that severe of a length.
I'm not how I would assume there have to be like safety regulations.
You would think I was like.
Because that's like such a like if somebody came on the ride with a veil,
like a bridal veil, they would say you can't wear that, I assume.
I'm just trying to think something that's not long.
It's also then hair ish.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'd be like, well, excuse me, you can't.
That's going to drag. Well, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Oh, I also I know we're not talking about this.
Oh, actually, can we talk about the wardrobe of the people who work?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Really love it.
Yeah. Yeah.
In favor of I also love the wardrobe on Big Thunder Mountain.
I actually think it's very stylish.
Grizzly River Run, if I am right, what do they wear?
They wear sort of like like kind of gingham.
Am I right about that?
I don't know. Is it like what a what a national parks employee would wear?
Is it a little like like a ranger?
I feel like a scoutish.
Which I am so in love with.
Do you have a bandana on as we speak?
Do they wear a bandana?
Is that I don't really call it a.
I feel like they might around their neck.
I think it's.
Which those can be those can be cool.
Those are very cool.
If you're yeah, like correctly styled,
they don't have to be stiff like J.
Audubon and Woodlore. Right.
Oh, they can be hip.
Paul Lind or Charles Nelson Riley would wear them on Match Game.
Sure. That's my thing with the bandana.
So more of a neckerchief.
And more of a neckerchief. Yeah.
Yeah. So that's good.
I like those. I would wear that.
I do think maybe I'm like 10 years away from wearing like a neckerchief.
I think that's right. I think that's right.
I worked on the thing in Oklahoma this summer and a lot of the people in the crew,
the young, the young, cool people there, like in their early 20s, they
like the key grip.
She was so cool and she wore a bandana tied around her neck,
like like where it was like not like a kind of like a railroad
esk feel to it.
But I was like, oh, yeah, no, it was that it was like tied around her neck.
And she was just working.
And I was like, that is so cool.
She looks awesome.
Anyway, so so bandanas are in.
So bandanas are in.
Yeah. So this outfit is very stylish right now.
The Grizzly River employee.
I have to like I want to I want to like look up a picture of like what it
what it actually is so that we can really critique it,
because I'm going off of memory and I don't know if it's accurate.
Some costumes, some employee costumes seem a little like mortifying.
Like if you had to wear that every day, be a tad embarrassing.
But there are some yes, sometimes in my wife, and I'll especially point out,
like that's that's pretty sharp.
That's pretty Foxy uniform. Right.
Yeah. Sometimes they get Foxy.
I love. Oh, go ahead. Oh, no, I was just saying.
Just you go. Indiana Jones.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And those clothes are cool. Yeah. Uh huh.
I was just going to say which one specifically has been referred
to as Foxy by you or Erin.
I'm not I can't I can't recall off.
But this genre for sure of like outdoorsy, like
beige khaki. Yeah.
Like for women, especially.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Some are pretty cool.
Like a lot of some feel like Karen Allen and yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yes. Everyone loves it.
As it not like the Little Mermaid ride where they're wearing like little sailor suits.
Yeah, I'd say that's not good or anything where you're in like a, you know,
I wouldn't want if I was working in a park, I wouldn't want to dress in anything
where I had to wear like a big floppy Renaissance hat or anything with like
the big big shoulder puffs.
I would love to wear the maid's outfits in Haunted Mansion.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Those are so cool. Those are pretty cool.
What were you wearing in the what was medieval times?
We were like it was similar to that.
It was like a peasant's blouse and like a skirt.
And they gave us like a little corset, cinchy thing that we sort of tie.
Sure. All right.
It's great. Huh?
I would like to wear the cars racing outfit.
The like that's the pit crew jumpsuit.
I love the pit crew jumpsuit.
That's fun. Yeah.
That's good.
You look kind of like Joel on Mystery Science Theater.
Original Mystery Science Theater.
That's right. Yeah.
And then Duffy has that my Duffy has that same outfit.
So Duffy and I could wear the same clothes.
Should we get another drink?
Ten years away from that, too. Right?
Oh, boy. I don't know.
Yeah, we know.
How do we? Yeah, we might be ten minutes as soon as we leave.
He puts the clothes he puts on a jumpsuit that matches his tiny stuffed bears jumpsuit.
And then Ed would get one, too.
You know, Duffy, the Disney teddy bear.
I had the name sounds familiar.
It's just a sort of a personality list.
Teddy bear they sell in the theme park.
His traits are no traits.
And he he mini made this.
The backstories that mini made Duffy for Mickey,
because Mickey is a sea captain and then he was going on a long sea voyage.
I see. So Duffy.
He's also kind of a cipher.
Mickey has had a million jobs or can do whatever you want him to do.
Yes. After he after they said maybe he shouldn't be insulting mini like that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let's keep you busy.
Maybe you shouldn't be a misogynist.
Or like some of the maybe some of the older Mickey's.
He's always like an arms reach away from a gun.
And some of those old shorts and comic strips.
He was always he wields a gun in the comic.
These comics I'm reading.
So, yeah, yeah.
So he was a wild man.
So anyway, mini knew he needed to be kept busy at sea.
And of course, a teddy bear was going to keep him company.
And Duffy was born.
And now you can get Duffy and his his friend,
Shelly May, and dress them in all sorts of fun outfits.
And this is what I'm describing to you, Mike's teddy bear, who he dresses.
And he's up. I have him upstairs.
Very fun. And he has a full cars jumpsuit.
So as soon as we leave, he has his own bed.
As soon as we leave, you'll put on Duffy's shoes and socks and then
and then discreetly take the shoes off and take the socks off
and then put the shoes back on.
That's right. In the bath.
We'll be in the bathtub.
It'll simulate the log.
Yikes. It's OK, Duffy.
No one is looking.
Who is going to come out of this episode looking weirder, me or Jason?
Is it me? For once, you maybe. OK.
Don't forget, I was moaning about Tiffany Lamps a while back.
That feels like it was yesterday.
Yeah, I know. Yeah.
It's been so much creepiness.
Covered so much since.
So we really have any closing thoughts about this ride, about California
Adventure, about theme parks, love, love, love.
I support I'm in favor of.
I love it.
I would just highly recommend going at night to any of these rides.
I think that's a great experience. Sure.
And listen, just.
Hey, get a little of that river water in your mouth and see what happens.
And let us know your immune system.
You'll never get sick again.
Cold and flu season is coming.
That's right.
Teach your teach your innards to fight.
Yeah, in shape.
Better than a vaccine, better than a flu vaccine.
Sure.
Drinking a little grizzly river run water.
And I say like, turn up the water, especially when I think so, too.
Turn up the water.
I've been there during heat waves and I still haven't gotten that way.
I want them to turn up the water and let's get a few more robots in there.
I think we all can agree on that.
We can all agree on that.
Whatever genre of robot they put in.
Yeah. Yeah.
We'll love it.
All right.
Well, great tips.
Great episode. Thanks for hanging out.
Mary Holland, you survived podcast the ride.
Thanks so much for being here.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
Oh, as I exit the gift shop, well, take this key chain of the picture of us.
And you know, what's the thing I forgot to mention is that the the little store,
I think it's called a Russian River Outpost or something.
Oh, yes. Love Russian River Outpost.
Oh, wait. OK. Well, that's literally the gift shop.
Fabulous. Seemingly. Very fun.
Very fun. A lot of fun odds and ends.
You know what? You know, it's weird.
They have a bunch.
There's they have like grizzly puppets and the puppets,
despite being a different kind of Disney bear than Duffy,
also have a little mouse ear shape in the paw.
Oh, interesting.
You can get those. Those seem pretty cute.
And you can get thermoses.
You can get all kinds of camping goods there, which is really fun.
You can also take a scoop and get a big big bag of gems.
You can buy. Yeah. When I was a kid.
Oh, yeah. Forget it.
You see those at a gift shop.
You're like, yeah, you know, it's not a matter of which if I've got to get it.
What size bag are they going to let me get?
It's so funny how like you love that so much.
Yeah. Bag a bag of hard plastic.
Plastic. Yeah. But what a dream.
Gems. We're like children.
I think Snow White trains us all that like that looks that's money, I guess, too.
It looks like treasure.
So anytime you see it, even if it's plastic,
I think I thought it was worth money, though.
I think I because there used to be that when the Wisconsin Dells,
you could sift and find them.
They did a whole show. A great idea.
Yeah. So we would like sift through and find the plastic gems
and then put them in an old bag.
And I remember being like, you know, with money, like I'm going to be rich.
And at that young age and an entrepreneur. Yeah.
Looking for it, looking to make a buck.
For me, I'm in it for the magic.
I love the they also look like candy, which I think is very appealing.
Yes. Want to put them in my mouth.
Yeah. When I eat.
Oh, I knew we couldn't.
I knew we couldn't make an episode about you saying something
that's something putting in your mouth.
Put it in your mouth, Jason.
I knew we couldn't.
God, we were so close.
We almost made it. We almost made it.
What are the things? What's going on?
What are you doing? What's going on?
I'm perform at UCB.
I'm there a lot with with various groups.
So come check it out.
Wild Horses and JV and NASCAR and all those guys.
If you're in L.A., come see a show.
And then in general, what I'm up to, I'm on that show, Robbie.
That's going to be coming out on Comedy Central soon.
And then a movie with Betsy Sodaro.
We don't know when that's coming out.
But that's called Golden Arm. And that's coming up.
So yeah, there's a lot of fun stuff happening.
That's great. So I guess just keep your ear to the ground.
Can you plug a Twitter maybe that you get or stuff?
Was that what you put things?
I post updates on Twitter at M Holland 85 and on Instagram at Mary Holland days.
Like the sauce. Of course.
Great sauce. Great sauce.
You don't say it. Just plug that in general.
Yeah. And as for us, hey, live shows coming up.
Those are those will still be in the future.
Chicago, Orlando happening.
Come see us if we're coming to your town or come to another town.
If those aren't your towns, go to one of those two.
Don't just go to any town.
Hey, and also check us to check out our Patreon at Patreon.com
slash podcast, right?
Check us out on Twitter, on Instagram, on T public, where you can buy
a fun t shirts and stuff.
No gems, though. Sorry to tell you.
No gems and no feet stuff either. Michael, what is that?
What would that even be?
I don't know.
You're an entrepreneur.
Yeah, I don't know.
Like hoes, hoes, hoes, hoes.
Buy Jason's old wet socks.
Forever wet.
Directly from our WikiFeet page, which doesn't exist as we record this,
but will exist by the end of the episode having aired.
Very good. Go to WikiFeet.com slash podcast.
Could we add a Patreon tier where, like, if we come to your come to a town,
we can set you up in a dunk tank.
Sounds like your dream.
Yeah, the logistics of getting a dunk tank, though.
I got to imagine that's a pain in the ass.
Why just get a big tank full of water?
I got you. It's local ordinances.
She's right. It doesn't matter.
Let's just get a Rubbermaid and then you can sit in a chair above it.
That's it. OK.
Just need a rubbermaid.
And then the listener will be able to just push you into the Rubbermaid.
There's no.
He's genius.
And we make a big sign that says put Jason in his natural state.
That's true.
Natural state booth.
Yeah. All right. That's easy.
Done. All right.
That'll do it. Check us out next week.
See you. Bye bye.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcast, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.