Forever.
Dog.
Warning.
Today's episode may be a joy overload if your favorite Disney character is a clever niece
named Bridget.
It may also contain some of fiction's greatest roosters, Matt Hooper cosplay fantasies, and
hawk lunches.
Who so listeneth of this podcast shallst be mildly amused.
This is Sword in the Stone on Podcast the Ride.
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the show where every episode a kooky old man turns the three
fish in order to teach us a lesson.
I'm Jason Sheridan, joined as always by Mike Carlson.
Hi, I'm Mike Carlson.
That doesn't happen.
That doesn't happen every episode.
What do you mean?
Teaches us to use our heads and we learn about being clever as opposed to using, you know-
It hasn't happened once.
Force of will.
Anyway, Scott Gardner's here too.
And you have to weigh in on this issue.
Let's account for the possibility that the wizard also wipes our memories, but leaves
us with the lesson.
Yeah.
Thank you.
But if he does it every time.
I would say a kooky old man talks about treats that he's recently enjoyed.
That would be Jason Sheridan.
Well, all right.
That's fair.
That happens every episode.
That's what I know.
He's Merlin's age at the height of wart.
Yeah.
Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
You're a combo of both.
Height of Archimedes, geez.
Well, here, look at this.
We're playing in our favorite mythology, the number one Disney property that we've been
waiting to get to for so long.
You know, before we unsheath the sword of the topic of today, just a quick thing I wanted
to mention because I wanted you guys and the listeners to know about some very good theme
park related news in the Gardner household recently.
Just last week, Erin was the winner of an 18 month free pass to Universal Studios.
Whoa.
Yeah.
18 months.
Sizable.
I didn't know such a thing was a possibility.
Universal is weird and stingy.
Even their annual passes, if you get it in August, it only goes through December.
Right.
This is crazy.
18 months.
So thrilled about it.
How did she earn this honor, you might be wondering?
By losing a kicking contest.
She, Erin, participated in a work foot golf competition.
It was a...
Erin, also your wife, for those of you who don't know.
Oh, yes.
Yes, Erin.
Foot golf is your...
What is foot golf?
I don't know.
I didn't know about it before.
Neither did she, which probably hurt her chances at foot golf, but everybody at her place of
work was playing foot golf.
I don't...
Honestly, it was at an official foot golf course even.
Wow.
I know.
What?
Frisbee golf, foot golf, I don't know.
I think it's a combo.
It's like soccer ball style kicking into bigger holes.
And next to golf, it's like a combo course of traditional golf and foot golf.
Okay.
It was six holes, at a total par 18.
The winner of the whole competition scored a 16.
Erin scored a 45.
And it involved her losing her final ball in a lake.
And so she was mildly ashamed by all this, but then at the end discovered that there
is a last place prize.
And that was an 18 month free pass.
Wow.
That's pretty good.
Very good.
And her was a theme park fan.
What was number one?
I think it was maybe also theme park.
It might have been a Disney thing.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
These were good.
This was a high stakes foot golf competition.
Right.
The last place prize was like sort of a, hey, don't worry about it.
You still get a prize.
It wasn't like a punishment.
No, no, no.
She did not increase her workload at her place of employment, at the mine where she worked.
She didn't have to shovel more coal.
Well, that's good.
No, fantastic.
So I get to like, you know, now I will have to pay to go along with her, but now it's
not free island new bar access.
Wow.
It's great.
It wasn't an 18 month pass to the unbuilt Universal Studios in Dubai.
No, no, no.
It wasn't something like that.
Not just, you don't just get to go into the gate and that's all that's there.
But you unlimited, like you can go in and out of that gate as many times as you want.
So okay.
Wow.
That's great.
Congratulations.
Feeling fine.
Yeah.
Wonderful.
Wonderful news to get.
And who knew her poor footsmanship would pay off so wonderfully.
That's great.
Thanks, Aaron.
Yeah.
Thanks.
We'll all thank Aaron for you.
Thank you, Aaron.
Also.
You're reaping the benefits of this.
I'm going to learn about foot golf because I don't know if this is going to really come
up maybe in passing.
I love miniature golf.
Sure.
They're miniature golf fans.
Oh wait, miniature golf counts.
We can talk about miniature golf.
Yeah.
Hey, great.
All right.
We cover, we just unlocked like seven more episodes.
Oh, sure.
And again, foot golf too because it came up here now.
But I'm intrigued by foot golf, especially because a listener emailed, Mark D. Natal
emailed that the Troutdale, the place that you could catch trout has closed.
What?
No.
The Troutdale Hills is no longer there.
Oh, bummer.
The ponds are all dried up and it is closed for good.
So I cannot go trout fishing.
I passed by the sign recently.
Oh no.
Cherished six-year-old memories of an activity that I didn't keep up beyond six years old.
Wow.
Bummer.
Well, I will say that the foot golf course is in the same county as the former Troutdale.
Residents of said county still have some fun on there, but it's not the fun of killing
an animal, of hooking a trout and gutting it.
But foot golf's a little fun too.
Okay.
A little fun to be had everywhere.
Yeah.
Sure.
Oh man.
I'm going to avoid, let me just not talk for the next 45 minutes though, because RIP Troutdale.
Yeah.
RIP.
We could take a break too if you need.
Yeah.
Let me go outside, take a deep breath and think about every individual trout.
They didn't get to die in the expected way.
They were all just tossed on the side of the road somewhere.
They got to live a full life with his trout friends.
That's sad.
Yeah.
I know.
I wanted to eat them.
They didn't get caught by a kid.
It sucks.
Anyways, so good news for me.
Jason, I feel like there's something you got locked and loaded to discuss as well.
I have a news story that was very interesting to me.
It's a couple months old, but it hasn't really come up on the show yet.
Only a few theme park news sites picked it up, but real news sites picked this one up
too.
The Orlando Sentinel, the Associated Press.
Okay.
So a few months ago, you know, all right, well, let me set this up.
There's a resurgent labor movement in America.
We've seen teacher strikes in multiple cities.
There's coal miners recently have been sitting on the tracks down in Kentucky blocking coal
trains because the company went bankrupt here in our own city of Los Angeles.
The Screen Actors Guild just had elections.
The Writers Guild is having very contested elections right now.
They're a blast.
We're getting so many great emails and so many great sons of terrible people who name
names.
Yeah.
And that's funny that sons came up because a famous son comes up in this story too.
So now Disney, in various Disney cast members are in various different unions, which is
down in Florida.
Disney World employs so many people.
So a few months ago, 600 out of a thousand costume performers threatened to cut ties
with their local union due to quote, horrible representation and unresponsiveness to grievances.
Now this is local 385 of which about half of 9,000 members are Disney cast members.
So and around a thousand of those are costumed are like goofy Mickey cast members.
OK.
So that but they're not all Disney people.
Some of them are other theme park.
Other lots of different stuff in this local.
And I'll explain what union it is in a second.
So OK.
All right.
The character performers have been in this union since the 1980s.
And this was such a huge deal that the head of this union had to fly down to Orlando,
hold hearings about this like corrupt leadership and put the local office into what is called
trusteeship where he appointed two people to take over and there'll be elections in
18 months.
OK.
Now the another independent office said in court filings that this local union,
these leaders may have created false records, committed embezzlement and obstruction.
Now so the union in question is the International Brotherhood of the Teamsters and the head
of this union is James P Hoffa.
Not to be confused with James R Hoffa, noticed Jimmy Hoffa, his father.
Oh.
The son of Jimmy Hoffa flew down to Orlando.
So Jimmy Hoffa famously had to deal with the mob and the Kennedys.
His son, James P Hoffa, is dealing with a guy explaining that, no, I'm not goofy.
I'm a friend of goofy.
I'm not goofy. I'm a friend of goofy.
Had to fly down to put local 385 into trusteeship.
Wow. Wow.
So a much sillier lineage than his father held.
Yeah. Yeah.
We have the dawn of costume characters and not yet happened during Elder Hoffa's time.
No. Well, he disappeared in the he disappeared in the 70s and I think was declared dead in
the 80s.
Uh huh.
They I think the Mythbusters conclusively proved he is not buried under Giants Stadium,
which was the longer word.
Jimmy Hoffa, for more context, once played by Jack Nicholson in a movie, will be played
by Al Pacino in the upcoming movie The Irishman.
Yes. In the de-aged Scorsese film.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
OK. So very strange.
There's no there's no property.
Does Disney now own something where they could create a costume character of Hoffa?
Do they own the rights to the film Hoffa?
Who owns? Yeah. Who owns Hoffa?
But if this is actually an interesting question is in general, could you make a walk around
character of any sort of notable figure?
Oh, yeah. What are the rules there?
Is there a law against just making, you know, say a Trump walk around character in?
Where would it go? Where would he be?
He'd be in the monkey cages in Animal Kingdom if he asked me.
We had something to say about he. Well, NBC owns the NBC made The Apprentice, so they could.
They might be the likely home of a Trump walk around.
And it's almost surprising they didn't do it at the time because you could go get a photo
with Billy Bush at the Access Hollywood red carpet at the end of the tour.
Right.
I'm amazed like there wasn't Trump presence on the studio tour at that time.
We know they were pushing that thing so hard.
Right. Yeah.
There's got to be something, though.
So wait, so this this union, though, is just it's costume characters, but it's other.
It's not just it's just a regular teamsters office, too.
So the costumes characters, there's about a thousand of them.
Two thirds of that number threatened to walk because of poor representation.
So I'm just confused. Like there's costume characters, but also there's truck drivers.
Truck drivers. So how do you maybe this is too much.
I don't know if this is in the article, but like how do you end up in a union that has like truck
drivers and a guy playing Daisy Duck or a lady playing Daisy Duck?
It's confusing to me.
Yeah, I don't know. I mean, lots of unions cover.
Right. Multiple things.
Multiple things.
It just seems like a performer's union would be the one that covers that.
But I don't I don't have no knowledge of this.
Well, it's interesting you bring that up because we're going to circle back around to unions
when it comes to today's topic.
What? Something I learned about this.
Wow. Total left turns coming. OK, interesting.
Huh, huh.
Mike, are you at this point just worried about the safety and well-being of the
many who has the hots for you at Disney World?
No, no.
There's a little crack in that.
No, it's fine. Everything's fine.
I said Daisy. I said Daisy, not Minnie.
I didn't say Minnie.
You thought you'd throw us off the scent.
I said another female character.
I didn't say Minnie.
Because if conditions are poor enough that she can't make kissy sounds from inside the head.
Right.
It's going to be fun. They're going to have elections within 18 months.
But can a truck driver still make a kissy face at me through the windshield of a car of his truck
while I'm driving alongside him?
Which would be a great joke in a National Lampoon's vacation type scenario.
Oh my gosh. Yeah, because Clark wants the sexy girl, but it's a gruff truck driver.
Or he was fantasizing about her, but then he's drifting and going mad and it's actually a
big gross dude.
Right. If I didn't know what scene is in the newest vacation movie, the horrible scene that
is the play on the old original one, I wouldn't think that was in the newest at Helms movie.
Are you talking about the one where she dies?
Yes, where they kill.
Yeah.
Kill what's her name?
Christie Brinkley.
Right. The killer in the new vacation.
Yeah.
It's the truck Moser down.
Yeah. He's like flirting with whoever. I mean, I think it's an equivalent.
Is it actually Christie Brinkley or is it a newer female character?
Oh, because it's, yeah, it's not.
Yeah. Because it's at Helms and he's like, you know, remember the original vacation?
Yeah.
Clark is flirting with Christie Brinkley on the highway.
She keeps showing up on the highway.
Yeah. Well, in the newest vacation at Helms is flirting with a young lady on the freeway
and then she just gets killed by a truck or something.
She just gets run over.
Yeah.
That's bleak.
Yeah, that's incredibly bleak.
That's the movie.
Anyway, your dad's vacation.
This is yeah.
Yeah.
So anyway, we're slaughtering your expectations.
On the pavement of what you think that vacation is going to be.
Yeah.
Is you thinking it's going to be funny?
What bridges are we burning talking about?
I'm thinking going through it in my head right now.
Yeah, we're doing the check.
I don't know.
It's deep in a podcast that's half about union relations.
Oh my gosh.
The union talk scared everyone away if the sword and the stone title didn't already.
So we're good.
People love my historical context and I've got even more of it.
This is interesting.
I don't know what could possibly be coming in this area.
Oh, sure.
Well, we can start diving in, I suppose, to the sword and the stone.
Well, it isn't a live show so much at all of the parks now.
I guess the main way the sword and the stone functions today is as a photo opportunity
and the bulk of the Magic Kingdoms and almost all of them except for Shanghai.
I think it is in Shanghai, isn't it?
Is it?
Maybe it is.
I think it's Hong Kong, right?
It's in Hong Kong.
But is that the one that's still on the show?
It is in Hong Kong.
That I know.
So it's still the show.
Well, then it brings down to which are still Merlin hosted.
Paris still has Merlin.
Okay.
I saw one in Hong Kong and Merlin was speaking.
I don't have an ear for it.
I wasn't sure if it was Cantonese or Mandarin.
Yeah, not sure what the go-to is at Hong Kong.
Yeah, we don't know much about Hong Kong, Disneyland.
Yeah, it seems like the official languages of Hong Kong,
from what I could tell, are written Chinese and spoken English.
It's cosmopolitan city.
Lots of language spoken.
Sure.
So there's not a show right now in Disneyland.
Yeah, it doesn't seem like it.
And I haven't seen this in a very long time.
2006 was the last time, I believe.
Something like that.
Oh, yeah.
They did it.
I found a 2012 posting by the Walt Disney Family Museum,
which was screening Sword in the Stone for an anniversary,
saying you could still get your picture with the Sword in the Stone at Disneyland,
but the show is not running right now.
Yes.
Okay.
So yeah, the main way day to day that it functions is that there is an anvil
with a sword sticking out of it, and you can try with all your might to pull the thing out,
but it will not budge.
And that is because the only way it will move is via magic.
Only the chosen few, as in the film, can pull the sword out of said stone.
And the only way that this is ever done day to day in the parks is via this show
that usually involves Merlin, but not always,
where Merlin is trying to find a placeholder king while King Arthur is away on vacation.
Is that what it is?
Yeah, because it's temporary.
It's the temporary king of the realm.
It's temporary.
They make it very clear to the children.
You are not the king here forever.
It's for like an hour tops.
You are not.
Pendragon put this sword in the anvil.
Disney Legal is very clear that they can't promise guests things even on rides.
Mara, there's like a, I think Tony Bexler talked about it,
because they have to make Mara so big and they say,
you know, you'll have eternal youth if you don't look into Mara's eyes.
So she's so big, everyone obviously looks,
unless you actually coordinated it with one person.
You might have a legal complaint.
We failed to do.
Right.
If everyone closed their eyes on Indiana Jones,
maybe there's a legal complaint to lodge, which of course would be insane,
but funny.
I mean, maybe we should try to do that and see where it would go.
Yeah.
So even all their offering is a very temporary kingship even,
but then at the end, the determination is of the show is that it took so long to find the king
that you don't even get that.
You aren't even, do you guys know this?
I read a transcript of the show.
Maybe I don't.
The justification that you get a crown and it is quickly taken away.
Yes.
Yeah.
And you don't actually get to be, you don't even get to be temporary king of Disneyland
or Disney World because there was so much business trying other people,
pulling the sword out of the stone.
Right.
So even like, oh, the time, like his alarm goes off.
I think a literal alarm sound is made even though it's a,
why can't I think of the word with the dust and the measures, the time.
Oh, what's the word?
A sundial?
No, no, the hourglass.
Yes.
God, I could not come up with the word hourglass.
I don't use them very often.
Sure.
It's not how I tell time, first of all, and I don't play a lot of games.
So yes, every board game used to include an hourglass.
Yeah.
You have a lot of hourglasses around.
Tiny plastic hourglasses.
And then if one broke, you used to have to dig out the other,
get the hourglass from the other board.
Now there's a board game I don't think I've talked about on the show or maybe briefly
because it's hard to avoid talking about it.
I had a game that was Planet Hollywood, the game.
Oh, I had that.
You had that too?
Yes.
It was the PII.
It was actually the globe itself with cards inside.
The famous globe from the logo, including the extruding one star.
And you set a little timer and then a little like very generic melody plays,
but good for them for writing original music for this game.
And then it dings.
Do one of you still have a copy of this?
I do.
I got it.
And Schomburg I may have it.
Or my Disney afternoon Avenue shit came from.
I'm just saying there's a lot of podcasts where people play games like D&D.
We could call a Cthulhu or something like that.
We could play around.
Well, and I think Hollywood recorded.
Absolutely.
Well, and there was a Disneyland board game as well, I believe.
Oh, yeah, that's like that was a lot of versions of that.
I feel like, yeah, there must be a lot of classic.
Yeah, right.
We are finding so many bits of bullshit that we can do.
The Planet Hollywood game is just like name Renee Russo movies.
Yeah.
And then you name as many as you can.
I love it.
Sure.
Yeah, I think we have that.
But unless we got rid of I don't know.
It's in Schomburg if it still exists for me, because then obviously we could like
if we had two versions of we could have like multiple games going at once,
cutting back forth.
It'd be a real elaborate.
Oh, that would be easy to follow up.
Like the back of a comic book store when they're like tabletop gaming
and there's so many games going on.
Or we host podcast game nights and people come play against us, the masters.
Mm hmm.
The experts know you're Renee Russo.
Yeah, we are three Renee Russo experts.
You better know your shit.
So are we allowed to say like Nightcrawler?
Yeah, because that wouldn't have been canon.
That would have been a movie.
I think we can play it from a little trouble will mainly be that the stars of today,
like Ansel Al Gore will not have be represented.
The stars that we know so much about today are not represented as cards.
So we and so like we couldn't do name Jeremy Renner endeavors and then
app Amazon storefront album music videos in car commercials.
But and also like there'll be questions like if you met Harvey Weinstein,
how many hugs would you give him to thank him for all the movies he's made over the years?
And you'd be like, well, three.
And obviously we don't want to talk about that.
Name all of your friends who you would love to see sit on John Lasseter's lap.
Oh, hey, this was a very this was a touchy huggy game.
These questions should have been canceled back then.
Yeah.
Well, we can't go backwards.
There have to be cancelable questions.
Yeah.
So once we go through, I'll go through first.
I'll pluck out all of the cancel questions.
It would also be funny to discover them while playing.
Yeah.
So either way.
Oh, certainly.
Original California Adventure had a casting couch joke on one of the windows.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Someone designed someone wrote designed.
It was approved.
It was painted on.
And that eventually pretty quickly someone was like, get that the hell out of here.
I think there was a disconnect between what the casting couch was and what people thought.
I think it's still not OK that people thought like,
and then you got to give a couple of smooches.
But I do think people didn't.
Was it like it's the word sounds fun.
It's even alliterative.
Oh, yeah.
I think by the 90s had like any representation of Hollywood just felt like schmoozy.
Go to Beverly Hills, baby.
You know, so do we need to cancel the word schmooze?
Yeah.
Schmoozing does potentially involve not so good things.
Well, let's just clarify what schmooze means.
Schmooze will now be called networking.
The the smoothie stand we love so much.
Wait, that's what it is.
Yeah.
It's smoothies.
They serve smoothies there.
So it's called schmooze.
Not schmooze.
No schmooze.
TH schmooze schmooze.
It's donuts and smoothies and you can get the big Donald Duck thick ass donut.
Yeah.
There is that why Donald Duck's thick ass came up before or were we just admiring it in another way?
I can't remember.
It's possible that we were talking about that because Jason and I split a large donut
when we were waiting for Guardians the first time we ever wrote it.
It was like a Hulk donut, right?
Yeah.
Or was it Captain America because it had apple pie filling?
No, I think it was Hulk.
I think it was green.
I'm pretty sure it was Hulk.
But it definitely had apple pie filling.
But I can't remember why I was talking about Donald's rear.
I don't know.
It's occurring to me now that I have some new cats recently and one of them I would have to
qualify as having a thick ass.
And I think it makes me love her more.
I do.
Like in a Donald way, I think it's one of her most adorable facets.
It's endearing.
It's very endearing animal quality.
Like Winnie the Pooh.
It would certainly get stuck in a tree hole.
I don't want to get canceled but throw some pics up on the Twitter.
My cats, the cats.
Yeah.
I don't think I'll be canceled for that but we're talking about it in an endearing term.
It almost feels a little too...
That feels like too abrasive of a term.
I've been calling it a rump.
Well, of course.
I love my cats rump.
That's very wholesome.
Yes.
The reason with the Donald ass is because I think I said the word ass and it was weird
to use it in context with Donald.
We should be using the words rear and bottom, hindquarters.
Any of those are very safe for this very nice podcast.
I don't know if I...
Something about hindquarters feels odd to me because that implies you're going to spend
some time in there.
I don't see it like that.
Quarters is like a place you live.
Okay.
That's my own odd connotations with mass terminology.
My last thought about this is that when I was a child in the Pinocchio song,
and maybe I've mentioned this before, when you would sing the song,
I forget exactly which song it is, but it's just like there's a line in there about his
little wooden seat.
I would lose my mind laughing.
I thought that was the funniest thing.
I still think I think it's funny.
Calling it a seat, little wooden seat.
That feels in our wheelhouse.
As much as we've already used, we've already talked about thick ass before.
I think us started like if we can try to from here on out.
Just call it a seat.
Call it seats.
Seats.
That's pretty funny.
All right, fine.
We'll use seats.
I think you managed to find the tamest word humanly possible.
Well, I love my cat's seat.
My cat's got a great seat.
Also, Pinocchio's seat has come up before because in that crazy song,
today I wept for the Geppetto song in that Christmas special that I'm a big fan of.
He talks about spanking.
He fondly recalls spanking Pinocchio and getting a blister.
And this is a nice memory.
So weirdly, this several Pinocchio's seat comes up in several ways in Disney mythology.
My Pinocchio song theory is that the high D and actor's life for me is what Walt thought of actors.
That they were good for nothing scumbags.
That they get punished for their sinful lives.
Anytime I do something like coming out of an audition, sometimes I get stuck in my head.
Awful audition, I get that song stuck in my head.
A full hour 45 leaving Santa Monica, you have actor's life for me.
Mocking you.
I disagree.
Kurt Russell, Suzanne Plachette, these are actors he had a lot of fondness for.
He couldn't think that the profession was.
I think there was some he liked.
I'll just say.
You're saying there was a handful of elite actors, Annette.
Julie Andrews, Dick Fanda, yeah.
Right, those people he liked, but your average working actor he had nothing but to stay in for.
Perhaps.
Or even if he loved them, he thought they are like.
Layabouts.
And yeah, and then silly creatures in pursuit of something silly.
Reaper heads.
He also took roles away from them by appearing on the show all the time by not hiring a host.
And by voicing Mickey himself, he kind of like took that spot for a decade or so.
Eventually we realized more capable Mickey voices.
That's true, yeah.
Walt's hatred of actors is very evident.
But he does seem supportive, at least in California Adventure's statue form of Mickey's
suitcase in a dream.
Right.
He's alive and like, here we, here you go, bud.
But that was obviously, you know, that statue is not based on
like, it's not from, it's a fantasy, you know, that wasn't really.
It's figurative.
It's a figurative statue, you know.
So like.
So he didn't show up to California with Mickey Mao with a fully rent out of a real life character.
Yeah, that wasn't actually what happened.
So I'm just saying it's possible he wouldn't have supported Mickey's suitcase in a dream.
They need a new mattress on that sleeper car, my fucking neck.
That is the narrative in suitcase.
Doesn't count as a meal.
I want money back.
Do you think they could, do you think Walt could have gotten a child seat
for him being that he's small?
For Mickey?
Or did he have to keep him on his lap?
Like you have to like, like parents of newborns to not pay for that extra seat.
I don't know.
It's a good question.
He was like, Mickey, Mickey, you'll be saying that you're under two.
Save us the feet.
It's my Walt, which is the same as my Obama.
Same as your Obama, right?
It's very Cronkite.
This is what I.
Yes, that's how old men talked in the old days.
Very clipped.
Stop.
And this is what we're going to do.
That sort of.
Or I mean, if it's Tom Hanks' version, of course, it's, well, Mickey,
we're going to say you're two years old.
Which is sort of his Mr. Rogers as well.
I think he looks great as Mr. Rogers, but the voice is a lot huskier.
Yeah.
But Mr. Rogers is a tough voice to do.
Tough voice to do.
So high and.
It's hard to not make it completely unnerving.
Yes.
Does it sound like a serial killer or that you're making fun of them?
Right.
Yeah.
I'm Mr. Rogers.
It's not.
Hello there.
You can't just go like.
George H.W. Bush, I guess, as well.
Like Kookie.
Merlin, the wizard of lore.
Are you trying to bring this back?
I am bringing it back around.
Jason, this is the lightest topic we've ever done.
I know.
I love it.
We have to have.
I've got a lot.
Well, yeah, we were texting on the way.
You've been convinced the whole time of the fullness of the top,
of the robustness of the topic.
I haven't been convinced on the fullness of the topic.
I just knew that I could just do a voice for a while.
And then we like that would kill enough time for the podcast to be over.
Anyway, back to.
So this podcast killing time.
I think it's all valuable, crucial information.
I guess that's one way to look at it.
Sword in the Stone, of course, based on the myths of King Arthur.
First kind of the myths of legend that were sort of collated by Sir Thomas Mallory and
and later on by T.H. White, who wrote the book, The Sword in the Stone, a shorter novel,
eventually the first part of the larger piece, the once and future king.
Which I learned a little bit about when I was younger because it is all that is the
basis of the musical Camelot, which I was in in high school.
Oh, my God.
Do we have the tape?
What did you do?
OK, so I was very excited because they said they were going to do a dual casting for this one,
which meant there were multiple people playing Arthur, Guinevere and Lancelot.
And there was also and Merlin and there was a kooky knight.
And I forget his name.
I did not get that part.
The part I got is the child who comes on at the end after Camelot has fallen and volunteers like,
Your Highness, my Lord, I'll fight.
I'll bring my bow and arrow, my Lord.
And then Arthur tells him about the glory days of Camelot, because of course, Camelot,
this grand happy place lured it over by Arthur and Guinevere until she leaves him for
the once good night, Lancelot.
And then there is a battle between them.
OK.
And then Camelot falls.
Did you go into any high school audition scenario dreading?
Am I going to be the kid?
No, I was fully prepared.
In fact, in MAME, I wanted to be the kid and did not get it.
I got to like the girlfriend's straight laced father, the fiance's father that
Auntie MAME's nephew is supposed to marry.
I did not do well in high school theater.
It sounds like you were in a lot of.
How many shows were you in?
Four.
We just did one musical a year.
So you were in the musical every year?
Yeah.
That's pretty good.
But like in middle school, I was usually like the bad guy or at least a supporting
lead or something.
Well, it's like it's bumping up to the majors and it gets it's a tougher and tougher slice
every time.
Well, now you're in that now in Hollywood.
Who's the only one who lives in Hollywood now?
Is that true?
Does nobody here?
A couple of people I know have like moved to L.A.
Actually, the older brother of like a childhood friend just sold a screenplay to Netflix.
So he used to win well.
OK.
I'll never be the number one in my class because I was next to me alphabetically was
David Gallagher, who is the who is the middle child, I believe, on the show Seventh Heaven.
Oh, right.
Oh, yeah.
Who was at the time.
So already had achieved more than.
Sure.
A direct to video Richie Rich due to Macaulay Culkin not returning to the franchise.
Well, yes.
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
So are we just judging it on same year or just in like around a class?
Because I just realized there was a guy who was a year older from Schomburg High School
that is like a very successful actor named Mike Rourke, who's in a bunch of things.
OK.
What do we know the time?
I don't know.
You should schmooze with him.
Oh, I know.
You mean that.
I know what you mean by that.
Excuse me.
What kind of schmooze?
I read you loud and clear, pal.
Yeah.
So the myths of legend of King Arthur, Disney never really made like
besides Sword in the Stone never really had like a King Arthur movie.
Yeah, there's no live action.
Well, besides kidding.
Kidding.
King Arthur.
Yeah.
But there's not like a Disney animation canon Arthur besides Wart, the boy who pulls.
Because Arthur doesn't factor into this tale.
Yes.
No, they like they allude to it.
In the movie Sword in the Stone, which it's been a long time since I watched some clips
just to confirm that Merlin did indeed turn himself and Arthur into fish at one point.
That was my most clear memory of it.
And like Wart or Arthur, whatever you want to call him, like casually pulling the sword out of the stone.
OK, yeah.
Yeah, so Arthur isn't a character in it, but Arthur is referred to.
And in this show, in the live show, Arthur is referenced as he's away.
So when you're on vacation, you rubs your duties or sconded with.
Which is probably good because it would be terrible for a small child to be enjoying the day
at Disney World and then be responsible for the fall of like dealing with the ramifications
of the fall out of Camelot falling.
So you view it as you're not becoming like the king of Disneyland.
You have to take care of Camelot.
You're running the same.
You're keeping it within their story.
Yeah, you're like the 10 minutes where they think on VEEP,
where they think Selena Myers has to be president in the first episode or something.
So you're just saying the kid is being set up as like the fall person, the fall guy.
Oh, well, now I'm saying it's good they're not the fall guy.
Right.
But you're saying that.
They could very well be the fall guy.
Right, where they're just they're just installed sort of towards the end.
I see Merlin is is good.
Merlin is pure.
I cannot speak to the other people who do the show, the Royal Majesty makers.
So sometimes it's Merlin.
Sometimes we know sometimes it's these two people.
I don't know where they're coming.
Sorry, there's four of them.
There are two of them, but there's four characters.
I learned about this because I was like, what the hell is this?
And I had to look it up on the Disney World website because on the Disney World website,
it's under the Royal Majesty makers.
It's not under the sword in the stone.
Does that imply that they do this show today at Disney World?
They do the show today.
In fact, it was running yesterday and today.
Oh, OK.
Few times a day.
Meet retired knight Sir Sterling, his clever niece, Bridget,
Squire Tobias and the kind Lady Llewellyn as the official ambassador to Cinderella's court.
They will put your skills to the test and school you in the finer points of regal behavior.
Next, D23.
If you want to win the most obscure costume contest, go with clever niece Bridget.
Clever niece.
Yeah.
Or Tobias.
So four characters will come out and you're saying they did this yesterday.
Two.
I think they alternate the characters.
OK, right.
You said that.
And this is where the unions come up again.
I learned I was told this and I had to look it up because I was surprised to learn this.
These roles are actors equity roles.
OK.
Which is the that is the union you join if you are a Broadway performer.
And this is the union that runs some of the other roles in Florida.
People will be in turtle talk with Crush and get their equity card and then they could go
join a Broadway chorus.
Well, this is some of the issue that we talked about this with Matt Gorley that he was like
when you're back when there's dialogue and you're improvise, if it's this like heightened level of
performing, you get to be you get much better pay seemingly.
Yeah.
And it's seemingly why they have Disney avoids doing too many things like this.
And it's maybe one of the first to go because the staffing is like Star Wars land like Galaxy.
Yeah.
A few of the people are equity because old the tyrant Bob Chapek just said, well,
the people that are at the in working in the stores, they'll be our characters.
They say three confusing phrases that you and that will replace right there being droids.
It's running around.
Yes, because so the droid operators would fall under the purview of the union that puppeteers
are in.
OK, I'm not sure which one that is, but I was shocked to learn.
And so I found a listing for the royal majesty makers.
Like to get the job.
Yeah.
On backstage on like the the.
Have you applied?
No, because it was a listing from like 2013, but they were also applying.
There was listings at that time for turtle talk with crush world showcase players.
So apparently in Florida, I think it is if you are using a microphone,
you are the role as equity because turtle talk with crush doesn't sing.
First, I thought it was saying you were equity, but singing might get you a bump.
OK.
So but still crazy to me because I don't know how much out here is equity.
It seemed like, yeah, Matt Gorley was saying a lot was ag, but the American Guild of Variety
artist.
So yeah.
So all right.
So Merlin's doing OK.
Yeah.
So I would assume Merlin equity, too.
But he's going to retire.
Bridget's doing OK.
My question is, why are there it's in a company that obviously cuts a lot of cost.
They're cutting costs now because Disneyland is empty.
It's empty today.
All the passes are unblocked.
So it never kicked back in Space Mountain 10 minute wait two hours ago.
And we're recording this in the middle of the afternoon.
Did Galaxy's Edge kill Disneyland?
Yeah, I guess it did.
It didn't happen.
I don't know because truly what time is it?
It's like five o'clock right now.
It was three o'clock.
And I look 10 minute wait for Space Mountain in the middle of the day.
Well, it's 93 degrees out.
It's hot out, but it's never stopped people.
Yeah, that was not like it would still like Guardians is 25.
I think cars would probably the longest wait.
I walked on Guardians last week.
I was there.
Yeah, I was there recently and everything was pretty light.
So anyway, so where was I going with this?
It seems odd to me that they wouldn't just keep having Merlin be the character
because it's only one person.
It's just one guy.
And there's two people.
You would think they would all be like, well, we just have Merlin do it,
not have these new characters.
Four of them.
Four of them to rotate.
Just always put the robe on.
Anybody can do it.
Merlin can be either gender.
Who cares?
Let's just do Merlin.
And he's more fun, I'm assuming.
I think he's more fun.
I think the Royal Majesty makers are a little sticky.
I mean, they're pretty tight and they have to do a lot of stuff.
I like Merlin.
I like a kooky old man, even if it's just a big beard and a hat.
I think all three of us probably we enjoy a bearded old man
over most type of characters.
That's definitely true.
Yes.
You're Marvel.
Does Marvel McFay have a beard?
Oh, yeah.
He does, right?
He is like a Dreamfinder kind of guy.
Yeah.
So like that's yeah.
So I'm just wondering what the thinking is.
Maybe kids don't connect with Merlin as much as they used to.
I mean, they've not kept this particular property alive as a vibrant.
Nor is there.
There's not really like a song, you know, from Sword in the Stone.
No.
Maybe the most iconic song free of classic Disney era.
Yeah, I couldn't pull it.
I was reading about Sword in the Stone because that was one of two rabbit holes.
I went down for this Sword in the Stone directed by a man named Wolfgang Reitherman.
He's one of the nine old men.
One of the nine old men.
Yeah.
Also credited as Woolly Reitherman,
credited as director on Jungle Book, Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree,
Aristocats, Robin Hood, co-directed the many adventures of Winnie the Pooh,
the Rescuers and 101 Dalmatians.
Geez, pretty good.
Pretty good.
And like this is also coming like in a period that started in 1950 with Cinderella when
they're like, OK, we're back to feature like that and animated features.
Before that, there was like six like package movies, like weird movies about planes.
Yes.
War Bonds.
War Bonds, Three Caballeros, Ichabod and Mr. Crane.
Mr. Toad.
Or Mr. Toad.
That's like Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde type movie.
Yeah.
Ichabod and Mr. Crane.
Peace Mealing anthology movies because so much of the staff was at the war.
And then it took so long to do animation at that time and new Disney anime feature would
only come out every few years.
Yeah.
The story of a confident rooster who believes that he's crowing can make the sunrise based on an old play.
Chanticleer, if that sounds familiar.
Were you in Chanticleer in high school or middle school?
No, it doesn't sound like a play that people super were into.
Like in the early 1900s, late 1800s, whatever it came out.
Chanticleer, the basis, though, for the movie Rock-A-Doodle.
He's gone at it.
It's exactly what I was looking up.
Yeah, wait, is that why there's that weird rooster thing?
Yeah.
Chanticleer was updated with an Elvis theme for Rock-A-Doodle.
For Rock-A-Doodle.
Chanticleer got so far.
I love Chanticleer.
Is that the name of the chicken?
That's the name of the chicken.
Oh, man.
What a mealy name.
Chanticleer.
Like chant, the word chant and then Echler.
E-C-L-E-R.
I think there is a French basis.
He is apparently, I think it's called a Gallic rooster,
which is one of the unofficial symbols of the nation of France.
So Chanticleer got far enough in the development process
that there's tons of Mark Davis concept art for Chanticleer.
Oh.
And it looks great.
Like look at these cool roosters.
Really?
Mark Davis, who, just a reminder, did a lot of the Haunted Mansion art
and a lot of the great characters in the parks are due to Mark Davis.
Country Bears.
I looked up Chanticleer and I think I spelled it wrong
because I just got a listing for Chanticleer Apartments,
one star, Garden Grove, California.
So that's not this.
Is the landlord this?
There wasn't going to be a movie based on that.
The landlord is a fancy chicken.
No, that's Chanticleer, I believe.
Is that him with the top hat?
Yeah.
Wow.
Because he really thinks very highly of himself.
Holy shit.
Jason, what you're showing us is extremely America Sings slash splash mountain.
Well, Scott, I'm glad you said that because this concept art of lady chickens
looks exactly like.
Like Southern Belle chickens?
Like America Sings chickens.
Exactly.
They belong on that boat in Splash Mountain.
Nothing ever really goes away at Disney, which also,
and this is a little bit of a leap, another piece of concept art for Chanticleer,
a dog with a key next to a jail cell.
Whoa.
Is a cop dog, but still like Pirates of the Caribbean.
And the dog himself also looks extremely like I feel like somebody looks like that in Splash
Mountain.
Yeah.
And furthermore, this owl character is exactly the way Archimedes Merlin's owl in Sword in
the Stone looks.
He stole that for the owl in the Sword in the Stone.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess he can.
He used it.
If it wasn't.
This is a secret Chanticleer episode.
What has happened now is the audience has stumbled into what they thought was Sword
in the Stone.
They thought it was about unions, but really, this is just about Chanticleer from here on
out.
I mean, I think Chanticleer rules.
There's even more concept.
All this concept art is amazing.
He's my new favorite character.
People could not get over, though, that like people aren't going to want to see a chicken
movie.
Of course they are.
And yeah, then Ratatouille down the road.
Now, and Don Bluth was like in the 50s, was around Disney Studios for some of his early
gigs.
So they didn't.
And the Chanticleer movie shares like one or two concepts, I think, with the Disney
Chanticleer development stuff.
I think the bad guy is a fox.
The love interest is a pheasant, but there's not a ton of crossover.
OK, there's fencing chickens here.
The fencing looks great.
I mean, it's Mark Davis stuff.
It's great.
I'm sure it's in that book.
The new like $80 Mark Davis Puffy Table Book.
Oh, right, right.
Or a two book set, I think just came out.
But yeah, is Chanticleer, is that a public domain play?
Can we put that up somewhere with you as Chanticleer?
I mean, I would love that.
Everyone in the play, similar ish to Animal Farm, every character is an animal.
The costumes for this play are like animal suits.
Can we use the Rock-A-Doodle songs?
Can we combine it all?
It's Mark Davis style design, but the songs from the iconic songs.
People screaming Rock-A-Doodle.
I have the play right here.
I have pulled it up.
I think by the time Rock-A-Doodle got made, it certainly would have been in the public domain.
Rock-A-Doodle also at the time competing with Beauty and the Beast and Five will Go West.
Don Bluth involved with American Tale, not really involved with Five will Go West.
Do you know who plays Chanticleer in the, they started spelling it with double E's
by the time the Rock-A-Doodle came around.
Disney was going to call it that too.
Do you know who plays the Chanticleer in Rock-A-Doodle?
I think I do.
What do you know?
Is it Glen Campbell?
Yeah.
Wow.
Isn't that wild?
Weird.
Yeah.
In 1990, we're like opposite Beauty and the Beast.
Essentially, there's a animated film starring Glen Campbell.
Yeah.
Very strange.
So we could have never had Rock-A-Doodle, which I had a VHS of Rock-A-Doodle growing up.
I watched Rock-A-Doodle a lot.
We can't stop singing the name.
Rock-A-Doodle?
Yeah.
And remember this is pre-Rock-A-Doodle time.
But now that we're post-Rock-A-Doodle, we have to remember that Rock-A-Doodle wouldn't happen.
It's really fun to say.
Yeah.
I've never seen it.
I've never seen it either.
Oh.
It can be pretty fun.
If you told me this was a Chanticleer episode, I would have watched Rock-A-Doodle.
Rock-A-Doodle has better songs than...
I remember the songs from Rock-A-Doodle.
I do not remember the Sword and the Stone songs.
I guess it has songs.
It has some music.
Maybe it doesn't have like song songs.
It doesn't have big numbers.
What is your favorite Rock-A-Doodle song?
Rock-A-Doodle.
Sundooshine from Dumb.
Sundooshine?
Yeah.
You said that like, oh yeah, Sundooshine.
That's my favorite.
Yeah.
My daddy taught me how to sing.
I remember that lyric.
Kiss and Coo is a song.
Yeah.
I remember watching Rock-A-Doodle a lot and that was just one where I was like,
this might be one for me and my brother.
I don't think anyone at school will want to talk about Rock-A-Doodle.
But I want to podcast one day.
Hey, let me call you out on something.
I feel like you've said you don't like doo-wop music and this is very Elvis doo-woppy old rock and roll.
Yeah, but a chicken is singing it.
That forgives.
Right.
I'm just saying I think there's an inconsistency there.
It's more like doo-squawk music.
Squawk.
All right.
Well, we'll do a full rock and roll.
Yeah, that's better.
That's better.
Thank you.
Jason's favorite genre of music is squawk and roll.
Wow.
Oh, what a discovery.
Well, yeah, Rock-A-Doodle will have to get on the queue soon enough.
Could you imagine if like talking about Disney animated classics, like, well, yeah,
the animation started to get scratchier and people who grew up at Disney animated movies
started making stuff.
You know, there was a 101 Dalmatians and Jungle Book.
And Chantecler and...
I mean, once Poco Loco got into the mix, the line up, like every Disney theme park,
five hour line to meet Poco Loco.
Different worlds.
What could have been?
No sword in the stone.
And the like incredible sums of money that could have gone to the estate of Edmund Rostlund.
Yeah.
It's best they don't think about it.
And if you're a Rostlund heir or heiress listening to this, my apologies.
You only you do have Rock-A-Doodle money.
No Disney, the feral cats of Disneyland don't exist.
There's just feral roosters everywhere.
If you're there at Rope Drop, it's just a nightmare.
It's an auto audio nightmare.
It's just screaming roosters in every land.
Walt's idea to promote it at the end of the 60s.
What if we release a thousand roosters into the park?
And of course, there would be a Disney plus Chantelier announced already.
A movie coming soon.
CGI, mix of live action and CGI.
Yep.
They can still do it.
That's true.
That's in the archives somewhere.
The Jacob Tremblay.
A Chanticleer?
Yeah.
I think you need like the guy from Magic Dragons or someone.
You need like...
Leto.
Oh man, Leto?
Leto is good.
Chanticleer.
I'm not sure who would own Rock-A-Doodle now.
Who put it out?
Was it Bob?
Samuel Goldwyn distributed it.
Oh, so it wasn't like any studio?
It wasn't partnered with the studio or anything?
That's so weird.
I'm not quite sure.
It was a weird time.
We look into it and realize like, wait, you know who owns Samuel Goldwyn?
I do.
I didn't even realize.
My parents didn't even think to tell me.
My last name is hyphenated?
Gardener slash Goldwyn?
It's never looked.
It was Samuel Goldwyn company.
Who owns that now?
Geez.
You see it every now and then, but it's sort of like every now and then.
They merged with United Artists.
Yeah.
Who owns United Artists?
United Artists shows up every now and then.
Columbia TriStar, I feel like is used now.
It doesn't.
You're just buying.
Why is there no theme park where I can meet the TriStar lady?
Give her a hug.
Even just an Instagram pop-up.
We need to find a lawyer and do an episode with a lawyer and we need to lay out our plan for
acquiring all of these different IP that have been my enjoyment for so long.
Yeah, because that's where the real money.
Just go down the list of things and lay it out with them.
They'll tell us how realistic it is, how much money we're looking at.
Marvel McFay portal, little Abner portal, Rockadoodle portal.
We are going to end up owning so many unpleasant IPs.
Yes.
If I could just own one of Heathcliff's Cadillac cats, Hector, please.
Just Hector.
But then he's got to get removed, a la Spider-Man from MCU.
Yeah, so when the Heathcliff reboot comes, he'll...
Are you saying in like old cartoons they'll have to remove Hector?
You don't have to replace him with a different cat.
Remove Hector, yeah.
Oh, that's fine.
Put a mustache on him.
Just put a mustache on him and color him differently and call him something else.
That's a lot of work for that reissue.
You earned it.
I earned it because that lawyer will do it.
People are sleeping on Hector ownership.
Yeah.
Well, okay.
Sword in the Stone.
Back to the Sword in the Stone.
Hey, hey, hey.
I like, you know what?
Good rabbit holes.
Yeah, thank you.
Yeah, I got so excited.
I mean, that Mark Davis art is great.
It's always so fun to uncover his stuff.
Did you see where for the Sword in the Stone experience where you actually hit the switch
that actually makes the sword available?
Do you know where that is?
Is a picture.
I found a picture.
I mean, this is according to some website.
I heard the technicians wander around sometimes and like we'll release it
throughout the day if people are trying it.
It's right by Pinocchio's Daring Journey, supposedly.
Supposedly there's a switch just in the bushes.
What?
So like you can go over there.
We're probably giving information out.
People are going to try to do it.
So I'm going to let me see what it says here.
Hit the button.
In the bushes by Pinocchio's Daring Journey, you'll spot the switch.
A custodial cast member accomplice.
They use that word.
It uses to activate the sword's release at the proper time in Merlin's show.
So it's somewhere on the left of Pinocchio's Daring Journey.
It's got to be like key operated though.
You can't just like hit a button.
I would think we're a fob.
Yeah.
Security fob.
Presumably digitized it.
Yeah.
I, you know, the, the, I had to give the Royal Majesty makers credit.
They do like a lot of interaction.
They do a lot of improv with the audience and the family and stuff.
But I do like Merlin, like when Merlin is doing it, he clearly always picks a dad first.
It's always a dad.
Big brawny guy.
You don't know the shtick of the show that they'll be.
Yeah, they pick a strong guy to try to pull the sword out of the stone.
And he fails, but they end up telling, you know, maybe you could be a bodyguard.
You could be like the guy who protects the king.
But I think the king is somebody else.
It is in the long history.
It is trying to embarrass your dad.
That is what another entry.
It's a hit.
And you can add it one time.
You could see it in French, Chinese, English, around the world.
Dads of all countries were being embarrassed regularly daily.
Daily.
By Merlin or these merry makers.
And then Merlin pulls out a stick, a Y-shaped stick, which I learned.
I always wonder what that's called.
A drowsing rod or a divining rod.
Will you look for water with a stick on the beach?
It's a pseudo science that these people used it to look for water, for ore, for minerals.
That feels like a thing you would have used as a child.
To try to find.
Your first toy was a divining rod.
Yeah, to find treasure on the beach.
I'll say this.
It eased it a lot.
It was a lot of 90s kids cartoons.
Yeah.
Like divining rod.
Like, yeah.
And I was looking for treasure on the beach.
Yeah.
I mean, I always was jealous of the metal detector guys.
I feel like I never see metal detector guys in the beach.
Only in movies.
They're like.
I saw all the time growing up, but now I really see.
Because I never saw.
In the Jersey Shore, I'd see them all the time.
Really?
Yeah.
Metal detector guys.
Metal detectors cost a fortune.
And what were they looking for in the Jersey Shore beach?
Money.
Hoffa.
Treasure.
Shimming off his metallic corpse.
Sea glass.
I don't think shells would come up.
So like they were just looking for change.
Yeah.
But a metal detector and a scooper.
Because you have to have a sifter, scooper sort of thing.
Or else you're bending down all the time.
Every now and then.
It's not a good plan to riches.
Pieces of ships or I think people thought they'd find the balloons or something.
If you were a metal detector guy or kid growing up, tweet at us.
Let us know please.
If you have a plan.
What was the plan?
And what was your greatest bounty that you found?
Which, yeah, somebody might really surprise us too.
We'll be eating crow soon enough.
Yeah, because it wasn't like a gold detector.
I found a Rolls Royce.
It fell off of a ship.
Quickly barely any water damage.
That was something I saw as a kid.
Someone finds a car.
They dig up a car.
Nothing found with a metal detector.
That'd be the dream.
I think I used a divining rod though as a kid.
I do think I pretended that that worked.
But Merlin had good pantomime skills with the divining rod.
Because he really makes it look like it's leaning him.
As opposed to the other way around.
The Merlin performers were pretty great.
I think they had to cut muster.
I ended up on a website, a blog, Confessions of a Walt Disney World Merlin.
Where he details the audition process and the training.
And that you couldn't really go do it in the park.
They'd first train you for a while in a taped off area
like you would in an audition setting.
Like here's the exact dimensions of everything.
And so you just pantomime it for a while backstage.
And then you'd have to go like, all right, let's go run it from 2 a.m. to 8 a.m.
Like when the when the parks closed.
And then you'd be then you'd be given your officially awarded your hat
and your divining rod and get to be a practicing Merlin.
Why was that called Confessions of a Merlin?
Was there anything like tawdry?
Was there anything?
Not at all.
Other than that, other than the like potentially not the best treatment of the doves that.
I just learned that Merlin would release.
I just learned that anytime you ever release doves, they're going to die quickly
because they're being put into captivity and they don't like they've been trained.
So anytime doves are released in like a ceremony or something.
Oh, you're throwing them into the wild.
Yeah.
Well, here he dictates to that.
And let me read a little passage from an excellent article, by the way.
Confessions of Walt Disney World Merlin.
Just opening the hands might result in the bird just sitting there in the palm
or casually dropping to the ground to search for French fries.
So there had to be an upward thrust to let the bird know how to fly.
You can't just say, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, you have to throw the bird.
Once the bird is thrown in the earliest days of the show,
clever hawks circles near the castle,
realizing that every hour Merlin would be releasing a free lunch.
Hadn't thought of that.
That's a good.
That's a good thought.
It was unclear how that situation was eventually resolved, he says.
I wonder it wasn't.
That's my head, it's realizing.
But every bird I released says this Merlin flew safely back to their cage
for a reward behind the Magic Kingdom.
But how can that be?
I don't know.
Is he trying to absolve them sad?
Does he know that every dove survived?
Yeah, I don't think.
The confessions you would think you would be like, yeah.
And then they all they all died every time.
An actor's life for me.
You have to tell yourself stories so you can sleep at night, you know?
Great absolves.
That's how he washed his hands after writing this article,
forgetting about all of the children whose arms broke as they lifted the heavy.
They didn't release the button on time.
Then the kids are like, just snap their shoulders clean off.
Well, I saw a kid, I watched a video of a kid doing it
and he pulled from the handles and it started to come up
and then he just grabs the blade.
And I was like, oh,
King Colin is intense and he's very trusting that it doesn't.
Very nice.
Holmes did it.
What did he get it?
Yeah, he got it.
OK, got it.
It was already pretty much up.
It doesn't come all the way out.
I feel like as a kid, because you don't want a kid just waving a prop sword around.
Of course not.
But that is does feel unsatisfying.
Today in Galaxy's Edge, this is possible around every corner.
Yes, that's very true.
Or I was got nailed by a kid who had the lightsaber like quiver.
But he had it sideways, like around it, like he was going down a pathway
with this like lightsaber thing falling off his shoulder and I wasn't nailing people.
That's funny that you were hit by a kid with a lightsaber
because I've been hit by several adults with lightsabers.
Yes, I would believe that too.
Yeah, with those black like cases for the blades.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Not like they were swinging it at me.
Not quite the dignified weapon that Obi-Wan.
And we described it as.
Watch it, grown lightsaber owners.
The other, you wouldn't call this a confession, but I like the detail that Merlin had to
greet kids, take photos, sign autographs after the show was done.
And a lot of kids, this being the early mid-90s, speaking of unpleasant IP,
a lot of kids thought that he was the page master.
Oh.
The Macaulay Culkin movie one, right?
Reference to Macaulay Culkin's lesser films.
I've never seen that page master.
Not to mention that what you were saying about the humor of the show,
really a lot of it is a kid's chance to, for getting even with dad.
I'm trying to get every Macaulay Culkin title into this episode.
I had like page master toys and I definitely remember seeing a lot of ads for it and did not push.
What was the premise of it again?
He goes into a bunch of a live books or something.
Yeah.
Does he go into the books?
This is only for us to know.
I know Andrew Grissom likes the page mass.
This is the Moog rules.
Grissom a movie.
Anyway, side note.
He doesn't listen to the podcast though.
He does.
So I'm a little bit.
I feel like the page master was trying to like, oh, people liked princess bride.
Right.
Similar like kid gets a book read.
I've never seen the princess.
I haven't either.
Oh my God.
Oh yeah.
I wasn't going to say anything, but since you went first.
I'll say it.
I'll say I'm not.
I also don't like Goonies at all.
Well, I've never, I don't think I've seen all Goonies either.
People are going to be really mad now.
I think there's enough anti-Goonie out there.
I remember playing a Nintendo video game that I never got past like level two of Goonies on.
There was a game of it?
There was a game.
You kept yo-yoing bad guys.
I don't know.
No offense if anyone likes Goonies.
I just found it sort of abrasive and unpleasant.
That's just me.
I don't know.
I like princess pride, but I am not like obsessed with it.
Like people are.
Yeah.
There was.
You got your wall of Sean and you're under the giant.
I mean, for sure.
What else could you want in a movie?
But I think I get suspicious of very like movies that are like should like shown at
midnight with like revival Hollywood forever ways all the time.
Maybe I do.
I have a bias or sorry.
I just like don't take the time to check them out.
If I didn't grow up with it, I'm sure that one's probably great at being Rob Reiner.
And yeah, it is.
It is good.
Yeah, it is good.
I don't want to even downplay that too much.
Yeah, I was looking at page.
I got bored looking at the page master wiki.
It's so exciting.
There's like a kid with like he's like he doesn't want to learn.
And I think then he goes and meets the page master and he likes to learn after that.
I feel like there was a big trend in 90s entertainment of like we got to get the
kids off the TV and the video games and teach them about books.
And I can only imagine that's even harder nowadays.
Yeah, probably.
I just saw I mean, Christopher Lloyd was the page master, though.
So now it's got that tension a little bit.
I loved Camp Nowhere.
He was the adult.
All the polls.
He was the adult in Camp Nowhere.
Well, I didn't even reference the future.
UPN's Deadly Games.
Sebastian Jackal.
That's my favorite Lloyd performance.
That's your Lloyd.
Christopher Lloyd's like on Instagram now and I follow him and he just goes to all the cons.
And I don't I don't believe he's actually posting because he'll just like post like
back to the future memes.
Yeah, and that might be corporatized.
Yeah.
But anyway, good to see him.
Good to see him out there.
He's live action in Page Master too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He's to the dual role.
Yeah, I see.
I see.
Okay.
And Phil Hartman is a slender and violent pirate.
Slender and violent.
Interesting.
Patrick Stewart in there too.
Great people.
Yeah.
All right.
We're going to do a double feature of Page Master and Rock-A-Doodle.
We might be in our words.
Love both of these films.
What else about Stewart and the Sto- Oh, did you see characters?
There's videos of Pinocchio tries to pull the sword.
Peter Pan.
Flynn Rider.
Flynn Rider?
Flynn Rider from Tangled.
I was going to say like from Tron.
That's a different Flynn.
Oh my God, if Flynn from Tron was in a fantasy land.
And then his lasers.
Wow.
Oh yeah.
That would be awesome.
And then apparently every YouTuber, a lot of YouTubers, a lot of videos of like,
I tried to pull the sword and I didn't.
Like backpack people?
Uh.
Like backpack.
Like, hey, what's up guys?
People.
Okay.
Just in general.
There's a lot of the-
Which why not do it?
I assume you haven't pulled the sword out of the stone, but if you have photos, I would imagine.
I have photos.
I think I have adult photos with it.
I do think it's fun.
I'm sad they don't do it at Disneyland.
I think it's a little bit of like-
I really liked the show.
I think it's charming.
If you're a kid who likes magic and stuff, it's like, it's not a full on magic show,
but you get the fun.
He like, he has his bag and then he turns it upside down and shows you there's nothing in the bag,
but then he's magically able to pull stuff out of it.
Larry Poppins style.
Yeah.
I saw one where like the kid gets a proclamation, rolled up proclamation and the medal,
like a medallion, and then the video cuts out and then they're eating in a restaurant
in Alice from Alice in Wonderland.
It's like, you were the ruler for it.
She got so excited to see he had pulled the sword from the stone.
Oh.
I think that's very charming.
They would do that.
They'd keep it up a little bit.
Play along.
A reputation.
The thing that doesn't seem to happen in Star Wars.
Right.
Yeah.
That's what they've claimed.
No, it is.
It does feel like I guess they stopped doing it a while ago, but it is the type of thing that
goes away, especially during budget cuts.
And like it is the stuff that really like makes the park feel extra good.
Like they're getting rid of this Pixar.
What's the, what's the band?
The Philharmonic.
The Pixar thing.
Or some.
Yeah.
It's some fun name.
The Pixarmonic.
Pixarmonic.
That's a fun little thing over on Pixar Pier when these, the musicians play those songs and
that sucks.
That's going away.
What else?
They're cutting the.
Oh, the Hoopty Doo show.
Right.
Which you just saw.
Which I just saw.
I didn't realize they were running something at the time.
And like, yeah, walked right in.
It was mostly people, tired people eating chicken fingers.
And I was like the only one sitting like in the balcony.
Like great view of the stage.
Good job, guys.
Good job.
Slew foot Sue.
Yeah.
These little like, I mean, it's actually tying it into current events.
If there is this feeling that why aren't the little like fun street shows happening on Batuu
that you might have expected.
I, yeah, I agree.
These things are not, and they are little, they aren't like necessary and the park survives
without them, but it is, it's great color indeed to end the idea that there's magic
around any corner.
And this being an especially magical little show.
Yeah.
Like running into shows is fun.
Like running, like turning a corner and going, oh, what the heck?
Oh, that's cool.
Oh yeah.
Well, and then, you know, like push the trash can or something.
Or like the percussion guys who you think they're janitors and then they start playing
those things where you don't even realize a show is occurring and you're swept up into it.
And I have to say, I don't think like a lot, I don't think Universal has something like,
there's no, like I wish there was a thing in Universal where you could fake throw chum
into water and summon jaws.
Then they end, they give you a short sleeve turtleneck and a pack of smokes.
And you're a chief Brody now.
That would have been what I liked as a kid.
You pull jaws magic tooth.
Yeah.
One of the teeth is magic and one of the teeth is magic and they release whatever tooth the kid picks.
Congratulations.
You have to temporarily deal with the mayor.
You're the deputy mayor of Amity Island.
Are open, but should they be?
But you decide, you decide wrong.
People will die.
Discuss next year's lifeguard budget.
It's July 4th.
We can't close.
That's most of the summer right there.
You might be wanting to protect people, but you'll do, the mayor is going to tell you why
you're wrong.
He's look, he's been in there for a while and he knows what he's doing.
So, you know, sit with him, but maybe just agree with him.
Just do what he says.
Just don't.
Yeah.
You can't fight city hall.
Thinks they know how to govern Amity until they're put in the chair.
Yeah.
You'd be good at writing like the campaign for this is the reason to keep this mayor.
I forget his name, but the existing mayor of, of Amity.
These are all good.
Larry the one was the actor.
Okay.
Yeah.
These are all good campaign.
This is very like, don't change horses midstream.
Oh yeah.
Just come on.
Yeah.
He knows he is still the mayor in jaws too.
I saw someone point out a while back.
He's still the mayor.
Is he, is a hologram of him, the mayor in jaws 12 and the future too,
whatever number it is, I've really got it wrong.
Yeah.
It's all the same.
Hollow Brody.
I never thought about how I'd like to see all of jaws.
Whatever just nine.
What is it?
That would be the, that would be the area where like how we're getting like IP overload.
That would be the area where you would then get like way on board.
I feel like Scott.
Yes.
That's one that I would bid on is can I do all of hologram jaws?
The hologram jaws from back to the future too, we're going to make that.
And it's going to look like that.
He's going to be all digitized and picked like he's going to,
it's going to be like TV static when he rises out of the water.
Yes.
Like that's, that's where the, uh, uh, choking on IP will get you.
You can get that micro targeted.
Oh, hell yeah.
I would love some micro targeting of just a line of menswear, uh,
based on Richard Dreyfus's character, which is most of the clothes I owned for colder,
uh, fall weather look like, uh, no, he's got like the gray varsity shirt and like beat up jeans and
a blue beanie.
Oh God.
Do you have a blue beanie?
You got to get a blue beanie.
I think I do.
You do.
Well, you gave me one.
Did I?
That's kind of like you ordered you like once you were like, do you want this winter cap?
Do you want this beat?
Like I, I, that's not as much of a beanie.
That's a more winter hat.
I see right through this.
You buy Jason dress up clothes, just like Duffy summer Jason.
I did get that backpack at an army surplus store.
They did have beanies at the counter, but I was like, oh, two warm outs.
I think a little bit more like smaller.
That's my feeling.
I like a beanie, but yeah, it's a winter hat.
Yeah.
Amazon sent me two of them.
So I gave him a gray, the gray winter hat, but it's not so much.
It's not a full on Richard Dreyfus costume.
You don't think it qualifies?
No, I don't think so.
But yeah, I think we, I think we can put on the Twitter side by side comparison of
Dreyfus and jaws and your look like to see if we can get it pretty close.
I have it pretty close.
It's a pretty easy menswear like beat up jeans, varsity gray.
Sweatshirt scruffy facial hair trainer, like canvas sneakers.
By the way, I've just been lost in the jaws.
3D.
Yeah, I'm thinking about it already.
It's jaws.
Jaws 19 is the, is the movie I was, I was coming up short, but it's yeah.
Jaws 19 and the only, my take when I go in and pitch the take, it is just,
it's just Jaws, but you just put the hollow before everything.
We have to get on the hollow orca, the whole orca.
We got to, we got to drop.
Holla chum.
That's all I got.
What could you, how fast can you get a meeting with some Mechis for this?
Do you have to even get it approved through him?
I'm not sure.
Yeah.
This might be outside of it.
Now suddenly I'm the plunderer trying to do extra back to the future, but not that like
Martin's story is done.
Jaws doesn't have the Mechis involved at all.
But back to the future does.
Oh, back to the future.
Oh, jaws 19 is the, okay yeah.
I think sort of even though they made a ton of.
Producer credit on back to the future.
Is that a steal?
Yeah.
But I think Spielberg is still gatekeeping jaws franchise, even though they made tons of jaws.
This is dicey because yeah, jaws is a whole other property from back to the future.
Universal owns all of it.
But yeah, I don't want everybody to have to sign off on everything, but we're dealing
with digital stuff.
So can the A be replaced by a one?
It's still, you'd say it out loud jaws, but it's a one instead of an A.
That just seems like a prequel.
What's that?
That sounds like a prequel to me.
Now you're right.
Huh, huh.
I'm just feeling out options.
Like how can I get.
But also maybe Spielberg's not so precious about it to the fact where you could do this.
Like he doesn't want maybe a full on reboot of jaws.
If this isn't a perfect quibi property, then I don't know.
It's perfect for quibi.
This is exactly what.
How does the Benchley estate feel?
I mean, they're probably chomping at the bit for a little more jaws.
Yeah.
Religals.
And they'll feel great when I tell a tale of digital horrors and.
Sure.
Also in the jaws novel.
The Dreyfus's character sleeps with Brody's wife.
Oh, right, right.
Well, this holo Dreyfus.
Oh, yeah.
Mrs. Hall of Mrs. Hall of Brody.
Yeah.
Do you foresee it being like a reboot style graphics kind of, or like.
It's exactly.
It's from the.
Exactly what Marty.
When it eats him.
Encounters.
But and so also obviously it would look if you were in the audience,
every individual audience member, it looks like jaws is rising up from a really small
source point and then getting bigger and bigger as he goes and he's going to bite you.
Are there any other.
And then he disappears in a way where only his eyeballs remain.
Right.
Man, I.
This is this is what I was.
That is your dream.
I do.
For years you've been like, everyone's doing IPs and now we've actually.
Had your perfect.
Nothing but complaints, but I just hadn't seen the light and it took
Sword and the Stone to get there and I've.
My mental sword has been pulled out of my stone and now all the synapses are firing.
I don't know.
I think you could.
I think with Spielberg, you could get him in on this take because it's so
far out from actually being like a totally new jaws.
And he's look, it's like it fits right alongside Ready Player One.
We're re contextualizing back to the future things.
Yes.
You're right that it's Spielberg controls both.
Spielberg is also back to the future.
So he's the he's the who I gotta talk to.
Yeah.
And I think he's back as always is the one vocally like protecting back to the future.
I feel like Spielberg might be as well, but he's always the one that's like,
we're all going to have to be dead before they make a new one.
Yeah, but this is totally different.
I would never step on the story of Marty and Doc and Jules and Vern.
That story is done and it's perfect, especially Jules and Vern, especially Vern touching his dick.
But this this is its whole I want to see what Marty didn't get to see.
Right.
He was busy having to stop that unspecified thing at the Cafe 80s.
This may have unlocked your whole like future in Hollywood.
Just in general, there are other movies you like where there's movies inside of those movies that you could make.
Like there this could be a whole genre for you.
There have to be.
I could make I'd like to make a lot of the shows that you see within Stay Tuned, the John Ritter,
because there's a lot of like demonic versions of like Married with Demons.
I don't remember what they actually are, but this that one.
I'd make all the Stay Tuned movies.
Right.
That one might not be as a flashy of a pitch.
No, but still pretty kind of more indulgent stuff I can do after Jaws 19 is a huge hit.
Huge hit.
And we would have to you would have to if you took maybe you just make a deal with the AMC theaters
and you convert every AMC into a holomax.
You mod it out.
You put the words holomax on it.
At the very least, just put the words on it like a promotion like when 7-Eleven was spring or was a
quickie mart for a while.
Exactly.
People would be so excited.
This is the most Instagrammable opportunity.
We should just again, this is something we should just cut out and you should just file this away.
Because what if somebody else does it?
Yeah.
What if I were to tell you there is an announced doesn't seem like it's far along,
but announced live action sword of the stone.
That's that's very believable.
From a writer of Game of Thrones and the director of 28 Weeks Later.
OK.
So that's apparently happening, but enough that IMDB does not have a lot of information.
One thing we know that movie is going to be full of shitty effects.
And so all all movies are shitty effects.
What's great about Jaws 19 is it just owned it doesn't be like, oh, like,
let's not try to make this look photorealistic.
Let's just be shitty.
Am I wrong, though, that it kind of look reminds me of reboot from the 90s?
It's a little bit.
And it's just a little more translucent polygons, which is going to help you get this done so much quicker.
Right.
It's going to be quick.
It's going to be a quick process.
90s nostalgia is like a thing right now.
I feel like we're seeing that.
Yeah, absolutely.
Well, and there's been so they brought that they brought Marty's self lacing shoes back.
And so, you know, the future Pepsi is back.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You've been able to get those bottles and yeah.
And that was, you know, I have an almanac at home.
Like, there's so many, you know, especially this movie so fetish.
Nobody's it's time to make the full time to make the full jaws.
Oh, man.
And the mute, the score is just you just run the John Williams score through.
You just make it a midi.
Oh, yeah.
Score's done.
Oh, my God.
Who knew Sword and the Stone was going to unlock so much chicken the rest of my career.
You're going to be the king of the realm.
Remix the realm of I was going to say Hollywood, but really hollow, hollow.
Well,
that is no joke.
No, that makes a lot of schmoozing.
Both go.
OK, I do have I do have a quick other thing about certain stone, though.
Well, first of all, you know, Mikey was saying it's such a like wonderful detail.
And it's those little details that make Disneyland magical.
I don't know if you could credit him specifically, but this sort of the stone was put in along with
Tony Baxter's 1983 fantasy land overlay.
And I dug out my ticket magazine that made me aware of Mr. Baxter as a kid.
And he talks in that.
I'll just read a quote.
You know, with all the work we did on the dark ride exteriors, do you know which detail
the guests noticed the most?
It's the sword and the stone by the carousel.
And that's probably the cheapest and easiest thing we put in there.
That was just an afterthought as a way of giving some theming integrity to King Arthur's carousel.
Yeah.
Because there's no other representation of the sword in the stone world.
So they like expanded it out a little bit.
Everybody looks at every photographs that stands around with their kids.
And they're in this courtyard surrounded by some of the most wonderful themed detailing
we've ever done.
And yet that's the thing that everybody goes to.
It's this weird.
It's the centerpiece.
It's like the like the the hull of the ship, the mermaid on the ship.
You're looking at that as opposed to it's like Dreamer's Point that Walt the statue
wall laying out at.
It is interesting because like it is I do think something about like pulling the sword
out of the stone, whether even you've seen the movie or not, there is something that
like draws you to it.
There's something like very iconic about it, whether you actually have that in your brain
or not.
Like, I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know if it's like myth, just general myth that we've all like, you know, been raised
on or something where you're like, I wonder if I could do like, I wonder what it is.
I mean, I think a sword in general, whether it's like, you know, Zelda, you know, that's
a very like a thing we've all have in our heads from playing like Zelda for our whole
lives.
So I wonder if it's like so much sword iconography in our brains and it's such a perfectly
placed little thing.
I have to think that was in Tony Baxter's mind when designing the Paris park, because
from when I watched the video of them doing the certain stone show in Paris, it is center
behind the castle.
It is right behind the castle.
And you can watch it from the balcony and notice that people on multiple tiers watching
it.
Huge place of prominence.
It's more complex rock work.
More complex rock work.
Merlin has like an Igor style helper.
That's a good character.
Wow.
Yeah.
But I think also, you know, the legends of King Arthur, if you go back to like British
history and European history and monarchy, all those countries just kind of all those
monarchies just blend together.
Like, I don't really understand it very well.
I've seen Mary Queen of Scots, a very boring movie, but like the British royal family is
related to the French monarchies related to German.
It's very complex.
But you don't got to think about all that shit.
Well, you just got to pull a sword.
But really given a center of prominence, the Paris park.
I also think it's interesting, like the whole like, am I worthy?
There's some weird psychological thing with that.
And that shows up a lot in myths, you know, Thor's hammer or whatever.
It's like, are you special?
Really is what the question is.
So like the question, are you going to win the lottery?
Like there's a.
Hero's journey shit.
Yeah, something in all of our brains.
Sure.
It's very funny in the American versions with Merlin when he gets a crowd to chant,
all hail King Colin.
Hip hip hooray.
All hail King Rider.
Perfectly mundane name.
You know, really quick also that reminded me that there's I was trying to remember,
isn't one of the doesn't one of the TGA of sitcoms have a thing where they go to Disney
World and then and like I was thinking, is it Michelle on Full House pulls the sword
out of the stone and then she's the she's the ruler of the realm and they take it more seriously
and she actually gets to issue commands and Stephanie's mad.
I was wrong.
What it is where they made up a thing that did not exist anywhere else,
but is a good idea of a show.
I think they were trying to cross promote a Latin.
So there is a thing where you rubbed a big lamp and if you if you rubbed the lamp and a
genie came out, then you're the ruler of Disneyland.
And that's what they use the float from the Aladdin parade at the time.
Smart.
I remember this.
Now, yeah.
Yeah.
I had the faintest memory of this and I knew you would have it.
Yep.
Yeah.
Like you are you like something with the something with the ruler of Disney.
I even wonder if the writers were like, what if they use what if we use that certain the
stone thing and they're like, yeah, we'd rather you know, needs to be a Latin.
We got to look at which offers a fun little crossover where DJ's story is that she really
wants to see Steve Scott Wenger.
Right.
And she's like seeing him all over.
She sees him as Indiana Jones in the stunt show and she sees him as Aladdin,
but he is the voice of Aladdin.
He is a lot.
You get to see the voice dressed as Aladdin.
Whoa.
Very special universe collapsing moment for sure.
But they're they're very like they're they're big.
It's like a lot of legalese even in this episode moment like and you and like this.
We don't do this all the time.
I think like I have to like Aladdin chic guy has to say like, no, we don't ever do this and
we won't do it if you at home.
I come to see this.
Come but just to be here.
Come to the don't expect.
Look, the magical day is your award.
If you're lucky, you'll get a royal medallion.
That was an older show I saw.
Colin receives the royal medallion.
Dad gets the memory which hit which got a big laugh.
So that's a joke.
And that's a joke.
And you know what?
I thought that was your joke and I liked the joke and realizing that that was a yeah.
Hey, they were funny.
Yeah.
No, Merlin.
Merlin lands that laugh.
You would get something though.
That's the last thing I have.
You would get a medal and you would get like a royal proclamation.
Yeah.
Can we look and see on eBay if these are available?
Well, here, look it up.
The other joke that I like legitimately is that Merlin implies that well, first of all,
the bird will choose who will be taking part in the ceremony and they release the bird.
The bird just leaves.
The bird doesn't pick anybody.
Oh, yeah.
And that's funny.
And then Merlin says like, well, that's all for the better because if the bird picks you,
you'll know it.
And he wipes something off of his shoulder.
Solid.
Implication that's yeah.
Solid joke.
I think you can cut if you're looking to save money, you can cut the bird.
I don't think you necessarily need the bird.
And the birds are equity.
So they're getting.
17 seeds an hour.
You can get genuine rare vintage Disney World Merlin Sword in the Stone medallion.
$45.
Buy it now.
$5 shipping.
And it is like it looks like a solid little piece.
But you didn't earn it.
But this is this is like this is like Harrison Hightower, Stolen Valor.
Yeah, that's true.
I feel like the majesty makers aren't giving out.
That's pretty good, though.
It says on the back in the royal lettering, like temporary ruler of the realm.
Sure.
It's funny.
It's up to you to decide Brexit.
No deal or will you get an extension?
Temporary.
The next John Oliver will be railing about you for 18 minutes.
Oh, there's a Disneyland one for $2.95.
And it's a different design.
And it just has says sort of the sword in the stone.
And then on the back, it just says Disneyland happiest place.
Kind of breaks the reality a little.
Yeah, a little less special.
Doesn't say it doesn't refer to your role in all of this.
Right.
But there's not many of these on here.
There's only like a couple.
Any listeners, if you were selected as temporary ruler of the realm, let us know.
How did your day go?
Did it give you false confidence?
Did you go back to school after the vacation?
Yeah.
Are you a jerk to everybody?
Do you feel bad about it?
Have you atoned?
Have you called the people that you wronged?
I hope not, because Merlin taught Arthur that you should not be cocky and you should not.
You should think before you act was the big lessons.
You're really listening to Merlin.
Yeah.
And we jerk.
Why were you so?
Why are you so fucking sure yourself?
I think Merlin, too, like from just reading summaries of sword in the stone, kind of
an early not version of Jeannie, but had some like self-aware modern gags at it.
Like you'll even be in movies, you know, like mentioning topical topical Merlin.
Topical Merlin.
Twitter.
Oh, topical Merlin.
Does he end up in Bermuda at some point?
I feel like that's a joke when he like disappears.
He like comes to like on a beach.
I don't remember.
Like I saw that.
Yeah, maybe we'll look it up.
Well, I guess we did it.
We did it.
I guess we talked about certain this for a while.
We boy, you know what?
We managed to do it.
You survived fuck has the ride.
And truly like how could I have been worried about it being a thin episode when it ended up
giving me this like, I know, I know what the next 15 years of my career are.
And I will when you all I will.
Yeah, I will feel like temporary ruler of the realm.
And when everyone's at the hall at the hall of max for the big premiere.
Yeah.
Wearing holoties and seating all popcorn.
And I've been development hell trying to get a Chanteclair project off the ground.
But you're also over on this Broadway, this Broadway, this Burbank theater over here playing
Chanteclair on stage.
Sure.
So that's somehow I also have to crow at dawn every morning to get the sun to rise in real life.
It sucks.
You were cursed with his actual duties.
Yes.
On this earth.
Yeah.
So you're trying to sell a project.
You're playing him on stage and you are also Chanteclair.
I was Chanteclair all the time, I guess.
And you lay the eggs that we eat for breakfast.
Famously rooster laid eggs.
Yeah, right.
Well, I don't know how animals work.
And that's the takeaway.
My future is just looking at pictures of adorable cat seats on Twitter for the rest of my life.
Sure.
They're thick seats.
That's what I'll be doing.
That's that's another I should probably start the Instagram.
My cat's seat.
There's no pictures of her face.
That's how we get them eight to 80.
The 80 year olds we call bottom seats.
For the young people, we spell thick with two C's.
Thick seat.
Until there's a cooler way to spell seat, we will use the traditional.
Yes.
Yeah, we have to do that.
But for now.
For now.
If you want to hear more of this kind of thing, go to our subscribe to our Patreon,
the second gate, follow us on Twitter, Facebook, Instagram, and all the things.
And keep an eye out for pictures of my cat seat.
Thanks for listening.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
Engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.