Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcasts may contain
heavy hair helmets, grown men posing as five year old girls
and snouts filled with snot.
Disney Princess Training Program graduate Amanda Lunn
joins us.
Beware of pansy dads.
We're talking Disney Princesses on podcast The Ride.
["Princess Meets and Greet's Theme Song"]
Welcome to podcast The Ride hosted by three guys
who do go to Disneyland by themselves,
but I swear do not do princess meet and greets
by themselves, although I don't wanna make an assumption
about you guys.
I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson.
Raised a finger.
I'm Mike Carlson and I have never, yeah, solo gone
and met a princess.
Other characters, 100%.
But not a princess.
I think seeing a human face is a little too much.
I couldn't deal with it and I don't want them judging me.
But like if it's Eeyore's face, I can't tell
what the performer is thinking about me.
You can't see their perpetual pout and disgust
with you as single man wanting to meet them.
Jason Sheridan, is this true of you?
Yes, that is true.
Much respect, much respect.
But no, not usually one of my go-to.
Shouldn't throw shade at anybody who wants to do it.
Just to have my questions.
Yes, we at least solo have not had a ton of experience
with the Disney Princess meet and greets,
but we're joined today by somebody who has lived it,
who's lived it internationally even.
She is a writer and a podcaster
from The Big Ones, her podcast.
Amanda Lund is here.
Thank you so much for having me.
Thank you for coming.
Thanks for coming, appreciate it.
No, I love talking about this stuff.
Oh boy, well and there is a ton to talk about, clearly.
A pretty tenured career, it would seem.
Yeah, definitely.
I was a princess at Disneyland and California Adventure
for probably six, seven years, I think,
from 2001, 2002 to 2008.
Wow, wow, geez, Alanta.
And then, were you exclusively that?
Were you doing other jobs in the meantime,
or just pursuing acting and stuff?
Well, I started, I got the job when I was in high school.
So I'm from Southern California.
I think so, end of my sophomore year,
I started working at Disney, when I turned,
I think I was 17 when I started working there.
You were that young, wow.
Yeah, definitely, yeah.
Wow, and I guess within the princess world,
that's the desire, I guess,
because they sort of, I was looking into qualifications
for this program, for being part of it,
and there is sort of an age cut off,
a little bit loosely, it would seem.
Like, 27, they say, is sort of.
He seems right, if you think about it,
because in the movies, I mean,
I think Princess Aurora is maybe 14?
Are you so sure?
Yeah, they're all, I feel like they're all younger
than you think.
I think Cinderella is 16, and Ariel, I think, is 16.
It's so funny, because seeing the movies as a child,
I was like, well, they all must be 30 years old.
Of course, must be that old.
They have this much responsibility, surely.
Well, they're all getting married.
Right, yeah, that's true.
I guess the laws in all the fairy tale kingdoms
are different, I suppose.
Straight, okay, so yeah, you entered this in high school.
Were you Orange County, or did you have to commute away?
Yeah, so I'm from Long Beach,
and Long Beach is technically LA County,
but it was probably a 25 minute, 20 minute drive
to Anaheim to go to Disneyland, so it wasn't bad.
And so I was, growing up, I had a season pass,
and I would just go to theme parks all the time,
and I had one of my best friends,
her older sister worked there,
and she would always see the princesses,
and they would have post flyers for open calls.
So she was like, Amanda, you should audition to do this.
Right, right, gotcha, huh, huh.
And then, was it part of a big cattle call,
or are they doing it sort of perpetually?
Yeah, I feel like they maybe auditioned
a couple times a year, but it was definitely a cattle call.
It was like a two or three day process.
Geez, wow, wow.
Could you estimate the amount of people on the way in?
I mean, I think like a couple hundred.
Yeah.
Probably.
Do you remember the mood of it?
Because I feel like that's the job that's very sought after.
I think other guests have talked about how that is
an elite status of theme park performer,
is the princesses specifically.
So is it, do you remember, was it tents in there?
Yeah, I mean, I definitely peaked in high school
when I was doing this job.
Absolutely.
But it was, so they have, the first call is a big open call,
and I think it was at some sort of big dance center,
in like a big sort of dancey, big open room,
and you had like hundreds and hundreds of people,
and it was just like all different types of people,
like people who you're like, oh, I could see them,
they're like the right age range,
like they kind of look like a character maybe I've seen.
And then there's just people who are Disney fans,
and they're just coming probably for dual purposes,
maybe one purpose is that they want a peek behind the curtain,
and then I think another is that they think
maybe they could get the job or some sort of job.
So you just have all sorts of people at these open calls,
and like everyone is just so excited to be there.
Because it must be like maximum chipperness,
like 300 princess types all in one room together.
But they're not all princess types,
like some people are just like, I mean,
just Disney fans who come from all over to like,
just I don't really know what their intention is.
But it's crazy because the first thing they do
is they bring you in in groups of I think 20 or 30,
and they line you up in sort of a grid,
so it's like, be like four rows of 10.
And they just, whoever it is,
it's usually three or four people running the audition,
and they're all like, you can tell
they used to be face characters,
and now they've kind of graduated to management.
And they just come up to you,
and they get really close to your face,
and they look at you, and they just go,
hi, how are you doing today?
And you just say, I'm good, thanks,
and you stand there smiling,
and then they cut 90% of the people.
Just from that.
Wow, it's like Miss America, right?
Where they cut like 40 of the contestants immediately
or something, right?
Isn't that what they do?
I haven't really watched pageants.
I don't know, my mom's a big pageant guy.
You follow?
Look, my mom made us watch Miss America
when we were really younger.
She did?
Yeah, she loved it, I guess, for whatever reason.
It was an event, our high school band
would play at it pretty regularly.
Play at the Miss America matches?
It was in Atlantic City,
because it's only two hours away, hour and a half drive.
Wait, you're on the stage in the?
You were playing.
I wasn't playing.
Oh, okay, okay.
Friends in the band would go down and play.
That's wild.
I mean, I definitely think there is
some Disney princess pageant girl crossover.
Sure, sure. That's for sure.
That makes sense.
Going into it, was it a thing you were like,
oh, I would do that, or were you like,
no, that is cool, I'm very excited about this?
I was just like, oh, I need to get a job.
This is something I could do.
I was a dancer, I always did ballet,
so I knew there was some dancing involved,
and I was like, oh, this could be fun.
I kind of had an interest in performing.
I was a Disney fan.
I grew up watching all the movies,
and I loved going to the theme park.
Also, a couple of my girlfriends worked at downtown Disney,
some of my best friends, so I was like,
oh, they're working at Disney.
They were at the Jazz Kitchen.
Sure, it'll work.
Being hostesses.
And so I just thought, oh, I'll audition for this,
and then yeah, I got it, and it became my life.
Wow, wow.
Not to sidetrack, we're heading into an extensive series
about downtown Disney in the near future.
We're gonna cover it in depth.
Do you recall anything specific about though,
about your friends and their experiences?
Do you think the Jazz Kitchen was a pleasant place to work?
Oh, I'm sure, if you want my friend Lauren on the podcast,
she has a lot of stories from the Jazz Kitchen.
But there was a whole, I mean, a period of my life
one summer where I was just like a Jazz Kitchen regular.
I was like 19, going to the Jazz Kitchen,
being served with my fake ID.
We would just go there and then just loiter around
and meet boys at downtown Disney.
One time we met these guys,
and we were probably like 19, and they were in their 30s,
and Anthrax was playing at the House of Blues.
Absolutely, yeah.
And we were like, we like Anthrax,
we had no idea what it was,
and we just would like go see concerts with,
I mean, it was a whole, I mean, I really,
that was my stomping ground.
Regular at the Jazz Kitchen with a fake ID,
committing fraud at-
Oh my God.
In Ralph Brennan's face.
Yes.
But no, I'm a big fan of all of the downtown Disney's
like around the world.
Oh sure, yeah.
Which there are a lot of them.
I guess, oh sorry.
No, I was just gonna say,
was Jazz Kitchen number one of a hangout
as far as did downtown Disney,
or were there other, like,
was Tortilla Joe's there at the time?
Yeah, Tortilla Joe's was there, but we weren't big fans.
I mean, we were definitely Jazz Kitchen loyalists.
Right, okay. For sure.
That's the one we haven't really done.
I think we have to- I've been there.
I've done the quick, I've done the express Jazz Kitchen.
I just did it, I just got a sandwich from the express.
Okay.
You need the full service.
I know, I know, I could do that.
Ralph Brennan is one of the acclaimed chefs of New Orleans,
but I went for a quick lunch in the restaurant once
and had like a fish sandwich
that was like filet-o-fish quality.
I was like, I'll have to come back
and have jambalaya or something.
Save it for the series, Jason.
I know, I know.
It'll come back.
I was curious to get any free information.
There's a spoiler there.
What you thought of the fish sandwich.
Okay.
So your dream is to have an excuse to use that as the home,
Anaheim as the home base
for your high school and college years.
And you, okay, so you pass by this bizarre,
this facial profiling essentially.
Yeah.
Very strange.
It also seems like there's just a height cutoff.
They have really specific criteria.
Whatever written down, it's okay.
Most princesses, five, four to five, seven,
and then fairies and Alice and Wendy
are all four, 11 to five, two.
Yeah, that sounds right.
And I'm five, seven, so I was on the tall end.
But they would, Princess Aurora could be a little bit taller.
I think some of the girls were, they'd make,
if you were five, eight, you could sneak in there.
Beesomely way.
You could slouch or something.
Or you could stand up taller.
Like you could.
I mean, you look, when you're Princess Aurora,
you look taller anyway
because the bangs are very, they're a feathered bang.
Oh, sure.
Isn't there some headpiece also that relates to the?
Yeah, you have a crown.
A lot of the princesses, Cinderella,
have the feathered sort of 1994 bang.
Sure, sure, still.
Yes.
Okay, so you pass the height requirement.
Then what?
What's after let me stare at you for a second?
What's the next angel step?
So that's the big cut.
And then later in the day, if you've made the cut,
they have you come back to learn a dance.
So it's, you spend maybe an hour
being taught very basic choreography.
Sort of like anyone who's done like a level one ballet class.
I mean, think about that.
It's kind of like a step touch, step touch, step twirl,
and take a bow and touch your heart and blow a kiss.
And then you have maybe a moment to freestyle
where you wave and laugh and put your hands next to your face
and raise your shoulders and go like, ah.
And you're physicalizing all of this right now
and you've still got it clearly.
Oh yeah, that's something you don't forget.
Sure, sure.
I was born with that.
Seems like it's a lot of risks to that.
Like a lot of what you were just doing is like,
what would you even call it?
What's, I don't know, there's just like wrist fluidity.
Yeah, well, it's the wave.
It's like nothing you've ever seen
unless you've literally seen royalty.
And this is how the royals actually wave.
Like there was something in the tabloids a while ago
about Queen Elizabeth reprimanding Meghan Markle
because her wave was too aggressive.
Like you're supposed to do it.
It's a very fluid wave.
Your hand doesn't face front, so your hand is more tilted
and then you move your wrist from the elbow.
So it's elbow, elbow, wrist, wrist,
touch your heart and blow a kiss.
Whoa.
That will haunt me a kind of bit.
It's really upsetting, I know.
The first part of it looks like you're just pretending
to wash the top of a car.
Yes, that's exactly what it is.
Cause if you think about it, when you're waving,
you might be on a float.
So you're looking down at your subjects.
And then if you were gonna wave at someone
in close proximity, like if I were passing you in the park,
I wouldn't do this.
I'm putting my hand out and kind of waving it crazily.
It's like this, like, tee tee tee.
Oh.
Which is like a little finger wave, tee tee tee.
Which as I'm watching you do this,
it occurs to me maybe the more aggressive wave
would not photograph well.
Maybe some of that maybe with Royals and Disney Royals,
it's something about like, it's slower so that you're,
there's no strobing or blur.
Exactly.
And you know about the point, right?
You never direct someone with a one finger point.
No, no, no, I don't.
Oh, okay, so all employees at Disney know this.
You never would point with one finger.
Like the restrooms are over there.
It's always the two finger point.
Oh.
It's less aggressive.
Yeah, it's less aggressive.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Huh, huh, just relieves the pressure.
Two fingers are like the full hand.
Like anything that's not, Walt just didn't like
an accusatory point.
Oh, which yeah, that feels extremely familiar.
As soon as you switch to the two,
I flash to like a hundred of those I've seen
in my park going career.
Right.
Huh, huh, makes sense.
So yeah, there's a dance audition
and then I think that was all for the first day.
They make another big cut after that
and then they bring you back the next day
and that's when you have to tell a story
and then do a little improv interaction
where you talk to a grown man as though,
who's role playing a five year old girl.
Okay.
Yeah, and then if you can make it through that,
then you get to come back the next day
where I think they put you,
you have to do like almost like a media.
Oh no, that was once you get into princess training,
which is a whole thing.
So then I think then they cast after you have
the interaction with the grown man
and pretending to be the little girl.
Wow, are these things all just happening
in sort of weird, undecorated back rooms somewhere?
Strange.
He's not literally like on his knees
and like doing a voice or like really?
He is.
Literally.
Oh no.
I think maybe even literally on his knees.
Wow, this sounds hellish.
Oh, it is.
It's very dystopian.
Yeah.
This is the future conservatives wordless have asked.
Yes.
I don't, but I guess that trains you for just,
you know, heights, people being so,
but also that like there's gotta be a little bit
of dude creepiness at some point in all the,
in your interactions.
Maybe not, I don't know.
Oh, for sure.
Oh yeah, the dads.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
You have to learn how to kind of navigate
some of the fathers.
Is that in the training or is that something
the princesses just discuss amongst themselves later?
They train you a little bit for it.
Like if you're, you know, people will try and get handsy
sometimes like the dads are, you know,
it's always the dads.
Like coming up and trying to put their hand
around your waist and you're not supposed to be photographed.
I mean, you're a married woman.
So when some guy comes up and tries.
And you're 15.
Yeah.
So right.
So you always say when a guy tries to take a picture
with his arm around your waist, you go,
oh, let me teach you how to stand like a prince.
And then you fold his arms in front of him
and then put loop your hand through his arm.
Right. Right, right, right.
Oh, so if anybody's listening and has been told that.
Yeah, you're a great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Face it, pal.
You need some hand training yourself.
Yeah.
Watch the wrist.
I did a little pre-research about this
and learned this from a WikiHow article
on how to be a Disney princess.
Of course the best place to learn stuff
and see wonderful drawings.
Oh.
This is the, watch out for the dads.
They're so creepy.
This is so scary.
It's sort of a Goofus and Gallant type,
like you're showing us diagrams of a,
that what you just showed us a bald man
angrily pointing at a Cinderella-esque woman.
And a brunette Cinderella, which is.
Maybe to get them.
Well, you know, copyright free.
There's other stuff in here like learn the requirements,
schedule your audition, attend your audition.
This is the picture for attend your audition.
It is a woman being signed in
by what appears to be a Frenchman.
He looks like young Waltz.
Like, he does look like young Waltz.
He looks like young Waltz in Europe.
And he's got like a Newsy hat.
Yeah.
Let's see.
We have to post a lot of these.
Oh, don't talk about Disney protocol.
We're breaking that today.
Oh, I know.
You're not on the clock anymore.
No, I think I'm in the clear.
You don't sign any agreement that says never.
You do sign something, but I, you know,
I'm not worried about it.
Have you done a one person show about this?
That's funny you say that because my senior thesis
in college was I wrote a one woman show about this,
but I never performed it.
I just wrote it.
Okay.
Yeah.
But I know there's part of me that knows someday
I need to like do something with this experience.
I mean, I did, Matt Gorley, who was on your podcast
is my husband and we met at a theme park.
We both worked at Disney at the same time,
but never met, although I'm sure our paths crossed,
but we, it's such a big place that you could work there
and never, you know, you'll only kind of stay
with your little group, but anyway, we wrote a show about it,
a pilot about it for Fox, but it didn't get picked up.
Oh, gotcha.
But yeah, eventually I want to do something with it.
I just have so many stories.
Yeah.
You know, he was saying by the time,
when you guys actually met, am I getting this right,
that it was a Universal Studios, like British street
rock urchin sort of experience.
Yeah, that was like an ill fated test they were doing.
Over at Universal.
Jason's guest, I recall, was,
oh, you wanted the like New Yorker in the window people
and like, no, no, no, there were British people
in the window for a little while
in the little British area.
And you, wait, were you, he described you
as being sort of like Spice Girl-esque?
Well, when I first got the job,
I was playing like a fancy lady who was drinking tea
and then they were like, this isn't working,
so we're gonna give the guy a guitar
and make him like a rock star and then you get drumsticks
and you're gonna sing while he plays the guitar.
And I was like, okay, I mean, I have the worst voice
and I've never sung publicly in my life,
but I was at Universal mic'd improvising songs
and I was just like, this is what I do.
Change, but found your life partner with Ru
during horrible singing.
It was a lot.
Singing doesn't come into play in Princess,
not that you're in shows, I guess.
Yeah, in fact, so the interesting thing
about being a princess is while it is,
it sounds like a really cool job,
you're actually non-union.
So there's the performers union called AGVA,
which is the representation for all of theme park employees,
which was actually started as a union for strippers
and circus performers,
and now it's the theme park employee union.
Oh yeah, yeah, we got into this a little,
cause in Florida recently,
the costume characters are in the Teamsters.
And James Hoffa, son of Jimmy Hoffa,
had to come down and clean up the local in Orlando.
But then some people are equity in Florida.
Right, but okay, so the princesses,
what you know is the face characters
and the parade princesses, none of them are union,
which means you cannot sing,
you can't be mic'd in a show.
So then if you ever see a princess
who's singing with a mic, she's union,
which means she's not really probably
an official face character.
She's like a performer portraying Cinderella
or a performer portraying Belle.
If you see the Beauty and the Beast live show,
that is not somebody moved from the princess program
into the show, they hire separately.
Right, which means the flip side of that is like,
while we're working twice as much as most of the AGVAs,
the union performers, we're getting paid half
of what they're getting paid.
So where the union performers would maybe work 25 minutes
and then have like a half hour break,
we're working 45 minutes with a 15 minute break
and getting paid, I think I was getting paid $14 an hour
while they're making like 25 an hour.
Oh my God, much like the Disney princesses in the films,
various degrees of subjugation and being limited
by the, in this case, Triton is the corporate overlord
of Disney in Toronto.
Or the Wicked Stepsisters, the same thing.
Yeah, yeah, I guess so, yeah, holding you down.
With the characters, and I just saw this,
did everyone see this, there's like an evil queen
at Disneyland that's gone viral, is this?
Oh no. I did just watch this last night.
What's she up to?
She's just, she's very good, she's in character
just kind of roaming around and telling little kids
to straighten up or whatever and it's like people.
She consistently refers to your phone as a mirror,
like all she knows is mirrors,
so which I kind of like that terminology.
That's fun, and then like a couple years ago,
Gaston, especially in, I think it's only in Florida,
honestly, he was doing pushups and like,
is that another tier performer or are they face characters?
They're face characters.
Okay.
Yeah, so some of them are really good,
but yeah, it's not, as far as I know,
at least when I was there, they were all in the same tier
as the princesses.
Okay, gotcha.
I wonder if there's the pressure today
to try to go viral.
Get a viral moment.
That's funny, I bet there is.
I mean, I was working there before iPhones,
so camera phones, there were camera phones,
but it wasn't like how it is today, so.
Yeah, like for sure, if you were walking around today,
there'd be like dozens of videos of you,
but yeah, is there evidence of that?
Did you ever like make a point of documenting?
Well, part of the job is like, it's all about pictures,
so yeah, I have tons and tons of photos.
Yeah, and just, I mean, not as much of my own photos,
but we would always like,
I would find some photos of myself online,
and then occasionally you'd have fans who come
and they would give you a big stack of your photos.
Whoa. Like heart regulars.
Wow. Who would, yeah,
kind of know all the different princesses and yeah.
Do you have those?
The photos? Yeah.
Oh yeah. You copped all of,
like you have like a,
they would bring a photo album to you
of you and them in many pictures?
Yes, or just candid of you like walking around.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, no, it's a whole thing, the fans,
is a whole sort of crazy thing.
Especially I worked in Tokyo Disney too,
and that's like beyond the fans there.
Geez, sure, sure. It's wild.
Did they, like they don't know your real name,
so they're just sort of classifying you,
but like, oh, you're, it's that Cinderella or whatever.
Yeah, we had one guy who would give us all nicknames.
Oh boy. So mine was Rookie,
cause I was new.
Oh no. And so yeah.
It's also like nagging you.
Yeah, it was a little nagging.
Yeah.
Geez.
Also becomes inaccurate at a certain point.
That's true, that is true.
You're no longer new, you just are.
And he's probably recycled that name too.
I would assume.
You know, that's not the first Rookie
that he's named.
No. What's going on in Japan?
How is it different in Japan?
I mean, I loved Tokyo Disney.
Have any of you guys been?
Yeah, Scott and I have gone.
We've been in love, like,
just still in the throes of love with the place
ever since we got back. It's so amazing.
Yeah, yeah.
And you went to Tokyo Disney Sea.
I'm sure you covered it all in this podcast.
Yeah, the longest episode.
We each did one that we're just like bursting at the seams.
There's too much, there's too much.
It's so good.
But yeah, being a fan is like a big part of Japanese culture.
It's like a lot of people are fans of various things
and they go all out.
I mean, whether it's baseball or like the Big Bang Theory.
It's like they love, and especially with Disney.
So yeah, we would have people,
I mean, that would be seemingly their full-time job
is they come to the park,
you'd see the same people every day
and they would take pictures of you
and they'd kind of decide on one of,
because you would go out on an eight-month contract,
or I think it was a six or seven-month contract,
and they would know when the new batch
of face characters would come in.
So they would kind of pick their favorite
and become, this is a negative word,
but your stalker in a way.
Or they would know where you would go,
the bar we'd all go to after work.
They would sometimes show up there.
One time I was on the train just as myself on a day off,
going into the city, and someone just handed me a package
and it was a stack of photos of myself.
Oh my God, it's like the start of a horror movie.
Yeah, and they wait for you outside of work
and will kind of walk you to the bus stop.
And it's a whole thing, but it's really,
you're not really supposed to accept
or exchange anything with them,
but people do all the time.
And a lot of them were really nice
and kind of became, you become friendly with them.
But it's this whole fan culture over there
that's taken to an extreme.
Wow, interesting.
Yeah, but it was a great place to work.
I loved doing that.
Okay, yeah, so you're out for how long then, all told?
In a day, so you usually.
I just meant like in Japan.
Oh, in Japan, I was there for seven months.
Jeez.
Which, okay, outside of Disney, how is that?
That's where you live for a extended period of time?
It was awesome.
You got your own little apartment
and I took a year off of college
and I went out there and did it.
So it was. Oh man, that's a dream.
It was my first time living really independently
and it was awesome.
I think us and a lot of people listening probably,
yeah, dream of, yeah, if you could just be there
for a long period of time.
I know.
It was so, like, it's the first vacation I've taken
where I was, since Disney World as a kid,
where I was teary-eyed leaving, like on the plane,
like, oh no, I don't wanna go.
I know, don't you wanna move there and live there for a while?
Yeah.
I was just looking at pictures like two nights ago,
like just going like, oh.
I know, I wanna go back.
Like, it's the only place I wanna ever travel to.
Yeah.
I could see that just making the choice, yeah,
I take trips to one place and it's here
because you'd have a completely different time every time.
Yeah, so that was when I was there when I turned 21
out there and then a couple of years ago,
I went back with Matt and we did the whole Disney thing
out there and just traveled around and he loved it too.
Oh geez, oh wonderful.
Yeah.
Where abouts in this?
Like in Tokyo proper and some weird outskirts.
Yeah, you're kind of, you know how Disneyland's
in like a suburb of Tokyo, it's like a 20 minute train ride.
So we were in a little suburb of the town where Disney is.
So I forget what it's called, I think it's,
oh it's called Shin-Urayasu.
So it was about a 10 minute train ride to get to work.
Geez, oh, that's easy and efficient
and then the job is silly and fun.
It's quicker than getting to anywhere,
from anywhere to Anaheim.
Yes, of course.
Like it's such a burden.
It was so fun and they put you in this,
it's called E-Village, when I lived there,
this big apartment complex.
So it's all the princesses, all the princes
and then you also have all the other people
that come in to be workers at Disneyland,
like the Polynesian fire throwers and the Mariachi band.
So you're living at this apartment complex
with like all these amazing weird performers,
like the acrobats, like everyone.
So it's like this big diverse place to live
and you'd be like, the Mariachis are having a party tonight,
let's all go cluster in their little one bedroom apartment
and like drink and watch a movie.
Wow. Oh my God.
Well and getting to go to,
if you're gonna live in Tokyo for a while
with a like base, a class of English speakers,
which must provide so much comfort and ease.
So would everyone start at the same time?
Was it a total, like was it getting on a cruise?
No, you don't have different call times.
Like when you got to Tokyo,
like you were saying contracts.
So was it most people started at the same time?
Yeah, everyone would, it would be a full,
you'd have like a crossover of two weeks
while you were kind of being trained
and the other people were like,
doing all their paperwork to leave.
So you'd have, you'd cross over for two weeks
and then you would, yeah, you would take over
and it would be like a full new fleet of people.
Although a few people would get extended
and some people stayed their contract after contract
after contract, like if they really liked you,
they would extend you.
So I don't wanna, if this is a source subject,
I'm so sorry, but were you offered an extension?
I was not offered an extension.
No, no, that's okay.
No, I don't think so,
because I had to go graduate college.
That's fair.
Let me ask this,
because I've heard stories about how like,
even at the domestic parks,
there's like the A team and the B team.
Like the A team is the one when a celebrity comes
or a cherry thing comes.
Did you ever get to do anything where it's like?
Yeah, that's interesting.
And it reminds me of that,
I've kind of forgotten about that.
But yeah, even at Disneyland,
there's definitely kind of, they have their favorites.
And so those are the people
who get asked to do special events.
So yeah, I did those a couple of times,
which were kind of fun.
Like, oh God, what was,
there was some movie, some Disney movie that came out.
I forget what it was,
but I got to like,
they wanted some of the characters on the red carpet.
I got to do that.
Was it a Pirates?
Did they do a Pirates premiere there?
Yeah, actually I think it maybe was a Pirates or something.
I think they closed off Main Street.
Yeah, it was something like that.
And then, yeah, you would get to do some special events.
One time I got to travel for work,
which was exciting to go,
well, it sounded exciting at the time,
but I had to go to Texas to work in a mall for a day
for the opening of a Disney store.
Oh, sure.
Yeah, and it was exciting for me,
because I had never, I was like 17,
I had never traveled for work.
But yeah, I remember like having to,
if you had to go to the bathroom,
you had to go to the Lenscrafters.
And they used the bathroom,
and it was not really glamorous.
But yeah, Johnny Depp would come all the time to Disney,
and there was like a specific Peter Pan
he would always request,
and they would have like a private meet and greet.
He was with kids or just himself?
He would have, I think there were children around as well.
Whether they were photo op children or his own,
we don't know.
Whether Lily was there or not.
Yeah, but at the time when I was working there,
it was before they put in the whole Princess Fantasy Fair,
so which is now the princesses are all in one location.
So you can go through a line
and hit three or four princesses,
and get the autograph from the picture,
and then exit through the gift shop,
and there's a whole little show that happens.
But before Princess Fan Fair, as we called it,
we were just roaming around.
Like we would just, they were like, you live here,
this is your castle, and you just walk around,
and then at some point you have to stop,
and there's a line.
But the line, wherever that was, would change
depending on where you wanted to stand,
and you had a lot more freedom.
If maybe sometimes, if it was toward the end of the day,
and you could go on a ride,
or you could find one really cute kid
and kind of walk around with them for 10 minutes,
or play a game, or you could have a lot more freedom.
Unless you worked in dining,
which was a whole different thing.
But otherwise, if you were just in the park,
it was really cool.
And now it was this whole thing of like,
they're penning us up,
and people just want the autograph.
And it's a little bit more,
they're just like kind of rubber stamping an experience
over and over, you're right, next, next, next.
It's interesting, because they're doing that now
in the Star Wars land,
where there's no characters that are not in a spot.
They're roaming, and there's videos of like,
Rey playing with a game with a little girl and stuff.
Which is so cool.
So maybe they're gonna get back to that.
But at the time when I was there,
and this started when I was a kid,
I mean, I had an autograph book.
It was like, people wanted to get their money's worth.
And they'd be like, I've been at the park all day,
and I haven't seen Cinderella.
I paid 150 bucks to be here.
So then they decided, well,
we'll just put Cinderella in a cage,
and everyone can take a picture.
Oh no.
Yeah.
Trap Ariel in the sea.
I think the wandering characters
is more built into Disneyland than Disney World in Florida,
from what I've read about it.
Oh, interesting.
Maybe, yeah.
Where it's, in Florida, they're a lot more planted.
So because people were saying like,
oh, how will the Galaxy's Edge wandering characters do,
how will people like that in Florida,
where that's less common than out here?
You just walk into Disneyland at any time of the day,
and you can stumble upon Mary Poppins,
or the Mad Hatter, or like Mickey on Main Street.
And they hate it.
They've rebelled.
They're setting the place on fire.
They're setting it on fire.
We want them stationary.
I would like to take a behind the scenes tour
of those Princess Fairy Tailhorses,
because it's like impossible architecture
of like the same room multiple times,
and like doors where it's set up where like,
the two Cinderella's couldn't come out at once,
they couldn't meet each other,
even if they're doing simultaneous meet and greet.
Yeah, you'd have a very delicate schedule
that you really had to go out at the correct time,
because if you misread,
the worst thing that could happen is,
you walk to your spot and there's another Cinderella there.
Oh yeah.
And then it's just, I mean, that happened to me one time,
but there was a story where this,
and I played Cinderella in Sleeping Beauty and Ariel.
I don't think we said that.
Yeah, we haven't said that.
So those were your big.
Those are my big three.
Yeah, pretty big three.
Yeah, and then in Tokyo,
it was Cinderella and Mary Poppins.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, so there was this one time
when I was walking out to my spot,
and I think I had gotten the time wrong
or the schedule was wrong, and I walk out,
and there's like another Cinderella there,
and there was like the fairy godmother there.
So she tried, I mean, this is so dumb,
but she tried to cover by pretending she had done like,
a spell to make two,
but then I just had to like run back,
and it just like was horrible.
I think I cried.
I felt like so ashamed.
There was a Cinderella straight to DVD movie about time travel.
I think it was called a Stitch in Time or something.
So you could have just, she could have referred,
well, if you've seen the DVD, my DVD or her DVD,
time travel is possible.
They love the princesses talking about technology.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, buy the DVD and Blu-ray.
We were talking about, so your characters,
when you were auditioning,
was there a character specifically you wanted?
Did it feel like there was one like superstar character
everyone wanted?
Yeah, I don't know about any particular character.
Cinderella was always my favorite movie,
so I think I wanted to do Cinderella.
But Ariel was really fun too,
just because you get to wear the fin.
Well, that's a question also.
That's always a weird,
how do you place Ariel in the timeline?
Is it pre or post transformation?
Right.
So you were finned Ariel.
I was finned Ariel,
and then I think maybe three years into working there,
it was a huge deal because they were like,
we're gonna give her legs.
And so then they gave her legs and a dress,
and then stuck her in Ariel's grotto.
Oh, okay.
Wait, and Ariel's grotto being the restaurant
in California Adventure that's now the Lamplight Lounge.
Oh, did they change?
They took out Ariel's grotto.
Yeah.
Okay, yeah, so I was there for the opening of Ariel's grotto,
and that would be the one place you could go
and see all the princesses.
But doing dining, I liked doing Ariel's grotto
because it was easy,
and when I first worked there before she had legs,
they would, you'd have to go to this really scary,
very damp backstage area that had an inch of water
on the floor.
And I don't know if you guys know this, but-
Appropriate?
Yeah.
When you're a princess and you're not in costume backstage,
they give you the old space mountain jumpsuits
that the line operators used to wear back in the 80s.
Those are your coveralls.
So all the princesses are backstage,
at least they used to be when I worked there,
in these blue coveralls and their wigs.
Whoa.
Wait, but then with the gown stuff in there?
You take your gown off and put the coveralls on,
and that would be your lounge wear,
but they were the old space mountain ride operator uniforms.
It's a bunch of astronauts with big updos.
Yes.
You could have done meet and greets
as Ripley from Elegance in that.
Exactly.
There.
A sci-fi princess Ripley.
Yeah.
They were actually, yeah, kind of fun to wear.
But yeah, so backstage behind the grotto
before you had legs, you would go back there,
you'd hop into your tail, and then you'd hop on
and sit on this plastic shiny seahorse,
and then someone would wheel you out
into the lobby of the restaurant,
and that would be, you would just sit there
for like a half hour while people came to be seated
and just be like, hi, welcome to my grotto.
Yeah.
What are you gonna get?
What are you gonna order?
I'm gonna get the specials.
Yeah.
Whoa, strange.
And I liked that job because you got to work alone,
which might sound bad, but I'm kind of an introvert,
so sometimes it was difficult to be in a break room
filled with people.
Oh, okay.
So this was nice because you could just be
in that scary warehouse.
Bizarre leaking.
Yeah, like bleeding or whatever.
Space suit zone.
Did you do any of the walk around,
like Goofy's Kitchen buffet, like,
buffet stuff too? Yeah, definitely.
Yeah, and those are odd because you go table to table,
and you think everyone would be there to meet the characters,
but not everyone is.
Some people, it's really like you're intruding
on their meal.
Jeez.
You know, and they'll just be like,
they don't even want a picture.
Like, they just came to eat pancakes,
and they're not interested in you,
but you still have to stop by.
So there's only a handful of breakfast buffets.
Yeah.
If you just wanted a breakfast buffet option.
That's right.
Yeah, I would imagine that there's probably people
that even just, when they're booking in,
it's like character buffet, and they're just like,
yeah, that's characters on the wall or something.
And then they get there, they don't give a shit about
like meeting anyone.
Yeah, do they just, anybody just ask you for coffee refills?
Oh, totally, yeah.
People would just be like, yeah,
asking you questions like that all the time.
Jeez, you're so, do you, what's the party?
You then have to like politely say,
what is it, just like, well, your server is over?
Not even, you just say like, oh, I'm not sure.
I had breakfast with Mickey this morning, so.
You know.
And then walk on.
Which is insane also, that all the,
that's a way, the fuzzy lines of that all the characters,
regardless of mythology, all live at Disneyland together,
and that Aurora's hanging out with Pluto and Gus Gus,
and it's all a big weird mishmash.
It is.
Is the training for the buffet different?
I'm trying to think now.
The buffet training.
Because I'm trying to think,
when I've done multiple character buffets
in the last few years, the characters,
the costume characters will sometimes like sneak up on you.
Like all of a sudden you'll be eating,
and I'll just feel like something touching me,
and I'll turn and it's Dale.
Yeah, no, they don't train you to do that.
So that just must be that particular Dale.
Okay.
You have these interactions with characters.
Well, a Minnie kisses me.
Minis kiss me multiple times.
Different Minis, I assume.
So I wonder if they like, yeah, do they say like,
yeah, just scare the shit out of someone
while they're eating a sausage.
No, that's just boredom.
Boredom breeds trying to mess with people.
Right.
Which is a good question in general,
and Matt talked about this a little,
just getting like, just drifting and like,
oh, what can I do to keep this interesting?
Because you did a number of years.
Yeah.
Were you like, did you push the limits
of what a princess could do just out of your own boredom?
Oh, of course.
I mean, yeah, definitely.
You get to the point where you're like,
I mean, because they watch you,
but when I was there,
they weren't really always watching you that closely.
So you had a lot of autonomy.
So it would be like,
depending on who you were working with,
you're like, let's just do a walking set,
where you just walk the whole time and wave at everyone.
And maybe if you're with a prince,
you stop and do a little dance
or put on some sort of little improvised play.
Just doing stuff like that.
I mean, sometimes you could go on a ride,
which would be really fun.
You'd find some little girl or little boy
and be like, come with me on the storybook ride.
And you'd go up and cut the line
and go on a storybook ride.
And that ate your whole set.
Really?
Oh, that's great.
But then you could also,
there was a chance if you did that,
you could get written up.
Oh, so that was against the rules.
It was kind of ambiguous.
If you got permission,
sometimes they're called leads.
They would be like, okay, the last set of the day,
you can go do this or let's do a game this set.
But then as I worked there,
as it got further along,
they started to not let you do that kind of stuff anymore.
Now they love that stuff going viral.
That's like free marketing for that.
That's all it feels very planned to me.
Sure.
Yeah.
But I mean, the kids freaking out.
There was a few stories recently
of princesses helping calm down very upset children.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I wasn't that.
Yeah, that wasn't a rant.
I mean, just again, the viral moments
weren't really a thing.
Unless it was something really bad,
like tigger groping someone.
Which would go viral in a different way.
That's in the crime blotter.
That's not really on the Instagram Discover page.
Do you recall anything that anyone got fired for?
Oh yeah, this was at Universal,
but a guy did a naked cartwheel in the break room.
I think that would get you fired from most positions
and most jobs.
I also like...
Do you think if he was just naked in general,
it wouldn't have been a fireball offense?
It's the cartwheel specifically while naked
that was the issue?
I don't know.
I'll have to, yeah, look at the files.
But at Disneyland, a couple of girls
got written up for kissing the kids
because again, I'm a broken record,
but when we first started working there,
you could kiss the kids and leave on their cheek, of course,
get your mind out of their gutter,
and leave a big princess kiss mark on their cheek
and it was really cute.
Kiss a little boy on his forehead
and they'd have a big kiss mark.
Then they started saying, hey, don't kiss the kids,
which is fair.
Fair?
A number of reasons.
For one, measles outbreaks recently.
That's right, but a couple of the girls,
they were resisting change, so they didn't like that
because they liked...
A couple of the Sleeping Beauty specifically
continued to kiss the kids.
And so they got in trouble.
Whoa, I was drawing a line in the sand.
Yeah.
Can you imagine though the conversation,
they're like, I am not gonna listen to their fucking rules.
I am kissing these kids, that's what I'm here to do.
I'm Sleeping Fucking Beauty.
Oh no, literally, those were the conversations.
Wow.
I'm the boots on the ground,
I'm the slippers on the ground.
These kids are gonna leave this place with empty foreheads.
I won't have it.
That stuff's funny to me.
Like, I was a tour guide at Universal.
Oh yeah?
And the kinds of things that everyone is all up in arms
about, like you describing,
they're gonna put everybody in the corner
and you're just gonna be in this one room
and you don't get to have the...
Those kinds of, I remember having a lot of that,
the things you're up in arms about
and then a decade goes by and you're not there anymore.
And like, why was I mad?
I know, and people are so into this job.
I mean, I was never like that.
I mean, I always thought it was cool and I liked doing it.
I also found it super exhausting
just having to talk to people like that all day.
So I was never, I mean, I never had a hill to die on.
There was never like a change that happened
that you were very upset about?
No, no.
Yeah, I'm fine.
No, it was all good.
Yeah, it's also like, you could say, hey, you podcast,
you talk for long stretches of time,
but there's a difference between doing this for a while
and doing height well high there.
I can imagine 45 minutes of that in the sun
has just gotta be physically pushing it.
Yeah, it was truly exhausting.
Right, right.
And that was sort of the, it's like 45,
something in that stretch.
Yeah, you do 45 minutes and then have a 15 minute break
and I think you do seven or eight of those a day.
Uh-huh, uh-huh, wow, wow.
What do you, and then in the meantime,
you're just chilling out, you're just?
Yeah, like in the break room.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, just chilling, just bring a book.
I mean, I was in school studying, reading.
Oh, sure, oh yes, you had stuff to do.
Yeah, I had stuff to homework.
Right, right.
I have a question about the language barrier in Tokyo.
Like how did that, how did you ever come back in?
Well, a lot of Japanese people,
they learn English in school.
So it was actually really cool because all the little kids,
they learned it really young,
so they would want to practice their English with you.
And then I learned a tiny, tiny bit of Japanese
where I could have a conversation with a three year old,
but nothing really beyond that.
But yeah, the language barrier wasn't really an issue
because even if they kind of were shy
about speaking English over there,
most people understood, I think, basic English.
Sure, sure, and maybe possibly a good chance
to practice and stuff.
Yeah, that's what they like.
When we were guests, there was somebody
at that Pan Galactic pizza port was just like,
asking really basic questions.
Like, I'm going to America soon, what should I do?
Which made me realize what it was like,
I probably would ask that to somebody living in Japan.
What do I do here?
And you go, it's a whole country.
It's a pretty hard question.
Where are you going specifically?
Yeah, there's a pretty, there's a world of difference.
It's weird how I never, I am disconnected from that.
Like Japan, it's all one thing.
And then when somebody asks me, what do you do in America?
Golden Gate Bridge, Statue of Liberty.
I don't know how you answer that.
Target, Walmart.
I'll say both, they're different.
Universal City Walk.
Yeah, mainly, yeah, at least five days.
Any bizarre interactions where you felt not up to speed
on mythology as much as you should have been?
Oh, I mean, people try to trip you up all the time.
I mean, you guys know, there's like, I mean,
there's a lot of like Disney fanatics out there
who are so into the minutia.
So yeah, you would, well, Ariel,
sometimes some jerks would come and be like,
name your six sisters, Ariel.
And I used to be able to do it,
but I think it's like Andrina, Adela, Arista.
I can't, oh, Alana.
They're all A's.
Which makes it much harder.
I know, so it's just stuff like that.
Yeah, people would wanna trip you up on everything.
Or they'd say like, oh, I just saw you at breakfast
this morning, how'd you get all the way over here so fast?
You know, or like, I saw you yesterday
and you looked different, you know,
if they saw another girl.
Like, they would try and catch you.
Or how are you here and at Disney World at the same time?
And I'd be like, I'm not.
Prove, so get someone on a, there's no FaceTime then,
so they can't like send somebody to see a Cinderella
at that moment.
Is there, yeah, was there a rule book response
to all of those things, I assume?
Yeah, there's a princess hand,
like a literal princess handbook for each character.
And in it, I should have brought it
because I still have one of them.
But it's all the questions you might get asked.
Like, Ariel, how do you go to the bathroom?
Do you have a canon response to that?
Yeah, of course, because you get asked that a lot
and you just go, well, that's a silly question.
How about a photo?
I mean, it's true that no, you shouldn't,
to no person should you ask how do you go to the bathroom?
No, it's rude.
Or if they ask how old are you, you say,
well, you never ask a princess your age.
How old are you?
You know, you just kind of spin it around.
Oh, okay.
Anything you ever, that came out of nowhere though?
Like, oh, I got nothing there.
Oh God, I mean, so many times.
I'm trying to remember a specific one,
but you just, I mean, you can always just play dumb.
I mean, really, that's what they,
you can just like laugh and then be like, ha ha, smile.
I mean, and then next, you know?
Like, if a kid's asking too many questions,
you can literally just like not answer them.
Right.
Fair, yeah, you gotta keep the line moving.
Would the worst questions come from the kids or the dads?
Yeah, I mean, the dads, every once in a while,
you'd get just like a dad who's like trying to be funny
and flirt with you and yeah.
But no, the kids were always pretty cute, you know?
I mean, usually the kids were good.
At their worst, they were like covered in something sticky.
Oh gosh.
And at their best, they were so cute
and they'd make your day.
Oh geez, oh that's nice.
I, in looking up a little bit of, you know,
Reddit threads or like people talking about
having this job, the one that really jumped out at me
was the issue of Pocahontas being a real character
or a real person in the world
and how do you like manage that mythology
with being Pocahontas in the party?
And somebody, a kid coming up to Pocahontas
in a meet and greet and saying,
when Mike Glass visited your grave last year.
Oh no!
That was a mental floss, I saw that.
Yeah, I don't know that they're,
I don't think, she might've been dumbfounded.
I'm not sure there was a response there.
How in the world do you?
I think you'd probably say like,
oh, I don't think that's quite right.
Let's have a photo.
Are you sure?
Rumors of my demise have been greatly exaggerated.
Yeah.
Oh my God, that's hilarious.
Pocahontas apparently the one of the few,
if not the only one who gets approved,
can get approved to use their own hair
because everything else is wigs, right?
No, Pocahontas is a wig.
Oh, it is?
Yeah, so I don't know where you got that information.
I think Buzzfeed did a big brain over that.
I think in some rare instances,
it's been their own hair,
but for the most part, it's usually not.
Yeah, because otherwise,
it's like you just have to look consistent.
So almost everything is a wig.
But yeah, maybe there's one girl
who just had such good hair,
but I think doesn't Pocahontas have a bang as well?
It's very long.
I don't know, I think there might also be a bang.
You all have a weird upswoosh like Catherine O'Hara
and waiting for Gufman.
Bizarre like front part.
How did you land on which ones you ended up playing?
They just cast you as it.
So a lot of times, Cinderella and Ariel could double
because they both have like,
Ariel, Cinderella, and Princess Aurora
are all like blue or green eyes.
Cinderella is blue typically,
and then Aurora can kind of be like,
it's a lot that has to do with eye color
and just like how your face looks.
Is there any voice testing?
Does that matter really?
It's all just like a generic princess voice.
They try to kind of tell you like,
Princess Aurora is a little bit more ethereal,
a little bit more princess-like.
They pose you in slightly different ways
where like Princess Aurora might have,
say your left hand kind of like poised at your heart
and your right hand out,
and then Ariel you could get away with hands on hips
where like Princess Aurora would never do that.
Cinderella maybe could have hands on hips
because she's a little bit more modern.
And then Ariel you could say things like,
neat and cool.
Like Cinderella would never say cool.
Oh, interesting.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Sort of hipper.
Take that at her.
I'm trying to add that.
That is like, I will remember that, honestly.
Yeah, yeah.
That's not a thing I'm gonna forget.
I think it just, does it just,
you know, it's a way stemming from the,
she came out in the 80s.
It does, yeah.
So you guys are like mall girls a little more.
I think, absolutely.
Elsa and Anna can like say fart and stuff probably.
Well, I don't know about fart.
Just saying they can get a little bit bawdier.
Yeah.
Me and that viral clip of Elsa going, ah shit.
I'm trying to find my reindeer thing.
But it is funny because you think,
oh, you just get someone who kind of looks like them
and slop a dress and a wig and some makeup on them.
But they put a lot of care into teaching you,
even though at the end of the day it doesn't really matter,
but there is a lot of,
there's a difference between all of those characters.
Sure, sure.
Is makeup different?
Yeah, makeup is different.
Yeah.
But it's funny how they,
a lot of girls when I worked there,
they would try and get creative.
They'd give you all the makeup
and teach you how to do it.
But it was like, it's like drag queen makeup.
Right.
I think they give you Bobbi Brown
and there's some other brand of makeup that is used,
it's like stage makeup.
Is it Ben Nye?
Yes, Ben Nye, it's Ben Nye.
Yeah, that's what it is.
So they give you all this Ben Nye makeup
and then you're taught to do it by this man
who has been working there for forever,
I think used to be a Prince Charming.
And it's just like,
the way they want you to do it is so 80s.
It's a lot.
So much blush.
It's like pink lips, blue eyeshadow,
like eyebrows.
And so when I was there, it's like the girls,
it's when Mac was really big.
I mean, this was in like the early 2000s.
And so they would try and get some highlighter going
and a lot of glitter
and then you could get written up
for experimenting with your makeup.
But I think maybe they've maybe changed the makeup now
since I've been there.
And I think they've also toned down the bangs a little bit.
Okay.
Yeah, that's a,
because now we're a long distance from the 80s.
It's pretty like crazy to stay with 80s makeup standards.
When you would get like a different character,
like when you would change,
was it like you got an assignment,
assignment essentially?
They're like, hey, today you're off.
You're doing this.
They would just dictate whatever depending on the day
or would you like,
did you do six months of one and then another six months?
Oh, it's day to day.
And sometimes in the same day,
you'd play more than one character
and meet the same family over and over again.
Really?
Wow.
And did you ever get called out about that?
Yes, all the time.
Oh wow.
Yeah, people, a lot of times parents would notice
and be like, we think we met your friend
at Goofy's kitchen this morning.
Cinderella, do you know her?
And you'd be like, yes, that's me.
And so that was kind of fun.
We also had a pair of twins who were working there.
So sometimes you'd have Cinderella
and Princess Aurora side by side.
And it was, they had the same face.
Oh, dear.
That's a certain cognitive dissonance.
Yeah, it's odd, right?
It's like uncanny rally.
Strange.
Hi, podcast, the Ride Listeners, it's Jason.
We're taking a quick break to talk about
an interesting story from the good people
at the LEAD we saw this week.
The LEAD, of course, a brand new daily sports podcast
from Wondery and the Athletic.
It's all about the stories behind sports,
drama, heartbreak, controversy, cultural impact.
Yeah, all of the things.
All of the things.
The stuff we talk about, about theme parks,
they talk about sports.
That's right.
Which helps fills in gaps
because our sports knowledge is very little.
You get to hear stories about all kinds of things
that you don't even realize are related to sports.
Things like the ice bucket challenge.
Remember that?
I remember the ice bucket challenge.
I make a point sometimes of going back
and watching specific ice bucket challenges.
The internet's just littered with them,
especially George W. Bush.
He says he's not gonna do the ice bucket challenge
because it wouldn't be presidential.
Then Laura sneaks up behind him and pours the bucket.
She says, I didn't wanna do it.
I don't wanna get my hair wet.
Then it gets very serious again.
But you get to see them joke around.
What a blast.
There's a Howard Stern ice bucket challenge
with a little tiny cup of water
because truly he thought,
and this is something I think my mom said at the time,
getting ice water on your head,
that'll give you a heart attack.
You'll get a heart attack and you'll die
if somebody dumps ice water on your head.
It would just trigger the temperatures to confusing.
My mom, when it was happening,
my mom texted me like, no ice bucket challenge.
She was really wanting me not to do it.
Seriously?
I swear that's happened.
If it's too cold, you could go into
a very mild version of shock, potentially.
Anyway.
So you didn't get to do it.
You didn't get challenged.
No, thank God.
Okay, yes.
We were too busy icing each other in 2014.
Remember that?
We were keeping that alive.
We're a little behind the times.
The ice bucket challenge,
you couldn't escape it in 2014.
People were pouring freezing buckets of water on each other
or just tiny cups in some cases
to raise money for ALS research and awareness.
Well, as it turns out, the ice bucket challenge,
when it all began, was the brainchild
of the University of Arizona women's basketball team.
That was for them to raise money
and then it ended up growing into
the most successful online fundraiser in history,
raising millions of dollars.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
From that to the former president
all around the world.
It did do a lot of good, even though culturally
it kind of got away from us.
Oh sure, yeah.
But the actual intention,
no matter how many failed bits it led to.
Yeah, so the coach of the Arizona team, Naya Butts,
is the one that actually came up with
the idea of making the ice bucket challenge competitive,
not just doing it yourself,
but challenging other people to do it as well.
So the virality of it was built into it
by the U of A women's basketball coach.
And how do I know all of this stuff?
Because I heard it on the lead.
I love hearing stories and then reframing them to people
because I found them interesting
and the lead's a great source for that.
Yeah, and the lead is like,
it takes you through the story, which is really fun
and it's an anecdotal and compelling way to tell a story.
They have great interview with Naya Butts herself,
all about how she applied coaching strategies
to turn the ice bucket challenge from a local fundraiser
into an international phenomenon.
It's an incredible story.
You should definitely check it out.
The lead has a new episode every day of the week
covering sports stories just like this one.
So let's say from Podcast The Ride,
go subscribe to the lead on Apple Podcasts
or wherever you listen to this podcast right now.
And now back to the show, Podcast The Ride.
Our interesting stories.
Yeah.
Was there like with this evil queen,
like that was, did you associate,
were the princesses ever associated with the villains?
Was that all in the same area?
Sometimes, like if you were lucky,
maybe you'd have like a pass by.
You would probably never do a whole set together,
but sometimes you'd have a little fun
when you kind of like walk past each other.
Or the queen might kind of circulate and come by you,
you know, Maleficent or whatever, if you're Aurora.
Oh, and you had to like,
have a little. Dark eyes.
Yeah, yeah. Interaction.
Throw shade. Yeah, throw some shade.
But were you at all clicky with the other princesses
and were the villains clicky with themselves?
I mean, I think that's usually in any sort of job.
That's what ends up happening is just whatever group
you've been lumped into,
you end up associating with those people more.
Yeah, I think that that's true.
And most of it had to do with what break room everyone was in.
So a lot of times the villains would be over in DCA,
which is, you know, talk for Disney's California Adventure,
which I'm sure your listeners know.
And then, you know, so sometimes you would make friends
across the tracks, the train tracks.
If you had, you know, were in a break room.
I also did this show called Drawn to the Magic,
which is in Disney's California Adventure.
I don't know if it's still there, but then you,
in that case, you were in a break room.
You were the only princess.
And then you had like a Goofy and a Mickey
and a couple of singers, Agvast singers.
And so you'd become really close with them.
OK, I gotcha. Yeah, wait.
So yeah, I was looking that up.
Drawn to the Magic is a that was in that.
It's in that weird stage that's just behind facades.
It's just big like steel beams.
Yeah. Basically.
And then it used to be right in front of what was that weird center
where you'd go in and it was all dark in there.
The animation building.
Yeah, the animation building.
It used to just be out on the street
right in front of the animation building.
And this was also this is where Matt did like improv shows to you.
You didn't cross paths with him.
I think I saw him once riding a bike in a lab coat and he
he refuses to admit that he ever wore a lab coat.
He did ride a bike.
Statistically, you must have worn a lab coat if he was doing improv in a theme park.
That's what I think.
And I think I remember seeing him.
But, you know, he would not have been able to pick me out of a crowd
because there were a million of me.
Yes, and several people with the same face.
It's confusing. Yes.
So OK, Drawn to the Magic was a show where animators sing and dance
and then draw on a piece of paper and then the drawing comes down
and then the real character is there. Yes.
OK. Uh huh. And like Aurora's in that.
You do the Aurora or Cinderella were interchangeable.
And then there's a Mickey.
And then I think it was either like a Woody or a Goofy.
OK, sure. Sure.
How did that one rank amidst a strong show?
I would say it's like a mid to low level show.
I mean, it was exciting, I guess, when we came out, but not really.
And then we would just do a little meet and greet.
So, yeah, that one, I mean, I think it was just kind of a time killer.
All of early California Adventure seems like sort of curb expectations.
Like this is fine. You'll see something. That's fine.
Definitely. Were you there like you were there
then when California Adventure opened?
I believe I was. What year did that open?
Do you know? 2001.
Yeah, I think I would have like just started working there.
Did you sense that a general feeling of like, oh, like this is
some problems here?
I loved California Adventure right off the bat.
I did. Yeah.
I mean, I guess I'm just I liked the roller coaster a lot.
I loved Soarin when it first opened.
I don't care for it now.
Oh, you're a California purist. Yeah, sure. Sure.
And so I really liked California Adventure.
And I think it's just because I was excited to have another theme park
in my backyard, basically. Sure. Yeah.
So I wasn't I didn't have a real refined theme park palette back then.
Now I see the flaws.
But at the time, I was just, you know, grateful to have an upside down ride.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Not one on the on the Disney property. Yeah.
Was it was Disney Sea open by the time you worked in Japan?
Yeah, Disney Sea was open. Sure.
So that's a mind blow that you're that you are there every day.
Is our dream.
You live in a game of thrones when you go into it.
Disney Sea. Yeah, it's incredible. Absolutely.
Yeah. Yeah. So epic.
We always say there's like no or Mike.
Mike had said that you can't take a bad picture in there.
It's crazy. It's impossible.
Yeah. When you're comparing California Adventure to Disney Sea, I mean, yeah.
Makes me want to throw up.
And we got what? Yeah.
They tried to hide it from the Americans, though.
I feel like, yeah, that's kind of true.
Yeah, you think that how like I wasn't even aware it was built at the time.
You would think there would have been a big thing like this.
Go visit this wonderful park overseas.
But it was like, don't let them see what we did. Right. Right.
We don't want them to know.
We put up all our own money.
This is we get to use it. Yeah.
There's like a special I found.
There's like some travel channel special on it on YouTube.
And I was like, this was not broadcast far and wide over here.
Your parents not trying to let trying to not show you that other people
are way richer than you. Yes. Right.
Yeah, we're all the same.
Shield them.
It was also like Hong Kong Disney, which opened in 2005.
I didn't know that existed for.
All not for years, at least.
Well, I didn't know that's when I had a couple of girlfriends
who did the Hong Kong Disney circuit as well and who were there for the opening of it.
And I mean, talk about crazy stories.
I mean, it sounded like hellish.
They just did not know what to do with the princesses.
Like it's just they just have the craziest in terms of.
They didn't have an established program, so it was a mess.
Yeah. And I just think there were some like cultural differences
where like it didn't really translate.
And yeah, it was it was an interesting experience.
I think they have it all worked out now and now it's like a OK place to work.
But yeah, at first I think it was just kind of nuts.
Is there like you have like a craziest day at working?
Do you that comes to mind?
Oh, I had one day that was really crazy because I got heckled
by this old man.
I was working.
Sometimes you would have a set at the front gate, which is when you first walk
in that little area before the where the train and like the flowers are.
And you would sometimes have to do a set there.
And it was always really chaotic because people would just like,
oh, like swarm you trying to get a picture real quick before they
went into the park.
So like no one wanted a fun, magical moment.
They just were like, get her.
And you would be sent there without any sort of assistant.
You normally would have a host with you who would help you kind of control
the crowd, but they would just send you out there on your own.
So I was just like, I had this circle of like a hundred people surrounding me.
And you have to be like trying to control them and still be polite and like pleasant.
And I was already getting really sort of overwhelmed.
And they tell you if you're about to snap,
you're allowed to go take a people break is what it's called.
So you can go like stand off stage, be like, excuse me, I need to go,
you know, talk to Mickey or whatever.
And then you'd go just like stand off stage and collect yourself
and then come back out because they don't want you to.
They understand you can be pushed to your limits.
Yeah. So I was kind of like almost about to take a people break
when this old man just starts shouting from the crowd.
He's kind of or he's not even shutting.
He's just standing there off to the side.
Cinderella, your mascara is running.
And I remember just being like looking at him like,
I don't know what he's talking about.
And and then he started saying like, my granddaughter is prettier than you.
Like, it was just really weird stuff.
It didn't make sense that he was just full on like heckling me.
And a couple of the moms were kind of looking at him like,
do we need to like get involved?
And he just he kept saying all these really weird things.
And I just burst out in tears and ran off.
Oh, my God. Oh, my goodness.
Ran off set.
She's what a ghoul.
It was really I don't know what was going on.
I feel like he had escaped from somewhere.
You know, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like some sort of center.
Or like there was a bus that like had a like the flat tire
and like he snuck off the bus into Disneyland.
Yeah. Knocked someone over the head and took their clothes.
He was like an escaped convict or something. Sure.
Finally, a target.
And I'm assuming you didn't have any time to like say,
I have to go talk to Mickey before you ran away.
No, I just I think I just started out of there.
I have to talk to her.
Screaming like.
Luckily, in those movies, a lot of princesses running.
So they probably just thought like, oh, like the movie.
It's great. Running away.
Oh, yeah. The clock's about to strike midnight.
It's like nine. Yeah, it is.
She's on a different time, I guess.
You also when we were emailing, you alluded to the the Plaza Inn
being a less than
a great place to do this.
My memory about the Plaza Inn is kind of fuzzy, but all I remember is
there was like a year when they were making us work at the Plaza Inn,
which is, you know, the dining.
It's like a buffet, I think.
Main Street restaurants. Yeah.
And for some reason, it was so terrible working there.
And I think there was some sort of there was some reason why they had put us there,
because there was construction happening somewhere else or something was
going on at the Plaza Inn where they needed to kind of like make up for something.
And so they had us there, but it was the worst place to work
because it wasn't advertised as a character dining experience.
So no one wanted to see you.
And you just kind of had to stand there and everyone was really mean.
And so at the end of the year, the people who worked there a lot
got like a bonus, like an apology bonus.
Wow. Wow. Yeah. Wow. All right.
For enduring the smell of fried chicken.
Yeah.
It is good fried chicken.
But yeah, actually, the fettuccine alfredo is pretty good, too.
Yeah. That's interesting.
But being around it all day, every day.
No, it was tough. Yeah.
Did you see a difference like in the over the years in the average guests?
Like types of like, is it less families, more
childless men in their 30s coming to the park?
Was there any difference you could spot or was it basically consistent?
I think it was basically consistent.
I mean, you always you know, it's always a big diverse group of people.
I mean, I think the only real difference I did kind of see
is people more just like out to get the picture and the autograph and like less
people wanting to have, you know, sort of just like an interaction.
However, that might have been an idea that was implanted in my brain by other people.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like, I feel like that was always something people were saying.
But I don't honestly know if that was really the case.
Yeah. It was like some corporate story.
Yeah. Some corporate idea that they sort of like were pushing.
Yeah. Or like the like some cast members who were like too into the job
were saying that, you know.
But there are always people who like, oh, there's a lot of guys there,
I think that go on their own, you know, the annual pass holders.
Like, yes. Yeah.
I just feel like that was just like, oh, there isn't.
That's an AP. Sure. Yeah.
Right. Which is us.
Yeah, we've all done it. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, for sure.
I mean, there's also a whole lot of people who have special needs.
And it's cheaper and adults.
It's cheaper for cheaper for their families to just get them annual passes
than to put them in any sort of care.
So you get a lot of people who are dropped off there every day
and just hang out at the park all day.
Talked about this, I think. Yeah.
Because it's kind of a place you could trust a safe space.
So you have those people who you get to know as well.
Oh, that's nice. Yeah.
Were there any regs?
Because there are other regulars who they're an older couple
who go on Peter Pan every night. Whoa.
Like, I think that's right.
I think I don't know if they're still doing it, but like supposedly for years
and years, and I feel like I read something about like if they would say
they were in line and then a person got in line behind them
at the end of the night, they would be like, no, no, please.
Like you go because they want to be the last ones.
Oh, how funny.
Yeah. Did you run into anyone like that?
I mean, we had a guy who had come in from Arizona like a couple of times a year.
And he was like this.
There was something going on there, but he'd come in with his mom.
He was maybe in his late mid 20s and he'd always bring all these brand new sharpies
and he'd give you one.
So you always got to pick like a nice new sharpie.
Oh, scented or plain?
No, just plain. That's right.
You could get the high.
You could get high from it.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
That's what he's trying to. Yeah.
And then there was Mr. Tuesday.
So he would come every Tuesday.
And yeah, actually, he has a really sad story.
So he ended up passing away.
Yeah. But anyway, he would come every Tuesday for a long time.
And I guess he was in recovery.
So this was like part of his recovery was to come every Tuesday to Disneyland.
Yeah. So there's all types of oh, there was someone named Norma.
I think her name was Norma and she was this like old kind of old broad.
And she was just like, what?
Aggressively flirt with Hercules.
Like really hard. Wow.
Wow. Follow him around.
His cast of characters.
Norma would flirt with Hercules.
Yeah. Huh?
Interesting. The regulars are interesting to hear about.
But if you had to hang out with the regular.
I mean, Mr. Tuesday is a great name.
Yeah. I was reacting to that.
Oh, no, he was nice.
Oh, yeah, it was that. Yeah.
It was a sad case.
But, you know, he loved coming to Disney.
So sure. I wonder like I have been to especially this year.
I've been a lot alone to Disney.
I wonder, do I have some nickname name among the people who work there?
You might be Mr. Laptop.
If you're working because I've been working around there.
That's cool.
Dipshit.
I mean, I'm sure people are recognizing you.
If you come and you kind of do the same thing.
I mean, like people pay attention to the guy.
Yeah, it's not that frequent.
But maybe. Yeah.
Maybe I have nothing wrong with it.
And some of the some of the regulars are really cool.
Yeah. Well, we'll see.
If anyone's out there that works there that knows that I'm there,
do I have a nickname?
Just answer. Some people think you're playing close like a cop.
Yeah. You're the undercover security.
I do look uptight like some sort of narc.
Busting people with the edibles in line.
That would be cool, honestly, if they thought I was a cop.
Yeah, that would kind of be like me.
You have a little spring in my step.
Yeah. Anyway, we'll see.
Undercover cop is a podcast.
I thought he was just an insane guy.
Yeah, no.
He does some of his life.
What have we not covered?
Yeah, you also did.
You said you did some things outside of Princess World at Universal.
You hosted the special effects stage.
Yeah, the special effects show.
Uh huh.
Was that a in the chronology?
Or what what were you pushing at that time?
Or is it is it the Statue of Liberty Hitchcock thing?
I have been removed.
So for me, it was a lot of minions and paranormal.
Oh, that's really specific.
Yeah, you might be the only person who has a strong feeling.
The werewolf, the werewolf that the kid controls with the.
That was gone.
I don't know.
No, no, no. That was there.
And that was when the werewolf stances jump out.
I know.
No, no, no. This is the one.
When I was there was the guy would come out in the green suit
and pretend to be like motion capturing.
And then I think I forget what was actually you would see like an alien
or some monster doing what he was doing.
It was sort of a fake mocap.
Yes, that's what it was.
Yeah. But the special effects show was so challenging.
I was terrible at it because there was just so much
like made up jargon you had to memorize.
And it was all really like the special effects.
I mean, it wasn't exactly cutting edge.
Yeah. So but still to me, it was mind boggling
because I don't understand any of that stuff.
But just having to like come out and get like a crowd hyped, like,
hey, everybody, how are you doing today?
I can't hear you.
Like, that's so not my energy.
So I was just like that was the very end of my theme park career.
I think once I I got that job, I did maybe a couple of shows.
And then I was just like, I just this isn't right.
This isn't a forever thing.
This isn't this one's not for me.
So I didn't flourish in the special effects show.
Well, those kinds of
those I've talked about the show, this Disney afternoon live show in Florida
hosted by CJ, who I was dying.
I was not really characterized.
She had a cap and a headset mic and seemed to be cool or self assured.
And I don't know what you're supposed to just like CJ off the bat.
And I'm not sure why.
I only remember all this because my dad after every show, like,
I'm going to see that CJ show again.
I kind of like the CJ.
Your dad was in love with CJ.
I really need to cover the CJ thing in full.
But I what you're describing in the special effects show, like,
like why like, what are you?
Are you you're like the production helper?
You're there's like nothing when you're a princess.
Everybody. Oh, I know her.
You had to like out of the gate, like I'm this made up thing and you love me.
Right. Yeah, it was like I was supposed to be like the young tech one.
And then there was like a slightly older man with like a corduroy blazer
who was supposed to be like, but what a remember from Hitchcock.
And I would be like, well, now we have technology like
you know, rear screen.
It was just like I literally don't remember a word of that show.
It was like my memory.
It's like something that my body has just blocked out for me.
So what what are you portraying?
There's nothing like that in the world.
You don't go to work on a movie and there's that person around.
Like and then speaking of like the special needs people who had come to the park,
you'd have the same people who would come and sit front row
and want to volunteer.
And they were like the special needs people who'd come.
You'd see the same people at every show.
And so they kind of warned me before my first show, like, hey, they're going to be there.
They're going to want to volunteer.
But they come to every show.
So like we try not to choose them every time, you know, because like otherwise.
Like, but they're going to be right there.
So I was like, OK, OK.
And I got out there and I had to pick the volunteers, you know,
and I just got nervous and I picked this
all special needs people to be all the volunteers in the whole show.
And I just saw my co-host like his face just like stared at me like,
what have you done to me?
Because he's the one who has to kind of like instruct them what to do.
They have to hold these big tentacles to play this big sea monster.
And anyway, it ended up they ended up doing a good job.
But I think I was their favorite after that because
I chose them because I was like, this is so rude to just ignore them.
They're like, I'm like anyone in the back.
And they're like literally waving their hands in my face.
I'm like, you're right. You can do this.
This is rocket science. Like you'll be fine.
And then you covered them.
Then you never had to pick those specific people again.
I know. What a strength was it in the castle theater?
Was it down in the lower lot?
Yeah, it was kind of on the way to the tram.
So it has its own theater. It's like this huge theater.
Yeah. I'm kind of like the Simpsons.
OK, yeah. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. I never saw it up there at some point.
For a long time, it was next to back draft on the lower lot.
Yeah. Yeah. Beetlejuice was there for a while.
Yeah, I guess I lost interest in that.
I never saw the latter day at a raise.
They still do it. They do. Yeah.
Do they? It was running the other day.
Oh, yeah, they definitely I know they still do it.
That's where the short lived
creature from the Black Lagoon musical.
That is practically a hate crime.
Yeah, that was an iconic failure.
Yeah. Spectacular failure.
Yeah. Right. Yeah.
And Spider-Man rocks. Same place.
Spider-Man rocks. Yeah. Boy.
When Universal fails, they fail.
They do it really well. Yeah.
They swing big.
May it made Spider-Man rocks look like Kamlet.
Yeah, I went to like an employee like preview of it.
They still work there.
It was to judge everyone.
Everyone walking out was like, how could that like that was there?
That was on the cover of the map.
That was like the new thing, like creature from the Black Lagoon, the musical.
Man, I think that's it.
We got to do a few.
Even in 2009, I was like, I don't know.
They should be telling that joke.
Like, I don't know, man.
Oh, yes.
I assume Universal wise, you're probably too young.
But was there ever any talk of you playing Lucille Ball?
Well, actually, they're really funny about their face characters.
So like, I think Marilyn and Lucy
have to be approved by the States.
Oh, wow. Yeah.
So maybe not Marilyn, but Lucy has to be approved by the estate.
So that's why there's really only one.
I think while I was there, there was one woman who had been doing it for a long time.
And then someone else got approved when I was there.
And it was kind of a big deal. Wow.
So, yeah, they're really picky about who plays.
They had the Lucy I've seen there is real good.
Yeah. Like you.
So I could see where. Yeah, that's interesting.
So much. But it's tougher to get the Lucy job than any of the Disney princesses.
Probably. Yeah, I would say so.
Yeah, I never did any face characters there.
I only did Agva performer stuff at Universal.
So I was something called a dino chaser.
My guys have ever talked to a dino chaser before.
They just was down by Jurassic Park with like dressed as a
I had this like little golf cart that kind of looked like a Jeep.
And it would play like the Jurassic Park music.
And I drove it around and then had half of like a weird animatronic dinosaur
I would control. And it was weird.
And then I did the British window and I did Grinchmas as well.
All right. Oh, sure. A who?
Oh, oh, so you had the snout.
Oh, yeah, it was horrible.
That was if you ever say that I did not pay my dues.
Let me tell you about Grinchmas because that was tough.
Self applying, awful, like nasal constricting. Horrible.
And then you would it was all during the winter.
So your nose would be running because it was cold.
So at the end of the eight hour shift, you'd lift up, like peel up the lip area
and it would just flood out. It was.
Oh, my God.
Horrible. It was torture.
Torture. She was all from this.
We talked to we did an episode about Grinchmas and the just that like
the choice in the in the making of the film that like, no, no, no.
They need big dog snouts.
Then leads to dozens of performers yearly on both coasts.
Having to wear these awful mechanism.
Why? Why can't they just be people? It was crazy.
Yeah, they have to.
The who's our dog ladies.
This is really important that they be upsetting.
How that looks? I do not like.
I had the pictures of myself with that. It's not right.
It is very unpleasant.
If you were handed a stack of those, you would slap it to the ground.
I'd run. Did you have a specific who or was it like random?
Oh, you work very hard to develop a character.
Really? Yeah.
So mine was like an ex beauty queen who I had like a candy cane suit
with fur trim and like this crazy red wig.
You're sort of like the Christine Baranski character.
Yeah, I'm like her her like friend.
Did you have a name as well?
I had a name, but I don't remember what it was.
Yeah. Is would you do like the Grinch meet and greet
or that show where the tram tour would drive by?
Yeah, not the show.
I was literally just like wandering around the snow zone.
OK. Snow zone.
It's just such a whimsical name said with so much disdain.
Another day in the snow zone.
It seems like you probably had to like you're in Disneyland
and people are pushing each other to the side to meet you like
Zinra Zinra Zinra.
Universalist like you are you more like forcing people to have this interaction
because somebody has paid for this.
And you aren't like famous like Cinderella.
They don't know. They don't know who the who is.
Also, like Universal, I don't know how they do it, but they just like
there's hundreds of you walking around.
It's like sometimes you're outnumbering the guests.
And so it's like people really don't care, which in some ways,
I mean, Universal is just a lot more relaxed.
So you would just kind of like talk to your who friends. Right.
Your who buddies. That counts as a shift.
Yeah. Just shoot the shit.
And like they don't care where you are.
You're just like roaming around. Right.
Could you go to like the lower lot?
Sometimes you just like ride the escalators.
Wow. Cool. Yeah.
Is there a craziest universal story?
Oh, my God. A universal.
Let me try to remember.
Just riding the escalator up and down.
There's mostly I mean, universal, like not a lot crazy.
Have you ever?
It's funny because you would think it would because it's more lax.
But the pressure cooker of Disney probably leads it to be more.
Disney is an event for people.
So it is a pressure cooker.
I think when you when you're at Universal, you've already done Disney.
You're probably a little white. Right. Yeah.
You know, I have I just recall being mellow and I'm like only
if one person smiled in the tram.
I was like, wow, I killed.
Yeah. But mostly they are not paying attention.
You realize they can't hear you that well.
And then employees, it's also you go back to that break room.
Nobody's it's not sad. It's just like, all right.
Yeah. It's a C plus five.
Totally. I mean, probably the craziest thing that happened to me at Universal
is like literally like falling in love with my husband, like on a balcony,
dressed as a British person.
That is pretty. Yeah, that's notable.
And just like sitting up there and like just I mean, we were just like
so into each other and like not doing our job at all.
Was it did it like cross the threshold where it was it literally like day one?
Oh, nice to meet you. Never met before.
And then like a month later, like, oh, our improv is a little flirty.
No, it was like instant.
It was on the first orientation day.
Whoa. That's why he said that, too.
I was curious to hear the other perspective. Yeah. Yeah.
That's great. That's insane.
No, it definitely was like love at first chit chat.
It's not like he thought that's what it was.
And then I'm like, you know, after, you know, I just recently fell in love with him.
Post marriage.
Or at least it happens.
Yeah, yeah, eventually.
So that's good.
Did you like then like change the characters to be like,
there were no real characters, the characters, those characters
are really underdeveloped.
Was the who character more developed than the British character?
Definitely. Yes. All right.
Well, there's like a specific place you come from.
Yeah. Yeah.
And there's another it is in the state there, too.
Of course. And the nose gives you like a weird character voice.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
It's a little bit, you know, a dying person.
Yeah. If the shift isn't over in 90 minutes, you'll pass out.
A pretty unique character disease as well.
Bacterial infection known only to who performers.
That nose was a sponge.
It was pretty disgusting.
Yeah. Of all of these jobs,
Scott has talked about how he would like to maybe like one day a year
do his tram job still. Oh, yeah.
Is there anything where you like once in a while it would be fun
to like do this aspect or like is it? Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I definitely would love to be a princess for a day again.
Like, I really that job was it was challenging.
I mean, I mean, obviously, it's not that hard.
You know, like a very literal it's it's not like operating a crane.
Yeah, it's a pretty cushy job that a lot of people would be
would really want to have.
So I would love to go work at Tokyo Disneyland.
Oh, yeah. I would honestly do that once a week.
Sure. Like for the rest of my life, I
you know, I just think that that was so fun.
And the kids, I mean, there's nothing cuter than a Japanese three year old.
I mean, they are so cute.
Who are there for you?
Yeah. And they love you.
You're number three almost.
And that really was like my only real brush with fame
was like being a Disneyland princess.
You know, it was like it was kind of a cool experience to have.
But yeah, just to be able to interact with the kids was would be really cool.
I would I would do that again, but not ever full time.
And also, I've aged out of it.
But you age out of it really quickly, seemingly like it's a pretty.
You know, a decade.
I mean, you can do it to like I mean, there were some people, especially in Japan,
people would kind of push it into their early 30s.
Sure. Yeah, because they have to like bring people out.
So they're not going to be as strict, I guess. Yeah.
There were a couple kind of lifers and then you kind of graduate
either into like management or, you know, you could become a fairy godmother.
I was going to say, yeah, wait, yeah, you could just shift over.
Which, by the way, I've seen fairy godmothers with like plastic faces.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Japan like there's a creepy way they do that.
And I think they do wear a head in Japan.
Yeah. The Jess.
No, no, it's not, Jesse. It's it's Bo Peep now.
There's a new Bo Peep out here and she's got the plastic mask.
Oh, it's so disconcerting.
V for Vendetta.
The purge, the purge doll mask.
I get why they're doing it with Buzz and Woody.
And I get I'm assuming that's the logic is like, well, she should have it too.
But her face is not as cartoonish, I feel like, as theirs is.
Yeah, that's not right. That shouldn't be happening.
Yeah, those crosses of border recycled spectra of magic.
I feel like, yeah, is the only older woman you could play the fairy god?
I guess there's like those queens.
Yeah, this is in the walk around.
It's like the evil queen.
You've got Cruella DeVille, who's really fun.
And you could be I mean, she's usually like late 20s, too.
Or mid to late 20s. Sure, sure.
Yeah. And then you get into the fairy godmother.
This is the mother and the step sisters.
But this stepmother and the step sisters, they're more they don't come out all the time.
So there was they're just more special occasions, maybe weekends.
I should also real quick for the 50th anniversary, I was working there
and they brought out like a bunch of characters that had been, you know, put away for good.
So I got to play Megara from Hercules.
Whoa. Cool.
And so, yeah, I was the only one who got to do it.
And her the reason why they don't have her anymore is because, well, one, that
she was not popular, but also she has this huge ponytail.
So the way the wig works is it's a helmet, like a hard helmet with this huge ponytail.
And you have to pin it into your head.
There's only two points where you pin it into your head.
So women were getting bald spots.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
She's when it was regularly in operation.
Yeah. She's suffering for your art.
Yeah, really. Wow. Insane.
The only the other I was saying the only other aging aging part
would be just auditioning for the Lucille Ball estate.
I guess this is what it's come to.
I would love a documentary about that.
Yeah. Like who runs it and who do you have to audition for?
And do you go to some weird like mansion and Chatsworth, like whatever,
like Desi Lu Manor where some of them still live?
Well, he did Warner Brothers very briefly did like some Halloween events
the last couple of years.
I don't think they're doing it this year.
But there was a huge show.
There was a Betty David, Betty versus Joan.
There was a maze. No, there was a show.
Oh, a show. And I'm like, do the estates have to weigh
through the Davis Crawford estates have to weigh in on this like
body haunt show?
Maybe. Probably. Probably. Yeah.
Yeah. Geez. That's a bizarre one.
Anybody you wish you could have played
or that if you wanted to add another to the arsenal.
I always well, I was glad I got to play Mary Poppins in
in Tokyo, because that was one of my other favorite movies.
And so that was just the costume is so good.
Yeah, I love that costume.
She in the parks is it like is it a hat with flowers?
Yeah, she's got the white the white the jolly holiday outfit on.
Oh, that one. Oh, wear it. OK.
Yeah. Sure. Sure. Sure. Little red belt.
So I love I loved playing her.
And otherwise, I mean, this would never happen.
But Jasmine would be fun. Sure.
Just because that outfit.
Sure. I saw complaints on the Reddit that they were
they were like the worst targets essentially for gross dudes,
because that's like a bra.
Essentially. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Jasmine and Ariel get sexually harassed all the time.
It's terrible. Yeah.
You know, Bear Midriff sends people a flutter.
I know it's weird.
Do you really weird?
Do you ever like watch like Tangled and you go, I could play.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I'd be I think maybe my face isn't around enough to play Tangled
to play. What's your face?
Oh, wait, who's so who are the latest Disney princesses?
I'm trying to think of it. I've watched this up because I was here
and I watched a weird ceremony, the like induction ceremony of Merida.
Oh, the redhead. Yeah. Yeah.
From Brave. Right.
Moana. Moana since then.
So which brings the granted all up to 12.
And then before that, in descending order, Rapunzel, Tiana,
Princess and the Moulin, Boccahontas.
And then so then it's the 90s. Right. Yeah.
And also, are they not the princesses?
Well, royalty.
The real. Right. Yeah.
Because I feel like I saw things that I think maybe they
I think it may be like
merch lines are the arbitrary divisions.
The big 12 princesses, they might have their own because they're so
they're probably popular enough to not be under the princess umbrella.
But maybe at some point they will be moved right to the princess area.
Interesting. Yeah.
No, none of them.
I mean, I honestly like Cinderella to me is like the most iconic one.
Yeah. Yeah.
She's got the hoop skirt.
I mean, that's kind of one of the best dresses, I think.
It's pretty you're wearing these like iconic
like things you've been watching since you were a kid.
That all they like you're probably talking to like little kids
who are dressed like you and like that adds to the magic of everything.
Yeah, it was pretty special getting to wear the the Cinderella outfit.
Like that never really got tiring, except it was itchy.
Sure. Yes.
But besides the physical nature of it.
Sure.
God, anything else?
I feel like we've like this is one of the guys that's been the most like
just question.
This has been the most pure interview.
Like this is like an inquisition, essentially.
And what else?
Also, I did you have to like, oh, here's there's there's one more thing.
Did anybody ever do you have to like keep mythology straight in your head?
Because I read a thing about how, you know, you if a kid,
it was very confusing if a kid asked about Thomas the Tank Engine.
Like, I don't know, Tom.
You just can't acknowledge other IP.
Oh, interesting. Yes.
I think, yeah, you were if they asked you about like, I mean,
I'm trying to think like, who's the princess?
What was that knockoff Disney movie?
Anastasia, Anastasia, which I actually loved Anastasia.
But yeah, you would just that it didn't exist to you.
Sure. You're like, I'll talk to Mickey about it, you would say.
Yeah, yeah. I'll talk to Mickey.
Yeah. All right. A letter about that.
I asked Mickey, he got very upset and stormed off.
So take from that what you will.
I'd say that he said something very mean about Jeffrey Katzenberg.
Whoever that is, whoever that is, I don't know who that is either.
I had to ask Mickey about that.
I got a lot of questions from Mickey.
I'm going to do that in my real life when I don't know the answer to a question.
I'm going to ask Mickey about that.
The boss. I just kind of like look away or something.
Yeah. Do you want a picture?
Oh, yeah, definitely.
I mean, I use my princess skills all the time.
Yeah. Sure. How so?
And just like diverting uncomfortable questions.
Sure. You know, and waving to people.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Has it affected your affected your real life waving?
I think it probably has.
Yeah, I mean, it definitely does.
I mean, I'm able to just like be super fake.
Really easily.
It's like you had a flip on the switch.
Yeah. It's like you'll get in the car after that and be like,
these three nerds, these fucking nerds.
That was terrible.
You're fooling me.
It's all it matters.
But it also is all like we're talking about this.
How it's all like it is improv.
It's like one of the most practical applications of improv skills.
Oh, for sure. Yeah.
You're like doing half of an improv show, essentially,
to somebody who doesn't know they're in an improv show.
Yeah, definitely. Yeah.
And just like being in character and I mean, yeah, it is.
It literally is improv.
But it's the same improv over and over and over again.
Sure. So it starts to become plug and play.
I know all of the answers here.
Also, well, hey, this is all this is also cool to hear about.
I'm in a London Survive podcast, the bride.
Thanks for thanks for telling us all this stuff for surviving the
the Inquisition, especially.
Let's exit to the gift shop.
Is there anything you would like to plug?
Oh, thank you. Well, thanks so much for having me.
This was really fun.
And I would love to plug my podcast, The Big Ones,
which I host with my friend Maria Blasucci.
And we discuss life's big moral quandaries.
Like, would you rather be 20 percent more attractive or 20 percent smarter?
Or God, we just did one of my favorites.
We had Matt on and we discussed.
So there is a murder trial.
You're on the jury and the defendant is guilty beyond a reasonable doubt.
But there can join twin and the twin is innocent.
Do you send them both to jail?
Or do you let a murderer go free?
Whoa. Gosh, I don't have an easy answer for that.
It's not there's no easy answer, I guarantee you.
Yeah. And there's no you couldn't like make somebody be in half of a jail
because they would still be stuck.
I know you could put them like the other side of the wall is a park.
But then there's you're still
then you're stuck between a wall, essentially.
I know it takes a lot of resources.
Yeah, you have to have somebody.
My my quick and now I'm thinking about it would be like as person follows
them around and make sure the one doesn't get to do anything fun
that the other one's doing.
That's kind of where we landed.
Not to give away too much, but we went down a lot of I mean, there was a lot.
Like if there were not no movies, if a movie you have to put headphones on
and like a mask on and they don't get to see the movie or the one.
The innocent one gets to decide what movie to watch every time.
That's good, too. Unless they probably share taste, though, if they're.
Yeah, because it's sharing similar things.
You know, VR helmet might take if you put somebody in a pleasant world
or unpleasant. Oh, yeah.
A VR helmet that is fixed to their head.
And they see jail and they see jail.
We did not think of this.
We may have solved it.
Solved the problem.
Well, actually, Matt did come up with some sort of head jail,
but he he didn't go as far as to say VR.
We were just thinking a bird cage man in the Iron Man.
But anyway, this was just a glimpse into the types of discussions
we have on the big ones.
And that's on my podcast network, ERIO's Network,
which is a woman run network.
So you go to ERIO's.
Just Google ERIO's podcast network.
We've got a bunch of good shows. Sure.
How do you spell that? It's E.A.R.I.O.S.
Cool.
Big moral.
Moral quandaries would be faced by the princesses because they as rulers
of kingdoms, you don't see that side of things.
They have to like probably sentence people to death
or decide whether to go into a war or not.
I mean, it's true.
We did do the Little Mermaid dilemma.
Would you give up your identity for love?
Oh, right. Yeah.
Is there a clear deterrent? Well, I shouldn't say it's.
I mean, listen, it's we all have different moral compasses.
That's true. Yeah.
So it's not really black and white all the time,
except for this VR helmet solution, which is genius.
All right.
I mean, truly, you win.
Like that is the solution.
Using my knowledge of theme park-esque technology.
Yeah, you're correct.
Awesome. Well, yeah.
Check all that out, ERIO's.com.
And as for us, hey, live shows are all happening.
Chicago is now out there.
Orlando, check the hyperlinks in this.
Right. We can do that.
Yeah, we can do that.
You can click right there and then buy tickets to see us in Chicago
and Orlando in October.
October 19th for Chicago.
Yes. October 24th in Orlando.
Yes, that's right.
And then, yeah, buy tickets to those.
Yeah. Come see us.
That's the main thing.
But besides that, for more podcasts, the right follow us on Twitter,
Instagram and Facebook.
And there's three bonus episodes every month.
If you subscribe to podcast, the second gate at Patreon.com slash podcast, the ride.
Thanks so much, everybody.
Dream is a wish your heart makes.
And let's go let's go ask Mickey about some stuff.
We'll go talk to Mickey. Bye. Bye.
Forever dog.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.