Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to podcast the Ride the Second Gate.
Jason here is rustling a little purple bag,
the tissue paper in the purple bag.
We're going to talk about Disney afternoon avenue.
By the way, my name is Mike Carlson.
Joining me is always Scott Gardner.
Hi.
And Jason Sheridan.
Hello.
And he's a little-
You're pile driving to Jason, what Jason has in store.
Yes, I am.
I want to go right to it.
Because we were just planning on talking about this thing
that happened in the early nineties at Disneyland,
but instead Jason came with a purple bag
from an estate sale of a dead celebrity.
And I have never been to an estate sale before.
Really?
Yeah.
I don't believe so.
I've seen sales that I guess technically
may have been estate sales,
but I don't really know the clarification
or what differentiates like a garage sale yard sale
from an estate sale.
I guess it was big enough and grand enough.
That's a guy's name you know, maybe.
Yeah, I think-
In this case, yes, I knew who it was.
Okay, so yeah, just quickly tell us
who's estate sale were you just at?
Okay, so our friend Anthony Geo,
who's been on the show before-
Right, he's dead.
That's a long time ago.
Sorry he's gone,
but glad you got some good stuff at the estate sale.
Yeah.
All right, Anthony.
Rest in peace, Geo.
We'll have to have him back one day.
So he texted the other day saying he was at the estate sale
of Joseph Cotton, who is one of my favorite actors.
Joseph Cotton, of course, the star of The Third Man,
the co-star of Citizen Kane,
also stars in a very odd movie that I like
called Hush, Hush, Sweet Charlotte,
which was the spiritual sequel
to whatever happened to Baby Jane.
Right.
It's where Betty and Joan hated each other even more,
so much so one of them quit the movie.
Yeah, keep going.
I was just gonna say, Joseph Cotton died in 1994.
1994, yes.
Oh.
Yes.
So-
And was born in 1905.
1905, yeah.
So I think I was out of town and I was like,
can you just get, like, he's, I love him,
can you get me something, just something to fit on,
he's like, oh, it goes until Tuesday.
So-
You were out of town and I was-
I was out of town, now I'm back.
So today is Tuesday.
Yesterday was Monday and I tried to go yesterday
and no one would open the door or answer the phone,
so I just wandered around Silver Lake for a while.
Do you know, is this his house?
Or was this his former house?
This is an abandoned church in Silver Lake.
When you say abandoned-
This is an empty church.
You can rent it.
No, yeah, you can rent it because also-
Regular service there is what you're saying.
Well, it's full of crap at the moment
and also there's contractors.
So I think there was two things going on,
this big liquidation of state sales going on
and then there was contractors there to,
whatever is gonna move in there,
if a church is gonna buy or they're gonna convert it
or something.
So I tried to go yesterday and no one showed up
and he warned me, this isn't the best organized thing.
Oh, GEO did?
GEO did.
Not some old prospector that was,
or not prospector, some old groundskeeper
on the church grounds being like, I must warn you.
There hasn't been an estate sale around these parts
25 years.
I was kind of, because any of the contractors
had no idea what I was talking about.
The third man, the spiritual sequel
to whatever happened to Ravi Jain?
So this morning I was working on research
for an upcoming episode and I was kind of wrapping up
and having breakfast and stuff.
I was like, I think I have enough time
to try to swing by this and then get to this recording.
And I was like, it probably won't be open.
But I drive by and this big gate is open.
So I park and I go in and it's just stuff everywhere.
And- Right, old looking stuff
from a man who was born in 1905.
And there is another, there is a person there
who is, the woman running it is talking to this guy
for a while and he's talking about how like,
one of his, he's like, oh, I buy,
yeah, I love to get this by Friday
because I have to fly to Paris on Saturday
and then I go to Belfast on Sunday.
And this guy is talking about how one of his clients
for furnishings is the Hard Rock Hotel in Paris.
And then when he leaves, she starts talking
to one of the other worker and she's like, oh yeah,
he owns the Jack Warner estate.
He owns the building, he owns the mansion
and all the stuff inside.
And- The skeletons of Yakko, Wacko and Don.
That's right.
And apparently this person had bought,
she's like, yeah, he just bought a desk for $2,200
that the cottons had bought for $15,000.
So he knew what he was getting.
So, and so-
So he's probably sitting on all of Jack Warner's stuff
and could have a similar estate sale if he so chose to do.
I overheard them saying that there was a chandelier
he sold from that house that cost more than the house.
Whoa.
So, so I find a moment to chime in and go,
so is all of this stuff from the cotton estate?
Like, cause I am like looking at like pins
and like- What do you have in the one to $7 range?
Yes, basically.
And she's like, oh no, some of it's from an antique sale.
Some of it's from another estate
and some of it's from the Joseph Cotton's estate.
I can tell you what's from which.
And I grabbed a couple of things.
I was like, how about this?
There's a little ceramic bumblebee.
And she's like, no, that's from the antique store.
It'd also be funny if she's just like,
yeah, yeah, that's his.
That'll be $3,000.
I was waiting for that.
But no, she was very, and I was like,
what about this little thing?
And she's like, oh, that is from the estate,
from the cotton estate.
But I think my partner was gonna get it for him.
Let me double check.
So I'm like, what, the clock is ticking.
This is another like the Mark Twain Sunday incident
where I'm like, I'm gonna be late.
And I have it, I need to get some food.
I need to go and trade her joes
and get a Clif Bar or something.
And so like the clock is ticking.
And finally she gets them on the phone
and she's like, okay, I can sell it.
And thanks, I was like, okay, I could sell it.
And so I was like, oh yes, it's all worked out.
So for $10, I bought this small glass bucket.
It is a little beautiful yellow glass bucket.
I think I'll keep pens on it.
Can I see it?
It's yellow.
It is, yeah.
And they had so many, they had so much glassware,
but so much of it was like $30, $40 for single glasses.
I am holding in my hand Joseph Cotton's
piss yellow glass bucket.
Little glass bucket.
And I was delighted.
So found a great deal, all worked out.
When this goes up, we gotta post a photo
of you holding your Joseph Cotton bucket.
Yeah, we'll post a photo with the bucket.
It's gonna sit on my desk next to a Marvel Mania plate.
A Marvel Mania plate.
Our coin from the world of, what was that movie?
Alita, Battle Angel.
The Battle Angel and the coffee coin,
the City Walk coffee coin.
Wow, your many treasures, treasures untold.
Yes.
So was that the cheapest thing that Joseph Cotton?
That was pretty much the cheapest thing.
Yeah, I think the cheapest thing,
there was these little ceramic bumblebees for $3 each,
but they were so tiny and they weren't from the estate.
If they had been from the estate,
they would have cost more than the chandelier.
I guess so, yeah.
There was a few film canisters with film inside,
and I was like, I don't know, this is a $25 mystery.
I would have no idea how to play them
or get them projected.
Anyway, but I'm thrilled with my little bucket.
Put that on a T-shirt.
So are we, and so are the listeners.
I'm thrilled, there's gonna be people at theme parks
across the country with,
I'm thrilled with my little bucket T-shirts.
Sure, yeah.
And let the record show, you were the one of like,
save this for the show,
because I was just telling you guys what I had done today,
and you said like, save it.
I didn't barrel in here and say like,
I gotta talk about my little bag on the show.
I was interested, I just think it's interesting
that you went to Joseph Cotton, who has been dead.
I'm curious about why he always took 25 years to get.
I think they had a lot of antiques in the house.
Oh, that was the other, she showed me a scrapbook,
because I said, oh, he's my favorite actor.
I really just wanted a small thing.
And she's like, oh, well, look at this scrapbook.
The family gave it to me as a gift.
Like she was the one pricing all these antiques
in this house, and it was just these giant photos
of each room of the house.
And he built this giant mansion up in Malibu,
and it really did look ironically like Xanadu,
like Charles Foster Cain's mansion.
So yeah.
If we picked up a biography of his,
an autobiography of his, and like a full chapter
was about that bucket, but of all my belongings,
of all my many awards and my riches,
nothing more important than my good old bucket.
And if my, God forbid my bucket fall into the wrong hands,
please smite that man, whoever should end up with it.
Smite him.
He's from the past, so he would have said smite,
you know, like the Bible.
During that Orson Welles, Peter Bogdanovich interview,
he's always talking about, and Joseph Cotton
always had his tiny piss colored yellow bucket.
His tiny fucking bucket.
He would never be without the bucket by his side.
Joseph, it's time for a take.
Get your hands off that bucket for one goddamn minute.
Scott, you are comparing, the bucket is to Joseph Cotton,
as the sled was to Cain, so.
I almost, I was very good.
I almost said as the snow globe was to.
My citizen Cain wires are so crossed.
Yes, it was all about his beloved snow globe.
That's right.
I'm glad you remembered it better than me.
Wow.
He had a snow globe though, didn't he?
Or is it the Burns, is that the Burns parody?
I'm confusing the Simpsons with, what does he drop?
He drops something.
It might be a snow globe.
It is a snow globe, yeah.
It's like it's the same shot.
Like he's trying to communicate, like,
his mind is gone, but like trying to communicate.
Right, he's dying and he's trying to sue Rosebud
and he's trying to get Rosebud back his whole childhood.
That's what he misses.
And of course we all know the dirty meaning of Rosebud, yes?
Yes.
Okay, then we don't have to say it.
Oh, you don't?
You gotta say it now.
Okay, well, supposedly.
On the spot.
I can't pull the name.
Fluster. Do you know the name?
I don't know the name.
It was an inside jab at William Randolph,
Hearst's wife.
Mistress, I believe.
A nickname he had for her private part.
So Orson Welles to get a jab in at him
called the Sled Rosebud.
And that was the name.
And that was supposedly the nickname for it.
And probably it was a little bit extra salt in the wound
on already a movie that was gonna make
William Randolph Hearst mad.
Totally insane.
And then totally ruin Orson Welles' career.
After having made it.
Yeah, and by bringing it up,
we are now guaranteeing that Chris Hardwick
will never do our podcast.
I did think that as I was saying it.
We blew it, guys.
We blew it.
He's married to a Hearst and they couldn't make fun of,
he could never make fun of Citizen Kane on the,
or I think he could reference Citizen Kane.
I think Mention, I think, is what I've heard.
You know, they're busy.
They're busy entertaining their friend Giseline
who's in town, so, you know.
They're not listening to podcasts.
They have guests.
They've been in and out.
You gotta go, oh my God, no.
Sickbergs, dude.
What's the Patreon?
You know, all bets are off on the Patreon.
What do we have to lose?
Disney afternoon episode starts with William Randolph
Hearst talk and Joseph Cotton's tiny yellow bucket.
Joseph Cotton, yeah, yeah.
Different types of nostalgia for the 1910s
and the era where Chris Hardwick was.
Out and about more.
But let's go back, hey, why don't we now go back
to the 90s, the totally 90s.
The 90s?
Does anyone listening to the show remember the 90s?
Guys, I'm gonna go out of limb.
The 90s fucking rocked.
Maybe it's almost like if it was the 90s again now,
maybe we wouldn't be having
some of the same problems that we're having.
Yeah, do you remember Trapper Keepers?
Cause those ruled.
Did a quiz recently about which Trapper Keeper am I?
I got purple.
Mine was Elisa Frank Trapper Keeper.
Mine was covered in.
It was a weird thing.
It was not cool for boys to have Elisa Frank,
but I had it cause they were cool.
Mine was covered in orbs.
Oh my God, I had a lot of folders.
Like 3D orbs and platforms and stuff.
I had a lot of folders with orbs on them.
I have no idea if today is a good time for folders
as our childhood was.
I don't know if the folder trend continued.
Let's talk folders real quick.
Did you as a child get all picture folders?
I would only get a couple and then a couple boring ones.
I was only allotted a certain,
like you could get the cheaper boring ones
and then as a little treat,
you would get maybe two picture ones.
Like, you know, do you have turtles
or Ninja Turtles or orbs?
I'm sure I had folders that I liked,
but I remain really fond of those.
But these folders are notebooks.
The like 50s sports ones.
You know what I mean?
Like the like, just like generic kind of old timey athletes.
Oh, I don't even know.
I don't know.
I'll look up later.
I think people know.
I know what you, yeah, I kind of know what you.
I have more, I oddly have more fondness
for the 50s athlete brand of school supplies than my own.
I was, I guess that's me trying to be a hipster
even as a child.
I like these old notebooks more than my generations.
That's yeah, I don't, I'm sure I would recognize them,
but my memory is just like Ninja Turtles
and then X-Men and then, yeah.
Then in high school, I had wrestling notebooks as well.
Really?
Yeah.
I had notebooks and like folders.
I think in elementary school,
I had a lot of the like notebooks with characters on them.
I liked, and then by middle school,
the teachers started dictating they want it,
what they wanted.
Like they wanted the folders with the tabs inside
to put your papers in, which I hate it.
It never kept it organized.
Like, yeah.
And then, yeah, at some point the teacher started saying
like, and this is the kind of note,
whether it was composition book or the wire,
but I know some teachers like the composition books
because they're harder to just start losing pages.
Yeah, I remember then,
I feel like anytime they dictated what we needed to buy,
we really would not utilize whatever feature that was.
Even like they would be like,
you need to buy the $150 math calculator, the TI-86,
and then it would be like, we didn't use it that much.
Maybe one thing in college, I used it like a lot,
but we just use it for that game
that you would deal drugs with.
Oh yeah.
You know what I'm talking about?
Drug Wars.
Drug Wars, yeah.
There was a game you could download on your TI-86
that was like a simulator for dealing drugs.
Wow.
And like it would just go around.
It was like, pretty harmless.
I might have had a snake or something.
Yeah, I had Snackers on there too.
There's Space Invaders.
But you'd have to find like a smart kid who had the cord
and he would plug yours into his and then, or hers.
Finding that kid a drug operation in and of itself.
Yes. Absolutely.
And as close as we, good boys, came.
Right, yes.
I just found my calculator.
Like I didn't know I brought it to California.
It was in a box and I was like, what is this?
I was like, this is my high school graphing calculator.
Is Drug Wars still on it?
Well, no, I had to, the batteries had all acidified.
They had all like explode.
So I had like pried it out and cleaned it out
and then I don't think it's, I think once that,
once it fully died, like I brought it back to life,
but I don't think there's anything saved on it.
You're gonna have super powers
from this graphing calculator.
The old battery rust.
Sure, yeah.
You're gonna mutate.
The power of irritated fingers.
The folders I was talking about,
they are, the brand apparently is P-C-E.
P-E, spelled like P-E.
Oh, interesting.
I like that.
P-E-C-H-E-E.
That doesn't look familiar.
This doesn't look familiar to you guys?
I don't know.
It was a regional thing.
There's enough Google results
when I looked up 50 sports folder.
So I know it's not a, you know,
it's not so specific of a fondness,
but I think my dad had them and it's, you know,
really like, it's the kind of characters
who now would be on a poster telling you about marijuana
or, you know, that kind of art.
That's, that shitty.
I like, yeah, I like them a lot.
I just don't recall that even being an option.
Never had a P-G-A.
I'm looking at one with the most popular
sports of the 50s.
Football, golf, and ballroom dancing.
Oh, I would have killed for ballroom dancing in gym class.
We did square dancing once or twice,
but never ballroom dancing.
Once in a while, our rigid characters on this show,
like crossover, like this is for sure
should be a Jason thing.
I know, I'm shocked.
Yeah, yeah, we're getting our, if we were pitching plots,
yeah, well, why wouldn't this be Jason?
Why wouldn't, no, Jason would be the peachy guy,
not Scott, that doesn't make sense.
Yeah, oh, you've never heard of a peachy before?
I've got a folder with some ballroom dancing people on it.
Like, huh?
Ballroom dancing folder!
And then the audience is like, I get it, I'm on Jason's side.
Right, yeah, they're being mean to Jason.
I had the ballroom dancing folder too.
Somebody did this, somebody pointed out
that Mitch told the story after we went to Mike Mitchell
from Doughboys, I went to a pizza place with him
after a wrestling show, and I ordered a calzone
and I got anchovies in it.
And it was too, and he thought that was crazy.
And the calzone was giant,
and it was way too many anchovies to eat.
But somebody in our Facebook group, I forget who it was,
was like, do you think Mike has
as many food hijinks as Jason?
And like, that was another, like, I'm like,
yeah, that should have been Jason.
Like, I should have, I should have ordered a normal thing.
And like, we should save the food,
weird food stuff for Jason.
It's too salty for me, but I,
that's not the first time you've ordered something
and been like, gotten a weird result.
Yeah, I'm just saying, if we were noting us as a script,
I would have not ordered anchovies
and you should not have had the 50s folder.
We shouldn't have been fond of peachy.
But you know what, we don't line up.
No, we're complicated.
We're multitudes, we contain multitudes, we are multitudes.
We're all Jason, let's be honest.
Well, let me add, let you to delve into our topic
of the Disney Afternoon shows represented
in Disney Afternoon Avenue.
Darkling Duck, Tailspin Duck, Tails and Gummy Bears.
What we-
Wait, before you finish that question,
we should say the Disney Afternoon Avenue
was an overlay in Disneyland in 1991
for what, they ran from March to November,
where everything from Fantasyland to Small World
up to what now is Mickey's Toontown,
which is being built at the time.
Everything transformed into this temporary area
devoted to the Disney Afternoon,
which is the block of shows.
You know that, people know what the Disney Afternoon is.
Much of it inflatable.
This was the height of Disney's experimentation
with inflatable temporary stuff,
like that Carnaval Mardi Gras parade
with giant inflatable Roger Rabbit.
Oh yes, and those interweaving teal and purple,
that's my color scheme, very Trapper Keeper.
Oh yeah, the colors are really great.
The colors are beautiful.
The inflatable balloon stripes
that ran through this entire tent.
Now this whole area, if you can picture Disneyland,
it's never really turned into anything.
It's essentially, it's like the second major parade route,
really, and Main Street and then this.
So there's never been room
to really have anything substantial,
but this was probably the most populated it ever was
with these balloons and little recreations
of Duckburg and what have you.
Sure.
Yeah, the balloons from the pictures,
I didn't get to experience this.
Again, I was a child, I never even heard of it.
I would never even, of course, let alone,
I knew I would never go to Disneyland.
Self-punishment.
Yeah, well, that's how I was raised.
But from the look of it, it's very appealing.
Like it really, like your memory of it,
is it like lived up to your?
It was so great.
Yeah. Yeah, and every picture from it,
it makes me so happy.
But here, I didn't want to interrupt,
I just wanted to make sure we got out
what Disney Afternoon afternoon was.
You were posing the question.
And yeah, the Disney Afternoon included a lot of shows,
it event, you know, Darkwing Duck and Goof Troop,
but in the era that this was done,
the four specific shows were, you were starting to say.
Gummy Bears, Dark Tales, Talespin.
Chip and Dale. Chip and Dale.
Wasn't Darkwing Duck.
It wasn't Darkwing Duck, excuse me.
Yeah, which did you, I liked all of them.
I did too, that lineup, yeah.
Yeah, which is funny to think that you read
like Disney history stuff, and that was kind of slapped at.
Like it was like Eisner's, like we need,
that was one I think, Eisner's endeavors was like,
let's get into the syndicated TV, like kids TV and stuff.
And. Yeah.
With some bumps in the road,
there was something called the Wuzzles
that did not. Oh yes.
Perform as well, but past, well wait,
was DuckTales first or was Gummy Bears first?
Gummy Bears was first. Gummy Bears was first.
Yes, I think. Which was successful, but maybe not,
but DuckTales like probably really blew it all
out of the water.
Yeah, it was really huge and had this full archive
of the like Carl Banks, Duck comic books to like draw upon
and inspire. It's a very popular area that, yeah,
that they weren't exploiting in any particular way.
Yeah, which now would never,
now once they find something to exploit,
like it's just immediately. Carl Barks.
Carl Barks and how he's do that, yeah.
Scrooge McDuck and his love of Banks.
Yes. Gummy Bears, I believe the impetus was like,
well, kids like Gummy Bears.
It was just a candy. Right?
It was just a candy.
Michael Eisner was eating the candy or his kid,
or Breck liked the candy. Something like that.
And then they might have like visited Europe
where the candy was more popular and it,
I think I'm not making that up.
I don't think, I feel like I've heard this story too.
And he's just like, make this a show.
It seems like a lot of these shows came from interpreting
the weird whim of Eisner. Yeah.
Him just kind of pointing at stuff and saying, do this.
Up to that rescue Rangers existed in a form,
like they had built out the team and they might've even had
Gadget and Monterey J and the idea of these,
a bunch of like little bugs and critters,
all solving crimes they had.
But he, Eisner said, we got to put like one of the main,
like look what happened that we,
the DuckTales had Scrooge and therefore Donald.
Right. So let's keep going on the list. Who makes sense?
Mickey is not small, even though he's a mouse,
that doesn't make, he's too big almost.
So it's just like, let's go literally down the list
of characters until we get to ones who might make sense
in this and it was Chippendale.
Honestly, it makes a lot of sense.
And I don't know why there's not more fun.
I know that we're doing,
there's a Chippendale movie coming to Disney Plus,
but it does make, I mean, as silly as some of the fun,
like Eisner stuff of like splash on splash mountain,
the Hannah character, mermaid character,
this does sort of make sense.
Like, yeah, we're just sitting on Chippendale.
Why not do something fun with them?
I agree. And it all came out very polished too.
All four of these, I think of as like, not like cheap looking.
And I think he pushed it to where, like, why does,
why is it assumed the TV animation has to be worse than,
Right.
Than the films.
And it's not, it's more limited and less glossy than,
you know, the Beast and the theaters at the same time.
But with the Lost Lamp movie, DuckTales movie.
Oh yeah, sure. Yeah.
Which is great.
Yeah, I love that movie.
I think I was DuckTales or Chippendale,
I think would have been in my like leading ones.
Yeah, I think DuckTales,
but I do really have an affection for rescue rangers.
Yeah, yeah, me too.
Like those, I don't know what, yeah.
I had all the McDonald's toys.
There was something about it that was real fun.
Dale for me fell into that character of the goofy one,
like Michelangelo.
Oh yeah. Yeah.
Bart Simpson, I guess you don't,
it's weird to think of it that way now,
but and that to a lesser extent,
that dinosaur, the cool brother dinosaur,
or Cody on step-by-step.
Any of the like, whoa, like I liked any character like that.
Yeah, 90s cool surfery kind of guy.
He's not that surfery, but he's a fun,
he's got the Hawaiian shirt.
He's got the vibe.
Which people say is the Tom Selleck nod.
Yeah, it must be.
And Chip is Indiana Jones nod.
Very clever.
Yeah, fun.
I was upset.
I think the one I watched the least was Gummy Bears,
but I do like Gummy Bears.
Purely by age, I think.
That is, yeah, it's 100%.
I don't think it was any malice towards Gummy Bears.
It was just like, I was made aware that all this existed
because one is Gummy Bears like 88, 89.
Something like that.
I think they inherited a lot too, that one especially.
But at that point, yeah, the block,
I feel like my awareness of it was when Chip and Dale started.
So it was just like the other two were more appealing to me.
I like Tailspin as well.
And I like it more even now in concept
because it's so funny and ridiculous.
I like the adventuring aesthetic.
Yeah, and the tropical thing.
Okay, so if you had to, because I'm thinking
the way this block worked is there were four shows
and then once there was a new one,
the old one was let go.
So they'd cycle them out.
So my ideal cycle probably would have been
Chip and Dale, Tailspin, Darkwing Duck, Goof Troop.
That's okay.
Yeah, so if you're talking to, do you call them bonkers in there?
I mean, that's the last one, right?
No, bonkers is where it starts going off the rails for me.
Yeah, same for me as well.
I was not that into bonkers.
I'm just wondering, I'm trying to remember.
That's the last one.
I don't remember what came directly after Goof Troop.
Right.
Was Marsupa?
That's a different, that's Warner Brothers.
Yeah.
Marsupa, what is that called?
Marsupa Lommy?
That's not Disney?
Am I wrong?
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe I'm thinking of a different thing.
That's one of the ones that was like a European comic
for decades and now it's a guy.
Maybe I'm misremembering.
The orange creature with the big yellow tail.
Oh yeah, is that Disney?
But is that Disney afternoon?
I don't know, look it up.
That could have been Disney Channel.
I'll give it a ranking.
Or it was a Saturday morning thing.
Yeah, that might have been.
It gets fuzzy beyond,
there's a real like cleanliness and clarity
to everything Gummy Bears through Goof Troop.
It's really, if you think about it,
similar to the Disney film renaissance,
where everyone agrees essentially on Little Mermaid,
Beauty and the Beast, Aladdin, Lion King,
and then it gets sloppier from that point.
There's this run that was so dead on and clean.
I think my number one is Darkwing Duck.
I was obsessed with Darkwing Duck.
It was like having a second Batman in a way.
Yes, a comedic Batman.
All the villains are very fun.
I liked the whole dynamic.
All of his vehicles,
this is all important stuff to me as a child.
His vehicles are fun.
I had the jet.
I never had the ship he flew in,
which I can't think of.
The one that looked like the giant duck beak.
Oh yeah.
The launch pad would fly.
I love that launch pad was on that show too.
Yeah, people crossing over between the shows.
That was fantastic.
Yeah.
That was number one.
Goof Troop could be number two.
Might be tied with DuckTales
and then Chip and Dale maybe last.
DuckTales I recognize is fantastic
and maybe even away the one that holds up the best
and there's a reason why that's the one they brought back.
Yeah.
And that's kind of the root of where the other,
because Darkwing Duck and the Talesman characters
are showing up now in DuckTales.
Right, but haven't officially spun out.
Yeah, yeah.
But I think purely it's age why I didn't,
but I don't have the same fawn as it was like,
I'm talking it was like two months before
I was watching the Disney afternoon.
Marsupilami was Disney.
Marsupilami.
Originally published in a French comic in 1952.
So he had been around for a while.
I'm thinking of some other weird Warner Brothers thing.
And the Darkwing Duck plane is called the Thunder Quack.
Oh yeah.
The Thunder Quack.
What a great name and that's a toy.
I should look on eBay and see if I can get
a Thunder Quack right now.
You can get a Thunder Quack.
I know, but let's see how much it is.
Sure.
Predated Batman the Animated series, right?
Who?
Barely.
Barely, right?
Like around.
Batman was like 92?
Yes.
What was it with the red Darkwing Duck?
Why was there a red one?
That was the bad guy.
You mean the bad guy Negaduck?
Yeah, yeah.
He had the yellow shirt.
Oh, okay.
And then had a red hat and black hat I believe.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, I'm trying to remember the,
he's not like a clone or anything.
I forget if he's a brother or not.
I don't know.
Negaduck was great.
Megavolt.
Quacker Jack.
Liquidator.
I was like, I really let all of this leak out of my brain,
but it may be the thing I was the most obsessed with
at some point in my life that I don't remember
at all anymore, but I loved the Darkwing Duck.
Yeah.
I had all the toys.
There was a, they only made like two waves of them
and there's a third unproduced wave if you look it up
that is just heartbreaking to me still that I don't have them.
So yeah, I would like a full revival.
This was one of the first things that trained my brain
in terms of TV programming,
because this got me into like,
well, that's on every day after school.
And then following this was Fox Kids.
Well, Fox had the Saturday morning stuff with the X-Men
and I believe briefly the Batman animated show
was part of Fox before Warner Brothers launched their-
Kids WB.
So there was competing ones and they were,
I would just get used to, I was like,
the summer's ending, I have to go back to school,
but at least there'll be new stuff on Fox Kids
or Kids WB soon.
My version of that is that I very specifically remember
that Sesame Street used to air in such a way
that the newest Sesame Street was first up to bat
and then following that would be the previous days,
which I would rewatch.
And then the previous days to that,
which I would also rewatch.
So every day in my probably pre before I started school
and then thank God when it's summer,
I can get back to watching every single Sesame Street
for three straight days in a row.
I would for sure do that with Muppet Babies.
Like there's a 10 a.m. airing
and then there's another airing later in the day.
I would sit waiting for Tom and Jerry to be over
so I could watch Ninja Turtles.
So I have a bad memory of Tom and Jerry
of like the last 15 minutes of it
and I just sit watching it being like,
soon, soon you'll hear that beautiful Chuck Lorre theme
and see the sewer shoot up.
Sewer mantle cover.
Getting through the boring sports part of the news
so I could get to Saturday Night Live
and see the cheerleaders.
That's right.
Mango.
Yeah.
I mean, believe me, I was waiting for Mango too.
We all loved Mango.
More of a Mr. Peepers man myself.
I loved Peepers too.
Follow up question that I think
is almost potentially more important.
Let's just take the four represented in the,
in the Gummy Bears, DuckTales,
Tailspin and Chip and Dale songs.
Rank the songs.
Well that's, yeah.
Yeah, DuckTales number one with the bullet.
Yeah, it has to be number one.
I was thinking with the,
because I considered the DuckTales song
to be like one of the,
maybe one of the 50 best songs of the century.
Period, right?
Yes, yeah.
I agree.
Yeah.
It's so fucking good.
Goof Troop and Darkwing are both similar,
like a 90s feeling to me.
And the others are sort of-
I think they're not as good as the show.
I agree with that.
They're fine.
They set the stage.
They're more, yeah, they're more era specific to me.
Both of them.
But like Chip and Dale's an underrated theme.
So is Tailspin.
Tailspin's real good.
I don't know if it's as good as the other,
I don't know if it's as good as the original.
I think Gummy Bears is underrated too.
I think Gummy Bears has got-
They're all underrated
in that no one only DuckTales gets talked about really.
Yes, that's what I mean.
Yeah.
But Gummy Bears, there's a soaring chorus of Gummy Bears.
Sing out in chorus.
Yes.
Go ahead, say chorus.
As the song fills the air,
Gummy Bears.
Such passion.
Shout out Joseph Williams,
singer of Toto for a long time.
Sang that one.
Oh my God.
There's a lot of covers of Gummy Bears
on Spotify and Apple Music,
which I have played all of, I think,
at a certain point.
Like punk covers?
There might be one punk cover,
but I don't know off the top of my head.
I need to talk about a thing
I've been obsessed with for a long time
that I don't know why I stumbled into this a long time ago,
but since I, as you might know,
I'm a fan of the movie, I think Tiny Fuppets.
I miss translation, I enjoy so much,
and there is just the harshness of language
that can come when you switch between language
and then convert it back to the original language.
I somehow stumbled upon the Russian version of Gummy Bears.
So English, back into Russian, back into English,
and what happens.
And let me just play a little clip
of what that sounds like in general,
but then I'll have to read the lyrics.
Hang on a second.
Okay, here we go.
Mishki Gummy.
["Mishki Gummy"]
Mishki Gummy!
That's great.
It's no longer on YouTube,
but I looked up the lyrics.
One of my favorite videos ever to exist
where you could read these very strange,
much stiffer lyrics along with that soaring,
Mishki Gummy!
Here are the, from English to Russian,
English lyrics of Gummy Bears.
"'All kids will love these bears.
"'Disney will tell us stories about them.
"'Smart, brave, kind, cute, they are really faithful friends.
"'Gummy bears will amuse us with their funny jumps.
"'You and I will visit them in the magic country of Gummy.
"'Disney will tell us mysteries.'"
Again, Disney, twice Disney factoring into the lyrics
despite not in the English version.
No, not at all.
"'Disney will tell us mysteries.
"'The Gummy Juice will disclose a wonderful secret.
"'Naughty ogres will be defeated.
"'The Bear Knights show no mercy.'"
Wow.
And that's one of my favorite things ever.
That is great.
I think I saw it elsewhere.
"'No mercy for them.'"
It's a lot harsher than the show.
To me, it's like the Bush's Axis of Evil speech,
rocker ran and the ogres of Gummy Glen.
Is it, in other languages though, those phrases,
those are the closest translations.
So perhaps the phrase-
It's an aphorism.
They will disclose, or what was it?
Disclose.
Disney will, well yeah,
Disney will tell us mysteries.
"'The Gummy Juice will disclose a wonderful secret.'"
So no mercy?
No mercy, maybe that is a softer thing.
What's the actual lyric there?
Oh, I gotta look it up.
Sophie, I don't remember.
It's dashing and daring, courageous and caring, right?
That's the first part.
The second, I don't quite remember.
I don't know the second then.
But I certainly don't recall anything about
decapitating ogres.
I like this humor because you can't,
you shouldn't make fun of somebody
for speaking a language poorly.
There's a victimization there,
but there's no victim here.
It's just, it's just like,
there's a big problem when you bounce between languages,
like the gummy bears bounce.
Blood will pour from the wounds of our villains.
Quickly, my friend, slice all their necks.
Drink the blood, that's the juice.
I've eaten their eyes and cut out their soft tongues.
The secret to it.
Gummy bears, murder bears that kill without care.
Their taste for juice is only passed or passed
by their taste for blood.
In terms of misinterpretation,
I have to say there's some great pictures.
The pictures of Disney afternoon, avenue,
look very good because of all the bright colors and stuff.
Very jealous, this picture is up on Yesterland.
This woman in the foreground is wearing a shirt
that I can't make out most of,
but in bright yellow letters, it says onion.
Not the onion, the onion wouldn't have really been a thing
at the time, but just a shirt that says onion
in big letters is very funny to me.
That's grilled.
Sorry, you can't have that.
I know.
No state sale where that's available.
But merch, another piece of merch for you.
Oh, yeah.
The yellow shirt that says onion.
Can we recreate it perfectly?
Okay, so the actual thing, Disney afternoon, avenue.
Well, you know what?
If you want an overview of what Disney afternoon, avenue was,
I came with my actual map.
Oh, that's great.
My poster signed by some of the stars themselves.
Wow.
My Dale.
This is great.
My announced favorite.
Yeah, look at the, yeah, this is like,
I've apparently kept it in very good position.
Just went through my childhood closet.
I was really concerned you were about to start playing
something else that we'll talk about in a little bit.
Uh-oh, oh no.
It's fine.
Okay, no, no, no.
We're looking at the whole gang together.
And how nice is it?
Now the sizes are a little off.
Are Chip and Dale as big as gummy bears?
No.
And Chip and Dale's fly friend, Zip?
What was he called?
Zip, yes.
By using him to demarcate.
I just don't think they're,
I don't think Chip and Dale are as tall
as he would do in Louis.
Yeah, the scale is wrong, for sure.
But here I am finding fault in this great old poster.
When I was six, I was too pure of heart to do such a thing.
I was just enjoying meeting Dale,
meeting Scrooge McDuck,
who signed his autograph with a dollar sign.
Wow. Yes.
Which was, I thought was great at the time.
That is great.
And that's it, I got two, I guess.
Come on, kids.
Why are you nagging me?
Join your Disney afternoon pals
for a fun, filled adventure.
Walk down Afternoon Avenue,
where you can collect all your favorite
Disney afternoon character stamps
and watch for your favorite stars along the way.
There's action and adventure waiting around every corner.
And you turn it around.
I love this map so much.
The simplified map of the area.
You can see just the tip of the Matterhorn,
a ride I probably thought I would never do in my life.
The entrance, which where these great
neon teal balloons start.
And that entryway balloon also, so fantastic.
It is a big hot air balloon
that the characters are all leaning out of
and greeting you hello.
Off to the side, the modded out
Autopia, just one track of the Autopia,
because there were two at the time.
There was the Tomorrowland Autopia
and the Fantasyland Autopia.
Fantasyland became for that run,
Rescue Rangers Raceway.
Which having a theme to the Autopia was so great.
I guess now we sort of have it
with the misadventures of Osimo and Bird.
But this was maybe the first that a little story
was ever added to the Autopia.
Above that you got the Motorboat Cruise,
which we have not talked about.
And people may not even know about the Motorboat Cruise,
because it has been for a very long time a smoking area.
But no more of that.
Is that gone?
Smoking is gone.
Oh, smoking altogether is gone.
Smoking in the parks is gone.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And they've clarified vaping.
It ain't happening anymore.
Oh, right.
We'll have to talk about the Motorboat Cruise.
That's a good episode.
We'll cover that and smoking,
Motorboat Cruise slash smoking.
Slash smoking area.
Uh, and, but yeah, they transformed that
into the Motorboat Cruise through gummy glen.
I love the gummy glen.
Where you can see, learn how the gummy berries are made.
And then there's a bunch of Xs,
and that marks where you can get stamps.
And I got all of them.
I completed them all.
It's a mix of all of the characters.
They don't group them all together.
It's, who did you get a stamp of?
Because there's like some characters like Snout.
I don't recall who Snout was,
but he looks like Rizzo and he's got a 40s hat.
Yeah, who is Snout?
I don't really know.
He is a baddie.
Yes.
From.
Is he a DuckTales or is he,
him being a mouse makes him maybe fit with Chip and Dale.
Maybe Chip and Dale, is he one of Fat Cat's goons?
Could be.
He's sort of placed on this near Fat Cat.
So. Yeah.
Not totally sure, but you know, there's Gruffy and Zummey.
The stamps you could get, Sunny, Zummey, Gadget,
Chip and Dale, Monterey Jack, A Beagle Boy,
Huey Dew and Louie, Uncle Scrooge, Louie.
Confusingly two Louies.
There's Duck Louie and King Louie.
Yeah.
And Blue and Kit Cloudkicker.
Oh, and Cubby.
I don't remember the, like,
if you pointed at the gummy bears and said,
describe this character, I don't think I could do.
Yeah, I am not good on my gummy character names.
No.
A lot of these names I was struggling with.
Yeah.
Not that I forgot this one,
but I gotta just give it up for Monterey Jack.
What a great joke.
That is a great nameslips joke.
I thought you were just giving up for the cheese in general.
No, I find, I like Monterey Jack.
I think I like it as a topping, but as a cheese,
like a sliced cheese, like I feel like it really,
it doesn't have enough oomph for me.
Interesting.
It's maybe, you know,
it's good in like a quesadilla, that kind of thing.
Perfect.
Where you don't get something like super strong, overwhelming.
Yeah, or the cracker has to be like extra flavorful
to balance it out.
But I for sure remember saying, Monterey Jack,
is this named after the character?
I thought it was the other way.
I am sure that was my introduction to the cheese.
I'm sure I did not know that name before.
And I think maybe my mom explained
that that was a funny joke.
And I'll go ahead and say, like,
I never really thought about Darkwing Duck
being like a parody of Batman.
I was like, well, there's Batman and there's Darkwing Duck
and they both gotta do their thing.
Like it wasn't.
As far as I knew, they both started last year.
Yeah.
These are new franchises for me.
I found the unproduced Darkwing Duck toys.
Oh my gosh, this liquidator.
This is like a trade magazine kind of thing.
And there's Quacker Jack.
Oh boy.
And I remember, yeah, just cause, yeah.
Wow.
Negaduck, there he is.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
And Gizmoduck.
Oh yes, Gizmo.
So yeah, I'm really glad I have this thing.
This is really neat.
I got all the stamps.
Fun to recall that these little kid activities
were pretty important as a kid.
We see them now and they don't matter to us,
us without children at the moment.
But the, you know, you,
this clearly meant a lot to me.
I had to collect them all.
I met so many characters.
I know I have pictures in front of a lot
of these storefronts and everything.
And I, this, I love this thing.
This thing was so cool.
To me it is like almost,
it's kind of the first Disneyland I remember
cause I went twice during this run.
And like, so it's probably the first time
I'm having memories that are still a little bit with me.
Right.
So to me, it was always gonna be Disney afternoon and avenue.
I was probably sad when I went
and they didn't have it anymore.
That really seems heartbreaking.
Yeah, yeah.
But Toontown was right around the bend.
Right.
And they kind of went straight from this into that.
There was a groundbreaking ceremony kind of as soon
as all of this stuff was out of the way.
Yeah, it's a nice transition, honestly,
like to prime kids for the cartoon world.
Yes.
And I think that Ballou's dressing room,
which was something that you could do
because there was a show called
We gotta talk about Ballou's dressing room.
Yeah.
Yes, yeah.
Well, then it hasn't been as good a time as any.
Ballou, you, there, you would go,
there was a big fake sound stage,
a kind of like pretty like huge building that they set up
despite it being temporary.
Yeah, impressive, like for a temporary thing.
Yeah, yeah, massive structure.
And you would go where today is the entrance of Toontown
under the train tracks.
And you would wait in line and you would get to go
into Ballou's dressing room where he was preparing
for the next performance of Playing Crazy.
And they used this as kind of a dry run
for the meeting Mickey, which was a more complex operation,
opened to Toontown a few years later
where there's multiple rooms.
And I think they'd never like done a concerted spot, really.
So let's give this a dry run.
How do we do this when it's not just the character comes out
and you take pictures willy nilly?
But it leaves us, yes, with Ballou's dressing room
or as one video I saw put it,
you can meet Ballou in Ballou's private dressing room.
Yeah, the weirdest, some of the weirdest phrasing for it too.
And for whatever reason,
I guess it's cause Mickey and Minnie have like
been in short shorts and you sort of think of them
as like the movie stars.
So it's not as weird when it's like Mickey's dressing room,
Ballou's private dressing room.
His private dressing room.
There's something odd about it.
There's a child on his lap in the commercial
and it's like what he's sitting.
This is cancelable now.
That's what I'm saying.
There's something weird going on here.
Ballou isn't a TV, like he's not a TV star in the world.
I think within this, he was preparing for performances
of playing crazy.
Right.
I think that was the justification.
Yeah, but I feel like I want a little more,
like why not meet him in his hanger?
Like Ballou's hanger or meeting him in the place
where all the pilots hang out.
Yeah, some little garage thing
would have been just as viable.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I think it got kids accustomed to the idea
of meeting a star in his private dressing room.
That's not- The thing that we don't know
should never have been done.
That's grooming behavior.
This is Ballou's grooming.
This might be like,
we were talking about Elvis before this.
Before I started.
And bear with me, cause this is kind of a journey.
But so Elvis- Bear with me,
can do little buddy.
No man.
So I was talking about like, there was a certain age
when I was a kid where I was like a little done
when cartoons, I was like, all right, yeah, Elvis.
Great.
Like enough with Elvis.
It's not funny to me.
I don't know about Elvis.
It's not, he's been dead for even, at the time I knew
like he's been dead for years.
Reference hammer, would you?
Something I know.
Yeah.
My guy.
But that, it does make sense to me
cause he was such a big like cultural reference point.
So it made sense.
They would reference Elvis back
when he hadn't been gone that long.
So at the time Ballou in his dressing room,
was that still close enough to old like,
you know, screwball comedies
where inevitably character would be high jinks
in a character's dressing room backstage
or on set or something.
I guess it just doesn't.
Where it was just like a location
where a scene would happen.
It wasn't necessarily seedy.
It was just like a setting.
My only thing is it doesn't make sense for the character.
If it's like Roger Rabbit,
that's like more of a show business property.
That makes sense.
Ballou though, especially, especially Tailspin Ballou
in his pilot's outfit.
We're already, he was in the jungle.
Now he's a pilot and now it's his dressing room.
And now it's his dressing room.
It's weird.
It doesn't make any sense.
And the commercial just is weird.
The commercials phrasing of it too is just strange.
It should just be the hanger of the air,
or like the break room or something.
They obviously, yeah, they were like,
we're gonna build the dressing room for Mickey and Minnie,
but like, let's put Ballou.
Is that the idea that they were like,
we're gonna, this is,
Ballou's gonna warm it up for Mickey and Minnie?
Yeah, I suppose so.
Come to my private gym, little buddy.
It's a little few steps removed.
Yeah, so I'm just saying character wise, yeah.
And I get it that he's in the show playing crazy,
but like, that's still.
That I think makes it fine.
He's, we know we're seeing Ballou in a play today.
Yeah.
That we're gonna go to his dressing room.
But the reality of, although playing crazy,
I would like to think is a real show
that's actually happening.
Yeah, I think that's actually happening.
Which to me as a child, I was recalling how I did.
I was, I feel like I somehow lived in a region
between I'm seeing a show at Disneyland and this is real.
Yes.
Like I knew it was people in suits,
and yet I was still kind of like, yeah,
but I don't trust fat cat.
Like, what's he gonna do?
How are you able to like still think some things are,
how can you be like percentages as a child?
I guess when you're still a former kid.
I think you can predict if the kid believes that hard
in the reality of like, we have to watch out for fat cat.
You can likely call it that that child will go
into the arts and entertainment industry.
If you're buying it that hard at that age.
Yeah.
It means you feel a little more than everybody else.
Yes, that and like, I would say a few years ago
if the kid is like, well, I gotta watch the special features
on the DVD, like have to figure out how they did this.
You know, that I feel like is a trait I,
for a lot of people I know gravitated towards
intensely believing the story and wanting to know
so badly how they did it.
Well, and also us both recalling, you know,
fondly recalling learning about time structures
of when our shows, our favorite shows were on.
Oh yeah, programming blocks.
Leads us perfectly to a future of like, okay,
so on Friday we got Jurassic World coming out,
but what do we have for next week?
It's all, it's, but it's also, I mean, there's,
I find that there's still a lot of problems
where I intellectually know something is real and right,
but my instincts or my emotions tell me I'm wrong.
Like, oh, some, some, I don't know what it is.
If it's a meeting or if like, even just like,
sometimes you're like traveling
and you're stressed out about that.
And you're like, it's gonna be fine.
Like it's gonna be two days.
You'll be a little tired.
You go back to bed, but your brain is like,
no, you should be scared of it.
It's gonna wreck you.
This is gonna be so bad.
Well, you run into travel mishaps
almost every time you go,
and it was so I could see why you'd be afraid.
Yeah, well, okay, so you're saying actually intellectually,
I shouldn't think that I should know
that something's gonna go wrong.
I should be 100% sure something bad will happen.
Did you, you're just back from a trip to Vegas.
Did hijinks happen?
No.
Okay, that's good.
Maybe I'm a little tired.
I wasn't really stressed about that,
but you know, Christmas time, especially,
I always get very stressed leading up to Christmas time.
It's snowy.
What are we gonna do with the dog?
Is it gonna be,
we're gonna circle the airport and the plane for an hour.
Like that's happened before.
So I'm just saying intellectually,
you go, well, whatever, it's fine.
You're gonna leave Edwin home alone?
No, we would never, but he would.
Edwin!
His two paws up to his snout.
No, we wouldn't do that.
But you know, I'm just saying like our brains do that.
But if there were like 18 other dogs around,
and there was one that from behind looked like Edwin.
We were carrying 18 different pet carriers,
and we only picked 17 up.
And there was one carrier left here, and it was Edwin.
We should say you have 17 other dogs,
and for some reason you only talk about Edwin.
Well, he's the favorite.
So the irony of leaving him home.
The rest is like a Jane Eyre situation.
The rest live in the attic, and we don't talk about them.
Yeah.
You're burning through dogs until you got a good one.
And here he is.
There he is, taking a nice nap.
And he's blinking, he's up.
He'll keep you updated.
He jumped to try and eat a bug earlier and scared me.
Scared the shit out of Jason, did you see that?
Really?
Yeah, he.
There was a little bug buzzing around,
and he jumped in the air a little bit,
and went, and like did a big bite down.
But Jason saw him.
But directly at me.
Jason thought he was coming at him
to take a big bite out of Jason.
And I could have, and I was like doing that,
I was fiddling with my phone at the time,
and I was like just turning it over in my hand,
and I'm like, he doesn't like that.
And I saw, I saw what was happening,
but you were like, your eyes were wide,
and I was like, no, no, it's fine.
I was just trying to figure out
how to make this symbol of a bug.
So I like put my thumb and index finger together,
and was trying to like make it fly,
to be like, no, it's a bug.
This is what a bug looks like.
My endorphins are still up from getting the bucket, okay?
Yeah, we have to, no, you're in a bucket-addled state.
It was like, boy, it's like Edwin was full of gummy juice.
He was like, Naughty Jason will be defeated.
The dog, Knight, shows no mercy.
That is the thing he thinks about Naughty Jason.
That's why I'm not allowed to watch him.
No mercy for Naughty Jason.
Another shirt, we've done three shirts today.
Cranking through them today.
No mercy for Naughty Jason.
So, I mean, is, well, you know what I'd like to play,
actually, while we're talking about Ballou
and Ballou's dressing room,
I have a couple good videos lit up,
and this, the song, the promo video announcing this thing
where they're really pushing the phrase live,
it's really important that Disney Afternoon is live.
I be live.
Come straight out of our cartoon show.
You can meet us, greet us, say hello.
Disney Afternoon, live, live at Disney Land.
We got pride, shows, dancing to the beat,
lots of adventures on a cartoon street.
DuckTales, gummy bears, Tailspin 2,
Rescue Rangers are here for you.
Disney Afternoon.
Wow.
That's perfect.
I love that so much.
That's like a...
Great time capsule.
Yeah, the video is so like blue screen,
zooming in and out to the brightest colors.
How all kids things, especially Nickelodeon,
why was everything that was like weird amorphous
kind of orb shapes and then like squiggles,
lots of like rotating squiggles.
That's what we like to see.
Yeah, like Clarissa explains it all
and Roundhouse, those logos had that.
Yeah.
You got at least 70 squiggles per frame
or kids lose interest.
So many squiggles.
Yeah, I would love if somebody,
is there a person that knows where that starts?
I'm always curious, like what started that trend?
Because something had to.
Is it like an interior design style
that is not coming to me,
that is sort of, I think where some of the,
it's where there's 80s and then there's super 80
when it got just like hyper, hyper colorful stylized
right at the end of the,
it's a little tackier,
but that definitely dove tails
into what Nickelodeon was playing with.
And it's not coming to me,
but there for sure is some...
There's like an art movement essentially,
or some style that it would be called something.
These playhouse, you would say.
Oh, okay.
Probably an early one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it's a little,
there's a little bit of a 50s air,
as there was a lot in a lot of Nickelodeon stuff,
there were always like 50s style dads and moms
telling us to eat meatloaf
and like lame things that parents do that we don't like.
Yeah, like a sweater vest dad with glasses or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And like mom dressed like June Cleaver
from Leave It to Beaver.
Like, yeah, like we're not this any,
we're not your parents' TV.
We're cool.
Do you recall the ago, Hi Honey, I'm home.
I am, yes, yes I do.
80s, more Roseanne family lives next door to a 50s,
like literally out of the TV family.
A show that I really didn't get at the time.
But in hindsight I go, I don't know if it's good or not,
but in hindsight I go.
I've given it a watch recently, I might vote no.
Okay, kind of a funny idea though.
Kind of like Pleasantville, Pleasantville,
Pleasantville, kind of similar premise.
90s people going to 50s.
That's absolutely right.
That was, I alluded to earlier, that is, it was not,
I thought you were gonna, when you pulled out the map,
I thought you were gonna play a different promo.
Oh, okay.
Did you find that one?
Did you find the Mary-Kate and Ashley promo?
I don't have it ready to go.
I don't either.
It's a nightmare, it's crazy.
Yeah, should I find it?
Find it, it's long.
You know, let me tell you why I didn't bring a clip of it.
Because, yeah, so Mary-Kate and Ashley are on a school bus
and the school bus is going to Disney Afternoon Avenue
where they get out and dance with all the characters.
And it is so hyperactive.
And my guess is that why that is the case
is that Mary-Kate and Ashley were having
like a meltdown that day.
Because they're barely in it.
And you gotta, and you're watching it
remembering more so than Full House
where they're, that's what they know how to do.
They're there every day.
This, like them out in the wild,
probably in a hot day in a theme park,
they were, I bet they like broke down into tears.
Because they're like five, they're so young.
It does seem like chaos.
This video is chaos.
I've never seen so many edits in like two minutes,
40 seconds.
The bus, I thought was just like,
oh, that bus isn't in Disneyland.
And then there's a shot where it looks like the bus
driving into like next to the Matterhorn.
And I'm like, did they drive a bus through Disneyland?
But the big thing for me is that Mary-Kate and Ashley
still would have been young enough
and Full House early enough in its run
that they were not exactly at the age
where they could enunciate.
And I feel like on Full House,
they gave them punch lines that were two to three words.
And in this video, they're trying to get them to say like,
I can't wait to go down to Disney after now.
And it just sounds like gibberish.
Is it Mary-Kate and Ashley, oh sorry,
Olsen bomb afternoon avenue?
Yeah, yeah.
That's the one?
I'll warn you, there's a reason I didn't pull it.
It's a, you will hear hissy video
of unintelligible five-year-olds.
It's 45 seconds.
Go to like the second half, essentially.
There's a longer version.
That's where you'll hear them attempt to explain,
you don't know what does not happen on the avenue
as in you're not really a kid.
Next stop, afternoon avenue.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is rad.
What is it?
You call yourself a kid?
Radical.
Let's take these kids in and show them.
That's a big 10-4, good buddy.
Let's go.
Let's take these kids in.
10.
There is.
That's a good 10-4, buddy.
One of the funniest things about the Olsen twins
is how bad of actors they were.
Yeah.
They were just really bad kid actors.
They were chosen without ever thinking
they would need to do lines,
much less need to do many, many series of videos
and their own shows and film.
It's amazing where they came.
An empire.
It's amazing that they are billionaires, sure.
Billionaires before they were 18,
or at least millionaire.
And the dignity that they have
by not appearing on Fuller House.
They deserve a lot of credit
for not even being remotely tempted.
We don't need it.
For child actors, I think have had a pretty good,
I mean, they had a little socialite age.
Yeah, they had some socialite year,
but I feel like they calmed down.
They're not the best.
There's some darkness.
There's some darkness, but there's not the most darkness.
You know what's the most darkness with them
is when they hosted Saturday Night Live
and then at the, in the good nights, and this is real,
they say, all right, we had a great time hosting the show.
Thanks to the cast.
And hey, guess what?
In 48 hours, we're legal.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
What a nightmare.
Two weeks after the episode where Lindsay Lohan hosted
and it was entirely about her, like,
look how big her boobs are.
And she was not 18. Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
2004, a different time.
That's dark.
The Heath Ledger overdosing in the apartment
is also pretty dark.
One of the Olsen twins apartments, I believe.
I'll double check this.
I'll cut this out if that's wrong,
but I'm pretty sure that's right.
The version of that promo I was referencing.
Patreon.
The version I was referencing is three minutes, 43 seconds.
Oh God, no, we don't need that.
The dialogue's out the door.
Is there a out the door?
There is a quick, you got it, dude.
Yeah.
Their catchphrase.
The catchphrase.
Four year olds with a catchphrase.
It's pretty insane.
And then there's clearly like professionally
trained child dancers doing the heavy lifting.
I think one of them might be one of the Maori twins, oddly.
Yes, yes, yes.
That does match up.
Okay, yeah.
I don't know which.
Match up of the beloved sitcom twins of the 90s.
But yeah, and they kind of stop appearing in it
and there's like one shot of one of them
looking really upset driving the utopia around.
Like I bet it was like,
we got the Olsen twins booked
and they're gonna carry it and it'll be,
and then as soon as the reality filming with,
and both of them, there's a reason why
they traded on and off.
Because when one got upset, you bring in the other.
Well yeah, and also you only have so many hours
and then you have to do classes, you have to do schooling
and then you gotta get them out of there.
So it's a wonder that they were able to like
turn around and act up a storm in things like
something we should probably cover,
the Mary Kate and Ashley mysteries
where they investigate a mystery at Sea World.
I know, yeah. Sure.
We'll be doing that.
That's fine.
I thought you were gonna say every single one
of their directed DHS movies.
Well yeah, so you got mysteries and you got party.
They had two series, both produced by
Dual Star Entertainment.
Is Dual Star still making anything?
I'm not sure.
Have you had a general at Dual Star lately?
Yeah I know, I should see if I can get a general
at Dual Star.
You know, we're just really looking to expand
beyond the twin brands, like you know,
doing stuff about just single people.
There's skeletons in the Dual Star archive.
Oh my god.
Metaphorical and literal probably.
Dual Star, I only can get a general with Dual Star Digital.
Their streaming platform.
Their streaming platform that only plays on Fitbit.
Yes, and only you can see it on Fitbit.
The four by three.
It's in only two colors.
Yeah, but that's the way people actually
wanna consume content.
That's what they've actually discovered through marketing
and questionnaires.
We're all consuming content on our wrists, constantly.
But we believe it can be more than the number of steps
you've taken that day or how fast your heart's beating.
We can tell a story.
Honestly, just put the website up with that quote on it
and people will, you'll get like inquiries probably.
Now we're gonna get your heart beating
with our compelling storytelling.
Put it on the website and you'll probably get meetings
with the writers, like you can pretend.
This is simultaneously a joke and the reality we live in
and this is all happening hours after I read the story
of like live action Mulan stars comments spike boycott
from Hong Kong protesters.
And I'm like, oh god.
The Disney live action remakes
are affecting geopolitical events.
What is going on?
What a time.
Oh boy.
But this, see that's what I'm saying.
The 90s.
The more just fun and innocent.
With stuff like, I don't think, I saw a promo
that explained everything you could do
at Disneyland afternoon Avenue.
And I think I forgot that there was a arcade
that was outdoors in sort of a little like Glen,
little gummy Glen area.
And it sort of utilizes the aesthetic of Videopolis,
which made me really happy to see more of that.
The Videopolis stage still there.
The Videopolis train station still there.
Although turned into.
They did a redo for this.
They were calling it the Disney afternoon train station.
But yeah, it was still Videopolis.
They temporarily sadly changed the name of the little cafe
from Yums with a Z to Louie's.
That's fun too.
But there was an outdoor arcade
and look at this logo Videocade.
Oh, music to my eyes.
That logo, the multiple fonts.
You got some neon on there.
Presented by Capcom.
And that was a way that Disney could feature
the then new Capcom video games
for Chip and Dale Duck Tales and Tailspin.
Perfect.
I have a quick little clip from one of those.
This news report that I watched about a kid who,
it was a news report from Portland, I believe.
Portland native who won his local semi-finals
of the Capcom Videocade contest
to go play in the finals at Disneyland
that he would eventually win, I believe.
Wow. Impressive.
But this little clip explaining the goals
of these several games.
In Chip and Dale Rescue Rangers,
players try to collect the most flowers.
In Tailspin, getting the most points is crucial.
While the game Duck Tales challenges kids
to collect the most money.
Just...
I said that.
In Chip and Dale, it is flowers.
In Chip and Dale, you would jump on top of objects
and pick them up and throw them at the bad guys.
You would jump on top of an apple
and throw a giant apple at someone.
It was fun.
Apple's also affected into the Aladdin video game,
which I was making.
Oh yeah, the Genesis one.
Yeah, that was kind of what,
he had the little counter of apples.
Yes, you kept collecting apples.
He's so hungry, but he has to use them to protect himself.
A precursor to Jar Jar Binks.
Oh, sure.
With the lust for apples.
I just bought the Disney,
there was a Disney afternoon collection.
It was not the remastered Duck Tales,
but for like four or five dollars on PS4,
I got Duck Tales, Darkwing Duck,
Tailspin and Rescue Rangers.
All these games?
All the original, yeah.
Eight-bit games.
Huh, huh.
Well, now you know when you play it,
if you're playing Tailspin, points are key.
Points. Got it.
Not, stay away from flowers.
Right, no flowers.
Blue doesn't care about flowers.
And Duck Tales is what, money?
Money. Money.
Getting the most money is key.
Uh-huh.
Those games, I only own Darkwing Duck Game as a child.
That was good.
I think I did too.
But I didn't have the other ones,
and we would rent them,
and we would go to like the pharmacy far more.
And I would just be,
because they never had the good games at like Blockbuster.
They'd always be out of them.
And Far More, which quickly went out of business
is my recollection.
And-
They would rent games?
They would rent games.
It was in one Schomburg place,
which is an offshoot mall of Woodfield.
That only lasted for-
Oh, my friend, just explain this to me
that there was a second, there was an adjacent.
And now it's called Streets of Woodfield, it's outdoors.
It's good, it's good.
There's a Game Works, a movie theater, fine.
But Streets of Woodfield was where it's at.
They had, was it was the child?
I'm trying to think of,
there's another toy store in there
that was totally new to me,
which is where I got several Darkwing Duck toys.
And that place was fantastic.
Where'd you get your videos as a kid?
You were Far More-
Well, not all-
Video games or Far More.
I could count on Far More having the games like DuckTales
that I wanted to rent.
But Family Video was the place we would go to,
which is still there.
Family Video's still open.
Fantastic.
Okay, First Memory is a very small,
it was a chain, West Coast video.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And then it was a big deal
when the one borough in my town got a big blockbuster.
And that was, we would stop a lot after church,
because it was on the way to and from church.
So we would run in afterwards
and then get stuff for a few days.
Or if we picked it up on Friday night,
then we'd probably be returning it on Sunday a lot of time.
Cool, cool.
Not a lot of time too.
You really had a timer to watch and play stuff
for those first few years of like two day rentals
at Blockbuster.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I would try to blast through a game in two days.
Jeez.
Video Take One was mine.
Video Take One.
A lot of fondness for that name, yeah.
And much better than Blockbuster.
And had weird garbage,
they have an Italian sex comedy that I rented as a teen
that I'm still really fond of called The Sex Machine.
That's about a world where all energy has been depleted
and a scientist uses the power of sex to,
and it's the future of 1999.
And it's a weird, it's like much like the 70s,
except everybody just,
they decided everybody wears ponchos in this future.
That's actually a documentary.
Italy is powered entirely by Eros, by sexual energy.
Wow.
Gave him the idea.
I wonder if it's based on Lindsay and I watched
and there's two of these,
Dr. Goldfoot and the Bikini Machine,
a Vincent Price movie from the 60s, I believe.
Yeah, you would put that on sometimes, years ago.
Yeah, so it's a weird movie where Vincent Price
like makes women in a machine, I think.
But there's two of them.
It's like Return of Gold, I forget what the second one is.
For sure what Vincent Price would want.
Yes, 100%.
Beautiful women.
Yes, he loved the women.
Bikinis as skimpy as possible.
We had a number of video store,
after Blockbuster, a few years after Blockbuster,
competition showed up and it was called Movies.
And then the cow,
Whoa!
There was a cow mascot.
And then eventually something happened,
I think got merged with another company
and it changed to the much less interesting name,
Video Update.
And then that got absorbed by Hollywood Video,
Blockbuster's big competitor.
Right, we had Hollywood Video.
Went out of business first, I think.
Yeah.
So we were mostly, yeah, family, I'm trying to think.
We had Hollywood Video too, that for a little while,
it was a short-lived, I feel like, Hollywood Video.
I could be wrong.
My mom will, this is the type of thing my mom will call
and tell me about.
She won't be like,
you know what, that was a really funny episode or anything.
She'll just be like, Hollywood Video lasted for 10 years.
She'll say that and then she'll be like,
your voice sounded good, you enunciate very well.
Does she critique your performance?
Only when it comes to,
Yes, exclusively.
Only when it, yeah, when it comes to enunciation,
getting facts right.
Whoa.
And like the quality, but she will be like,
you know, you have a very nice,
she'll say, you all have a very nice voice,
you have a very nice speaking voice,
but it's never like, oh, that was funny or entertaining.
She's just like listening, wanting to grade me,
I think on like the basics of it,
just tone quality, accuracy.
Any other like hiccups that have come up?
Well, she, I'm trying to think,
she will, I'm trying to think she'll correct like a word.
She'll say like, you know,
I don't think you use that word correctly.
I'm trying to think of exactly what that, yeah.
I'm trying to think, I can't think of a good example.
She thinks that I,
my story that I told a couple months ago
was that on Snow White, I said my eyes are shut too tight.
She claims it's toad that I said it on,
and then we went on toad first.
But my memory in my head and could be mixing stuff up
is that I saw the witch right around the same time
I said that, but I could be missing.
So that's the type of thing I'm saying.
She'll like, maybe she recalls
that the family vacation went differently.
And then she'll also like,
and my dad will lightly complain about me acting like
I ruined their child, the right,
they ruined my childhood by depriving me of things.
Oh, so let's get that out there.
Like, I don't think they like when I, yeah.
They don't think they like that when I say like,
I thought I would never go to California.
Like there was no way.
That doesn't seem like an indictment of them.
That seems like it like, oh, you were a very neurotic child.
Yeah.
You were already war children clearly.
Yeah, I'm not trying to indict them,
but I do think it was like, we go one place,
we go there every three years and that's it.
There's just a rigidity.
Now she's going to be mad at me for saying that we're wrong.
Well, there's a routine, you know.
You're doing a dance between them and us and the audience.
Yeah.
You're in a corner now.
I just think like-
Consistency, repeatability, traditions.
It's comforting for them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The box wasn't opened a lot is all I was saying.
And I don't, that's not a, I'm not really trying to cry.
I'm just, look, I'm making fun light
of my childhood for content.
Sure, you're exaggerating.
Yeah.
Aspects of it for comedic effect.
Yeah, sure I am.
Got it.
That's-
I'm exaggerating all of it.
Let me ask this, what does your mom think of Bugsy?
Uh, my mom has never mentioned Bugsy.
I'd like to get that report.
I don't know if she's actually heard the first one.
And I don't know the live,
I don't know if she heard the live episode.
I assume she did.
My dad likes Bugsy.
I know that.
I know my dad likes Bugsy.
Mm-hmm.
I know he said he almost spit out his drink
during the first one on a certain line.
And you can guess which line that was.
So yeah.
Fill his mouth with jewels instead.
This is, well, I want to avoid these kinds of pitfalls.
And that's why I'll stay in the world
where my parents do not get a smartphone
and thus do not listen to this podcast.
What a luxury.
Yeah, it's a little bit,
I don't know why I'm wanting them to get one.
Have you been pushing for it?
Other than that, I think they, you know,
there's a way to get around town
that isn't the Thomas Guide.
Oh wow, really?
When I came out here for college,
for like that semester in college,
they were like, very first thing you have to do,
get a bank account at the Bank of America down the street
and second, get a Thomas Guide.
Yeah.
I have it.
Yeah, I got my Thomas Guide.
When we moved, when we were on one,
we would have moved out here,
which is a decade, over a decade ago.
I had a map and then like when I was doing runs
for the CW network, I had to go to MapQuest
and I printed out where I was going.
Sure, but that was, we all did that to some extent.
I just, my parents still do this.
Well, no, that's wild.
Yeah, and they just like drove up the coast and back
that way and not with a...
Well, that one I understand,
coast only goes one to two ways.
Hey, good point.
Yeah, that's a simpler one.
North or south.
Up or down, yeah.
Ocean left.
Don't need no phone to help you with that.
Yeah, interesting.
Okay, we gotta get back to this thing.
I don't, you know, I don't have much to say about
the cruise to Gummy Glen or Rescue Rangers Raceway
because these are not documented.
Not documented.
Yeah, I know, that's sad.
Yeah, I wish they were more.
I ended up finding some photos
of motorboat cruise to Gummy Glen.
This was a, motorboat cruise is a pretty nothing ride.
So to add, that was a big plus up to have like anything.
But still it was essentially, you know, wooden cutouts.
But still fun little scenarios.
A nothing ride but a three hour episode.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is this the picture?
I don't think I've seen that one.
That's a motorboat and it's just like, there's a flat.
It's very flat and it's like kind of nothing.
Yeah, but to me as a kid, not having a level
that I was seeking to hit yet and being too, you know,
it's six, I'm not going on the coasters or anything.
Like this was super thrilling.
I loved it all.
And also, the motorboat cruise to Gummy Glen,
a ride where you see bears make berries into products,
oddly akin to Knott's Berry Tales.
Yeah. Yeah.
A while back.
Kind of a cousin of that.
Industrious creatures, business minded folk.
I wonder if Michael Eisner ever went on Berry Tales.
Maybe.
Like I wonder if that was in his head with the gummy bears.
Like, you know, Disney can do this better, more efficiently.
With wood and not.
Right.
I'm trying to spike that hippie Raleigh Crump.
There's some really great,
there's a blog with some like great pictures of like,
dad, a dad and I don't know whose dad this is,
but a dad, a child and launch pad.
Like just perfect 90s photos.
Do you have, Scott, do you have any photos of you
as a little kid with the characters?
I do.
I haven't had a chance to dig around for them,
but I for sure do.
Yesterland had this great picture of,
what are the guys from, what are these guys named?
The Beagle Boys.
The Beagle Boys, yes.
Beagle.
The Beagle Boys.
And next to him.
I'm not C.H. Jason.
The next to him.
Your mom's gonna be mad at you.
Is a guy just a.
Oh, that's a great picture too.
There's a couple of guys, it's just a guy,
but it's just, they just look like a couple of kings.
They just both look like they're on top of the world.
Couple of kings.
Couple of kings, a Beagle Boy and then a dad.
There's an inherently like visual quality to this stuff
that makes it a little challenging to talk about
on a podcast, but it's so, if anybody didn't get to go
and you look at pictures of this,
so you'll be instantly jealous you didn't get to go.
Yeah, they.
Just so bright and vibrant in the, all the 90s,
it was the most 90s thing Disneyland had done,
or it's still pretty new into the 90s.
Yeah, the pictures do a good job.
I do have to call out, a couple places did this.
I don't know why we were talking earlier about
like weird language in terms of Ballou's dressing room.
Weird language again, the fandom page for this event
describes it as, here's the attraction that celebrates
Disney's successful entry into
afternoon syndicated television,
which is the driest way to describe it.
But then on yesterland, the, for advice has the same,
the park is celebrating Disney's successful entry
into afternoon syndicated television.
So maybe that was just the press release, but.
Like kids TV, I would have just said like afternoon,
kids TV, like.
Resistant, resistant affiliates will be defeated.
The Disney nights show no mercy.
Yeah, it's very stiff.
It's very formal.
Yeah, I know that's not what it is.
It's where the kids get to bounce with the gummies,
with Zummy.
You know, this is a little, this is certainly a side note.
I just remembered, I should have brought this up earlier.
I didn't think about this, but on tailspin,
let me read the characters names to you.
Yes.
These are just the first five that pop up.
And then no particular order,
even though yes it is in an order.
Ballou, Don Carnage.
Yeah.
Kit Cloud Kicker.
Wildcat, Rebecca Cunningham.
Do you see something here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is the Helen test.
Yeah.
It's back.
The female character has a less fun name
than the male characters.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, we just got an email that was proposing that
via Claire Dearing, of course, from Jurassic World,
her theory was that Claire is the new, like,
boring name meant to be, like, apparently thoughtful.
Let me find this email really quick.
I saw this too, and I get the theory.
Sean Urie sent it.
I get the theory behind it, but the examples they gave
stretched over a 30 year period.
So not exactly perfect,
but you might be onto something, Sean.
Like, let me read the other names.
I'm just going down the list.
Ballou, Louie, Don Carnage, Kit Cloud Kicker,
Wildcat, Mad Dog, Dump Truck,
Cher Khan, Colonel Ivanod Spigot,
Sergeant Dunder, Colonel Grog, Ice Cream Man,
Barney O'Turrett, Buzz, and then the two female characters,
Rebecca Cunningham and Molly Cunningham.
Yep, I think this is a Helen Tess scenario.
I think this is for sure a Helen Tess scenario.
And those characters do not appear in Plain Crazy.
Right.
Yep.
Yes, they're walk-around characters, though, I believe, right?
Or what Rebecca is?
Yeah, I believe I had a picture with Rebecca.
I think I liked Rebecca a lot
because she reminded me of my mom.
She seems like a figure I could trust, like my mom.
I get that.
If I was in trouble, I would turn to Rebecca.
This happened to-
Rebecca Cunningham.
Famously an X-Men, of course.
I mean, she's had code names, but it was all, you know,
in the 90s, I always thought, oh, Cyclops Beast,
Wolverine, Jean Grey.
They would just call her Jean Grey.
I wrote something- They switched though,
because it was-
She was Phoenix and Marvel Girl
and all of these other things.
Marvel Girl, much better, obviously.
But yeah, the 90s, she was Jean Grey.
And then they started calling her Phoenix again.
I wrote something once with superheroes,
where everyone has a cool nickname,
and then there's just a guy named Eric Henderson.
So I gender-squat-ed him, but that was my refer,
that was my nod to the weird,
when there's just a weird full name person.
You know who this test does not apply to
is Gadget of Chip and Dale.
Until researching this episode,
I didn't know Gadget's last name.
Do you guys know?
Oh, I don't.
Gadget Hackwrench.
That's good.
Hell yeah.
That is good, yeah, thank God that works.
I don't think that's even in my brain.
Yeah, I don't recall that ever being said.
Yeah, maybe I would have known on a very specific day
as a seven-year-old, but not now.
One odd thing about Gadget's presence
in Disney Afternoon Avenue,
here's a photo of regular Gadget, you know,
bright, wide-eyed.
Did you notice Gadget?
Oh, I did notice Gadget.
Her eyelids are half down.
Aaron said it looks like she's on Quaaludes.
She seems really sedated.
I don't know what's wrong with Park Gadget.
Yeah, I mean, it could be anything.
But Gadget, one of the only characters
from Disney Afternoon that still has a ride.
Yeah.
One of the only pieces of representation, you're right.
Aside from, I mean, the goof troop occasional presence
feels way more about a goofy movie.
Yes, for sure.
It feels separate to me.
Yeah, you're right.
Gadget stuck around, and you get the Gadget instructions
before you take off, the great Trish MacNeil.
You know, the voice actors,
and there's been weirdness with Jim Cummings
in the respect, but I think we can say Jim Cummings.
Holy shit, he's all the voice actors.
He's everybody, yeah.
We're talking about, and within the Plane Crazy show,
he's Don Carnage and Fat Cat and Louie.
Right.
Same.
Plane Crazy and interesting, like,
the name of it is a nod to the first Mickey short,
but it, and it does have planes in it,
but that's such like an odd postmodern,
like it's called Plane Crazy.
Oh yeah, like first, but it's not related
to that first Mickey short at all.
It's just a reference.
Just a reference without any significance, besides planes.
Yeah.
But the show is a lot of fun.
Did you guys watch our performance of Plane Crazy?
Like I said, it was somewhat terrifying to me
to be in that close of proximity to Fat Cat.
Were you more scared of Don Carnage or Fat Cat?
I think Don Carnage.
I'm not sure.
Fat Cat's bringing in my head more
as the one to be scared of.
Right.
Don Carnage seemed like goofier to me in a way.
He's, so he's like a, he's a Fernando,
he's a Billy Crystal Fernando-esque character for sure.
My mom tried to give me the history of Fernando.
That happened once when I was like, yeah, he didn't.
She like told me the actor she thinks that's based on.
Is it Fernando Lamas?
Yeah, I think.
And she's like, oh, you know, that's,
you were talking about that
and I think you were looking for Fernando Lamas.
I was like, oh, okay.
We like, we didn't understand what Fernando was all about.
Right, I think we were just like,
you know, when you would say it every week,
I think we were sort of just like kind of goofing on,
is that actually that funny for the most part?
Like, do people really like,
I think they actually did really like it.
But anyway, yeah, that was the gist.
Anyway, that struck my memory.
So, Playing Crazy is a tale where all of the characters
come together to solve a US government problem.
Seems that they get recruited by the Air Force
or the FBI and Air Force themed attire.
Well, and it's the whatever agency it is,
they're in like the biggest shoulder padded outfit,
seemingly possible.
Yes, and there's like some original music.
Yeah, I think Monkey C, Monkey D is a jam.
Yeah, it's pretty good.
I wish there was, that's one that's like not like
saved anywhere.
I mean, there's a lot of stuff from live shows
that aren't saved, like,
because there's some decent archives
or there's some decent collections of park music
and a little obscure park music, but nothing, this stuff,
I wonder if there's even a good recording of this somewhere.
Like did they ever film it pro?
Well, that for sure, but like at least just the audio,
like the demo of it, like does that stuff exist?
Like that would be an archive collection
I would be very interested in.
Yeah.
It's like all the different lives, live shows,
the demos of the live shows.
Yeah, when I hear Disney demos.
Yeah, well, there's all those versions
of Universe of Energy that we found
and like one does sound like a demo and I don't know,
maybe that was actually played in the exit queue,
but like there's three different versions
and I'm not sure where they all are placed
in the history of the ride, but yeah, there's never.
When we're digging through Disney demo bootlegs.
The show's gonna get really good.
Then we're gonna be very engaged.
Tapiss here, you can see they haven't quite
cracked the bridge yet, but.
That seems like it's the inevitable transformation
of this just becoming a prog rock podcast.
That's where it's slowly heading.
It slowly becomes.
We'll lose you at some point, you just drift away.
Start a far more successful tree based podcast.
But somehow I still get my share of money.
I'm like the manager.
Like I've created some sort of insane contract.
You've made it clear.
I'm not here, but it is called Jason Sheridan's podcast.
It seems odd that we would agree to that, but okay.
We already signed some contract we don't know about
where this is inevitable.
You tricked us like Ursula.
I was gonna say it's like Ursula's contract.
I knew when you brought your eel friends around.
Those guys are cool, they're just fans.
They're just fans, I assure you.
Super cool guys.
You met them at an estate sale.
You met them at Josef Kahn's estate sale.
I met them at Ursula's estate sale.
Show some respect.
That bucket had a soul in it once.
Until she dumped it out, flushed it down the toilet.
You could probably buy some souls at her estate sale.
Yeah.
Souls that she took.
Does Ursula do that sometimes?
She runs out of jars and like, fuck it.
Whatever's around.
A diet Pepsi bottle.
Feeds them to flotsam and jetsam.
Here you go, boys.
The plot of the plane crazy is that Don Carnage
and Fat Cat have stolen the X-22 spy plane.
It's an experimental plane and they shrunk it.
They shrunk a jet and Baloo and Chip and Dale
someone else have to get them back.
Who else, who's in the show?
Louie shows up at some point.
There's no women in the show.
Gummy bears, yeah, there's no female characters.
Except the Baloo and Chip and Dale wear hula skirts
and that's as close as you get to a female character.
Which they do in the opening to the show.
Yes.
That's a thing, that's a setup.
So they're using that.
So you would identify that as,
oh, I know where that's from.
Yeah, yeah.
And Don Carnage and Fat Cat are tricked by this.
Right, yes.
Baloo does not alter his face in any way
nor did Chip and Dale.
Cause in the opening they put like a,
he puts like a coconut over his face to obscure it
I think when they're in disguise
but they don't, they didn't have the budget for that.
No, no, no, no, to get a coconut mask.
So the main, the heroes who the villains are obsessed
with thwarting, they don't recognize them
once they put on a skirt.
Yeah. Right.
I'm just clarifying.
Just making sure I'm not getting any details.
It's also the logic, like they're gonna take all the cookies
in the world.
This is a real crisis and then all the heroes come out
and just sing about friendship.
You think they'd be a little more pressed.
Yeah.
You're a little bit upset that you don't feel
that they're urgency in that problem.
I don't think they're treating the espionage angle
with enough seriousness.
Right.
I was thinking how if some foreign entity,
if Iran shrunk a US plane, that would be plenty
for us to go to war with them.
Yes, right.
That's absolutely enough of a hostile act.
Yeah, for sure.
We shrunk a plane, you can unshrink it with water
but no, who cares, bomb them, they're done, bomb them.
Yes, that is probably what would happen.
Well, until it's discovered a day later that it's like,
oh, actually it was the CIA who shrunk,
a bumbling CIA agent shrunk the plane.
Who cares, close enough, come on.
We haven't done a war in so long.
It's time.
So antsy.
What would John Bolton have done
if he was in the playing crazy show?
John Bolton does look like a cartoon stunt show villain.
Yeah, for sure he does.
Yeah, he really, I'm trying to think which one,
which of the Disney afternoon cartoons John Bolton
would fit right in with.
I wanna say- Come along, Chippendale.
John Bolton's got a mission for us.
I was gonna say, I feel like he's more of a DuckTales villain.
Yeah.
Maybe, I don't know why that is.
Maybe just because of like the, he's not that he's wealthy
or maybe he probably is honestly wealthy.
His name was John Beakton, then yes.
John Beakton, he helps get the Beagle Boys out of prison
in one episode and not Mob Beagle.
He's married to Mob Beagle?
That's a good way to get him in, yeah.
Did Mob Beagle ever have a husband?
One of, I'm not sure.
So yeah, sure, yeah, why not?
Yeah.
Yeah, so it's John Bolton.
Cause like the Beagle Boys were all supposedly
Mob Beagle's kids, I believe.
Or she just was the gang leader and she called them her boys
and she'd always like put a nail, like a file into the cake
to get them out of prison.
Cause they were always locked up.
Yeah.
So they're extradited and one of them ends up in the cabinet.
Yes.
John Bolton may be like their stepfather.
The Beagle Boys' stepfather.
So yeah, then like later they all,
they're all in a Republican administration.
Webby is killed, Trump speaks at the funeral
and gets her name wrong.
Wendy, everybody loved Wendy.
We love Wendy.
Isabella Gray, everybody loved her.
Very real tragedy, her inducted in the town name wrong.
Merging the Trump-iverse with the Duck-iverse.
Sure, no, it all, look, it also was seamless, I think,
for our listeners.
When they're fired.
The sloppy Beagle Boys.
Sloppy Mob Beagle and her sloppy boys.
Pathetic.
The Clintons killed Webby.
Nothing to do with it.
Oh, now we gotta have fan art with John Bolton
and the Beagle Boys.
It's really the leader they always needed.
Yeah.
They can get a lot more done.
So there's, I don't know, a plane shrinks,
which makes it confusing when another plane goes by.
Is it that plane that they chase it that goes by on a wire
and then, no, no, no, that's supposed to be the plane
that our heroes are in, I think.
And then it goes behind a wall.
A plane on a wire flies over the audience
and then crash lands, a bunch of noise,
a bunch of smoke shoots up.
To me, that was the most violent thing
I'd ever seen at age six.
Still scary to me.
And then all the characters come back out
and I like this, they're all bandaged up
and they have like flies or birds, birdies on strings,
on their heads.
That is great.
That's a fun cartoon thing that they brought to the stage.
Yeah, I think this show is a lot of fun.
This might be one of the best shows ever performed
at that Fantasyland stage.
Yeah, I need to see the full history,
but yeah, I think this seemed a lot of fun.
Again, I was hoping there was like a soundboard recording.
Somebody have a bootleg out there of this show?
I mean, the full show's on YouTube.
It's just, you're just saying it's a little grainy.
Crisp audio quality.
You want the crisp.
I want to enjoy, yeah, the jam.
You want the Videopolis vault to be opened.
Yes, that is what I want.
Let's get some remixes of Monkey C, Monkey Do.
Oh my gosh, yes.
Well, like on that deconstructed album
that I love, hate so much,
with the Pineapple Princess remix,
I want some Monkey C, Monkey Do, like DJ remixes.
Multiples, please.
Who's who?
Yeah, Marshmello.
I was gonna say, who's my, Jason knows, he knows DJs.
Before he passed, Avicii did finish a remix
of Monkey C, Monkey Do.
Okay, well that's good.
And that's, I feel like you maybe don't know so many DJs.
I don't know any.
I was, but more than we are.
Yeah.
Dead Mouse.
Dead Mouse, there we go.
Zed, yes.
Yeah.
We were in Las Vegas and I'm trying to think.
Calvin Harris.
Calvin Harris, there you go.
Oh, Steve Aoki.
There you go.
The Pizza Maven.
Yeah, I feel like all of these references are still like,
if anyone's into this, they'd be like,
those are five year old references.
They are definitely five years.
Five to 10 years old.
This is the situation.
Shaq.
Shaq was DJing at Allapalooza.
Yeah, yeah, they're all DJs.
He's a DJ.
All right, well somebody you'll find out.
Idris Elba.
I know I heard, was it Coachella he was DJing?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's real.
DJ Idris Elba.
Sick.
I'm not sick.
So you go to Louie's.
There's a, you see Louie in the Louettes.
The Louettes are Chip and Dale and Blue.
There's a performance of Monkey See Monkey Do.
Then there's, things come to a head and
you've been given earlier the secret of,
Don Carnage slips and says that the way to make
the spy plane big again is with water.
So it's clear you're supposed to retain
this information for later.
And Blue then asks you, well gang,
how do we make the plane bigger?
Everybody yells water.
Then I can't tell what happens.
Then confetti pours and steam.
I don't see it.
No, I don't even know if any water factors in.
It's just to indicate action.
Yeah.
It's just to make you go, oh something happened.
Not specifically what, but just something happened.
Yeah, yeah.
And then a plane inflates in front of you
and that's the show.
So many inflatables.
In the whole land.
And I feel like there aren't, I'm trying to think
what's the most modern use of inflatables in Disneyland?
I say take it easy on the screens for a few years.
Bring back the inflatables.
I agree with that.
Yeah.
Is there still the balloon atop Muppet Vision 3D?
Hmm.
Florida.
I don't think usually.
I don't know.
I don't think so, but maybe.
But nothing in Disneyland that's inflatable.
And there's not that, you know what's an episode some days
that Mickey hot air balloon.
At Disney Springs.
No, I mean sure yes.
The one from the commercials.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, I think it was called,
was it called like the Air Force One or something?
Or was that a plane?
I feel like that was a plane that I could totally be wrong.
I don't know about that.
But I know what you're talking about.
Is it acceptable to merge all of the Mickey aircraft
into one episode or do they have to?
Do they have to be their own episode?
Yes, they do I think, but maybe.
We'll see, we'll see.
I know it's always thin ice to propose.
Yeah, separating any topic is thin ice.
I know what the answer will be.
Who knows who's the state sale I will go to next, Scott?
We gotta talk about that too.
We need monthly updates now.
That's your solo podcast is the state sale.
Oh, estate sale.
Oh my gosh.
Estate raiders with Jason Sheridan.
I was out of town for Rosemarie's estate sale,
which I believe Eva Anderson went to.
Rosemarie from the Dick Van Dyke show
who passed away two years ago maybe.
But I would have gone to that.
It was in the Valley, it's not far from here.
I would have gotten a tiny little bucket
for $10 if Rosemarie owned it.
Yeah, we just are getting all the DeadStars buckets.
Collect them all like the stamps
at Disney afternoon avenue.
I feel like we've been talking for seven hours.
Very possible.
Yeah, that's about the pace that it's at.
What have we missed?
Any?
Well, Duckburg, City Hall and Scrooge's Vault,
those were little flats you could go stand.
You would meet Scrooge, I would assume.
It was special to me as a child
to be in a little tiny town, size, to my size.
Yeah.
It was wonderful.
I will cherish this.
It was to not be infantilized by adult heights.
Sure.
It was a wonderful feeling.
I relate, brother.
I'm still infantilized by adult heights.
You need tiny towns this day.
I think when, it was a couple years ago,
were they promoting the new DuckTales cartoon
or was it the video game remaster
where they were bringing around Scrooge's little money bin
to Comic-Con and I have a photo in there.
There was, do you know what I'm talking about?
Yeah, yeah, the money, yeah.
Oh yeah, oh sure.
I was so, it was soft money.
I was thrilled to get in there
and take that photo with the top hat.
The idea of Scrooge's money bin is just as a child,
my child brain was like,
obviously being rich was something that was very important
to make sure we knew as kids
that that was good to be very rich.
But also just fun, looked like fun,
he was swimming around.
He was turning around.
He turned all his money to coins as well.
Coins and you would imagine like,
you would be in a one piece old time bathing suit
and swimming around in coins.
So when I got to do a slight version,
the lesser version of it, I was still thrilled.
So the idea, you even go outside the money bin, ooh.
Yeah. Like a whole money bin ride.
That just presses all the right buttons in my brain.
Like, I don't know what it is.
It's a tough one to, yeah, tough to physically manufacture.
I think I can crack it.
Maybe not right now, but I'll get back to everyone.
Well, I guess, I don't know.
Is there some technology where if you add water
to the coins, then it changes the physical solvency.
Yes, there is some technology.
All right, if we can crack that,
we need Don Carnage on the team.
So coin bath ride.
A coin bath ride, yeah.
I'm trying to think what else?
Did you have something you wanted to say?
Was this whole endeavor actually called Disney Afternoon Live
and Disney Afternoon Avenue was a segment of it?
I'm not sure.
Okay.
What is my official literature?
Tell us what the map says,
because I kept running into different things.
It says the Disney Afternoon Live,
but that is the part of the place that you go
for the Disney Afternoon Live.
The heart and soul is Disney Afternoon Avenue.
Yeah.
Can we still call the episode Disney Afternoon Avenue?
I think we can.
Yes, well, since we're not children anymore,
we're adults, we can do whatever we want.
Yeah, you're right.
Oh yeah, good point.
Hell yeah.
Everything's sized to the way I want it to be now, always.
Regular and...
Oh yeah, we're gonna do whatever we want.
Let's start by signing this piece of paper
I put in front of you.
All right.
Hang on.
Any prog rock related part.
Now we know to watch out for this scheme,
this Don Carnage-esque scheme.
Sure.
Please do not get water on this paper.
Jason Carnage.
It will also undo my plan.
Harmful.
Yeah, I mean, I know they brought,
the last thing I had was that they brought
a little bit of it back for an event.
For 90s night, right?
For 90s night, a little bit.
It said this was gonna be,
yeah, Disney Afternoon Avenue's returning,
but what did that actually mean?
It just meant, I think, some character opportunities with...
Some flats.
Yeah, it was not any, there was no inflatables.
Lack of inflatables, which is a big bummer.
But I think, yeah, I really think
they're missing the boat on the nostalgia in a lot of ways.
They've got certain parts of nostalgia.
They had some coffee mugs and stuff for the characters.
There's gotta be a better way
that they can always have the like...
It's, I think Disneyland nostalgia is very, you know,
there's the 60s bucket, there's the 80s bucket,
there's the 90s bucket, and I think they can play stronger
at everybody's individual entry points.
Yes, for sure.
And like, just to evive, we've talked about it before,
like bringing Videopolis back in some capacity
for six weeks.
Like right now, there are supposed,
like a lot of passes unblocked as we're recording this,
and the crowds are not yet back to where they were thinking,
because they were thinking maybe, okay,
the problem with attendance was that
all the passes were blocked,
and it's gonna be a crazy thing once it's back,
but I just saw something online,
and it was like, Smuggler's Run was 30-minute wait,
which is not a good indication for Disney.
30 minutes?
30 minutes, yeah.
That's not still bad.
They're still keeping it under an hour.
No, I'm saying that they were expecting it to be two hours
now that all the passes were unblocked.
So I'm saying...
Do Disney fans want it to be crowded or not?
That's what I can't tell.
Well, they want both, I think.
Yes, because we were talking about this,
because you want, there's two things,
and there's a lot of, on our Anaheim episode,
we talked about the dual-nate.
This is, we're talking about having two thoughts
in your head at once.
This is what that is, because the success,
an unbridled success of Galaxy's Edge with two-hour waits
and Disney making money hand over fist
means we get more stuff quicker, Tomorrowland quicker.
They're feeling confident and bullish on the parks,
but yeah, that's what we want that,
but as far as Disneyland being crowded, who wants...
In terms of a pleasant experience, we wanted,
we were talking about this in the car the other day.
I brought this up to you, Scott, of like,
I really feel like Disney was a damned if they do,
damned if they don't situation with Galaxy's Edge,
where if they had eight to 10-hour lines like Hagrid's,
people would have been so fucking pissed
and they would have gotten dragged.
Instead, they kind of rationed it out,
that reservation month, and then,
I think they went a little crazy with the blacking out passes,
but like, I don't, but people, we all got in,
and we all enjoyed it, and we all got to do most of the stuff.
So that's positive, and everyone's posting it
on social media, that's free advertising.
I also think expectations are usually set by NBA dipshits,
and they are usually driven by their two passions,
working a 60-hour work week in cocaine.
So, you know.
Harsh words for the NBA, from Jason Sheridan on the Patreon.
The...
Scrooge McDuck would be so offended.
I assume Scrooge McDuck loved cocaine.
He loved cocaine, yeah, as the earlier days.
Whether it's Galaxy's Edge or Hobbs and Shaw,
where it's like, this has to make a billion dollars
immediately for me to keep my job, you know?
For this to be successful by the insane metrics
we hold ourselves to.
Well, yeah, I mean, if the...
But if they cost two billion dollars for both part,
both Galaxy's Edge's, I'm just saying,
I get there, I'm feeling a little antsy about,
maybe people aren't as into it as they hope.
I mean, I suppose,
but it's also a 20 to 30-year endeavor, isn't it?
Well, you know, here's a point I wanna make.
We've been recording this episode for 19 hours.
So, this is all nice to talk about,
but let's maybe wrap it up.
Yeah, I think we're done as soon as you finish this thought.
Oh, great, oh, it's just on me now?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because I'm really,
I'm just tired of going over and doing the,
no, hey, I don't know, Disney Avenue, fun stuff.
Yeah.
And, you know, this is like a big important thought
that you have to sum up the whole episode.
If you could call back a couple of the jokes too,
that would be really good.
All of it has to happen right now?
I think it honestly,
unfortunately, that's the way it has to happen.
Okay.
So, Joseph Cotton, the Gummy Bear song.
Gummy Bears.
Cocaine.
Cocaine, Jason's Contracts.
We've been recording for so long, I'm feeling tired,
and I need a Joseph Cotton bucket full of cocaine
to give me the energy to drive home.
So, I'm gonna work on that.
And Rebecca Cunningham, who reminds you of your mom,
you'll call her later tonight.
My Rebecca.
Thank you.
Thank you for listening.
Thank you for listening to Podcast The Ride,
The Second Gate.
You survived it, so you still have to say that.
We do, sorry.
Yeah, fun trip down memory lane.
Goodbye. Bye.