Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may contain vodka consumption in a dark hole, teen recklessness
that's both dangerous and nerdy, and a child being crushed by Norbit's wife.
Crazy Ex-Girlfriend star Rachel Bloom takes us to the only theme park with rides guaranteed
to make you wet your pants.
It's Raging Waters on podcast The Ride.
Welcome to podcast The Ride, a show about theme parks hosted by three guys who shower
in pure chlorine so they always smell waterpark fresh.
I'm Scott Gertner joined by Mike Carlson.
Yup, I'm here and I do that.
Yeah, true premise, not a joke.
Jason Sheridan is here as well.
Yeah, I love it.
The smell of chlorine or just like-
I do like it, yeah.
But if it's too strong I get a headache.
I was thinking though the smell of Splash Mountain is my favorite theme park smell I
think.
Oh really?
I guess I was saying we should do like a whole bracket for theme park smells and maybe I
just reveal it already.
Oh, you're gonna matter.
Well, but now we know what you're coming into the bracket with.
It doesn't mean we're all gonna agree.
Are we announcing that casually?
I guess I just made an announcement.
If this is your first podcast The Ride there may be an exciting episode determining what
is the best fake theme park smell.
But stay tuned for that.
Let's ask our guests.
First things first.
Let's bring our guest in.
Yeah, you know her from Crazy Ex-Girlfriend, her monthly show at Largo.
She's got a tour.
This is Rachel Bloom everybody.
Hi.
She's here on podcast.
It's my pleasure.
I have so many things to say already.
Yes, please.
Haven't they started, hasn't Disney started releasing candles that smell like the rides?
Disney is not officially releasing those.
Those are third party offshoot companies trying to approximate the smells.
They have not actually released official Disney smells.
But it's surprising Disney has not jumped on that.
Yeah, because everything else they've turned into such meta product whores of themselves.
Everything in the park now is like stuffed versions of their snacks.
You can get dresses and fanny packs now that pay homage to other merchandise.
Yes, like churros.
A magnet that looks like a churro.
They're very subtly aware of what their brand is.
They really have found a way to cater to the pass holders who are going there every single
day who are in the biker gangs, which I'm sure you've heard about.
What do they call the?
The social clubs.
Yeah, which are basically like, I guess, pacifist gangs that go to Disneyland.
They kind of died out in the last few years.
They peaked a little.
You don't see them as a lot.
You see the cuts every now and then.
But how has Disney not played into that?
How have they not started to sell the vests themselves?
I think it's hard to.
Oh, oh, right.
Well, they don't want to encourage like gang stuff, I think.
But if you think about it, the Mickey Mouse Club was kind of a gang to begin with.
Everybody they were there representing its colors.
They have their names on it, patches.
So really, they they're responsible for all this.
They would kill in his name?
I think so.
Yeah, they would rough up the little rascals.
Cubby was bloodthirsty.
I want to get one of those candles, though.
I mean, yeah, man, the Disney smells are.
Yeah, it's hard.
I have a few of them.
They're not perfect because like a lot of the smells that we like are chemicals or some
sort of compound.
Bromine.
One of them is bromine.
It's like stuff you can actually put into a candle and make you hoof because you're
not supposed to.
So I don't.
It's hard to approximate because some of the smells are just old building.
Some of the smells are like weird thing you add to water to make sure it's not poison
if it gets into kids mouth.
So like, wait, what smells?
What smell is that?
I think it's industrial grade bromine is like one of the smells that you associate with
theme parks.
Like that's like stronger than like in Pirates of the Caribbean's water.
Yeah.
And stuff like could be totally wrong.
That's what's in like the water instead of chlorine.
I think it's got chlorine too.
We talked about this a while back and I forget what episode it was on.
But like that is what your brain is smelling that you are associating positively to.
But in terms of extracting it to put into a candle scent, it's kind of impossible.
It's probably illegal.
Although I don't know.
Is there a jewel?
Is there like a, is there a jewel pod of Splash Mountain scent?
Oh my gosh.
If you want it to market to kids any better than jewel already has.
Right?
That's so smart.
That is, I would start vaping instantly.
Oh, that's a billion dollar idea.
Yeah.
If I could breathe in ET pine as a jewel flavor.
Yep.
I'm addicted right away.
There was a time when we were at Disney when they used, they still, they had the, that
projection of Davy Jones on Pirates.
It's gone now again.
Really?
Yeah.
They got rid of it like a year ago.
But what are they doing?
What are they doing in that tunnel now?
It's like it used to be, there's no back there.
They add a little like kind of, it's not an animatronic, but they added like a little
character that when you go by him, he turns from a skeleton into a man, which is very
cool.
It transitions you for like now, now the story makes sense.
I was just there and I swear I saw Davy.
Well, he, so, so a guy when that was still there, a guy was, had his jewel out and he,
into the air and he like blew a big plume of like strawberry vape at Davy Jones.
He's fighting him.
That guy's cool.
Yeah, actually, I don't usually think that stuff's cool, but in that instance.
So you liked that.
I kind of think that's neat.
Were you with us?
No, I don't think I was.
Jason, you were with me, right?
I can't remember.
I think you were.
We talked about it once.
Yeah.
He's fighting steam with steam.
But we got a full blast of strawberry vape in our face because of that.
If I were like 17 years old, I'd fuck that guy.
That's like, that would be like the sexiest thing I ever saw.
So I should begin by saying like, I'm obsessed with amusement parks.
I grew up in Southern California.
I'm an only child.
So I grew up with, it was like me and my parents and I was like, they're kind of like being
an only child, especially when you have like whimsical parents, it feels like you're just
like their idiot sidekick.
And so my parents were also like obsessed with amusement parks.
And so we got a year long pass to Disneyland when I was six and I would go on like school
nights.
I mean, I really, Disneyland is like where I grew up.
I would go to Knott's constantly, Six Flags a little less and then Raging Waters, which
I'm here to really talk about.
But like that was my first and I got to say like, I think my only water park, I think
I've only ever just been to Raging Waters.
This stuff is incredibly like, it's incredibly like near and dear to my heart.
I mean, I really, being an Imagineer was like a close second career and then I realized
I was terrible at physics.
Yeah, that's the bummer about it.
It does involve, you know, science and math and numbers and stuff that I can only assume
none of us are very good at.
Yeah, that's fair, I guess.
But we throw a lot of ideas out on the podcast that we think are very good.
So somebody else could work out the physics of it.
I think they need more of that and they have people to, every ride has a writer because
my husband and his writing partner wrote The Secret Life of Pets Ride for Universal Studios
Florida.
We've heard this through the rumors.
Oh, interesting.
Yeah.
And I don't know if there's an, I mean, whatever, it's fine.
But I don't know when the ride's opening or if it's...
Next summer.
So it's here.
It's down the street.
Okay.
So about five years ago, they got hired to write this ride and they partially took it
because my husband knew how much I'd like geek out over this.
And we went to Disney World so that they could kind of go on rides.
And then we went around Universal Studios with some of the people who create the rides
at Universal Studios.
We went to Harry Potter World with some of the creators and I don't know what the term,
it's not imaginary universal, but with some of the people who created the things at Harry
Potter World.
And it was, I mean, it was unbelievable.
And my husband's not, he likes amusement park because he's not an amusement park guy.
My husband's writing partner is actively kind of scared of roller coasters.
So he got over some of those fears, some of those fears on that trip.
But every ride has a writer.
And now that I'm thinking about it, I don't have a job right now.
I could easily like...
You can take a meeting.
You can get to the ride.
You can go over there.
Oh man, that's all I want to do actually.
Wait, what the fuck am I doing here?
Goodbye.
Make some calls, come back if you want, but we understand.
We can tell you the fastest way to get to the Flower Street campus.
You have a picture of your own campus.
Oh, you're right there, right?
We're very close.
We're really close.
Wild.
But I love it.
Oh, if you want to see the worst written ride, the Six Flags has a...
Justice League?
Yes.
We haven't done it yet.
Oh, holy fucking shit.
The writing on the Justice League ride, it's the worst writing you've ever seen, right?
It's a lot.
So it's full on two person audition scenes.
That last...
So the opening movie to let you know what the Justice League ride is about, it's a scene
between Joker and Harley Quinn with bad, terrible CGI.
And it's them just talking, it's them just shooting the shit for, I want to say, 10 minutes.
And it feels like people in a scene study class doing a bad audition scene.
And it's not the last one.
There's a few of those scenes.
No, it's filled with those scenes.
Oh, I'm doing it in a week.
I'm going in a week.
Oh, yeah.
I'm very excited.
It's some of the weirdest fucking writing.
It's for a bunch of people there who are like, I mean, anywhere from like 6 to 36.
No one cares about the writing of the Justice League ride.
It's terrible.
It was made by a company called the Sally Corporation, who we've talked about on the
show before.
They made a very short lived ride for a hard rock themed theme park in Myrtle Beach based
on the moody blues song Knights and White Satin.
So trying to turn that and it's very, there's a full video ride through of it online on
their official YouTube channel, on the Sally Corporation channel.
And it's a trip, but it's like they definitely went very ethereal with it.
It's not a literal story.
Not a lot of story.
Because it's, I mean, it's kind of a nonsense song anyway.
They're better at doing rides based on songs.
They still have moody blues songs.
Based on DC Universe characters.
Where there were, there's inherent context.
And well, I guess they're better doing poetic rides rather than like with a coherent narrative.
I mean, it's hard to get into a ride.
It just dawned on me as we were talking about this, that finding an excuse for why the ride
exists is very similar to like finding an excuse for why sex exists in porn.
It's the same type of like-
Oh, right, right, right.
It's the same type of like, you have to find the antidote, but you have to suck his dick.
Or you have to find the antidote, so get in this mine car.
You know, it's the same kind of like stretch of the imagination.
Why do people need 16 strangers to perform a task in mass?
You have to come up with very contrived reasons.
Or something goes wrong.
Like this is not at all how this tutoring session was supposed to go.
Yeah.
Yes, and it's immediate.
But it's a thrilling experience now.
Yes.
So you're telling me that they're taking tourists.
It's the 1920s.
They're taking tourists into this temple.
They've invented a Jeep system and all you have to do is close your eyes and you'll be
rewarded with riches.
And like scientists aren't studying this.
They're just allowing tourists to go in.
But the tourists are in to find Indiana Jones as well.
Oh, Indiana Jones has disappeared, right.
They were already charging tourists to go in to make up the money that they were not
making because they had run over on their expedition or whatever it's called.
But the wisdom of crowds, if you give them one thing to do, that is one thing too many.
Keep your eyes closed.
Everyone's immediately opening their eyes.
I think there should be a version of Indiana Jones where if everyone closes their eyes,
you get a completely different ride.
And it's like a pleasant, beautiful temple ride.
And at the end of it, you get a bunch of free snacks.
Yeah, that would be great.
I think you'd have to get like 16 of those annual pass holders though to do it.
Like you'd have to really formulate like 16 of us are going or whatever.
No, 12.
12 of us are going.
What do you think is going to happen?
No, I'm just saying it's not going to happen.
I'm not saying I believe it to happen.
I'm just saying.
There's always going to be that one fucking kid who's going to open their eyes and.
Yeah, our grandma is going to look.
Come on, grandma.
I would love the giant Mara head to say like, thank you for listening to me,
respecting our culture.
I know whatever does this.
Yeah. Yeah.
Every ride, I guess, has the version where it's fine.
Star tours, you just fly to Endor and Rex lets you out and says, so.
Right. Watch your head on the way out.
And thanks for flying with us.
I wish that if you didn't put your hands up on the Guardians ride, he'd go, what?
What are you doing?
Yeah, that's the one thing I said.
You gotta put your hands in the air.
And it's like, what are you doing?
Just like it's a standoff until it happens.
They're going to kill Star Lord.
You know, he's dead.
It's on your hands now.
God damn it.
These leaves. Yeah.
Yeah, it's yeah, there there.
There's only so many real setups they can do, I think, really, too,
with it, with the ride like now, especially if it's like kind of an actiony ride.
But it used to be that rides would just start and there isn't like,
we don't know why we're in Snow White's forest or
you know, that's going to pleasure.
Because there is a narrative inherent in that.
I mean, I think I have a certain respect for things like Matterhorn or Big Thunder
or Space Mountain, where it's like, you know what?
You're on a ride.
Enjoy the ride.
There's no like there's no like
mountain explorers.
You need to find the abominable snowman.
Yes. So we've invented a track made of ice.
But but but where if you don't collect the urine sample by the end of the track,
you will be in a wet splashdown zone.
You know, this open house is going terribly wrong.
There is a good chance it involves an open house that goes wrong.
Yeah. There's space.
Space Mountain is the best one because the name Space Mountain doesn't make any sense.
And they never explain it.
There's speculation of it.
But like it just doesn't.
They're just yeah, you're in a rocket.
It doesn't matter. Yeah. Space Mountain.
It's fine. You're in space.
Doesn't matter. Yeah.
I care. No one and like only we are paying attention to any of this.
Most people.
No, no, most people don't give a shit.
I mean, the thing that always bothered me about Tower of Terror
was that Tower of Terror was an unfinished story.
So you're telling me, OK, I'm going to go on a freight elevator just for funsies.
I'm going to get struck by lightning and I'm going to disappear
along with the people who disappeared in the 30s.
So when I exit the ride, for all intents and purposes, I should be dead.
There is no explanation of why I'm suddenly alive again.
That always bothered me about Tower of Terror.
That's a good point. Yeah.
They should explain like, oh, you just missed it.
You just missed dying.
Like, oh, good for you. Oh, it's in Thursday? Never mind.
Hey, good luck. Good work.
Yours was weaker lightning than what hit the old man and the little girl.
Yeah. So you left out. It should just be you.
It should just be you.
Like, oh, yeah.
Like that thing is like the ride should end and you just come on.
You go, oh, never mind.
Oh, just me. I just explained every. Yeah.
Oh, hey, what's up?
Hey, just to let you know, real quick, you got weak lightning.
Thank God. Anyway, merch is available.
Step this way.
Man, he's lucked out for the man.
Everything worked out. That famous Rod Serling phrase.
Oh, hey, man. Hey, just to let you know, real quick.
Oh, what's up?
Welcome back from the 30s. So anyway.
Right. Rock on, man.
It just ends like Haunted Mansion has a says like a ghost is going to follow you home
and then for the rest of your life, you're then haunted by the Hat Box Ghost.
That I can deal with. Yeah.
And the fact that they don't need proof that he can be invisible.
The Hat Box Ghost. Is that the right reference?
Well, that's the answer.
Clear which ghost he's not.
He's not in one of the ones that I can go.
So the one confusingly there is one of them has a big top hat.
So he's Hat Box Ghost. That's why I think it's like Gus is one of them.
I forget the other two.
Gus is a name of one of their names is Gus.
One of their names is Gus.
Yeah. So that's a fact.
But that's fine. I can live with that.
So I've gone on the Haunted Mansion ride.
So a ghost is now always following me.
Right. Yes. That is a great narrative. Easy.
Great for me to take home.
Yeah. Is the I guess this tower the most incomplete narrative of all the rides?
It does feel like it off the top of my head.
Well, Little Mermaid skips the entire end of the movie.
Yes, right. I mean, but it ends with them happy ever after.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Well, just in the background or so is drowning.
It's a very it's like they ran.
I think they just ran out of they wanted to do all the big musical set pieces.
I mean, that's the problem with most especially Disney musicals is you have
once you get to like the plot of Act three, you can't have musical numbers anymore
because musical numbers inherently are a stop in the plot.
And so that's why the kind of third act of any Disney movie is
arguably the most forgettable.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Because you're a little like, let's just get let's let's just get
let's just get to the end.
Like unless you have like a reprise like in Aladdin with the Prince Ali or you have
King Prince Ali, Pocahontas does it very well, actually.
Pocahontas has like the moment where they're going into
savages, savages.
That's like the kind of one finale that's going into kind of the
the darker plot of your parts.
But anyway, Little Mermaid is a testament to they put the musical numbers in.
And once you're done with all the musical numbers, you just want to skip to the end.
Well, yeah, because it's just like, yeah, it's fighting for a while.
You don't want to just be in two fighting scenes in a row in a ride.
You know, kind of does it is
kill the beast a little bit in Beauty and the Beast.
It's like not exactly.
But maybe that's a that's like a section that can work is the like
building to the to the big fight.
And then once you get into the fight, it's more of the battle is in itself kind of a
a musical number, like the way that battle is in Beauty and the Beast is very it's scored.
It's very like fun.
It's the it's another fun in game set piece.
Right. Because the furniture is like a drawer hits a guy in the face.
That's why I like that.
It doesn't be our guest.
Get reprised in that instrumentally, isn't it?
Yes, it is. Yeah, I think so.
Is there not a Beauty and the Beast ride anywhere?
They're building one in Japan.
And there have been some videos showing the Bell robots and the horse and it looks.
I'm surprised they're not building in Paris.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, Paris is weird and cheap.
I got to go to Euro Disney.
Have you been to Euro Disney?
I went. I've had a lot of like grapes.
I feel like. Really? How was your?
Well, I went.
I was champagne tasting and then we were champagne tasting and champagne.
I was there with my friend, Brendan, because I was there for a press thing.
And I went, wait, it was like four p.m.
I was like, Brendan, you realize what we're close to?
I was like Euro Disney.
And I was like, let's fucking go.
He's like, it closes in two and a half hours.
And I was like, I don't care.
So we did all we managed to do every major attraction in Euro
Disney in like an hour and a half. Wow. Wow.
So I remember I loved Crush's coaster.
I didn't get I didn't get to do I wasn't going to wait.
That was fucking awesome.
I want to say it's a rotating.
Yeah. You're spinning.
You're surfing with Crush, but it's like a roller coaster as well.
The Ratatouille ride was great. Yeah, that's really good.
Yeah. I clearly couldn't do both, I think, in the morning I had there.
Yeah, I think because we went in February when no one
when no one was there towards the end of the day. Sure.
We got on things.
But what were your gripes with Disneyland?
Why was there in December where it is so bitterly cold?
And you can tell that this used to be like a brittle farmland.
Yeah, essentially.
And they it was like because the weather was bad, they like closed half
the restaurants and it was just weird and understaffed.
And we scanned our own tickets on the way in.
It was just yeah, that was the weirdest.
We just have like crumpled pieces of paper and we scan them ourselves
in the mall outside.
And I don't know if you wandered around there.
That's like a nightmare. This wasn't a dream.
Yeah, yeah.
This does actually I do have like stressed dreams where Disneyland is bad
in some way, really something something bad happened to it.
Where you scan yourself in like I've had dreams, Disney, about Disney
all the time where the ride breaks down and I get to walk on the land.
Like I suddenly snow and I get to walk among the dolls of It's a Small World.
Like sure, this trippy.
Like we are.
Disneyland is a perfect place for like the things to serially rearrange themselves.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, like if you have you ever seen the videos of Nara Dreamland?
It's like a Tokyo and I know it's in Japan, but it's a ripoff Disney park
that's closed now and it's abandoned.
Oh, that's that.
But it has like a ripoff Sleeping Beauty Castle on a main street.
So there's like urban explorers go through it and it's like overgrown
shrub hedges, grass, and it's the creepiest nightmare
because it's a surreal Disneyland.
Oh, no. I really want to.
I'm going to look. I'm going to Nara.
Nara Dreamland.
Yeah. Yeah. Very creepy.
Don't. Yeah. Don't get killed or have a wild animal.
Don't explore.
You do. Yeah.
Seems like a dangerous place, potentially.
There's an abandoned amusement park in it's Florida, right?
That's it's Disney's River Country.
That's what it is. Yeah.
But did they take it? Did they rip it up already?
They're building a hotel over.
Yeah, they finally ripped it up. Yeah.
Yeah, because Discovery Island is still abandoned.
Oh, yeah.
Island in the middle of the body of water by Magic Kingdom,
where you used to be able to go and see exotic animals and stuff.
And they eventually shut that down.
It's just it's just a it's in the middle of a body of water.
Now and then someone inflates an inflatable raft close by and rows out to it.
And there's just like sheds, sheds still with like stuff in them.
The animals are all gone, except the wild animals that have taken the island.
And the creepy detail, I always say that there's a shed
that's just full of vultures that have never been outside.
There's just dozens and dozens of indoor vultures who are malformed.
And I believe so. I think so.
No way. Yeah. Yeah.
It might not be as scary as what I'm describing, but preserved animals.
Like, you know, when they preserve like something and have it in a jar.
Jelly or James? No, like like an embryo, like an animal embryo and stuff.
There's still some some of that. That's horrifying.
Yeah. Well, like it's like Jurassic Park abandoned.
Basically. Yeah, kind of.
This is a great opening to a horror movie.
This is the cold open of a movie called Discover.
And we're recording the podcast and then the title, the title,
you know, like the title comes on and goes like, discover.
And then you cut to people who are like with backpacks on
with a handheld camera being like, OK, we're going to go see
Discovery Fun Time should be fun.
Yeah. They all die. And they all die.
That podcast said it was a good idea.
We haven't mentioned this on the show, but some listeners brought us
a gift from the abandoned Hard Rock Park. Oh, right.
Which is still there.
And they brought us what looks like brand new merchandise
from Hard Rock Park because it's just sitting somewhere in a warehouse.
It's a room, just a bunch of loose shit in the ground.
In Myrtle Beach.
Inland, inland from the ocean. OK, I'll feel it.
So it was poorly promoted and it was far from like the main drag.
So they went in it.
So it's just you can just what it's it's what fenced it like it's boarded up.
I don't think it's even a little or boarded.
They showed me a picture of just a giant warehouse
with merch strewn on the floor.
And it's like, and if you see it, it looks new.
It doesn't look like dirty or anything.
Also, all of that was supposed to be destroyed per the bankruptcy agreement.
And it clearly wasn't. But now.
But now it's there.
But literally, as I was getting out of the car, I saw a headline on my phone
or my phone that said mysterious fire at Old Theme Park. Like.
Yeah, I saw there was a fire down there.
So who knows if that merchandise is still there?
We have some of the last merch.
What was it again? What did we get?
I forget. It's like a water bottle.
It's like a big water bottle in the shape of a guitar, I think.
It's a bag. It's a plastic bag.
All of it looks brand new.
What is the fascination with hard?
Because there are people who have to go to hard rocks in every city.
Have you talked about this on the podcast?
Yeah, a little bit. Yeah, this year sort of this has been my take a little bit.
What is I don't even know.
It's a cafe that celebrates rock and roll.
What what? Well, love all.
Surf all that is no food definition whatsoever.
I don't know what kind of terrible, terrible food, really bad food.
So what? But it's like you can order like Joe Perry macaroni.
I know. I know the story behind.
So I believe the initial
impetus of it was like the founders couldn't find a good burger in London.
So they and they had some rock and roll connection.
So they're like, hey, can we get some guitars?
We're going to open this restaurant that does burgers and stuff.
And then at some point, they were also like, we can do barbecue
because they have like a decent like a.
And they bought like they bought 300 guitars from Scott Weiland
Chris Cornell. And that's it.
And that's all just only velvet revolver will be shown in this.
So what's the thing that people have to go to the hard rock
in every major city like and get the merchandise?
My friend's mom loves merchandise from every hard rock.
Wow. And she's not the only one.
Yeah, I mean, they're very popular because they're still around.
They've been around for years. And it's like, I mean, I used to do it
from when I was a kid with Planet Hollywood.
If there was a planet Hollywood somewhere, we went on vacation
because I loved the movies.
But like just movies.
Were they different in each location?
Were they all they all had different props?
Oh, OK. And still there's still two or three hanging on.
But like, yeah, you go to the one.
First of all, I've never had a good meal at the one universal.
I've been there like maybe three times in 10 years.
It's horrible. And it's horrible. Yeah.
And it's like, what is even the identity of the hard hard?
What does hard rock mean to them?
Well, does it mean Gwen Stefani, because that's in there?
The rest of us. And that doesn't mean Lenny Kravitz.
The restaurant is different than the hotel spokesman for Hard Rock today.
But it's all owned by the Seminole tribe now. Right.
Who? Like, that's another development.
Yes. Mm hmm.
They they own the Hard Rock Company now.
That's great. Yeah.
That makes me want to support them. Yeah.
All right. Just a little mom and pop.
Is rock and roller coaster Hard Rock?
No, no, no. That's I mean, it rocks.
It certainly is.
Yeah, it's still the best tribute to Hard Rock out there.
It's ending in Paris, though. It just closed.
Oh, you know, the one in Paris, I went on it was very bumpy.
OK. Well, they aren't changing the trick.
They're just saying is the fireman now.
So yeah, so same. Yeah, same shit.
Oh, they're just closing it to make it more relevant. OK.
I think so. Yeah.
That actually brings up a good
you as a music person favorite music in the park, favorite music related attraction.
I mean, I assume it's Aerosmith.
I assume Aerosmith's number one for everybody. Yeah, of course.
I love any time a roller coaster has music associated with it.
So I love the old California Screamin track.
I think I ride. That was great.
Are you mad that it would change?
No, no. I think in credit coasters also very good, actually.
And I I have a problem.
I have a very I have very mixed feelings about and this is everything now
about rides that center around movie properties because you inherently
have to know the movie to appreciate the ride and the ride promotes the movie.
I'm a big fan of rides that contain their own narrative, that tell their own story.
I mean, which is what Pirates of the Caribbean used to be, which is what
Haunted Mansion, you know, kind of still is.
And then they made that terrible movie, but no one really talks about it.
Yeah. So I like if you gave me a billion dollars,
I would start an amusement park
where the rides didn't feed into any sort of book or movie.
The rides told their own story.
So that's just a little bit of a problem.
It's a it's a problem that I have with Disneyland that that now
everything is just feeding into a Disney property.
There's no unique story anymore. Sure.
And it is and it is what it is.
And I'm not saying California Screamin was a story.
It was just the theme was the theme.
I mean, because I remember when it first opened, the theme was just
celebrating California. And yeah, it was a little boring.
My dad actually wrote an angry letter to Disney saying how boring it was.
I don't think he was the only one.
I know. Yeah, yeah, no.
So he was really we were really bored.
But but looking back on it, there was something really noble about that
where it was like, you know what?
We're just going to fucking celebrate California and we're going to have this
old fashioned boardwalk and you can go and make tortillas
at the Mission Tortilla Factory.
And and then they just were like, fuck it, it's cars.
I've never seen cars. I love the cars ride.
I don't really understand why the cars are talking.
I mean, I get it. The cars are talking.
All I have to do is see cars once.
But it it always just it's it's it bothers me.
It bothers me that everything now has to feed into a property
that you have to have seen to fully appreciate the ride. Sure.
And you know, you talk about we talk about like ride stories.
I think they're almost the most likely to be confusing
if you need to have seen the film.
Well, that's what I'm more lost than I mean, I guess Indiana Jones is one.
You have you done Avatar in Florida?
Have you been to Orlando?
No, I haven't been.
I haven't been recently enough to do Avatar.
It's that's the most confusing thing.
It shouldn't be. You're just on the back of a monster.
The mighty Akron, of course, we remember. Yeah.
From the movie. The thing that he tames.
Yeah, the Banshee.
But then like all it is is just flying and you enjoy it.
That's really what they should say.
Hey, get on the back of that thing and enjoy it.
But it's not it's like three different rooms of explaining
how you're going to be downloaded into an avnavi.
And then you're getting on here.
And now we have to scan your heat signature.
Also scanning like guardians is getting scanned everywhere.
Both roadie, both roadie attraction, Joe roadie attraction scans.
I just saw a Joe roadie lecture and he did cover this.
He talked about really, OK?
He did talk about this because and this was very funny
because a friend had written the roundup of like, here's
I'm like you wrote the article for the L.A.
Times about like, I'm concerned IP coming out of D23
is so much intellectual property based attractions.
Is this kind of killing the theme parks?
And the curator, when interviewing Joe roadie, brought up this article.
And this guy was like white knuckling like, oh, my God, like Joe roadie.
He was there. Oh.
And so roadie's theory is that like there every every piece,
you know, if you think about like the film school or art school,
you're given a prompt for a project.
So as imagineers, they're given a prompt for an attraction
or they're giving a topic or something.
And then they have to go back to zero anyway, because they have to
try to then make it work for ages eight to 80.
And every person, people from all over the world coming to see it.
And I think his theory is that when done at the highest level,
done on the best attractions, that does work.
Like, it doesn't matter if you don't know the property will give from
when you come into the queue to when you'll leave,
you will understand this whole experience.
Do they always accomplish that?
It's clearly up for debate.
How is that? That lecture sounds like a blast.
You get wasted. Yeah, got hammered.
Got hammered and fell down the hill at the getty.
Rody. But that makes a lot of sense because I I want to say
I rode Star Tours before I ever saw Star Wars and Star Tours makes sense.
Like, yeah, it's a it's a coherent narrative.
Indiana Jones makes sense.
Yeah, you're in a temple and they and they also have that great introductory
video before and cars doesn't have to necessarily make sense.
Guardians does not make sense.
Like Guardians is tougher. It's a tougher one.
But it's so fun. I mean, it's it's it's really fun.
I think are we just all worried about the is this a slippery slope situation?
Are we worried? This is what I'm worried about Marvel.
I'm worried that I need to have seen all that.
Well, there's going to be as Marvel is going to they have a cinematic
universe, of course, but they're going to have a theme park universe,
which is a different continuity than the movie.
And the movie was different than the comic books one parks.
But maybe he's spoiler alert dead in the movies.
So like that's going to be a whole nother thing that you'll have to learn.
Well, that's what Harry Potter does it.
I mean, yes, I love Harry Potter world.
Well, I like Harry Potter world.
I like Harry Potter world and Harry Potter world specifically.
It takes place in the start of Book Three.
Right. Because you have this wanted serious black posters around.
Right. And the kid and they're like kids forever.
They're kids forever.
I mean, the thing that bothers me about Harry Potter land is I
there's no escaping this because it's made by Warner Brothers.
It's meant to promote the movies.
Everything is strictly looks like the movies.
Yeah. Yeah. Which when I read the books,
I don't picture people wearing like muggle clothing with a robe.
I picture just robes.
So like the Quidditch stuff in the movies is kind of this,
you know, it's it's like athletic.
It's like athletic like armor
with a robe that's just kind of like attached to it.
But the way it's described in the book is just robes.
There are all these little things where where I just I'm like,
oh, when I'm in Harry Potter land, I'm not completely immersing myself
in the fantasy of the books because it's the movies. Right.
And there are certain things that differ in the movies from the books.
And then also Daniel Radcliffe is not how I picture Harry Potter.
Oh, no.
And it's not how I picture Hermione. Right. Right.
I mean, I don't I don't picture the way I picture Harry
Ron and Hermione are different than the actors who play them. Sure.
And it does feel like well, because like what I want, I have not read the books.
I've seen all the movies, but I've been told by people read the books.
The books are like way better than movies are fine. Yeah, they're fun.
But obviously, that's the one that's the thing people associate more.
So they want people just to recognize, oh, that's Harry. I know him.
I would much rather the the rides be based on like the illustrations
of Mary Grandprey, who did all the books than the movies,
because it takes me out of it a little.
But that's also me being like
a dork who who wants to go to an amusement park and really fully imagine
that I'm in this experience.
And I'm never going to fully imagine that I'm in Harry Potter world
when I see the actors playing Harry Ron and Hermione
that I know aren't really Harry Ron and Hermione. Right.
Because it would actually be it would be more immersive
if you didn't recognize the people in a weird way of like, well, that's actually them.
That's not the movie versions.
Those are the these are people. I don't.
These are the guys. Yeah, I guess that's what I'm saying.
Like, you'd be like, well, those are the real ones.
They're on the ride, but they're not the actors. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, that's kind of what I'm like.
They cast different actors for the land.
Then those would actually be the real ones.
You know what? That's a great idea.
And I completely agree with that. Yes, totally.
And I know that that's completely not how capitalism works. Right.
And and that's exactly the opposite of what they want.
They want to be promoting the movies.
But yeah, that's kind of what I'm craving.
I'm just kind of craving it being an being an immersive being an immersive land.
I mean, I like Harry Potter, The Forbidden Journey, but also
I just kind of would love to immerse myself in the world
and not necessarily see the characters from the books.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I mean, you're living in the world, you're not seeing
you're not helping Harry, Ron and Hermione.
You're just kind of like living your life as a wizard.
There is something different between like when you go on a ride
that's like IP ride versus Haunted Mansion, where it's like it's like recco.
Like, oh, I recall that this looks like the thing I watched on TV versus like
I'm wandering into an experience.
I'm wandering into something that is totally different.
I can't get it at home.
I can't I can't get any version of it in a book or at home.
And it's truly special in this place.
And that's it. And maybe Florida and Tokyo.
Does Indiana Jones, like almost accidentally hit this the best
because Harrison Ford isn't involved.
So you get like glimpses of indie, but it's not like there's not a monitor
in front on your Jeep where Harrison Ford is giving you instructions.
And maybe it's all happening to you.
And it's a new story.
Mm hmm. Yeah. Yeah.
And the fact that's and also like Star Tours
isn't C3VN or TDD tour in it, but it's not like, well, you know,
well, new Star Tours, now the new characters appear in the window
as opposed to this is sort of its own thing.
And I don't know who that pilot is who shows up and Rex is only
only in that and no original Star Tours was that whole that new character.
The pilot who keeps fucking up and my favorite character in fiction, Rex.
Right. Right.
Our show. It's your first ride.
It's my first time to.
And he's DJing now and he's gotten to go.
Have you gotten to see him, DJ?
No, I haven't. What is he in the cantina? Yeah.
Yeah. So I couldn't get in.
I couldn't get in. Oh, yeah.
I couldn't get into the cantina because by the time I went,
I went to one of the preview days, but tickets were already sold out. Yeah.
Yeah, because it was a mad dash to get there.
Like, it would be like I saw a person get trampled running to get to the cantina.
And then like most people didn't help.
Like I was way behind, so I didn't even have a chance to help them.
But, you know, they were.
You would have loved to.
There were like at least five.
You tell the judge. Yeah, of course.
There are five to seven people who just ran over the person.
That's so fantastic.
Oh, my God.
And now you can just make a reservation on the app.
You can. Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
They should have done that from the beginning.
You would think. You would think that would make sense.
So can I say I hated the blue and green milk?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Well, that's not that didn't taste like milk.
It was a fruit smoothie.
It was like a shitty vegan fruit smoothie.
And I understand like you don't want to make people sick.
But like when I picture blue milk, I don't picture like a fruit smoothie.
If you don't want people to get sick from all the dairy, do like a sweetened
almond milk or a sweetened cashew milk.
But instead, it's like fruity.
No, that's bullshit.
That fight. So they played the color and not not the word milk.
It's called blue milk.
So milk is sort of if they call it something different, maybe.
Yeah, but it's but the whole thing is you drink blue milk.
Mm hmm. Do they call it blue milk in the movie? Yeah.
They like say Uncle Owen, I want my blue milk or something.
I'm not. My milk cup is empty.
And bro is like, finish your blue milk.
I am 85 percent sure they do.
I can't remember what they do.
Why would we all do? It's not milk.
It's not the consistency of milk.
It's like it's like a fruit smoothie.
And I got to say, like kind of a shitty smoothie.
I think my take on it has because I was expecting to not like it at all.
And then I liked it.
I tried both and I liked both for like four sips.
And then it started to become how am I not?
This is a pretty crazy flavor to be drinking a lot of and not getting drunk.
Like this that I'm not getting the reward of a little buzz.
And I'm just sucking down so much sugar and weird artificial.
Maybe in Florida, you can get a shot.
Yes, that's the point.
So that would improve the entire thing. Yeah, I think so.
But when you think about butter beer at Harry Potter World,
like butterbeer is amazing. Yeah.
Like butterbeer really lives up to like, you know what?
Especially when you get it hot, like, yeah, that's exactly how I pictured
butterbeer tasting and more.
And especially when you get it with some some whiskey in it.
Yeah. I mean, I forgot about that.
I was at Universal the other day and like when I am up there,
I can just like passively consume butter.
Like I'll just like get it without even thinking and drink it.
Like it's it's just like a coma.
No, like I will.
I will not even hesitate to get it in the way of like,
do I really feel like this blue milk today?
Getting water out of the fridge.
You're not even like, OK, basically.
But I also I the other day I was it was so hot and I had a sore throat.
And I was like, oh, wait, there's frozen butter beer.
And it felt great. Like I felt so much better.
It was so soothing frozen for a sore throat, not a worm.
Well, it was like 98 degrees up on top of that hill.
So I think I wanted to cool down and also soothe my throat.
The frozen butter beer is it's delicious.
Would you recommend it for a sore throat, though?
Anything anything cold for a sore throat is really.
I guess I always go warm for a cold, not in the long run,
because it's so much dairy and sugar.
It's going to probably fuck your immune system.
But to soothe your throat. Yeah.
Yeah. Not daily butter beer.
I'm always warm for sore throat.
But maybe I'm doing it wrong.
We did like a supersize me with just butter beer.
You drank butter beer for 30 days.
I feel like you had magic powers.
That lives up to like the hype of life.
Yeah, it's we've we've talked a little bit about this on the show, too.
It's like that one also, from the way I've heard it described
in the book in the way kids like they talk about it in the movie.
It's like, wow, this magical great drink.
And I never except for Jason, who was the first person I ever heard
say he watched Star Wars and was like, got to try that blue milk.
Like I was like, oh, that's some gross thing they're pouring in.
Like it's also not the name Blue Milk.
It's also not the name Blue Milk does not sound good.
It's like there's nothing magical.
It's not like Lucas, like, wow, I get to get back to tattooing
to drink my delicious blue milk.
No, but it's all the idea of like immersion and fantasy and feeling.
I mean, the most I went with, I went to Harry Potter World
a couple of months ago with a bunch of my friends who like love Harry Potter.
And our favorite thing was just drinking butter beer in the three broomsticks.
And then we like talked in British accents and pretended we were wizards.
Like that was my favorite part.
And you didn't have to.
I didn't have to look at like CGI Dan Radcliffe,
because I could just pretend I was in the books.
Mm hmm. Yes. OK.
You're not there to meet the characters, especially the actors in the film.
Yeah. No, I don't. You want it to you're there.
I want it that I'm I want it completely immersive that I'm that I'm there.
I mean, they've been rumoring Harry Potter Hotel for so long,
but that feels like if they had a little like that feels like what you're saying.
The ultimate version of it is like you're just living in it.
It's not so much of seeing the actors.
It's just like maybe they make a little restaurant bar
and you just get to hang out and pretend you're in Hogwarts.
That's what I want, because when I was there on a Harry Potter night,
they also you can pose with like Bo Baton's and Durmstrang students.
But but I in the real world, Bo Baton's students and Durmstrang students
would just be like around to pose with.
They'd be students.
They wouldn't they wouldn't just be waiting.
That doesn't that doesn't how Harry Potter works.
Yeah, I think I took I want I went to Harry Potter land
with future guest Aaron Whitehead, and she liked it, but was very
was like, what did all these humans walk like she was really kind of almost upset
by like she is a big yes, she is.
She almost want you want there to be a dress code.
You want everyone to have to be in a robe. You want.
You want to de-mentor terrorist attack to be happening suddenly.
I think that is because that happens on the ride.
First off, you're in the middle of a Quidditch match.
Yeah. If you were on like a jet pack and just landed in a major league
baseball game, but then also like an attack starts happening
to a major league baseball game.
It's like, wait, I just got over the jet pack guy.
Why are there why are there SWAT people in the Yankee Stadium?
Didn't we get stuck in front of one of them?
Oh, in the front of the de-mentor.
Yeah, I've gotten stuck in front of the giant spider.
I've gotten stuck in the room full of de-mentors.
It's not a great place to just hang out.
Oh, I mean, the ride breaking down.
Yeah. Oh, the ride broke down when I was on and we just got the screen went out.
So then but the ride kept moving.
So it was just going through and we're like, oh, yeah, if this goes on for 10
minutes, we're going to throw up.
This is the most nauseous thing you got stuck in the loop of.
We got stuck in the loop of moving, but the screens went out.
Oh, that's so.
So it was really weird.
Wow. All the all your mind is getting that is like jerking movement.
It's not even fooling you with the visuals that you're going through.
Yeah, you're just getting jerked around.
You're just getting jerked around.
I think it was the whopping.
I think it was in front of the one.
Yeah, we got stuck.
I remember the music went out.
We were stuck. We were static.
Yeah, but we could.
There was still the music tracks or the audio tracks of Harry.
So you just hear like, get away from them.
And there were no music.
There was no nothing.
You just hear, hey, like just no, stop.
And then like every minute.
And then we were just like upside, not upside down, but like staring at the
ceiling, waiting for it to start.
When I wrote it the other day, I actually got all the way through it.
But one of the times they had accidentally left at the very end,
the I saw the maintenance bay.
They left the lights on.
I was like, oh, that's where the maintenance bay is.
But for people like us, I'm like, oh, yes, now I know where the maintenance bay is.
Nice, nice.
That happened on pirates.
If you go by the pirate ship, sometimes you see the door
where they send boats and the door will be open straight away.
And like light was coming out of it once.
Oh, yeah.
And I was like, yeah.
And then I was like, come on, can we go
like send us into the maintenance bay?
I love Googling pictures of Space Mountain with the lights on.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
We got sent off.
We got sent off to the left recently.
We will tell that story at a different time.
But we got sent.
We were going to Space Mountain and you go to the right and you go up the hill.
We were going, going, going.
Also, we took a left and we went, what the hell is another way?
What the fuck was the left?
Well, we are with a person that will be a guest and we'll see if he wants to tell
the story, honestly, I'll tell you off after.
It's just a little secret.
This is you can't tell this.
Well, I feel like your spoilers.
No, no, this is big news.
This is big news.
Yeah, this is a big this is going to tease.
This is people going to be like, oh, have you guys seen Club 33?
Yes, we did.
We all get together.
After the you were you went to the That's From Disneyland gallery.
We did. We did a show there.
And you were on Paul's show and we got to go to Club 33 with those
foot with the the craft who did the.
Actually, yeah.
How was it? How was your.
Oh, wait. Well, OK. Yeah. Club 33, first of all. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, you've talked about on the podcast.
I was going to say, what do I know that?
Well, I'll tell you what I what I've done
a numerous times now that is is the is the VIP tour, which anyone can do.
Anyone can pay for it.
But I because I'm like on TV,
I get it like so when you pay the when you do the VIP tour,
what you normally do is you just get like in the in the fast pass lines
on every ride, I think.
But because I'm on TV, I get in the exits again, the exits.
And so I get to see the kind of behind the scenes of every ride.
And they're like, please don't take pictures.
It's very cool. Oh, man.
Have you seen anything weird that we would know?
It's mostly you know, it's it just reminds me of like when I worked at a restaurant,
like you see like ship schedules and you see lockers.
And it's pretty it's pretty what you would expect.
So strange that it's just a play.
And really, it doesn't you think that might ruin the magic.
But I find that no, I think that's true.
I find it cooler. I like seeing the back because I because I
we come from the theater. Sure.
You know, there's a backstage and then there's when you're on stage.
And so if you view the whole thing as a theatrical experience, no, it's fine.
Maybe makes you appreciate more that like, but it isn't magic.
There's human beings putting this together just like any job.
I use the star tours bathroom.
Dan, when I because I did I went with a person who's on TV.
So we got to do that.
The stars are spoilers.
Yeah, we talked about that.
It's Jeff Garland. I'm Jeff Garland.
He took. But yeah, there's a we went in like a little side door.
And the guy was like, do you want to use the bathroom?
And I went, oh, my God, of course, there's a secret little bathroom.
It's not for regular guests, just for employees.
And they let me use it. And I was thrilled.
What was it like? All over it.
You got it so messy.
Yeah, I marked it. I marked my territory.
Never be able to last to use the star tours.
It was unexciting.
It's like a standard bathroom.
Yeah, it was not like there was wrecks in there like cheering me on.
It wasn't blue milk in the toilet.
No, there was no blue milk.
It was not spending the money on like the they're not spending
the money to like entertain the employees.
No, no. In fact, they want the opposite. Yeah. Sure. Sure.
But Rachel, did you bid on anything?
It's a That's from Disneyland exhibit.
Yeah, I I bid and I and I got
us the a poster from when Splash Mountain opened.
I want to say it's a poster from 1989.
I got some.
I mean, they're very cool, but like they're they're these kind of souvenir
souvenir, like I want to say 30th anniversary
commemorative haunted mansion like brick bookends.
Oh, great. Which was it was I guess it was it was a Disney item
that they were selling at the time.
And I bid like looking back on it, like way too much money on those.
But that thing like I got to do an auction a couple of years prior
and it was not nearly as bad that that's from Disneyland
when everything spiked insanely, like three times what the one I went to.
So when I went to the original auction, it said the sky bucket was going.
The starting price was six thousand dollars.
That's what it said.
So I really thought and I was like and everything was like kind of personal.
I really thought I could get this sky bucket.
And I was like, all right, it's not going to be six thousand dollars.
Maybe it'll go up to fifteen thousand dollars.
And I was I was willing to spend like a chunk of change
for that Disneyland sky bucket because I rode the sky buckets as a kid.
I mean, I have I not only have a video of sky buckets, I have a video that my mom
because my mom grew up in Southern California.
There's a video of her and her parents at Disneyland in the in the 60s
in a sky bucket.
So like that is a that is a huge.
Oh, my God. To have a sky bucket in my backyard, like that would have been
the budget for like my backyard decoration. Yeah.
Just never. You don't spend that every. No, no, no, no.
So I was I was prepared to buy a sky bucket.
And then when they the fact that they had online voting.
So the starting the starting bid for the sky bucket was one hundred thousand.
As soon as it began.
And you're there in person.
I'm there in person.
I specifically wanted the sky bucket.
I think I went both days, but I was waiting for the fucking sky bucket.
And when the starting bid came on at a hundred thousand.
A bid from Brunei has come in.
It was it was devastating.
It was absolutely devastating because I was fucking there.
I was there. I was there in the room.
And then Drew Carey was a couple of rows in front of me.
He tried to bid on a Dumbo car and he was in the mix.
And the host of prices, right?
Is bidding in front of you.
And he was in the mix.
And then it went up.
He was in the mix up until it was like maybe three hundred fifty thousand dollars.
Whoa. And then like it hit like half a million.
And he's like, I'm out.
Drew Carey's tapping out.
Drew Carey tapped out. And someone got it online.
And and I think he cried.
Oh, man. It was it was it was absolutely it was devastating.
You look at the sky bucket.
If I was like, I get this for six thousand dollars.
It sounds great. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, my God. Yeah.
Not insane at all.
Yeah. You'd spend more than that on, like, you know, like redoing a counter or something.
I was shocked. And then there was a rocket rods car.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, we saw that.
Which the guy told us I got to do record.
Yeah, it was a garbage ride.
Nicky Craft, part of the auction, said that he would like part his like first car in high school.
He'd get out of the garage and like, guys, watch the rocket rod.
He'd have to like, it was parked in there, not ding it up with his car.
Growing up with a rocket rod in your garage.
What a really. That's very cool.
Did you do you did record? Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I wasn't nostalgic enough to like want to buy a rocket rod car.
Now, and that thing seemed like it would require a real a team to move it to get it anywhere.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, no one's really like missing rocket rods.
There's a reason the ride.
So for those of you don't know, rocket rods was a short lived
roller coaster that was built over the people mover track.
The people mover, which is a ride that still exists in Florida, doesn't exist here.
And so it was a flat roller coaster.
Yeah. Where they did not have the budget to bank the turns.
Right. So you slowed down at the turn and it wrecked the track
so that the people mover could never come back. Right.
And the and it just made it so being in Tomorrowland for those two years
it was open was just like, like the most unpleasant grinding.
Yeah. Every 10 seconds. Yeah. Remember that? Yeah.
The sound of tomorrow.
And it's like really, if you think about it, has like ruined
Tomorrowland for the last 20 years.
Yeah. Because there's no movement in it.
Those tracks are just sitting there unused.
Yeah. Like the whole thing. They're still there, right?
The track is. Yeah.
Also, the law has changed where like
if the people mover just kept going, it would have been fine
because it would have been grandfathered in.
But there's portions of that ride where you can you can reach out and touch the walls.
And now there has to be a certain
you're not supposed to be able to touch the walls anymore from like an attraction.
It is funny, though, because if it was just existing, they'd be like, yeah, that's fine.
Which is doesn't make any sense.
Well, it's a classic.
It's a it's at that point would have been a classic Disney ride.
I mean, it but it was like a 20 minute long ride.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You didn't really bliss out there.
Yeah. It was a way, as I've said before, is a way to like
because it goes into Space Mountain.
So it like got me accustomed to the feel of Space Mountain
when I was too scared to go on the ride. Yeah.
I missed the old line of Space Mountain.
I miss all those parody commercials.
Oh, you liked all that stuff.
I did. I was like a child.
But like it was a it was a way to take up to take up the time. Yeah.
Well, now you're just now you just don't go in the building at all.
So there's not even like you're barely you have as little time in that tunnel as possible.
Yeah. So there wouldn't be time to watch the videos.
And you'd see the ride.
I remember you'd be watching the videos.
And there was a big window where you could watch people on the ride.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
That's the fall. Yeah.
They still you can kind of see that in the people move in Florida still.
Well, the last time I went, it felt like there was less of that.
But I could be wrong. Yeah.
There were funny people, I feel like.
And I don't quite remember who is in those Space Mountain videos.
But I think somebody I think I believe the actress Kelly Caulfield from In Living Color
was in it and funny in it.
And I'm from blanking somebody.
Somebody famous is in those.
And I'm sure they're all on YouTube.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I think so.
Yeah. Yeah. We'll we'll get to that at some point.
You guys wanted me to talk about Raging Waters.
We do. I'm not rushing you through Disney stuff because there's so much.
There's so much to talk about.
But but yeah, that is the when you when you sent us a couple of ideas,
it felt like this has to be the thing because we know about the history
of Crazy Ex-Girlfriend and Raging Waters.
It seems like it was like a little like, you know, runner slash
slash obsession within the show.
And which seems like so that comes from your upbringing.
Like you grew up near you're like in San Gabriel Valley somewhere.
No, no, I grew up Manhattan Beach.
But the reason the show takes place in San Gabriel Valley was because
a guy that I was in love with lived in the San Gabriel Valley.
And so like I I always tried to find excuses to go to the San Gabriel Valley,
which is never a place that you try to find an excuse to go to.
And so once it was set in the San Gabriel Valley, then they were like,
OK, what's there?
And I remember talking to someone.
I was like, all right, so if you're living in West Covina,
what are the cool jobs?
And they're like in and out of Raging Waters.
Those are the two places you want to work. OK.
And in Raging Waters was and still is like the only water park
I've ever really been to.
It was the first water park I'd been to, definitely.
And that's where you went for special birthday parties when I was in middle school.
And so I I became I was like, oh, my God, we're doing and I'm obsessed
with amusement parks. So I was like, guys, we're we're doing a show
set right next to like a major water park.
We have to talk about it. We have to do that.
So it's so it's just Raging Waters is such a SoCal specific.
And so like, yeah, because the show always wanted to do a plot there,
it became Rebecca's like kind of
it became her Paris.
It became like her dream to go to Raging Waters.
And so when we finally got to shoot there, it was I mean,
it was a whole thing where we contacted them to shoot at Raging Waters.
They hadn't been getting back to us.
So then I was like, fuck it.
And I tweeted, I want to shoot at Raging Waters.
They're not getting back to us.
Who can help me?
This guy, Gary, who I know at Warner Brothers,
knew the head of PR for Raging Waters, put me in touch
with the head of Raging Waters, and we made it work.
And what they did was they opened up.
We did just it just shut down for the season in,
I want to say September.
And we wanted to shoot in November.
So there was still water, like stagnant water in a couple of the rides.
They were about to drain the rides when we called.
So they they left.
So they we managed.
We always wanted to set set a scene on this ride, Dark Hole,
which is an actual the actual name of the ride.
And that that happened to have water in it.
So what they did was they showed you wanted Dark Hole specifically.
We wanted. Wow. And it's not the Dark Hole.
It is just Dark Hole.
Dark Hole. It's just Dark Hole.
So they so they
they had that running and then they had Neptune's Revenge running
just as kind of background for us.
So they got the rides moving.
But there was no there's no way to heat the water at Raging Waters,
because when it's when it's hot out, it's hot out or the or the
maybe they have a heater normally, but the park wasn't fully in service.
So they put water there. Right. But it wasn't heated.
So Skyler Aston, I we when we rode Dark Hole
and I had a GoPro in one of the show, basically rode it about five times.
And the water was like 50 degree water.
And so we were so they had
the heaters every time we came off the ride, they had heaters for us.
And they had like immediately would wrap us in warm towels.
And it was the one time that I have
I have imbibed in alcohol on set, just literally to keep myself
just to warm as if you were freezing to death.
I couldn't have done it.
I couldn't have done it sober.
It was it was really little.
So we needed volunteers to go down the other slide
just for like B roll in the background and little kids volunteered to do it
because kids are crazy.
But yes, Skyler and I riding Dark Hole over and over and over again.
And it's a it's a it's an indoor, you know, it's an indoor dark ride.
Even colder than probably.
It was so cold. It was it was so so.
I think there's a I don't know if we use it, but there's
there's a scene where I'm getting into the raft
and I went to trick my brain.
I went, oh, my God, the water feels so good.
Oh, it's so warm.
The water is so warm.
I just kept saying this water feels so good.
Method method. It was so cold.
It was it was so cold.
That sounds like something like you would see on like a mission impossible
after they're explaining how to make it.
And it's like I had to go in 50 degree water.
It was the coldest water I ever realized.
Tom, obviously. Yeah, yeah.
We hear that the making of like Titanic. Right.
It's like what we were in really cold. Right.
Because that sounds like you got blankets on.
It sounds. Yeah. Yeah.
Every time it was very it was very, very, very cold.
And so there is a so I had a GoPro.
I wish I could find this footage somewhere.
So I had a GoPro for a couple of the times I went down the water slide.
And I was holding the GoPro when I got back when we because they took a tram.
They would take us in a tram back up to the entrance of the ride.
And at that point, I was I was like drunk.
I was drunk and freezing.
I was like, what did you drink?
What was the I had some I had some vodka.
Sweet. Good.
I kept it very simple.
I mean, this is actually literally goes against everything.
I mean, this is very unprofessional for me to admit.
Hopefully I don't get sued by CBS, but like I need you are drinking ever clear.
You're not doing 90 proof.
I needed vodka like inside.
Literally to warm me from the inside.
Like a snow dog, like a rescue dog coming to get you for like the barrel.
Yeah, it made it made doing that seem like bearable.
And and but I have the GoPro and I'm like, who's shivering in a in a car
in the tram going back up to the entrance of raising raging waters.
But I'm also kind of drunk.
So I'm just like, it's so it's so cold.
How are you doing, Skylar?
Are you getting I could do this like six more times.
It's really cool.
Oh, I'm so cold. I don't know.
I'm just from the Netherlands.
How's Skylar?
I mean, that's what I felt really terrible about is he was this new.
He was the new guy who joined the cast.
It was I mean, it was I guess it was three or four episodes into him
being on the show and I was this poor guy out of everyone on the show
has to ride the 15 degree water slide with me.
And he says, I've muscled it into existence like this almost didn't happen.
And I insisted it happened.
You will get it.
Yeah, it was your mission.
There are so many times that it didn't have to have happened.
And the fact that I willed it into existence
and then like was like, come on, Skylar, you're right.
But also for a satisfying story arc,
you guys had built up Raging Waters as a reference point for so long.
Oh, it was it was wonderful.
And had had there been a world where the whole park could have been open
if we shot it like during the summer there, I mean,
I'd wanted to do a Raging Waters opera episode.
Like there was a lot I wanted to do.
But we worked around, OK, we can open up to we can open up like really two rides.
What can we do with that?
So it's interesting.
And you knew that by the like,
was it during the writing process or was it like a later production thing or
it was interesting logistics of.
Yeah, it was a mix.
We started breaking the episode months before we
we knew for a fact we could film there.
But but when we started the season, I gave the line producer heads up.
I was like, let's already be in contact with Raging Waters.
I know I want to do something in Raging Waters.
And then they weren't because they were like shutting down for the summer.
Then they weren't getting back to us, because by the time I told the line
producer that it was like July, so they were in the thick of the summer.
And then you're dealing with kids dying of heat stroke,
dealing with the dead kids. Exactly.
So I think we had the script written.
And then once we knew this is what we could get at Raging Waters,
I went on a location scout with the director of the episode, Jack,
and with the writer of the episode, I think it was Alana.
Yeah, it was Alana Alana Pena.
And so we rewrote parts of the episode to fit that location scout.
Oh, OK. OK, OK.
Is that what inspired the specifically the choice of the
the snack area?
Sharky's is the setting of the musical number.
So we knew we wanted to do I hate everything but you a musical
number in Raging Waters.
And then the fact that like we could have we could somehow get the rights
to have sharkies and have that whole area at our disposal was like
we have to use this not affiliated with the Tex-Mex brand.
No, we're separate, separate sharkies, not affiliated.
But like we get all the cred for having sharkies there
because that was just an area that so right behind where sharky was
was is the main part of the park, all of which was completely dry
and completely shut down.
Oh, it's like wave pool kind of stuff is just barren.
So I walked I walked past the I'll show you pictures.
I have pictures like next to the barren wave pool, the barren vortex,
the barren like children's player. It's all dry. Creepy.
It was very borderline creepy, but like eerily beautiful.
Oh, yeah. When getting to this is like weird nightmare
feel like that you're in in a bit like not abandoned, but a closed down.
So most of the park was was shut down.
And so we couldn't like, you know, in an ideal world,
we would have been in that kind of open area.
And it would have been more of a montage of going of us going on different rides.
It would have maybe you would have set parts of I hate everything,
but you on different rides.
But because we only had two rides at our disposal and originally
we wanted to do the lazy river, but to fill up a lazy river.
I mean, so we couldn't do that.
But luckily, the whole sharkies refreshment area was directly across
from all the dry water rides.
So we all you had to do was just shoot in that one direction
or shoot in the kind of, I guess, like 180 degrees direction
and just not show the stuff directly behind it.
The saddest water park.
Like background holding and stuff was all in the like dry part of the water park.
Just in this barren pit.
I thought we should have just said we should have just set
have the background kids in the in the dry wave pool.
It was very surreal.
It was very bizarre and very surreal.
And I want to say, I think we tried to sneak some shots of like the dry rides,
but it's it's hard to fake water.
Yeah, I would imagine. Sure. CGI.
The worst looking floppy water.
Yeah. Were you just so relieved?
Like, OK, we got we did this chunk of the episode here.
Or do you still feel like you have some sort of a raging waters project in you?
Oh, no, I feel pretty good.
I feel like that's good.
I think that I got I really, I think, blew my wad on the thrill,
because I grew up in Southern California, as you know, which is a very sunny
but very like almost like bland chain based place.
And I was a very kind of big fan of musicals, big fan of like, you know,
when you think about all the classic musicals, movie musicals,
it takes place in like New York City, these very kind of
lush, East Coasty, old fashioned looking places
and where every little bookstore is magical.
Yes, exactly. It feels like whimsical.
So the idea that we got to do numerous musical numbers
in these like strip mall chain places is is exactly what like
I and what I only wanted the show to be.
So I'm I'm good now on like I'm boring.
Weird. Yeah, I mean, I still would love to.
I'm going to do some stuff that's Amusement Park based
because I haven't even begun to really touch, like,
dip my toe into like my love of amusement parks.
And I thought of doing
when I when I have like the time, I thought of doing like a mini album
to listen to specifically when just when you're at Disneyland,
where it's like, here's the song to play in your earbuds
as you're like entering this line.
But that's cool.
But I mean, I did a I did a Hanukkah album
like six years ago called Suck It Christmas, which like to this day
still has not made back its money.
So I am I am a very big fan of doing like niche ideas
that only 100 people will enjoy.
So I don't know if I'll get around to that, but I am.
So a lot of it requires time and a willingness to
be had not get to see any financial return.
Yeah, exactly.
So I have to I would self release it or whatever.
I would also have to probably avoid the calling at Disneyland.
I don't know. I don't know.
I would even. Yeah, well, in that weird, it's akin to the like,
you know, timing up, you know, Dark Side of the Moon to play with Wizard of Oz.
That's what it really is. You can't like say that it's.
There's a scene in Almost Famous, I think, where now it's on the DVD.
But you like, OK, so put on, you know, that one.
So they somehow obliquely allude to Stairway to Heaven
since they couldn't get the rights to just like if you play Stairway
to Heaven at home and then watch the scene and time it up correctly.
Oh, is that true?
I think, yeah, there's something like that.
I forget. But like, they can't say it legally.
They have to imply in other media like.
Yeah, I have to ask my lawyer what exactly I could do because I couldn't have any
of the audio from any of the amusement parks. Sure. Sure.
Yeah. But could I legally sync up a song
to like exactly match like the line to Peter Pan?
Mm hmm. You could probably say like sync,
sync up this one to the pirate one.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. The ghost place.
But also, are they really going to sue me?
Well, because like YouTube, you can have a ride through video
with the songs playing. Yeah.
So like Peter Pan songs are on the Peter Pan ride through.
So it does feel like there's a kind of a gray area there.
They also something really cool, really quickly,
because a bunch of people that I grew up with also had yearlong passes to Disneyland.
There was this guy, Zan, I knew, who had a Jeep who he'd been borrowing.
He had like his cousin's Jeep for the summer and the school parking lot,
like his high school parking lot.
It was like the high school near mine.
The high school parking lot was like all inside.
And he basically had been on Indiana Jones so much.
He memorized every twist and turn of the Indiana Jones ride to sync up with.
And he had the soundtrack of the ride.
So one day he took us all in his Jeep and he sped through this parking lot.
It was a Saturday and did every exact twist and turn
that you would do on the Indiana Jones ride in this parking lot, in a real Jeep,
including like really tight turns to the point where I was like,
oh, this is how teens die.
This is exactly how teens die all the time.
And it was one of the most like thrilling two and a half minutes of my life.
Damn. Wow.
Knowing, I mean, speeding in a car, whatever,
but speeding to the exact left and right turn ratio.
It was just what an exhilarating time.
Wow. I'm going to put the thing.
I'm not going to do that, but I do kind of want to like listen to it now
to see if I know what what's what.
Like, oh, now we're on the bridge by listening to this song.
Yeah, like when I when I get to that,
that that bump up, like I know that we're on some sort of precipice
and there's a dip there. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I got certain music cues sort of time up to little sensations.
Right. That's cool.
That's yeah. That's scary. How old were you? Sixteen.
OK, so yeah, that is the most brazen time.
The height of recklessness.
I was going to say it's such a it's the dorkiest recklessness I've ever heard.
Yeah, it's so great because it's both at once.
If that had been how I died, I mean,
well, that says it all.
Geez. I mean, yeah.
You want to know the person.
I kind of still think that's how I that's what happened,
is that I died and this is all just like after after life.
And you're surreal, like having a show and everything is like. Yeah.
The having the musical show that gets to take place in Southern California
that also like talks about mental illness feels very like when I grew up,
I want to be like an astronaut ballerina.
Like it's very it's very on the nose.
To the point where I still don't trust it. Yeah.
Sure. I would imagine.
Yeah, that's how I feel every time I have a glass of wine in front of Rex.
A ultimate dream fantasy come true that you've died.
This is too good. You're dead.
But I paid 16 bucks for a glass of wine and I'm drinking it next to a wine
that Padme had.
I thought you just meant a wine in front of Rex here.
Oh, sure. I thought you meant just like that's all you want.
I have one at home, too.
And I definitely definitely a lot of one just the one.
This is your place, right?
No, it's my place. Yeah.
So he greeted you, but I was here calling the dog.
That was your dog. That makes sense.
And you know, it's when you leave, we'll make you shake hands with Mike Rex.
Fantastic. Yeah.
Mine's at home, so you can skip that.
I OK with the with with your raging waters thing.
I was realizing how you are part of a very proud tradition of things
that have filmed at Raging Waters.
I feel like probably like I think Hurricane Harbor, probably closer to
Hollywood, more in the TMZ, the 30 mile zone at this point.
But it wasn't open to the to the late 90s.
Yes. So a lot of stuff in the 80s.
I think Raging Waters opened in 83, I believe.
And so it was like the closest Hollywood back lot water park, essentially.
And the list is just that you get the list that you have joined.
I find so delightful.
I want to say there's been other various things
and probably like music videos and commercials.
But I think Craziest Girlfriend was the first narrative
projects to film in Raging Waters since Norbit.
I think you are.
No, always sunny did an episode there before you really.
Yes. Oh, I always said it did an episode because they said they were
because when you when you film at a place, you have to send them
the script beforehand so they can make sure you're presenting it in a good light.
Always sunny shot at Raging Waters posing for another water park.
But I think when they did it, they didn't reveal that part of the script
was that like the water was filled with piss and shit or whatever.
Like it ended up being like a pretty negative episode about water parks
and raging and it kind of took Raging Waters by surprise.
OK, so we weren't saying it was Raging Waters like you did or like Norbit.
No, they weren't.
Norbit Norbit didn't say it was Raging Waters.
Norbit is it is Raging Waters.
They're wearing the shirts.
So, yeah, so like you can.
So but we were very careful not to like disparage like Raging Waters,
like like in the episode, Greg hates fun and he hates the sun
and he hates general fun, like we couldn't say water parks are fucking disgusting.
They're filled with piss like kids are peeing in the water
and people are dying of heat stroke.
Like we couldn't say that.
Sharkies gives me diarrhea.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Like we couldn't we couldn't.
It was all like, you know, implied like Rebecca like love the chili cheese dog.
So he was like, I I'm I'm not going to partake in that.
So you didn't even have it to me.
OK, yeah. Weird little rules.
Oh, interesting.
Well, they did approve the character
Rasputia going down a big, tall slide after saying,
I must show you how a bitch go down a slide.
Of course, that famous scene where she where she causes a wave to drown
a bunch of children. Yeah, yeah.
I think there were trailers that were only that scene.
Yeah, that's all I know about Norbit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I guess I watched I was like laughing and clapping and watching it.
I got to say, I don't maybe I'm underrated.
That's your reaction every time you watch Norbit.
Yeah, yeah. The hundreds of doings.
OK, elsewhere in this list, Justin Bieber's Beauty in the Beat music video
films there, which including an in Raging Waters appearance
by the now retired Nicki Minaj.
Oh, God. Yeah.
She fitted in before her sure to last retirement.
You can have a family and still still rap anyway.
You would say yes.
That's also like a PR stunt, right?
That's like fun to say you retired and you come back.
It's like when Barbra Streisand said it was her last concert.
Yeah, it's like a Sony Disney Spider-Man stuff.
It's all a play. It's all a game.
I don't know if it's that.
It's just working to earn more money.
This will be resolved by the end of the year.
Nicki Minaj will be in the Spider-Man.
Yeah, she's being as they're trading her.
Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure filmed there.
It's Waterloo in that we're in a place.
Oh, yeah. Napoleon and he ends up at Waterloo.
They watch my recent obsession, a really great episode of Raging Waters.
Where there's there's a water slide sabotage going on.
Somebody's going around loosening bolts.
Oh, yeah.
And they think it's a creepy guy who's been walking around,
who's like yelling at all the lifeguards about his son's recent suicide
at Raging Waters.
And so they kind of unfairly blame him.
I don't want to give away the ending.
Obviously, of course, also they would need to hire
the Baywatch lifeguards who work on the coast to
like temporarily be at Raging Waters.
It's one of those.
That's a like porn forced plot scenario.
Like why? Why are they?
So you're binging Baywatch?
I've been real deep into Baywatch.
It's everything I can do to not talk about it on every episode.
But Baywatch has been recently remastered and it's on Amazon and Hulu.
And it looks legitimately great because it was 35 millimeter film.
So there's shots where I'm like, this is a great looking.
It's just a good restoration.
I feel like I'm appreciating and appreciating in a Tarantino kind of way.
It looks really great.
And then it's the dumbest shit you've ever seen.
And they couldn't.
My favorite thing about it, they couldn't get the rights to all the music
that it originally aired with.
So it's all new sound like music made this year.
So that's all this bizarre like one note off.
That's like I look the I've looked ones up like, OK,
so that was spice up your life.
But now it's some generic song like, hey, hey, let's go.
Oh, that's like the state DVDs.
Oh, do they have a lot of like a lot of like a lot of like Nirvana sound alike?
I guess everything on MTV back in the day.
Yeah. Yeah.
So like you they how can you not have the rights to that music?
I'm confused.
I don't know. Like they didn't get a license.
They paid for like 20 years into the future.
Yeah. Yeah.
There's a lot of I think TV shows.
I think Daria had that problem, too, when they were reissuing.
Because I think like MTV, MTV had some anything.
Right. They had some general licensing agreement with them.
I don't know what they watch this problem was, but I don't know.
But I love the and honestly, I've gone back and watched clips with the real music.
Like there's a good vibrations one.
Oh, that's the best I just found.
I found out the original episode had good vibrations and in the new
the one that's on Amazon now, it's a made up Beach Boys song with the lyric.
She reminds me of ice cream.
It is ever at every corner.
Wow. Like that.
She reminds me of ice cream.
Vastly better than good vibrations.
So these Baywatch, the Baywatch special editions, as I'm going to call them.
Yeah, those are the Baywatch remastered.
I think they call it that in the ads.
Yeah. Those are the superior cuts, you would say.
I think so. I think they ended up finding new humor.
I think it sounds like you do a podcast based just all about Baywatch.
I think we're all nearing the point of like without doing our own spin off
podcasts where we're just each other's guests.
And I would very happily.
I came up with my watch remastered the podcast.
Yeah, we should do it. Yeah.
I sure. Yeah. Why not? Yeah.
Let's say confirm if you're interested audience, but it doesn't matter
because we're doing it anyway.
I recommend it.
But then my favorite thing that's filmed at Raging Waters and that I have
such strong memories of wild and crazy kids.
Oh, right. Nickelodeon.
Nickelodeon game show.
Just to be honest.
Yeah, I think they filmed at a park near my house one time.
And and I saw it after the fact.
And I was I was livid.
I was livid that they were that somehow they
filmed at Polylog Park and I didn't know about.
Oh, man. Oh, bummer.
That is heartbreaking.
Oh, when they go on the rollercoasters and they have to you to try to eat
a burger and fries like wall on a rollercoaster.
Yeah, they did magic mountain stuff.
I think. Yeah. Yeah.
OK, they did a thing exactly like that.
That was one of the competitions in Raging Waters.
It was parents versus kids.
And they had to do things like unpeeled bananas
and keep ice cream cones from melting and dropping into the water while on water
slides. And it's a kids versus adults thing.
So there's this great stuff where it is phrased probably not the best.
Like Donnie Jeff Coates or one of those is like.
So what do you think? Do you think you can beat your son?
And then later on, similarly, a dad answering a question.
All right. Well, the pressure's on, but we're going to beat those kids.
So that's a delight.
Look up those episodes on Daily Motion, where they're available
with very poor VHS quality.
I'm the west of Internet video streaming for Daily Motion.
I know. I miss like that.
I mean, because because I I'm sure like you guys,
like I grew up in like the heyday of like Nickelodeon.
We're gross. We're going to play with slime and GAC.
And like, you know, I've gone to a couple general meetings at Nickelodeon
like years ago where I was like, hey, what happened to kids being gross?
What happened to like loving?
How they all have brands now?
They all have brands.
Brands and something like hydro flasks.
And it's all but it's all like very clean and neat and aspirational.
Like what happened to kids just like fucking being like Booger Town?
Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
And there was also there was a grotesque aspect to Nickelodeon, too, with shows
like Wienerville is just so bizarre.
You remember that show?
That's any weird in your good.
That's like a bad maybe a bad example.
But yeah, no, Ren Stimpy is fucking weird and gross.
Weird and gross.
Don't whiz on the electric fence.
This is like Ren.
Is that from Ren and Stimpy?
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, my God.
I literally just realized that because a guy in high school would play that on
guitar and I thought he made it up.
Oh, man.
Oh, he was getting like cred for being like a random comedy guy.
I never knew Don't Whiz on the Electric Fence.
So that's such a dirty song.
Yeah. Yeah.
In the kids' show. Yeah.
My friend had said, because if you whiz on the electric fence,
bolts of electricity will go up your penis and you'll die. Yeah.
I imagine that's not that.
Yeah, that was a no.
The song was just don't whiz on the electric fence.
But Ren like unzips off.
He suddenly has a fly in his skin and he like unzips himself.
Yeah, it's really unnerving.
He on something Stimpy likes.
I'm going to as revenge.
It's so crazy.
One of the first body horror things I ever saw was that episode where they're in
jail with that guy who's like losing his mind and his ears just
just close up on his ear, which slides off of his head.
And I remember being like a child being like, oh, my God, what the hell?
Like it was so like scarring.
I liked it, but it was scarring.
You know, I remember I remember an episode where Stimpy got really skinny
and he needed to gain weight.
And so they took liposuction fat and they made it into milkshakes for him.
And he had to drink it.
You drink a bunch of fat.
Like I remember even as like a kid being like, this is too much.
This gratuitous. Sure. Yeah.
Oddly, they were not.
Now I feel like every every kids show has to be vetted by like
30 groups of psychologists.
That one should have been vetted.
Everyone came out about the co-creator.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's why it's like, why did the one creator leave the show
so early in the run 20 years later?
Oh, OK. We have. All right.
Why did he? Oh, it's a bit.
It's one of the grimest issues you've ever.
Well, let's just say it's a grooming situation. Oh, no.
Yeah, it's real bad. Yeah.
But I know when nobody.
He's the only creator.
You know the way creators of shows just leave one season in.
I thought there was only John.
There's another guy who did a lot of like little girl children's TV.
I want to say it was like Lizzie McGuire.
Oh, well, the creator.
That's a whole other thing.
Yeah. The creator of all those kids shows.
So the Nickelodeon shows, not the Disney shows.
So there was another rumor that like that creepy guy got like
this is a this is a rumor.
Yeah, sweet names out.
Allegedly. I'm remembering this from hearing it like 10 years ago
that like he got like Jamie Lynn Spears pregnant.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, we're talking about.
Yeah. Who else are just like we Nickelodeon says goodbye
after a great career to thanks for the memories and you know what?
Why just suddenly?
That's not suspicious at all.
Yep. Just see you later.
People just leave lucrative.
Please do not Google the phrase open secret.
Please do not.
Yeah. Yeah.
So, yeah, you guys can look into that if you know.
If I was her wise.
Yeah, good.
Let me I was going to link to boot back to body horror with the, you know,
and I don't want to I don't want to go around, you know, saying negative things
about Raging Waters and Ivan Bin and you know, they were they were great to you
and your show.
There's there's Yelp reviews that are not thrilled with things
that have that have happened there.
One, I just really liked this this review.
I liked this assertion.
You never know what these Yelp people, they're exaggerating or the but
I don't know.
There was feces and vomit and sanitary napkins on the floors of the bathroom,
which also had no TP or paper towels.
Trash was overflowing onto the floors and there was an enormous amount of bees.
On top of it, bees, bees,
so that's great.
But then also there is this other review.
And I thought of this with body horror because the
it's a review by his and his Yelp name is Kenny G.
I can't imagine he is the smooth sex man.
But but could be.
But it is this review is such a novel.
I mean, I couldn't possibly read the whole thing.
It takes up like you got to keep scrolling and scrolling.
It's, you know, half of that page.
And it's it is so bonkers.
There's like scenes between characters in his review.
There's hashtags like a hashtag doesn't link to anything
in the middle of a Yelp review.
That's not how it works.
But there's also the assertion that he says he has a lot of complaints,
but then says, like, I don't really like to go in the water at these places
because you might, you know, come out of the water with 14 toes and two penises.
You know what?
That's a pretty that's a pretty major assertion.
I'm not sure is correct.
But the main yes, I was sorry.
The main thing about this art, this review is it has a motif.
And he starts the motif at the beginning by saying, don't go chase in waterfalls.
Please stick to the rivers and the lakes that you're used to.
I know that you're going to have it all another and all that you're moving too fast.
I'm starting to think that TLC might have been light years ahead of their time.
And then the entire review keeps quoting TLC.
It's a motif throughout it.
And he finds crazy ways just like when you come out of the water,
you might look gross. You're not going to be too.
You're going to look very unpretty.
He works the name fan mail in the name of their album. Right.
He says, you know, try and stetizing yourself from an unexplainable rash
that no scrub can get rid of.
This is a to applaud that one.
I can't really manage to fit in those scrubs.
This is a college entrance essay that the teachers like, OK, nice first effort.
We're not going to send this one in.
But let's go back to the original idea.
It's going to get an hour.
Something we can salvage.
He does. This person needs like a creative outlet.
And Yelp is the place for it.
I mean, I applaud it.
It is one of the most creative.
And I don't know why TLC needed to be a part of it.
But I haven't seen a bunch of band references jammed into Yelp
review before this good work.
Was the San Dimas raging waters not the San Jose or Sacramento location?
No, yes. Specifically San Dimas.
That's pretty much what we've been covering.
Right. We should say there are other ones.
But there are two others.
Well, and and there is a they sold this one.
There's a raging waters in Wildwood, New Jersey, unaffiliated.
Has the same name owned by the Maury's company.
Maury's Pier runs most of the entertainment in Wildwood, New Jersey.
At this point, the parent company, Palace Entertainment, owns Kennywood,
Dutch Wonderland and the new Cartoon Network Hotel across from Dutch Wonderland.
Both in all in Pennsylvania and the Noah's Ark Water Park in the Wisconsin Dells.
Now that's my.
Given thumbs up.
That was your favorite.
No, no. Yeah.
A couple of times. Is it good?
How religious is it?
It's not I haven't been in like a deck over a decade.
So I wasn't I didn't notice it being very religious.
It was like a fun cartoon version of the religious story.
But I don't I would like to when we go, we should go.
I think we're going to go with you guys.
Haven't done like a gotten a van and done a road trip to all the major
like amusement parks. Yeah, that might be the next.
Because we want to go to Dali.
We got to go to Daliwood.
We got to do a lot of this.
So, yeah, there's some money who scolded us into doing this podcast.
In the beginning also said, why have you got into a van and gone to all the places?
Have you joined the have you joined the roller coaster enthusiasts?
Not yet. We haven't done that either.
I've looked into I've looked I've looked into doing that.
But then you just need to take a lot of your time out of the year
to travel and go on different roller coasters.
You can do roller coasters.
Wait, is like a quota you have to fill?
Is it a commitment of some kind? What is your commitment of some kind?
I think there's dues. Right.
And then they have special events.
You just have to I mean, in order to take advantage of it,
you have to be willing to travel to roller coasters
because there are events at different amusement parks. Right.
You should have on David Hall, who was on my show,
was a performer at Kings Island. Oh, boy.
And he did all the shows there, but also rode all the rides and is a continuing.
He continues to be a huge roller coaster enthusiast.
Wow. Sure. Yeah, that sounds great.
In the organization, he's in the club.
No, no, no. OK. Casually.
Oh, sorry. I was eating crackers and got down my bra.
It happens. Hey, everything's fine.
I'll just find random crumbs. Sure.
Save for later.
We were talking about I don't want to be so negative either,
but we were talking about the Sacramento location.
I don't know. Do we find you found this?
I don't know. I don't know where you're going with this.
I'm very excited.
I was going to read the KCRA
NBC Channel three headline on the website.
40 person brawl at Raging Waters started over beach towel.
Man remains hospitalized after being attacked.
This is August 26th, 2019. Yeah, I actually saw this headline.
I mean, I think what we're learning is water parks would be great
if it weren't for the people attending them.
Oh, yeah. All you need is all you need is like a water park.
And just if it was to yourself, it would be perfect.
Which you sort of got to have and some vodka. And it was great.
Mm hmm. Yes. Besides almost dying of hypothermia.
Yeah, but you know, you'll know the memories.
The memories were so special.
What's the disorientation increased by what appears to be Raging Waters
is one of their big innovations is multiple the water slides in the darkness.
Yeah. Which they're very obsessed with that.
There's Dark Hole, there's Neptune's Revenge, there's the vortex.
You know, there's there's just only so much you can do with a water slide.
And especially I can't imagine that Raging Waters has.
I don't think they have the budget of like, certainly not like a Disney.
Oh, absolutely. Yeah.
But I don't even think of like a Six Flags Hurricane Harbor.
And so like, there's just not your resources are limited.
And the one thing you can do is make a water slide that is nearly in the dark.
That is the like cheapest theme for sure.
Yeah. And it is just it is very disorienting.
Dark Hole is very disorienting.
And yet they did manage to get some major theming
and even some characters into the genre of dark water slide.
And I know you know about this with the slide Dr.
Von Darke's Tunnel of You know what?
That actually I think I'm that was the one that was open for us.
It wasn't Neptune's Revenge.
It was Dr. Von Darke's Tunnel. Oh, OK. OK.
So that was this is referenced in a song in the show elsewhere. Yes.
I am this seems like for Raging Water, because I'm looking at the slides.
They're all whatever one is called High Extreme.
That's not anything.
There's not a lot of like red meat in terms of what the and we're about themes
or theme theme park play like we like characters exclusive to the parks.
Yeah. We talk about that all the time.
No, Dr. Von Darke is a different is a different beast.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm pretty impressed by it.
And while it seems to me like, OK, Dr.
Von Darke's Tunnel of Terror is not it's at multiple water parks
and they aren't even all raging waters.
And I am actually forgetting offhand the name one of the other places
where I think water country, which is in like New Hampshire, I believe.
So I don't think the I don't think you maybe you could tell me
if there's any evidence of the character.
Is there any physical representation of Dr.
Von Darke? I have I have some pictures of our location scout.
OK, yes, please do. OK, great.
So there is so.
So I have pictures from our location scout.
And as you'll see, I'll pass this around.
There is a character named Dr.
Von Darke, and it says there's a sign that says School of Darkology.
It's not about turning off the lights.
It's about turning on the darkness.
And here's a picture.
He's got a joker phrase.
My friend Jack in front of that sign.
If you zoom in, you can see what Dr.
Von Darke looks like the motto of the School of Darkology.
By the way, the School of Darkology is bright yellow with purple trim.
It looks like a Barbie dream house. Yeah.
And yet it is the School of Darkology.
Hell, yeah, that's fantastic.
And there's a depiction of Dr. Von Darke.
I love this. Is this the only I mean, there's I think there's characters
now in Disney water parks, but this might be the only like
non-brand water park with a character, which I love.
And I think well, I think because the problem is they had Dark Hole
and they're like, fuck, we have another route.
The word dark in it.
We got to differentiate this.
OK, there's going to be a whole character.
There's going to be
we got to make it a premise to differentiate it from Dark Hole.
Yeah, I have pictures of the school.
You scroll through this.
You can see pictures of the of the empty wave pool.
Oh, boy. Oh, wonderful.
OK, you're good.
Oh, man. Sorry.
Barren water park.
I know everyone loves if you like, you can see.
Imagine the saddest water park.
Imagine the words high extreme with no one around.
Dry as a bone.
Not nearly as brought to life as it is in that Bieber video at night, even
a lot more active.
So that phrase that you just said, his motto
very delightfully, I this morning discovered
OK, this is from the YouTube channel of my I already can't remember
the name of the place.
So water country, I believe.
And this is a little ad where they're announcing new water slides for 2012.
And there is a host who's probably a real employee of the park.
And then and there's a bunch of construction workers.
They're working on the next slide.
But then something unpredictable happens.
With that said, we're proud to announce that we're adding a new attract.
Hey, who turned out the lights?
There is a certain amount of money.
It's about turning on the darkness.
And he's German. Yeah.
Dr. Von Darks, total of terror, just one ride.
And you'll be begging your mommy for a nightlight.
Yeah, there is a living actor playing Dr.
Von Dark so fint.
And then here's another quick hit from another.
It's all voiceover in the thing.
It's like it's voiceover.
He's not actually moving his mouth that he's just like looking at you.
He might be a pantomime actor. Yeah.
I think he well, he might be here's another money as you hire a voiceover actor.
Sure. One day.
And then you just get like a back.
You get like guy being paid extra rates another day.
Oh, different. Yeah.
Well, Baywatch, my beloved Baywatch is full of that a lot of.
Hey, watch out. You're running too fast.
Or somebody they didn't pay.
So here's another Dr.
Von Dark.
You're not as a dog.
Are you?
Well, three introduces.
And then it's kind of the same from there.
OK, that was a close up.
So they did. Yes, he may have earned like two under.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
So this fucking rules.
But I do. It does seem to me, first of all, I think we can all agree.
It fucking rules.
And then but it does seem to me like what is actually going on
at the school of darkology because you see him flip a switch and then it gets dark.
So his evil technology seems to be turning off a light.
Right. But he calls it turning on the dark.
Turning which is different.
Spider-Man and turning off the dark.
Whoa. Wow.
I'm clear also whether or not you're a test subject
or a student or Dr.
Von Darks wife or Dr.
Von Dark himself.
When you're writing it, when you're writing it, it's not clear what.
It's not clear what what the premise is.
It's just you're generally in the school of darkology.
They should hand you a little diploma when you get out.
Yeah, absolutely. A waterproof one like a laminated.
I like your premise that you are him and that you're like
you're paying for your sins against the light.
Oh, yeah. The school of darkology has gone haywire.
I like the idea that you're his wife. Yeah.
Yeah, I just like Mrs.
Von Dark, Mrs. Von Dark.
There's just occasional video where it's just like, come
on, our our sons graduations today.
Can you make it?
I have too many dark experiments.
My birthday.
Sometimes it feels like you love dark more than you love me.
Me, me, me.
I've lost all my friends to the darkness.
Like how NASA is expanding the whole Calico mythology.
Maybe it's time for Raging Waters to expand.
Not just expanding the Calico, the ghost.
Yeah, the ghost town and like they're all the rides kind of connect now.
Apparently, Calico Rapids connects to the mine train, connects to the.
And there's mazes now, the haunted mazes.
A couple of them are all connected to the story as well this year.
So I think maybe it's time to expand Dr.
Von Darks presence in Raging Waters.
And Dr.
Von DeWell for Halloween, if they kept it open, Dr.
Von Dark could completely take over Raging Waters.
I mean, it'd be crazy.
It's all his experiments.
Yeah. Oh, man.
And you could get actually hurt because it's night.
Yeah. And you slip and fall.
We'll run a few slides without the water.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Danger.
I would like them to incorporate because I looked up a map of San Dimas
because I didn't really know it.
This park is next to the pudding stone reservoir.
It's beautiful.
Oh, this park is actually in the middle of like a Griffith Park
like area, San Dimas. It's gorgeous.
Oh, wow. Oh, but no actual pudding, I'm assuming.
Like I got excited by that name.
It did look nice from the satellite photos.
You know, after we location scouted, because it is right next to this reservoir,
I had a dream that I was on a waterslide
and that it like shot off, you know, and then you were 100 feet in the air
and you landed in a reservoir and you had to like swim.
And then you got caught onto like another track
while you were like still underwater.
Like I had a really cool ride idea dream.
Wow. Yeah, that sounds great.
Wow. The kind of concoction only Von Dark could be crafty enough.
Von Darkian concoction.
Very von Darkian of you.
Did you have like a favorite one favorite slide of all these?
High extreme, I remember getting the courage to go on.
And it is very fun because you're very high up and it is a super extreme.
And I never I never I've never
I never went on like the tall slide, the thing that where it's like it's just super.
You know, it's like, I don't know, a 75 foot like straight down drop.
I've never done that.
And then I never did the wedge.
There was this thing at Raging Waters.
I don't know if it's still there, but it's like basically you you.
It's you're almost like it's like you're on a skateboarding ramp
where you just your body,
your body goes to until you literally there's like a funnel
and you go down the funnel into like a pool.
I never did that. OK.
Yeah, I've never done one of those like a little curlicue, whatever.
I feel like I haven't done a lot of I feel like I've recently conquered haunts.
I'm ready to conquer drop slide type things and like more extreme slides.
What you're talking about, because as a child, I was very scared of everything.
My mom also we've talked about many times.
My mom wouldn't let me go to certain water parks just that for a birthday.
She was afraid I would die. Boy.
Which is fair.
I mean, that's the scary thing about water parks is that you have way more control
over your own experience at a water park than you would on a given ride. Right.
You you in order to go on those high slides,
you really do have to like sit with your hands across your chest or like,
you know, behind your head. You can't flail around.
It actually is really dangerous if if you flail around like you,
you know, if someone pisses in the water.
I mean, that's why they have chlorine, I guess.
But like you really can ruin a slide in a way that you you can't.
I trust rides.
I don't trust myself nearly as much as I trust the people who make the rides.
So I think that's why I don't know if I trust my body
to know what to do on like a high slide,
but I completely trust the roller coaster on like a big drop.
Right. Yes, that makes sense.
Yeah, because you feel like it really does feel like when you're on some of the slides
that you could just slip out.
Like it does. Like you don't I don't feel safe as much.
You know, it does.
I mean, obviously there's some sort of physics, but like the type of slides
where you're in a giant inner tube and you go right up against the edge
and you come down, doesn't that feel like one of these times
that thing's just going to fly and go sailing out of the gates of the theme park?
Yeah, it feels very imprecise in a way that that is a lot.
That is a lot scarier to me. Yeah.
But they they know what they're doing.
Theoretically, I think there are stories I've heard of people
falling off those big slides because they're doing something stupid.
Yeah, that's true. Yeah. Yeah.
But I feel like I'd be the one who didn't cross my arms like, no, not like that.
What do you mean? I don't even know how I did it wrong.
And you crossed them over your stomach and not over here somehow.
And that leads to instant decapitation.
Yeah, it's very vulnerable to be on a water slide because it's just you.
Your ride suddenly becomes your body becomes your ride car.
Yeah. And you also feel like the ridges of the slide sometimes.
Yeah. You feel like the slumps on the slide.
Oh, the little like connector piece.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely.
I like that shouldn't be going over my back. Yeah.
Do you guys like big, big roller coasters?
Well, that's it.
I haven't done a lot of the Six Flags coasters,
but again, that's another thing I'm working on. Yeah.
But I just I just went.
I mean, those are there.
They're. I've been to Six Flags.
Sorry, you were answering a question. I completely interrupted.
Oh, no, I was just going to say, like, I my I don't like the dangling legs.
That's what I don't like. Oh, I feel vulnerable with my legs dangling.
But everything else I feel OK about.
But like there's ones that are really crazy.
There's like Green Lantern, one that apparently hurts.
That is shut down. Oh, yeah.
The Green Lantern one is shut down because that's been a ride
that they've been trying to do at Six Flags.
They call it a 4D coaster.
That's been a ride they've been trying to do for a while, but it
they're they're shutting it down because it fucks people up somehow.
Like the helmet, like where you're watching a simulator movie.
No, that's different.
No, that's something else.
You're almost like on the side of like a like
it's like you're on the side of the coaster.
And then also you drop and then like spinning and like, I don't know.
I don't know how to describe it. Yeah.
People hurt. It hurts. Yeah, it's a weird.
I mean, the because I've been going to Six Flags since I was
I've been going on upside down roller coasters since I was like 13.
And there is something to the taller you get and the older you get.
It just stresses your body out more.
And I can handle roller coasters.
I love roller coasters.
But I was just a Six Flags and like, I mean, you the
the thing you need before big roller coasters is you actually need food
in your stomach. Yeah.
It's a misconception to do an empty stomach.
You actually you need like a hearty meal and you need like a healthy meal.
And so you have to prep really well for it.
And then there are just some coasters there, man, that like
it is borderline unpleasant.
Some of them are aging very poorly.
Like I'll do pretty much anything.
I don't like the standing up ones because they never really
for five foot one, man, it's not pleasant to have that like bicycle seat.
Like like I'm like half standing, half sitting.
It's not good.
And also like some shoulder restraints, if it
because I am so sure I will just my head will bonk around in between them.
And that's really bad on the older ones.
But the newer ones tend to be pretty smooth.
I'll tell you what really fucked me up
last time that I'd been on a couple of years ago was fine is X2 is not aging well.
Oh, no. And because it was so incredibly bumpy
that I felt like, oh, I actually need to hold my head steady on this.
Otherwise, I'm going to seriously fuck up my body.
So X2 is the one where you're
you're you're like to the side of the roller coaster.
You're basically it's double upside down.
You're as you're on the ride.
You're on an axis that turns you.
And the first time I went on it, this is like five years ago.
I was like, this is the greatest ride I've ever been on because it was very smooth.
Because when you have the hat on a hatness of you're going upside down
while you're going upside down, you don't also need bumpiness.
I mean, you never really need bumpiness on a steel roller coaster.
I don't know. That's never that's never relevant to the situation.
But X2 has gotten like really bumpy now and it it really fucked with my head.
But I'll tell you what I loved that I didn't think I would love their new ride
Crazanity, which is the worst name.
It's I forget what they call it, but basically you're
it's one of those like vomit, vomit inducing rides you'd think.
But like you're on basically a giant wheel that spins
while you're doing like the Dragon Boat up and down thing.
It's one of the most like intense rides I've ever been on,
but like shockingly enjoyable. Wow.
I've seen there's a version of that in the Warner Brothers Dubai Park, I think.
It's a big like this kind of thing. Yes, yes.
That sounds fun, honestly.
That sounds like a thing I would have gone on as a kid.
So I'll try that when I go.
Yeah, I'm going soon. You're building up bravery.
The Twisted Colossus is amazing.
OK, that's the best one. Oh, really?
I like it aesthetically.
Like, have you been on it? No, I've been to it.
It's fantastic because what they did was somehow they kept
so Colossus was this classic wooden roller coaster at Six Flags.
We really should have just been talking about Six Flags this whole time.
New podcast. OK.
But they but they they they put a steel track like on top of on top of like
the wooden structure and they kept the cars very similar.
So there's no shoulder restraint.
And somehow the the upside down is so subtle.
You don't like it doesn't register you're going up that you're going upside down.
And this one, it's not a zero gravity turn.
They call it a there's a term that they use for the like specific
like upside down loop on Twisted Colossus that like
you can't believe you're upside down.
Like it feels it's so cool.
It's so many roller coasters that we're not we're we all like roller coasters.
But like there's a certain subsect of people who really like roller coasters.
And I was up there for a media thing and I was like, oh, there's roller
coaster people here today. Like we've been at theme park events.
This is like a mix of theme park people and roller coaster people.
And yeah, I am one of those I'm I am I've always been a huge roller coaster.
I'm a I'm a both but like I love I love those roller coaster people.
It's it's a there's a certain hearty heartiness.
I mean, especially the older you get.
It's a certain type of person who can still ride these coasters
when they're in their 60s. Right. Sure.
Yeah, it's like it's it's athleticism a little bit.
Yeah, you're putting your body through trauma. Yeah. Yeah.
And as a kid, like I was so scared of going upside down for some reason.
I would just do the wooden ones, which were so bumpy and so rickety,
probably worse in the long run.
But like that I can always pretty much do.
But like revolution, it's like this is the very first inverted
like major theme park roller coaster.
I was like, yeah, I can tell that it's 40 years old.
I can feel it in my brain. Yeah. Yeah.
And yet as scary as a lot of these rides are, just to bring it back to Raging Waters,
Raging Waters is was still bold enough to and probably incorrects
to make this assertion that they are the only theme park with rides
guaranteed to make you wet your pants.
Official ad that I'm holding up.
That's something they actually got to watch at the company Christmas party
for that. That's really good.
I got it. Is that 90s? Is that the 90s?
I think it's when it opened. I think this is 83.
OK, in the 90s, everything was gross.
They were. Yeah. We were fine being gross.
Yeah. Yeah. I wonder what happened.
I'm going to bring gross back. Yeah. Sure.
Yeah. I'm going to create a show called Blooms Booger Fart Shit Party.
Yeah. That kids show, though.
Yeah. Did you say shit party?
OK, Booger Fart Poop Party.
Great. Hey, great. Hey, great.
It's not even better. I was a fan for a second.
The sillier. And it's just it's a competition to see how gross kids
who to find the grossest kid in America.
Gross America's grossest kid.
Oh, no, I'm on this entire.
I take this entire from his back.
Wait a minute. You're imagining a bunch of gross children.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Well, yeah. Hey, on on that note, Rachel Bloom, you survived podcast.
The ride. Thank you so much for being here. Oh, my God.
Did you take my picture at some point in it and I didn't notice?
I've thought how what we should do is something like
like we do if we had a little photo booth set up that was like the end of ride
thing, we need to rig something up. Yeah, we really should do that.
It's hard to put that together.
Next time you're in a room. Thanks for giving it to us.
But hey, let's exit through the gift shop.
Anything you would like to plug?
Oh, yeah, I'm on a casual tour.
Check my website for details.
Just a casual. Sounds chill.
It's a very chill tour.
I'm doing domestic away dates every month and a half.
And then I have a monthly show at Largo in L.A., which is
which will be when this podcast release is coming up in three days.
And hopefully I'll have a better idea of what I'm doing at it than I do now,
which is I have no idea what I do.
Well, hopefully it adds to the excitement.
That's to the thrill.
Text us if you don't.
If you say to be like, edit out the I'm going to I'm going to bail.
I'm going to leave the night off.
Just have you guys come.
I mean, there's a it's anything I want to do at Largo.
So I could always just have other people come and perform.
And I just want to.
Well, as you learn, we can do two hours as long as it's about water slides.
You need a lot of time filled.
What a bait and switch, if that was what it was.
So I'm going to come and see some musical comedy.
And it's like, well, do you want to know the ride systems that we like?
So then Dr.
Von Tark, Kuka Arms, Sally Corporation.
Hey, we've got a live show coming up.
If you're in the Disney World area in Orlando, we're coming to the sat
comedy lab on October 24th.
Get your tickets now.
And for more podcasts, the right follow us on Twitter, Instagram, Facebook.
There's three bonus episodes every month if you subscribe to podcast, the ride,
the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
And I think that's all the things.
Thanks for splishing and splashing.
We made you hopefully.
Hopefully we made you wet your pants.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Bowen, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey,
engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.