Forever...
Doog!
Hauntcast, The Fright.
Welcome once again to Hauntcast, The Fright, the Scream Park podcast hosted by three headless men in their 30s.
I'm Rott Skardiner, joined by Mike Coffinson and Jason Skeleton.
We got some feedback from last week about the names.
Somebody correctly pointed out that Lindsay Cat's Eye could have easily been Lindsay Slaytie.
That is good, yeah.
And I have to say that I agree with that.
In the heat of the moment, you know, you toss stuff out.
I thought Cat's Eye was a real good solve, I thought, but Slaytie, pretty good.
As part of this, somebody also pointed out that Jason could be Slayson.
So I just wanted to put that on the table if you want it.
Because you should have agency in your own scary name.
But that's up to you.
I'll sleep on it.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, we got till next year because this is the last one.
Well, we're doing more on the second gate.
But a little more, I will say, Haunted Mansion related.
And I don't want to say more than that.
So patreon.com slash podcast the Fright and you'll hear a little bit more.
But there's a real aura for boating on that one.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See if you can figure it out.
But anyway, yeah, we're they were plowing through it because we got live shows to do.
Y'all next. We're hitting the road.
And I think as you hear this, I forget Orlando for sure.
You could still do if you're if you've been thinking about it.
Yes. Pull the trigger.
Come see us in Orlando on October 24th.
If you're listening on the day this has come out, you can still make it to Chicago.
Yes, tomorrow.
Chicago is tomorrow.
If you're listening Friday, whatever the date is, the 18th.
I believe this is out the Friday the 18th.
That's correct.
And if you're jumping on it day one and you're in Chicago, then why would you not come say hello?
You got to come.
Yes. Fun stuff in store.
We're excited.
But we and we there's so many like, you know, we're navigating this hot cast, the fright.
There's the tour where we've been shipping away at the downtown Disney or deal.
There's so many mini franchises and little tasks within the podcast that we're worried about.
But now we are back to our slowest go franchise within the show.
We are here at Haunted Mansion to Hard at Mansion Part two, as we have said,
because in the spirit of Halloween, we will discuss the Haunted Mansion every once a year every year, because I mean,
I think it started a lot of things start as like, oh, wouldn't that be funny?
And then we thought on it and it's like, well, I think it is probably the ride with the most text, text, subtext stuff.
Yes. There's so much.
I'm overwhelmed where I'm looking at Doom Buggies, the website, and I don't even like I so much about individual rooms.
Who knows where to begin?
I have the most amount of notes I may have ever taken.
This is number one in the series.
Bigger than Hard Rock Park.
But it's possible because what happened was I started following.
I started at like Doom Buggies and some other Haunted Mansion websites.
And every time there was a thread, I was like, let me see how far I can follow this historical thread before I start to lose my mind.
Wow. Yeah.
So if you're listening to this just for and you haven't listened to last year's Haunted Mansion, let's recap a little.
Yeah, I was going to say, like, maybe actually go back and listen to that one first.
That might actually be something that I joke that you need to listen to, like all the city walk.
I think maybe listen to the first time. I think so, because last year was mostly about the Genesis and creation of the ride.
It was a very long birth, a very long run up and creation.
And so by the many versions of the ride and different narratives that didn't make it.
Tons of people involved. The World's Fair delaying it.
Walt's death delaying it.
And we're talking about the Disneyland version and that building, the exterior of the ride, sat there with no ride for almost a year.
Yeah, some long time.
Like an actual abandoned haunted house. It sat empty.
So the idea, yeah, the idea would you be just walking around Disneyland and you'd be like, well, is it a house there?
The mystery mysterious house. And then all of a sudden I can go in the house finally.
Yeah, people must have assumed that was just a facade.
Right.
Like you've seen the Julio Torres is stand up special.
No, my favorite shapes.
He has a there's a whole bit of the way and talk about this and he did his own bit about how you can't go in Daisy's house.
And I mean, Mickey's Toon Town, right. And his like fantasy dream of what like he just did being awfully.
He was so upset that you could not go into Daisy's house.
But this is the Haunted Mansion must have seemed like Daisy's house.
One of those. Yeah, there is no thing in here.
So when it opens in sixty nine, it's a huge deal.
It is a ride, as we all know, it's a ride. And this is the goal that I want to throw out to you guys.
We've talked about this all fair. Let's talk about it on air.
I want to get on the ride in this episode.
Oh, I don't know.
Yes, Jason and I are a little bit more skeptical that we're going to make it all to the rest.
Last year we got kind of to the door, but we realized we forgot a lot of the graveyard to the gate.
We got to the gate. Excuse me. You're right.
I got to the front gate. So if you're thinking about us, we were walking on the gate.
Well, on the sign we were walking.
Yeah, we were walking to the ride and on the way discussing all the different versions that were going to happen.
So history origins.
I will say I will I will guarantee that we'll get to the front door of the mansion and we'll see how far inside we get.
We might not get in the door. I don't know. I'm not going to.
Again, the most substance maybe of any attraction.
I will say this. I will make a file. I will not artificially delay.
I will not try to tangent any more than a normal episode.
I like that I suggested that we talk about the ride that's our topic and what followed was.
Well, I don't know if I can make it. I mean, unfortunately, here every year, if you thought this was going to be a speedy endeavor.
No, of course not. Build a mansion in faster time.
And we're only talking about Disneyland version.
We said that's another rule because I agree. I got overwhelmed in terms of differences.
Too much. Let's leave that off.
To put it to also just a side note, I was I was like, let me go back and listen to what we were talking about last year just to make sure we don't repeat a lot.
And this is how this shows you the difference a year makes that we were making a joke about future President Michael Avenatti.
That's where we were in October 2018.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm not. He feels like I was thinking how if you told me that Michael Avenatti came and went and played out in like 2011, I'd believe it.
That's how the pace of the news cycle and the exhaustion of the Trump era is like, yeah, was he from was Avenatti from 2002?
What is he again? Yeah, right. Exactly. Can I do one for 2019?
Oh, just put kind of a bookmark in the year. President John Delaney. Right, folks.
Here we go. We will forget about him. I forgot that already. I forgot about that already.
Yeah, we'll see where we're at. We'll compare this. Little time capsule.
I feel like the Haunted Mansion episode is maybe our least funny episode because I feel like we were just fact, fact, fact. Let's talk more.
I felt that too. Well, let's take that pressure off. We don't need to. Let's have fun. We're a comedy podcast. Let's have some fun.
I'm sure I think I have an audience important to remember the good times. Now I don't remember him or what he was, but he makes me smile.
He's not the mooch that I know. But he's the guy that's like look stressed outside getting a phone call.
He kept saying he was going to sue people. Stormy's lawyer. Stormy's lawyer. Stormy feels like forever ago.
Stormy feels like forever ago. Yeah. I think I'm actually I was misremembering who he was. Stormy Daniels lawyer, of course.
We're going to be still be doing this in twenty twenty six and talking about the deep into third term Trump.
With our comparing of notes is going to be much. Now we're talking about like what's what's currently happening.
Castro's running for president and in twenty twenty six will be like, well, you know, Baltimore's gone. Trump. Yeah.
You are arrested if you sell share streaming service passwords. Trump had his brain implanted in a young person's head.
And like he's like a young handsome Trump now, but he's got the same old brain as Trump.
But the body is starting to curve. Air is starting to rot.
Imagine like something, a twenty something hunk with Trump's brain. So it's obviously still trying to like stand in that odd way.
Still a big puff out. But yeah, it's like the wolf boy in Twilight. What's his name? That handsome boy.
It's a boy. Yeah, I know. Taylor Lawner. Taylor. Taylor Lawner. He will look like Taylor. Yeah, I don't know.
But he's going to be we're going to use his body for Trump.
Trump is going to Trump has sold three states to Saudi Arabia and they're in the process of picking which ones they want.
They don't have to all be next to each other. They could be spread out.
And he's they're going to actually take the state somehow. They're going to remove it.
They're going to remove it from the United States and move it.
But maybe just be floating near. That's actually cool.
All the Trump maniacs are like, we love Sharia law now. We love it. Mr. Trump, thank you for Sharia law. Mr. Trump.
It's tidy. It's organized, you know. Well, watch every prediction come exactly true.
Yeah. And by that point, we will look like, well, no, we can't. We have to talk. We can't talk about floating.
Leota, we haven't gotten past still Leota yet. Right. I mean, that's coming.
All that's coming. So let's get in the game. I would like to start.
Yes. So I would like to start with an example of one of the threads I started to follow.
OK. Which so the sign, the sign outside of the Haunted Mansion.
Mike, you have a replica. That's right over there. Sitting on a thing. I need to hang it up.
We just I think at the very end, we're like, we like that sign. I wanted to know more about the sign and I started at Doom Buggies and then ended at the history of some landmarks and the L.A. Times archives.
So that sign was sculpted by a Disney employee named Chris Muller Jr.
He also did the giant squid in twenty thousand leagues under the sea and he did the smaller squid in twenty thousand leagues under the sea, sculpted a number of the jungle cruise animals.
And in pop culture history, he sculpted the mask and hands of the creature from the Black Lagoon, the original creature from the Black Lagoon.
All right. That's pretty cool. So it goes even further.
The designer of the creature from the Black Lagoon was a the costume was designed by a woman named Millicent Patrick, who happened to be one of Disney's first female animators.
Designed a costume of a creature from the Black Lagoon. Designed the costume from the creature from the Black Lagoon.
She was also an actress and an artist. Her father is a man named Camille Charles Rosie.
Now, this is where I hit my first oddball speed bump. I found an incorrect fact on Doom Buggies website.
They said that Rosie is the architect behind Hearst Castle. He is not.
He was a construction manager at Hearst Castle and helped design some of the interiors because he got friendly with William Randolph Hearst.
The designer of Hearst Castle, the architect behind it, was a woman named Julia Morgan, who was the first female architect in California.
So give her her credit. Doom Buggies.
So you're calling out Doom Buggies.
What you found out is that Doom Buggies has incorrect information.
And that is what a lot of this episode is going to be about is correcting the Doom Buggies website.
But this now this did circle back around because it's I would they said like an anecdote that Raleigh Crump always said.
Walt Disney cited Hearst Castle, among many other things, as an inspiration for the haunting mansion.
Hearst Castle on top of a hill by San Simeon, California, kind of imposing, kind of kind of kind of kind of.
Yeah. So that's that's the threads that come off the sign.
The sign of just the sign and it connects back to other Disney Imagineering projects, other American history is sinister American history.
Yeah. Is there a more iconic sign like the you can think of the pie?
Guess Pirates of the Caribbean like the sign outside is really iconic, but it's not as good up there.
Yeah, it's not quite as good and simple words ultimately.
But that it's the oval, the crest is in that frame is fantastic.
And it's been the it does feel like scaly like the creature from the Black Lagoon.
And having it in the apartment, I guess, like, you know, I can touch it, which is nice.
Yeah. So you can touch the sign.
So I'm trying to think if there's anything I don't think so, because like space, my sign that I have at home.
But that's just me. That's because I see it every day.
Yeah. And that's my caution doors open automatically up.
God, I mean, that's up there.
But yes, based on his different logos everywhere.
I mean, there's a slightly different variation font, and sometimes they use like gross 90s alien fonts and like that Tokyo font for Space Mountain.
That looks like the spawn, the 90s comic spawn logo.
Oh, sure. So a final feature panel for could be signs.
Yes, I would say the best and worst signs competition.
Yeah, that's good contenders. That is good. Yeah.
Gomer's Gentlemen's Lair bathroom sign is definitely in the running for one of my favorites.
That's over by Hungry Bear. It's the bathroom level.
Yeah, about bottom level of Hungry Bear bathroom. It says Gomer's Gentlemen's Lair over the male bathroom.
Wow. I think Trixie is the female. I believe that's right.
Yeah. There's like a Trixie's powder room or something.
Anyway, walk up there and figure it out.
What's your sign, ladies? People are yelling right now. They know it.
Of course. We know the name of the bathroom.
So that's the sign. So that's the sign.
You said things about the gate as well.
No, sorry. I meant the sign. The area around the gate.
You don't have any information about who made the gate?
No, don't be foolish.
Foolish mortal? Don't be a foolish mortal.
The gate is cool. I will say I like the gate a lot.
It's I'm trying to think it's like we can't talk about Disney World, but it's good because it does seem like a gate that would keep you out.
It seems like a scary house in Disneyland, but not as scary and setback like Disney World.
But the gate is like I could see if I was a kid and I'd be like, you shouldn't go over that gate.
Like somebody weird lives there. Like it feels right. It feels right to me.
It's not. Yeah. Well, and it like that it is a little sectioned off area from the rest.
Yeah. Yeah, I think that's what I'm saying.
Disney World is kind of like a massive birth, a massive walkway.
I think they knew the crowds. It would be a hit.
But that one is setback. But this one just feels like like if I lost a ball over the fence, don't go get it.
Don't go get it. Yeah. Yeah. But we're in now. We made it in.
But we're in the gate. Yes. Now we're in. I'm glad just we made it through the gate.
So we're talking cemetery, the grounds. What do you want to call it?
Well, there's the hearse. Let's not get the stuff. Yes. Yes.
That's the hearse, I think is that part of the graveyard. Oh, that counts.
The grounds. We're in the grounds. Sure. Yes. That's what a lot of websites refer to as outside of the house.
So did everyone read the insane urban legend about the hearse? Not the urban legend.
No. OK. I don't know. Maybe I didn't. So this is it's sad.
It's a funny urban legend. It has been well.
It's been debunked that this hearse is the hearse used in former Mormon church leader,
Brigham Young's funeral procession. What? No, I did not read this.
This is a not real. It's not real.
No, it is an urban legend that circulated a bunch to the point that like multiple news sites like had to debunk it.
So church archives show that Brigham Young was carried through the streets by pallbearers.
There was no wagon involved, although it is possible this wagon could have been in Utah in the eighteen hundreds.
It's also possible that some information that the Mormons collected about their back story is incorrect.
Yeah, for sure. Well, that's what the big debunked article I found in
was a guy named Glenn M. Leonard.
He's the director of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints, his Museum of Church History and Art.
But the article was in the desert news, the longest running paper in Utah,
which is owned by the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints.
And there is some wild shit in that newspaper.
Like there is we don't have time to get into that.
We're on Mormon newspapers.
Do you know? Did you read what it is, what it was in the hearse?
The hearse? Yeah. So about the John Wayne movie.
No, that's Florida. Oh, that's the Florida hearse.
Oh, I got my hearse is mixed up.
So the hearse outside of the Disneyland Mansion painted white was bought by from an antique dealer in California.
And the urban legend around this is that Knott's Berry Farm was about to buy it for a ghost town for the ghost town section.
And the guy, the owner, called Disney and said, like, hey, he left to get a check if you really want this.
Because Tony Baxter wanted it in the 90s because it was going to be used in that insane.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Indiana Jones stunt show.
Right. Where like it was going to be part of a chase.
And the train was in the train was involved. Yes.
Yes. Going to use the Disneyland train.
I believe that's the same one. Right.
It was going to be like a scene with the train over back by Big Thunder Trail.
But how could they use the train? How could they coordinate it?
I think that was a big I don't know if that was just a blue sky idea, but there was going to be like the train would stop and there would be a little show.
I wouldn't whatever once an hour or something.
So you would have had to coordinate times to have the show.
Wow. It's a cool idea, but it does seem logistically impossible.
It slows down the train operation. Yeah.
So weird that that what a weird backwards we got a thing we got a ride that maybe might get built.
But we better buy this hearse.
That said, turning lemons into lemonade, Tony Baxter cited as one who came up with the floating hitch gimmick.
There's a hitch on top in front of the hearse that looks like it's attached to a horse that is just floating in midair as if a ghost horse is hooked up to it.
Now, let me say this. I never noticed that it did not register the hearse itself.
I never know the floating. Oh, I never ever occurred to me.
I didn't know about it. I didn't. Yeah. Yeah. I read it and I went, oh, yeah. Yeah.
Now it makes sense. But it does not necessarily.
That is my my one not to criticize Tony.
Obviously, I mean, there's sure Tony, but Tony's done so many things we barely we probably haven't even noticed half of them.
We may have talked a lot of shit about. Yeah.
He designed the planet Hollywood at Disney Village Paris.
I know. Yeah. Sign inside.
Tony. Oh, hold on. I was going to say Tony.
There's a friends of the show season pass.
They did a Doug Barnes did a panel at Midsummer Scream with a bunch of people, including Tony and this woman, Tanya Norris, who did like design and like picked out the wallpaper of the Haunted Mansion.
And she has amazing stories on there about like being on a plane with Walt.
But I was Tony was talking about Haunted Mansion. He's very big on updating it and like keeping it.
He said it on the panel like, you know, we can do a lot better with the effects now.
And I think they should go in there and do that. Yeah.
So he's very much, I think, always been like, what can we do to like bring this up to today's standard? Yeah.
Which is cool. I like that. I'm pro that anyway.
I'm kind of. Yeah, I'm proud of it, too.
If you like all this stuff, go to season pass and listen to that.
I listened to that panel what you were there for and now celebrating it occurs to me now.
I mean, we're late on it, but this is this year is the 50th anniversary of Haunted Mansion and we look we celebrate the 50th and we look forward to celebrating the 60th as well.
I think you're going to say 100th for some.
By which point we will be 15 percent through the graveyard.
We will be. Yes, I was going to say like we'll be at the third DOOM buggy because we have to obviously do each DOOM buggy.
They all have a history, of course.
So we'll have to do that. Well, if Futurama's predictions are correct when we celebrate the 100th anniversary of the Haunted Mansion, Richard Nixon will be president once again.
So just as he was.
Where things are heading. If we're body transferring Trump and younglings, then sure.
Younglings.
Yeah, so the hearse in Florida, again, we're not really talking about the hearse in Florida, was used in the John Wayne movie, The Sons of Katie Elder.
I screwed up. I said something about the hearse in Florida.
That's OK. That's OK. But the hearse has that fun ghost relations sign inside.
You guys know. Yeah, yeah. Ever notice that?
That was apparently on the like coming soon signs of like if you're interested in dwelling in our happy hunting ground, send your right to the ghost relations department.
Like guest relations. It's fun.
It's just the start of the wordplay that will haunt to this episode.
No, no phone number you can call them.
There should be a phone number. There should be somebody that writes back with like a spooky letter.
But well, yeah, maybe that's one of the things Tony was talking about enhancing it.
He wants an address or a phone number for that joke.
That would be good. If I have something to say about the something that happens behind the columns.
So really, it's you're on the porch, really, of the mansion.
Should I save that for? Yes, I think that would come later, I suppose.
I think it would come. I would like to because like as you cross through the gate and you pass by the hearse, this is your first glimpse of the imposing house itself.
And did you guys read it? You can see it from the outside, too.
But yes, you can see it from the outside, but it kind of looms over you as you sort of round the corner here.
Did you guys read about like the architecture at all?
We did some of this. We talked a little bit about it last time.
It sounds familiar. I'll say buzz.
This is a Victorian style house, kind of a southern kind of a southern vibe, southern Gothic vibe.
And very different from the other Haunted Mansions, which are kind of more like perpendicular lines, more like stone and stuff rising above you.
And more of the like it's far away effect of Main Street where like.
Yes. Forest perspective.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Getting smaller as it goes, seems larger.
Yeah. So and this it's a mix of Victorian styles with the Roman columns that were very popular in the south in like the 1800s and all.
And I was reading about like our idea of Victorian homes is like haunted houses like they often look. This is one of the styles.
People think of a haunted house being and that came like in the early 20th century.
It's like this looks old to us now here in the 21st century.
Everything is just like Victorian just means old to me.
So like, yeah, we lose track of the individual types of old.
Yeah, the flattening of history. Everything just becomes like old.
Everything in the past is old timey. Yeah.
So but it has to fit in like there's not I don't think of it as like the southern Haunted Mansion, but it has to look appropriate.
New Orleans Square. New Orleans Square.
And everything. Yeah, there's all the other the Dixie sort of vibe of everything and the bands playing along the river.
Yeah, and it is it fits. It does really fit like it really does like working in the same.
I know it's like the Haunted Mansion in Florida.
And we're not supposed to talk about it like that sort of technically like fits Liberty Square and everything.
But it still seems a little bit more out of place to me.
When then in Tokyo, weirdly in and then in the land, not quite.
It's enough. It's close enough to frontier land that you counted as part of that.
But it's sort of like a theme into itself.
That's maybe the oddest placement of a Haunted Mansion is.
Yeah, that is it is odd. It's just like in the back.
Yeah, it's like if you were in fantasy land and Disneyland and instead of Dumbo, the Haunted Mansion was just sitting there.
Yeah. And it just jumps out. I remember turned like turning around and like, oh, there's the Haunted Mansion.
OK. Yeah. Yeah. It's, you know, weird.
Yeah. Here it's it's fantastic. Here. It's great.
Tony Baxter once again has said like, oh, the southern style house is more foreign to like California.
Get visitors in the way that like the more New England style brick mansion in Florida is kind of a like if they put a southern mansion in Florida, it wouldn't be that weird.
It wouldn't be that odd. That architectural style.
That's why they changed the style. Sure, sure, sure.
It's interesting because he talks about that a lot philosophy wise when like when he's talking about Phantom Manor and in France, it's like, well, you know, American West is a little more foreign to people in Europe.
So like they're always constantly thinking about things that are like not so familiar to the place that the park is located, which is funny that California Adventure got built because that couldn't be the most opposite of what Tony was saying.
Like you're Hollywood south of just south of Hollywood. Right. What's the point?
Yeah, it makes sense to have like maybe Hollywood in Florida because yeah, you're not near that actual place.
I was supposed to I was just explaining to a friend to the weird Disney Studios Paris Park, the worst park Disney's built.
And I found a picture that I didn't even I didn't even stare at since I went there and there's like, you know, bad like facades of Hollywood kind of buildings and one of them says Larchmont Hotel on it.
And like in the other ones, Los Feliz, I think, like I'm like, that's so bizarre.
That's a Larchmont nod in a field in Paris. But very far. So maybe that one works.
Yeah, I was going to say the building's very ugly. So no. And it's also that one wasn't even attempt to be a studio, which makes it extra weird.
I feel no, not really. Yeah. Yeah. The themes all. Yeah. Yeah. Well, the main drag of California Adventure being Buena Vista Street now.
But it looked Buena Vista Street is street in Burbank adjacent to the Disney Studios.
And it looks like 1920s Atwater Village, which is a different Los Angeles neighborhood. Yeah, that's true.
I was going to say at least that's in the past. It is in the past.
That makes sense because that was that was their plus up of like, well, at least let's make this in the past.
I do attribute to current Hollywood, a place that where no one likes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So there's Aaron and I will be driving in there and we'll go, wow, we even had to be in Hollywood in like four months.
Fuck. Yeah. Yeah. No, I did. That's a great four months.
My friend had a birthday on Hollywood Boulevard two weeks ago and we were parking.
I was like, oh, God, I haven't been here forever. Your friend, Spider-Man, or was it Elmo? Yeah.
It was your oldest friend in Los Angeles. It was Jack Sparrow. Oh, my.
Oh, I hope you gave him a ball run. Yeah, I did.
Did I tell that story on this podcast when we saw Spider-Man at the Grownlings Chinese?
I don't remember. And I went there's a Randy's Donuts location on Hollywood Boulevard now.
And I went in and you had a donut to get a donut, but also in there because it was later in the night.
Jack Sparrow haggling to try and get them to knock some bucks off the dough.
Oh, no. See, end of the night, you're going to throw them away in character.
Talking. It was kind of in character.
We also saw him eating at the Cabo Wabo Cantina earlier in the evening.
Yeah, we did see Jack Sparrow Cabo Wabo Cantina, which in character, he'd be friends with Hagar for sure.
Yeah, that's true. Cabo Wabo Cantina, which has had gotten much worse in the years since we've been there.
A little rough. Yeah. Yeah. It was always fine. It was always fine.
But we were in there and we were like, oh, my God, as if we had come back 50 years later and they hadn't changed anything.
If we did a I think it's I just heard it's getting a facelift, I believe.
Oh, it is. Maybe not that, but the Hollywood and Highland District in general.
Oh, yes, that's true. We did a city walk, Denton Disney style thing about Hollywood and Highland.
We would kill ourselves. We'd be done like sector five.
We all cut ourselves and that's the end of the fight.
Well, also, every time we'd go back to try something, the thing we had just tried will have closed.
Yes. Yeah. We have to record it all in a day or else it's totally and release it the next day.
The leases there are like 10 months long.
And that works. That's a that's a tweet. Give some tourists and travel tips.
If you're kind of you don't live in Los Angeles and you're coming to Disneyland, do not go to Hollywood Boulevard, but all especially Hollywood and Highland.
If you're fucking rat's nest, if you're the type of person that likes garbage, go like if you want to go like I want to go to city walk before you go.
Yes, for sure. Go to city. I mean, going to getting to see the movie in the big IMAX Chinese.
Sure, the Chinese theater. But also you can tour the Egyptian down the road, a much more pleasant stretch by Musa and Frank.
Yeah. So anyway, don't go anywhere.
But we will do a series on it. Jason will do two hours on Beard Papa.
I never eat a beard. I want to eat a beard. Really? What is it? Is it like Pops?
Oh, I love it. Beard Papa's son, I think. Oh, my God. Who owns the Beard Papa IP?
Doesn't your dad have a beard? My dad does have a beard. Yeah. I wonder.
I have seen a picture of your dad and I'm picturing Beard Papa. I could be wrong. I think there's a little bit across.
Look up Beard Papa if you don't know what we're talking about. He's like a little David the Gnome style man who has sells pastry puffs.
Great. Am I wrong about what he looks like? I like him too. Yeah, he's great. Yeah, we love.
We had a working lunch the other day and afterwards I ran a couple errands close by and then I was walking by a pastry shop and I'm like, no, I don't need it.
And then when I was almost home, I wanted something sweet. So I just got a milkshake at McDonald's. There he is. Beard Papa.
That story was just I wanted one sweet and then I got a different sweet. So this one time, the marketing was with the pastry shop was literally like under new owners.
I was like, well, it's got new owners. I'd never been there before. I'm just so you're describing. I feel like your everyday life. It would seem. Yeah.
Oh, is it a Japanese company? I think so. Oh, I didn't know that actually. Beard Papa fresh and natural cream puffs. That's what it says.
I love it. OK, so from Beard Papa, yeah, our bizarre rules were Beard Papa and stuff allowed. The spooky Victorian architecture kind of fits in with like what the American myths and legends.
What a haunted house should be. I feel like it either looks like a castle kind of like Florida or it looks like this.
It looks like Radley's and we talked about how he didn't want like a rundown shitty house in his park. It had to be like the stately kind of scary.
He said, we'll keep up the outside and the ghosts will take care of the inside. Something like that.
I like that. You know, I'm going to declare what I'm talking about is fits within the area geographically that we are.
My primary association with the with the grounds and with the, you know, the the grass in front of the mansion is the Disney sing along songs.
Of course, today there is a Disney sing along VHS that is at Disneyland and there is a performance of Grim Grinning Ghosts sort of sung by Thorol Ravenscroft sound alike.
And this was its neck and neck with Ernest goes to Splash Mountain in terms of like the biggest terrors that young Scott Gardner ever faced.
This was the scariest shit to me. I saw YouTube comments where people seem to agree that this thing just just haunted their dreams.
That is so charming. All really cute. It's a pretty specific thing to be scared of.
All the villains get together on the lawn, all the villains and Donald under a sheet and Donald posing as a ghost.
You can see his seat is sticking out of the ghost. That's the tell that it's him.
He turned like who's this ghost? And then he turns around and scurries away.
Seat is showing. So the villain. Yes, it's a gathering of all of the villains.
The Disney's scariest villains go of ghosts and creeps, those being the Snow White Witch Maleficent, a very like that shiny Maleficent, the brightest makeup little like pearls of sweat.
She is. Yeah, she reflects so much light. Her face.
The makeup is one of the like the top most vivid memories in my brain like top 50.
Her face makeup and the way that it shines is so burned into my brain.
I don't know exactly. We both held on to the Maleficent makeup.
I am sure that is much more common than we're thinking it is. Yeah, I bet. I bet. Yeah, it's very striking.
It's just a really bold green, a sweaty green. It is like, yeah, I don't know. I don't know if it's sweat.
Something's going on with it. It probably plays much better. Like the whole thing, all those Disney singalongs, anytime they would shoot something in the park, it looks like they had an hour to do it.
Yeah. So it's not like they were testing out the cameras and the makeup or whatever. So they must have just been like slap whatever we have on.
Maybe they made some big adjustment and it just is so striking. I love this connection.
I'm glad I'm not the only one. And I think I didn't I think I think maybe I hadn't even seen Sleeping Beauty, so I didn't know what Maleficent was.
So to me, maybe it's like the Joker's makeup, quote unquote, in some worlds, it's not makeup or Christie the clown where it's like that's like on him.
So I think not really knowing what Maleficent was, it's like what is why is she this shiny green monster?
Uh huh. Like some chemical must have turned her this. So yeah, Maleficent's big shiny green cheek, one of the most scarring memories in much other.
I believe that if we people listening to this will post something on Twitter, they will.
We will have a lot of support for people that have this memory in their brain. I hope so. A supporters club.
That's the thing I remember the most about this is her face. I got to say, I really don't. I remember watching these.
I feel like music teacher wanted to break that day. Put in a sing along tape. Oh, smart.
I don't even know that we really sang along. I think we all just like watched it because we were happy to watch TV instructions. But I that is like I can picture my one like music class room from childhood.
And I remember weird that they showed it in your school at all. Oh, we all we had tons of tapes where it's like teacher needed a teacher was out sick.
We had that teacher. Yeah, she was there an hour a week. I told the story on the show where they were just going to show us Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, which is an hour and a half or more.
Yeah. And then they turned it off because Rafael said damn twice. No teacher had they had for that part. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, on on like fun days like towards the end of the year and stuff, we would we were a little older and would switch classes for each subject. They would like pause the movie and then restart it like on the intro TV network.
Interschool network and and yeah, that's what we die watching all of that. I don't know what that is. I didn't have that like there were TVs in every room, but the VCRs were centralized or centrally located like where you could make the
same movie play in multiple classrooms. Whoa, did you go to school in the future? It seemed like it, but it felt like they could never get it to work right. And then one guy knew how to do it sometimes.
Wow. We know we we just had the old VCR. Yeah, we had that too. Yeah. To this day, the only way I've ever seen Lord of the Rings is on a small TV far away.
That's in the back row. It's in the front row. That's a letter boxed. I've only seen what you see in Lord of the Rings, like from another room. Essentially, is that like your last half a mile away? You watched that in high school? Yeah, I never saw it for real. But was it a regular class or was it some other some class?
I don't know. The movie's like two and a half hours. I don't think we finished it. I think we're just like we got an hour. All right, here's some of Lord of the Rings. OK, bye. You want to see the rest? Bye. We finished Batman and Robin over a few periods. That's educated.
Wow. Of all the things you learned in school that were relevant to your future, your profession. Knowing a lot about Batman and Robin is the most important. Certainly for me. I'm not I'm amazingly not done with the with the Grim Grinning Ghost, which is so. Take your time, please.
The so be a Maleficent. But also there's these scary tree before you meet the villains. Yes, these scary trees sway around. And I remember going to Disneyland going those trees aren't here.
And I couldn't I couldn't know if that was like a relief or a guy. I was scared of him, but I kind of wanted to see the trees. Right. And I think to this day, I find the lawn bare because there's no scary trees. That's interesting.
But also so all right. All the monsters and ghosts, because it's a song about ghosts. So here's where the ghosts come out. Maleficent, the witch, Captain Hook. Yes. And the big bad. Yes. My favorite ghost.
One of the most terrifying ghosts, the big bad wolf. Now there is this part. Here's what I was talking about between the columns.
There is a part where each of these four initial villains before Donald and his seat join and they all go between the two columns and they do this double twitch. I will play this little I will play this clip of it.
One second. And this specifically one of the most terrifying things of my child. And I'm not getting it up quickly enough.
I'm curious if people know what I'm talking about with the double twitch. Where's the goddamn somebody else talks. I was just going to say that this was a situation where, of course, as I said many, many times on the show, I was looking at the Disneyland Haunted Mansion and it just looked like fake to me.
Like it was almost a set. Yeah, like a set. Because I obviously I did not know what it looked like. And out of the context of this video, I had never seen a picture of. I mean, I saw a picture of it, but I don't didn't remember it. And it just looks strange. It didn't look as scary as the one in Disney World.
Yeah, it's kind of. Oh, sorry. Oh, no, I was going to say, I think the buildings themselves, I think the building in Florida and Tokyo is scarier. I think the grounds are more unnerving. And yes, and obviously, like I think it's scary now, but just watching it on a VHS tape and it's like, well, that's the one.
This is also like my association with those sing alongs is like this is one of the only times with my peers and like in school, I had any interaction with theme parks because I felt like it was such a me thing. Me and my family.
It wasn't until like my college roommate, Jack, like also was like, yeah, no, I get I want to die. Go a lot like he got it. And then Mike meeting you that was like really had someone to like do this kind of insane level of discussion about it.
And then a third and then Scott. And now are now all our audience joins.
The army we've created. You are bidding. Here's this little moment.
So all the characters are walking by the door with the sort of, you know, the monkey's effect where the camera stays. It's like an impossible amount of space and it stays frozen and the monsters go into monsters like the witch go in and out.
But when the big bad wolf with his big long strappy tongue just just goes back and forth and sort of like a thriller dance pose for some reason, I found that so fucking scary and not even the other ones as much the wolf.
And I have this recurring nightmare as a kid. I my my childhood bedroom was like at the at the end of a long hallway and I would look out at the end of the hallway and imagine the big bad wolf walking in the front door and doing a double twitch.
I hope it's a very vivid. I was scared of the long time. I'm more scared of the long tongue than anything in any horror film in the last 20 years.
So like if there was like a David Cronenberg movie with a long tongue, that would be your nightmare. Yeah, there probably is, right? A perma-out tongue, I guess. I'm not scared of dogs or anything.
I'm not scared of real wolves as much as I am that up bright standing big bad wolf. But like a hanging tongue is really the issue.
Yeah, I imagine the tongue going all the way down the hallway and like grabbing wrapping around me and pulling me into his mouth. That's kind of like Beetlejuice, the stop motion stuff wrapping around.
Oh, sure. I was pretty scared of that, too. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. They're very much that style. If we could go back in time, we could sit little Scott down and go like Scott was just a non-union actor at three in the morning.
And they just said do something spooky. And that's what they came up with. They made a hundred dollars. And also, Scott, keep in mind, it's not scary at all.
Oh, yeah. Your weird warped brain should be scared of this. I'm trying to remember if I was scared of that. That's the thing with creative kids is we would fill in the holes like we would fill in with actual like.
That's the case with our creative kids, too. Yeah, but then creative kids never stop doing it. And that's why we do what we do. That's right. Talking about it. That's on the curse of this tongue.
That sounds like some sort of Aaron Sorkin monologue from Studio 60. Stop. No, I'm saying we we we exacerbate the fear by picking the most the least reliable job in the country.
Jason Sheridan doing Danny Tripp monologues. Oh, come on, man. Print that on a shirt.
Do you guys get stressed out when the giant clock that we have up in your apartment is ticking all the way down and we haven't come up with our episode idea yet?
Wait, what? That huge you see it's right. Yeah, yeah. They don't act like you forget about the club. That's a huge clock that clicks down. It ticks down until we have an idea.
On Friday when we start with 11 p.m. on Friday when we record all these episodes. Well, yeah, the nation is like it kind of waits for us to sort of set the tone for the week's theme park.
Oh, yeah. Now he sounds like Aaron Sorkin. Yeah, that's what we're talking about. Everybody knows. Everybody remembers the big clock. We all remember the big.
It's all canon. Studio 60 big clock on the studio 60 red hat that lets you know that we're in the past and 9-11 has just happened and Matthew Perry's younger and coping with it.
Right. Young red hat equals younger. Let me say about the Disney with the video. I do. There is something tongue related in my memory.
I believe Pluto licked me as a child. The costumed Pluto licked me with his big fake tongue because he had them. Right. I'm right. He has the big hanging tongue.
And I do remember him licking me. I remember being conflicted about it. On one hand, it was like nice to be like, you know, shown affection by Pluto.
On the other hand, I was thinking like, oh, the tongue is gross, even though it's just a piece of plastic.
I think in my mind, I was imagining like getting like saliva by a dog filling in as Jason said, filling in details that weren't there.
Filling in the saliva part. And don't they say like a dog's mouths are like actually very not disgusting at all? Like it's pretty clean.
Yeah. I mean, I think yes, that's true. I didn't know that at the time. Well, I think it was, you know, it was a strange dog. Even though I knew Pluto, I still had spent a lot of time with Pluto.
So that's maybe why I was a little uncomfortable. I'm just saying if we could sit young Mike down and say like dog's mouths are actually very clean.
Don't worry. Would that have worked? Or would you have been like, it doesn't matter? No, my mom probably was like dog's mouths will kill you if you touch saliva from them, especially orange ones.
Yeah. Their paws are the things touching dirt and filth all day long. Honestly, Pluto's tongue probably dirtier than a regular dog's tongue. Probably because he's licking every kid.
Yeah. Probably. The sicknesses you might like have today, something that will eventually kill you, you got from Pluto's tongue. It's been in your body for 20 years.
Pluto's tongue is carrying Legionnaires disease. It's dormant, but it's going to get you. It was Pluto's tongue. It'll get you.
OK, so all that being said, when I see the I just, you know, truly and now we're right where I am going.
I don't know how we're going to get on the ride because I realized, oh, I have shit to say about the grass because the grass is where this fucking thing happened.
Yeah. And I think that's a big part of the place making. There's doom buggies has that whole section on the flora, like the plants around it, which I don't.
I'm not good at science, but the takeaways I got were that one, everything looks a little dangerous or a little sinister, but obviously it can't be poisoned.
It like it can't be. It's got to look. So it's thorny and gnarly and like everything's droopy, which ties into the southern thing, the sort of wilting looking.
Well, yeah. And just that it like looks unnerve it like you are in an unnerving place.
The other illusion of the landscape architecture is that everything is overgrown. This is an old place that's not been kept up.
In reality, it is meticulously kept up, meticulously landscaped architecture.
It would be funny if they like let it go like the grass is overgrown.
I think some of the others they have water shortages in Los Angeles.
Well, we need to save some money.
Chay Pek could just cut out the budget for maintaining the lawn.
It's going to save a few bucks. Sure.
So we veer off to the left and you end up in this little courtyard area for a while where all the like back and forth crisscrossing happens.
What do we have to say about the like the cemetery and stuff, which I don't have a lot on?
Well, it's changed a lot over the years.
They have because you are right at the big the big thing is that there are gravestones honoring the imagineers who worked on it,
which were removed in 2001, the first time they did Haunted Mansion Holiday.
OK, then facsimiles put back in in 2016 and they were lost.
Yeah, really? Yeah, there's a video on a Disney blog with Kim Irvine, who is what's her name's daughter, right?
Leota's daughter. Isn't it Leota's daughter? Oh, Leota.
Yeah, yeah. Kim Irvine. She oversaw the restoration of the castle.
Not repainting the castle. Yeah, she talks about her mother. Yeah.
Yeah. So she's Madame Leota's daughter, essentially.
Well, but yeah, they lost the originals.
Apparently they couldn't find them.
Some of them given, I think, Accentio given his.
Yes, you're right. He took his and put it in his backyard, I believe. Yes.
But all that we talked in the last episode a lot about all the many, many figures who this was like a trademark attraction of theirs.
And yeah, they were all honored in here.
And I have all of the names and all of the things that says. Yeah, I got that. Yeah. You got this too.
All right. You take one and then I go the next one. OK, we might not be looking at the same place.
I found a list on the Disney Parks blog.
Claude Coats, lead designer specializing in backgrounds and environments.
He also developed at the Omnimovir Leia. Can we just tweet the list?
No. All right, we'll do a couple.
And it said, at peaceful rest lies brother Claude planted here beneath this sod.
We have to hear every one of these things. People want us to read.
Jason, people. Yeah, Jason's right. Mark Davis, lead designer specializing in character design and psych gags.
Just a reminder, Claude Coats, Mark Davis, kind of the two warring influences from the Haunted Mansion.
In memory of our patriarch, dear departed grandpa Mark. That's nice.
Tensio. We'll do a couple more. Tensio who married the two.
Married kind of like. Dasharolly. Smoothered over. Dasharolly Crump.
Dasharolly Crump. Tensio wrote the lyrics to Grim Grin and Grost, I believe.
Go ahead. Grost. Excuse me.
What's that word? Requis. Requiscat. Requiscat Francis Xavier.
No time off for good behavior. RIP.
Just do Bill Martin. Yeah, Bill Martin, concept artist.
Here lies the man named Martin. The lights went out on this old Spartan.
I wonder if they actually called him that. We should look into that or if that was just like, oh, we don't got to rhyme for Martin.
Let me do Fred Jerger. He was models and effects modeling because I always laugh. I always like this one.
Here lies good old Fred. A great big rock fell on his head.
Yeah, that is maybe the best one. I hope that's not real either.
No. That's all insensitive to make a joke out of it.
Did you guys? I wrote some for us. Did you guys? I did know. Did anyone?
I actually didn't know. Please. Let's see how these are.
I'm sure good. Here lies Michael. So very tall, tripped on Edwin and had a big fall.
Oh, man. That's how I go. Yeah, that's how you go. I trip over a dog.
We do a trip down into an empty sewer grate. And then you're here for like a oh, you know, you're saying you keep falling.
Well, that's what I'm saying. Like, where am I? Where do I? Is there like, did I? He's always on your foot.
You just fall. I'm just saying, what do I fall? Is there like railroad railroad spike that I fall on?
Your head open on a regular head on your stairs. God, that would be.
I mean, you're just here for hours that Edwin just humping your leg.
You're licking my life. This is truly a honkest of fright.
Yeah, I'm licking my blood up off the ground. Dog's tongue. The scariest thing.
There it is. Oh, Edwin, let me see that tongue.
Oh, God, it's three feet long, but it's clean. But it's clean.
Scott, if you want yours, please rest in peace.
Our beloved Scott drank mold, but fuck.
No. Rest in peace. Our beloved Scott drank mold wine that was scalding hot.
I just thought wine was too hot.
Just one sip. My heart just burst open.
Just melted your organs, I think. Just liquid and liquid organs.
And Jason. And I'll let you guys punch mine up because I kind of got a little talk.
OK, Jason so loved his sugary eats or fuck.
She's Jason so loved his desert eats, not his way to death on sugary treats.
I like it. He's a desert. Yeah. Yeah.
If you punch it up with that. Deezer. Deezer.
So so those were ours. And then I had an alternate for mine that is based on this.
Did you guys come across the by your own haunted mansion tombstone souvenir that they sold in the park?
Yes. No. This great. I got to open this image.
So they sold like you could get a personalized like I'm assuming miniature gravestone.
Mike, did you do you have this? Did you see it open? I saw it, though.
Let me try and so you could get a could you write your own encryption like inscription?
Yeah, I think there was like you could write the name.
I think you personalize it with your name. I think they had some set.
They have like you couldn't you couldn't be like using an F word on there, could you?
You can't. There's got to be a restriction. You can't do that.
But the sample one is insane. OK. Here lies Randy, a dirty old man.
So my alternate be mine for you. My alternate is just here lies Jason, a dirty old man.
This personalized tombstone. I didn't mean sexually.
I mean, like like pig pen and old, not like horny or anything. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that kind of thing. So this says with name and saying of your choice, a dollar fifty.
What? It cost a dollar fifty.
Unless that's I don't think that's yeah.
Or is it fifteen? It's a weird looking.
I think it's meant to be a dollar fifty.
But that kind of like glues it to a certain point.
I don't even think you get like a side of bacon for a dollar fifty in Disney now.
Or like avocado on something I think is more than a dollar fifty.
Yeah, avocado is very expensive. So that's a fun.
That's a fun little game you invented. Everybody write your own.
Write your own little tombstone epitaph, your own comical death and the Senate test posted in the
Please. The comments on the tweet.
I loved this kind of thing growing up and I my I but the where I grew up is a very like
southern is that kind of southern plantation style sort of just had a big, big porch and
there I had a sort of little like little hill I lived on top of almost.
And so plenty of room to put basically my dad and I made when I was a kid made a bunch of
gravestone markers and I wasn't clever enough to come up with them.
Then I think I tried and it was just really like not kind of having my dad's like, I don't know.
But he was like being a head writer of these things.
But going through my dad, I mean, I let me just say case they ever hear this, I was delighted by
making the tombstone, having those in front of our house made me so happy during Halloween season,
walking in the door, passed a bunch of tombstones and stuff.
But there is this one that didn't occur to me as odd until I got older.
And this was my dad's invention.
There was a Halloween tombstone that said, here lies an atheist all dressed up with no place to go.
Well, that doesn't rhyme at all.
It's not a rhyme. It's not one of the rhyme ones.
No, no, it's just a or found it in a book or something and put it.
So we used my family used Halloween decorations to shame atheists.
Yes, the decorations had an agenda.
Yes. And it truly did not occur to me until I went and met more people.
That was a bizarre thing.
It's I will say this, it is funny.
Yeah. Yeah. It's not a bad joke.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll give you that.
So it is funny. So at least it has that.
But yes, it is it is funny because it's like, yeah, it's turning its nose at atheists, turning up its nose.
Yeah. It's for the best.
The Disney doesn't have this joke. Yeah.
It's not welcome in Disneyland.
I wonder if they could have gotten away with that, though, in the early days, because maybe people would have just thought that's a funny joke.
Mm hmm. And as opposed to like feeling like it was commenting more of like because you could just say, well, that's just a funny joke about atheists.
Because since they don't believe in a heaven, they don't have anywhere to go.
They're dressed up in no place to go. They don't have anything.
That might be my dad's defense that it's not like a hard attack.
Right. It's just a play. It's a it's just a clever use of words to display that like there's no.
Yeah. I'm curious now if that was his invention or not, or if you can find.
I am curious about that. Yeah.
It's like, do you guys ever watch? They used to show it after Are You Afraid of the Dark? The Alfred Hitchcock Presents show.
Oh, yeah. Very similar to Twilight Zone, but he would always do these very like darkly funny, morbid intros and stuff.
And that I think I like that as a kid. I really don't remember the episodes, but I love those intros because it's just this odd, weird man and the style of humor of these of the Haunted Mansion.
And also a lot of religious judgment. Yes. I don't care for the Jews.
That was in the outtakes where they couldn't show him on the famous Hitchcock.
What do they even believe? What else we got?
Yeah. So there were there were different. Yeah. What are what's the so those are back. All of those are bad.
So there's one thing you probably saw this in the book that one of them is devoted to Yale Gracie.
Yes. And that he's referred to as Master Gracie. And that made a lot of people think that master means you're in charge of the house.
And therefore, does that mean the ghost host is Yale Gracie? Does not mean that.
It does not mean that. Yeah. For it mean the master was back in the past.
You would call like master was a child who wasn't old enough to be called Mr. Master Wayne.
Master Wayne. Master Bruce. My grandmother called me that once. Really?
Very confusing. The other thing is I learned today Yale Gracie.
It was not there like we don't think of him as the ghost host because Yale Gracie, the ghost host, it's implied he commits suicide.
Oh, sure. Yale Gracie was murdered. Really?
The Yale Gracie was murdered at a hotel on the Pacific Coast Highway. Like it was a completely random like burglary.
Oh, no. Yes. I never knew this until this morning.
So in some case we were talking what if a big rock fall on that guy's head?
In this case, one of them really did. I mean, I've served some of the number of them have passed away by now, but oh my God.
Yeah. Yeah. Happened in the 80s. So like I mean, so they had already this had already been built.
But I was I was shocked by that. That is insane. Yeah. It was like a burglar.
Yeah, it was a burglar. It didn't seem to have any like rhyme or reason or anything. Oh, no.
So yes. But again, a big old house with a family graveyard next to it.
Another thing we traditionally think of like imagining a haunted house, a graveyard by it.
But in the 19th century, how big old houses had family graveyards by it.
But it wasn't necessarily like seen as spooky at the time. I was reading a little bit about this.
Let's see. This was from I think Doom Buggies was citing a book going to the cemetery was a favorite outing,
one in which duty was mingled with pleasurable and sensuous melancholy is in.
I forget what book this is from. The Doom Bunkies cites a lot.
So but back in the 19th century, you have to think about like the world is speeding up, right?
Like technology is changing so rapidly and everything.
But antibiotics aren't coming for a while. So everyone is dying all the time.
Like populations are increasing. The Industrial Revolution has begun to happen.
Like so it's a real fucking shit show. Western expansion.
People like leaving to move somewhere and just never coming back or never hearing from them again.
So people dealing with death is part of daily life a lot more, I feel like back in that era.
What's this? What does all this stem from? Just the family graveyard.
Like people would pick that family graveyard.
And there's also the 19th century saw the rise of spiritualism of people being obsessed with like,
can we communicate with the spirit world? The dead smarter than the living.
They're more wise, more powerful than the can we try to communicate with them?
We also saw Houdini at the time debunking insane like spirit mediums who were con artists, psychics and frauds.
He said supposedly he had a word that he told his wife when he died.
He said you go to all the psychics and they should be able to contact me.
It was their favorite song. I saw it was like the Roosevelt or something.
And he said you're going to go to all of them and they're going to do supposedly if they're doing a seance they can contact me
and they'll be able to tell you what we know together. And none of them could do it.
None of them could do it.
He was an advocate for debunking all of that.
He was debunked all of it. But after he died, his wife held a seance for 10 years after his death.
And at the end of the last one said 10 years is long enough to wait for any man and extinguished the candle.
She kept burning and they were on the roof of the Knickerbocker Hotel.
And at the moment that happened, a thunderstorm broke out in Los Angeles.
Every woman in the old days was like Tallulah Bankhead just like has a great quippy line.
Like it's just like a very perfect.
Sure.
I don't know why I picked her. I like her.
Mrs. Houdini, I'm assuming a bit of a for around it.
You know, I don't know what her occupation was.
I'm sure she picked up some of the showmanship.
Of course. Anyway.
So yeah, this is to get us back to. Yes, the graveyard.
This was one of the threads I started to follow and that they would have been when designing the mansion, like when we need a family graveyard.
This old house is spooky. The family graveyard is spooky.
Even though back then people would be having a swinging wake at the family graveyard.
Oh, that it's not so bizarre. If you had a family graveyard now would be really insane.
But yeah, it makes us spookify it more than they may have.
Sure. In the time the house would have been built.
All right. And then is this tell me if I'm not going the right order.
The pet cemetery. Yeah. That was added later.
This was not original. It seemed like it was kind of off the beaten path and then they moved it to a more central spot.
Yeah, it was around like the side.
Initially on the side like what? Like, no, I don't know.
I think it was just like a little fun thing that there was a secret. Yeah.
And then they sort of moved it more where you can see now all the animals and stuff.
It was created in the early 1980s. Kim Irvine.
Yeah. And mostly like store bought statues, store bought animal statues that they then made the custom made the headstones for.
OK. Well, I always this is so dumb of me to not think about this,
but it's so funny when you hear like Imagineers and that person I was mentioning, Tanya Norris,
who like went to New Orleans with Walt to like figure out decorations for New Orleans Square and Haunted Mansion.
It's like they're just going into shops, New Orleans and buying lamps and buying in my brain.
It's like all of it's invented. They fabricated everything from scratch.
Right. Whereas why? It doesn't make any sense.
And like on Expedition Everest, Joe Rodey is going to like bazaars and marketplaces
and buying all of this different stuff to populate the queue with to make it feel authentic.
It's like I think in my non thinking brain, I was like, well, they're all made in house.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Imagineers with like what sense would that make?
Yeah. I mean, that like any TV or movies, like if you meet set decorators or wardrobe people like I think as a kid,
I always thought like, well, this is from a big building at Warner Brothers.
And that's like half true. Like half the wardrobe is rented from the studios
and the other half is just wardrobe people buying shit at Marshalls and thrift stores.
Like we got to have like 20 options a person like just to.
So for someone to look at for 30 seconds or less and go like, not that one, that one.
And then it's like, get them to set. We need to get this done.
All that thought just get you.
There's a hundred people on the clock right now that we need to get out of here.
There are a lot of unsung heroes on movie and TV sets and whatever.
But the costume department, I'm always impressed.
Like just like somebody walking in with like 15 different coats, just holding 15 different coats and an assistant trying to help.
And there's just like racks and racks of clothes, only which like five percent will be used or less.
Yeah. So they have enough to like like satiate the insane directors appetite to see choices.
Let's get you a watch or a tie clip.
And they're just pulling these boxes out of stuff and Greek like fixing it so it fits you.
I wear a lot of my own clothes sometimes for shoots because I have the weirdest sizes, the weirdest proportions.
Yeah. Yeah. To find bizarre things and have them be the right size.
Yeah. All right. Where are we?
We're at the cemetery. We're getting close to the door.
We're getting close. We're getting close.
I have to say, one of the funny things I found when I was trying to find out about the cemetery.
So like there's like 13 Imagineer headstones now.
And there's the vault.
There's like a call of the mall, the vault kind of thing that we took pictures in front of that one day.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Which I'm trying to find those photos.
I was trying to post those photos of you, me and Aaron. Oh, I have them.
Oh, you do. OK. Good.
Because there's photos of us in front of the area that you're not supposed to walk because the photographer let us go down there in that little area.
Yeah. So what was I going to say? Oh, I found a blog where someone had it tracked the graveyard changes and we're not happy.
They were not happy about the Disneyland, the new Imagineer headstones.
They were definitely not happy about the interactive queue in Florida.
The title of that blog post was just called Decadence.
So I was like as I'm like diving through all this stuff, trying to write stuff down, I'm like, OK, maybe I found my line.
Yeah. Yeah. As you're digging, there still is a way you could be that you're not willing to be.
Yeah. I. Jesus. Yeah. I'm just look, there's a lot we could do.
I really want to talk about the stretching room. I think we would be sure.
I think we would be out of our minds if we didn't get to the stretching room and say in this.
It feels like we're going to get there. I can't guarantee it.
We have a foyer to talk about. We have the door and the porch.
There's more porch. Let's go then.
Wrap around poor. I mean, the queue is like just switchbacks in California.
Like that is the one thing it's like kind of claustrophobic.
Hold on. Hold on. We have time. We have time. I agree that the queue in Florida is a little bit more of mystery.
And then this kind of switchback is a little bit like I do kind of find that a little boring.
Yeah. Especially if it like kind of backs up for a little too long.
You're just standing there. I always like pirates always feels a little more fun just because there's a like a scenery change and on the queue.
Usually, although also that's a quick, but you are limited by space like the berm is right there.
The edge of the part of the train tracks are right. Right. There's not a lot of room there to like theme it a little bit more.
But yeah, you're just kind of on top of each other. But that's obviously a minor gripe.
I'm always I will say is always and I've seen they do this at like events.
Sometimes I always want to go up stairs. I always want to be up there.
I want like give us a bar up there. Pretty small. Small bar. It would be a very small bar.
But that walkway, I mean, it was thrilling to be on the second level with Club 33. Yeah, for sure.
But that's always I'm always looking up there and like, come on, can they like build out behind?
Can they just build a extra section? I think you had a tunnel.
Yeah, you're probably right. You had a large stowed train tunnel.
There's got to be a way. There's got to be something up there to hang out.
So but I I Scott, I'm going to say I think we will get a stretching room.
And I did not make a lot of notes about the stretch group because I'm notes about the stretch.
Like the thing you didn't think we know. Well, I know a lot of it off the top.
Oh, I had and I had notes from last year where I was very ambitious trying to cover the whole.
Yeah, my notes are like through half the ride. But these notes will stay.
They'll gather dust till 2022. That's good.
I had to know I didn't make new. I should save me work this year.
But it's a very important fact about this Haunted Mansion.
It's the only one you enter through the front door of the house.
Sure. The others you enter through the servants quarters.
So this one, you see the house and you see right where you're going to go into.
And you enter a foyer foyer foyer.
How are you saying? OK, for you, the foyer being my terminology is mixed up.
Foyer is we are inside. That's the room.
Yes, we're inside. We're inside.
We're staying inside. Oh, no.
So that is the room before the stretch and grill.
Yes. Yes. All right.
Many American homes have a foyer.
Some have what is known as a general foyer.
People need to know what a foyer is to get context for this section of the podcast.
Only on a man you enter through the front door, the others you enter through the side servants quarters.
So the foyer, does someone have the narration?
Yeah, I don't know. You can do it.
I have it somewhere. But yeah, when hinges creep in doorless chambers and just creep.
You're like reading it all cool.
Isn't it? I read that is it?
Is creep is a creeper creek? I don't know.
I don't know. I could be wrong.
No, just read the thing. What do you read?
You got a list chambers and strange and frightening sounds echo through the halls.
Whenever candle lights flicker, when the air is deathly still, that is the time when ghosts are present, practicing their terror with ghoulish delight.
Great. Very good. Thank you.
I want to make sure is now the time with that being said, OK, we didn't really talk.
Let's talk about the fucking ghost host. Yes, the man.
Perhaps the greatest performance in a Disney park. Yeah.
What else could beat this?
That's tough to beat. Obviously, there's single bears in the country, bears that are up there.
But as far as iconic, long lasting performances where people know it, more people all know it.
And it is Mr. Paul Fries, one of the great voice actors of that era.
Also Ludwig von Drake, also Boris and Rocky and Bullwinkle.
He narrated the original great moments of Mr. Lincoln.
I think he's back on it now. He's one of the Beatles on the Beatles cartoon.
That's right. From the 60s. I forget which Beatles.
Really? Yeah. Yeah. Wow. He's done a ton of stuff.
He's the Pillsbury Doughboy. Yeah. He's so many things.
And truly what you just read, Jason, when you hear that paired with the music, with the first strains of Grim Grin and Ghosts, the minimal organ.
I just think that music and that voice, that is the best little and you like just the best combo of music and performance.
And you can hear it. I was just pulled it up, pulled it up on Spotify on the way here.
And it transports you there. There's other bits of theme park music you could hear that don't have that same effect.
But just like it's like it teleports you. It's such a weird feeling of dread and excitement.
Yeah, it is. I don't know. Yeah. There's no more perfect marriage of that anywhere in the parks.
I mean, there's great. I mean, there's obviously pirates. Part of pirates is perfect. But like that one.
Yeah, probably the top. Oh, Paul Friese. Also Dead Men Telling No Tales.
Dead Men. Oh, sure. I think I was not clear on that. Exatencio, I think, is the voice of the skull.
But the dead, the droning Dead Men Telling No Tales. I didn't know it's all today.
So like, yeah, in the two iconic classic from the 60s, perennial attractions, it's both of these.
I think he's the auctioneer as well. Yes, he was the auctioneer. They replaced him.
All got replaced, which is a bummer. Not the thing that changed. They replaced his voice.
I cannot talk about Paul Friese without mentioning that playing this little clip, his most iconic villain, certainly the the ghost host.
But if he's a villain, he's pretty friendly, honestly. But very similar voice. Here's this.
Let me play this clip. If I am destroyed, so shall you be.
That is the voice of Carr, K.A.R.R., the evil Kit from Knight Rider.
He was an alternate villain version of Kit. He's the opposite of William Daniels.
This is I've talked a lot about Baywatch. I am a Hasselhoff completist. I am also a giant fan of Knight Rider.
The evil character Carr appears twice. One time it is Paul Friese and the other it is not.
It is so much worse when it's not Paul Friese. And with it, you can tell within Knight Rider fandom online, a great area to poke around.
Of course. People love Carr, Carr, and which I do too. K.A.R.R. That rules.
So the first time I saw that, like, oh, my God, the ghost host is on Knight Rider. This fucking rules. That's wild.
I'm trying to find the Beatles. Which Beatle he did. Oh, yeah. Well, there's these great videos where it's all the voices.
And then the video of the raw audio of him recording all of these parts. Oh, my God.
It is a two part video on YouTube. Just phenomenal to listen to. Like 15 minutes of raw audio.
Watching this guy nail this performance that is now so iconic.
And also just hearing like it's so amazing to hear him do these things that we can all narrate perfectly with the exact timing and then hear him go like, that was it?
Another one. Like, I hear him just do a sides. And then he does a version like he's Peter Lorre. Oh, right.
He does it a total different way. Like you see, they're trying this stuff too. God, they have this whole alternate version. Yeah.
When he did like, which exactly like, do we want to be more monster with it or do we just want it to be this sort of looming?
He was George Harrison and John Lennon on the Beatles cartoon. Wow. That's crazy.
He Beatles. There is a full Paul Fries episode in our future. Oh, for sure. Which we could do all the imaginaries for.
But let me let me voice other wasn't all of them.
Yeah, just a little taste and please just look up this video of Paul Fries voice recordings. But hang on.
And it is this cadaverous Pella betrays pastoral fine.
Rudi first heavy neck at all.
Take two from welcome foolish models. I may as well give you another one, right?
All right. You're in backwards all of a sudden. Like, what's that about? Yeah. He also says some very offensive things, but this is the 16th. Oh, yeah.
Sure. There's a clip I was like, oh, I got to play this. And then an offensive thing is said and I did not want to play it or talk about it.
You can explore it yourself. However, the rest of the thing is so cool.
And it gives me the same little shades of like when you're hearing raw takes of Brian Wilson make working on pet sounds like or I just always love like old the guys like having to condense like,
oh, you were three seconds over here in the like, you know, just very workman like engineer dudes like, I don't know.
And the fact that they had this also perfectly timed out that like that they're that they had the timing ready to get.
They knew that the ride mechanism enough to know like that's going to be too long. Yeah, right.
It does like it does seem like you would be especially back then when it was like this stuff is still not a science completely, but especially back then you'd think it would have been like, well, we have two weeks solid worth of takes.
And we're just going to figure this out where it does seem like you're doing there. Like they know.
And maybe in the lack of any non digital time, tape is more precious and recording studio time is more precious.
So they really did have to like nail it precisely. I mean, I guess like show wise, like you're writing and you're like, well, people are going to be in the room for two minutes and like you can ballpark it, I guess.
Yeah, yeah. He was also. I was going to say he's also the thing on the 1960s Fantastic Four cartoon.
Oh, yeah. The one with Herbie. Herbie the robot. I think Herbie is in that version, I believe. I think it is.
This was the cartoon where Marvel replaced the human torch with a robot named Herbie because they didn't want kids to try to light themselves on fire.
No, wait, this is different. This is different. The human torch was in this version.
OK, Herbie is a later version. Yeah. Yeah. So just also when you hear this radio, hearing like the difference between like what was a pretty good take and what's an iconic take and you hear a guy just like, that's pretty good.
Just do it once more. You know, to be a little more whispery with it, you know, definitely, definitely still.
And then he does it. And then you hear hearing like a B plus version and hearing the A plus iconic one little note from some stiff shirt and a white colored shirt.
Yeah. Gives him like and now that is iconic and is heard around the world for 50 years.
And and you hear takes where like he does it, you know, it's wall to wall creeps.
And that's not nearly the same as wall to wall creeps. Yeah. Little choices.
It's just that's why I'm obsessed with this. This performance. Every little where he just finds weird little bends.
And it's so iconic. And you love the Knight Rider remake from 2008 to. Oh, of course. Yeah. Sure.
With I was that was I remember gladiators 2008 and I wrote two thousand and they all they all they nailed it.
My first job gladiators 2008. And I remember at the rap party or like the big premiere party, the live broadcast of the premiere just rolled from gladiators right into Knight Rider.
And I thought those were the same. That was their big white hope after the writer strike was Knight Rider.
And white hope crashed, crashed and burned. That was the one where it was supposed to be Will Arnett.
But he had done it was associated with associated with another car or whatever that was.
And then it became Val Kilmer. Is that right? So and but no car. I don't believe a car.
I don't think they had a car. So so by that I mean K.A.R. Oh, right. Oh, they did not. There was a car.
But not a K.A.R. Sure. And Michael Knight showed up in one episode. Hasselhoff himself showed up in one.
Palfrey's a guy I feel like there's a lot.
Not that voice actors, voice actors, I don't think even get that much as much recognition as they deserve in general.
But it's like a name I feel like doesn't get said even like you're obviously your Mel Blanks is the top of it.
But like Mel Blanker, think of the time he was maybe because he was on air a little more too.
Yeah, but I feel like I'm like lasting wise. Sure. You know, you hear June Foret's name and these are all people that deserve a lot of credit.
She was rocky on Rocky and Bullwinkle and she did a lot of voices.
But I feel like for yeah, for the Haunted Mansion narration, more people probably heard that.
Like if you go to the amount of people that have had a feeling because of this man's voice.
You know what I mean? Like like how many people actually he is. Yeah.
And I think maybe that is a good moment to say this.
The reading along with the narration. Oh, shut the hell. No, the hard stance.
I'm making an assumption here. Yeah, I'm going to say the podcast, the right stance is shut the fuck up.
Don't read along with the thing. Let's listen to Palfreys. What are you doing?
Why does everyone do this? What are you a hardliner like that or no? I hate it.
I think people have gotten better at it. I think so too.
It was really out of control in the more ironic 90s.
And I think now people are more willing to just enjoy it and be part of it.
And I, you know, it just to me, that's like this weird like trying to take control of it.
It was like, yes, like bratty people going like I've outsmarted this.
I know what it is. I'm cooler than it. And you're not. It's the best. Shut up.
Yeah, I guess I think so. I mean, there's two things, two reasons I say I don't like it.
Number one, I want to sit there and I would like to I've been on this a lot.
I've gone on this a lot, but I would like to sit there, stand there quietly and try to feel.
I want to feel it. I want to enjoy it. I want to feel it the way.
And then number two, there's people that haven't been on this before.
Now, Southern California, a lot of us have probably half the room has been on it or more, maybe more.
Yeah, it might be 75 percent. Who knows? But people that are on it for the first time,
maybe they're coming to a theme park for the first time.
Why would you want to have your voice talk over this perfect narration and change the experience
for people that might be going on at the first time and blown away by how cool it is?
Because you're selfish, because you want it to be about you.
I think it's like singing louder than the musician at the concert.
It's like, let's I don't like this guy having a spotlight.
Put the spotlight on me. I say no.
The concert's different because singing along and singing like it is a line.
There's a line at a concert between really enjoying into it versus this about me.
I mean, it's pornography. You know when you see it at the concert, you go, that guy's too much.
But in your case, it's seeing a woman's knees.
Well, that is pornography. Yes, too much.
But movies and plays.
I cannot be tempted by a lower leg.
If you're in a dark theater, if you're watching a movie or watching a play, no, I think the same thing as this.
It's it's you are the audience. You be a polite audience member.
I want to sit there perfectly still and perfectly quiet.
And I want to take it all in.
I'm and I'm going to only say this a tad.
I am a tad more lenient on the blackout scream a tad.
I still prefer no scream.
I'm relieved when there isn't a big group scream.
I am, too. But OK, that actually maybe you could argue adds a little something, but also is a little too showy for me.
They might be like seeking it by having that scream in there.
It's like all the voices going, the bean bunnies up there.
Like they may be sort of they want you to scream.
But then there's also the people who get on and like I'm going to shatter eardrums with my scream.
Yes, that I don't care for because that just feels so performative.
And you're not trying to help anything other than just be like, let's see how loud and let's see if I can like make a spectacle of my voice.
Well, when it's adults like when it's like teens or tweens, like I'm like, oh, you don't have empathy.
Your brain is still growing. I can forgive it a little.
When it's like some dipshit like 30 year old Orange County dude, it's like you you have been on this before.
You've done this a million times. Why are you chanting along?
You weird man. I not like us. Not like there's nothing weird about the way we like weird men and yelling on a podcast on a free Sunday they have to everybody shut up.
Yeah, I mean, this is a crank. I wonder what the prevailing wisdom.
I wonder if we've just lost like a third of our audience.
We like chanting along. I wonder what the consensus is.
I feel like I get the least of I feel like I have a sense of the Facebook group and I think we're going to get a lot of support on that.
I would think so.
Hopefully on Melissa's cheek.
And I get it that there's some fun stuff that you want to since you go a lot to the parks, there's fun stuff to participate in.
Like I mean, if you liked if your thing was singing, it's a small world in a tasteful manner. I find the songs playing. That's not my thing.
I'm just saying I sometimes I find myself if I'm on pirates as we're going down, I'll just be like dead men telling the tales though.
And this is for a Pirates episode.
Don't talk in the boat when you're before you have the waterfall that I've done it probably once or twice of my hundred times.
I've been on it, but there are people full on conversations when you're going into the into the dark area.
Consider that the pre show. It's like checking your phone during the trailers.
Yeah, but it's so mood setting.
I told some people to be quiet once because they were fucking hammered and my family was visiting and then someone went to the bathroom afterwards and they these drunks were complaining that I told.
Can you believe that guy told us to be quiet like in the like quietest part of the ride?
I would love to have seen that happen.
Boy, I would not do that. I don't think unless it was like total truly like out of control.
But there's mood mood mood that that place sets a mood.
The Haunted Mansion surely sets the mood and it's like let's all let's all be present.
I think there are conversation rides. I think on the train you can talk on the people mover.
You can talk. Sure. Yeah.
You look as long as you're not shouting on the ride the Haunted Mansion and also when we're walking in the hall, talk at a normal volume.
That's fine. I'm not saying like we have to be portraits.
Right. I'm just saying there's plenty of times when I'm not we're not being insane.
It's just when that that specific thing happens and people talk.
And again, I have noticed it's gone way down because I think it's bothered the employees and they start they've started saying don't talk.
Yes, in character. Yes.
They will say also I should say if you are a child and you are scared by all means, do what you have to do.
Like do if you are a scared child, you are freaking out because you are scared by the ghosts and the hanging skeleton.
Please. Yes. Go nuts.
I do not judge a child. I would love to see you shout a child down for it.
I'm saying I would never do that.
I don't know. But what if he was a loud child?
What if he was hammered? You know what I do?
I just hang back at the loading. I just slow my walk and I let them I let a bunch of cars.
I let them go first, get a bunch of cars in between, solve the problem without any conflict.
Here's what I'll say. If you want, I will approve if say you're like Disneyland is very empty and maybe you're in there with just like a group of your friends.
This happened maybe once or twice.
Have a little fun there. There's not a lot of other folks there.
That's a unique situation, obviously. And I think like if it was a group of maybe like six or seven of us and one of us had a killer idea for a bit or a joke, go for it.
That's fun. I'm just saying that when it's packed in there, there's no reason.
That's the show. Enjoy the show. Yeah, we're not the show.
And that's the podcast, the right. That's our truth.
Hot take about that situation.
That being said, the stretching room, the stretching room.
Well, can we go back? There was going to be they toyed.
Apparently, did you see this with the ghost host in the foyer having a talking like bust?
Oh, wow. It was not going to just be a narration.
There was going to be a little figure. Really? Oh, that's it.
I would like have moved its mouth with Paul Freese's narration.
Well, and I guess there's that thing as well is like, what is the ghost host? Because some people think it's the bird. It's the raven.
Yes, it is. I guess it's the body that's hanging.
You know, it's my. Yeah, that's him. That I think has been so that that was there.
Like, we don't like to call that hanging man Master Gracie because he didn't commit suicide.
He was murdered. But we can assume. Yes. As the ghost host tell us his way out.
Yeah. So but what is he to any of this is the question.
Does it matter? Oh, just a ghost who's around. Yeah.
Well, the ghost host is a shoot. Am I wrong?
Am I wrong? But the ghost host supposedly is the one playing the piano in the attic.
Oh, I think I caught that. That's that's right. Right.
The shadow playing the shadow. Right. Yes.
It's like you remember that effect in the in the when the piano is being played, which is very similar to the fact that we're at the party.
No, no, it's in the attic. I believe I'll double check this right now.
I've seen this as well. OK, so that makes me feel better about that information.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. OK. I think the kind of like rumors and urban legends and stuff is so correct is so diegetic to this ride because that's what happens with haunted houses or abandoned houses like, oh, did you hear that?
Well, you know, it really happened there. It all makes sense.
It just adds to the legend that you are right. Yeah, it's like a real murder house. We're like, oh, yeah, I think it's this.
No, the husband did this. No, no, this guy. Crazy guy came in. Yeah, it's like it is an urban.
And I think like leaving it a little open to interpretation adds some joy.
I feel like everything is like, you know, double checked, tees crossed, eyes dotted.
Nowadays, there's like mythology really if it was made nowadays, they'd be like, OK, well, let's write out all nine hundred and ninety nine ghosts.
Let's figure out how they all got there. And it's like, fuck off. No, it's a house full of ghosts.
I know. I prefer this to it. I'm making up mythology as you go.
Let's talk about the portraits. We got a yes. We got a girl on a tightrope.
And as we go downward, we see that there is an alligator. And these are guests. Is that that's right? Am I wrong?
They're people who stayed at the mansion in various times are some of our guests in their more corruptible. These are some of our guests.
So I see. Oh, that's a line in there. Yeah. Yeah. So this is like sort of a warning, essentially to us.
Yeah, because I was a little bit even though that's in the narration, I was a little ironic thing beneath us.
Yes. We don't know about or but we're all also like all of these people.
Well, all of these people, except for the woman on the gravestone, are going to die. Right? Yeah.
Because I've always did. I always see. I feel like that one is revealing like she killed the husband. You're right.
Yeah, like they all all of the stretching portraits add information.
And yeah, and that yeah, I guess in some cases they're going to die and they don't know it.
In other cases, though, this person is a murder. Right. So this is supposed to like be a kooky way to scare us and not the originals.
What we look at now are not the original paintings. These have been updated over the years and kind of have gotten more lifelike.
But they're the same idea. Same idea. Yeah. Yeah.
But they're not the original. I believe are the paintings that Raleigh Crump drew originally.
And Mark Davis said, no, that's no good. I'll redraw them. Whoa. Wow. Other people have redone them since.
Well, they got that sense of humor. And then Mark Davis. They're the Mark Davis thing.
It is funny because like they thought we've talked about this in the last episode last year.
It's Claude Coats versus Mark Davis. Claude Coats wanted it to be creepy, a little more traditionally like a haunted house.
Mark Davis, very whimsical characters, big, fun, silly things. And kind of their backgrounds. Claude Coats, a background painter. Yes. Yes.
Mark Davis, yeah, as you said, character designer. Yeah. But yeah, early on we have a big dose of character and silly.
Yes. And it's like the first half of the halfish, maybe more of the mansion is more Claude Coats.
But you get a little of your Mark Davis in this room. Yeah. Yeah. That's the most I'm trying to think with the next Mark Davis thing is I'm sure he had plenty to do with everything.
But especially the graveyard at the end. But yeah, of course. Yes. But this is like the first silly thing.
But it's still in the tone of we're trying to scare you. Yeah. Well, almost a lot of them are like not funny when you look at it at first.
And then stretching reveals the fact that it's sort of in keeping with the theme of scary, but then surprisingly silly. Right.
And of course, you know, and really, I think with silly, if you took out man with no pants on. Dynamite guy.
It would like if I'm looking at all four of them and if this was gone, it would look a lot less silly.
I think no pants man with boxer shorts on does read and make the whole thing sillier. Sure.
It's still silly, but boxer shorts, striped boxer shorts. It's a comedy. Comedy move. Classic.
The vaudeville ass move. The name of that man. Do we know the name offhand? I don't know where I found this.
This is where I yeah, this starts to get interesting. Go ahead.
Well, the name of the guy stood. We reveal is standing on top of dynamite. His name is Alexander Nitra cough.
I did not know that. I don't know. Forget where I found that. I found it last year.
But next time you go on there, tell your list. Whisper to your friend or loved one that there is Alexander Nitra cough.
And in very few, this will come up later, but not very many names.
There's all these characters, but almost none of them have specific names.
So that's actually a rare one. Not very many, but I think over the years they've been like giving back stories here.
And there were like in additions. Oh, this addition references this character who we gave a background to that didn't have one before.
Right. Like a ride with the next is Constance Hatchaway. Oh, yeah.
And then there's like think that's right. Eleven different they sold. They were selling around the mansion time.
They were selling eleven different like spirit jars. So they had eleven different characters.
So you had your hitchhiking ghosts and you had your hat box. But then like Constance Hatchaway and all these other way.
Now, that's where it starts to get like pins. They have sold pins of like the changing portrait that either said the ghost host or master.
It said something that people had assumed over the years and imagineers were like, well, let it slide.
But we didn't approve that. So the myth, all people are inventing their own mythology.
Again, urban legends, rumors and stuff. Those three guys in the quicksand, they don't got names.
I didn't see we know the husband is George because we see his tombstone. Yeah.
Anyway, these are wonderful. I realize that these are sort of like it's it's the really what it is is an opposite direction.
Mad Foulding, where that's nice. And then this is sliding down and revealing info.
But right at the time, the peak of Mad Magazine, like very clever, great, really good comical illustration.
They're sort of like oddly similar, super detailed and great character design. Yeah.
The room itself, one of the early like pieces of trivia that's fun is how in Disneyland it the you know, the question is this haunted room actually straight?
Wait, no, that doesn't answer the question. It's in Disneyland. You are going down. It's an elevator.
Yes, you are descending and the top of the top of the room stays where it is.
You're when you walk in the room, you're right next to the the hanging ghost host. You don't really. It's like right on top of you in Disney World.
They kept the effect and tell you they kept the effect, but it's the ceiling that goes.
Yes. And which that was all a mind blow to me as a kid and like we're having like guessing and seeing if you can tell.
And you know, you can tell because you feel yourself moving in Disneyland, but it's all to get you out and under the berm.
But it's cool that they recreated the same effect, but did it opposite.
Yeah, because like so and I'm assuming I this I'm sure I'm assuming I'm right.
I remember I've talked about this in the show when I was in Pirates.
I truly up until a couple of years ago didn't realize that Pirates, the ride itself, the majority of it in Disneyland is sea level is the normal land.
And when you enter, you're of course entering up on the second or whatever you'd maybe even third story.
I don't know what you call it necessarily. And then all of that is built up. New Orleans Square is built up on top of where the earth was when they started building.
I was like, oh, yeah, of course it is. They didn't dig in my brain.
I was like, they must have dug under and made this whole thing here.
This sort of impossible architecture dawned on me.
And I'm sure I learned this at some point, but it freaked me out this week when I saw the diagram.
This little purple box is the foyer and the stretching room.
This is all that exists in the facade. The facade you look at of the mansion is just the stretching room.
It's like a tenth of the land.
I mean, not even not even a massive show building behind it that you never see from in front of the mansion.
It is all the ride is it is so odd that I don't I didn't think about that up until a few years ago.
Also, yeah, I didn't really think about it. I knew it must, of course, be bigger somehow.
But how many people go in there and walk into this mansion and go like, oh, we're in this elevator.
OK. And never think about the fact that it has to it has to be that big.
But seeing yes, as you're saying, seeing it blows your mind.
You still are sort of picturing that you're going around different rooms of this house.
Yeah, like, OK, well, it's the basement of this house. We're in a basement now.
Yeah. When, in fact, of course, I think just like pirates, I could be wrong. They just built the house up one story, essentially.
Right. Like they did with all the different parts of New Orleans Square.
And then you're just taking an elevator down to like normal level.
And there's a massive, unmarked show building behind it.
And it go away green. Oh, yeah.
Oh, the avoidable, the color. You don't really there was an even odder term for it online.
I forgot to write down. I was like, Tata, like there was some very weird.
I was like, that's never what I've heard it called.
There's another thing with this effect where you I saw it framed in some listicle.
Like when you're in that elevator, you're in a cage, essentially.
The fact that you're in I don't know whether the line was first or the technology was first,
but that this room has no windows and no doors.
That partially comes from that you're stepping into this just like octagon.
I forget how many sides there are, but that you're like,
you know, extending a couple of feet above your head is this you're in this like brown space.
And that is if you weren't like completely swallowed by that, you'd be able to see the stretching of the walls better.
Like it's like hiding the the the descending essentially. Right.
So yeah, like the with the no windows, no doors makes that effects work.
Yeah, it's all like slight. It's like that slight effect, like a miss magic misdirects.
Yeah. All of it working together to like disorient you a little bit and distract you a little bit to make it so you don't know.
You are in that thing going, how are we going to get out of here?
And that when the lights go out and the fact that it is all around you, you like lose sense of direction.
Yes. And you and you. So when a door does open and you have somewhere to go, you're like, wait, it's over there.
But I came in that way. Yeah, I think it took me like 50, maybe not 50, but like 30 to 50 times on the Disneyland Haunted Mansion before I even fully was like, OK, now I know where the doors are.
And because there's two different. Yes. I figured that out this year.
I know it crazy because I'm sure I've been in both of them. But like it took me so many times doing it to go, OK, great.
These two doors both open. They are two separate elevators.
And I know which one, depending on I go in and I know where the door will open up and I know that I always rush to the back.
Like if I go in the left one or the or the right one, I know which way to go now to like get into the line faster. Yes.
But it took forever. Yeah. But I was still disoriented by the trick.
They're saying don't touch the walls. It's because they don't want people to happen to lean on the wall that's about to slide open and eat shit.
Oh, that's why they say go to the dead center of the dead center. Right. Right. Right.
Yeah, because I always thought it was like something like the wall was moving when I was like, no, no, it can't because that section is all fixed.
The section by the wall is not actually moving. It's that part is going down with us.
It's what you're saying. It's that there's a door and if somebody's leaning and gets comfortable, the thing slides open, fall right out. Yeah.
I have to say this was definitely an early influence for me, one like liking eccentric weirdos and flowery language because I hated spelling tests, like spelling and definition tests in school.
But as a kid, I knew your cadaverous pallor betrays an aura of foreboding.
I knew that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I knew I knew what that meant. I was like, yeah, I'm scared.
Yeah, I was the same way with I remember asking my mom what all the words meant in Grim Grinning Ghosts because there's such like hyper vocabulary in there.
So, yeah, it's it's educational. I remember that feeling as a kid like I have that big crazy word. I got to know what that means.
Why can't I remember the ones in Grim Grinning Ghosts? There's some there's some vocab in there.
I can't remember anything else. I got really upset too recently speaking about behaving like children because I was like Haunted Mansion was coming out.
I should drive down there and ride it, but I can't because it's Haunted Mansion holiday.
Oh, right. We're right. We don't even have time. We don't have time for that.
We'll do it after they stop doing Haunted Mansion. Yeah, it'll be gone. The year after they stop doing it. We'll do it.
The stretching. So the first part of the ride is a ride. I mean, it's an elevator.
Yeah, and we're hoping that Rise of the Resistance is a similar thing where like it's it's this multi-part experience where the pre-ride essentially is part of it too.
You know, as well, we'll find out.
Yes, because Chapek said 15 minutes of being chased around by Kylo Ren.
But does he mean that's the actual ride? Because I don't think you get chased until you're actually on the transport.
So does he mean the ride itself is 15 minutes? I hope he does.
Or is the whole experience. But it's the whole experience 15 minutes.
This is sort of the best case scenario on a mansion where it's like you don't even nobody's complaining.
I'm not on the ride yet because this thing. Right. Which is how I feel doing the episodes as well.
He's talking about the cool effects before you're there. I wonder if we can get there still.
So the hanging. Is there much to say about that? I think like, yeah, it is. We've talked about it is oddly, oddly grim.
The darkest stroke in the Disney park. It's an effect.
I think I talked to I for sure talked about this on both haunt episodes that on the not scary farm maze that's paranormal ink is they have an effect right at the end when you're in this hospital and they do like a light flicker and you just see sort of normal hallway and the lights flicker.
And all of a sudden you can see into hell. You can see through the walls. Because you see a grim thing.
Yes. You can see a demon coming at you. And I put two and two together until doing some research and like, oh, that's what this is.
And it's a very like old school analog like fit that is digital about it.
Throw a light age craft throw a light on it.
It's also how they do like the rooms that you can't see in the carousel of progress.
Like suddenly a light comes out. It was just fabric. And now we turn a light on with this whole other scene there.
We didn't even know about. There's a trick to the wallpapers in the stretching room, the candy stripe wallpaper.
The vertical lines make it feel much larger, even larger than it is.
And just as a kid, like the breading, I don't know, the candy stripe made it unnerving, made it like a scary circuit, something.
It was weird. Another thing where it's like, it's fine. It's not going to hurt you, but it makes you feel a little odd.
So nothing in the in this right. The that that light comes on and the lightning cues and like, OK, now you can see up there.
And you didn't realize there was this whole this whole hidden area.
The lighting in the stretching room is crazy because it being 360, there's nowhere to put lights.
So everything's lit by the candles. And then you can't see up there like the lightning up there.
It's like not as similar when we talked about the Back to the Future ride where you had to see all directions around you because it was this weird like.
Almost 360 way of shooting. So everything has to be lit from within.
Like there's nowhere to just like unlike Small World where you can see the lights, which I like.
There's nowhere to just hang a light anywhere in that. So it all has to be practical and no, it's a bunch of goblins.
It's goblin statues holding candles.
Those are so cool. Yeah, those are very cool. You can see if you look up, I think you can kind of see the hanging guy a little bit right when you enter.
Now, a little bit. I have a question, which is did he was he in the mansion for many, many years or was he only in that room for as long as we were?
And he was like, fuck it. That's it.
And he's like 30 seconds and he's out. Was he listening to a podcast that went on too long?
Really stretched out. People are hanging themselves with their earbuds.
Free Adnan. Adnan did nothing wrong.
Why do they have so many? Why do they have extra feed drop episodes that are ads?
Too much. So lightning flashes, you crash. You are now the door swings open.
You're in this room. Hold on a second. Yeah. And we can tell me if this is too morbid.
But it is fascinating in a very morbid way.
Do you look at Paul Freese's Wikipedia? Do you see his cause of death listed?
No. Suicide. You're kidding. It's not hanging.
It's like pills. But Paul Freese died of suicide.
That will be hard to learn. I know.
We're in that ride. I didn't know this until today.
The guy who said there's always my way. Is that is that not insane?
I thought the Brigham Young stuff was weird and like the fucking Hearst Castle connection.
Let alone all the Yale Gracie. The Yale Gracie and the Paul Freese stuff is very morbid.
It's insane. I didn't. That's a Wikipedia thing.
I'm not looking at doom buggies in their yellow journalism.
You're looking at Wikipedia. They always are liable.
But still, I mean insane. I mean, fuck. I don't know how you top that.
RIP. Yeah, I know. Well, we could just be done. We don't have to.
Although winding on such a grim note.
What do we think? We're out of the facade. We made it out.
We're in the lower level. We'll go through this room.
Let's do it. Let's do it. Because that was such a morbid way to say there.
There's not a portrait room. Let's go. What do we got?
There is a lot in there. We have like we have like go.
Portraits. OK, first of all, the water out of your mouth.
We're walking through.
First of all, the fact that it's, you know, it's a rainstorm thunderstorm down there in the windows.
Simple, effective. Sure.
Truly makes me forget what the weather outside was.
Not that I know it's not a thunderstorm, but truly like mood atmosphere.
There's nothing fake about it to me when I'm down there.
True. Really, really great.
Yes, you're right. Cool portraits, cool portraits.
Now this is you are under the railroad tracks.
This room exists for practical reasons.
Yes, to get you from the basement of the facade building into underneath the railroad tracks.
So just that part is under. Yeah, you are literally going under the tracks.
And I honestly am not sure at what point you step from under tracks into exact show building.
But you are underground. That's why the ride, the doom buggies go up the stairs.
OK, OK. To get back to the ramp at the end. Yes.
Yeah. OK. I did. I will think about the next time I'm on that.
Yeah, you're right under the train. That's pretty great.
Yeah, this is kind of a holdover from like when the whole place was going to be a walk through.
Right. But this solved the problem.
Yeah, and those effects. And yeah, we talked a little about the bus and stuff.
I know. Why can't I picture? OK, you got like a Cleopatra kind of what are notable?
You've got him in front of you. These are some of the older sketches.
Do we have favorites of these of the paintings? Well, there's like the cat lady.
I mean, the old guy, the Dorian Gray kind of old guy. The cat lady is so odd.
You have doom buggies open and the cat is flashing between the two.
Well, the ship. I think the ship is a highlight.
And there's a there's a recreate. There's things very much like this in Club 33,
which is a cool secret to discover when you're in there and that we're spoiling for you.
Yeah, the cat lady, for whatever reason, that's the one that always sticks out in my memory.
Do these paintings remind you a little bit of like black velvet paintings like sexy 70?
Honestly, the paintings remind me of the video, your Adam West video.
Oh, hey, I hold paintings with Adam West.
Check it out on my YouTube because the fun of your night went away.
So I put it on my channel. Are there actual are there I hope things in the high nation?
It's a good question. You would think there would be.
It's such an old time gag in all these types of things.
There are. There is that in the film. I'll say in the Haunted and the Eddie Murphy movie,
which is a whole other thing. Yeah.
But yeah, of all the weird effects and that was certainly a Disney inspired thing.
But the bus kind of serve a similar purpose. Oh, they they follow you. Absolutely.
And we talked about that last time how that's a reverse thing. You're looking into a sculpture.
A lot of people were like, how did they not know that? Well, we didn't.
And I feel like one person said that. But I still a lot of people are saying.
But as soon as you said that, though, that was that was my memory of someone like
making fun of us for not knowing that effect. It makes a lot of sense.
But I didn't know it either.
This is unique. Again, this is all a necessity at Disneyland.
At Disney World, you come out of the stretching room and you are right there.
You get on your doom buggy right there.
Which is why and some of these the busts are on the ride.
Yes, they were on the ride. And now let's talk about this.
I think that, you know, you can say things you like or don't like.
But better or worse, Disney World, Disneyland.
I think the first couple, the beginning of the ride in Disney World and Tokyo,
which are pretty similar, I think is a little superior because I think the
probably due to space issues that they do throw you right into it. I like.
And I think this very the very first room is kind of the most underwhelming route,
like the load area. Well, because there's sort of just nothing.
Yes. And this is what you will hear this.
If you I was referenced earlier that season pass episode about Haunted Mansion.
Tony Baxter says when Haunted Mansion, the movie was happening,
there's some sort of conservatory scene setting.
There was a plan in place to put that setting in the load area of Haunted Mansion.
Now is that like staircases and usually like if you think if picture the movie Clue,
it's kind of like conservatory.
I think that's what conservative maybe I could be getting glass, glass everywhere.
I could be getting the term when I'm pretty sure I'm right.
But it's some scene from the Haunted Mansion.
It's like a weird prominent location in the Haunted Mansion movie.
Well, I guess I guess what's got to saying, I'm just saying I think that at least Tony
and other imagineers had identified that as the weak, a weak scene.
Yeah, which is a little better in Disney World and Tokyo and way better in Phantom Manor.
Like that's where you get on the doom buggies.
And it's a thing that I like about Haunted Mansion holiday.
That big tableau of all the characters.
Yes, it's fun. It's very fun.
It makes that that really livens the room up.
So that is if I could say, you know, I'll I'll throw shade on this right here and there.
I like that Tony's identified that I think that is one weak spot.
And I and I also I don't think it's better or worse.
I like the the bus that follow you either way.
But it is cool to see there's like a library room you go to or just filled with them.
Yeah, yeah, Disney World, which I do like.
So that maybe Disney World may have the edge for those first couple of rooms.
And then it becomes pretty identical. Yeah.
The ride itself. The differences are more outside.
Right. There's this Disneyland or this this Haunted Mansion book.
Jason Sorrell wrote or put together that is very cool.
We've mentioned last time, but that's where a lot of information is coming from.
A lot of cool other things that didn't make it on the ride like this.
Like, why can't I think of Medusa? Medusa.
Thank you. Yes. Isn't that on there?
That's in the portrait. Yeah. Is it in there? Yeah.
What am I misremembering? Am I this? Yeah, that's on there.
Oh, she looks a little different. OK, OK.
But at this she's not wearing a yellow dress.
Oh, excuse me.
But there's cool stuff that isn't in there.
This scary little skeleton horse, it seems like.
Yes, the skeleton horse is cool. Skeleton horse is in there.
It looks like one of those body world things that Eva told us is the organ harvesting.
Yeah, political prisoners.
OK, this feels like, well, we're coming towards an end.
I'm going to get to I'm going to get to my goal.
So you're out you're around the corner.
We've talked about those stanchions. The stanchions are cool.
Yes, very cool. The bats.
Those are fantastic. I'd love to have one.
I like to touch those. Yeah.
And they're dirty as shit, but I like to touch them.
I know I get over a little bit of germaphobia with those.
But they age beautifully. They age to gold.
Whoa. Yeah.
As you rub it, the gold like if you see statues that people rub for good luck, that part wears away to gold.
Oh, and that the final one, they said, is like especially everybody touches the last one.
Yeah. And then you step on to a moving walkway.
We step off to the right.
You sit down in your doom buggy and we're on the ride.
We made it. We made it.
We made it. Wow.
A little under two hours in under two hours, maybe more with ads.
Holy shit. We did it.
You know what? Let's even go a little bit further.
Whoa. A little bit further.
Let's go out on a hike. We've already compromised.
Let's go out on a hike because we're sitting in the thing and we're moving forward and we want to reach forward and we want to pull that lamp bar down.
No, no, no.
And then the ghost host pops in. We haven't heard him since the elevator and he tells us no, no, no.
I will lower it for you. One of the coolest moments.
Yeah. And I will then add and then the sexy Spanish ghost host comes in.
Yes, that is in my notes. I want to compliment the Spanish ghost host very much an unsung hero.
He and that's where this is where we're going to end it.
But he is look, you know, when you're doing something that's been done already, you don't want to do the same thing, which so I appreciate not doing a Paul Fries impression.
He decided to go very sexy with it.
And it is it is truly brazos.
I love like maybe even as much as as iconic as all the Paul Fries is to me, I'm a big fan of Manos Brazos.
He is so excited. He's like he's like a like a soccer announcer.
Yeah. Yeah. So excited.
PPA supernos. Is that what he says?
I guess. Yeah. Yeah. But those are good.
But it doesn't have quite the gusto of Manos Brazos.
He's having so much fun.
There's a coziness to that, too. I don't know what it is because you're going up. I'm just like, yeah, like you feel like a little like warm.
You're on the ride. Just happened.
Yeah. No, I want to say sexy. You get like he's like Zora.
He's like Antonio Banderas. Yeah.
Swarthy. Yeah.
In good hand. Like if you got rescued by that guy, you were in some peril and that guy swung down our rope.
I'd love it. We should really find out.
Did a calm sea voyage with him back to your home.
We will find that we'll spend a year researching it.
And the first thing next year is we will find out that gentleman's name.
Who did the Spanish ghost? And that's how we'll lead off next year's episode with.
Yeah. Let's just we should just open it with just saying it before we say anything else.
OK. It's like I'll set a reminder to myself to do that.
Yeah. Any year we're at John Collins, John Collins.
I don't think it's John Collins. Probably not.
Let's just that. Mayamo John Collins. So we'll kick it off with a bang.
We'll find out his name and we'll shout it. So tune in next year.
And until then, you survived haunt cast the fright haunted mansion to guys.
We got there. I'm so happy to be on the ride.
We did it. Do it. If just with a little bit of discipline and love, we we made it there.
And now we just love love, Scott.
I'm very excited to go on this ride with you in 2020.
How many rooms per episode? I wonder. Yeah, I don't know.
Recapping the foyer stretching room and portrait hall will take 30 minutes.
Things we missed. And how grim we for sure grim.
Yeah. How grim will the the 2020 election be?
We will be in the thick of my god. You're right.
I think 10 times worse election cycle. Yeah.
So we're going to need that to cheer us up because it's going to be it's going to be bad.
Yeah. So a little message to us then hang in there.
Unless Trump just like died like you died in Jason's scenario, if he just like fell and hit his head because the dog was under him.
Yeah, that could happen, too. You never know. Anything's possible.
And then he'll have a fun tombstone.
Well, hang in there. Future Mike Scott and Jason and hey, next week, one more installment of on cast the fright, the cemetery.
Yes. If you go behind the cemetery gate on the Patreon.
Yeah, there's a little bit more. And as we said, it's it's it's a Haunted Mansion related.
And you know, to to wait, I forget the week of the twenty eighth one day, the week of the twenty eight.
I think on Halloween, right? Probably. Oh, yeah, probably.
I think that's that falls on a Wednesday. So that's all right.
So there's a little there's a little bit more left.
But as and that's a Patreon dot com slash podcast, right?
With this three bonus episodes every month. But for regular us main feed us, we're heading to Chicago, Phyllis.
Yes. See us tomorrow. Oh, my guess.
Some people here today and Friday listening Saturday morning and it just came out.
Come on out, Chicago. Oh, my. For our big boy. That's right.
That's our large, our large son, our large son.
Yeah. Well, we're looking forward to it. We'll see you there.
And happy hauntings, everybody. Let's go on this ride next year.
Goodbye. Bye. Forever.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey, engineered and mastered by Alex Arshay.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcast.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple Podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.