Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate,
where we're celebrating a historic anniversary,
a historic event that celebrated a historic anniversary.
The anniversary of an anniversary.
Of an anniversary.
October 1st, 1971, the opening of Walt Disney World
and then October 1st, 1996, the unveiling of the Castle Cake.
Yes, perhaps more important than the original opening.
Perhaps.
Of the park itself.
Perhaps more important.
Or if you will, I've been thinking about this,
do some people call it the Cake Castle?
I wasn't sure what to call the episode even.
I assume you'll be listening to it
and there will be a title,
but maybe we should talk about it now.
Yeah, is it Cinderella Castle Cake?
Is it the Cake Castle?
Is it the what's the, the Castle Cake?
I think we all very quickly started using the term Castle Cake.
All right, so we'll stick with that.
So we'll stick with that
and I'm gonna go ahead. And Cinderella
just clunks it up too, so.
Yeah. Okay.
If I Google, by the way, my name's Mike Carlson,
Jason shared an intro, that's Scott Gartner over there.
Oh yeah.
If I Google Castle Cake,
it doesn't come up in the first batch of Google search images.
You do Disney Castle Cake?
Well, I'm sure if I did that.
I'm just wondering what like the internet wants to call it.
If I look up Disney Castle Cake, oh, it doesn't,
well, hold on, let me go image search.
Well, the trouble is, you end up with a lot of like
wedding cakes. Yes, that is the problem.
That are shaped like the castle.
And that's not what it is what we're talking about.
Someone did, I forget, it's a Twitter account
of someone who works in theme park design,
I think had their like turn 25 and their birthday cake
was a replica Cake Castle.
Nice. And it looked great.
You even look up Cinderella Castle Cake
and it's like the 12th image result.
Yeah, this is right on the edge where I feel like
when I would read stuff about it online,
people would say, well, here was what the chatter
was going on about the Castle Cake in Usenet groups.
Like this is right before like,
I feel like AOL was just starting to break big.
I remember around then getting an AOL floppy disk,
like pre CD, like we got a mailing with an AOL floppy disk.
And I gotta say, I think I forgot to introduce our names
because I'm jacked up for this episode
because I love the Castle Cake.
Haters back off.
Scott Hader or I forget.
I have to admit Scott Hader.
And if I could, you know, look,
you guys have already melted my icy heart a little bit.
You've already melted my internal frosting
about the Castle Cake.
I am a little more fond of it now,
but just to back it up, I just on the way here
called my mom and she asked what I was doing today.
And I said, I'm about to do a podcast
about when Cinderella Castle was a cake for a little while.
And my mom was like, oh yeah, ugh.
So this opinion is out there.
A lot of people have this opinion.
That's the majority.
I think it's a common opinion,
which is I truly no troll, hashtag no troll.
I don't understand it.
I don't like, yeah, yeah, I love it too.
I love it.
We went that year.
I was like, this is awesome.
Yeah, I was like, I did the same thing.
I texted my dad like, hey, we're gonna do a Castle Cake
episode, the family, we all liked the Castle Cake, right?
And he's like, yeah, absolutely.
This is weird.
It divides, it goes along family lines with us.
I think it's like, let me text my mom and my sister
and see if they have an opinion and they can respond back.
Yes, please do.
I thought it was awesome.
Wow.
And maybe I had just been to Disney World enough.
I was like, something else new.
I mean, this is around,
this is like the gold and the go-go 90s,
new stuff coming left and right.
I mean, this is kind of the tail end of it.
But when you only go every few years,
the new thing from a year and a half ago,
you're like, oh, cool, something new.
It's really bold.
You gotta give it that.
And just so, just to be totally clear,
what we're talking about is that for the 25th anniversary
of Walt Disney World, for a period of 18 months,
Cinderella Castle was transformed into a big cake,
a big pink cake.
A big pink cake.
Yeah, painted multiple shades.
I think I read three different shades of pink.
And then there's a lot of like 16,
five foot high candy bears, 12, five foot high gumdrops,
four, six foot high life savers.
We're reading off the same thing.
And I like that whatever we're reading,
we're both reading has, it calls them candy bears,
not gummy bears.
Candy bears.
No, inflatable icing.
That was the thing I learned.
It didn't dawn on me at the time that like,
oh, that icing is inflatable,
which makes practical sense.
Very impressive.
Okay, so those are, that was my question
because I didn't, so those are life savers on the cake.
Yeah.
That's the idea.
That's one of my qualms.
Life savers?
What are you talking about?
We should talk about this as a practical cake.
Oh, if you were to eat the cake.
Yeah, we should address this from a standpoint of like,
the different things on the cake.
And if it makes sense or if that's good or not.
Well, are we addressing, but then we have to break down.
Is that a practical cake that you would take to a party
or is like a more elaborate wedding cake or like ace of cakes?
I mean, ace of cakes and-
This has to be transported by a baker of some kind.
The cake boss.
Like there's no way that like, I'm bringing this over.
We live in a post ace of cakes, cake boss,
duff world where cakes are insane and largely fondant,
which is purely deck, which tastes like shit.
Don't wanna eat it.
I have the first family weigh in from my sister.
I sent a picture and I said,
did you like this Cinderella castle
when they turned it into a cake?
And my sister just wrote, of course.
Wow.
The families line up.
Kicked, I thought it kicked ass.
I agree.
I'm sorry, everyone got mad.
You didn't get to see the castle that's 80% gray.
I'm sorry, there's beautiful technicolor magic
at the end of Main Street.
I wouldn't mind if every couple of years
they switched it back to this.
I want it back.
I want it back for 50th.
I want it back bad.
Because, or back for-
I don't think it's gonna happen that way, but-
This isn't the first, this wasn't the last time.
Like when the Stitch's Great Escape opened,
the castle was covered in toilet paper
and like spray painted Stitch was here.
It said Stitch is king.
Stitch is king, that sucks.
That was, I don't think anyone likes that.
And it was only for a day.
It was just to announce the arrival
of what is now considered Disney World's worst attraction,
Stitch's Great Escape.
But for the 50th anniversary of Disneyland,
not even Disney World, in 2005,
they added all this gold trim
and like a video screen that would show all the castles
around the world. The magic mirror
that cycles through all the different castles
around the world.
I gotta say, fuck out of here with this.
This looks like shit.
This looks like Trump Tower, gaudy ass gold.
Like, I hate this.
This looks worse to me than Castle Cake.
Sure. Castle Cake has a-
Castle Cake's like the best castle.
I might be with you.
I might be- Oh man.
I might be with you on that.
Oh, I'm getting shot down.
I wish we had even sides.
It's two against one.
Yeah, we should have had a guest.
You could have found someone who doesn't like the Castle Cake.
This is full of fucking world that we know
who would have opinions about this.
This is East Coast, West Coast right here.
Or this is, I mean- It might be.
In terms of the Mississippi River, I guess.
Or is it Chicago, West of the Mississippi, or East?
Yeah, it's, I should know.
I think it's West.
Fuck.
The dividing, like Disney World, Disneyland,
in terms of East and West, I mean.
I also, you know what I have to confess?
I didn't see it in person.
So that might color it.
It's East, I'm an idiot, it's East.
That would be Mississippi River.
Yeah, so as a dividing-
Or Chicago is East of the Mississippi River.
I think it's safe to say you were a Disneyland family
and we were Disney World families.
And Disneyland might have been on Mars,
like as we've established.
So you're more, you're just like,
you're going there more often, so any change is exciting.
And this is a pretty sizable change.
And we're not going that often.
We're going every three or four years.
So we had just timed the trip to be at the anniversary.
So it was just like, holy shit, cake.
Like we were- Look at this.
As kids, we were very obsessed with sweets
and the looks of like crazy cakes and desserts and colors.
Just remove as kids.
Well, that's fair.
Currently, I'm obsessed with sweets.
That's fair.
Colors, as we know.
So, yeah, yeah, it wasn't even like-
Mr. Colors.
Did I, we'll reveal more of these details down the line.
Did I eat it too much last night and get a stomach ache?
Yes, I did.
Was part of that sweets.
I wasn't feeling great either.
Yes, it was.
The little Downtown Disney ordeal preview.
Little Downtown Disney ordeal.
Was it all delicious?
Yes, it was.
Absolutely.
No regrets really, at the end of the day.
You know where I think I'm landing is that I'm not
vehemently against the castle cake.
I have found angles to like it and I enjoy your enthusiasm.
But I think how I feel is a little similar
to another ongoing back and forth discussion,
pop cultural discussion that we were into last night
a little bit, which is the Star Wars prequels.
It has started to become kind of cooler to say,
I like the prequels.
It's kind of like an anti-opinion.
Like it was so, it felt like the people who didn't like it,
it was so much more deafening at the time.
And I know all these people who are like,
you know what, actually the prequels are good.
And it's been making me go back and check them out
and see like, you know, I kind of would like to be
one of those guys who is into the pre,
and then I just watched Attack of the Clones and like,
I don't like sand.
I hate them.
And I'm like, I can't do it.
I can't fucking do it.
I can't lie about how I feel inside.
I don't like this movie and I don't like this castle cake.
Right, well I would say there's a difference.
I would think there's no time.
Like the prequels is a different,
my sister just texted, how could you not like that?
Oh man, God.
I love these live updates.
You don't even have, as you said,
you don't have, you're not vehemently like, fuck off.
I'm not, I think it's just like a taste of,
and now I should answer your sister's question.
I should attempt to justify it.
And I probably don't have the strongest justification.
I think I just like, I think I just thought it looked dumb.
I think I thought it looked like,
despite clearly not being cheap, I think it looked cheap.
It looks like a huge miniature golf obstacle to me.
I think it looks like fiberglass silly.
Yeah.
And I think there's like a stateliness
to the castles especially.
You know what, if you, if like separately
in another Disney park, there was a big castle cake,
I'd probably go, yeah.
But something about it replacing what is a classier,
more ornate affair, I think just bothered me.
And I was also trying to analyze like,
well, hey, but what is it?
There's gotta be some greater reason.
And I think it's this, and I'm curious your thoughts.
I think it's the pink.
I don't like the pink.
And I saw a lot of haters of it describing it as Pepto pink
because I think a lot of cast members started to not like it
and they encountered a lot of guests who were disappointed
they weren't seeing the regular castle.
And I think in that Pepto pink comment,
I think that conveys a lot to me
because Pepto is a gross kind of pink.
I think if it had been a more subtle pink
or perhaps even a white,
because who's eating a big pink cake?
I would love to eat a big pink cake.
That's the problem here is that I see,
is there an anti-pink in general bias?
Is there some sort of sexism going on here?
Because that pink is a very,
no, no.
I'm not saying you're being sexist.
I'm saying though people with the anti-pink,
I feel like pink actually might be the most divisive color
because it's so tied to maybe identity.
Feminine, there is a trivialization in popular culture
of like feminine interests, movies aimed at women.
That's where we are now.
Look, I didn't expect to be here either, but here we are.
But, and then I think you get into a semiotic argument
of the idea of cake.
How do you simply communicate the idea of cake?
There's a couple ways to do it.
White frosting, brown frosting for chocolate,
pure white would look like you get dirty immediately.
Brown would be hated by everyone.
But pink, like Looney Tunes, Mickey Mouse,
pink denotes cakes in those cartoons.
You know, there's a poet once wrote,
pink, it's my new obsession.
Pink, it's not even a question.
Yes, of course.
Pink, it's the color of passion.
Cause today it just goes with the fashion.
Yes, of course.
I think we have to consider that
with any semiotic argument.
It's a song that's still played in Disney World.
True.
It's outside of a ride in Disney World.
Do you know what we're talking about?
What song is, I can't.
Aerosmiths.
It's Aerosmiths Pink.
You see.
A song I wasn't listening to just a couple days ago.
As a noted fan of pink.
It's about a dirtier topic, Jason.
Obviously you know that.
But that's.
I know what it's about.
Yeah, really the cake should make me horny
cause pink is the color of passion.
Right.
I can't say I was horny for it.
Okay, you know, I think that cleanliness argument is good.
And the white just might kind of look like nothing.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think it could be a shade issue.
I am no opponent of pink in any way.
I wear a lot of pink clothing.
This is not the problem.
I think the shade.
When I said.
I have a problem with the shade.
I think it is a gaudy pink.
I wasn't accusing you of being an anti-pink person.
Sure.
I was just saying, I wonder in general.
Let me defend anybody who might have felt
victimized by that.
I would get made fun of.
I would get made fun of for in elementary school
saying my favorite color was purple.
Because people would say, oh purple is a girl's color.
So pink for sure was a girl's color.
So I do wonder.
I'm wondering if pink has a connotation.
I wonder now.
Because I feel like because of Brett the Hitman Heart
and other famous pink wearers.
If that's sort of now.
The history is that pink was gender defined
and then Brett the Hitman Heart changed it permanently.
That was his color.
I mean that was his.
That was black.
Pink and black.
Very cool look.
He looks cool.
Gender warrior, Brett the Hitman Heart.
I think you don't even point to a lot of things
that he helped to fix.
To tie it.
Steven Tyler.
To tie it back to the prequel talk.
I think one of the things you can say
about both of them.
Is that there is a clear vision.
There is a singular vision of the prequels.
Whether you like them or not.
There is a singular vision of the castle cake.
And it is presented boldly and confidently.
Bold and silly and visual.
And silly and visual.
I mean it does look like a cake that if there was a cartoon
where Mickey is a baker.
Like this might be a cake in the background.
Or one he makes and then big Pete.
Plops down on it or something.
You might say that the castle that you just showed
with the magic mirror and just the gold trim.
That that's more the equivalent of the new trilogy.
Where it's like slightly dressing up
what was there already.
That's fair.
But the prequels equaling the castle cake.
It's like well it's crazier and it might lose some of you.
It's got some new stuff.
You might not like it but it's certainly different.
I gotta say.
And the boldness of it.
I like that it being super bold
is something I can respect about it more now.
I can studiously appreciate today the castle cake.
And I'm glad we're talking about it.
But at my core and apparently my mom's core.
We just don't like it.
I can also respectively say I understand
why people don't like it.
And I understand why people were upset.
And I can see that.
But from my, my thing was I wasn't super heart broke.
Cause I knew the castle would be back.
And I also like we, I loved Main Street.
I loved all the vehicles.
I loved the vibe.
But we weren't a Cinderella's Royal Table family.
We didn't, I've never been up there.
I've never even.
Are you trying to talk about how you were working class?
Is that what you're?
No, no.
Just that like.
We never went.
We didn't get invited to the Royal Table.
No I just didn't care.
We weren't a Crystal Pallets.
The reputation of my family was that I love,
I liked the, the vibe of Main Street.
But Main Street had the worst restaurants.
Kind of true to this day I feel.
You liked it.
No longer the monarchy reigned for those 18 months.
Cake reigned.
Well everyone loves cake.
I mean that's true.
The social confines.
Yeah the cake was a democratization of Disney World.
Of the Magic Kingdom.
You know no longer did you see this oppressive castle
where you were ruled by these hopefully benevolent people
but probably oppressive leaders.
Definitely thought I had it at 11.
Yeah.
How does this tie into a leader famously flippantly saying
let them eat cake?
Hmm good question.
Maybe that's not, that's viewed now as like a fuck off.
Or that's what it was intended as.
But imagine, you know.
Cinderella saying oh let them eat cake.
Yeah actually sounds nice.
And one of the only good qualities you could ascribe
to our current leader Donald Trump
is his affinity for desserts.
Mm hmm good point.
So it is, there's a populism to cake.
Well he also, he will eat the cake that Marie Antoinette,
historically I believe people were like,
she was referring to cake the soot buildup in a fireplace.
That's what cake meant?
That's what like people have interpreted.
Yeah I like, so there's an interpretation of like
let them eat cake, fuck off.
I have got a, my mother has weighed in.
This is great, these live updates.
Yeah.
I didn't ask my dad, he's probably, he'll be upset
he wasn't asked but like he probably doesn't have an opinion.
My mother said so pretty exclamation point
but maybe not forever.
Yeah. Okay.
Fair.
This is a good centrist point.
But still she's, that's a pretty big endorsement
of the look of it.
This is pretty limited time magic.
Before that was shoved down all our throats.
That's a good question, I don't think they did.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh that is a marketing term that they overuse now.
And like, oh everyone, limited time magic,
the Main Street Electrical Parade is back.
It's like, oh is it six months from when it last left?
Like they just keep doing this stuff.
Right, right.
Can I throw this opinion out there?
And I'm not even saying it's my opinion exactly
but if I could get in the heads of the,
I was not a person who was upset.
I didn't, well I didn't go.
I don't think I would have cared.
I didn't get to see the castle.
But people did feel that way.
I read the, there were brides who were livid
because they found out they wouldn't have photos
with the fairy tale castle.
I get that.
Sure you imagine the specific photo op.
That seems to be the verdict that they lost a ton of money
because the wedding pavilion looks,
has a direct view of the castle.
Oh sure, sure, sure.
Well and also, okay so I have recently
encountered this opinion that is not my opinion
and it's a surprising opinion to me
that people do not like the Nightmare Before Christmas
haunted mansion overlay because you're going on Halloween
and you wanna see the real scary haunted mansion.
Is it possible that this was an opinion
for the 25th anniversary?
You wanna see the real castle and not this,
not this alterna version?
Now that, there's one step of it.
If I could just do one more, people another complaint,
a sub opinion of Nightmare Before Christmas is I like it
but it goes too long.
Right, yes.
I think 18 months was a long time to have a castle cake.
I think if that had been up for like just the year
or just for seven months, I think the amount of time
like Nightmare Before Christmas is some of the complaint.
Perhaps.
Yeah I wonder, I think, I would think
that could be part of it.
I think the majority is probably just didn't like,
my mom, okay my mom, sorry to distract,
my mom has added another interesting thing
that I think is maybe part of why I like it.
She said, you know, maybe not forever
but she said unless they did a second one elsewhere
in the park which means she would like this somewhere else
but then she just wrote Candyland exclamation point.
And that is a very good point.
And it's a very good point because I loved Candyland.
I loved Candyland too.
I was obsessed with it and really looks like something
straight out of Candyland.
If there were some physical Candyland place
that you could hang out and like go,
who are the scary guys like the molasses guys or whatever?
I almost wanna hang out there the most.
Well this is funny because we were talking,
I feel like we have an inside joke
about one of the Candyland characters with you.
What?
With the fudge monster I think.
That I am him?
I think that maybe you're just friends with him.
When there's an inevitable Candyland film,
I think the goal needs to be to popularize Jason
via this podcast to like get you like a scene stealing part
on a show because of this podcast
and then that gives you the one up to be in the,
be a voice or a mocap guy in the Candyland film.
I would love that.
Plumpy, I think it was plumpy.
He's like a plump.
Plumpy plum?
He's not plumb though.
He's like, he's hold on, let me find out where plumpy.
So I remember now it's because it's between you, me
and Marissa Strickland, past guest
and we would call Marissa Strickland grandma nut.
Grandma nut, yeah.
And then I think we called it,
we were talking about you and plumpy.
Yeah, it's all 100% possible.
Oh yeah, I see it.
He's a little like green.
The purple man?
He's a gingerbread plump, he's cute.
He's not the fudge monster.
No.
He's a green guy with like,
he looks kind of like a friendly grouch.
Yeah.
And he's got a big medallion around his neck
that looks like a plum and he's eating a plum.
I've seen a lot of different pictures.
I love, this is a similar thing to
when I was watching Alice in Wonderland
and I was like, oh, I love Alice in Wonderland.
I'm looking at Candyland and I'm like, I love Candyland.
I love Candyland.
I think I'm with you.
I would love to star in the Candyland movie
and then fix the script like Ed Norton would
every night on the Incredible Hulk movie
and I would go home and like, I'm fixing a piece of trash.
Marissa would be an excellent grandma nut.
I'm scanning through photos.
You'd be a great plumpy,
but I'd also like to not deny you the opportunity to be,
wait, I lost him, King Candy.
I think you'd be a great King Candy as well.
And Gloppy is the monster.
Gloppy?
Is the fudge monster.
I think you'd be a great Jolly.
You could be, you like, this could be your,
the Jim Carrey Christmas Carol.
Oh, this is good.
You play three of the parts.
Mike, I think as a taller fellow
who could play a more gangly character,
I think you could be a great Lord Licorice
or who's Mr. Mint.
Mr. Mint is super pink and peppermint,
so you might prefer to play Mr. Mint.
And he gets to, he's, what I'm looking at,
he's carrying a big peppermint ax,
which is pretty rad.
That's cool, yeah.
I mean, I'd take that too,
if you wanted to give in to your evil side
and be Lord Licorice.
I don't know if that leaves me to be Gloppy.
I don't feel a strong personal connection
to any of the characters.
My mom and sister want me to ask my,
my sister wants me to ask my dad now.
I hadn't asked him, but I'm now asking my father.
Throw it out.
Yes.
Dear dad, I know we haven't talked in seven years, but.
You're his father.
While we're waiting on a response, so.
My sister, my sister thing has a theory,
and this is a relation to the hosts of the show.
My sister thinks that Scott doesn't like treats
like the Carlson's and Sheridan's do.
This is absolutely correct.
And it goes with my alcohol taste.
I don't understand what you drink.
I don't understand these multicolor,
the five colors in the beverage.
Right.
I think that that aligns with it.
I think it's just not, I liked dessert and I ate dessert,
but I don't think I was like,
I don't think I hung on to the affinity.
And I don't eat a lot of dessert now.
And I ended up getting desserts for Christmas and Easter.
And then they just like pile up and Erin,
my wife has to come like nerve sheepishly say like,
can I have your candy, please?
Like I don't go through my candy at home enough.
I try not to keep desserts candy in the house,
but if I'm out, I get a little something.
And I do like something that feels fantastical.
That does feel like it would have been given to me
by Plumpy or Loppy or Mr. Mint, you know?
Maybe not Mr. Mint, I don't like mint as much.
I think I also eat much like saltier bullshit.
Like where I indulge is alcohol
and it's like fries and tortilla chips.
And I know my like bad health is gonna go to that.
So I cut off dessert a little more
just to make room for the other.
Prince, I wish that I would have married Princess Lolly
as a child.
I'd be a different guy.
I'd be Freddy fries.
Well, you would be in what's the candy.
Yeah, I guess it's more McDonald land.
Oh yeah, it'd be a fry gun.
Yeah.
I go crazy if I don't have sweets in the house.
I'm sorry to say, I don't have much of a taste for salt.
And I feel like my grandfather at some point
had to cut salt out of his diet,
which then my mother before she lived on her own
was still living at home.
She was the youngest.
And so she kind of like,
I don't know if they ever were a big salt family either.
And my father was never big on salt.
So we were not a salt household.
So I hit something recently with sea salt.
Oh, that's what it was.
I'm not a big, I like sweet salt a little,
but I had like these caramel cookies
that had sea salt on top.
And I'm like, I fucking hate this.
Like, can I take these back?
This is fucking, this is a disaster.
You wouldn't do that.
Sea salt on dessert doesn't square with you.
No, I'm okay with sea salt caramel when it's real.
Like when it's real caramel,
but when it's like, you can tell the fakeness of it.
It's like, ah, this sucks.
I hate this.
But like, I at least need,
I try not to have cookies, chocolate,
and ice cream in the house,
but I feel good when I do with three.
And I don't really, I don't drink a lot anymore.
I really don't drink a lot anymore.
So I don't, I mean, that's my vice.
And I try to drink a lot of water to balance out anything.
I have like white claws in the fridge,
but I don't think I have any, there's no ice cream here.
There's no sugar of any kind.
Any bagged candy in the house currently.
No bagged candy in the house.
I need something either like small cookies
to just graze on like in between meals
or like chocolate almonds.
How many days have you,
do you think you've gone without that in the house?
A couple.
Two?
Well, but then the problem is,
is that I don't keep it in the house.
Then I spend money at like, you know,
Carl's Jr. milkshakes are really good,
but that's like $4 or like,
I spend it, I waste money on shorter term options.
I feel like-
Does that make sense?
I'm not, I'm goofing around a little bit,
but I do, there's a, there is food and compulsion
is absolutely obviously a real thing.
I feel like my thing with when I'm feeling compulsive
is I want like a big iced tea.
And then I started drinking a lot more diet soda recently,
which I need to stop-
Yeah, you gotta stop.
Because I think it's creating my stomach up.
But I feel a compulsion,
when I feel like that compulsion,
oftentimes I will drive to McDonald's
and get a dollar large unsweetened iced tea.
Because I just need to be doing something.
No, I know it's totally fine.
I'm just saying, I'm wrecking that-
Good price on that too.
I switched over from Starbucks.
I was wasting a lot of Starbucks money.
Yeah, you got it.
Yeah, that's really easy.
The McDonald's thing also-
I mean, you should cold brew at home.
You should cold brew pitchers at home.
Yeah, I could do that.
There's a Del Taco also dollar large iced tea as well.
Yeah, that's good.
Or you can get like a 30 ounce, not 30 ounce,
it's slightly smaller.
It's a strawberry lemonade, but it's not that caloric.
It's a little smaller though.
But if you need a little some sweet in there.
Sure, sure, sure.
Sometimes I've gotten both
and I put a little inside of the iced tea.
Oh, that's smart.
I don't get sugar from drinks.
I rarely drink like full fat soda.
Really drink, I don't drink sweet stuff a lot
because I had to, I cut soda one summer in high school
and I immediately dropped weight.
Yeah, I like that.
I switched to bottle water,
which I try not to go too hard on nowadays.
I try to use a refillable bottle.
But yeah, once I-
That's the kind of shit that drives me crazy
with alcohol, like margarita mix, get out of here.
I want like a squeeze a line,
like as little shit in there.
Fresh lime, I love.
Yeah, I try not to.
No slush, I want no slush.
No, I, yeah, even like,
I'm sure some people will think this is heresy,
but like I like bottled beer
because I've had so many bad draft pulls.
Really?
Well, I just, if it's like a dive bar or a questionable place,
it's like, I know the bottle beer will be reliable.
Oh yeah, yeah, not tampered with.
Yeah.
I'd like to propose that you would also be a great
mocap cookie crisp dog.
Oh my God, of course.
I would love the dog or the burglar.
You don't see the burglar much anymore.
I would love it.
My friends, I love those commercials, my friends.
My friends.
Cookie crisp dog, yeah, with the-
We get cookie crisps in the house sometimes.
To stay a little bit on topic, one thing I will say,
and I'll just throw this out there
and I bet I'll get agreement, but who knows?
I think there's no question that of temporary
anniversary celebration amending of Disney World landmarks,
this is vastly superior to the giant hat
in front of the Chinese theater at Disney Studios
and the big wand next to the Epcot ball.
I think you got no proponents of either of those things.
Of course, no, there's-
Uh oh, uh oh.
I mean, the hat I like, okay.
So my dad was like, I liked all the anniversary stuff,
but I think we were in agreement
that those stuck around way too long.
Yeah, the hat was way too long.
Was way too long.
Maybe for a second, but I think,
but also, and again, put the hat in there,
but why is it blocking the thing that you wanna say?
Well, that's because they lost rights to display.
It is like the icon of the park.
It was there like six years ago.
It was like-
You saw the merchandise go from the Grailmans
to the Earful Tower.
The Earful to the Water Tower is still there.
The place had to switch what the landmark was.
Epcot wand, get out of here.
Did that ruin the policy-
Ruins the funliness of the orb.
Where was that different?
The wand-
It's in 2000 for a little bit.
Did it say 2001?
Did they keep changing it?
They did keep changing it,
and then it just became Epcot in the ugliest font,
in which an ugly font in Epcot,
that is my worst nightmare.
Yeah, get out of here.
Oh yeah.
Fonts are the main appeal of Epcot to this day.
Why did-
It's a harsh script.
Plush it down the toilet.
Why didn't they turn them all into sort of sweets?
Absolutely.
They should have all been.
We've talked about this to some extent,
but why don't we,
let's go with just Spaceship Earth and Shaney's Theater.
How do you sweetify them?
Yeah, that's a good question.
I mean, a circular,
I mean, now I would say,
could you make it a circular ball of ice,
like in the Carthay Manhattan?
But that would be a little hard to smooth it out.
It looks like nothing.
Yeah.
Chocolate orb, like molten chocolate orb,
but I don't think those were really in fashion at the time.
And if you just painted it,
of just an even color,
but then doesn't that just look like-
Big pink, yeah.
It just looks,
that looks like the mission space,
like a planet or something.
Yes.
I guess you could,
I mean, I'm sure there's a way to fill in and smooth it out.
I mean, it would take a while,
but you know,
they changed some of the textures on the castle.
If you keep the textures of Spaceship Earth,
it tastes like a burnt peanut.
You know, those red, sugary,
very acquired taste.
And I think it would be lost on a lot of people,
like why does Spaceship Earth look mad?
It's like a burnt peanut?
It's like a burnt peanut.
That might not be the most fun.
I don't know what you're talking about either.
It's those red, like spiky,
like bulk candy.
They're peanuts that are covered in like,
just like a sugary shell.
You could just do like a Tuft of whipped cream on top
and a cherry,
and it's just is the Epcot ball,
but somebody put whipped cream.
Oh, like a scoop of ice cream.
Oh, that's what it is.
You add a second scoop
and then like add a little plastic-y,
like the little runoff.
Or it's an upside down,
it's like a cookie puss.
It's an upside, you put a cone on top.
It's a clown cone.
Oh, it's a great, great.
Is that wrong about what cookie puss is?
Yeah, that's the Carvel cake with,
it's a different,
Blaskin-Robbins has the clown cone,
which again is another thing I was obsessed with
as a child and still mildly might be to this day.
You've brought those two events
and everyone's like, oh.
Yeah, everyone loves them.
It's a crowd pleaser.
Yes.
Chinese theater, what do you do?
Yeah, I mean, I think it's probably similar
to what they did with Cake Castle.
Yeah, I think so.
It's a building, so it's like,
we're turning it into like a gingerbread house.
That's kinda nice. Kind of a thing.
Yes, sure.
Do you keep it Chinese
and it's a bunch of,
it's made out of fortune cookies?
Seems to.
I don't think it would look like anything.
Yeah, I think it has to.
Now, a fortune cookie giveaway
in front of the Chinese theater
would have been a good idea.
Well, that is a good question.
My mom is throwing many ideas out now
that we've opened this up.
She said if they made a candy land with this castle,
they could sell smaller edible replicas,
which I think is good.
Did they have anything,
because now it would make a lot of sense
that they would be selling cake
that looked like the castle.
That is so easy Instagram bait.
Right, but I don't think they were doing it back then.
I don't think so.
I mean, they had merchandise.
Yeah.
Structurally very difficult cake.
We were talking about it being a practical dessert
and you saying a team would need to move it.
I mean, not the full,
but they would be selling little pieces.
It's an easy cookie.
A cook or a cupcake too, honestly,
because you could do it
one of the different spire type things.
But if you flatten it to two dimensions,
that's an easy shape of cookie and draw on it.
But even you could present it like,
oh, we cut pieces out
and it's like this is just a little piece of the castle.
It doesn't have to necessarily replicate the look of it.
Let me bring up a weakness to it as well.
I didn't realize how this is from a TPM vids on YouTube.
I had a rare shot of the back of the castle.
This is shit.
They didn't paint all of it.
It was like a facade.
So some of it stayed gray.
This is a big old weakness I gotta say.
I can't really hold that against it
because it's mainly about that front view,
but truly they should be ashamed
of how bad it looked from the back.
I think it was also very bizarre
to watch this thing get built
because as Jason was saying, this is pre-internet
and the castle was just being painted pink
and nobody knew why.
Now you'd know two years in advance they were gonna do this.
But truly they didn't want to say what it was gonna be
and they'd even tell guests maybe Barbie is moving it.
They'd make up some dumb story.
So I think it was very awkward for a while
when the castle was partially pink,
but like halfway.
Again, that's what they had to do to prep the thing.
Some of people's bad memories might be watching it rise
and going, what is this?
This looks weird.
But if you just saw the completed vision,
much more appealing.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I wonder how long, I'm seeing a picture of it
just sort of pink here.
And I think that might be, unless it's Photoshopped.
It looks, I mean, it looks strange.
Let me also throw out, I didn't realize
that there was a precedent for the Castle Cake
that for the one year anniversary of then Euro Disney,
they did sort of a sweetified version of the castle.
Which is a little bit, I do,
I don't think this is better than the Castle Cake.
We'll post a picture of this.
But I think it's a little more stately in the colors.
I think this is getting away from the Pepto pink.
Hey, you know what?
The Europe Castle always pink.
And I think a good shade of pink.
I think I don't like that shade of pink.
I also like that it's a bunch of big giant strawberries
at the base.
This looks like a good cake.
That, yeah, that looks, I like that.
It looks like the frosting is still inflatable.
Mm-hmm.
It's a little more minimal.
Yeah, it's more minimal.
It's a subtler Castle Cake. I do like that.
Did you guys see at the,
when you walked into the Magic Kingdom,
there were 25 candles.
In front of the train station?
At the train station.
They just looked like big candles.
Yeah, those weren't really anything.
That didn't really.
Yeah, why do that?
Yeah. That doesn't, yeah.
Not a fan of that.
So I think maybe this, I truly think if you,
I think I have an aesthetic problem.
I think you toned down that pink
and I'm more on board with it.
And I do like in the Europe one, the smaller whipped cream.
It was a little less silly of Tufts,
but maybe that wouldn't be.
Maybe you want it to be big and bold and silly.
Yeah.
It is, I mean, it's certainly gaudy,
but it's a gaudy in the way that I like.
That's the thing.
So I guess it is just a design.
I mean, I get that it's so different.
Like the castle itself is not,
the Cinderella's Castle is very grand and pristine.
I don't know what the other word I'm looking for
is prestigious or awe.
It's got the size, it's got the awe.
I think it's so changed the character.
Of what that castle was like,
which makes it, it really sticks out like a sore thumb
at the end of Main Street, which with the vibe as it.
I think what's good about the Europe one,
which I don't think is bad, I'm not saying,
this feels like a snooty opinion to say that,
oh, the European one was better,
but it's like more in the character
of how the castle always is.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess it does.
If you look at the, I'm looking at the picture.
Yeah, it does look like, it's like,
I guess it contains, it gets the character
a little bit more of the castle
as opposed to the Cinderella one
that does really completely look like almost a new structure.
And you can see, obviously it's the same,
but it looks, they've changed so much of it.
It looks like a totally different thing.
I should just try to, I should just pull this into Photoshop
and de-saturate the color and see how I feel.
Maybe I can post my idea, like here's what I did.
I just like, side of things are at 10%
and this is how I, this is important revisionist work.
Very important.
What was the Euro castle, the beta test for Magic Kingdom?
Like did they know they wanted to do something like this?
Did they know they wanted to do it?
Potentially.
Yeah, I mean, for Euro Disney,
didn't matter if people hated it.
It's one year old, everyone hated it anyway.
They hated everything.
Yeah.
Think about it, yes, absolutely.
I guess it's, we're on a little long time,
but the, we should, we need to talk about the fact
that on this day, like we're one day behind.
October 1st, 1996, this was the 25th anniversary
and there was a huge event that part of which
was the unveiling of the castle cake.
And as part of this, a big celebration,
big children's choir saying Michael Eisner spoke, of course.
Of course.
But mainly an address, the castle cake,
there was a speech given in front of the castle cake
by Hillary Rodham Clinton.
Wow.
She addressed the nation before the castle cake.
I did some cross checking to see what was Bill doing then.
And I was really hoping that literally one of the
Clinton Lewinsky affair dates happened
on the day of the speech, but not sure.
It was actually in the biggest,
that was the biggest window of them not really
seeing each other.
Literally, Hillary is speaking in front of the castle cake
and Bill is at the White House with Netanyahu and Arafat.
Holy shack.
Yeah, yeah, pretty crazy.
Do you think like if Bill had seen this,
he would have asked them to do the same thing
to the White House?
Ha!
Turn the White House into a cake.
I can't eat it anymore, but I'd love to look at it.
Michelle Obama wouldn't have put up with that shit.
No, that's true, but then Trump would have put it back in.
Bigger, gaudier cake.
Again, my Trump hatred goes down by a significant degree
if every year he, for some thing, there was a...
He turns the White House into a cake.
Yeah, I was almost gonna call it a castle cake.
But a Mar-a-Lago.
If he turned the White House into a castle cake.
Mar-a-Lago cake as well?
I think it's not defined and I don't know,
I don't have a vision of what Mar-a-Lago looks like.
I know they have very good cake.
We're certainly aware of that.
I imagine they do, yeah.
Oh, but a dessert White House.
Yeah, hell yeah.
Dessert White House, please.
Some very talented person that's listening to this
is going to draw that, I assume.
Oh yes, absolutely.
Dessert White House.
I also, just to put things in the timeline,
October 1st, she's in front of the castle cake.
Clinton's meeting with Netanyahu and Arafat.
The end of that week, that very same week, October 7th,
Clinton beats Dole in the first presidential debate
of that season and that day, I couldn't believe this,
that same day, the launch of the Fox News channel.
Wow.
This really puts things in bed
and it cut to what they're doing about Hillary.
Who knew that they would entirely be about Hillary 24-7
still in 2019.
Little, did you know you were setting me up
for all of my shit about this day?
Yes.
So did you get this picture?
Did you see this picture?
Not specifically.
So this is a picture, it's for sale.
Like it's a news archive print.
It's got stuff on the back, like Kodak logos.
It's got the like, excuse me, the poll.
Ears to you, it says.
So in this picture from the event,
Mickey Mouse, Roy E. Disney, son of Roy O. Disney,
Michael Eisner, Hillary Clinton,
and then Florida governor Lawton Chiles,
walking Lawton Chiles.
They called him.
So this was my, I texted, I asked you guys the other day,
did you, did anyone come across Lawton Chiles?
Cause I'm like, oh, who is this ghoul?
He's gotta be a ghoul.
He was actually pretty, pretty kind of like,
he was, he was democratic governor of Florida.
Doesn't mean anything.
Which doesn't mean anything.
Seemed to mostly start, it's a lot of headstart,
like children's health programs and stuff.
Was a reformer when it came to healthcare and education.
I am not smart enough to look at this stuff
and see if that means actual reform
or like privatization, ghoul reform.
Got the name walking Lawton Chiles
when he ran for United States Senate
and walked 1,003 miles from Pensacola to Key West.
He earned that nickname.
And it sort of earned like that gave him the image
of like a folksy Southern man.
Forrest Gump.
Very, very Gump.
So, unfortunately, walking Lawton Chiles,
the reverberations, he died.
Not long after this, right?
Not long after this.
Walking Lawton Chiles is, I think we can safely say,
a man who helped the start of breaking the world
because he appointed multiple judges
who ruled in the Bush v. Gore decision.
He appointed multiple Florida Supreme Court judges.
Ruling in the majority instead,
Perriente, Lewis, and Judge Quince,
who was jointly appointed with George Bush.
There was an agreement.
They had to do a press conference
because there was an opening
and it would have looked bad as Lawton was leaving office
if he appointed this judge last minute.
Now, who gives a shit?
We don't have that sort of matters now.
So, Heeman Bush jointly agreed to appoint this judge.
Do you mean Jeb Bush?
Because Jeb was-
Jeb Bush, yes.
Did Jeb take over from this guy?
Lawton beat him once for governor.
But then as Lawton was leaving, Jeb was coming in.
Descending, Judges Wells and Harding
were appointed by Lawton.
And then Judge Shaw was appointed by Bob Graham.
I'm trying to picture all of these justices
as cake candles either lit or not.
That's a chart I need to see in my head
to tell who's on what side.
So, even though he was a Democrat,
he's four judges or three judges he appointed,
one judge he co-appointed ruled in favor of Bush.
And so that kind of started the downhill trend of that.
They judges also ruled on the Terry, was it Skyvo?
Shyvo.
Oh, right.
Case-
So much was happening in Florida.
They did strike down.
There was a bunch of nuts who were trying to get
pro-life license plate.
That's a common, this happened in multiple states.
People get enough signatures to like,
well, you'll be able to get a pro-life license plate
usually struck down as an inappropriate place
for politicking.
Okay, okay.
So-
So of the people standing in front of the castle cake.
Standing in front of the castle cake.
One of them installed a bunch of the people
who made Bush win through weird, incorrect,
the first popular electoral votes, NAFU.
The second person, obviously, obviously,
the primary person, the biggest victim
of the electoral popular vote.
Michael Eisner getting screwed out of office
by Al Lutz and his string pullers.
I mean, I'm more torn up about that one
than Hillary, for sure.
Roy E. Disney too, I was trying to figure out like,
wait, so what is the Disney family tree looks like?
Roy Disney is the father of Abigail Disney,
the rabble rouser.
Who's, oh yeah, who's like against their labor practices now
and who like says her father was a piece of shit.
Like a abuser.
He has inferred that her father
was not the nicest man always.
I believe that.
This made me think, for all you succession heads out there,
is Abigail the Shiv?
Pfft.
Comment on this video and let us know
if you think Abigail's the Shiv.
Jason got real sassy.
Or is she the Kendall?
You got real sassy all of a sudden.
But I don't think she's in the running
to take over or anything.
No, she's not.
But well, within the Roy side of the family,
I mean, there's so much money in the family.
Down in the low, is Abigail the Shiv?
He's the guy who made the caveman movie?
Is he the Romula?
Is he the Roman?
I mean, where does Minnie Mouse fall into all this?
Yeah, where does Minnie Mouse fall in?
Is she Rhea?
Is she the devious Rhea?
So these are, this photo in front
of the unveiling of the castle cake,
these are truly the horsemen of the epagulate.
Literally two gigantic figures
in the two biggest electoral disasters in American history.
This is an ominous, an unknowingly ominous photo
that you can own a real high quality print of for $8.
And I'll try to find that link.
Where can you get that?
This is for sale.
This photo print is for sale.
I feel like there's only one of them.
We should get it, right?
Yeah, boy.
How big can we get it?
No, it's a physical item.
Oh, it's not a print, it's an ice ice ice.
It's like it was a news archive photo.
So we'll have to take that and then take it
somewhere else to blow it up.
Yeah, we probably get it scanned and blown up.
I'd like a 72 inch TV size of it.
Do you think that Hillary said,
all right, so I'm heading down to Florida.
Do you think Bill was like,
oh, you should take my friend Jeffrey's plane.
He's heading down there.
He's making a quick start doing a couple of pickups.
I think.
Hey, and.
Drop you off.
He probably.
In 20 years, make sure to campaign down there a bunch.
Down there and like up north,
a little don't forget, don't forget.
I'm telling you this now.
I was gonna say both of those things happened.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
She'll also be noted that she failed
in her Disney World visit to reach out to the,
to the Rust Belt of Mickey's Toontown Fair.
Mickey's birthday.
Mickey's birthday land, Scott.
No, not then, no, no, no.
Was it Toontown Fair then?
Was it Toontown by 1996?
It was at least by then,
it had been Starland for a little while.
So what you're saying is grandma's petting zoo
had already been gentrified.
Had already been bulldozed and gentrified.
I'm curious about that.
When it was Toontown Fair,
that's not worth waiting on.
No.
I don't know, maybe it is.
So the castle cake.
We haven't reviewed the cake itself yet.
We haven't?
No, we haven't talked about actually the ingredients
and if that would be good on an actual cake.
That's what I wanna do.
Well, I think it's like these crazy milkshakes.
Like you get a black tab.
It became Mickey's Toontown Fair on that very same day.
Really?
Wow, geez.
Big day.
That was convenient though.
No, I barely squeaked in there.
But no way was it birthday land.
Get out of here.
Get out of your mind.
I will say, I wanted to say like so,
lifesavers shouldn't be on the cake.
Oh, you're saying if we're gonna eat the cake.
I'm saying yes.
That's what I think the final thing should be
unless you have more stuff is we should assess the cake.
It's like crazy shakes.
My father has not texted back to if he likes.
Deconstruct it before you start digging into it.
I feel like a lot of this.
Right, I'm just saying it should have been something else.
It should have been like,
those should have been Froot Loops or something.
Cause that really would go well with the cake.
That would be good.
Cause lifesavers honestly, I don't love them.
I never bought by them.
I would have one if someone offered, but I don't.
It's just not the same.
You couldn't take a bite and then like chomp.
You'd have to remove those.
Yes, Froot Loops, perfect in my mind.
Very good.
If you take those and make those Froot Loops
or make them, you know, generic.
Is the pink icing strawberry flavored
or is it just colored?
Is it buttercream that's colored?
I think honestly, a strawberry icing
might be a little overwhelming.
So I think it's just food coloring in my mind.
You think it's just food coloring.
Is the inflatable white icing,
that's gotta be like a buttercream, right?
Yeah, I think that's right.
But I like a buttercream.
Yeah, I love that.
And then the blue is probably the same flavor,
but it would be cool if it's a little bit, you know,
tinged with a blueberry or something,
but probably the same buttercream.
That would be the thing.
The red and white, are those like peppermint sticks?
Or are they, is that?
That's what it looks like.
Yeah, but also weird.
I agree with that.
I think that even though you're right,
Crazy Shakes do put stuff in there.
I still think that's like,
if you got a piece with the peppermint sticks,
it's like, now I gotta eat a peppermint stick with this.
But that's the most manageable.
You had one of the Crazy Shakes.
I know, and it had like a-
Let's save it, but it had a wrapper.
It had candy still in it.
Yeah, which I did not like.
I did not like there was a wrapped piece of candy in there.
I thought that there, that was a little too much.
Just like when you get a straw
and just a little bit of the papers on top.
I'm okay with that, but you gotta rip a lot.
I don't like a hard anything involved in the cake,
cause cake is all soft.
I don't wanna actually have to be dealing with something
that I'm gonna have to suck.
I mean, I, there's no other way to say it.
I know you guys couldn't, you could have kept talking.
So it didn't sound like I'm a pervert or something.
It blew me back.
I had nothing to say after that.
Like that's what you go,
you have to suck on a thing like that during a cake.
It's not, it's different.
It's two different types of eating.
There's something in the air recently with this podcast.
It's been a little profane.
It's been a little bawdy.
I could have said, oh, I don't wanna lick something.
That would have been just as bad.
The lusty month of October is almost a-
Suck is weird.
Suck is definitely weird.
I guess, but that's what you're gonna have to do
with a candy cane.
You suck on a candy cane.
But aren't, there's a lot of acts
that are like multiple,
it is about balancing several types of-
Is there a thing I could have said
about what you do to a candy cane
that wouldn't have sounded sexual?
Naw.
Naw on a candy cane.
You're a thousand percent right.
That is in no way a sexual word.
You have to be demented to use naw in a sexual setting.
Can't wait to gnaw on your ear, darling.
When are you gonna-
Rawr, rawr, rawr.
Like, I feel like, I feel like naw,
you have to, naw is guaranteed to involve the sound.
Rawr, rawr, rawr.
When are you gonna gnaw me out?
When this business-
Oh, oh, second gate.
When this business trip is over,
I assure you, I'm not gonna-
I'm not gonna-
This business trip-
You're right, something's been in the air.
When I get my co-
When this business trip is over,
I love this synapse.
You're describing tension between partners
on a business trip.
No, I think he's talking to his wife.
And then it ends with the biggest naw out.
I think just he's talking to his wife.
That's when I come home.
Yeah, yeah, when I get home, the gnawing.
I thought it was sexual tension between two people
doing presentations across the country,
and then by the end of the trip,
the sexual tension just builds to an apex,
and then they get, and then just major gnawing.
Big time gnawing.
It's complicated with coworkers,
but if everyone's single and ready to mingle, you know.
It's those hotel travel, hotel life can get lonely.
But sexual harassment synonyms, I have to say,
but just because, talking to an employee at work,
a fellow employee at work does not mean that you,
that they are interested in being gnawed.
Not me.
I mean, I need one more num num num.
That was the craziest-
Arrgh!
Like a dog.
That delights me.
Like I got, I got started,
I was walking through my neighborhood the other day,
and like a Scottish terrier had gotten out,
like Ed was just like by my feet,
going like, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr,
like trying, I'm like, okay, man,
like I can tell that it's like a dog whose bark is worth,
it's not its bite.
And then they were rad, I was like,
sorry, sorry, it's being a real turd today.
And just can't say, like,
it's being a pain in the ass to get back inside.
It's like, why are you being such a turd?
But the sound he was making was,
rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr,
He wasn't gnawing at anything though.
No, but I was wearing flip flops,
and I'm like, I see a little, but please don't,
come on, man, like I was just,
I wasn't scared, I was just annoyed, like-
Edwin gnaw on Jason's feet.
If Edwin made that perfect exact sound.
Rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr, rarrr,
I'd be so impressed.
He yawns, the noises he makes are barks and yawns.
I mean, security did politely have to ask 11-year-old me.
It's like, sir, please, the cake,
it's still the castle, please stop going for the,
going for, you're gonna crack a tooth trying to do that
on a lifesaver, on a five-foot-tall life-saver.
11-year-old. Fiberglass life-saver.
Jumping up on the, you climbed it, you scaled the tower.
Yeah.
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
It is surprising to me that Disney does not sell,
like, the traditional princess cake more,
that that's not pushed as like,
a dessert at the- I love a princess cake.
Cafeteria, yeah.
Raspberry filling, green, ice,
I don't think you'd have the inner pinks on purple.
They make it on great British pink.
I don't think you'd have the confidence to say that
if it were not for Brett the Hitman heart.
Well, that's true.
He led the way.
He's a pioneer.
I think, well, I think we're finding there is some oddity
with the cake itself.
Also, a bunch of lollipops on top, also weird.
Yeah, I don't like that as much.
It's a neat decoration, but you certainly couldn't.
The candles on top, I think, would be,
if it was a real cake, they're edible candles.
There's real candles at the base of it.
Yeah, there should be candles on the spires.
There should be candles.
I am, I'm okay though, if those are fun,
like, frosting candles.
That's fun to me.
The candles on the bottom should be
carelessly strewn about,
like someone had just picked them out,
because it was ready to slice.
So you think they'd just be lying on the ground,
burned out? That's my fuss up, yeah.
Looked like shit.
Yeah, they're burned out.
They're kind of laying on the side.
They still have a little icing on it on the bottom.
My plus up is, we were talking about how it was,
maybe just didn't kind of fit,
and people wanted, like, people thought that,
oh, it's such a contrast from the Main Street
and everything.
My plus up is make Main Street all Castle cake as well.
Wonderful.
That would help. Mini cake.
So all the whole thing, the whole stretch of it,
it looks just like this, with the same color.
If you, for the anniversary, invited the gang
from Candylands. Almost.
Nom nom nom. Nom nom nom.
What's the one?
It's a delivery, probably.
2020 is 60?
Yeah.
Usually we can ignore Edwin, but this one's a pretty.
As he's going nuts, I think it's because there's,
Edwin!
Yeah, someone's delivering something.
I want some Castle cake merch, at least.
Yeah. Yes.
I want some Castle cake merch for the anniversary.
At least, and a dessert,
a dessert that at least resembles a piece of it.
Should we try to make it?
Oh, that's interesting.
Yeah.
Seems like a disaster.
It might be a disaster.
I think I could do a cupcake of one of the Spires
pretty easily.
I may want to like store buy the cupcake
and then add to it, but.
Yeah.
We were by a pin trading thing,
and I feel like there was multiple power line pins.
Yeah.
Give me some Castle cake pins.
I think so.
Yeah.
Are you getting emotional?
No, I'm getting gassy.
I'm getting gassy.
Which means, yes, that's my emotion.
Give me some Castle.
That's how you vent your feelings.
I'm upset.
Pretty perfect episode for us.
We hate left and right politics talk.
Some, it got a little weird and sexual,
and mainly it was a ton of dessert.
A lot of dessert.
It was an excellent recipe for a Castle cake
and when my dad finally responds,
we'll post it on the Twitter.
The beginning of the end of the 20th century
and maybe the beginning of the end of the modern world.
This kickoff, this cake.
I was also thinking that's Hillary speaking
mere steps away from where she was nearly installed
as a robot forever.
That's a good point.
Instead.
What could have been?
Well, what a time.
All of history flushed down the toilet
along with the Castle cake.
If you have a piece of it, send it to me.
Oh, you're right.
Where did it all go?
Yeah, somebody's gotta have the lifesaver.
Like a piece of the life of something.
The theme park connection must have gotten this.
Must have gotten chunks of this.
Oh man, that'd be incredible.
Do the PS members probably work?
Does Richard Kraft have any of this
somewhere in his house?
That's me you'd have to throw down.
I've had an auction for.
Yeah.
I got one cake topper lollipop.
And you hug it, you sleep with it.
What would you.
Cradle it into bed every night.
What would you want?
If you could pick a piece off of it.
That's a good point.
What would you want?
Jason?
I don't know.
I mean, probably a big pink chunk.
Where if like I could somehow.
A lot of the pink is just the castle itself.
So I don't think that's able to be.
The inflatable icing, if I could somehow repurpose that
into what do you do with that?
A tarp or patio furniture?
It needs to be like the frosting candle.
I think it would have to be something like that.
One of the sprinkles from the 25.
Like if I would just have that propped up in a corner.
Yeah, that's good.
Yes, and that's doable.
You could keep that in a home and it's not.
Or there's an icing flower underneath it.
Yeah, I see that.
I'm thinking about that.
I'm remembering now, my sister had all these food toys.
You have like a fridge and the fake food.
She had a cake toy that was plastic.
It was just a piece of like circular plastic.
And then you would put the different types of frosting
and decorate it.
And we were obsessed with it.
Like there was different pieces of plastic frosting
that you would put together
and you would make different cakes.
And it was probably a Fisher Price thing.
Yeah, we had the Fisher Price kitchen.
The little kitchen in the corner of the playroom.
And like that all plays into it.
All of this cake fantasy.
And at one point in time, it was real.
Yeah.
Before the downfall, things were good
on October 1st, 1996.
Maybe that's the last time they were good.
You know, Joe Biden is just trying to get us back
to the time of the cake capsule.
No.
That's what he's doing.
We're gonna have to register with the FCC
if you keep that up.
Common sense.
Me and Corn Pop sliding down the candles.
Corn Pop and the castle cake.
Mm-hmm.
I was there.
I was handing out slices, you remember.
You shouldn't have been goofing around with candles,
but I shouldn't have called you the cake boss, okay?
I apologize.
I apologize to you, Corn Pop.
Soon as you elect me
and then you turn on your phonograph player
and you'll hear me saying
that we're bringing the castle cakes back everywhere.
You're walking up to the castle.
Thank you so much for admiring me.
I was at the castle cake
the day Martin Luther King was shot.
So elect me, God bless America.
And then his teeth fall to the ground and shatter.
Remember the magic.
Time to remember the magic.
I have material about that,
but we don't have time separately to remember the magic.
So I'll press pause on that.
Yeah, pause that.
You survived podcast the ride, the second gate.
Hey, keep following this Patreon
for three bonus episodes every month.
We got merch available at T-Public
and I feel like we gotta think about
something castle cake related.
Sure, hey, get some of those designs on pink shirts.
I bet they look nice.
That is a good, yeah, maybe we'd narrow it
for the only make pink available.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, the Pepto-iest pink you can find.
Sure.
And for more podcasts, right,
follow us on Twitter, Instagram,
and Facebook, tickets still available
to see us in Chicago and Orlando at the end of the month.
Come say hello and we will,
as we visit the town where the castle cake once stood
and we'll all mourn and Jason will cry.
And he'll still tear his butt.
I was gonna say another joke,
but I guess we'll end on that.
Does anyone have a handkerchief?