Welcome, Foolish Patreon subscribers, to Hauntcast this week.
It's the Fright, the Cemetery Gate.
I'm Rod Skardner, joined by Mike Koffinson and Jason Skeleton.
Boo to you, listeners.
Let's boo this, as the advertising in the Magic Kingdom says for the Halloween party.
Oh yeah, there was that as soon as, that was one of the first things I saw at the Orlando
airport.
Let's boo this.
Yeah.
Like let's do this.
Yes.
Let's all boo this, and this is a film that deserves boos.
Yeah.
And I don't mean do's, but flipped.
I mean, this is a, yeah, I mean, we knew, obviously we knew, and we're talking about
the, if you didn't fully, if you didn't pay attention to whatever we titled this, it is
not, we're not doing some, God knows we are not chipping off Haunted Mansion the Ride
over here on the second gate.
This is about the Haunted Mansion film from 2003.
2003.
Starring one Eddie Murphy.
Yeah.
Which we all subjected ourselves to.
But you know, before we get into that, this is sort of, this will close out Haunt Cast
the Fright for this year, and this is the last episode for October.
And I would be remiss if I didn't say just at the top of the episode, if you're waffling,
if you're thinking about not continuing to subscribe to the second gate, big stuff coming
in November.
Oh, sure.
Stay tuned.
A lot of fun, some adventures, some guests, which we don't always do behind the second
or cemetery gate.
So fun stuff's coming up.
Keep subscribing and thanks for subscribing.
Yes.
I agree with all of it.
Sure.
Thanks.
Glad I said it.
Glad I got it out there.
This is also our first episode we're recording since we got back from Chicago and Orlando.
Oh yeah.
More of that soon.
For anybody who was there, this is the first chance to say thank you.
Thank you to everyone.
I think we probably personally met some folks who are listening to this right now.
Thanks for everything.
Oh my God.
Some of the most, like, getting to leave a show where you had a good time and then face
a hallway full of people wearing shirts affiliated with this podcast or shirts affiliated with
the parks that we like so much.
And some people gave us things and just delightful conversations and a really wonderful time.
Real highlights in trips that included lots of fun stuff anyway.
So that's saying something.
And then meeting all of you is some of the best stuff.
So Dan, thank you for coming out.
Thank you for saying hello.
All of it.
Yeah.
And if you want Podcast the Ride to come to your town, it remains a little confusing how
to tell if enough of an audience in a place will come out.
So if you're in a place, you know, tweet or email and say, come to my place.
Not your house.
But still not a great way to tell if we can draw a crowd.
Two of those emails. But if we get, you know, 100 to 200.
That's true.
Yes.
Let us know.
OK.
But boy, we would like to do more tours and shows.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Yeah.
But for now, let's talk about a terrible movie.
All right.
Let's talk about this bad movie.
Kind of boring, too.
That's the real crime of it.
Agreed.
That's the rub.
Look, let's do right here right now.
We need to agree that if we're going to do more of these movies, they have to be like
bad, bad, not bad.
Well, that's the trouble that we have because it's hard to tell.
Only other real movie review we've done, Aladdin.
Yes. Yes.
Which is also I feel more boring bad than bad bad.
Yeah. But I like Aladdin a lot more than this.
I would agree. I would agree.
And that's a thought resonating with me throughout that you're tempted to go, well,
movies now, Disney movies are just recycling the IP and they're out of ideas and
they're just these like dull trod's.
And then you see what a real dull trod used to be.
Yeah. Back in the early 2000s.
I meant to I was going to buy this because there's like a ten dollar for movie
set you can get.
That's this the Tower of Terror.
Kirsten Dunst, which I have fond memories of, which I'm not sure.
I'm the same level of this movie.
I argue.
I have to think that's better.
Disney ABC night like like Sunday night movie or something.
It should have been. Were it not Eddie Murphy, there's nothing keeping it out of that
territory. Yes.
Country Bears is on this disk.
That at least seems interesting.
Yes. Well, I have to do that for specifically like research purposes and for claims made
by people that I won't mention.
And then a thing that seems much it seems still to me seems like it's
actually a mass hallucination.
The Mr. Toad Wind in the Willows live action movie by a bunch of money Python, a
bunch of British comedians in the 90s that I learned about like three months.
I was like, no way.
Yeah. Michael Palin did what?
It's pretty quiet.
I think that maybe that movie was a bigger deal in England.
I think so.
And maybe not called Mr.
Toad's Wild Ride in England.
I think it was not.
I think that was a way to put a more recognizable title on it in America.
Was it still a Toad Man, though?
Was it a different Toad Man?
I think it is.
And I think they just ice.
They were branding it with the ride specifically something like the instead of
when in the wind, when country bears insure like I'm curious.
Yeah, I wasn't even curious in 2003.
Yeah, I didn't see it in the theater.
Yeah, no, I didn't see.
I didn't see it.
I think I was like in my first semester of college, so I don't think I was like,
hey, everyone, let's go see this theme park movie.
Yeah, I was running up my film school.
Like I'm finally in film school with intellectual giants and I can go
appreciate the cinema Kill Bill Part One and Lost in Translation and make way
too big of a deal out of both of those movies.
Matrix opening night, Matrix Revolutions.
Of course.
Um, yeah, we were I wasn't seeing this kind of trash in November,
sort of 2003, I was trying to improve myself as a person being educated.
Luckily, though, you would regress years later.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I now like, please let me show you the like agreed upon top 10 films of the year
and let me tell you how few of them I saw.
I'll give myself credit.
I think this was one of the first connections I made where like, oh, wait,
they saw Pirates of the Caribbean was successful.
So they did Haunted Mansion and it seems like they did a worse job.
They were greenlit around the same time because what is Pirates the same year?
I believe. Yeah. So they wouldn't be seen it.
And then, yeah, I think there was maybe a mass operation of let's do theme park
stuff. Country Bears got figured out first, then Pirates, then Haunted Mansion.
And it's weird to think about how it all just seemed like sort of this junky pile
at once. And then isn't it weird in retrospect that Pirates of the Caribbean
was so much stickier and better done and yeah, yeah, it has so much more of an
impact. Like is the agreed upon thing?
I have not I have not seen one Pirates of the Caribbean.
Really? No, not even the first.
No, I know.
I saw it a couple of times.
I know people enjoy that first one especially.
And even some of the other ones, I still like the just like every frame I see looks
unpleasant to me. I haven't seen my taste years.
But is the deal basically that that first one was like, wow, I'm kind of surprised.
And then the and then the rest were garbage.
Yeah, I think that well, I don't know, because the people made a big deal out of it.
I feel like it didn't look bad, which is why people went to see it.
And then I think everyone was very happy with the weird Johnny Depp performance.
It's the it's the full mainstreaming Johnny Depp performance for the first one,
for the first one. Yeah, I kind of have diminishing return, much like the Matrix
sequels. I like the second one.
That's my memory is that I really like the second one.
And then the third one is horrible.
And I don't think I've seen other two more.
Yes, there are. I don't think I've seen either of them told.
Yeah, because there's
a.
I think there's dead.
I got to look this up now. I think there's five.
I think there's five. Yeah.
So I think now I'll have increasingly worse British rock stars.
Yeah. Paul McCartney was in the last one, right?
Yeah. Yeah. The Richards is in the third one.
Peter Noon is
Jack Sparrow's great uncle.
They're stepping down. Yeah.
Roger Daltrey was in the first one.
He was Will Turner's older brother.
They were going to get to Rod Argent sooner than we are.
But now we do who knows if they're going to make more.
Yeah. I mean, they're going to try because the Craig Mazin is making them.
Yeah. He's writing those friend of writers.
Craig Mazin. Yeah.
We'll be doing some writing all around smart man.
So Curse of the Black Pearl, Dead Man's Chest at World's End
took a break for four years.
Then you got on Stranger Tides.
And just in the last few years, you got is it Dead Men Tell No Tales?
I believe that it would call Dead Men Tell No Tales.
Of course, you wouldn't call the second one that like, well, you know,
what was the second one called? Stranger Tides?
Or is that the third? I don't know.
I forgot the list. I forgot the list being said there's Bill.
There's what's his Mackenzie Crook is in the Pirates movies.
He's what's his name from the office in the English office?
Oh, yes. They're Dwight. They're Dwight.
Gareth. Thank you.
He's very good.
Jack Dawson in the office from Smash.
Bill Nye. Right.
Bill Nye is what's his name?
You know, the bad guy.
Ian McChane. I feel like those movies were different
because they felt like real movies also.
Even when they were bad, they felt like modern big blockbuster movies
whereas Country Bears, which I have not seen all of.
And this movie feel like Sunday night, goofy, don't take themselves seriously,
maybe in a bad way.
Movies still feel cheap.
Yes. Even though, you know, the budget must have been like 80 million dollars.
Yes. It's still just like any frame of Pirates of the Caribbean feels.
This is a big adventure film. Right.
Whether or not you enjoy it, it's like this is like epic and real.
This thing is just so junky.
Posters are junky.
Yeah, they're junky.
Joyless, too. Yeah.
The Haunted Mansion references to the ride feel so crowbarred in.
Yes. And and like, well, we have boxes and a drinking game.
Just like, hey, got that one. Got that one. Got that one.
That's a perfect way of saying it.
And it's even more confusing when you think about the director is Rob Minkoff,
who co-directed The Lion King.
Yeah. And produced by Don Hahn, who produced The Lion King and Beauty and the Beast.
Oh, Rob Minkoff also involved in the who framed Roger Rabbit shorts
that they did for a few years.
Directed to Tummy Trouble and very, very, very strong live action
or animation, animation and shifted to like to live.
The merger. Well, Stuart Little, Stuart Little, the bridge.
Yeah. Part animation and part.
I remember being charming.
Yeah. Like a charming movie.
Also, Stuart Little, co-written by M.
Knight Shyamalan.
Maybe you should have.
Yes. Stuart Little is co-written by M.
Knight Shyamalan. No idea. Whoa.
By point being that Rob Minkoff, maybe you should have checked in with M.
Knight Shyamalan on how to make a spooky movie.
Scary. This one.
This feels like one where I like who I don't know how this all played out.
Yeah. You could blame specific people.
But this also seems like such a the system chose it movie.
It felt like just someone declared like there was papal smoke that said
there will be a Haunted Mansion film.
Yeah. Everyone followed those orders.
Yeah. No one, anyone, anywhere was excited about it.
From from director to Eddie Murphy.
I mean, maybe I you know, who probably enjoyed themselves
is like production designer.
I didn't write down his name, but a very good production designer
who also did Mary Poppins Returns and Rick Baker.
Rick Baker was surprising to see.
Who's doing some podcasts right now, which I recommend.
I haven't heard him on the Gilbert Gottfried one yet,
but his Mark Maron is fantastic.
Oh, man. There's this insane stuff about how he was King Kong
in the 76 King Kong with Jeff Bridges.
And but the producer, Dina De Laurentiis, was so dead set on
we have to advertise the that it was a robot.
It is a robotic Kong, much like they had at Universal Studios later.
It's the first robot con, but it's they used a robot
for only like six seconds of the movie because it didn't work.
And the rest of it is all Rick Baker doing his own makeup, applying his own.
Wow. Really? Like Lon Chaney.
Yeah. Oh, did he do his own?
A lot of those early Universal guys did.
I think Chaney invented a lot of movie monster techniques, like trial and error.
Oh, no kidding. Wow. That's cool stuff.
Anyway, that Rick Baker, it's it just builds to the point
where like Time magazine is coming and you cannot say that you are playing Kong.
We have to keep up the story that it is a robot.
And this is being told to Rick Baker dressed as a full ape.
He's like, what do you want me to say?
Look at me. Like, what is the story I can tell here?
I'm a robot. Yeah.
How about I go to lunch?
That seems like the easiest solution.
Just go hide in a hole. Just go hide. Wow.
Anyway, Dino De Laurentiis seems like that's one that's like,
I could read more on him because every time I feel like there's stuff there,
I feel like there's a Copperfield level.
I would imagine. Yeah.
And part of also the around that same time, the movie Orca,
this bad jaws rip off, which is really, really bonkers.
And what's the relation to Giada Food Network's Giada?
Who is wonderful and perfect.
And I wish my wife and I were friends with.
I don't know.
I think there is a familiar relation.
Yeah. Let me not throw all the De Laurentiis under the bus.
Giada is wonderful.
But so it's also funny that we're talking about this
right during a like if there was ever a shot at the full Eddie Murphy
Renaissance, it seems like we are in the attempt at that right now.
And we were traveling. I've been busy.
I've not gotten to watch. Dolemite is my name.
I really want to like it. I really hope I like it.
It seems like people do.
And that's from that world, those screenwriters, Alexander, Scott and Larry,
whatever did Ed Wood and people who are very fit.
I feel like I am going to like this thing.
I really hope that I do.
And it's cool to see Eddie Murphy like it.
And hopefully that's and all it's coming is good.
And his return to stand up by fingers crossed.
Because I think everybody would like if Eddie Murphy was back in form.
And he's doing all the sequels.
Yeah, he's doing coming up.
Excuse me. Coming to America, too.
Yeah. Right. Right.
And he says Beverly Hills Cop is coming.
And it'd be wonderful if this was all great.
And he was just back in good because we were going back to 2003.
This is certainly the nadir.
This came right after Daddy Daycare,
which is like seems like a highlight in this family run.
Yeah. As opposed to the one before Pluto Nash,
which is for God, Dave.
Meet Dave was like a little later, 2007. OK.
But the family run of Eddie Murphy, truly.
What a dreadful. Yeah.
I'm for him.
I was a little too young for like height of his power.
Eddie Murphy, I think I think Comedy Central used to play coming to America a lot.
Mm hmm. But when I was like a teenager, I knew Eddie Murphy is like,
oh, yeah, used to be a big stand up.
He was on SNL.
He made huge movies in the 80s and now he makes these kind of broad
like nutty professor like, oh, like already that was the read on him.
Yeah. He was he was not one of my guys.
And then when I got older, I saw 48 hours.
I was like, God damn, like, this is good.
Like, this is I liked this a lot.
Yeah. It's also I mean,
I certainly was going through those like best of SNL's.
Yeah. His is just like, I don't know.
It's like a fucking like, you know, punk album where everything's perfect.
Like it's just like, you know, like two minutes, all killer.
Like another one, another one, another one. Yeah.
He's like 20 years old or something. 21. Yeah. Yeah.
Insanely. I stood in and out of there in two and a half years.
Saved the show.
Wouldn't exist without him. Literally. Yeah.
Yeah, I hold him in pretty high regard, but this it was getting tough to.
Do you guys feel bothered at all by like, we're all supposed to forget
that Sandler got very bad and still as bad sometimes.
It just became like, well, I hate doubters.
How dare you and like go back and watch the bad Sandler's.
I can you blame?
Well, we all live in our own reality now more than ever.
So the prequels are good.
Adam Sandler is good.
Like whatever you want.
Not good.
Even once there was no not a single time he would not ever you want to live in.
You live in it.
So whatever out there you believe you believe it's real.
Like so. Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, Sandler, I loved Punch Drunk Love when that first came out.
I think it's still a great movie.
I mean, I was saying what Jim Carrey with with Eternal Sunshine, I was like,
oh, cool, these guys are going to be serious actors now.
And that kind of didn't happen.
They just made.
Yeah, those were the peaks.
Those were the peaks.
But then like Truman Show, Truman Show.
But I mean, I'm psyched for Uncut Gems.
The Sandler.
Oh, yes.
Yeah.
I think we're in the Sandler Renaissance and I like the Sandler Renaissance and I want the Murphy.
It was starting to feel like there would never be the Murphy Renaissance.
And I think where I seems like a shot.
Well, there's also the Murray.
There's the couple of years where Murray is doing the elephant movie.
And the man who knew too little.
Oh, yeah.
And it's like I remember being a kid and like thinking he was different now.
I remember I don't know.
I couldn't articulate it, but I remember seeing commercials for that and thinking he was like
the coolest guy because of Ghostbusters and Groundhog Day and then seeing those movies
and just sort of knowing they were like kind of boring ish family movies or something.
Yeah.
And then he like switched.
And this is the start of the Murray Renaissance of like Lost in Translation and then Broken
Flowers and then and then like a different annoying thing.
Of course, is born out of all of this Murray stuff.
But that's another more fans.
Yeah.
But yes, he had a he I feel like he flirted with having that 10 to 15 years.
He only did it in a couple of years, though, of like doing a bunch of stuff for probably
a lot of money and not a lot of days shooting.
I think a lot of these guys fell into I throw Steve Martin in there, too.
Like, I think it became just like there's 10 guys who can open comedies and let's just
see who's ready.
Who can we plug in?
And that's how Haunted Mansion feels to me, where this does not feel made for Eddie Murphy.
Oh, yeah.
No.
What he's doing in it isn't even that Eddie Murphy esque.
And I feel like this just as easily could have been like this to Steve Martin have a
couple of months.
Great.
Does Bill Murray have a couple months?
Like, it's just like, I think it's like, I think it's like, I think it's like, I think
I don't know.
It feels so phoned in.
Yeah.
He mostly is concerned about real estate deals.
Yes.
This is an extremely pre housing crisis movie.
Because this guy sells like four houses in a day and just comes home to grief.
Yeah.
The problem in this movie.
Eddie.
So Eddie Murphy is a real estate agent, which is what brings him to the Haunted Mansion
ultimately.
And he's like a workaholic.
And the problem is he's selling too many houses.
Too many people want to buy nice houses from me.
And then there's scenes where characters are like, I don't know, I wanted a different kind
of nice house.
People are being picky about houses.
And Jason, you were just saying there's a similar thing in the movie.
I love you, man.
With.
Oh, yes.
Paul Rudd.
That's also a like the housing market is going to great.
I yeah, he was like like Paul Rudd's character in a similar fashion is like, I'm really struggling.
I can't like I can't make a big deal that saved my life.
And then he gets into like a BMW and drives into like a beautiful Los Angeles home.
And like it's it's just so it's it's forced in the way of like in this movie.
The the like you're working too much is forced or my probably one of my least favorite parts
of this movie, The Sun's Spider Fear, like all this stuff about overcoming fear of spider.
I was like, this sucks.
Like this is rough.
Well, you could see it coming later to play in.
For sure.
It is set up so hard.
How dare a kid not like a spider?
Like setting that up is like a quality.
You can't live your life without a lot of people don't like spiders.
And most of us are not going to end up in a spooky mansion.
So it's OK.
I watched and the daughter and it also helps set up that like the daughter is like she's a little braver and a little brasher.
But there's about 15 minutes of joyless behind the scenes B roll on YouTube.
And I thought it was making of.
But it's just, you know, a camcorder shooting them shooting a scene.
And I from from behind the actors, I watched the moment where like they pull up to the mansion and like the daughter closes the door too hard.
And he's like, hey, don't do that.
This is a nice machine.
And I'm like, why is this in the movie?
This sucks.
They've already set up that he's kind of a stuffy guy and he's too focused on work.
Like he's not taking a vacation, but that's complicated by the fact that his wife is a partner in the real estate business.
Oh, that's right.
What's the what's the name of it?
I haven't written down.
Evers and Evers Evers and Evers.
For you.
He says that you're almost in like, OK, are we in Eddie Murphy?
Fun, because he says that really fast.
Evers and Evers.
And like, are we going to have some Eddie Murphy fun?
No, because that doesn't like keep going.
Let me just real quick before we get too deep into it.
The premise of Eddie Murphy is a realtor who tries to sell the haunted mansion.
Sounds like a funny, like fun.
Sure.
Sounds like a funny.
And some of the there was there's behind the scenes material somewhere I've seen one of either Minkoff or Han saying, you know, I just got to say that putting Eddie Murphy in a haunted house.
That's gold.
And like, yeah, it would be if anyone tried.
I like I don't it's not on its face a bad idea.
And there was a teaser trailer I watched that were if you all if that was all you saw, you'd go, oh, here we go.
And it's the Haunted Mansion with this star we've all like something from.
And they do they do like a number count of.
Yes, I saw that.
16 rooms and 999 ghosts and he's going to meet all of them.
Well, which sounds cool.
I don't know if he did.
I don't think he met them.
What do you count as meeting?
Seeing seeing meeting.
I guess seeing his meeting of seeing his meeting by interesting ghosts who you like and know from the ride.
Yeah.
And just driving past them.
Does that matter?
We got to pay off the spider stuff.
It's all about.
Yeah.
In a world we've we've got we've there's so much mythology to Haunted Mansion that we're going to do an event where it's going to end up being 14 episodes about it.
And they chose none of it.
It is about made up.
It's about Evers and Evers helping their son with a spider fear.
Yes.
And mistaken ghost identity.
I don't this is not really a hard and fast rule, but Pirates of the Caribbean is the closest one to like a tone or a feeling.
Maybe you have on a ride because like the rider have rides of jokes, but they do have like a tone that like conveys like adventure.
You're in the middle of a cannonball fight between, you know, the ships or whatever on pirates and Haunted Mansion as a tone.
It's scary and it's like not in this movie.
It's not they don't convey anything.
You get it says, yeah, if it truly were you set up the maybe if this the beginning of the movie was more we're in the Haunted Mansion and then Eddie Murphy shows up and what you're bringing a totally different vibe to this, but they don't get the Haunted Mansion tone right.
And the Eddie Murphy vibe is very flat.
Yeah.
And I understand that all of these.
Look, making a movie out of a ride.
The rides are thin.
Even like with all the mythology we've talked about, I still couldn't tell you what exactly the absolute this needs to be the plot of a Haunted Mansion movie is.
Pirates of the Caribbean seems to have gotten it right and that like, yeah, it's like some of the set pieces and there's little nods to tableaus from the ride.
But we made up our own thing because you got to make up your own thing.
They did that in Haunted Mansion, too, but I don't like any of what they made up.
Okay, I some some quick things I did like so we're not just being nice.
Okay, I think it's cute.
They got the dapper dance to be the singing busts.
Yeah, sure.
Not super excited.
I can tell.
I don't think it's essential that the eight is nice.
I don't think it's essential that the that the singing buss are good at singing.
I like that it's a these all these weird old men who like it's not that sure.
And you end up losing one.
You end up there's only four instead of five, which is a bummer.
Yeah, yeah, I was upset.
The thorough wasn't there.
But a cute little nod, a cute little wink.
The movie could have been two dozen more of those because it doesn't have that.
Yeah, okay.
You're right.
The saving grace performance wise, obviously Wallace Shawn.
Sure.
As usual, he has one line where he just yells at Eddie Murphy.
Are you upset?
And I legitimately laughed at that because I think it was like they had just explained that Master Gracie was going to kill his wife so that Master Gracie could be reunited with his lover.
Mm hmm.
And just Wallace Shawn.
They explained all this and Wallace Shawn asked, Are you upset?
And his delivery was very good.
That said, it was immediately followed up with him saying, there's always my way and there's always my way.
There's always my way.
And then he crashes a carriage through the wall of the man.
It doesn't make any sense.
So in case you haven't seen this, Wallace Shawn is one of two ghosts, housekeepers, essentially.
And then he sometimes looks like a human, but then sometimes looks like a blue ghost that you could put your arm through.
I mean, there's other characters like this as well.
Yeah.
So he is driving a carriage as a ghost right from when that gets cut.
Got to cut to.
Yeah, Wallace Shawn, you're never going to be mad at Wallace Shawn.
No.
So that's good.
But he can't save it himself.
He can't save it himself.
And then they go right from that carriage scene into what's kind of a mashup of the ballroom and the grim grinning ghosts like graveyard party.
And they blow through that setup so quick.
Yeah.
It's just like, hey, you know, that fun thing on the ride.
There you go.
Hi.
Wave at it.
It's gone.
You go past the characters faster than you do on the ride.
Yes.
All right.
Here's these guys.
There's the dueling guys.
Great.
Gone.
Yeah.
You see hitchhiking ghosts.
They factor in a little more, a little bit.
They give some lines.
Yeah.
But still not a lot.
I feel like I'm bad at synopsizing plots.
But if we had to do that fast for anyone who will not watch the film as we did.
Yes.
It's a workaholic real estate agent who's not spending enough time with his family.
And then he commits to spending a weekend with his family.
But on the way, he's going to check out this house that he thinks he can make a killing on.
But the house is full of haunts and happy haunts and some unhappy haunts because a woman committed suicide.
Who happens to look exactly like Eddie Murphy's wife.
Yes.
Yeah.
And then the master of the house who was in love with her kills himself.
That happens at the very end of the opening credits.
They do the hanging from the.
Oh, yeah.
Which is sharring.
Yeah.
Soon to be comedy.
So he's a good.
So everybody's basically a ghost in the house.
Not.
But not.
Terrence Stamp.
No, no, no.
He is.
He's a ghost.
He punches through him.
He tries to punch Eddie Murphy tries to punch Terrence Stamp and it's like ghost.
I now watch this movie like five weeks ago.
So I don't.
I have I'm going to be lost in some stuff, but that is the character.
Ramsley.
A normal regular name.
Yeah.
Very good name.
And he's scary.
Yeah.
I mean, he's scary just in the way a regular butler would be scary.
But spoiler, then he's a little more scary because he's he's not just unsettling to look
at.
He's all he also did bad things.
Yes.
To the people who lived in the house.
What a shocker.
Swapped a letter.
No.
OK.
So there was a letter.
He no he poisoned.
He poisoned Master Gracie's the love of Master Gracie's life.
Elizabeth Elizabeth.
She dies.
And then Master Gracie.
I think he gives a fake letter to Master Gracie that I believe is a forgery.
And he is overcome that he's overcome with grief and commits suicide in this children's
movie, which yeah, that happens in the ride.
You would have cut the suicide.
I don't know.
I think you got to have a hanging in the movie.
I mean, as we talked about on the the economy episode, they purposely on the raw, the imagineers
are like, no, no, the guy who hung himself is not Mr. Gracie because he killed Gracie
was murdered.
So we don't.
Oh, yeah.
So again, you're we're back to that.
The character in this movie is named after this real imagineer who died, not at his own
hand.
And then and obviously then crucial to the plot is Madame Leota played by Jennifer Tilley.
And what she does is be there and get carried around in the car.
A little gag.
She gets a couple of good lines towards the end.
I guess a couple does she?
What are they?
Like I think Eddie Murphy says, don't go anywhere.
And she goes like, oh, not a problem.
There's a hole.
They like have all the Sean.
He grabs the whatever you call it.
The crystal ball.
And they're like kind of grossed out by it a little bit.
They're like scared.
There's a little bit of gag in the back.
I'm not going to say I like it.
I'm just explaining there is a gag where all Sean picks up Jennifer Tilley's head, which
I guess if I say it like that, it sounds fun.
She she encourages Eddie Murphy not to give up.
And instead of hitting the conservatory glass with pipe, he should drive his sedan through
it.
And that'll fix that actually works.
Right.
Because, yeah, he she gives him a speech about, yeah, like you got to do try again.
You got to try again.
You can't quit.
And then he drives a car into the haunted mansion.
Also, he gets that's right.
That's right after he gets thrown out of the window in a really like gruesome like fall
from my Terrence Stamp by Grimmsley Grimsley Grimsley Grimsley.
Is his name Grimsby?
Grimsby.
OK, sorry.
It's Ram's Lee Ram's Lee.
But he throws Eddie Murphy out the window.
Eddie Murphy takes a really hard hit on his car and is not.
Oh, yeah, really destroys the car.
Also, a nice BMW, just like in I Love You Man.
Yeah.
You're saying.
Yeah, pretty much.
Multiple 2000s films with real estate agents and nice BMWs, the most relatable characters.
And then, yes, just like in I Love You Man, he closes that big real estate deal in this.
They go on.
They go on vacation with the family.
Also, the other problem with that is him and the wife own the business.
They can go on vacation whenever.
Mm hmm.
And he's a workaholic.
He doesn't want it.
And he's selling so many houses.
He is haunted by eager buyers and sellers like like and he likes the opening.
He's in a bar and he's getting people to sign their final papers and they're like,
you're not leaving until you have a drink, like almost threatening.
And then when he finally gets out of there, someone else goes like, oh, you're a real estate person.
We need a real estate person.
And it's like, what the fuck is this batting away offers to sell nice houses?
Just having is it Rachel Harris or Beth Littleford?
It's a daily show.
Rachel Harris.
Yeah.
I.
And then but then the Haunted Mansion comes up.
His wife, Sarah, is contacted specifically because they must see an ad with her and she is identical to.
Elizabeth.
The yes.
Master Gracie's wife who died.
And so the whole thing is that it's her.
It must be her.
She's lying.
I'm I must forcibly marry her.
Yeah.
She must.
We have to kill her and keep her here.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, she's dead.
Also.
OK.
There's these are all ghosts.
Yeah.
Like, don't they have access to some like higher?
First of all, let's just say this.
Heaven and hell exist.
This movie proves that heaven exists because Walsh is so excited he's going to go to heaven.
Yeah.
And then at the end, the literal gates of hell.
Yes.
So heaven.
So this this is something that is not in the ride.
No, they don't explain that heaven and hell exist on the Disneyland ride, the Haunted Mansion, but they do in the movie.
It seems like the 99 happy haunts leave the Haunted Mansion.
Except for Madame Leota and the singing bus who go on vacation with the Evers family.
Right.
That's a whole week.
We need some time to deconstruct.
We need to build.
We can build to the end credits.
Which haunts me.
Which that that's what really haunts me.
Yeah.
Is the end of this.
I'm with you.
Yeah.
But so, yeah, it's a world where two people can be exactly identical, like not even, you know, yes.
Similar looking, similar types, but she's just an exact.
Eddie Murphy's wife is an exact double of a ghost.
My point is, I guess, is like I thought that once you're a ghost, you have maybe have some access to like knowledge or something or, you know, there's an afterlife.
Oh, you know, I know who really killed her.
That's usually what it happens with ghosts is like now the ghost is haunting because they know who killed them or they know who betrayed them.
Not the case here.
Ghosts are way in the dark.
I mean, they are just as clueless.
They have exactly the same access to the exact same information they did when they were alive.
I don't.
It seems weird to me.
They're all ghosts, but they're all just acting like humans.
That's distressing to think about because I'm not sure I believe in an afterlife, but I assume if there is one that you get to know everything you would hope.
Yeah.
Don't still or you're like, you know, like reading different afterlife media and being, you know, confused by what's right and what's wrong and what's a lie and what's not just like here on Earth.
Ghost fake news.
Those fake news.
That's not an after world I want to live in.
No, it's a real bummer because I was like, well, somebody's got to be alive here and somebody's got to be a ghost.
No, they're all ghosts.
They're all ghosts, but there's only like there's Wally Sean and Dina's Bay Spy Bay.
I don't know the actresses.
The person playing Emma, Emma and Ezra, which Ezra Reno is one of the hitchhiking ghosts.
That is the name of one of the hitchhiking ghosts.
Right.
Kind of.
Wally Sean also is at the Oregon playing the Oregon at one point, which is kind of a cute.
And the hitchhiking ghosts are separate people.
So one of the he's not one of the hitchhiking.
No, but they yes, they show up in the in the carriage.
You're right.
But there the whole mansion was cursed, but only Master Gracie killed him.
And there's only two members of the domestic staff.
But then there's ghosts in the summit.
The ghost rules don't quite line up for me because in the opening credits, there's all these people ballroom dancing.
And I thought that was a nod to the ballroom scene.
But then there's no ghost ballroom scene.
There's the split ballroom dance.
That happened before.
That was the lead up to Elizabeth dying.
Yes, that's when the treachery occurred.
They're showing you the night that she died.
Yeah.
That was the exact moment that I knew I was not going to like this movie when it cut to this masquerade ball.
The masquerade and the signing.
No, I hate masquerade balls.
I'm not going to.
And that all seems like cut scenes.
Like, let's just jam it into the opening credits.
Tell it as quickly as possible.
So, you know, they're re-editing this movie like crazy.
This is this reeks of being one of those like 35 screenwriter disasters.
And oh, you know, here a quick side trick.
Did anybody look into the history of previous Haunted Mansion movies?
No, no.
Oh, my God.
OK, so if you look, there's different Wikipedia's and different sources you can look at that tell you that, you know, we ended up with this one.
And it's this guy who got into a Disney writing conservatory kind of program.
Who also wrote the movie Elf.
And that was before Elf was produced.
He wrote Elf on spec in 96 and used that as a sample to get a bunch of other work.
And then Elf was made and huge.
It was such a huge hit.
You know, so a very successful screenwriter who ended up writing this.
But before that, there was an attempt by a screenwriting pair.
And forgive me, I don't remember the second person because I'm so distracted by the first.
Apparently, there was a Haunted Mansion film written by a screenwriter named Jim Hill.
What?
Yep.
Yep. And it's that one.
I forgot about Jim Hill, who is the source of much of our theme park information and hosts the titan of Jim Hill Media Podcast Industries.
And there's always been a lot.
There's a lot of confusion about who is Jim Hill.
Right.
Even his own bio is like he's done stand up and he's and there he there's he he tried to write a show based on the Adventures Club.
But so supposedly in the 80s or 90s, he came to Disney with an idea for a Haunted Mansion film.
And this is written up in several settings.
That's a that's a confusing one, isn't it?
I we maybe we see if we can get it from.
Yeah. Does he have the script out?
I don't know.
Good day. Was it a pitch?
Do we know if there was a script or was it a pitch?
I don't know.
And it seems the story seems to be told like he just like contacted the Disney company blind.
I got to get we got to get him on the show.
Yeah, we got it.
We have a lot of questions, including this.
Yeah.
I mean, the most infamous one is the Guillermo del Toro was going to make one at Comic Con.
There was a teaser with Ian McShane reading the ghost host lines.
Really?
People lost their minds.
Yeah.
It's just like spooky, ethereal, like a mist that spells out the Haunted Mansion while he's reading Foolish Mortals and stuff.
But it made a video and people went wild.
And that 15 second teaser is better than this movie.
Well, I mean, then he's talking about it, the movie revolved around the Hat Box ghost, which was not on the Disneyland ride yet.
So he hadn't Hat Box had not his.
We were talking about Eddie Murphy's resurgence and Adam Sandler Hat Box had his resurgence a couple of years ago because he had been sort of just down in the first Safdie Brothers in good time.
Hat Box ghost was in the first Safdie Brothers movie.
He took the hat off.
So it's hard to recognize him.
But yeah, he tries to buy the liquid ecstasy in the Sprite bottle.
Can I also just say I was trying to find more information and I googled Jim Hill Haunted Mansion and the second result is an article he wrote called A PC Haunted Mansion.
Now that's scary.
Well, what year?
2008.
Oh, interesting.
What was it?
Was it where there changes to Haunted Mansion to make a PC?
I'm trying to remember.
I'll try to read while we keep talking.
Yeah, Hat Box ghost.
So yeah, Guillermo was talking about.
Next first line.
Forget about grim grinning ghosts.
Get ready for prim.
We don't mean to offend anyone ghosts.
What the fuck?
What is going on?
What changed in the Haunted Mansion?
Everybody's so goddamn scared of the PC police.
Get your guns out.
The PC police are going to come into your house and stop you from doing an accent.
Sorry, Charlie Brown.
Sorry, the great pumpkin.
Hat Box ghost.
This is a long time ago already.
Guillermo announced that movie that for some weird reason, Disney won't make.
I don't know what the hell the problem is, but he was he was an OG Hat Box ghost guy.
Yeah, he deserves credit for him before like mentioning it before.
Crazy houses in the valley in San Fernando Valley.
I know he is losing one.
He's divorced as well recently.
Oh, so I don't know if he has both houses.
He has half those houses probably.
I'm sure he has one of the houses.
I'm sure his like.
He has the nerd house.
He has the house that's like this is the Haunted Mansion room.
This is the Kaiju.
Maybe he bought the house then next to the other house.
So there's three houses now.
The ex-wife, the monster house, then his other house.
OK.
I don't know.
I'm just spitballing here.
Jim claims that they cut or maybe going to cut the line.
Drag your wretched bodies to the dead center of the room.
Is that that's the one?
I think so.
People found that offensive.
This seems like a fake.
We got to get more.
They do not get and do not let any employee say, please follow the blood red carpet into the foyer.
Sorry, death.
You're canceled.
I don't know about that.
I don't think they say blood red anymore, but I don't know that I ever heard that to begin with.
Yeah, I don't remember that.
And that's great.
You don't say that line.
The haunted mansion is dead.
It is burnt to the ground.
Might as well not even.
There's a guy hanging in the first scene.
The article seems to be a slippery slope type argument where like, well, then when do we cut that?
And then when next we're not going to be allowed to smoke as soon as we get out of our tomb.
I want one of the stops on Louie's upcoming standup tour to be in the foyer of the haunted mansion.
See, I see.
It used to be better.
It used to be better to be a ghost.
Those PC police will be white as ghosts when they see Louie's.
Well, we got to look into this.
Now we got to look if there was like just some crazy racist stuff on the haunted mansion that we forgot about in 2007.
That's the list.
What I just told you is the list.
The PC police are coming.
They're putting their PC police tape all over the mansion.
They cut the number from Miss Saigon that used to be in the Dida groups.
Oh, right.
Oh, that's right.
It was the ghost of Mickey Rooney's character from Breakfast at Tiffany's.
Well, they had to find 999 ghosts, so they were kind of scraping the bottom of the barrel.
And there was that song of the South reference in the graveyard.
I remember that now.
Yeah.
Yeah, they got rid of that.
There's also maybe a good time to mention the also making Disney fans at the time very upset.
Jennifer Tilley gave an interview where she said she was so excited about it and I'm in the ball.
It's just like the thing from the ride.
And if the movie does well, they're going to put me into the ball and the ride.
Oh, great.
So I always wonder where that came from.
And it came from her, apparently.
And I remember people being all a tizzy.
I think I was mad.
I probably like talked to my parents about it.
Mom, Dad, can we talk for a little bit?
It's probably right, though.
Like, there's probably like because I think we might mention this in the Haunted Mansion.
Tony Baxter said there was a plan in place to change the load area of Disneyland's Haunted Mansion into their like conservatory area.
Yeah, because he's famous conservatory.
He's always said.
I don't know what he's talking about.
What was the conservatory?
It's the glass room on the side of the mansion that a car goes in.
Yeah, it's not on the real Haunted Mansion.
It's sort of an invention for the movie or it's a part of that house.
Conservatories first became popular, apparently, after people got used to the more hot weather fruits, citrus and such.
The hot weather fruits.
They would get that would come as the British Empire expanded.
And they're like, can we grow this here back in the motherland?
Hot weather fruits.
Can I go with oranges?
Bananas?
OK, I see.
I got you.
I mean, I like I'm a big orange and banana fan as well.
Sure.
Yeah, that's crazy.
What do you like oranges or bananas?
Believe it or not.
What are cold weather fruits?
Oh, yeah, I there are some stuff that grows in cold weather.
I mean, grapes are very temperature sensitive.
Scott, you got an hour on this.
You got a cold weather.
I'm looking it up.
Twenty one winter fruits to grow or buy in every climate.
Honey, crisp apples, cherry plums, pears, apricots, cherries.
Your best bet is pears, they say.
So if you're a big pear person and you don't have a conservatory, don't worry about it.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
So that was going to be they obviously had a plan in place because it wasn't like the movie was a hit.
So they had to have that plan before it came out.
So I'm sure there was a version where Eddie Murphy's on the ride and where Jennifer Tilly is on the ride.
But that would require them to do something iconic, even just like all Jack Sparrow really does is like kind of shimmy around.
Jack Sparrow's shimmying is way more memorable than anything that either Murphy or Tilly does.
Yeah, I want to do this.
Oh, wait, what's the release date?
Did Pirates come out a couple of months before?
Yeah, this was like summer.
And this was in November.
So I would imagine when Pirates is a giant smash, there's some people in the company that are like, this is going to be a giant smash too.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
So we have to be ready.
Right.
Because maybe they already had the Jack Sparrow animatronic plan, but it was going to take forever to enact.
So they're like, this time, let's pounce on it.
So, you know, it could have been like some executive telling Jennifer Tilly that as well.
It's possible there wasn't like they hadn't made the head yet.
They're going to be on the ride.
Yes, it's going to be great.
You're going to be on the ride.
You know where they did put specifically Jennifer Tilly and I amazingly this does not come up in a later Denton Disney or deal episode coming soon.
But there was.
Oh, wait. Oh, I do.
I have it.
This is part of my research for that.
And it didn't come up.
But here is outside of the AMC theaters now defunct at Denton Disney.
Here is at the time of the release a giant Jennifer Tilly inflatable.
Whoa.
Yeah, that's scary.
That is hideous.
That is scarier than anything in the Haunted Mansion.
I'll post a picture of that.
Thanks to an old trip report from MousePlanet.com.
But yeah, she well, you know what an inflatable woman looks like an inflatable plastic woman is like with a cloudy glass ball.
It just looks like something that maybe you have sex with.
Oh, I see what you say.
She's got that like inflatable eyes.
Just.
Yeah.
There's a there's a vacancy to inflatable eyes that I've only prior seen in a sex doll.
And that's basically what this looks like.
And she's a suffocating this lady.
She looks like somebody's trying to murder various fetishes are all tied up in this one like a long line to get pictures with it.
Yeah, a really certain type.
Yeah.
Good thing this movie wasn't a ties together.
Yeah, sex dolls, suffocation, fantasies and you get your pictures and there's a paddy wagon right next to it.
Like they're just ready.
All right. So like I'm over a while.
The searches browser history and it's like it's a sting operation.
It man. Yeah.
Yeah. But the Johnny Depp animatronic to a lot of like it was I remember at the time when it got in the right.
It was like, wow, it's so human. It's so lifelike.
And so I'm half the time when stuff gets into the parks, it's like a test for a grander, a grander that like there was like a game in frontier land a while back on like heroes of frontier land.
And that was a test for Star Wars.
So what was what was Captain Jack testing?
What were you?
Just I think was the first in the line of like a next generation of animatronics, whatever it came after.
So they were testing for Eddie Murphy.
Oh, maybe they were ready for Eddie Murphy to be appearing out there around every corner.
I mean, maybe he would have replaced the shaky need Brownskeeper in the cemetery at the end.
Like you would have ran instead of that corner.
And he said one of his classic lines like that guy looks like he had a bad clam in his jambalaya or looking at a scary house and saying Bob Vila would have a field day with this.
That's maybe my favorite line that he says in the movie.
Why?
I mean, well, I had to pick one.
I'm not saying I like it.
I'm saying I'm the ranking.
It is a joke.
I just I like the Bob Vila reference.
It reminds me of the 90s.
It reminds me of home improvement.
So that's why I like that.
My best.
That's maybe my favorite line.
Eddie Murphy says, But I want to keep asking if I were there in person, I'd say he a field day.
You mean like an old like a British child in 1902, whatever Bob Vila would have a field.
He would see this decrepit house and go, ooh, hooray.
Well, if the idea that Bob Vila really gets excited, it gets like horny when he sees a dilapidated house because he gets to fix it up because he loves to do that.
By the way, where is Bob Vila?
Is he still alive?
Everyone talks about Bob Ross, but Bob Vila doesn't get enough credit.
Not on any shirts.
No ironic Halloween costumes.
I was a Bob Vila kid.
What?
I don't really remember watching Bob Ross that much growing up on PBS, but I would stop and watch Bob Vila sometimes.
And I was a big Paul Prudhomme kid.
Well, of course.
What's your fault?
I had a different floppy hat for every day of the week.
Different beret at eight.
Sure.
Bob Vila is alive.
Yeah.
Oh, good.
I know he's alive.
I just was he OK?
I don't know.
He's got a dot com where he seems to have various projects and wares.
OK.
Yeah, that's good.
Second gate.
He's not like Roddenberry.
He's not like Roddenberry who just destroyed his body with drugs and alcohol.
Wouldn't that be funny, though, if Bob Vila partied a lot?
Partier.
Yeah.
We got to look into that.
I'll say something that brought the John Bligh reminded me.
I forgot this movie takes place in like Louisiana.
New Orleans.
Yeah.
And I only remembered because should we talk about like that last sequence?
The the the driving sequence, the end of the end of the film.
Sure.
OK, because this this is I was really expecting more to go like, oh, my God, this is unbelievable.
And I really didn't feel that until the very end.
They've resolved the problems and then they're driving.
And there's a joke about them finally going on vacation.
And then the camera zooms out of a CGI car and I thought it zoomed out and then they're on a very long road going on.
Most digital bridge.
The digital apparent.
So that is apparently a real bridge.
Oh, that is the Lake Punch train causeway.
And it crosses like a man.
That was your vocal warm up before we started.
All right.
Punch straight punch.
Oh, no.
You nailed it in the in the test.
You got two in your own head.
Now, I've been on some there.
I've been on long bridges like that, like in the Chesapeake Bay.
We believe you.
I've seen long.
I know they exist.
What's the history of causeways?
It connects to one point to another.
It's it's long.
It's a big part.
Have you been on winter bridges as well as summer bridges?
Bridges that are good for the heat and the cold.
In the winter, you have to be careful because bridges usually ice first before road.
So you must.
Is that true?
Yes.
Because there's less like it doesn't go that deep.
I don't know the science behind it, but you see signs a lot in the northeast.
Bridges ice first.
Because the core of the earth is hot.
So if there's nothing going up, if it's just a cold air, it's what caused a problem for theme park owner, Kendall Roy.
And she wanted to win without spoiling anything.
Watch out for the ice.
Yes.
Don't do coke.
So but that yes, it looks like they're just driving in a digital bridge into a screen saver, like into the needs.
So the bridge is real, but the city, everything else is in theory is real.
I don't know if it's a real brick because it all looks very bad.
I has aged very really awful.
But what's happening here is that you think it's a family vacation and then you zoom out and it's there's a bunch of other also strapped into the car.
Leota and the singing bus.
The bus are on the back and the bus.
We didn't say earlier the bus are part of a really extended set piece.
One of the longer just here's let's let's settle into the scene for a while.
And they're always in barbershop quartet mode and they sing everything you say and are very unhelpful.
In fact, they don't help Eddie achieve his goal in talking to them.
He's looking for a key and they just like sing whatever they sing, repeat whatever he says and sing like coming around the mountain.
Yes. So then at the end, this reprises and they drive off into the sunset.
Sometimes they're singing with a backing track, which again, barbershop quartet doesn't quite make sense.
But aren't they they're singing something mundane.
It's something about like art like, are we there yet or which way is northeast or so?
Remember, those got called up to heaven at the end.
Yeah, they're spirits and the five bus have to go on vacation.
I have to imagine that was done because they're like, well, there's going to be a sequel and we're going to know some of the characters back.
So they're just going to be like their friends.
And I guess going on a trip is nice.
But like if you're trapped in a bus, don't you want to have a body again?
They'd rather just be in the back of a flat bed going into digital city USA.
And yeah, no, I you're right.
Afraid of spiders.
They probably thought that was the funniest for like gags later.
Like they're all holding heads, essentially, just the heads.
I guess I'm got my guess.
But I'm fighting for the rights of the characters.
Right. You're right.
To have their spirits free.
Yes, you would argue with them like you should go to heaven.
Heaven is exists. It exists.
It's real. We saw it.
We saw heaven and hell.
And why they don't get to go.
They just like take a trip with Eddie Murphy's boring kids.
Yes, I guess it doesn't look quality free children.
I guess you could make the argument they could go to heaven later.
They could put it off.
Maybe a quick trip. See a little bit of heaven can wait.
I suppose you could say there is a you can't take it with you line because like Emma,
the other housekeeper, like has all these bags and stuff.
Someone yells, you can't take it.
Oh, yeah. Right. Right. Right.
She's got a hat box.
I don't think that's a nod that the hat box goes.
Probably not.
Probably just her own woman with her own hat.
That's also it's also funny.
This has the beauty and the beast situation where love needs to unlock a curse.
Yes. In a crazy house.
Yeah. And free the spirits of everybody who works there.
But Elizabeth. OK.
So let's go back before we address the what I think is the weirdest thing in this movie.
So there is an insane like checking off kids movie like, well, you have to go on this quest and get this key.
The key they find in a vault full of spiders that the sun overcomes his fear of.
And the key unlocks the trunk that reveals Ramsley's treachery.
Meanwhile, oh, Sarah Elizabeth.
No, I'm not all right.
Describing the plot of the Honored Mansion for 2003.
No one's all right.
She agrees to marry to die and marry Master Gracie because he vaguely threatens her children.
And Ramsley does, too.
And then they have the wedding.
Ramsley somehow ordained like Ramsley in a minister frock or priest frock.
Everyone shows up to stop the wedding.
She has already drank the poison.
They do stop the wedding.
But she dies.
But then the ghost ball, there's a ghost ball.
We haven't talked about the ghost ball.
There's like a word following everyone.
I believe I have this written down in quotation marks.
The ghost ball was Elizabeth.
Someone says that.
Yes.
Ghost ball was ghost ball.
It's kind of an orb.
Oh, wait.
Oh, I remember this now.
Yeah.
Ghost ball.
The ghost ball.
So then Sarah collapses, but then Elizabeth shows up and takes Master Grace like it's OK.
We can be together now.
It's fine.
And then through the power of love, the poison is undone.
Like Sarah is fine.
I'm realizing now in my notes, I do have the phrase the ghost ball was Elizabeth, but I didn't put it in quotes.
So I assumed that was my bad job to myself.
Not an actual line from the film.
Maybe our description for this episode should just be the ghost ball was Elizabeth.
The ghost ball was Elizabeth.
So and Ramsley gets his comeuppance somehow.
Because he goes to hell.
He goes to hell.
He yells, damn you all to hell.
And then the gates of hell, the ground opens up and you see into hell.
And Eddie Murphy almost falls into hell.
We watch Eddie Murphy almost go to hell.
That's a crazy ending.
That's really crazy.
I mean, I guess ghosts suggest an afterlife.
But this confirmation of your Judeo-Christian afterlife.
Ramsley will be seated at the right hand of Satan.
Yeah.
You watch him fall in and the camera kind of tracks with him down into fire.
And it's such a silly CGI laden shot.
And it reminds me so much of the moment in MacGruber where Dieter von Knth is blasted off of a cliff.
And he's already like a mutant.
And then he like splatters into blood on the ground.
It's like the right, it's like the silly CGI MacGruber is like this meant to be taken seriously CGI of.
And it did really make me wish that Eddie Murphy would then urinate on Ramsley's body and say, fuck you, dude.
Well, you know, they made a sequel.
Ramsley would have come back to like mess with the Evers family at a different Haunted Mansion.
This Haunted Mansion 2 is like a mashup of all the Haunted Mansions.
So overly art directed.
I would argue that Eddie Murphy, they should go travel to hell to get Ramsley again.
That they should go stick it to them one more time.
There's a Haunted Mansion in hell.
Let's go re-kill them.
Re-kill them.
Ooh, a Haunted Mansion in hell is a pretty cool idea.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Werner Herzog in there.
They're waiting for you.
They're all waiting for you on sale, Ramsley.
It's all made, it's made of bones.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's cool.
Haunted Mansion.
The movie, all the trivia on IMDB, I'm always skeptical that it's all, any of it's really real.
But it's like, it says that the fan, it's this sort of Phantom Manor more than any of the other ones.
Kind of.
A little bit.
From what I understand, kind of is the answer to that.
I don't mind how it looks, but why wouldn't they just make it one of the ones that we know?
Well, especially since it's set in the South.
Like just make it look like the New Orleans Square one.
But I guess so many people go to Disney World.
It needs to look a little like, this is tiring just talking this.
Yeah.
I mean, that's the, I think this is clearly from an era where Disney didn't realize that there are fans of this stuff who would be really excited to see good depictions of how it is in the ride.
And again, I don't want a film that's just like swirling, just connecting the dots between things I know from the ride.
Because you can just go on the ride.
You got to tell a good story too.
But I find it so baffling.
They just blasted through all the ghosts.
We don't get a scene with the guys dueling.
You just pass by them.
Screw that.
Hitchhiking ghosts barely factor in.
There's always my way is just the prelude to a silly car crash.
Bus that follow you door that looks like it's going to explode comes so fast and are just afterthoughts.
Yeah.
Hurry back is after the credits.
Is it?
Yeah. Yeah.
There's a little after the credits tag.
Is it Leota?
Yeah, it's Leota.
And she's floating around in a very digital way.
It's not little Leota.
No.
No, no, no.
And that's not the right person.
It's like the bride who says it.
Not early.
Yeah, Leota doesn't say hurry back.
Yeah.
Oh, right. Sorry.
So that's incorrect.
So it doesn't sound right.
They got it all wrong.
And clearly they didn't know.
Clearly, like, I think the fact that there are there's so much more merch and all of we just got back from Epcot, which is currently all about.
So, OK, if you like Epcot, it's going to be fine.
We're going to fix it.
There's going to be stuff that even with Guardians, there's going to be stuff that you like that feels very classic Epcot.
Now they're like pleading with theme park fans.
They know we're out there in 2003.
I don't think they knew they were like, as an Easter egg, we could throw in the hitchhiking ghosts.
But people are really going to want to see the story about Evers and Evers helping their son get over his fear of spiders.
I think you're right.
I think that now it's interesting.
We'll see with Jungle Cruise.
We'll see where they're at.
Jungle Cruise guaranteed to be better than this.
Even that the trailer was so coherent.
Yeah, for sure.
As you know, the most some of the most charismatic actors we have.
2003, my memory of Disney World is like the Haunted Mansion merchandise was on a cart like the Memento Mori store that we went in.
I went into last week.
Shock full to the rafters of Haunted Mansion merchandise.
But a newer thing, a new a newer store location like they did not have a lot of Haunted Mansion stuff in the parks at the time, even though it's the caliber of ride that like like Splash Mountain or Space Mountain.
It is shorthand for theme park or shorthand for Disney World.
Yeah.
Haunted Mansion, Splash Mountain.
I think they need to do make a Splash Mountain movie that has nothing to do with Song of the South and then like reset it entirely.
So now the ride can be based.
It's no longer based on Song of the South in any way.
Yeah, I guess then you'd have to like if you have all the the Brayer characters.
Yeah, that's the characters are still like Mary those tales.
And let's just like call it like Brian Bear and Brian Rabbit.
Just change the name and make sure the shirt.
Zootopia.
All the Zootopia characters are going on a trip.
That's fine too.
And decided to like kill each other.
I don't know.
I think I like.
They're all named Brian instead.
I think Brian Bear and Brian Rabbit.
No, no, no.
It's not Brian.
It's not Brayer Bear.
It's Brian Bear.
Brian Bear and he's got a different color shirt and a different color hat.
So you don't have to do too much work on the animatronics.
Still got a very thick seat, though.
Sure.
You can't change that.
That's another seat wedged into a wall.
Yeah.
It's another airborne seat.
One of the best theme park seats for sure.
Is this the is it the seat?
Is it the thick seat?
Final four.
Which theme park seat?
There's not a lot to deal with.
OK, we got that.
We got Donald.
We got Pooh Bear.
Brian Bear.
Pooh Bear.
Shrek.
Donald.
Yeah, Shrek.
Shrek seat.
Yeah.
Didn't we see in.
Oh, oh, Donald in.
Well, this is Donald again.
I think Donald in Fill Our Magic is different than Donald in Three Caballeros.
Yes.
During Fiesta.
So there's a Donald division.
Did you say did you say Hulk or Polk?
I said Hulk.
Like the Hulk statue.
Not the President Polk.
President Polk's thick seat.
Was Polk a larger gentleman?
No, I said Hulk.
Like a Hulk statue ripping apart the track.
He's got a thick seat.
If that had been true and just did.
What if Polk?
James K. Polk was a skinny, slight man except for his large seat.
Well, we know which president has the largest seat.
Oh, yeah.
And he'll be in there.
He's in this final four maybe.
Oh, no.
Do we have to?
This is horrible.
It's all weird.
Well, it's all male, which is weird.
But how horrible would it be if we three men put like a nice, a nice female seat?
No, no, no.
Disgusting.
No, absolutely not.
No, I mean weird as hell.
Yeah, we shouldn't do this.
Big boys only.
Big boys season's coming.
Temperatures dropping.
Get yourself a big boy.
We're good boys admiring big boy butts.
But they're mostly animal butts.
Yeah.
They're big animal butts.
That's what it is.
That's what makes it wholesome.
There's a couple big boys in How to Train Your Dragon, that universe.
So we've got to see about the epic universe.
Well, it's called an epic universe.
You think we should wait till 2023 to do the thick seats?
No, I'm just saying we might have some thick seats on the horizon.
Final four?
Final four.
I was just saying brace yourselves, fellas.
All right.
I'm brazing myself.
I'm just saying we have to talk about the thick seats now.
Sure.
Big Al, probably a lot of the country bears.
Big Al seems like it'll sweep in.
A lot of the country bears are in the conversation.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
So we can't discount Henry.
No.
You can't get to discount any of them.
You didn't even know or should you try?
Pooh bear.
Pooh, yeah.
Why is it Pooh already?
But you really see, is there really seat involved?
Yeah, isn't there?
Yeah.
Mainly if he's stuck, it's like the other way.
Yeah, he gets stuck.
Yeah, he gets, well, but then he like floats around when he has his like honey hallucination.
Mm-hmm.
So.
Are there any universal, well, obviously.
Check.
Homer J. Simpson.
Of course.
Yeah.
Uh.
I'm trying to think if there's a.
Vin Diesel?
Vin Diesel.
I don't think that's a thick seat.
I'm a bum.
Dominic Toretto.
Bum Bumblebee?
No.
Would you refer to a.
They have.
Fast and Furious Cars having a thick seat.
Well, Bumble, the Transformers and the Fast and Furious Cars all have seats.
Literal seats.
So you could put them in there too.
Because they're cars.
Michael, don't be ridiculous.
I'm just saying maybe there's a cushion, a thick cushion in their seats.
I think they're getting bumped ASAP.
All right, fine.
In favor of real seats.
Fine.
Maybe they'll, maybe they'll make it in.
We don't, we haven't talked about this.
We're just brainstorming.
Hagrid.
Hagrid animatronic.
Big boy.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
Three out of dog probably.
Yeah.
Wouldn't want to clean up after that.
No.
Well, I guess we have to do it.
Thick.
Ugh.
That's where.
You feel who haven't checked in on the podcast are like friends of ours.
Like, like.
How's the podcast going?
Good.
We just did the thick seat final four.
We spent two hours, 45 minutes talking about which animal's butt was the best or fluffiest.
And then people get home from the, that party where that conversation was said, like, Oh,
I ran into a Gardener.
Yeah, he's not, I don't.
Something's wrong.
I don't know if I'm going to talk to him at a party again.
Yeah.
I think I'm done with that guy.
They were doing the theme park podcast.
I thought it was like, they're talking about like, you know, the haunted mansion or whatever,
but they're.
Like they are just very, very slowly.
Very.
Yeah.
But it's the furry robots, but they were talking about it for 45 minutes.
And he talked to me.
He cornered me and talked to me at the party about it for 75.
Show me photos of it.
I kept telling him I had to go to the bathroom.
So he said, I'll follow you there.
Carlson wrote a, spent a week writing a song about the robots, but I don't know.
He's cracking up.
We all did at least two song parodies for the thick seat final four.
Yeah.
All right.
And I got a third.
Oh, I knew you would.
Yeah.
Oh, a glimpse into our future.
We all know we have to do it.
I'm like, yeah.
I'm looking in a scary mirror.
Yeah.
Oh, what a burden.
Watching our brains decay.
Looking at each other like, well, like as if we just accidentally killed someone, we're
like, well, we have to cover it up.
We have to do this now.
Like we're all in this together.
This didn't happen.
Yeah.
Well, that's, or this will happen.
I was going to say this will happen.
Okay.
So I think I've braced myself enough.
Oh yeah.
Let's talk about, so the end credits, you zoom out of the car.
Leo is there.
The bus are there.
They're driving on an endless bridge to a digital vacation, presumably, but it looks
like a limbo and we hit the credits and what song are you greeted with?
You're thinking grim grinning ghosts.
You're thinking that we're good music.
No, it's a song called is you by Nelly.
It is a song by Nelly that samples the people's court theme song.
I forgot.
I truly thought I was losing it.
Nothing glues this more to 2003 than credit song by Nelly.
But the fact that it's a Nelly song that samples the people's court theme song, I truly thought
I was losing my mind as I was watching this because I was going, is that the people's
court?
Yeah.
I, and you, and you know it and you're like, is it like a scared, is it from a scary movie
or something?
No, no, no.
It's the people's court.
I'm now on the Wikipedia of is you.
This was not made for the haunted mansion.
It was originally on Nelly's album, the dirty versions, the reinvention.
And let me just, this is a case where why say it in my own words when I could just read
the Wikipedia music video similar to the film, the haunted mansion.
Nelly inherits a mansion from his recently deceased uncle.
Sorry, Nelly.
Sorry.
Your uncle died.
Nelly condolences and throws a house party.
However, his guests soon start falling victim to the haunting of the house.
Falling victim to the haunting of the house.
Nelly soon confronts the evil spirit causing it all also played by him and defeats it by
throwing an enchanted orb he received from a zombie.
Whoa.
The evil spirit.
Mike, can you throw this on your TV or something while we wrap this up?
I really regret not knowing there was a music video or watching it.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to leave Evo and watch the video.
This music video sounds better than this movie.
Yeah, it seems like it does everything the movie does, but in quicker time.
And then in the end, the evil spirit is destroyed and the ghosts of the mansion are free.
So that all happens.
There's a ghost ball who in this version is not Elizabeth.
And this wasn't made in conjunction with the movie.
The video maybe finally.
The video was probably like.
Was.
Yeah.
You know, those music videos back in the day were like it would be a music video and
there would just be one or two clips from the movie just shoved in.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Those are always interesting.
I'm also in this vein.
This is a similar probably within the year, the couple year period of Master of Disguise,
which has a song by Cleopatra called Master of Disguise.
He's the M A S T E R of Disguise.
True change right in front of your eyes.
I'd like to recommend that one too.
That's the haunted mansion.
Like this.
The video is clearly made.
Do we need to pause recording and just watch this?
Yeah, let's pause this.
Okay, hang on.
We are back.
Okay, I really regret not finding out about this because we have to wrap it up because
I have to leave for something.
So we just got to like take it all.
It's tough to take it all in.
Let's try to describe what we just saw.
Also though, stop what you're doing and watch first.
Stop what you're doing.
Watch this horny video.
This extremely horny video.
Horny, not horny.
Horny.
That's pretty horny too.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
So you kick right into a really green screeny scene where a woman is very impatient outside
the haunted mansion looking at her watch.
Where's Nellie?
Nellie gets there.
You're late.
I've been waiting for you for over an hour.
I'm sorry to hear about your uncle, but you just got to sign this very quickly.
She says it as flat and quick as that.
That's not me rushing.
Your uncle left you this great house.
Oh cool.
Hey, do you want to stick around and hang out in the house?
No, I got to go.
Sorry.
Bye.
He's in like a yellow Lambo that now beats Eddie's BMW as the nicest car to drive into
the haunted mansion.
So Eddie's been shown up.
I mean, this whole thing shows up the movie big time.
This is better than the movie for sure.
This is better.
Better than the movie.
This is a wild Nellie at the height of his powers, I feel like.
Yeah.
2003.
Yeah, a couple of years.
All that's too hot in here is not far.
Budget, effects, acting.
Let's see Nellie act a lot.
Acting, three different Nellies, some ghost Nellies, zero Band-Aids.
Yeah, you're right.
No Band-Aids.
He excused the Band-Aid.
Also, this is a music video in a haunted house where there's multiple Nellies and it reminds
me a lot of Michael Jackson's Ghosts, which is, if you've never seen it, insanely high
production value, goes on for like an unnecessary full hour.
Nellie gets it all done in Is You in four minutes.
He gets more done than the Haunted Mansion movie.
It's funnier than the Haunted Mansion movie.
He does multiple characters much faster than Michael Jackson does.
I'm a big fan of this.
Yeah, it's really, I mean, there's a lot of narrative in this video.
Yeah.
Yeah, it covers so much.
Part of it, we didn't really say, and this, we oddly talk about this in a different episode
you'll hear in a long time from now, but the first half hour of the Haunted Mansion is
so wretchedly slow.
Yeah.
What are we doing?
Like, you're not anywhere near a ghost for so long.
It's like, come on, come on.
Nellie, this jams so much story.
The woman does you the courtesy of talking as quickly as possible to throw you into it.
I wish the Haunted Mansion movie had been done at this pace.
I would have no complaints.
They should have, my only complaint with this Nellie video is they should have put some
of the actors in.
So like, Wallace Shawn should have been in there.
Like there's a scene where like a ghost sticks its tongue in like one of this woman's ear
and that should have been Wallace Shawn.
There's a sexy tongue goes like licking a woman's ear, but you don't see it on a camcorder
monitor.
Right.
Sexy tongue goes should have been played by Wallace Shawn.
Sure.
That's what I'm saying.
Can I be a Saint Lunatic?
Wallace Shawn and Nellie in a video together.
Come on.
This is still gonna happen.
Nellie is making it rain at one point in the video.
If Wallace Shawn was next to him also making it rain, this would have been the cultural
event of the year.
Yeah, that's true.
I think my butt getting big.
Oh, well now he's in the whole Nellie extended universe.
So a lot of 2003 flip cams and then like ghosts start appearing in those like this creepy
tongue ghost.
Nellie, I just wrote down, he rapped Nellie raps in that one way Nellie raps.
It's just kind of like all the Nellie songs.
He hooks up with somebody in a haunted bed.
He seems like excited.
Here we go.
This is the sweetest bed I've ever hooked up in.
And then it starts bouncing around, but he but not the not because of the fucking it's
because of ghosts.
And then the woman stays in the bed and is like seizureing.
It's very disturbing.
Yeah, like the exorcist or something.
Yeah.
And then there's some poltergeist stuff with TVs too.
Again more types of ghosts than the movie.
Yeah.
It was superior in every way.
Scarier than the movie.
Yeah.
There was a genuine like jump scare with that tongue ghost appearing in the camera.
And we all went, oh, it's actually yeah, actually a little bit freaky.
Someone turns their neck a full like three set layers, like a creepy makeup effect.
And yeah, a toilet explodes with water.
A lot of the rapping is done via Nellie in a leota ball.
Yeah.
As a park nerd, I had no idea this was has been sitting there for so long.
Yeah, really video where Nellie is in Madame Leota's crystal ball.
Yeah.
Yeah, we need to there needs to be merch of that.
And that I will allow in the ride.
Oh, yeah.
OK.
Maybe on every 420, the ball is full of green smoke and it's Nellie rapping is you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, now that's a holiday overlay.
We can all hear him says like in the song and in note that when the woman walks into
town, that's what he says in the song.
And he says, I've never been the type to break up a happy home, but there's something about
baby girl.
I just can't leave her alone.
So he'll say that in the room.
I can't leave alone.
I also thought I said while we were watching it, there's some censoring there.
They heard the word poppin and then they censored what's after that.
And I thought that was going to be about poppin P, but it's about poppin B bottles.
They censored it because you can't talk about poppin bottles.
There's a couple.
There's an F word.
There's yeah.
There's a lot.
I'm surprised by this.
I'm surprised Disney put this.
Do they know?
They just didn't know.
The Internet was so slow.
They had to run it on a DV tape over and the PA got lost and they were all like just rush.
Just get it out.
The theaters.
Who cares?
So the zombie shows up.
Nellie hits it with a frying pan and then goes in the fridge and gets a bottle of champagne.
You pour one pours one out and a coffin comes through the ground.
Yeah, that's great.
Good idea.
You pour one out and then the dead body comes up.
Yeah.
Where you poured one out.
And that's where he gets the orb, the orb that he throws at Ghost Nellie.
That makes Ghost Nellie's head explode.
He explodes his own head.
But before that, Ghost Nellie waves his arms and seals regular Nellie's mouth shut.
Yeah.
It's a Wu-Tang torture sketch-esque event.
It's very disturbing.
His mouth is like buttoned up.
Looks like a butthole.
Yeah, it's scary.
Yeah.
That's again a freakier thing than happens in Eddie Murphy Haunted Mansion.
Man, this is so much better than the Haunted Mansion.
Nellie decapitates himself.
It is so much more memorable than any single one part.
Wow.
This saved the episode.
I am so much more excited than when we started it.
I know.
If only I knew Nellie was coming at the end.
I can't wait to share.
The best is at the end.
Like the ghost following you home.
We gave you a good little like a good little fun hit of something at the end of this episode.
Just like when he was alive, Master Gracie, sharing his beautiful home with ballroom dancing
guests, we're so excited to share Is You with you, the listener.
Yes.
It's the same exact thing.
It's tough to obviously Grim Grin Ghosts.
I'll still barely give the edge as the best Haunted Mansion affiliated song, but a very
close second.
Nipping at his heels.
Yeah.
Is You.
In 2003, it would have been tempting to say, take out Grim Grin Ghosts.
I think it's Is You now.
Do we know anyone who?
There has to be someone we know that works Haunted Mansion is high up enough to let us
ride through the Haunted Mansion with Is You blasting.
One ride through.
We got some fun little hookups in Florida.
We got to go in a place in the Haunted Mansion that we didn't know existed.
We'll talk about that, of course, in a few years when we get to that.
Yes.
On the Haunted Mansion in Florida.
But yes, that's what I'm thinking.
Like maybe we know someone that works like Ops that could just, you know, put a CD in
a disc drive.
Yeah.
I don't want to say names, but did anyone we just met, if there's anyone listening
to this, can you arrange?
Obviously, we are.
Thank you so much for everything you did for us while we were down there.
But now we've got a new dream.
Yeah.
Which is bumping Is You the whole mansion long.
I honestly think it would play well too, because there's a couple of party scenes and it's
a party song.
Oh yeah.
And I think the graveyard.
All those ghosts would have a fun time with that.
Yeah.
I guess what we could do is, at the very least, what we'll do is have our phones bring your
headphones or your AirPods and blast Is You in your headphones while you're on the Haunted
Mansion.
Yeah.
And we'll all put on face band-aids in solidarity.
Hey, and you know what else we got to do.
We got to get high, y'all.
Oh, well.
You know what that means?
My standard one quarter of a weed gummy that gets me sleepy.
Hell yeah.
Nellie would be proud.
Yeah, I'm going to have to figure that out.
I'm going to have to really test that out, because I don't want to freak out.
Because I'm going to freak out hearing the party song and seeing.
Too intense.
It's too much of a party, my brain.
You're going to be looking for the tongue ghost.
You're like, oh, I don't want that tongue ghost to get me.
Yeah.
I thought I liked this song, but now it feels like a tongue ghost licking my ear.
All right.
Well, I'll look.
I'll work on my weed tolerance so we can do this.
Yeah.
I guess we have to do that.
I guess we do actually have to do this, too.
We have to get them to or do we just know we should go.
I'm saying we at least have to get high and bring our headphones and see what the haunted
mansion is like with is you play.
I think we have to do this.
I think we really.
That that that that.
And then I think we.
Yeah, I think it's hard to bring these rides to life for yourself again.
But this we found a way.
We're not saying we're mansion records records, but we can't leave it alone.
Oh, man.
Well, what a great exit.
You survived haunt cast the fright 2019.
Wow.
What about.
And hey, you don't have to wait for it next time you're in Disneyland.
Bring headphones.
Yeah, you know, whatever you feel comfortable doing.
If you want to bring in your own quarter of a weed coming, I'm not going to stop you.
I would say do it in the car, though.
You don't want to disrespect the sanctity of the park.
That would be my preference.
But that whatever you want devouring of a gummy.
Yeah.
I think that is you.
Hell, yeah.
That was a lot of fun.
As I said, please stick around for November.
The second gate there's it's been transformed.
If the spirit our spirits are set free, it's no longer the cemetery gate.
Yeah.
It'll be the second gate again in a couple of days and fun stuff coming.
Bye.
Ding, Ding, Ding, Ding, Ding, Ding.