Forever...
...Dark!
Darkness falls out on the street, Evil rears its head.
Get your crazy shake to go, And your fried donut bread.
The villains threaten this sacred place, This downtown shopping mall.
We must defend the Lego store, And the Splitsville bowling balls.
The Downtown Disney or to you, We must protect our AP discount meals.
The Downtown Disney or to you, With secrets does the Earl of Sandwich conceal.
Boys, boys, my cousin has been taken by evil forces that have inhabited Downtown Disney.
In order to find them, he will need to thoroughly discuss every aspect of the mall.
Stores, restaurants, both of the Starbucks.
We have 18 daily, very necessary episodes and much to do so.
I will be there to guide you and keep your conversations from getting too off topic or boring.
The Downtown Disney ordeal, Why do we do this to ourselves?
Welcome to Podcast The Raya, The Downtown Disney ordeal, level five, stage three, final stage.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always, Jason Sheridan.
Yeah, I'm here.
Yes, and Scott Garner also here.
The most relieved man in the world.
This is it. Yeah.
Made it. What started as 15 became 18.
Yes.
Is now zero.
And I'm sure we'll never do something like this again.
There's no way that's something.
I don't like your tone.
I like the words you're saying, but I don't like the smile with which you're saying it or the way that you're saying it.
My fiendish grin maybe suggests that we will do this again.
I don't know.
We got a lot to get to though.
What's the order of bringing in people?
You know, should it be our guests first? Let's bring our guests in first.
Yeah, let's get them in.
You all know him. He's from Doughboys. He's from a lot of other things.
He's from the very special episodes of Podcast The Ride.
Ladies and gentlemen, Nick Weiger is here.
Hi.
How are you?
How are you doing? You know him from his trademark high.
I'm the high guy. That's me.
Get your high guy swag at teespring.com.
It's an important note to come in on.
You come in all mumbly and low energy top of a podcast.
The whole thing falls apart.
Yeah, for sure.
No, but yeah, we got we got high guy stickers.
We got high guy shirts, sweatshirts, hoodies.
We got onesies for your babies.
We got it all.
You got a big ring on like a high school graduation type ring.
That's like that must cost like upwards of 500 bucks.
I spent a lot of money on my high guy ring, but it's great, especially if someone gets up in my face.
Oh, yeah.
I'd like, you know, pull my fist up to him and then they like they didn't make a move.
I fucking hit him.
And then you still that you don't just written.
Then you still hit fucking hit him with the range and they got a high guy like fucking imprint in their cheekbone.
Like the Phantom, like the Phantom.
Yeah, much like the Phantom.
The high guy is like really violent.
Well, yeah, I mean, that's kind of my energy is that I come in and I'm trying to be friendly and jovial and convivial.
But if someone comes at me with negative energy, the high guy is going to be the by guy.
I don't want to end up incurring your your rage.
But, you know, if you do when you punch the imprint actually says IH more like it's backwards and it's just unreadable.
So here's what's happening in response to that, because I've found that after a few different
may lays, I've gotten in a few different scraps.
I've noticed that when I've seen, you know, police photos or whatever, I have.
And so I'm currently financing.
I've got a down payment on a reversed ring.
Oh, so that's going to be the next stage of that.
Then if I if I feel like I'm going to get into fracas, I'll just swap out the ring for the reverse one real quick.
Oh, that's yeah.
I do a quick slide.
You've already got the relationship with the ring place for sure.
You're working with the Jostens, right?
Yeah, I'm working with the Jostens people.
Good people, good people.
They're great.
People mostly know them for Clash Rings, but they're trying to expand into novelty podcast adjacent rings because they're Jostens is always innovating.
Check them out, Jostens.com.
And if you follow at Jostens and use the hashtag high guy on social media, you'll enter you're entered in a code for a you're in the contest for a possible
$25 discount off of ring of your choice. This is great synergy because Scott doesn't actually know that we just agreed to do a whole series about the Jostens class rings.
Oh, wow.
This is going to be perfect.
This has nothing.
It's nothing even tangible to do with theme park.
It does because if it's a high school is within 10 miles of a theme park.
Yeah, that falls in the radius.
That opens up anything.
Yeah, of course.
We can do it.
Exactly.
We can show her what sewers or her crosswalks.
Well, yeah, the sewer system actually very interesting.
We touched on a little of the utility that places of this magnitude have to deal with.
But Florida, once you start factoring in like they run a small area.
We have confused the bounds where now any object is eligible for a daily series.
Well, we have someone who can tell us if this I mean, like if this sounds like a good thing or if we're staying in bounds, he's here.
You all know.
I don't know.
You you developed a little bit of a bond with him during the course of this.
I think so. I'm the cool uncle.
Help me out.
Yeah. But the sector keeper is here.
Boys, boys, you give me strength.
Hey, hi, Mr. Wiger.
I love it.
Man after my heart.
Mr. Wiger, too.
So official like so I'm a high guy.
Are you on like Wiger?
You on like tick tock?
Is that how he's seen you?
Yeah, I mean, I'm on tick tock.
I'm on tick tock and only fans.
So so, you know, check out a high guy on both those platforms.
The only fans content is a little bit, you know, it's for mommy and daddy.
But I was trying to get Mike to sign up for only fans.
Like, I was trying to get.
But if you want to see that hiring wrapped around a hog, it's a place to go.
Leaving it into an imprint on something different.
That Twitter, that Twitter joke going around of the cost of streaming services
and then high guy only fans like thirty dollars to watch the high guy jerk off.
This was supposed to save us money.
So yes, you know him from there where he where he goes by his formal mischief.
Right.
Yeah.
Glad to see him.
So stay away, though.
Keep your distance.
Boys, boys, the the final stage, final level.
Amazing. Yeah, yeah.
Final stage of the final daily podcast series.
I don't hold you to that.
Don't don't spring any more levels or stages on us.
OK, of course. Of course, boys.
There's a lot to do. Let's just stay focused.
OK. OK. What's in the stage on what?
Yeah. Like what's going on? Tell us. Tell us.
Hurry up and help us out.
Tell us where you need a poll.
You need to take a quick poll. Yeah. Just give me a sec.
Oh, yeah. That's the good stuff.
Nice, nice flavor on that one.
Mm hmm. That's Junior Bacon cheeseburger.
Oh, Wendy's branded jewel.
You got a ration of those now. They were starting to all even mint.
That's crazy. I didn't know that Wendy's was making their own jewel pod.
Yeah. Wendy's jewel pod.
I figure if my high guy's coming through, I'm flying high from a high guy.
I love it. I love it. Junior Junior Cheeseburger Mint.
Yeah, it's flavored after the size, too.
Wow. Wait, did you say there's mint? Yeah.
Also, they have to make they for a while they had to make every flavor mint to get away with it.
But now even mints, they're like eyeing to outlaw.
So ration. Yeah, I know. I'm sorry. You'll only be able to get tobacco flavor.
It's a good and isn't jewel having a lot of financial trouble currently?
I think so. Like, yeah, I listen to a I forget if it was the DailyPodcap.
But yeah, there's like a lot of I don't know.
They might not be around for that much longer, dude. Fallen Brothers.
They could be Fallen Brother.
So does that imply that we have to do a podcast series about all of the former flavors of jewel that are no longer available for purchase?
If they're within a 10 mile of any theme park. I see.
I have one more thing before you read that I'm glad we were men.
We talked about your jewel use a little bit.
There was a comment on Reddit that I just I thought Baird mentioning on the show.
A Paul G on our Reddit said Sector Keeper loves sucking on jewels.
Bugsy loves sucking on jewels. What does it mean?
Oh, Hugsy Brother. Yes.
That's right. It clearly runs in the family.
The love of sucking on something pronounced jewel, but it can be spelled differently.
Right. Because we did find out we've we've been talking about your cousins a lot.
But of course, your brother is Bugsy slash Hugsy, the 40s gangster who bothers us sometimes.
You guys get having back. I don't know about that.
I don't know. I think I liked Bugsy more than Hugsy is good version at the end.
I'm the most scared of having a G on.
Can I ask you, Sector Keeper, are you and Hugsy excited about the upcoming movie Richard Jewel?
Oh, there's a bomb and Centennial.
Yeah, yeah, there was. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He has to keep that's that's the trailer line.
They make him say that he makes him sit down and makes him say, yeah, I want to see that.
And I want to see Good Boys double feature.
Oh, that's right. Oh, yeah. We promised you a movie, but we can't get you to the movie until we've completed this entire thing.
So yeah, I don't boys still in theaters. I was going to say, I think we know it's not a dollar theater in Pasadena.
Maybe the idea, I think, was that we were going if successful, we're going to go into the vacant AMC theater at downtown Disney.
We have to sneak in with the projector. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
With my projector and screen from home and like in the empty shell of a movie theater, we will watch a DVD or a stream of Good Boys.
Right. And then a bootleg, the Richard Jewel. Yeah.
And that will be in theaters, but we won't be able to get a print. Can I pitch a Funny or Die video? Oh, of course.
Always. I think if you like you were talking about it.
Oh, wow. Sector Cuber is a big fan of Funny or Die. Yeah, I always click funny.
That's good, because, you know, if our video is getting the crypt, our pay would be docked.
So we want those funny votes. Yeah, cut your rates significantly.
Yes. What's left to cut? But, you know, we're talking about it being the Jewel homophones.
If you did, you could do Richard Jewel, G-U-U-L.
Like if you did like a Richard Jewel trailer and it was about him, maybe the Jewel company getting in trouble.
Or blow it like there's a bomb that is caused by a bunch of Jewels all being set off at the same time. Yeah.
They could also do a video. They could do something with Jewel, the singer Jewel.
She made a couple. I made a video with her at Funny or Die. She's a Funny or Die All-Star Jewel.
Yeah, she's down to clown. And the Funny or Die All-Star means that you can get them in a branded video for a $200.
$200,000. So, right. So like a UCB actor is free.
And yes, it's $200,000. No pay.
Jewel would get $200,000. Yes. Sounds fair.
We saw it leaked Funny or Die memo.
I mean, they earned it. Their start. Yeah. Jewel and Alfonso Ribeiro are our superiors.
So they deserve it. OK, so that all we have. We've got some great video ideas.
Before we can make any of it, before we can watch Good Boys with you, what do we have to learn about?
Oh, boys, boys, today you have to learn about and discuss Pixar Pals parking structure, Magic Way pedestrian bridge in downtown Disney surface lots.
Wow. Surface lots. So we're back. We're back with another parking structure episode.
I'm thrilled. Yeah. Yeah. Here you are. Continuing the series. Yeah. It's too bad.
Like you're an interesting guy with a lot of opinions. People on your podcast look forward to having a lot of things you have to say.
I think people. Well, I don't know. I think it'd be interesting to talk to you about rides and stuff.
And it's just too bad that we're not allowed to hear what you think about any ride. They'll never happen.
Yeah. I mean, I think I'm OK with it, though, because for me, a big part of the theme park experience is you want a smooth arrival and a not too stressful departure.
Right. Good night. Yeah. You want to kiss. Good night. Exactly. And so it's that's part of the magic.
If it's just stress, like, you know, you go to a ball game or something or that that has like like a terrible parking situation and it's just like 40 minutes to get out of there.
No matter how much fun you had, it's just like it's exhausting at the end of the night and you're pissed off. You come out there with angry energy.
So, yeah, I think it's to me, it's an important part of the theme park experience. Yeah, yeah, sure.
I had an unpleasant I talked about this on the show not long ago, but I had a rare unpleasant experience leaving Disney where traffic was back all the way up through the Mickey and Friends Parking Structure.
And that is because somebody died on the freeway one exit north. Oh, my God. It didn't even shut down the entire freeway.
All it did was specifically fuck Disneyland because 10,000 people were leaving from that one point, like one exit down.
So that was that was pretty hellish. I'm not sure who to be mad at.
Probably. I mean, maybe the Jewel Corporation. I think he probably died from inhaling too much. Yeah. From too much fuel consumption.
Certainly. But now I guess I can't complain about that one because I ended up then just drinking alone in the empty Grand Californian lobby at 1 a.m. So it worked out for me.
But you're seeing that parking structure just full of the brim with cars was terrible. Disheartening. For sure. Yeah.
And you're absolutely right. And by adding this new parking structure, which they have recent like a lot of people on Twitter,
I think you've probably gotten a lot of people tweeting at you about the progress of this structure.
And I'm sure you appreciate that. And finally, it's here. Honestly, frankly, I've been getting hammered in my mentions since it was announced because I don't know if you guys recall this, but I very much recall it.
That when I appeared on the podcast initially to review the Mickey and Friends Parking Structure, I threw out one of my trademark Weiger locks.
My guarantee was when they made a new parking structure, they were going to rename it the Avengers lot and each level was going to be a different Avenger.
Unfortunately, that did not come true. They went with a Pixar pals theming. Yes. We were defeated by the power of friendship. Yeah.
So friendship, the theme between the two massive garages, pals and friends. Yeah. So it didn't. That didn't work out for me, unfortunately.
I mean, you would say that I would argue that the Avengers are maybe the ultimate group of friends. Yeah. But you know, whatever.
Well, they survived a lot. Yeah. So many more of them than there used to be. Yeah.
Mm hmm. I mean, they're going to make another giant parking structure eventually. It might go in the place they were initially going to do it, which is behind Harbor.
So do you want to make a prediction for next time they make a big parking structure? Right.
So I would say I'm going to say I'm going to stay away from Avengers because I think they don't want to lock themselves to a Marvel property. And I'm also going to stay away from Star Wars because I think that's maybe a little too obvious.
I'm going to say this is a little bit of a curve ball, but I think they're going to take Mickey and friends, Pixar pals. And the next step, the the DreamWorks dudes.
They're going to license the character. They're going to like the dream or this use the DreamWorks characters for the parking structure exclusively.
You're a donkey. Minions. Yeah. Well, no minions is illumination. Yeah. That's different from dream. Yeah, that's universal. They don't. Oh, they. OK.
Universal. Yeah. Oh, but no, DreamWorks is like your I mean, it's like Shrek. And Dragon. Yeah. I think how to turn your dragon. I think Epic is under that umbrella.
No, well, I mean, it's now Epic is actually Fox. OK. Epic is Fox. OK. So Disney, I believe owns Epic now. OK. I'm going to change my prediction because this is I'm realizing the DreamWorks properties I had crossed my head.
I'm going to say they're going to make it the Fox and Friends lot. So we call it Shep Smith. Shep Smith will be there. He's gone. He's gone. He's gone. He's gone.
Sorry. There'll be a Hannity level. They're going to have to change these names out frequently because he collects it so often. Brian Kilmeade. Brian Kilmeade will be on there.
The guy who they're like, this is our funny guy. Yes. Does this awful correspondent Greg Gutfeld. No, no. The other funny guy. Oh, you're talking about. Yeah. The guy who reads text from his mom, his liberal mom on the show.
There's a calling him a disgrace.
There'll be a Kennedy level. She's a prominent personality. Oh, that's right. Yeah. Dennis Miller. Is he on enough? I think he's in the family. Yeah. There might be like some just, you know, in the same way that the Luxo ball is used in the Pixar.
Oh, yeah. Dennis Miller might just be kind of be the face of the lot. A big revolving fountain of Dennis Miller's face. Right.
Okay. That's a that is a little bit left to center pick. I mean, a right of center pick actually. Right. You know. Okay. Well, that's a lot. Is that a lock? Are you giving that the wider lock? Okay. Great. We'll see. We'll see.
Twenty twenty two. Yeah. Never. I don't know when they're going to get it together.
Can I can I ask a legit question? Where would they build it? Do you have any any sense of the acreage that's reserved for another structure? Well, they were building. They're still building something behind Harbor. They were going to build this whole thing behind Harbor Boulevard.
And it was going to be like they weren't going to do Pixar pals there. I just flew a bunch of dog hair because I was petting Edwin.
They bought a bunch of industrial park kind of properties and they're demolishing it, but it requires create like you creating this weird path between hotels. There was going to be a pedestrian bridge over Harbor Harbor that was essentially going to show the businesses on Harbor, which is what the city was upset about. Right.
And instead of just saying, well, we'll leave a little space for them to walk down to go to the business on Harbor, Disney said, fuck no, we will not let the businesses on Harbor be patronized.
So they moved, which is why clearly this is why it's out of bounds. Disney does not want anything to do with the harbor businesses. And it's why it has to be a separate harbor hoedown.
And that can't couldn't have been part of the downtown Disney. Now you're getting it. Yes. Now I'm going to propose another idea, which is never doing the harbor.
Huh? Okay. But when people want to know what you think about Captain Kids buffet restaurant in Orange County. Wow. Captain kids favorite. Do you know about restaurant ratings though? They might be in a C or a D restaurants get ratings like you do.
It's at school. I forget if you ever went to school, but fake it's homework. Sort of. It's close that it's hard. Sorry to explain. Not quite, but yeah, kind of.
Yeah, we'll get that. We'll explain it off Mike. I think. Okay.
Is Captain Kid, is it a franchise? Are there more than one? I don't know. I feel like I've only seen that one ever. And Captain Kid is a pirate. I guess. Yes. Yeah. Is he a little kid pirate or is he an adult?
The more questions you ask, the more it's becoming likely that we have to do this. The boundaries are the metal detectors. Yes. Star Wars, Galaxy's Edge, Honda Odyssey. I have been clicking with the sector keeper this entire time. Thank you, SK.
All right. Well, I'd like to go ahead and say let's start with the surface lots. Let's go in reverse order and build to the grand Pixar pals parking structure. Okay, fair enough.
I'm looking forward to. Okay, so the surface lots. Now these are important because this is where you, if you're just going to downtown Disney, this is really where they want you to park.
The entrance is off of Magical Way. The lots. Magic Way. Sorry, Magic Way. Magic Way. Well, it is. I mean, it's magical. Sure. It is magic. Yes. Magic Way is the official road.
So they are the stitch lot. That's after you go past the guard booths. You make a left. That is on Google Maps labeled the stitch lot and their stitch lot signs.
Sure. And now what would that character sound like if he said Ohana means family? Ohana means family.
Okay, just checking in. Now to the right of the guard booths when you're going in is the limo lot. Unfortunately, we don't know what she sounds like. I'm not going to make you do that.
No. So this is where you're probably going to end up if it's not busy. And this is where they were going to build the first when they were going to build the luxury hotel.
The smaller version was going to get built on top of the stitch lot. Now, if it's crowded, you get sent down the road past the Paradise Pier Hotel, past the Disneyland Hotel, and you end up like in overflow lots, which when we went to Ralph Brennan's, that's where we got put.
Yes. And we were driving down with our guest Jason Walliner. And when we saw the sign saying, Oh, we're gonna have to go to the further lot, you in the back of the car were like, Oh, this will give us something to talk about. Yes. And I was like, will it?
I've parked here before. And I actually think it's pretty convenient. You just come out right by the Disneyland Hotel by like the Rose Garden.
Now, or they maybe forget about validation and you're just waving everybody through. That's happened. Yeah. Oh, that's nice. Yeah. Don't you know, don't count on. Yeah, because I left after Ralph Brennan and I when they first put the ticket in, it said forty six dollars, but it was validated.
Luckily, so it became zero. These are lying. Your heart really jumps in that moment. Yes, really scared. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Forty six dollars. That's like allowance for 10 years.
There's been a lot of inflation, though, since you were since you got locked in your state in the 90s.
And I go as far. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You know what? I know it's he's still at large. You know, we have to kind of dealt with Mr. Wager. Be careful. Your evil spirits are in play.
Well, you know, if he comes at me, the high guys got him covered. Oh, yeah. I forgot about. Yeah. I'm so glad we have we have your own inventory. I know you brought your own weapon.
Smartest guest we've had the overflow lots are the Zazu lot and the Simba lot.
And they all kind of blend together. Why does Zazu have a lot? It's a great question. Yeah. Organized and about rules.
But Simba. And epic takedowns of Donald Trump.
The new Zazu is not old Rowan Atkinson. He didn't care. He couldn't have foreseen the rise. Yeah.
I will say that just I think Natalie's parking my wife, my wife, Natalie, who came with me on our most recent trip and has come with me for most of my adult Disneyland adventures.
She was convinced that the entirety of the downtown Disney parking structure was the Simba lot like structure rather the surface lot.
She thought the whole surface lot was the Simba lot. And I think that it was because she we park there in the Simba lot one time and she just got that stuck in her brain.
But it is it is like kind of confusingly portioned out. It does get confusing because sort of gated like hotel parking around here, too, for all for most of the hotels, except the Disneyland one.
You went so you went down. Did you do a Disneyland trip or did you just go down and park and leave what for this episode? Yes. We parked and left.
Really? God bless. Yeah. Well, I mean, I had an experience of the Pixar Pals parking structure and I feel like I needed to get some firsthand experience.
So, yeah, we parked and left the downtown Disney service lot. I couldn't justify reparking there for that because I've had that experience before I parked there before.
So I'm familiar with it. Yeah. Yeah. And and it's been a little while since I parked in the down.
No, actually, I because I park for for doughboys, my chain restaurant podcast.
We went to the ESPN zone shortly before it closed for good. Oh, you made it in there.
We made it in there. And that was the last time I parked in the downtown Disney surface lot.
And it's fine. I just I feel like it's very bare bones, like very exciting about that lot, that that lot.
That's why we only have to do like 35 minutes. Yeah, we can limit our time.
It's like parking at a suburban Best Buy. It's like nothing. It's, you know, like a like a courtyard Marriott.
It's like a normal parking structure.
And you've eliminated a lot of the weird like the free hours and the ways you could kind of gamify being able to park at the park, go to the parks and park there for free.
So I have no interest in going in that like they they they cut off all of the free or cheap options, essentially.
So it gets very complicated with validations and stuff like you cannot.
If you go to a restaurant, one of the hotels you want to park at the hotel and the table service restaurants for that hotel will validate there.
They will not validate for downtown Disney. If you want to get validated for downtown Disney, you need to spend twenty dollars at a store or a quick service restaurant.
And that will get you three hours. If you go to a table service restaurant, they'll validate for five hours.
And this is kind of how they're preventing hacks, hacking the system to get free parking.
And Carly Wiseau gave us a very good tip. Of course, I am conflicted about it.
It's the Starbucks twenty dollar gift card loading.
And I would like to declare officially that has been a very mentioned thing during this ordeal on social media.
People in lockstep agreement with me about this being an injustice, having to do with apps and making you load 10, 15, 20 dollars instead of just letting you pay the amount you're paying on an app.
For sure. Very annoying. People agree with me. I have won this.
You're right, because they want to take the float. They want to basically be a bank and be taking the float on all that extra money that they have deposited in their accounts.
Three dollars and two cents. I have declared victory. I have declared victory.
Let me parse out a different issue here. I think you can take victory on that.
I think what I'm against less like, hey, if they offered customizable reloads, I'd be in support of that.
I think what I'm more against is you being upset about a different thing related to apps and math because you already have like a hundred of them in your brain at all times.
So to find a new one, well, that's just my brain.
But it's these companies wanting to minimize the number of credit card transactions because they get hit 20 cents or so a transaction.
I don't give a shit about lightning the load for like Target or Dunkin Donuts or something.
Yeah, target. Hey, that's don't speak ill of CEO Target Brian Cornell.
Well, he's the man with the target plan.
But I mean, it's the same thing as then like, do you want to round up and give some of the money to charity?
And it's like, no, don't do that. Just give the money to charity yourself.
They are getting the tax write off from that charity like, oh, you think I shouldn't do that?
I do that a lot. I mean, just just do it yourself.
Some real signaling there, wasn't it? No, I guess it was.
But I'm saying, is it a bad thing to do that? Well, it's the I mean, the money does go to charity.
But then like Target gets the tax that I see that going to charity is bad.
Yeah, I yeah, it's not like bad because bad, but it's it's your they're taking advantage of your goodwill as a consumer.
I honestly didn't think about this. Yeah, it's a similar sort of thing.
It's like, you know, I do it so often. I don't think about it.
It's like because I'm just and honestly, sometimes they'll be like upset because I try to get like they'll be like, sir, you can't give like an extra.
So that's more than your order. Yeah, I'll give like a 20 and I'll say just put this in it.
And they're like, you can't do that. Right. A check for a thousand dollars. Don't say it's very generous.
So interesting. Yeah, I also I know and Carlson, I know you do get a lot of like points for like airlines and hotels
and you're always using programs to donate those to veterans so they can go home for the holidays.
Yeah, I know that that's like very nice of you. But you like that's not your responsibility.
Well, it's just the thing that makes me feel good. Right.
But you're spending a lot of money that you don't need to spend to get more miles to send veterans home for the holidays.
I've been I also been driving veterans home. Yeah.
Well, that's the other thing, because, you know, you bought that that escalate and so you can transport more more veterans personally.
I think it's starting to affect you poorly. I mean, you said, can you bring over one of your old barrels and straps?
Because like I asked you if you asked to borrow one of my old barrels because you were like my clothes are threadbare
and I've given most of them to veterans organizations. You've got 10 or so. So you have one. Yeah. Yeah.
Here's the thing that there's a size difference between you and Sheridan that means that the barrel that you're borrowing from him is not leaving a lot to the imagination.
You're Donald Ducking it pretty hardcore. Yeah. Yeah. It's kind of like it's the barrel to kind of a halter top.
Yeah. It's just like a shirt. You still need pants. Yeah. You need separate barrel pants.
It's like a baby Huey barrel shirt. It's one thing if you're a duck, but you're a man.
I had to hide the Casamigos beefy tee t-shirt from our from our inventory.
You know, you were going to give it away. Oh, well, yeah. I want to charity.
Is that something in our inventory? Yeah. Randy Gerber's company with George Clooney, the premium tequila Casamigos tequila.
I would have tried to stuff it inside one of those red buckets outside of a store when someone's ringing the bell. Yeah. Yeah.
You got to just stop stuffing your possessions in those like this.
Don't go like you. I saw you trying to put a PlayStation 4 into the Salvation Army bucket.
The Salad, the guy ringing the bell was trying to stop you. Was he? I thought he was like trying to help.
No. Yeah. Taking my arm and he was pushing it in toward. I thought I didn't think he was actually pulling it out.
Helpful. Honestly, I think he was restraining you and saying, you don't need to do this. Huh?
Yeah. That's weird because I heard go good. You're doing the right thing. You hear the word away after go.
Oh, and you didn't just do that once. You took me around town. You said, keep the car running.
You distributed like a hundred PlayStation 4s. Tell those veterans, go to the bathroom later.
We got 20 more Playstations to give away. Yeah, look, I'll think about this now.
You've aggravated the people at the parking at Disneyland, too, because you were just like, everyone go ahead of me.
You keep saying, go ahead of me. And the parking attendants are like, no, sir, please just go and find a spot.
You don't need to let everyone. You are being polite. Yeah, but it's dozens and dozens and dozens.
But Jason's so frugal. That's expensive. Time is money to Jason.
And the face is crunching up. You know, you love to see it.
You love to see the bit about Mike being maniac, ending with Jason getting dumped on the prestige.
Oh, great. Great. We done with the surface lots? Oh, I don't know.
I will say I don't like that. It's the right like I like an angled park.
I don't like having to pull in at a full 90 degree up the perpendicular lines.
It's a tougher turn. It's tougher to back out. I just I don't love it. Sure.
Yeah, that place gets credit and it's a it's a parking lot next to a magical place.
So it should be more magical like the the magical perpendicular parking of Pixar pals. Right. Yeah.
Yeah. Give me that angle. What were you going to say?
I was going to say like it's all of this. It's outgrown the resort for sure.
Like it has said it is or that classic podcast race for sure.
Enthusiastic for sure. You guys are going to become the for sure.
Boys. Oh, boy. I can only dream rings needed on Tick Tock.
Will you like pop up in this for sure?
It's way more popular than this. I learned from the master.
Nick over here was my sketch one on one teacher.
Well, I heard that was a bit you guys thought of then.
Yeah, this is the thing is that part of being a sketch teacher is that you also you learn a lot from your students
and Sheridan brought that for sure thing to the table.
And I was like, this is I was like, I encourage you to like run with that.
Like that's your thing. You know, it's like Jeff Ross is like the roastmaster.
And for years he like didn't want to be the roastmaster general and eventually embraced it.
Like you got to run with your hook and you're sure is what you're we're all about.
But you guys needed to wait for the like the right medium.
You needed to wait for for technology to catch up, which is why Tick Tock is perfect.
And then you know, yes, yeah, for sure. For sure.
That was a little not. Yeah, you got to stagger.
You don't want you don't want people people to get comfortable.
The other thing we learned in sketch classes that by class to half the class drops out because they realize there's a lot of homework.
Yeah, maybe you're an adult with a job and you don't feel like having to spend a couple hours of your week writing a sketch.
For something that you paid for. That's not like a fun way.
Crazy. No. Yeah. Yeah. They need to build parking structures for the end.
These lots, honestly. Yeah. Right. I don't know if that's even in the plan.
I don't think we've heard anything. We haven't heard any on the rumor mill.
Anything about that. But I feel like it's it's got to come soon.
But like they want people coming to these places like Friday and Saturday nights on the weekends.
And it does suck when it's like you're getting routed all over. Yes, it's confusing and hard just to get like
a burger. It is. What are you going to?
But like how logistically it feels like closing that surface lot for enough time to build a structure seems like that seems
untenable. Yeah. Are you going to do that? I guess you'd have to do it in sections.
Well, it's kind of what they did to build Pixar Palace. I think like was was that previously a surface lot that was for employees
a lot that got it. Yeah, I believe it's employees and tram parking and stuff.
OK. Yeah. So I eventually these are all going vertical maybe.
And the and the Disney employees will be pushed further and further away.
Yes. I think some of them park currently at Angel Stadium. Wow.
It'll be like that'll become like the park at the Ontario Raceway.
It's like the Simpson episode where I think we've made this joke before or someone has the Homer rollerblades to work,
but he's parked right behind his own house. Yeah.
The power plant. Yeah, it'll. Yeah, it's I wonder if like once they build another giant parking structure,
maybe they could actually offer similar incentives for Pixar pals or making friends because now we'll talk about the walkway.
That makes it a lot more convenient, honestly. It used to feel like much more of a hike.
But this is really what allows us to talk about Pixar pals because it would have maybe been outside the bounds.
But with the addition of the downtown Disney pedestrian bridge, that now brings it that that literally connects it so that we're able to use it as a topic.
So thank God. Can I hear the official name of the walkway again? Jason.
You know, they just call it the pedestrian bridge.
But a lot of blogs are saying the Magic Way pedestrian bridge because that's what it crosses over.
But I've seen it as a downtown Disney pedestrian bridge. Yes. And other people calling it the downtown Disney pedestrian bridge.
We need an official word on this. It's not just the bridge, though.
That's is that that the only new part because it feels like the walkway is new as well.
Definitely. Yeah, they manicured it and and added a lot of lights and planting and stuff.
I like that bridge a lot. I love it. The bridge is fantastic.
Yeah, it was just I was like I texted Carlson that like while I was on it like this owns. It's very, very good.
I will say that Natalie was a little disappointed because she was expecting like the Golden Hand Bridge hands bridge in Vietnam.
Have you seen that? That it's this amazing structure where like two hands are holding up this this bridge.
She expected something that was like really grand and maybe thematically, you know, tied to Disney.
And it's not really that it's kind of a functional sort of thing. You might see it at a corporate campus, but it gets the job done.
And it's it's great. What I was feeling was and we got there in the late afternoon and you know, again, we we parked.
We took the pedestrian bridge to security. We turned around and then we left.
But I will say that the it must be great for families, for kids to get energy out on that pedestrian bridge instead of being like on the tram.
And they're just like they've got all this energy. They're like just like ready to go.
And then when they are unleashed in the park, they're just animals, you know, it must be nice that your young kid can kind of like run out a little bit of that before you get into the park proper.
Sure, sure. Get them sleepy a little bit. Yeah. Did Natalie need a lot of selling on doing this? Oh, she was furious.
No, yes. Relationship is free. Yeah, she ruined her Saturday. I will say that we.
The way I could hold her into coming along with me is that she we went to a restaurant that she really likes afterwards.
It's an orange county. So shout out to a God bistro. If anyone likes Vietnamese food, check it out.
I thought you were going to say Captain Kids Buffet. Well, so here's the thing. Captain Kids Buffet.
There was just a huge line. So we went there. That was our first choice.
And then we went to God Bistro as our backup. We hit we tried to go to Mimi's on Harbor Boulevard second. Also, like a 90 minute wait there.
So then we went to God Bistro. Yeah. And all people like dressed to the nines to fancy suit like real Hollywood agent types waiting to get in.
Yeah, I think there's a lot of big shots who are in the theme park industry who dine it.
You know, they have power lunches at at the Mimi's. So yeah, they have their booth.
You're beating with that crowd. Sure, sure. It's tough.
I do want to say I was incorrect. The Pumba lot is on the other side of the property.
The lot that closed to build Pixar pals. I'm still trying to get confirmation.
I think I just got my peas mixed up and it's the Pinocchio lot that closed. I think that is correct.
Yes, of course, of course. No wonder. That correction gives me strength.
You look scared ever since Pumba was said you were sort of like keeling over. I thought maybe you were going to die.
Thank you. Anytime there's a time lapse between a factual error and a correction on a podcast,
I just think of the listener who is just thinking about that for the entire duration.
Like the 12 minutes are passing and that's all they're thinking about is the Pumba lot was I am just praying to my God.
No one drove off the road out in fury. That incorrect inverting to character names,
two beloved characters who needs to start with peas. Their parents asking the police.
So what happened? But also that's poor show on Disney's part because the Pumba lot being on the other side of the property.
You're going to blame Disney for your mistake? Simba and Zazu lot. Yeah, why not? Poor show.
Poor show. Yeah, that is confusing. You're right. Speaking of poor show,
I kind of had that feeling with regards to the the aesthetics of the pedestrian bridge and particularly the walkway in that it just feels so generic.
Like and my guess is that that was a that was intentional.
I think that they were looking at it and were like, we don't want this to be a thing where we need we need there to be a flow of pedestrian traffic.
We don't want people to be stopping for photo ops. But there really isn't just any sort of hint of Disney at all.
It's just, you know, it's nice greenery, but it just feels like a like a nicely manicured sidewalk in a in a planned community.
Yeah. Yeah, it's it's boring. Yeah, it runs parallel to the monorail track at one point.
But if you don't hit it at the right time, it's just an empty track.
Yeah, that's there's there was no real exciting monorail encounter when we were walking it.
What would you say? I mean, I don't want to get to I guess we could do plus ups as we go.
Do you have a plus up idea off the top of your head?
I think if just a little bit of, you know, maybe even just like a like a light effect that's just like a silhouette of like Donald or something on the walkway, you know, just just like a little bit of a shadowy, you know, Mickey ears or something like that.
I don't know, just something that feels kind of Disney.
I guess like probably a standee would be too like the Apollo 13 standee at Universal Studios.
Yeah, that might be too much.
But I mean, I think there's some subtle Disney effication you could do of it.
There's one thing there is one thing there is a little like metal plate in the ground on the bridge that says no dumping to ocean.
And it is a kind of abstract representation of flounder. Okay. Right. So look for anybody taking this bridge. Look for that that little Easter egg. There is one character and it's a very tiny flounder.
But I think those are I don't know that that's exclusive to that bridge. I feel like there's more of those throughout the resort. Not a bridge exclusive. Not a bridge exclusive. Also not a Pixar character.
Oh, I see. Yeah. Yeah, you're right. It should be a good point. Yeah. So it should be I guess because it's connected to Pixar pals. It should probably be a Pixar. Should be Nemo. Yeah.
Yeah. Or there should be more. Now, did you let me ask you this. Did you go to tram loading? No, we did not go to tram loading.
Okay. I mean, took the took the escalator down to where that would be just to sort of get that escalator ride experience.
I'm not sure I'm just going to skip ahead to Pixar pals. But no, no, no, it's fine.
I think we're amblin over there. How did you get into the garage? Did you enter on Magic Way? Like it has its own entrance. We entered on Magic Way. Yeah. Yeah, we went.
I did the Maps app in the car straight for the the parking structure. So I just followed in. Oh, you can do that. You can enter it separately. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's not always open, though.
So I think it's open. It depends. I honestly they don't have hours posted. I tried to go in last time, not open. I had to enter through Mickey and friends.
But it looks like that's a much better way to enter. Yeah, it was pretty convenient. I mean, again, we went it off hours, but on a weekend and it was pretty it was pretty easy to get in there.
I will say that we so so here's a little bit of a of a of a specific to the vehicle we just acquired. We got a Chevy Bolt, which is a an EV.
And so Natalie had the idea of like, hey, let's see if they have EV charging. We didn't need a charge, but just to sort of see what they had.
And so we went up there. The the cast member working in the parking structure entrance was very, very helpful. And we we asked, like, hey, is there EV charging? And he was like, yes, it's on the third level, but there's no guarantee that there will be available.
And so but so here's what happens. Have you have you guys parked an EV there before? Yes. My guess. Yeah. So you get the little blue. I took a picture of it.
And in case you need for your social media, but you get like a little blue thing they put on your windshield. And that tells another cast member later on to guide you specifically to the EV level. Right.
And so unfortunately, this is a thing I've learned in my short time owning an EV. One complication is, yeah, you don't have to get gas, but you do have to deal with Tesla assholes at fucking charging stations.
And that's a big thing, especially if they're in short supply and they're like it was basically all Teslas like all of them. And so there wasn't a free one. But we also had another and I'm sorry for monologuing a little bit here, but we had a we had a little encounter with a Tesla asshole.
So we went up to we're going through they wind through the cones are a little confusing. Level three was blocked off. So the guy had to like move cones to guide us over there. But he saw our blue tag like a little late and was like and so we stopped and he was telling us to back up. But this Tesla SUV was like parked right behind us.
And so we turned on our, you know, our reverse lights. The guy would not budge and he was just like sitting there and we were like trying to gesture at him and he was just like, you know, kind of give him one of those. I'm just give the expression I'm making is like is like, what are you going to do?
You know, he's getting one though. You kind of the cast member came over and was like was like, sir, can you please back up? And the guy was still not budging. And he was like, sir, I'm just asking you to back up a little bit so they can get up to the third level.
And it was like a whole ordeal. And eventually he like kind of like got pissed off way agreed to back up like as little as possible. And then we we zoomed up there and the cast member came up to us and we were like, thank you.
So we said it nicely. We're like, thank you. Thank you so much. And the guy, the cast member goes, that guy was an asshole.
Whoa, the Disney cast members. Bad words. Sometimes it feels good. Sometimes it feels good to be bad. But that guy must deal with a lot like, you know, panicked parents and he must deal with a lot of stressed out people in the structure for him to really be like, that's the that guy was that bad.
I was like, yeah, that sucks. He handled it very well. It also seems like they did not build enough EV station. They definitely did not. Because you've run into this a couple of times now. 100%. Do not plan on charging your car there.
There's there's an outside chance one will be available, but more it seems like they're mostly going to be occupied. Yeah. And the app also tells you because there's different apps to tell you if there's a charging station nearby.
And the Apple sometimes be wrong too. It'll say if it's green, it usually means there is available. But that is not the case with the Disney. Because I checked two two days ago. Not available. Like it said available. Not available. I think there's like 20 spaces. Yeah, there's not enough.
I think part of it too might be I didn't have any reception inside the Pixar Palace structure. So it could be that maybe there's some, you know, connectivity issue with the stations. I don't and the app updating. I have no idea.
They what they should do because they they they I depends sometimes they load from the top down. I feel like sometimes they load from the top up. I don't know. But they should have them on two levels. So maybe you get your first like bunch of cars that come in and do it. And then like a few hours later when they're finally loading on the top. They're loading you up there and then there's more available for people to come midday or later. Because people that park in the morning are parking there probably all day. Yes. So they don't need to be there all day, but they're not going to come back and move their car.
So I do keep it. What do you think of that plan?
Vehicles are electric now. Yeah, some. Some are. Yeah, it's a it's a magical world. First couple first few generations of them, you know, plugins. I mean, oh, wow. So you like plug them into an outlet like a Nintendo. Yes. Yeah, like a Nintendo, I guess.
And driving a car is like driving a big Mario cart. Oh, yeah. No shells, though, not equipped with shells. Mr. Weigert, will you take me driving? Sure. Give him lessons. We're going to.
We can borrow Carlson's SUV. There's some veterans like there's veterans in the escalator right now. They're in the escalator.
They're honking. They're not trapped. I left them some trail mix in there and they obviously they know how to like survive. Well, is the window because it's like kind of hot outside is the window lock on because you might you might have trapped a bunch of veterans in a hot car.
The window lock is on. Yeah, see. Yeah, that's an issue. Yeah.
Can you lower it via an app or do you have to go physically out there? I can download the app. I have to download it. All right. All right. So that's less. I don't have to break from the pug. Yeah. They'll be fine.
I will say about the Pixar pals parking structure. I don't love the theming because the theming instead of being based on instead of each level being a character, each level is a movie. Yeah. It's just like that's it's harder to remember for some reason. And it's also not on it doesn't connect with what we've established with the Mickey and Friends parking structure. It's not a true second beat of the parking structure.
Because it's because of the pals like it's like Mickey and Friends Pixar pals. Obviously, you're saying it's friends. But yes, it should be single single characters or if they're a duo together like Chip and Dale or something.
Well, it's duos and trios like pals hanging out together. Right. Until Inside Out. Because Inside Out is just Inside Out and the little emblem they use at least in the whatever sign I'm looking at is abstract. Yes. Inside Out is not. Those aren't pals. What emblem are you? Well, oh, you're looking at a different. Yes, I am. We should have coordinated our Pixar pals parking emblems. Yes. But the emblem doesn't matter. The point is Inside Out is not friends. There are friends in the movie.
But you would not call that group of people Inside Out. No, for sure. So level one Incredibles level two Coco level three cars level four Monsters Inc level five Finding Nemo level six Inside Out. We parked on level three cars. Again, I just wanted to be the Cruz Ramirez level or something like just give it just take a character.
Give me the give me the Lightning McQueen level. Give me something because it almost feels like they're not trusting Pixar's property. That's what I was going to break out characters enough. And I think they're wrong. Yeah, people know that level two.
They would recognize the characters of Coco and the Bone Man, a character I was doing. I cannot remember his actual name. So I was doing he goes by Coco and the Bone Man. Well, Ben, you're also you prove my because I always when I see the boy, I call him Coco.
But that is not Coco. Yeah, I've seen the film and I know that's not true. But still, every time my knee jerk is, oh, look, Coco. I forgot his name is not Coco. Yeah. So yeah, you.
I don't know that name offhand, but the other guys for sure the Bone Man. So this is why this is answering the question. People don't know these characters. You don't think people know like, OK, first off, they're they're not including Toy Story at all.
And I assume that's because they already have a lot. Yeah. Yeah. So so that's like that makes it a little bit difficult because those are their most identifiable characters. Yeah. I still think Mike and Sully like people know those characters from from Monsters Inc.
But what is Nemo's father's name? I've been sitting here trying to think of it. Does anyone know what off the top of the head? I don't know it. Marlin. Marlin. Yeah. OK. Oh, yeah. Actually, that's kind of a funny joke. Yeah, it's funny.
But I thought I thought he was just Nemo's dad. I didn't realize he had a character. I think so. Yeah. Dory. People know Dory. They can have a Dory. Dory. I would think would be the most.
But you could not. Besides Mater, you couldn't do. I don't think Dory Marlin Nemo. No, you would get confused between the fish. Yes. I think you take one character from each of the properties and then you just like make it like that's the the equivalent of finding Nemo level is the Dory level.
You know, and people or the Nemo level and people will associate it with that property, with that franchise. And then also they have a character that they can remember. And that's fun. Unless you take one of Pixar's most beloved franchises and just name it all based on that.
And that is the good dinosaur. Sure. Sure. You have the Arlo level, the thunder clap level, the downpour level, the closest I ever came to walking out of a movie.
The cold front. Just remembering all your files. You know, forest wood brush, Purvis. You know that thing when you start making a movie and you hire a voice cast for an animated movie and then the entire cast leaves or gets fired and they get replaced by a different voice cast.
And that also happens with directors and writers. That did that happen in this. Yes. Yes. But I so but in my head, Steve Zahn will always be thunder clap.
How could it have been someone else? I read something a while back and I don't think this was an I think it's been said a million times, but like I hadn't seen it before that.
Like most Pixar movies are about people doing their jobs and your job is your life and the job of the dinosaurs to suck shit.
Wow.
I got so mad and the catchphrase, the line in that movie that they keep repeating that is supposed to be like pathos is like you are me and more.
And I'm just sitting in a movie theater, just move squarely in my seat, just going like, I hate this. I can't.
There with Tomorrowlands, there are two wolves.
I saw it too. I just refuse to believe that there was ever anyone else as Bubba besides Dave Boat.
See, but what you vote born to be Bubba.
Okay, so they fucked up, obviously. I wonder if they did like a survey. They do surveys about everything. So they probably did like an average survey of like, who is this to people?
And it was coming in under a certain percentage. That's my guess. I mean, I think you need to remember the character to know where they parked. No, I get.
So that's like I would imagine like if if dads were scoring under 50 percent on recall, right? Who is this dad? And then he's like, I had that car, the junk car, the car, the junkie car.
But I think that Lightning McQueen and Mater are probably the two most recognizable besides Mike Insali. I think Mater is number one.
Mater, I think, is probably number one. Dory, number two. They did a quiz and dad like didn't get he scored zero. He didn't get any of them until Mrs. Incredible came up.
So I do declare Mrs. Incredible. Her name is Helen. Helen is her name.
The guy by the escalators doesn't even list the Incredibles as level one because there is no escalator for level one, obviously. So it's just the Luxo ball. Oh, yeah.
OK. But yeah, it is clearly when you're walking around, there's incredible signage. Yes. But do we like that ball? The ball fountain? Yes. That's neat. I think it's cool. It's a nice photo.
I mean, that's a very Instagram like photo op sort of thing, I think. I will say that I don't think the ball is as iconic as the Mickey ears.
And they're using the Mickey ears. I mean, obviously, what is the Nike swoosh, I guess, but the McDonald's M. But the Mickey ears are like the iconography of the Mickey and friends.
And then they're using the Luxo ball for the Pixar pals. I don't know. I guess what else would you use? There's really nothing that's equivalent to the mouse ears.
And the lamp is already used in various places. Yeah, the lamp wouldn't work. I guess it's pretty good. I mean, it is a very you don't realize how recognizable it is.
John Lasseter with outstretched arms waiting for a hug.
You should enter V. You should enter under John Lasseter's arms. You're driving your car in to get a hug.
Every now and then the music is interrupted to say, where my hug at? Probably one of the worst phrases in the English language.
Did he say that? I don't know. I think that's just the thing. That was from an affidavit or something. Is that a phrase? Where my hug at? Where my hug at?
That's a thing like sad dudes say. Is it? Yeah. That does sound familiar. Yes.
The kind of guy who's only physical contact with a woman is like via the unspoken thing that like you hug any female acquaintance. Hello or goodbye. Right.
There are those. So this is a friend of mine I could picture who's like that's like his one chance is that. Yeah. That like owed hug.
I don't believe in and I try not to do. I hear it. Makes me uncomfortable. I like to I like to give handshakes to everyone.
But people are some people are expecting a hug. And so that interaction is hard to navigate. I will say that the other thing that that you'll see from that that kind of guy is the unsolicited unsolicited shoulder rub.
Like just like kind of going behind of like oh yeah. You're tense. You know and just start start giving a girl. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Don't you don't do that. I know. Don't do that.
Well you have good manners. Yeah. You just inherently know even though you died in the fountain before the meeting. Yeah. Everyone should know.
We were talking about the Luxo ball a little bit and they kind of carry that through the rest of the garage.
And then yes into the statue the trash cans here you can see how it the floor the elevator has it.
That's good. I think that's a big thing. A lot of people are commenting on this this garage a lot more elevators than the McKeith Friends.
What like it's easier to navigate. Yeah. Three instead of one more elevators although I'll say we parked in a in a middle aisle and we're like oh here's an elevator and went over to it.
And it was a cast members only elevator. Oh great. Very like I felt naughty. Someone make fun of you.
No one made fun of me but like there were no there was no one in there was just us in there and then we were just like oh wait the buttons aren't working.
And then we saw the sign and it felt. Yeah I think if I was a if I was a guest I'd be a little confused and peeved. Sure.
I don't think there. Yeah there's I don't use the elevators a lot. I mean obviously they're probably for like kids strollers and stuff. Yes. More.
So I guess I should have done some better journalism and done all the elevators to make sure they should have done each and every. Yeah. And the escalators kind of all are in the spiral sort of.
I like the spiral spiral spiral spiral fan and it's I think it's a better cooler setup than the Mickey and Friends just big escalators.
It's got kind of an architectural landmark now. Yes. It looks better. It looks I also like I like the greenery on the roof and then the if you look from the outside the lighting on the levels is different.
There's a different coloration which which is very pleasing to the eye. To me the comparison is because it very it very much is just another Mickey and Friends but just a little nicer. Yeah.
It is kind of like the win and the encore in Vegas. It's just like they built another one right next to it and then it's just like a little newer.
So it's a little classier a little snazzier. Sure. But they you know they need to like pair well they need to seem like two parts of the same whole. Yes. You wouldn't want to go radically different for sure.
For sure. And also they they do connect these garages connect and the Pixar pals doesn't have an exit. No. You enter the Mickey and Friends garage in order to exit. That was confusing. Yes. That was we were we were going to the exit.
And then Ali was driving and we were making turns and she was like wait so is there no exit. I was like oh because we're now in Mickey and Friends and we're like what do we go the right way or did we just get turned around and then we eventually gleaned that that is the only exit that it has a separate entrance but not a separate exit from Mickey and Friends. Right.
Which maybe maybe does that get backed up. I don't know. We weren't there at Prime Hours. Absolutely. So it does get backed up. So I don't know. Yeah I don't know what that what the thinking behind that was. I think there is a way to get out the way you come in on Magic Way but I don't know if they just never route people that way.
Yes. Didn't we leave that day when we were down there with the Sector Keeper. I'm trying to think did we leave. I have video going out the other way. Oh yeah. It can be done. It can be done but maybe they just never have it open. Maybe it's rare that it's open.
I get bummed in both of these lots every time anytime you're like ready to go and if you're especially if your car is a little close then you probably have to do the most circuitous like longest path all the way back around. Right. Doing doing that big giant loop and then having to merge with cars again is annoying.
But that's something that annoys me after I you know have gone to Disneyland for the fifth time in a month. So so a tiny thing to complain about. I think honestly yeah I think like it's a little annoying but the only thing is bad and it hasn't happened to me is when that thing is backed up like crazy which I've seen videos where that thing is like crazy like you're just stuck in a gridlock. But maybe they do open the other exit if that's the case. I don't know. It was I believe this lot was open when I had that when I was there for that disaster day with the freeway.
Issue. And it was horrible. It was like it totally affected Pixar Pals. They had no way to get out of there. Yeah. I mean I think they want people thinking of this as just one big parking structure because you know there's that speed ramp that sort of goes right to the parking garages in the morning and exit the garages at night. You know there's not a separate. There's one entrance.
Excuse me for Pixar Pals you're in your time. No I got all. I'll tell the Randy Gerber story again. Well that's Jason's story to tell I would never take that away from him. That's his favorite story where you just get a million dollars from your friend. Jason were you drinking out of a canteen.
What is that. I have one of the swells. That's how it's an old school. It's one of those like a wood finish on the bottle I see.
Oh boy. You all right?
Take a sec.
Set it this out.
Sorry, just something caught in my throat.
It's a touching subject, so.
We're all on edge.
Okay. I think you were saying the speed ramp in was the last thing.
Yeah. The speed ramp in that they switch around at night to get people out.
Take another minute.
I'm okay.
It sounded like you were really struggling to get those words out.
I've recovered.
Just like I sounded where I did, I did all the stage directions for a table read.
Oh yeah.
Which is a lot of talking. You're talking more than anybody, but I did very well.
I didn't mess up one word of the thing. I was like, this is crazy.
I don't know how I'm doing so well. I am on fire.
And then it got to the end and I made it and the director said, Hey, geez,
and thanks Scott for getting through all those words.
And I was like, and I coughed my lungs out right there.
Like I made it all the way to the end until the end.
And then that's saying what this project was.
Molly Shannon was there and laughed at me.
Said, Oh, that's so sad.
I did. I did stage directions at a table read once and it is, you know,
it is exhausting and mentally taxing and also not fun because you're like,
you don't get to read any jokes or anything, especially for comedy.
But, but afterwards, the, the one bit of gratification I got is that afterwards,
Chris Parnell looked at me and was like, Hey man, great job on those stage directions.
And I was like, Oh, okay. I'll tell you.
Somebody with one of the best voices in the biz.
Who's got better pipes than Parnell?
Yeah, geez. That's true. Very good.
That's why he's the hamburger helper.
I do like that. He's that.
And I like the hamburger helper.
I will say I like him too. Yeah. Yeah.
Jason's favorite character in fiction.
He helps hamburgers be made.
Mine is the hamburger helper.
Yours is Henry from country bears.
Nah, yeah.
It's a nine way time.
All the bears.
I think what I was driving at is they just want people thinking of like,
just follow the signs for Disney parks parking.
They don't want weirdos like us going like, well, I'd rather park in the Pixar pals.
They have the indicator lights and they haven't retrofitted all of Mickey and friends with the indicator lights yet.
Yeah. So the indicator lights are a red and green light that tell you if somebody's in the spot.
So you can be able to see down a row how many, like you can see, Oh, it's mostly red.
I shouldn't go down this road.
It's not exact.
No, it's not.
There's not one light per one spot.
Yeah. It's imperfect.
These are always annoying.
Yeah.
I think it's a thing that seems great in theory, but in practice, because the accuracy has to be there.
And because there's enough of a fail rate where sometimes a red is unoccupied or sometimes a green is occupied,
it adds to the frustration in terms of searching for a space.
It reminds me of being at the Century City Mall, which I don't know your feelings.
I am always annoyed to be there.
Yes.
Especially that lot.
That lot is horrible.
And I got really lost in there once. I got lost for like half an hour.
A truly cavernous and confusing lot with it's, because I think it's...
So many entrances, as many ways and levels to go on.
You're talking about the Westfield Century City Mall?
Yes.
Yeah. Yeah. It's crazy. That one's crazy.
It's confusing. And I try to take the bus when I go there, partly because I don't want to have to deal with that parking.
But you sometimes have to go there because it has an IMAX screen.
And it's like the... For instance, when I saw The Hobbit 2 in a high frame rate, that was the one theater that was offering it.
So I had to suck it up.
Howard Hughes, no IMAX?
Howard Hughes does have it.
But they don't always play it.
They are always showing the same things. Yeah.
Well, so fuck the Century City Mall. No ordeal about that. I'll say that right here and now.
Yeah. I don't think there's a there's a much reason to do an ordeal for that one.
Right. So we're all in agreement, right?
We're all in agreement. It's just down the list, way down the list.
That's all this does.
Just way down. Yeah. I agree. It's not coming up in the next two years.
It'll be in 2041.
I'll say this. The Pixar pals, I mean, I think we've all gotten lost to Mickey and Friends at one point or another.
It doesn't help. It's technically kind of two garages connected by like foot bridges.
The Pixar pals just one garage.
And I think that is why the Pixar pals is around five thousand spaces, whereas Mickey and Friends is around ten thousand spaces.
Oh, wow. So it's like it is half the size.
I didn't realize that. They look like they're the same.
They look like they're the same. Yeah.
Let's let's get negative here.
The lighting sucks in the Pixar pals versus Mickey and Friends. It's dim.
You think so? It is dim. I don't know why it's so dim.
It's weird. They spent all of their lighting money at the tram loading on the ground floor.
Which is the best part, I think, of all of this is tram loading now down in these parking.
Because tram loading is, bless you, tram loading has music.
There's like music playing and it's got characters on the wall and it's a much more pleasant experience than tram loading ever used to be.
Yeah, it kicks off your Disney party. Party begins before you leave the parking garage.
That's right. And then you get to see some of you could see the outlines like what you're talking about, which should be on the bridge.
They're doing in the loading area. They've got pictures of Pixar friends.
Silhouettes. Silhouettes.
Point of much conversation when this garage first opened, because there was this weird blobby thing and everyone like, what fucking character is that?
And then they fixed it and it was clearly supposed to be Eva. Oh, OK. Wally.
But her arms were closed. She just looks like a manatee.
Yeah. And everyone's like, is this a new character? Is this how they tell us? Oh, that's a little leak.
But it was just a bad job. And they had Forky ready to go real fast after.
Oh, it's opened around the same time as Toy Story 4 and new characters already represented.
Uh huh. That's fun. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So that's that's the best place. And that's not that's got a mood like that's got like Virgin America airplane lighting in there.
Yes. Yeah. Which is fun. Dear Depart, Fallen Brother, Virgin. Yeah. Good airline. Yeah. Very good.
There was one good airline. It had to be taken away. Yeah. It really sucks. That was really fine.
I think Absinthe on a airline flight once. Oh, yeah. You did Skoll. Oh, man.
Well, you do that on all airlines. Yeah. Virgin. They did come. Yeah.
And they gave you they can you can order dip from your console in front of you the screen.
Make a flight attendant. Was the Epstein plane Virgin America. Yeah.
All I know is I'm sure. I'm sure Richard Branson was on whatever plane it was. That's all I know. Seems right.
Yeah. So I don't know why. I mean, it would be nice if they would do like this cool lighting in the parking structure.
I guess that's too much to ask. But just give me some more light. I don't know what the hell is wrong.
It was oddly dim in there. And I attribute it to the time of day we were there. We're kind of like, you know, the sun was starting to come down.
And so I was like, oh, maybe it's not fully lit. But that is to hear that that's just how it always is.
That's interesting. That's that is definitely a negative. Yeah.
People on message boards blame Bob Chapek for this for cheaping out on lights because maybe you need to double the lights that granular of decisions.
According to the lights, according to Mouse chatter dot net message boards.
Yes, he does. He's responsible for all of it. I mean, wherever they can cut costs and maximize profits, that seems to be like the company's thing for the last 20 years.
But what if people get robbed or children are abducted? I don't care.
I'm Chapek as long as I have their money. Yeah. And the rest of their lives on a sex boat.
I mean, there is I read something that like when attendance is up, that, of course, causes petty crime to ride, you know, in the park.
Well, just in the property in general, like in Florida, when there's more people there, speaking of crime, as Jason and I were walking back to my car.
Oh, yeah. We saw two empty white clock hands. Oh, boy. In the Pixar pals parking structure.
So there was petty crime. Someone was partying. Someone was in that person wasn't around, almost like they disappeared like a ghost.
Hmm. I don't know.
Let's just say I needed to refresh a little. Are you drinking White Claws Sector Keeper? I tried a few.
Bad man Nick Mundy gave me White Claw. Oh, he did. Oh, God. I believe it. Yeah, I believe it, too.
He said he said you want to be like one of the good boys. And he meant the movie Good Boys, not us good boys.
No, yeah. He meant Tremblay. Did you did you go like on an adventure with him or something?
What did you go to Vegas with him to see Steve Miller Band? Yeah, that's exactly what we did. Oh, man. You knew it.
Hey, yeah. He was floated that idea to me, but then it all of a sudden just never came up again. Yeah, he picked me up and gave me a variety pack of Kodiak chew.
Wow. White Claw flavored white flavor chew. That's really gross. I know it was a bad decision. Don't tell my parents.
OK, we won't. We will. This is really this whole thing is very shocking to me that Nick Mundy followed up on something he suggested.
Huh? This is very, very hot. My experience.
I don't know a way out of this. Well, I guess I should say apologies to Nick Mundy for tagging the wrong Nick Mundy on Twitter for tagging a member of the band Sister Sledge.
Great. That's what we have to apologize for.
Nick Mundy.
He does not play in the band Sister Sledge. It's like Warren Ellis. It happens. It's like Warren Ellis, the comic book writer and Warren Ellis from Nick Cave's band, that sort of thing. I'm assuming happens a lot.
Sure. We're very good to the person who suggested we do this podcast. Yeah, sure. We really treat him with the highest respect.
And look, we all love Mundy. Mundy's great. Yes, of course. And he's just he's busy because he's hanging out with so many Ghost Children. It's true. Yeah. Joy rides with Ghost Kids. You got lucky this one time.
So the Virgin America, we have to really wind back here. We were talking about Richard Branson. Do we have to wind down? Well, I was just getting riled up.
So, yeah, I think that like that's the best part of it is for sure the tram loading, the circular thing, the lights got to change. The indicator lights, they have to figure that out. I get the idea of it.
This is you being riled up. Yeah, my adrenaline is pumping.
I've never been in a parking situation where those green and red lights functioned correctly. I've never been in one where it's just like, oh, this is as accurate as it needs to be for this to be a bonus, not a hindrance.
I also think often when you go to the Americana at Brand and Glendale that when they tell you how many spaces are filled, I don't think that's accurate. Oh, yeah. In the least, which is another thing to say bad about the Americana at Brand and therefore at Americana at Brand memes.
Yes, I agree with that. Try to defend that one. Just try. Valiant effort this week, but nice try. Try again.
Yeah, fake, fake parking. I was gonna say news, but it's not news. It's statistics, I guess. Fake stats, fake stats, unreliable.
Fake board, fake digital display. Yeah. I think the ceilings in Pixar, pal, a bit lower. A little lower. A little lower. It makes me feel a little more claustrophobic. Lower and darker. Everyone's favorite quality is about a parking garage.
Yeah, I don't know. Again, is that a Chapec cheapen out? He's like, no, cut the height of the ceilings. Cut the cement budget. Precious cement. Are there more levels than the Mickey and Friends of the same height? Same heights. Same numbers. Same height.
The weirdest thing about it is they have to be even, so what's the point of the lower ceilings? Yeah, I don't get it. It doesn't make sense to me. We should have had a construction worker on here to tell us what was the thought behind it. Let's pause, go out to the street, find one.
Okay. They're actually one of the veterans in my car. I bet whoever we find, oh yeah, get one of the veterans. Yeah, he worked construction in the military, so he could maybe tell us. He's stuck in your car. Yeah, he's fine. I'm driving him home later. He's fine.
He's driving to Santa Fe, New Mexico.
We're going to stop in Vegas too. Go see Steve Miller. Park MGM. Money of season tickets to Steve Miller in Vegas. Should I sell my seats this week or you want to come along, Duder?
Subletting your Stephen Miller van. Did you say Stephen Miller? Oh no, I didn't mean that. Oh, the joke? Stephen Miller van. Another Funny or Die video. Oh yeah. People would love that. Got some blowback for that one.
What's the Fly Like an Eagle parody? Fly Like a White Nationalist. Fine. Yeah, good enough. Yeah, we got three more of these to crank out today. We can all agree. Great exposure though. Very good exposure.
You're getting so savvy, Sector Key. Our careers took off after it. Yeah, if you appeared in a video next to the Steve Miller, or perhaps in this case, the Stephen Miller, a man willing to still do a Funny or Die video. Right.
Stephen Miller as himself or you start off like, hey, we're going to cast, we're thinking we're going to get Brendan Fraser to be Stephen Miller and then eventually you settle on, hey, we've got a guy who knows French Stewart.
French Stewart's friend is going to play Stephen Miller. You know, I was going to be shot in a big mansion and like with a bunch of cranes and swooping cameras and they said, can we do it in front of green screen? Can we do it in 15 minutes?
Also, can we put the green screen up at your house? We don't have any issues with office space. Can you cook craft service, please?
Oh, yeah. Good exposure. Right. Good exposure. Great exposure. The Hicks are pal. I mean, they needed more parking for years. Yes. They needed more parking, but then they went and opened a Star Wars land that somehow course corrected the overcrowding problems of Disneyland.
They killed the park that killed so they don't need they could implode this now, but we're going to hit Christmas. So it's crowded. I've been seeing things filling up to capacity like parking has been filling up to capacity lately and Halloween got it going. So obviously they needed it anyway.
If we weren't it seemed pretty full. We were routed to the third level because specifically because of the reason. But it's if we looked at how the cones were laid out, it looked like they were taking us up to six or seven, whatever the highest level is.
So it looks like that was that was where cars were being cordoned off to. Yeah. I mean, it's so it's necessary. It's not like this thing sitting empty. Yeah. So I mean, the problem is, I do feel I'd love to fully say this is slam dunk way better than Mickey and Friends.
But the fact that I feel like it's dark and and low, like it feels when the actual parking experience itself, this is a core. If we're talking about the parking experience itself, we've had difficult times with this electric vehicle stuff.
Yes, it's less. It's less good parking. Yeah, this is the meat of the experience. Yes. Less good parking than when you park in Mickey and Friends. But you're probably right. Is that a trade off with a much better tram loading and security security experience?
Because there are cues now for like get in this row for the tram. There's people fighting on roads. There's pleasant music playing. It's the most pleasant security gate. I would say. Yeah, I agree. 100 percent. Get backed up. So I did a back. I was I went with my mom and the backup was so like we lost like an hour, hour and a half. At the tram? Yeah. Wow. Really? Yeah. I don't know if just that day was insane. That's right. I've never seen that. Yeah. And like it was very unclear. Like like some like you didn't know where a line was.
You didn't know where a line began and ended and I don't know. That's frustrating. Yeah. Yeah. My mom passed away. I buried the lead there. Fainted and I should have reported that on the bucket. Yeah. Bury the lead on that one. Yeah. Jesus. Just give up. Why keep trying? Like Joe Biden.
No way. I like it. All the way to the White House. I was going to say Padme Amidala. Oh, yeah. It was like Padme. Yeah. Just quit. Biden's kind of like Padme. They're the very similar figures.
In effectual. Biden kind of looks like Anakin before he was put in the Darth Vader. His eye is pretty banged up in that third movie.
That's the sin. But just before election, they got to put him in some big suit and then it'll be funny. Yeah. How's he looking there? Don't worry about it.
I'm going to say this. I've only been in this garage a couple of times now. I feel like there's probably not enough signage for the pedestrian bridge because you have to use level two.
One pedestrian bridge is on level two. And I think if they put up more signage that would cue more people to like, oh, let's just walk. Let's just walk. Let's skip the. It's confusing to the point where I was. We were wandering through the garage.
We ended up at that cast member elevator, which I mentioned. We started actually doubling back towards the Mickey and Friends lot because we're like, maybe it's that way. And I just I Googled it and I didn't have like there wasn't clear.
So I texted Carlson, like, where's the pedestrian bridge? And then he was like, oh, you have to go down to level two. We're on level three and you have to take the stairs.
Like you have to go all the way to the end where the escalators are. Take the stairs down to level two and then or I guess you could take an escalator down there depending if you wanted to go all the way down and then back up.
Yeah. And then and then and then it's accessible. So it's very unclear how you get there if you're a novice. Yeah. And it is. And the best thing bridge is great. And I would just say like in terms of the the if the Pixar pals lot, even though it's got some negatives as compared to the Mickey and Friends lot needs to exist for that pedestrian bridge to exist.
Then it's worth it because that pedestrian bridge is great. Sure. But it is confusing in terms of how to get there. More signage would be very helpful. I think to the dedicated security at the tram loading and dedicated security by the old ESPN zone where if you cross the path from that the ends the pedestrian bridge walkway, you get your own security right there.
And it's separate from the security for the people coming from the Disneyland Hotel. So I think that is smoothing things out a little more security checkpoints. I didn't realize that and realize that was his own cue. So we're seeing that Pixar pals is more.
It's a little worse. It's a little more confusing, a little more unpleasant than the other parking garage we've addressed. I'm just saying from the outside. It's all nice. Yeah. There's some decent things about it. But on the whole, more it seems like it's kind of a little encapsulation of the downtown Disney ordeal itself.
Less than the last one. Got it. More confusing. Yeah. But a lot of high points. More polish. Yeah. Maybe that's not true.
We kept notes. I kept some notes.
Remembered what the items were. You used three pieces of loose leaf paper. Yeah. A couple of loose white claws, just like we had a couple of episodes where we were drunk.
It's still possible on this episode. Yeah, we got time.
So yeah, I think that honestly the good stuff that it ushered in is worth the less good parking experience. Yeah. So overall, it's a net positive for sure. But I do think if they could just brighten that up, if they brighten it up, it's really that's most of the battle.
They can't. I don't think they can raise the ceilings. Well, again, we should ask that construction veteran, that guy who used to, you know, work as a foreman. He probably would know if logistically you could raise the ceiling. I'm guessing you're right. I'm guessing it would be impossible.
Yeah. Oh yeah. Very hard. But they could definitely add some signage in terms of how do you get to the pedestrian bridge. That feels like a thing like paint something on the ground. Like paint like a big like like this way pedestrian bridge. Yeah, for sure.
For sure. I think it would I think they would should really be advertising that more because I think the idea sort of at least my idea for the first few years was this is a crazy walk to take from the parking structure to Disneyland. But it's not that bad, especially when you're act you're factoring in that bridge and the fact that you can get right on the monorail if the monorail is open.
It's I think it's delightful and I think it's a great way to start and end your day. I think we're very pro bridge bridge bridge that it overlaid. Oh, it's you serve some of what's a little more negative about the Pixar Pals garage. Yes, I agree.
I think a lot of this would be alleviated to if they got another garage on the other side of harbor to serve to direct people coming from south of Anaheim because they're causing everyone coming from the south to go essentially around the resort to come to the same garage.
Everyone coming north of Anaheim is going to. Well, they just have to Anaheim just has to let them completely completely shut out all the other businesses so they can bleed them dry and then buy that land cheap.
Yes, and hopefully do that before any of any of us have the idea to have to do the harbor Houghton. Insane Banana Republic ask Reedy Creek Improvement District that runs the Florida property have a West Coast equivalent to run what will happen though.
Yeah, that's that could happen. I think they'll they'll just make that more of downtown Disney and it'll make us have to do more at stores. Because then that yeah once they sell that land to Disney then they'll just build more you know voids cupcake stores right milkshake stores, you know, more places to get a burger that is fine.
Yes, yeah, a lot of fine places. So that's coming. Yeah.
Do we do it. Are we done. I was anyone have a final thought I mean final Nick you're the parking expert you're our parking expert. Yes, that's what you're. Yeah, I thought it was a you know I think it was a just to summarize, it's a it's a very nice parking experience.
But off hours it's a little bit more confusing because there's less there are fewer cast members to guide you in terms of exactly where to go and that the cones are maybe not as the the the cones I feel like the cones alone I feel like didn't didn't necessarily get the job done
especially if we're going to the dedicated EV level. That was a little bit confusing. Not enough EV charging stations, don't love the theming looks better from the outside but the insides not not as great and but the pedestrian bridge is wonderful that is that is like great and that
that alone makes me want to go back to Disney so yeah I mean I think we talked about I think plussing it up and then such I think already I mean I think just yeah we've also stopped doing that so long ago. Yeah, we don't ever make it.
Yeah, it's not an official segment it's sort of just waves in and out. Right, it kind of gets worked in. If anyone misses that let us know. Yeah. Yeah.
If you want us to do like a really hard version of it at the end we can maybe do it. Yeah, you want to be able to make a little like chart and a graph. Right. You guys get with the forks. People do like that stuff people do like making spreadsheets. So, you know, maybe a thing to consider.
You ever check your old your spreadsheets just to like remember like oh yeah that one two and a half years ago, there was a guy who was maintaining a golden plate club for for doughboys or chain restaurant podcast that all the the the rankings of all the restaurants and then at some point and I would refer to that sometimes
because I was trying to remember like oh what did we give you know Olive Garden the first time we reviewed it if we're going to review it a second time. Oh, you actually consulted it. Yeah. It was handy to have. But then I think he's lost interest in the podcast and stopped updating it. So then it kind of like. As one day will you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Hopefully, hopefully soon. But yeah, the archive kind of ends in like mid 2018 kind of abruptly. So there you go. If he was responsible, he would have found someone to take it over. Yeah, you'd you'd wish. But you know, hey, whatever. He was probably in mid 2018. He was maybe he was canvassing for a House of Representatives or something. Lost interest in podcasting. Maybe he got elected. Maybe he's in the House of Representatives. I'm remembering that now that it's actually it was Representative Katie
Porter who was maintaining it. So she I mean she's got she's got other things to worry about. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely. Well, now there's only one way to know if we if we finished. Well, yeah. Well, I don't even know exactly what happens here.
Hmm. Boys, boys, you give me strength. OK. I just received a text message from the level keeper on his pre his or her prepaid cricket wireless phones. Of course. Oh, boy. Boy, is the boys that the dark spirits there, they're emerging again. Oh, no.
What you read the text quick and then we don't we don't have to deal with that. He says that the walkway is no longer a walkway or a bridge. It's a bridge of souls.
And the evil spirits are emerging. Shit. Boys, boys. I'm scared. The clouds are coming over. Oh, the little indicators are flashing red and green.
They're turning black. Mr. Weiger, you should run or maybe you should stay. Oh, yeah. What did we decide today? You should stay. You should check on the veterans and the escalate or are you going to stay?
I think I should stay. Is there anything I should be doing? Um, I think there's any reason to get out of here. No, no, you have to stay. I do. But my cat or even though you have to why your go. Yes. Yes.
And Jason, you must as well. Boys, this isn't good. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. It's Nick Valenti. It's Rick Wetzel. Why? It's Robert Earl. We killed all these people. It's Ralph Brennan and Dan Aykroyd.
They're taking over my soul. All of them. Oh, my God. Hey, it's Nick Valenti. I'm possessing souls over here. Oh, we go. You fuck you.
Fuck you. Wow. Well, well, well, isn't four pots of gumbo piping hot and horny is you bastard. You're the one who propelled us to the underworld in episodes you could still listen to at Patreon.com slash podcast.
The ride that's right behind a gorgeous paywall. I mean, I did like that part of it, but the rest of it was horrible. You trapped our friend Eva. Yeah, that's right.
And if you want a free Eva and Jason Woolliner and all your friends, you have a mall. They've all been captured. They're all captured and they're in my escalade. They're all sitting in my escalator room with the those veterans.
That's right. Shoot. Trapped in a small space. This was even Stephen Miller's plan. I am from France. Oh, shit. Right. The excellent, very accurate Dan Aykroyd is back.
Not new, not new. Oh, no. All of them at once. Sky overwhelming. You have a lot of nerve coming in here. That's right. This is me. Rick Wetzel. The regular voice. Hey, a regular voice. That's a good idea.
What? You're stealing your ideas again. Of course, the thing Rick Wetzel does. Everybody's backing up to their old tricks. It's almost like all of our items did nothing. Yeah, yeah, they did nothing. And don't forget about me, Robert.
Oh, of course, we know all about you and what you did to us. Lifestyles of the famous, sound and ass Robert Earl. Your sandwiches were okay at best.
So you boys think that you can just waltz around my parking garage. That is what we cross into my area, my district. It's yours now you took over the parking garage over it. See, boys, you forgot to take a peek inside the ESPN zone.
That's where my whole operation is. Oh, yeah, we didn't go in. It's off limits now. It's close to the public. It's close to the public. That's where your machines are that pump new life into those spirits that we killed. Yes, that's right. That's right.
And I don't think there's anything you can do about it. I don't know. Do we have anything? So says you. Well, the good news is that the level keeper texted me with one of his very last precious text messages. He or she. Yeah.
And he replenished all of our or she or she replenished all of our items. Oh, wow. We have the full stockpile. Wow. I would love to hear what that is. Well, you're gonna.
It's a sourdough loaf signed by Nancy Silverton, her husband, Mark Peele, three black aprons, two pizzas from Tootie Rudy's and fornication pamphlet. Hey, Tootie Rudy's Rudy Giuliani. That's my best friend. God bless him. That's right.
We're gonna fuck you up with those items just like we did before. I like to see you try. I've got diplomatic immunity.
Because from Rudy Giuliani, Giuliani, Giuliani, he gave me diplomatic immunity. I mean, he's in some hot water illegally. I mean, he I don't know if that's going to stick. He lives for that shit. Are you. Let me ask you this. Are you starting any other restaurants with him recently or trying to? Yeah, we're going to open an ice cream parlor.
OK, well, is there a gimmick to that? It's not. I mean, it's mostly just Rudy scooping ice cream. Sounds like you guys are running out of steam. Yeah, it sounds like the same idea as the pizza place, but it's just hey, Rudy scooping ice cream. Now that's a good idea.
No, don't steal. Rick, what's the honor among thieves even? You're going to steal Nick Valenti's idea. That's right. I'll steal his idea. I'm a fucking idiot.
Hold on. Hold on. They're fighting with each other. Fighting with each other.
I am from France. Hey, watch it, buddy. I don't care where the fuck you're from. Unless it's lower Manhattan, Wall Street, one percenters, you can suck my fat ass. Wait a minute. It's not going to take that lying down. He's probably going to be the shit out of you with his harmonica. Yeah. Does he have his trademark harmonica with him? He does. Nanu Nanu Nanu. I am from France. Who are you going to call?
I'd bears. Hey, what the fuck is this guy talking about? While they're distracted with each other, a jug of oat milk, a sparkling pink backpack filled with suckling pig, a boot that I can hop in from Sunook, a medium sized sculpin, a chocolate chip cookie pint glass filled with milkshake that has collapsed.
Nothing because Ralph Brennan kicked our ass. An open skull container, a thin mint cookie bear filled with organ meat, a paddle, I think, a pitcher of sangria, our little Lego avatars that we've been carrying in our pockets this whole time. That's right.
A super sized party sized toasted Earl of Sandwich gobbler for the holiday. Randy Gerber's Casamigos tea. That's a big beefy tea. I don't like that one. And a hard hat from the unbuilt luxury hotel plus a sugar cookie bath bomb that the four of us have to split. Four of us have to split evenly.
Huh? Wow. That's an incredible amount. And I'm sure we can remember what all of them are without them all being presented really big in front of us in some way. Yeah, that's true. Well, Jason, get in the boot first. All right. I'm in the boot.
Nick, put on this Casamigos beefy tea. Okay, I got it. It's barely fitting. That's right. It's thick and tight. And I will change into my other my alter ego, Micademus, the evil character from the void VR. Oh, that's right. Yes. Become Micademus.
You can only do it with the magical song that imbues you with evil powers. Hey, look, he's dancing and kicking on the stairs in your apartment. I'm Micademus. Maybe I need to crank that pitcher of sangria.
Scott is just drinking the pitcher of sangria. Whoa, I feel good. I feel better than good. I feel incredibly violent. Yeah.
Oh, his muscles are bursting like Popeye. Popeye rules apply. I want to bash some skulls. I'm going to give a little to Lego Scott too. What do you think Lego Scott? I want to bash some skulls. Lego Scott just got jacked. Yeah, jacked as a Lego can be. Micademus, zap him with your electric energy. Yeah, here it is.
Zap. Great. Oh, damn, that hurts. He can't move now. I'm going to bash. I'm expecting something more spectacular. No, I thought it was cool as hell, as cool as something in the void. Now I'm going to bash his brains in and when it's done, Jason, get in the boot and stomp on his brains until they turn to powder. Die, die, die, die, die. Fuck you, fuck off, bitch.
Remember, this is the sector keeper's body. Oh, that's right. Well, we'll figure out a way around that. Fuck, punch, punch. Sangria energy. I'll bring the sector keeper back by showing him his favorite brand of celebrity tequila. Look at my shirt. Look at my shirt. Oh, boys, boys, Casamigos, Casamigos. Oh, not so fast, little one.
Jason, I'll have to hit him with this in his weak spot. Jason, wait. Fragile skull. I'll hop on him in my giant boot. No, not my sourdough skull.
It's made of sourdough. That's right, because it's patched up. Don't forget, this is the sector keeper's body. Oh, that's right. I rebuilt it after I came. OK, OK, go for it, Jason. Mike, what were you going to say?
I was going to say, Jason, why are your clothes off? Yeah, why is this one naked? It's for aerodynamics, you fool. OK, fine. You can hop higher and faster. I can hop higher. Sorry, sector keeper.
That's right, boys. You did it. You did it. They're all gone. They're all dead. They're all burning in hell with Jeffrey Epstein and Joe Biden. I'm so proud of you boys. I can't believe you did it. Wow.
This was exhausting. This is an exhausting one, even harder than the city walk saga. I'm really proud of all of us. It was supposed to be 15 episodes. It became 18 episodes. You went to the underworld. And folks, if you haven't listened to that yet, I highly recommend going to Patreon.com slash podcast.
Cast the ride. It's behind a paywall. But some of the best things in life are. Well, that's true. Yeah, I think you're going to say then free. I thought you were going to say to our free free. But also some of the best things are behind a paywall.
And folks, and don't forget, folks, to use the hashtag sector keeper cricket. Why are the severance? Wow. Wait a minute. So if we're done with this whole thing, doesn't isn't this where we finally get to meet the level keeper? We get to find out who the level keeper is.
Isn't it? It's time to finally meet your favorite person in your entire universe. We get to meet your cousin. Boys, boys, it is I, the level keeper.
You did it, boys. You saved me from the evil spirits of downtown Disney. Now I'm free to upgrade my cricket wireless prepaid plan to a cricket wireless monthly plan. My dreams have come true.
But guess what, boys? Oh, it was never just me. You see, I was trapped with many other cousins who are all keepers of different lately themed malls. Now you must visit them and record a daily podcast series with each and every one.
Look, their spirits are ascending. And listen, they all have messages for you. Oh, God, I got a bad feeling. Boys, boys, it's me, the Disney Springs keeper.
I drowned in an amphicar, free my spirit by visiting all 180 stores and restaurants and meet me at the Build a Dino, the Build a Bear in the T-Rex Cafe. Hurry, boys. Hurry. I'm not doing that.
Boys, boys, I'm the keeper of CityWalk Orlando. Professor Tootsom is going to murder me unless you say what's different about our voodoo donuts, Menchies, Cinnabon and Fossil. They're much different from Hollywood's voodoo donuts, Menchies, Cinnabon and Fossil. Don't let me die, boys.
Boys, boys, I am the keeper of Harbor Boulevard during the wild Harbor Hoedown. You'll discuss one of the most exciting streets in the USA from the CVS to the Social Security Administration Building. There's so much fun to be had on Harbor Boulevard.
Oh, and another fun aspect, the Harbor Hoedown will have a video component. Boys, boys, I'm the keeper of the King of Prussia Mall in King of Prussia, Pennsylvania. It's a large mall next to a second, even larger mall. We're going to have so much fun together.
Boys, boys, I am the keeper of the American Dream Mall in New Jersey. We just opened a Nickelodeon amusement park, which includes three Ninja Turtles rides. Remember, discussing those rides will be off limits when you embark on the event of summer 2025. The American Dream Disaster.
Boys, boys, I'm from the Lansing Mall in Michigan. Our hula hands just closed. I'll see you soon. That was sad. No, no, I don't want to do that. Boys, boys, it is I, keeper of the Citadel Outlets off the 5th Freeway on the way to Disneyland. Sad sec. Come, learn about our facade based on the castle of King Sargon II. Oh, boys, I know we'll be best of friends.
I will not know.
I'm the keeper of the island at Pigeon Forge. We got a Ferris wheel and a landlocked Margaritaville Hotel. I need your help solving the mystery of the Yeehaw Snack Shack. Giddy up, go home.
Boys, boys, I'm the keeper of the Venice Beach Boardwalk. You gotta swing by. It's real crunchy and mellow.
Boys, boys, we are the keepers of Studio Village, the strip mall down the street from Universal City Walk.
The spirits are trapped in the greeting card store aptly named Car Heaven. To free us, we need you to answer a variety of important questions like, do you like the font choice in the Western Union sign? What is the computer processing speed of the Wells Fargo ATMs?
And what is the computer processing speed of the Coinstar machine in the Ralphs? We must know the answers. See you soon, boys.
Boys, boys, boys, it's me, Commissioner Evan Susser. As you know, Hershey Park is building a new entrance called Hershey's Chocolate Town. And guess what? I'm the keeper of that.
Love the Hershey Fountain. It's not even built yet. But boom, I died in it anyway.
Boys, boys, I'm the keeper of San Diego's Horton Plaza. I'll tell you about our La Salsa and its giant red pepper.
How many of these are there?
Boys, boys, it's me, the keeper of Americana Brand. Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm just a regular guy, see. Ain't no tricks up my sleeve.
So just mind your P's and Q's and we will have a beautiful time. Capiche? And sector keeper, why don't you keep soaking on that jewel?
Why don't you keep soaking on that jewel? Yeah, soak on that jewel. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Boys, boys, I am the keeper of Orlando's Crestland Shopping Center, right outside of Gatorland.
And I am the keeper of Settler's Green Outlet Village, the mall 10 minutes down the road from New Hampshire's Amusements Park story land.
I can't wait for you to come here and save my spirit by thoroughly discussing and reviewing our boot barn. They have lots of interesting types of boots.
Oh, you have a boot barn? We have a dress barn.
Oh, does the dress barn carry boots? Because boot barn carries dresses.
I will reveal all once the boys have come to the outlet mall and recorded 20 episodes about it. See you soon, boys.
No, it just feels like there's a lot of overlap in the barn based retail segment. I'm just saying.
You know, I like the banter between those keepers, honestly. I like that.
Wow, boys, all the keepers from all over the world. Amazing.
Listen, dude, you're pushing your luck. That is a lot of keepers. And if the implication is that every one of those keepers is another daily podcast, I don't care about your cut. You're cool. I like you, man.
But your cousins, why do I have to care? How many cousins do you have? They need help, Scott. Why do I have to care about all of them? They need help. They need help. They're all trapped.
Well, I know you're well, you're Mr. Helping out veterans and show playstations and salvation already been. But like, I know you're a generous man. Maybe I'm a little bit stodgy. I'm just like, how many cousins could there possibly be? How many daily podcasts could we possibly have to do?
If you think about it in a way, all of us are cousins. Oh, amen to that, brother. I'll give that a big hearty for sure on that one.
I'm not doing that because that implies everyone like that by that logic. Now everyone's a keeper. We can do an episode about anything that's 10 miles away from an amusement park. These rules are getting so loose.
What a slippery slope, folks. What I like about the end of this and Last Jedi is that now it sort of introduces the idea that anyone can be a keeper.
That's true. I mean, I was very inspired by that ending, but in this case, I don't know if I can go along with it. What if I were to tell you a lot of these establishments have bars that likely stock premium beverages, your crystal head vodka, your Casamigos tequila.
No, that is the last thing I want to hear. How many more times do I need to hear about these people? This bear, this premium beverages in my house where I could stay. Well, think about all the good times we had.
Sure. The city walk saga to the downtown Disney ordeal to the Mall of America or I'm not been there. I don't need to do it again. Well, Mike and I have been there.
We've never been there. Let's do it. Is Mall of America spelled M-A-U-L of America? Oh, that's good. Yeah. That's pretty good. That's cool. Yeah.
Are you stirring up a joke for later? Is that what that is? But when we do the series, you mean? Oh, that's what the series is called. Yeah, that's what the series is called. Yeah, it could be like Halloween time. Yeah, it'll be like spooky.
Because like the stores have to have decorations for Halloween. Absolutely. I'm kind of getting excited about this, honestly. Mall of America was also that was if I was still working at Funny or Die, I would have made that after Solo comes out.
And then it would be like Darth Maul of America. Oh, yeah. Very good. Very good. Sure. Sure. For sure. It'd be like him. It could be like a green screen bit and it would be a guy in the Darth Maul mask. They just do a mask.
The makeup would be too laborious. They just do a mask. I think I speak for everyone and I say, immortal. You think it would be immortal? You're voting that one immortal. The famous voting system of Funny or Die.
Yeah. I mean, that's look, you're building on Mike's idea. This is great. I think like and your podcast empire is growing. Is there could we maybe arrange some sort of like tap out or trade? Nick, I would love if you took over my position as third host to podcast the right for all of these various events.
I'm contractually linked to Doughboy's media, so I can't I can't. I mean, you can tell you can talk to Mike Mitchell, the president of the company. He might let me wiggle out, but I just I don't think it's going to be tenable. You do another podcast, though, as well.
Yeah, that too. That one is well, see, here's the thing. That's an ear wolf podcast. So that's its own script. Another whole thing with script. Get into it with scripts. OK, well, I'll start that matches your personal politics perfectly. Yeah. Well, that's why I wanted to get into business with them. I'm a big scripts guy.
So I did. And until Sinclair owns a podcast network, I think scripts is the one I want to be with. Yeah, I'm going to start delving into your your legality. I'm going to I'm going to start poking around. You don't have to open them to look through your books and see if there's a way to slot.
You would be open to it if I could slot you in as the new third host. I mean, I'm trying to say I'm trying to say no in a nice way. This is trying to give you I'm trying to say I'm trying to decline by prior commitments. OK, well,
I mean, I think you're going to be the king of pressure mall rocks. I mean, I like all of these places. I like the Mall of America, but enough is enough. And also, we're a couple of those guys, Jim Hill and Lynn Testa, the theme park podcasters,
who are your cousins? Sound sounded a little to me like the host of Disney dish. I didn't say anything. I didn't notice that. Yeah, I guess I'm just hearing things. I'm just seeing things again.
You're gaslighting me again. Like with Choco, I have a confession to make this entire time. I dropped the bath bomb in the boot.
I filled the boot with the rest of the sink area and I've been soaking in the bath bomb and eating the chocolate chip cookie pint glass milkshake mess. Let's anyone think we didn't utilize every item.
I have been enjoying myself. That was yeah, that was a narrative thread that was really going to bother people. Yeah, I mean, I was hoping that would pay off. So boys, boys, congratulations. Now you officially did it.
Yes, yes. All right. But all the Keeper stuff still stands. Yes, Scott, you still have to do.
I, uh, Sector Keeper. I don't. Okay. Well, I guess it's settled, right? You'll go help all the Keepers. And now we go to downtown Disney for one last romp or we break into the AMC and we watch Good Boys and a bootlaid copy of Richard Jewell.
That's right. That's right. And any funnier die parody sketches that get made surrounding this, uh, this film. You know what? I don't know how I feel about all of these, uh, these, these ordeals and sojourns and odysseys and whatever, but you round up all those cousins.
We're all breaking into that movie theater together. Let's all be good boys together. Yeah, there we go. All right. Mike, first you have to go to Santa Fe.
Yeah. Yeah, I do. Okay. Well, I'll meet you guys. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Veterans aren't invited. They don't get to come. Oh yeah. They could come. Right. Mike. Yeah. So quick stop for a good boy screening. Yeah. Santa Fe. It might. The humor might offend them though.
Yeah, possibly. We don't know. Yeah. Might defend us. It's a little body. It's I that's what I've heard is body. Yeah. But sometimes it's good to be body.
That's true. All right. We don't have to commit to a date on any of this shit. Do we? Um, a couple of them had dates in there. Yeah. Year wise. I think we can all agree. There's going to be at least one per year for many years. And I think like Marvel movies, like they're eventually there's going to have to be like starting to do two or three per year.
And like TV shows, little mini ones. Well, this is the point where just to keep up, we are just going to need other hosts and perhaps entirely different replacement hosts. Sure. Well, you can interview your replacement, I guess. Oh, if I do it. And if the sector keeper approves and says that he's Scott-esque enough to take over, then maybe I've got a way out of this.
As long as the interview is an episode that we put out. Yeah, for sure. All right. Fair enough. It's all it's all content. Okay. I'll wrap my head around this mentally, but we've all survived the downtown Disney ordeal. Wow. Wow. Holy shit. Nick Weiger, you survived the downtown Disney ordeal. Thanks for all your help. What a treat. I was going to add a thing I'd loaded up about an hour ago about this episode's length comparing to the runtime of good boys.
But now I think I could just say like just compare the third act of this episode to the runtime of good boys.
Most of them. Yeah. Yes. Well, we everybody has Irishman fever. We're getting close to Irishman runtime. Yeah. Well, thanks for bearing with it. Thank you. Thanks for having me. Is there anything you want to play?
You know, check out check out the podcast dough boys podcast about chain restaurants. We also do a lot of dumb shit like this. And then also check out my video game podcast. How did this get played? It's me and Heather and Campbell and review bad video games. Yeah. Yeah. Great podcasts that are sure to run their course soon. And you're going to need another podcast to jump on.
I'm trying to kind of get out of phase out of podcasting. I feel you know kind of like TikTok is the new thing. And me and Sheridan are doing pretty well over there. So for sure. Wow. For sure. For sure. Let's see. We need we need one. We need one more instinct. The classic the boys. All right. We'll give it to you. It's usually behind a paywall. We'll do it. For sure. Hell yeah. Thanks for listening everybody. So long. For sure.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey. For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.
Facebook.
Master Chairman of Disney parks experiences and products. Those three good boy merchants are no doubt celebrating with adults like patients next time it won't be so easy. Remember this podcast to the ride.
We're the amusement park news and rumor website that goes both in the night. Fear the bumper car boys. Fear the bumper car boys.