Forever...
...Dark!
Darkness falls out on the street, Evil rears its head.
Get your crazy shake to go, And your fried donut bread.
The villains threaten this sacred place, This downtown shopping mall.
We must defend the Lego store, And the Splitsville bowling balls.
The Downtown Disney or to you, We must protect our AP discount meals.
The Downtown Disney or to you, With secrets does the Earl of Sandwich conceal.
Boys, boys, my cousin has been taken by evil forces that have inhabited Downtown Disney.
In order to find them, he will need to thoroughly discuss every aspect of the mall.
Stores, restaurants, both of the Starbucks.
We have 18 daily, very necessary episodes and much to do so.
I will be there to guide you and keep your conversations from getting too off topic or boring.
The Downtown Disney ordeal, Why do we do this to ourselves?
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, the Downtown Disney ordeal, level five, stage two.
My name as always is Mike Carlson.
It is, it's remained consistent.
It's consistent the whole time, I'm a little tired.
Except for the podcast then it changes, but besides that...
Yeah, that's true. Same name. Scott Gardner is mine.
That's Scott Gardner talking, that's Jason Sheridan.
His name as always. Jason Skeleton.
Jason, oh, you're back to the... You kept on case.
It comes in and out. Yeah.
You pulled like what I pull where I'm like, all right, I got this intro down and then...
Oh, I... Did you see confidence?
I immediately trip off the diving board.
Did you see confidence when I said I would do it?
Because I wasn't like, watch me smoke these guys with this introduction.
We're all broken men.
Yes, that is what's happening.
We're amblin to the end.
We have... The boss has not appeared yet.
No. Still, there hasn't been some early exit.
We're still trying to find him.
In fact, of course, we had more episodes than planned.
Yeah. But one less than City Walk Saga.
Still, but if you think about it...
So far, but also remember, yeah, we have no idea if bonuses will get added,
but also we sort of didn't really do the food court.
So that is the same amount if you think about it.
That's true.
But I think that the distinction of having the episodes with a start and finish still,
there'll be people that will argue that with us.
Have you heard how I think our Facebook group, somebody pointed out how the four-minute episode
about the food court where we don't talk about it is just ravaged by ads
because they still plug all the ads in.
Because the algorithm is still putting stuff on top of it.
Yeah. So I think you listen to it and it's like three minutes of ad content
and then two and a half minutes of us not doing what we...
But which of course was that we had...
Remember how all the research we had for the City Walk food court?
We had so much we wanted to say.
But honestly, the Sector Keeper wouldn't let us.
So I hope to God he allows us to talk about this stuff today because this is a good...
If I remember correctly what's in this sector...
No, stage, stage!
Stage is not a sector.
It's a pretty strong one.
So let's bring him in and get his official permission.
Oh, great one, the Sector Keeper.
Boys, boys, you give me strength and I hope this ordeal gives you strength.
You said that in a way that I feel like you know it's not giving us strength.
I feel like you were f-ing with us.
Looking at you, I see three buoyant boys.
You seem up.
Like you see, did you find some of those like the higher nicotine jewel pods
that like are harder to get now?
Yeah, there it is.
Higher nicotine content?
There's like double nicotine pods?
There are different levels of nicotine content in them.
Is that Rolo?
It smells like Rolo.
That's cigarette flavor.
It just is cigarette?
Okay.
Oh, God.
That seems unpleasant, honestly.
I'm eating Rolos, you want one?
I do. You know I do.
Popping Rolos and oh my gosh, you're like, you're amped.
This is a high level Sector Keeper we're getting.
This is an exciting level.
An exciting stage, I should say.
Yeah.
Whatever the f-ck this is.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey.
Hey, don't take your agitation out on us.
We're already, we've been losing it, okay?
And who God knows where you've been, we've been like,
we've been facing bosses and dealing with shit and you know,
what did we do yesterday?
I don't remember.
I don't even know.
We talked about the Cosmete goes tequila for an hour.
Oh, God damn it.
Yeah, we had to loop back around the Cindy Crawford guy.
Yeah, now that you've reminded me.
Randy Gerber will have to be coming up on this episode in some capacity.
Sure.
All right, we'll see.
I won't force it.
Gerber's an old friend.
What?
Oh, really?
Yes.
No.
Did you ride, have you ever ridden on the back of his motorcycle with him?
Yes.
Wow, really?
Or does he have a sidecar?
He has a sidecar, but I ride on the back and Clooney rides in the sidecar.
Oh, wow.
And you like just like grip him, like just rub, put your arms around him and go for a
for a joyride.
Just go for a ride.
Boys, boys, focus though, because we must get you moving.
Today's level five stage two, the downtown Disney stage, food trucks, the unbuilt luxury
hotel, security checkpoints and as always, rinse bath and body company.
As always.
Something going around today.
Has it like been there since the beginning?
Maybe it predated downtown Disney or something?
It predates downtown Disney.
That's not like physically correct.
But maybe like under the ground as minerals and there were like bath bombs like found.
If you dug under it, like under the surface, you'd find just like big deposits of glittery
bath bombs.
Yeah, that you could clean yourself with.
So and pucker sticks, ancient pucker sticks.
So, I feel like it's all coming apart here.
Well, this is the area that's just left.
We got nothing happening now because the hotel didn't get built.
Sure.
To to recap, we can do that real quick.
We have a whole episode about this unbuilt luxury hotel.
There was originally supposed to be a hotel on the downtown Disney surface parking lot.
Just a bragging about a four diamond hotel, Disney's first four diamond hotel.
And you could see fireworks from a rooftop bar.
Right. So the hotel, the hotels they already have that you pay nine hundred dollars a night
for are not four diamonds.
Those aren't considered nice enough.
Right. So what because what it is, is that if you're a business and you want to send
your businessmen to have a conference in Anaheim, they need the hotel to be a certain level.
Like they only like to send those important businessmen and women to a very high end hotel.
To a very high end hotel.
They don't want to slum it at the Grand Californian.
No.
A bunch of garbage.
Those expense accounts aren't going to get stretched enough at the Grand Californian.
So that first hotel eventually morphed into a second hotel that was going to have seven
hundred rooms and be built on this part of downtown Disney and incorporate the monorail
station for perspective.
Seven hundred rooms in this unbuilt hotel.
The Disneyland Hotel is nine hundred ninety rooms.
The Grand California is one thousand nineteen rooms and Paradise Pier has four hundred and
eighty one rooms.
And this whole thing was very seemingly rushed.
Very rushed.
Sector keepers just started laughing for some reason at the all you remember.
Please don't forget the device of the coughing.
If you're ever feeling bored, just if you need to cough to keep us moving, feel free to cough.
People love our infrastructure.
Sorry, I just zoomed.
So now the problem that happened with this is that Disney got a two hundred and sixty
seven million dollar tax subsidy to build that.
Yes.
Original hotel.
When they shifted it a block away, it caused multiple businesses to close and jobs lost.
Oh, that's right.
When it was going to be not in this downtown.
This is a cursed stage.
Yeah.
It killed the entire.
It killed the whole problem.
The whole parking garage.
It all came apart.
And this seemingly was a very this hotel we're going to build over downtown is very fast.
It felt like all of a sudden they were like, oh, yeah, well, we're not going to do it here.
We're new here and we're going to just design something quick and like just throw it out
and cramped like the concept art is very cramped.
The other thing is if they had taken all those tax subsidy dollars, they would have been on
the hook to raise the minimum wage to eighteen dollars an hour by 2022.
Yes.
So that was another factor in play.
That one wasn't happening.
They don't know.
Yeah.
So thus we're left with this weird graveyard of like they don't know what to do because
they had gotten so far as to gut the rainforest cafe.
Sure.
Yeah.
Got ESPN zone.
They obviously theaters, movie theaters gutted like they were moving so quick with this whole
thing.
Yeah.
There was not even time to go back once.
It did.
It cursed other stages.
Yes.
Yeah.
We could be talking about we could be doing an hour and a half on just the AMC theater
alone in the Disney ordeal.
But of course, this for a hotel construction site.
What a mess.
Could you imagine though?
Could you imagine?
That would be a killer app.
If we yeah, if we just like kind of we're like peering over the construction wall for
30 minutes to an hour.
I saw some lunch boxes.
Construction worker lunchbox.
Jason could do an hour on lunchboxes.
I could do an hour on lunchboxes.
What did you have as a child lunchbox wise?
Oh, great question.
How to Ghostbusters for sure.
How to plastic Ghostbusters and then a Ninja Turtle, I think.
And then my mom got real into.
Yeah.
Good stuff.
Then my mom got real into like the freezer bag, like the kind of fabric bags that were
insulated.
I had mostly unfortunately.
I wanted always wanted the fun plastic, but I usually had just like an insulated bag with
a turkey sandwich that was so wet because there was an ice pack in the thing to keep
it like crushing it.
Yeah, to get cold.
But like my mom was so worried the food would spoil within three hours.
Well, but then by the time I got to high school, it was just a brown paper bag.
Like I because I was like, I don't want to carry around the freezer bag all day.
Right.
I do cafeteria.
Yeah.
In high school.
I eventually.
So anybody else want to chime in on this conversation?
I don't remember.
I don't remember what lunchboxes I had.
And well, it's just like it will keep us moving.
Luckily, if you're looking for some eats in this stage, there's a bunch of fucking food
trucks parked here sometimes.
They are trying to just dress it up and make people not notice that they destroyed three
of their businesses.
That a giant temple ruin is legitimately a ruin now.
Yes, that is true.
You could like.
Yeah.
So they're trying to.
They put banners up and some lights to dress up.
The area party.
Yeah, it's fun.
Early sandwich in Starbucks were able to reopen, which good.
I like them.
They're convenient.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, that's yeah, they didn't go in there and bomb those places.
No.
So there was a big ones because how do you fill those like the like everything ending
up being a Halloween superstore, these big spaces, there's nothing to do.
And they already have that's the giant retail spaces.
All you can do is Halloween superstore or avoid and they already have a void.
So there's nothing they can do with this.
These giant boxes just left to rot.
Yes.
Yeah.
Could they if it's truly like empty, I wonder what it looks like in there.
Is it truly empty in there or is it just like rubble?
Like, is it?
I wonder.
There's no no leaked photos.
I feel like there's more leaked photos from Disney World of stuff like that.
And did they leave all the rainforest props or did they did they take it to put in other
rainforest cafes?
But there's not that many of those.
Right.
But still, I mean, they need parts.
I'm sure they need parts.
So I'm yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Are any robots left?
You could maybe they like yanked out a gorilla jaw to use in case like Niagara Falls gorilla
jaw drops out.
Or Schomburg.
Schomburg gorilla.
Yeah.
Sure.
God.
Well, if the car zoom around that mall, the car that busted in had been successful and
driven into the gorilla for straight into the gorilla and decapitated it, then it would
be a but thank God nothing happened.
But they need one.
If he had hit any themed characters, we would be we talk about him every single episode.
We would be raising money for the rainforest cafe if that had happened.
Yes.
Our favorite charity.
Go fund me.
Not for us, but for.
And not for the conservation groups that rainforest cafe donates money to.
Oh, yeah.
Like real animals and plants.
No, no.
No.
The restaurant group.
Get out of here.
Save the robots.
They should reopen it for a special event.
Or my favorite movie coming out soon.
Oh, yeah, we heard your about Robert Downey Jr.'s do little.
Take me to do little.
If we get out of this whole thing unscathed, yeah, we should all go to do little.
Now, does that supplant taking you to good boys or do we now owe you two movies to please
double feature?
What a fun double feature.
Good boys and do little 2020.
And wait.
And by that point, it's November now.
Good boys hasn't been we're going to have to go find a discount theater and then and
regroup in what January, February when do little comes out.
I'm saying I shouldn't be saying this like it's a problem.
I would love to hang out with you.
I'm excited to hang out with you.
Also, Scott, I think you're overthinking it.
We can rent a theater and host a screening of good boys.
Rent the vacant.
Maybe and then fill the and then walk over to do an after party at the empty rainforest
cafe.
Yeah.
Yeah, using whatever robot remnants are there.
Oh, boys, boys, you give me strength and parental guidance.
Wow.
I wasn't even thinking that far.
That's a great idea.
We can rent the abandoned AMC to do a double feature of good boys.
We have to bring our own screen, though.
I bring a projector.
That's fine.
We did that for our Anaheim show.
So all right.
So I'll get on the ground and plug in my my home projector to fill an empty movie theater
that has no seats.
We have to bring our own seats to bring lawn chairs.
Well, we got you covered.
Sector.
This is going to be great.
We now have to host.
We're also going to have to sneak in and do all of this.
Yeah.
Disney is not going to let us know.
I have to find a bootleg DCP of do little like a bootleg copy with Chinese subtitles.
Little.
That's fine, though.
So all right.
So opening day of do little.
Yeah, we will.
All right.
So assuming that we have a hookup in China to film it off of a screen.
Yeah.
And send it to us and adjust the subtitles, then join us.
We'll just say the day of do.
The day after let's go buy ourselves a day.
Go just walk into the AMC theater, break it open if you have to.
And you'll find us in the sector keeper hosting a screening.
And yeah, you'll be filled with wonder seeing downy as do little.
Yeah.
Bring one of your podcasts, the right T-shirts, wrap it around your wrist.
Punch the glass, glass and then Jimmy the door.
And if any if you get any shards stuck to your hand, we'll remove the shard and autograph
it.
Yeah.
That's also just a good thing.
If you're on the fence about getting one of our shirts from T-Public, that's just a great
use for it.
If you need to punch some glass to bandage your hand.
If you don't want to wear it, I have to answer questions about what is your shirt about.
You can use it to break into spaces you shouldn't be into.
Yep.
At Disneyland.
Yeah, sure.
Oh boy.
All right.
So we have we got a good plan now, but until then, this area is just in decay.
And you know, this might be a good opportunity to talk about, you know, we're talking about
the never built luxury hotel.
Something we haven't talked about in this ordeal that we've talked we in both the saga
and the ordeal, we've talked about Fallen Brothers.
What we haven't talked about is Neverborn Brothers.
Yes.
You'll probably feel a little twinge of their spirit every time I bring them up, though
the ones who weren't lucky enough to live and walk and talk with us.
Yes.
Like two little animals.
I was wondering about this because, you know, like plans that never came into fruition
and there was no real source of it until that weird Al Lutz controversy that happened a
little while ago.
That's the highlight of my fucking year.
For anyone who doesn't know, there was a longtime Disney blogger in the 90s who apparently has
been usurped by an interloper within the Disney company who is using a fake using this real
bloggers name in a fake way to try to get Bob Chapek fired.
That's the long head of the park.
That's the most confusing way to put it.
Sort of like how dear Abby died years ago and they kept the column going.
Right.
Yeah.
Or the Boxcar Children.
The author of the Boxcar Children died years ago and they kept writing Boxcar Children
with their name on it.
Oh really?
Yeah.
Oh wow.
You've read every page.
Well yeah, that's his favorite book series.
Reminds him of his childhood.
I knew the Boxcar Children.
Whoa, really?
The originals.
You're like Benny.
What was Benny like?
I don't remember.
I read the first one.
Benny slept a lot.
I remember the Boxcar Children.
The thing I liked about them is that they had a boxcar they lived in, but they would
keep their food cool by putting it next to like a waterfall that was by the boxcar.
Yeah, you pack it up.
You like, this dream is colder.
Lunch cooling situations.
Yeah.
And I thought that was awesome.
I'd like to live in that boxcar and keep my food cool by a nearby waterfall.
As opposed to a refrigerator.
Yeah, no.
Jason, do you use a refrigerator or a waterfall?
A refrigerator, but I have an overflow waterfall.
Like your uncle who's got like a meat fridge in the garage.
If the fridge is full.
Move it over to the waterfall.
And I hate to keep sidetracking this, but the Boxcar Children at the end of the first
book got adopted by a very rich man, and he brought the boxcar into their backyard.
Into the backyard.
It sort of became their clubhouse.
And then they just didn't live, but the fun of it to me was that they lived out on their
own in the middle of the woods in a boxcar.
Now they were just adopted by a rich guy and they solved mysteries.
Was that the idea?
Yes.
100% right.
That's a bummer though, isn't it?
They should have been in the boxcar in the middle of the woods forever.
You, their suffering was your enjoyment.
I guess, yeah, I guess if I think about it, that is true.
That is the tagline for this series.
Our suffering is your enjoyment.
All right.
Scott, anyway, back to the Lutziverse.
All that was just to say in the middle of all that, somebody, we texted about this,
somebody tweeted out, here is the entirety of the Al Lutz archives.
All this like, this like website that would like detailed all of the rumors and everything
that like from 1997 to 2004 or something.
And I went into the Al Lutz archives, searched for downtown Disney to get material for this
series.
And there still wasn't that much.
It was just a lot of finance.
The sacred text.
It was really, this was the Al Lutz archives were the Pentagon papers of the downtown Disney
or deal.
They cracked the whole thing open.
Page turners, they were not.
So just to name check, that was the explanation was longer than what I have to say.
His things that were not built, the Neverborn Brothers of downtown Disney, the Virgin Megastore
was not built.
Planet Hollywood was never built.
Oh God.
There was apparently supposed to somewhere be a gigantic Barbie collection.
I think Disney did own for a while a big Barbie collection and was trying to figure out is
there a way we can shoehorn it into California Adventure or put it in here somewhere.
There was a whole thing and I don't know if this is tied into it, but there was a whole
thing with trying to get Barbie in the original Toy Story.
And that was Bo Peep, I believe.
I could be totally wrong about this, but there was some version of this.
I know this for sure, but I don't know if I think it was Bo Peep.
And then they eventually did get Barbie because I think that Mattel owns Barbie at this point.
I believe so.
They finally were like, well, obviously Toy Story is a giant hit and it would be good
for us to have Barbie involved.
So then that finally happened.
So I wonder if that's all.
Well, this is in the same era.
So maybe Disney formed this Barbie partnership and also around the same time, one of our
most overdue episodes, Barbie at Epcot.
Right, yes.
Yeah, we got to do that.
There was this live show and a video that came with it.
Yeah, we really owe that one.
Right, also, but I think a lot of these, like these bigger retailers stopped, like didn't
want to end up in there because they were cutting costs everywhere and California Adventure
was going badly.
And in fact, like Wolfgang Puck.
Oh, wait a minute.
No, I had it wrong.
Wolfgang Puck was offered a spot in downtown Disney, but he didn't want to be in downtown
Disney because he missed the lunch crowd.
He was like, people aren't going to leave the parks, go have lunch and then go out.
So he wanted to be in California Adventure instead.
So thus he was in Avalon Cove, which is now, what's it called?
Lamplighter?
Yeah.
But then that was very bad for him and he pulled out of that as fast as possible.
And he was, this is in the outlets, he was apparently so disappointed that Disney may
give him another location in downtown Disney, either at a discount or free as a make good,
possibly due to the terrible attendance they're getting at California Adventure.
Wow.
Wolfgang Puck is calling him throwing a fit.
I want a free restaurant given to me.
But yet that is a never built Wolfgang Puck did not get his free downtown Disney restaurant.
He was probably in the right.
Like he, I feel like he has goodwill.
I feel like it's a trustworthy brand and they fucked him around.
Classy name.
Absolutely.
Same with Robert Mondavi.
He pulled out of there.
He took his shitty wine out of California Adventure as fast as he could.
And also Disney Quest, Disney Quest.
Disney Quest.
Yeah.
Intended to be here at some point and maybe that Copperfield Magic Underground restaurant.
I would imagine if it had gotten off the ground.
These were all.
That would have been a big plan.
Potentially.
If now imagine downtown Disney where all of that was built.
There was one spot I read that they had talked about a West Coast Adventurers Club too.
And I never was able to confirm.
I think Tony Baxter did not.
I think I asked him about it.
You did and he did not know.
And he did not remember.
And I have not found like three sources.
I think I found like once.
I mean it makes sense.
You should tweet it, Rhodey.
Yeah.
I could try that.
I mean it would be expensive to build the building, the themed environment and then
all those equity actors and puppets and stuff.
And it doesn't.
It adds up.
Would it make sense?
You'd have to put plaques all over downtown Disney to make it fit into a narrative like
it did in Pleasure Island.
So you mean they didn't want to have a bunch of puppets and robots and equity actors and
instead they built a store where you got three socks instead of two.
That was somehow more cost effective.
You do not bring up the three sock pair.
If you didn't hear about the three socks, go back into the underworld at patreon.com
slash podcast.
If that doesn't entice you, I don't know.
Well, it will.
So there you have it.
The Never Builds.
Truly with all of those things, this would have been the greatest place.
It really does.
It's so tragic, honestly.
Like having, especially if they were all like, they'd probably be replaced maybe by today,
but like three years ago.
They all would have failed in three years.
But well, I think that a couple of them would have hung on up until like 2016 and been decaying
so badly that we would still have gotten to enjoy like a rotting Disney quest.
Yeah.
A Copperfield restaurant that has like nine rooms and only one is open.
Right.
Yes.
There's three people working at the.
They do lay, they taught them how to, you know, like put the, put a handkerchief for
like fake, pull a handkerchief out of your ear real fast.
And that's all the magic that happens.
Otherwise.
Okay.
So specials are we got a cod.
It's like shares a kitchen with the rainforest cut down on costs.
Somebody has to walk a hamburger across the.
So if you order a monkey burger from the rainforest cafe, that's also the magic burger.
It's a magic burger.
Yeah.
Five things on the menu.
So yeah, it's a weird one.
It's a weird sector that you've got.
Now the stage has been there for a long time.
I don't know much about the stage.
I've got a little about this stage because the stage kind of plays in into a classic
Disneyland event.
So the stage is where the Saturday night swing dancing moved when they closed Carnation Gardens.
Do you remember, do you know about this?
No.
For years and years and years, decades.
Carnation Gardens, right by the castle, hosted Saturday night swing dancing.
And eventually that was closed for the fantasy fair.
And people were very upset because there is a contingent of people that would go and do
swing dancing every Saturday.
So while they were rebuilt at like doing all this construction, they moved the swing dancing
and the big band to the downtown Disney stage.
Eventually fantasy fair, they put the swing dancing back in there on Saturday.
So you can still go Saturday nights to go to swing dancing some Saturdays.
But then also there are swing dancing other nights at the downtown Disney stage and swing
dancing at the Splitsville stage.
So there's more swing dancing than ever.
And there is a Facebook group that uses very confusing abbreviations to say like Saturday
10 17.
Dan, Dan Whoopi, like it says like DW at DTDS.
So like Dan Whoopi at the downtown Disney stage.
It's like all the abbreviations.
Is that a real name?
No, I just made that up.
I couldn't believe though that Dan Whoopi was a real swing dancer that loves downtown
Disney.
Dan Whoopi.
So you can still see.
The alter ego of yours.
Go see Jason do swing music.
I call when I play my tunes, I call it making whoopee.
Oh my God.
Disneyland has asked me to not do that anymore.
To body for it is your body.
So you've had to learn the code of the Disneyland swing.
You're now a code talker of Disneyland swingers.
I am a kind of swinger swingsters.
Swinger is if you're hooking up with the multiple swingsters.
If you're a dancer.
I know about Dan Whoopi, the Wop Opaloo Bops, all of the guys.
If there's daddies who are cherry popping.
The pencil skirt sisters, all of the local swing dance bands.
When I said on Twitter, is there anything you like from downtown Disney?
Somebody said I should shout out the Suburban Legends, which I did notice, which is a ska
band that seems very popular locally and with a giant discography.
They seem to have amassed a huge following primarily from their appearances at downtown
Disney.
So there are legitimate bands around there.
As we learned with the House of Blues, downtown Disney is a legitimate part of the OC, ska,
and punk, and now we know swing scene.
I like the stage.
The only thing I don't like about when I go up, because I like watching a little bit of
every performance.
There was an Elvis guy, Elvis-y guy, I forget his name.
I like that.
I just don't like it when there's only like 10 people because I don't want too much eye
contact from the performer.
Because if I want to leave, I want to leave.
So I like try to hang back and enjoy because I just don't want to.
I feel pressure to stay.
Yes, because I feel like if there's 10 people and you're playing and one of them leaves,
that is devastating.
Like as a performer.
You act as if you know that from your years of improv performances.
10 audience members is a blessing.
10 is generous.
And especially if there are not people performing in 10 minutes, that's even better.
Yes, that's true.
That's very common as well.
The audience of the downtown Disney stage probably aren't taking classes from the downtown
Disney stage and have to go.
Yes, that's a good point.
They're not taking classes to be the next Elvis impersonator.
Although an Elvis, a UCB style Elvis training academy.
Or just UCB teaching an Elvis class in general.
Well, if you want to be performing in a paid manner, Elvis is one of your best bets.
It's true.
You go to Vegas, like almost like every hotel has like four Elvis's at any given time.
And you would think that that wouldn't regenerate at this point.
He's been dead for an awfully long time.
Sure.
But I guess.
But Elvis maintains and we need new young Elvis's to replace the Elvis's who are dying
off.
Or is he?
Oh, interesting.
I don't know.
You know something from the after world.
We don't.
Let's just say we never crossed paths.
Okay.
So, oh, and you've met a lot of other dead people.
Pat, let me ask you this.
Have you crossed paths with Jimi Hendrix?
Yes.
Okay.
How about DB Cooper?
Yes.
Uh, uh.
A chance to confirm once and for all.
Beethoven?
The dog, not the dog, the composer.
The composer.
Yes, the dog.
No.
Oh, wait a minute.
The original Beethoven, the dog is still alive.
That's a conspiracy theory that he's passed away.
I'll send you a link.
Oh, boy.
YouTube video explaining all this.
Some very interesting thoughts out there.
So we even like the conspiracy theory that the original Beethoven is still alive.
The original dog who played Beethoven is still alive.
It's very impressive.
But his big dogs die more easily.
I read that he's making a cameo in Do Little.
That would put him at least at, what did Beethoven come out, 92?
Dogs 27 years old?
At least?
28, 29?
He's old enough to have gone way past Beethoven's second.
We're talking Beethoven's 29th.
Yeah.
Whoa.
This is big, honestly.
This is a big revelation.
It's this late in the ordeal.
Yeah, holy shit.
Yeah.
Who cares about like his Tupac still out there?
His original Beethoven.
His original Beethoven still alive.
Any St. Bernard you see, or any other big dog, maybe he's in disguise.
He painted his fur a different color.
I don't know.
If anyone has any more information about this, tweet at us.
Yeah.
He has blood transfusions of younger dogs.
Oh no.
What?
Oh my God.
He gets like stem cell treatments?
Yes.
Wow.
That's crazy.
It's transplants.
What's that thing the celebrities get, the hormone in the face?
HGH?
What are you talking about?
Botox?
Yeah, or the, I don't know, the thing you talked about.
HGH is human growth hormone.
You don't necessarily get it in your face.
I think I've talked about what I believe is HGH head, which is what makes your head big
and puffy.
Sure.
He would be, if Beethoven got it.
Right.
DGH.
Nobody would be the wiser.
I think Edwin just walked down here and I think maybe it's time for him to get a little
DGH.
If you want Edwin to stay around forever, make his face huge.
I just want him to be more strong.
I want him to be more powerful.
Just jacked.
Which you'll need if you ever run into original Beethoven.
He'll knock you through the hall when he humps.
Yeah, original.
He's a stress humps, simply knocking you, giving you a concussion.
Original Beethoven looks a lot like Sylvester Stallone looks now.
Where like he looks pretty good for in his seventies, but something's weird.
Get up close.
It's a little strange.
Okay.
So we're almost out of here, but are we?
Security checkpoints.
Oh yeah.
Security checkpoints on this side.
We didn't talk about it because they're gone on the other side.
Well, this area gets a little weird because you have the security checkpoints and sort
of on a straight line laterally is rinse.
Rinse is technically outside.
We have to talk about the points first.
I know.
I'm just saying it gets weird.
Do we?
Sector keeper, do we?
Yes.
Fuck.
Hey, all right.
Well, there's like a bunch of metals.
They give you those little white jars.
They give you little dog bowls to put your stuff in.
They give you little dog bowls.
They'll check your bags.
Boys, boys.
I just received a text message from my cousin, the level key level keeper.
Oh, oh.
He says, make sure you spend ample time on this.
Level keeper.
Thinking about that wherever he's lost.
We can't find him.
He or she.
We don't know.
I would text back, but he's texting or she is texting from his, his or her prepaid cricket
wireless phone.
Right.
All right.
What does count as ample?
I don't know.
I got stuck the last time we went and we were there with you, sector keeper.
They got rid of the line.
That's just no bag.
No bags.
Interesting.
Which I think is interesting.
Yeah.
Because like, because you both said interesting.
Well, I find that interesting.
Well, they it's changed.
The security system has changed for many years.
You just had to get your bag checked.
You did not have to go through a metal detector.
And then they had them further down and it was a fucking mess.
Yeah.
And now they have them at the tram.
When you get on the tram or here, if you walk over or you're coming from the hotel.
Yes.
Talking about this is as interesting as being stuck in a security line.
People love our infrastructure.
I will say sometimes I don't think I like a thorough bag.
I'm a paranoid person.
Sure.
The world we live in is scary sometimes.
I don't like it when I see a guy or a girl just put their hand in and like do a little
glance and don't do the thorough check.
They maybe opened my glasses cases before.
Good.
Yeah, sure.
I like that.
That makes me feel good.
Sitting next to Wawa West, you can just walk in and out.
Yeah.
So I appreciate the time they're taking.
But if I'm just a single passenger, essentially, I'm just a man in his 30s alone going into
downtown Disney as you are once a week, at least once a week this summer.
I just want an express lane or a TSA pre-check for downtown.
We talked about this already.
Yeah, we talked about it already.
But I want that and it would be nice.
I'd also like, I think also with any of these types of lines, generally you try to go to
the farthest one away.
That's the quickest.
Right.
I guess so, yeah.
That's usually the case because people generally just psychologically I think go to the first
line.
How we do, if you had to guess your cousin's thoughts.
Do you think that we need more here?
Maybe a little more.
Okay, well.
I got stuck and I had to, they went down to my belt and they made me turn my belt buckle
around and show that there was nothing hidden on the other side of the belt buckle.
I did find that a little interesting.
I find it interesting that I have a belt that I generally wear and 90% of the time does
not set a metal detector off, but once in a while it does.
Once in a while.
Which is weird.
At airports they're really strict about belts now, I find.
It does and at airports it never sets it off, but at downtown Disney once in a while this
belt that I wear sets it off.
I don't know if they can, can they turn up the intensity on a metal detector?
Why is this not always working?
Yeah, that's a good question.
Yeah, I thought you knew.
Oh no, I don't.
Well, let's all just wear ropes instead of belts.
So we don't have this problem anymore.
Hang it on your cord, man.
Did that do it?
Did that kick it over the edge?
Wow, boys, boys.
You gave the level keeper and I great strength.
Keep moving.
You aren't even looking at your phone.
You're making up these.
I'm not sure he ever texted.
Well, but now.
Or she.
He or she.
But now we're at the pice de resistance.
Rinse.
But now wait a minute.
Yeah, though, Jason, wait.
Why do we have to?
We're at this.
You said the security checkpoint was the end, but there's this store.
I didn't know this.
Look at this map.
See?
See this map I'm showing you?
Yes, it's distance wise.
It's technically behind.
You have to go outside the security checkpoint, but it's realistically the side of the movie
theater sandwich.
So therefore.
But it's the only store.
It's technically downtown Disney that's outside the security checkpoints.
Right.
Yes.
And the only store you could bring a weapon in, I guess.
I mean, that's true.
I'm not saying use it, but if you felt like you might encounter a problem in the soap
store.
If you had a saber, you could bring it.
If you had a nunchuck, a single nunchuck.
You could bring it into rinse.
That's true.
Yes.
It runs parallel with a security checkpoint and it shares a space with Earl a sandwich.
So boys, you must explore.
Tell us.
I didn't know this existed.
I didn't either.
Before the ordeal started.
I know it's very newish.
I thought it was part of the store with all the wooden sides.
I thought that was technically like half rinse.
I knew.
I brought this to the table.
I figured it might be on the table.
So I was like, let me we should be prepped.
Yes.
We don't get stuck and like have to go back down just to do that.
Right.
But once you said like once a bad supply was in contention, like I started rubbing my little
hands together.
I bought because last time so in the in the city walk saga, we went to nectar bath treats
where everything looks like donuts and cakes.
Yes.
And you guys are did only one of you do a bath.
We both.
Well, we both did different approaches.
Yeah, I did a bath.
Okay.
Bath bomb.
I got a bar of soap that smell looked like a donut shaped like a donut.
I just would like to remember, mind everyone and anyone who didn't know for a period of
a couple of weeks, a few weeks, I cleaned his body with a donut, coconut, pineapple,
donut soap.
I would just like it to say just you clean yourself with a donut.
That's better than even saying it's a so fair.
Yeah.
So Mike and I were bath buddies again for this deal.
We went in and I we were looking around.
And you bought two things or did I?
Yes, I bought I bought a bar of oat and honey soap.
Okay.
Yes.
I bought the bamboo loofah soap.
It was a bar of soap with a with a loofah inside to exfoliate, which is a problem.
I feel like I don't exfoliate enough.
Yeah.
Which is good to scrub those dead skin cells off.
It smells like tea tree oil, which really smells like it smells like like the gift shop
at Knott's Berry Farm or like like it smells like vacation, which is what I like.
And I feel like maybe I will do more tea tree oil based soap in the future.
Yeah.
After using it, you found your flavor profile or whatever.
Yeah, it's a nostalgic smell.
The loofah is a little hardcore.
When it started, it's a little rough.
But you know what?
That's good.
That's good to get that dead skin off.
Okay.
Mine, as I've been using it, has revealed to me more and more oats.
It's filled with oats.
It's an oat and honey soap that has oats in it.
That kind of de facto exfoliate.
Be honest.
Did you eat them?
I mean, it's real tempting.
Did you be honest when you were cleaning yourself with that donut?
Did you take a bite?
I had posted wet post-it notes everywhere saying don't eat the soap.
In case you wake up at 4 a.m. and forget.
Yeah.
I just have a donut sitting in the tub.
Really?
Which happens to them a lot.
It's a scrubbing donut, not an eating donut.
You have different donuts in different corners of the tub.
These are not eating sprinkles.
They're exfoliating sprinkles.
I was just chanting myself.
Bazen became rinse.
Okay.
So did you like your baths?
Well, so okay.
Yes.
That's not the only thing.
We did.
I saw the name of a certain thing and I said, oh my gosh, Jason and I both have to do this.
They sell something called tub truffles.
And I was like, oh my God.
And before we get into our tub truffle experiences, I have to give it up for everything all natural
handmade.
I think she said in Georgia and I thought priced very fairly.
Those soap bars were like seven dollars.
Very fairly.
Tub truffles four bucks.
Four dollars for a tub truffle.
If this were City Walk, it would be like eight or nine dollars.
If not more for some sort of a bath bomb situation.
I found also this soap less dry.
Like the nectar stuff kind of dried my skin out.
This I felt much more moisturizing.
I will be honest with you.
I also felt very moisturized.
So tub truffle is a little I guess you would call it like a bath bomb.
It's a little bath bomb.
It's got a different.
What flavor did you get?
I got not scent flavor.
Coconut mango.
I got a fun coconut mango one.
I got lavender tub truffle.
I'll just read for the listeners who might be a little confused what it is.
This cocoa butter based bath bomb fizzes in your tub as the cocoa butter slowly melts
away conditioning your bath and skin.
There is just enough cocoa butter to lightly moisturize the skin.
Scent lavender.
The only problem I have is that the bathtub I have is too small for a man of six three.
Which came up the last time.
Yes.
And still same apartment.
The last time I took a bath was the City Walk saga.
I don't do that regularly.
But I was like this would be nice to do more often.
But it's also wasteful too.
So obviously we're being journalists right now.
We have to take the bath.
But I don't want to be wasteful.
We're required by work.
Yeah, this is a work thing.
Honestly to waste all that water on my body.
I like the fizzing.
I found it very relaxing and no like dyes and stuff.
So it didn't like dye the tub or anything.
Like mine was just like clear.
Did you let me ask you about the experience.
Last year I had I sipped a diet grape soda while I was in the bath.
This year I drank a white claw.
Oh that is very funny.
I had a screwdriver.
You both drank while you did the tub truffles.
If I take like two baths a year and I'm having a beer or a glass of wine.
I'm having some sort of drink and I was just getting over a cold.
So I had orange juice in the house for once and I had some vodka.
I've been trying to get rid of for ages.
So now.
Bring me over.
I'll get rid of it for you.
I got to say I got too relaxed because I think I almost drown.
No not that bad.
I was like light headed by because like that water like hot.
I don't like so on us that much.
I get light headed from them like very so between the screwdriver the very relaxing
tub truffle and he the vapors.
I really had to steal myself getting out of the tub and like I have to go lie down.
Oh my God.
You almost had to go to the hospital.
I know it's great.
It was great.
It was like it was like it sounds like you couldn't walk.
I mean I got out of there.
A wheelchair to will you from the bathroom to your bed.
Jason didn't make it out of the downtown Disney or deal.
Oh my God.
You know, I'm so relaxed that they find him and he's just smiling eyes closed in the bath.
If only we stayed behind the security checkpoints.
Oh, these rules.
Jason died.
He's like he died of happiness.
I took a quick 20 minute lie down and then I made the notes required for this episode.
Wow.
Well, I I had the last year I took a photo.
Yeah.
With and I was like, well, what do I have in the house to drink?
And I have a thing of white cloths because I love hard water.
It's all the rage now.
But I didn't I didn't get hammered in there.
I was I was not I I have I have I think I've said it on the last episode.
I can't go right to bed, though.
My body's too hot to go to bed and it's readjusting to the temperature of the apartment.
Hot boy ordeal.
Yeah.
So I take like an hour to get back to my normal body temperature before I can go back to bed.
Cough please cough.
He loves all this time.
That's why he isn't coughing.
I got to say hi Marks to rent the worker in there was so she was very funny.
She kept asking if we were a boy band.
Oh, yeah.
I'll send the sector.
I'll send the sector keeper.
We were having a lot of fun.
She was thrilled to see some customers.
Very nice.
Annual pass discount works at Rinse.
Yes, it is alive.
Yeah.
He said her name on her name tag wasn't her real name.
Oh, yeah, that is right.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
But she was that a lie.
Why did she say I used to work retail and if you forgot your name tag at home, you
just grabbed an extra from the breaker.
It's just whatever was around.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Doesn't have to be your name.
I had my last name on my name tag for the last couple of years of working at Container
Store.
Wow.
I never earned my name tag at Cricket Wireless.
Oh, no.
Would it just say sector keeper?
Did you used to have a name?
Is there any continuity for your name?
I can't remember.
I don't think so.
Maybe we need to do another series looking for my name.
That's the goal of the next one.
Who were you before all this?
Yeah.
Before you got amnesia from having to listen to all these episodes.
You forgot your own name because now you have to know.
Nick Valenti.
You have to know who Nick Valenti is and how the Owl Lutz archives told us where Disney
Quest was going to be.
Well, it seems like a pretty good experience for everybody.
Yeah, I liked it.
Again, I don't want to be wasteful, so I shouldn't take a lot of baths.
But aren't you wasting the rest of the truffle?
No, the truffle all went away.
Yeah, yeah.
The truffle is a one shot.
I mean, I guess you could cut it in half.
Well, that's fair.
I wanted a full cocoa.
Let me read it again.
Full cocoa butter based bath bomb that fizzes in your tub and slowly melts away.
I wanted the full experience of that.
That's nice.
Yeah, I think this was so it was such a nice.
It seems like this place is so successful that I think in honor of it that Chumbawumba
should return and write a new anthem to this place called Tub Truffling.
You speak my language rather than have lyrics for it.
I splash right down and drop the truffle in and it conditions my skin again.
I prefer coconut and it's in its fizzing in the tub again.
There you go.
I love it.
That's good.
Thanks.
But it's up to them to write it.
We need all 17 members of Chumbawumba who were like we like there was something up with
them.
They were like, yeah, what was the deal with them?
They were like terrorists.
I don't forget.
They would say they said like shoplift or music.
They were encouraging people to shoplift.
That's right.
Man, right when the new radicals were encouraging everybody to storm the mall and put the security
guards in cages and get Beck and Marilyn Manson to run back to their mansions.
This is a violent time for dull radio rock.
Yeah, the late mid to late 90s.
We get mad about Limp Bizkit and Korn, but the new radicals in Chumbawumba were the real
threats.
Yeah, they were rebel rousers.
Yeah.
You missed all those bands.
Yeah, I'm trying to keep up.
What's up now?
Billie Eilish, Kamiya.
Kamiya, yeah.
Cabello.
Yeah.
Cabrera, which like Ryan Cabrera.
That's not right.
No, Ryan Cabrera is from years ago already.
That's a long time ago.
That's a long time ago already.
Extremely irrelevant.
Yeah, especially then.
Billie Eilish is kind of bad and you're kind of breaking bad as we speak.
Might be a good little role model for you.
Sometimes it feels good to be mad.
That has become one of your sayings.
So wait a minute.
This is it.
So we've got to wait.
OK, so we like face a boss now, right?
Is the boss like a huge tub truffle or are you going to get inhabited by a big tub truffle?
Because we're done.
Well, that's it, guys.
Well, let's hold on.
This is a stage two.
Bosses come at stage.
Something doesn't add up.
My math is off.
Boys, boys, you did it.
Almost.
Almost?
There's still another bit to explore.
But you said the security.
We made the exception for rinse, but the security checkpoint is the that's the final.
That's the end of it.
I brackets it.
But think of all the emptiness in this level.
The AMC, you know, all the empty.
You know, I'm getting it right.
So you must fill it with something very ample.
A parking structure.
That's right.
Well, I guess it does connect to downtown Disney.
It is the conduit that takes you to downtown Disney.
And in fact, when they recently built this new parking garage and a pedestrian bridge
even more recently, they opened the pedestrian bridge that gets you to downtown Disney.
Yes, yes.
The pedestrian bridge to pedestrian bridge to.
Yes.
In one episode.
How are we going to manage?
That's a lot to tackle.
You can do it, boys.
You can do it.
And you have the help of a dear friend.
Oh, really?
Well, I wonder who it'll be.
Yeah.
Let's let the rumors start flying.
It's only there only be 24 hours.
There's 24 hours of exciting rumors.
Yeah.
So let your imagination come alive.
What friend are we going to meet in the parking garage and what boss and what are and will
we finally meet the level keeper?
Yeah.
Will she or he be there?
God willing.
Yes.
Can we have you don't know?
He doesn't know.
He's just sending us.
You're right.
You're just we're on this journey with you.
We're on this quest with you.
Schedules permitting.
Yes.
OK.
Yeah.
Sector keeper.
Can we have an item to carry into this brave new frontier?
We're going to need something in there.
We need something to add to our inventory.
Something from level five stage two.
Yes.
The item that you'll put in your inventory to take into the parking structure from level
five stage two is a hard hat from the unbuilt luxury hotel.
Oh, wow.
OK.
More armor, I guess.
One hard hat.
One, though.
So we got to decide.
Just one.
Yes.
Share it between you three.
OK.
Jason might still be a little weak from the screwdriver and the vapor.
Yeah.
Maybe we want to put it on his noggin so he doesn't crack it open in case.
What if like a steam vent burst in the parking garage and you got a little tipsy again?
Yeah.
He may have some post-traumatic stress from the bath.
So he could just fall into a.
Is there like a good version of post-traumatic stress?
Yeah, I'm sure there is.
Post-bliss stress?
Post-traumatic bliss?
Post-traumatic bliss.
That's it.
I guess traumatic is probably not going to go on there either.
They toured with the new radicals for a while.
They had a couple members of Faroukhi Salt.
Yeah.
One hit wonder.
Mall Rock.
Wow.
OK.
Well, with that in mind and with item in hand or on head, we have all survived level five
stage two of the downtown Disney ordeal and tomorrow it all ends.
I hope.
Hopefully.
We all hope.
So tune in.
Oh man.
We can end it.
All right.
Smells like cigarettes.
Cigarette flavored vape.
OK.
Well, tune in tomorrow for the grand finale and be sure to follow us on Twitter, Instagram
and Facebook, Facebook, Facebook, hashtag DDDO, hashtag save the level keeper, which
hopefully we'll do tomorrow and hashtag sector keeper cricket wireless severance tweeted at
cricket wireless and not at us.
Yeah.
As you know from the underworld, if you want more podcasts, the ride, then go to the Patreon.com
slash podcast, the ride, the podcast, the second gate for three bonus episodes every
month.
So here we go.
It would have been good if we got a bath bomb and we could use a bomb in the fight.
I just received a text message from the level keeper.
He or she says you receive one bath bomb.
Oh, OK, cool.
However, what flavor you must cut it up and share it between the three of you.
OK.
I'm doing what flavor is the bath?
Sugar cookie.
Hell yeah.
What a tease for tomorrow.
So as long as it doesn't get eaten in the interim, be sure to share it with your friend who will
be helping you.
OK, we're going to split it in four.
Yeah.
All right.
So like so then do we just like have four parts and then reform it?
I don't know.
I think we'll just kind of have to be on the fly.
See how we're going to use it.
Yeah.
We'll run it by him and see what he wants to do or her.
Who will the guest be?
We don't know that.
Wake up tomorrow AM and find out.
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
Sugar cookie.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production, executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Silio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at Forever
Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.