Forever...
...Dark!
Darkness falls out on the street, Evil rears its head.
Get your crazy shake to go, And your fried doughnut bread.
Beignets.
The villains threaten this sacred place, This downtown shopping mall.
We must defend the Lego store, And the Splitsville bowling balls.
The Downtown Disney or to you, We must protect our AP discount meals.
The Downtown Disney or to you, With secrets does the Earl of Sandwich conceal?
Glory's board is my cousin has been taken by evil forces that have inhabited Downtown Disney.
In order to find them, he will need to thoroughly discuss every aspect of them all.
Stores, restaurants, both of the Starbucks.
We have 15 daily very necessary episodes and much to do so. I will be there to guide you and keep your conversations from getting too off topic for...
...boring.
The Downtown Disney ordeal, Why do we do this to ourselves?
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Downtown Disney ordeal level one, stage three.
I'm Scott Gardener, joined by Mike Carlson.
Hello.
And Jason Sheridan as well.
Hi.
You guys feel a little nervous? This is the first boss level.
Yeah, I'm feeling very nervous. I used to as a kid, I would get very stressed out when I'd have to fight a boss.
Yeah.
Me too, still to this day.
Agreed.
Even just like casually playing Super Mario 2 that I've played a thousand times.
Yeah.
You see that big mouse, I'm gonna have to jump on some bombs.
It would just like, yeah, like when Bowser was in that big Super Mario world, remember he had like a big face thing with a propeller on the bottom?
Sure.
Yeah, that, oh my God, I felt like I was going to die by getting hit by a propeller like in real life.
Just seeing it on the map, just seeing the airship on the map and knowing it was coming ruined my enjoyment of all the other levels.
So will today's boss be as fearsome as Bowser?
I, there's no way of knowing, we don't even know who the boss is yet or really how this works.
So I'm a little nervous, but that's why I feel lucky that we are joined by a favorite guest of ours and a veteran of the City Walk saga.
So glad she's here for this journey.
Eva Anderson is with us.
Hey guys.
Hello.
I'm really happy to be back.
Hey.
And quest with you.
Oh, wonderful.
Yes, the stakes are higher if you don't know.
The Sector Keeper's back.
You know about the Sector Keeper.
My friend.
Yes, sure. Yeah, yeah. A good buddy of all of ours, but it's not about him.
It's about the Level Keeper who is a cousin.
His cousin.
The Sector Keeper is a cousin who's been captured and his name is, or he or she, we actually don't know who this is.
So the Sector Keeper doesn't know, neither do we.
Doesn't know. He's been vaping a lot, so that's kind of affecting him.
Okay.
He's really juuling a lot nowadays.
Okay, juuling tobacco.
Yeah.
Flavored to there.
Whatever it is, I'm not even sure.
But so we got to find the Level Keeper.
The Level Keeper could be around any turn.
It could be in this stage if we get to the end, but I have a feeling it will not be until there's as many episodes as possible.
That seems right.
Probably.
But we don't know.
Scott is holding out hope that this will all get wrapped up quickly.
Yeah.
Of course it won't.
It's going to be today, but if I don't carry that spring in my step, what's going to take me there?
What did you mean by boss level?
For today's episode or when I was a child.
Well, I know what bosses are in video games, but how can Downtown Disney have a boss?
It doesn't make sense to me.
Evil spirits have invaded Downtown Disney.
This is what's going on right now.
Yes, yes, you explained that.
Yeah.
And they kidnapped the Level Keeper and they've sort of inhabited all of our favorite places.
So this is necessary for us to do because by discussing and reviewing, we're going to be, of course, freeing Downtown Disney of evil spirits.
And you were warned that there might be a big spirit here?
I think that in every level, there's three stages in every level.
Yeah.
And we're told that at the end of every level, there is a boss that we have to do battle with, but we don't really know what that means, how that's going to manifest itself.
So we're all sort of in the dark.
Yeah.
The game has changed.
Last year, there was one boss of all five boroughs, Manhattan, Brooklyn, Queens, Staten Island and the Bronx, and his name was Gotti.
There are multiple bosses, multiple families, some might say, controlling Downtown Disney.
OK, OK, I got it.
This is more of a games of New York situation.
Yes.
Do you think Gotti would think that Downtown Disney is the greatest fucking outdoor shopping center in the world?
I think he might think this part of it is the greatest fucking, you know, true.
Well, real paisan.
Oh, yeah, I got some some genuine Italian.
I feel like he would like Chelsea Piers or something like like local South Sea Port.
Yeah, I mean, it wouldn't be bad to have John Gotti's Jazz Kitchen down at Downtown Disney.
That wouldn't be bad.
Italiano.
Right. A little more. Not the New Orleans flavor.
More than Italiano.
John Gotti cleaned up downtown Disney.
Free John Gotti.
Oh, I missed you guys.
Nice versa.
We're so happy to bring you back to talk about a bunch of boring shit.
Oh, yay.
I starting with.
Well, oh, wait, we have to get our mission from the sector keeper who's not here, but we'll summon him in just for, you know, 20 seconds or so.
Right.
We'll get him in just for the sake of the paper.
Boys, boys.
Hello, Eva.
Today's stage is Mickey and Friends Tram loading California Churro Cart religious pamphlets Naples Restorante E bar Napolini.
Good luck.
All right.
So I know it's nice to talk to him again.
He's moody or than he was, he's not the white eyed child.
He's had some real character development.
Did he hit puberty?
He still likes like kids stuff.
But then again, so do we.
He's kind of getting pulled.
He's simultaneously about our age, but also still like has a lot of catching up to do.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I'm sure happy to fill them in.
Yeah, I'm like the little girl from the act.
Yes.
The way that she got munchausen.
She got munchausen to thinking she was younger than she was and sick and then she got out.
But then she killed her mom.
So she had to go right to prison.
But now she loves it because she's like catching up on culture and just stuff in general.
Yeah.
Great.
She has friends.
Maybe we should show the sector keeper the act as kind of a guide of what he can do.
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, no.
Killing us with secondhand vape.
It's really slow death, but it's happening and killing us with boredom, I think, because
the first thing we have to do is the Mickey and friends tram loading.
Oh, thank God.
Yeah.
Tram loading zone.
I do.
I guess it is part of it.
It is part of it.
Yeah, it is.
It is within the boundaries of the security checkpoint by the hotel and the Honda Odyssey,
promotional Star Wars Galaxy's Edge Honda Odyssey that forms the other border of downtown
Disney.
You can see La Brea Bakery from it.
Yep.
Uh huh.
Yes.
I don't take the tram, guys.
I walk.
Every time.
I like to walk from the parking structure where you walk by those little bushes.
It's nice.
It warms me up.
It's much more superior now thanks to the bridge.
Have you gotten to go on the bridge yet?
No, I haven't.
This time I, well, this time I parked in the downtown Disney parking.
Oh, I see.
Sure.
But so, and the last time I was there was like a year ago, so I guess I missed this bridge.
It's only a few weeks old.
It's new.
It's like weeks old.
It's as it goes over the street.
Yeah.
Ooh, so you don't have to wait.
And it's a new path.
It's wonderful.
It is wonderful.
Is the bridge part of this, do we know?
We'll have to find out.
We'll have to find out when we get closer.
Check again later when vape smoke clears.
So, well, and you taking a walk means that you get to pass through downtown Disney, beautiful
downtown Disney.
Yeah, you can see all of it.
Any favorites outside of your stage?
Fantastic Sephora.
I think you've mentioned this before.
It's one of the best ones I've ever been in.
Sure, sure.
That's coming out of the bend.
I think the sector, he were mad, but after I'd had a couple drinks at the, in my sector,
I bought a whole bunch of shit at Sephora and I just had so much fun.
I was like, just went cam in there.
Oh, great.
Oh, man.
Got to get that parking validated.
Yeah.
So that was great.
And I also, I like looking at, I mean, I don't know, like the bowling alley is okay.
People seem to really enjoy it.
I'm usually surprised by how many people are just like hanging out in downtown Disney,
like eating.
So I got there, I went early.
I went at eight in the morning and people were just sitting, having breakfast at Earl
of Sandwich all over the place.
I find that I'll be walking around downtown Disney and I'll just be thinking like these
lucky people, I bet they live around here.
Oh, I think that they're all, it makes me, I think more like these people have been at
the park for too long and they're just trying to do something else with their kids.
Like.
I'm imagining like five minutes away living and they're like, you know what, let's go
to Earl of Sandwich for breakfast.
You're jealous of that?
A little bit, yeah.
I don't think there's anywhere nice to live by Disneyland, right?
Well, Anaheim Hills is a little bit farther, but that's what was really pretty nice.
Okay.
There's an Anaheim, there's a richer section, I guess you'd call it, of Anaheim.
Yeah.
Cause I think I talked to you, was it with you guys?
That I did the Disney marathon.
Oh yeah.
With Jess Jarden and we, you run around Disneyland and it's very.
Crimey.
Yeah.
Oh, it's like part of, it goes through the neighborhood too.
Cause there's only about two miles you can run through the parks, maybe three.
And then they have to fill all this space.
It was a half marathon, but there was like 10 miles through just downtown Anaheim and
it was bleak.
Yeah.
Oh, right.
That's fair.
I mean, our beloved Buena Park is not maybe the best area to live.
Oh man.
One time when I was in college, my boyfriend and I at the time, this is bad guys.
We took acid at Knott's Berry farm and then we stayed overnight in a hotel we could walk
to a motel, which turned out to be a very, very bad place, especially on drugs.
But there was a guy, it was just, it was a terrible place.
And at one point my boyfriend, Travis peaked out on the balcony and there was a guy just
holding an unplugged phone, like a hotel phone, having a conversation on it, like doing a
deal, but there wasn't, it wasn't connected to anything.
And he was like, Hey, Oh, excuse me.
A man just walked by and I'll ask him this question.
He turned to Travis was like, excuse me.
And Travis just like slammed the door and locked it.
He was just trying to get in a scheme on an unplugged phone.
It was terrifying.
So that's, that's what's around Knott's Berry farm.
Oh no.
Wow.
If only the Snoopy tuck in was an option for you guys.
Oh man, we didn't even think about it.
That would have been crazy.
I don't think it was there yet.
I don't think you could have.
We could have just, we should have just stayed at that hotel.
I don't know what we were thinking.
We could not stay at the hotel was clearly the move.
More interesting than anything that happened to me in four years of college.
Really?
I taking acid at Knott's Berry farm, witness an insane man have a phone call to no one
is, yeah.
I mean, also rides on acid are not.
Is it all more stressful?
Yeah, you, you can smell all the oil and like, and then like it'll go backwards and kind
of leave you where you were.
Your soul stays at the bottom and you go up.
Have I said this in the focus before about how when I'm assigned that I have not been
like, uh, I've been pretty off weed for a while.
And part of it was cause I was watching a lot of movies and realizing I was like seeing
through to how miserable the set must've been.
I was making me flash past the film and the fun story that's being told to just like,
I'm just seeing the cruddiness and the faking and the general depression of long film shoot
hours.
Yeah.
And I'm choosing to do this to myself to ruin movies.
Watching like, uh, I just, I watched a beyond the sea that Kevin Spacey movie and I was
like, man, they had to like choreograph this whole number where he's like being Bobby
Darren and people had to like learn this dance.
21 year old Bobby Darren.
21 year old Bobby Darren with his dyed hair.
And it's like, he's probably harassing everyone on set.
And so, and like, uh, uh, did he direct it too?
Oh yeah.
And he wrote it.
There's a child.
Have you not seen it?
I made you watch it, right?
It takes me or were you, was I seeing scenes you were posting on Instagram or vice versa?
Yeah.
Cause there's the kid version of themselves like Bobby, tell them all about this.
Like, oh yeah.
He speaks to his child version.
Doesn't he do a dance number with his child version?
No, I'm not.
I don't know.
And then you realize he's stupid.
It was just like, that's a whole new level when you know Kevin Spacey is stupid.
Like he's not smart.
He's dumb and he's bad.
And he's like a bad person who's dumb.
He really terrible taste.
I don't know how like, I mean, we could, I could do it all Kevin Spacey novelties podcast,
but that when he, the, the, the Bobby on the sea in general, when he, uh, sings mind games
in the nine 11, uh, memorial,
You introduced me to that and I watch it like once a year.
We used to watch it in the comedy bang bang writers room.
Oh wow.
Yeah.
Because of you.
It was like a favorite.
Oh, I'm so glad I found out about it from the Conan writers room because they told a
story where he, uh, apparently was like, uh, like I want to sing, uh, I'd like to sing
lady Madonna and they said, well, that's a McCartney song.
And like, ah, God damn it.
Yeah.
Well then I don't know.
Bluebird, blackbird then.
Um, just named another McCartney.
He like, it was crazy.
He had no way.
It was an all John Lennon tribute show and he had no idea what was a John Lennon song.
It was a bonkers.
I like when he has a, that he's wearing that weird, you should post this link.
He is wearing a weird button up shirt, like, like slacks, very like business casual.
Yeah.
Just as like my dad.
And he start comes out and says, he's really pissed off and then he sings mind games with
a full orchestra and he keeps jumping up and down like hitting all the,
We all have to do what we can to restore New York city.
And that includes your host.
And then he jumps and that's the reveal that he's going to sing.
I could really, that's like a, that's like twice a year at least for me.
And then when he sings a black eyed peas parody at a British sports awards and it's supposed
to be one of those openings where he's like going around the backstage and like fixing
things up and fixing this guy's tie and he takes a basketball and throws it in a hoop
and he misses.
Did I tell you that in high school I was in love with him?
What?
I was like deeply crushing out on him.
We won't say who it is, but Jason and I have a good friend who, when I said like, who's
your number one guy, you're crushing Hollywood.
She was like Kevin Spacey.
Oh my God.
Recently?
No, year, three years ago.
Okay.
So our, before time.
After all this stuff came out.
Then she's like now more than ever.
No, but I like, I watched every single movie he was in up to, cause this all was like the
year of usual suspects and swimming with sharks and seven, which was all one year.
And I got hugely crushed out on him and I watched every movie he had ever been into
that point.
Wow.
And it was like pre internet.
So I had to like find these things, I had to rent them.
I watched, yeah, I watched rocket Gibraltar.
I watched consenting adults to the erotic thriller he's in with Kevin Klein where he
wife swaps and then murders someone.
What?
I watched, I mean, he's in one scene in working girl, which I watched.
He's in a, oh man.
You ever see him accepting his MTV movie award for seven.
Oh, I didn't have that recorded as a clip on my computer at all.
Whoa.
He's wearing a Kangol hat.
Oh God.
Yes he was.
He's wearing like a cool vest and sunglasses he doesn't take off.
I know.
So cool.
Didn't he have a two season like procedural show?
Uh, yes, it was called, um, wait, he was the bad guy.
I have not heard about that.
It was called profit.
Yeah.
And he was the bad guy on profit.
I couldn't get a, I couldn't get a hold of that one.
Yeah.
That is on DVD now.
You see it every now and then like walking through a Best Buy.
Yeah.
Like in the TV show section.
Oh, he's the bad guy in See No Evil Hear No Evil with a.
Is he really?
Yeah.
Yes he is.
Like don't, are you really questioning me?
No I'm not.
No I'm sure.
Yeah.
No that's a surprise.
That's me being delighted.
He's kind of a Boris and Natasha sort of duo.
He's got a British accent.
Oh my God.
And a little pencil thin mustache.
Does he count as theme park entertainment now enough that we could do an episode all
about Kevin Spacey?
Is he in the voice?
He's in Bugs Life, right?
Yeah.
He doesn't do it in the, in, um, in It's Tough to Be a Bug.
Okay.
I think maybe Andrew Stanton does the voice.
I think you should do a podcast episode about Kevin Spacey novelties.
It's enough like the Green Goblin and stuff.
Like it's, I think he's theme parky enough at this point.
He, did you see the recent video of him playing La Bamba in the streets with a Spanish band?
No.
Should we cancel plans and just do this, the Kevin Spacey episode right now?
It feels like we need a lot of prep for this.
Yeah.
I think we need to.
The most delightful prep we could ever do.
I was sad I never could see him in, uh, um, Guys and Dolls.
What?
Yeah.
He was on Broadway in Guys and Dolls.
Was he Sky or Nathan?
I think he was Nathan.
He Sue me, Sue me.
Yeah.
He couldn't be Sky.
Peter.
No.
Gallagher?
Yeah.
It was like, it was right before the one up.
It was Peter Gallagher and Nathan Lane were right after him.
Okay.
But before that he was in, yeah.
I just want to show you a shot from the video.
Oh man.
Joyously holding up an acoustic guitar.
It's like on the day.
In the way only like non-guitar players hold guitars.
Yeah.
On the day one of his court cases was dismissed, I think.
Not one of the days when one of his accusers ended up dead, which is also something that
happens.
Are we allowed to laugh about him when things like that are happening?
He's a vile creature.
Yeah.
Check out the second gate episode on Let Me Be Frank.
Even that.
It's, all right, we're doing it.
We're doing it.
Prespa, you'll come back if you're down and we'll, let's talk spacey.
I used to have a shrine like my friend made for me as a joke, but I kept it like until
like a year ago.
It was like a wooden shrine with his photo on it.
Oh man.
I was so confused, you guys.
I was really confused.
This is where you're, I know.
And then for all that to happen, like what that does to your psyche.
By then, I mean, K-Pax started the slide and I was like, oh, he's done.
I remember being, I saw K-Pax opening weekend because everyone, spacey fever, with usual
suspects and American beauty.
Yeah.
Everyone was jacked.
He burned all his American beauty goodwill making Beyond the Sea.
Uh-huh.
And America could not have cared less.
And also what's that one with Haley Joel Osment where it's about pay it forward.
Where he like we're ups his shirt open and shows like his, his burn scars to Helen Hunt.
If you like, cause it's, it's, he does this, you would love, okay.
She like, what's, there's something up with her in that too.
She's just like heavily tan.
She's heavily tan.
He does a monologue about a stepdad lighting on fire, which is, it's going to go in the
novelties episode.
Oh my God.
And I thought, why would water smell so bad?
Why would water smell so bad?
And I looked up and he was holding a red gas can and then he lit a match.
So the Mickey and Friends triplet area.
This is coming up.
We will do this.
All right.
I can't wait for that episode.
Okay.
2001.
Oh boy.
Mickey and Friends.
Oh no.
I'm just going to be staring out the window thinking about that episode the whole time.
We talked about the, we've already talked about that garage.
And we got to talk about the tram loading.
This is where the payoff is.
This is where the tram lets you off.
This is, here's my problem with talking about it is that I sort of have to reveal a little
bit about my feelings on the new parking structure because the parking structure shows a better
way to do certain things.
The parking structure is outside of the confines.
We're not, until there's permission given, we can't go assuming we can do the parking
structure.
Okay.
So, all right, fair.
Let me then hypothesize of a better way to make it so that it's not just this big mass
of people and there's a little bit uncertainty of who's going to get on the tram because
when there's that big group at the end of the night, you're fighting with teens, you're
fighting with families.
Just hoof it, man.
Yeah.
Which is what we do a lot of the time.
But if I'm reviewing this experience.
Much better option usually.
Kind of kid with you then you have to go on the tram.
Single file rows is all I'm going to say.
Wouldn't that be better?
Isn't that how you board the tram at Universal?
Isn't that like a little more clear who's getting on the tram at Universal?
Oh, the tram tour tram?
Yeah.
Yeah, there's stars and the system.
It's like a ride.
It's a single file line and they just load you in.
Yeah.
That mass where you feel like you got cheated, like I should have been first, but somebody
kind of veered in front of me.
Some pushy mom.
Oof.
You know.
Get it.
It's just a little, because you see those groups and it's just very intimidating.
It doesn't look good.
It looks like just a big mob.
And it's so, yeah, when you're leaving the park and you see all that, like, oh God, we
got like another mile to go then I guess we got to walk in.
Yeah.
My only note for this thing is I'm bummed when I have to be there.
Yes.
Leaving.
If I arrive, then I'm happy for all the fun that's in store.
But like, yeah, I don't wait to leave in that area very often.
No.
I always think the only thing that makes me think is like, do I like La Brea bakery?
We weren't sure either.
Yeah.
I'm like looking at it.
I'm like, do I want that?
Do I want to just go in the park and get something?
Yeah.
We said it's fine.
It's fine.
We declared do a drinking game with this podcast series when we call things fine.
Fine.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah.
It's fine.
I don't think the tram is fine.
I think it's bad.
Yeah.
Again, I don't want to talk about the other side of the tram, but the other one is a little
better.
There's rows.
It's a row.
There's no rows now.
So I'm not, I'm pro that side.
This side is chaos.
But this side is chaos.
It's a little bit chaos.
I like all the plants.
I'm always in favor of more plants.
More plants for sure.
Yeah.
It's just mentally soothing.
Water features and plants are help keep people from going insane in these massive crowded
spaces.
I think that's very true.
That's nice.
So there's that.
Water features and plants.
Great.
Is that it?
California churro cart?
California churro cart.
You did it.
I got a rose gold churro.
Huh.
Oh, interesting.
Lightly strawberry flavored.
What'd you think?
A little, you know, it's warm, which is always a plus for a pastry.
I feel like I've, I don't have a strong opinion on churros one way or the other.
I think if they, I had a fresh one, like out of the oil.
Yeah.
I think it would be incredible, but usually they're just sitting there all day and they
always taste a little stale.
Even if they're like the best churro, even the best churro in the world is just like
fine.
Inherent fine.
Oh no, I'm sorry.
No, it's good.
No, keep it in mind.
This is also, I think the start of like a weird feature of downtown Disney.
These little kiosks of like, well, it's not a Disney churro and it's not a Disney hot
dog.
It's a diggity dog.
It's a lady trying to sell you Disney vacation club.
Oh yeah.
And then it's like.
Is that over here too?
Should we be talking about that?
The vacation club?
There is a kiosk.
Yeah.
For vacation club.
Did you, did anyone here belong to the vacation club?
I did.
Jason.
How was it?
Are you, did you, I mean, you guys were like a hardcore Disney family, huh?
Uh, yeah, we, I mean, we were in it from like 95 to 2000 and I always joke, well, that
was the first thing going into divorce.
That was the first thing to fund the lawyer.
Uh, uh, but we, I mean, we had a lot of fun.
So it did let us go.
I think we went a handful of times.
There was a run in there where we, we went every summer.
Right.
We went every year.
And then.
We go for like two weeks?
Only one time did we go for two weeks.
Okay.
And that is, that was a trip.
Like that was like not leaving Disney world for two weeks.
I mean, we went to Universal.
We went to Sea World.
We went to like, yeah, we broke it up a little bit theme park theme park guy who was doing
a job at Orlando last time I was in Orlando.
So it was more than 10 years ago, but, um, he was shooting something there and I went
along and we stayed in one of those condos for the Disney vacation club and they were
wild.
Like they were, they had a kitchen and they were like, we would cook hot breakfast and
stuff.
That's nice.
It was nice.
Yeah.
And then we went for a week and got like a one bedroom, but it's essentially a one bedroom
apartment.
So that's cool.
And it was also like, now I think it's a little more unwieldy cost wise.
Like in the nineties, it just was like, Oh, this makes financial sense if you're going
to go even up like every other year.
And cause you could also, Oh, one thing we would do is we would get an annual, like I
was a Disney world annual pass holder for a little while.
It was like, well, if we come back next year in less than 12 months, we don't have to buy
tickets again.
They have a pretty sweet annual pass deal right now for SoCal residents.
I was eyeing it.
I was like, that looks good.
The $600 one.
No, it's like 20 bucks a month.
Is that it?
Really?
That's what it said.
I'm in pack pass flux at the moment and I'm needing to decide my next situation.
Look into this one.
I almost bought one when I was there.
It was low price by then.
I just bought the day ticket.
She was stupid.
They are, I keep getting hotel offers for Disneyland and they're not super, they're
still not cheap enough.
They're very expensive still.
It's still very expensive, but like they're scrambling because they, uh, there's plenty
of great stuff about galaxy's edge, but they set their expectations too high.
So on the spreadsheets, they did not meet their financial goal or their guest number
goal because they set it too high.
So now they're like, Oh, what do we do?
And I spent too much money on the Honda elite.
That's sitting on.
Yeah.
I got an email today from the Disney vacation club person I met with a few months ago.
Oh yeah.
Cause you sat through a seminar.
I sat through a full seminar to get four free fast passes.
And a Diet Coke.
You willing, he willingly went and sat through a presentation.
Yeah.
I got four fast passes.
And he goes on all these rides once a week.
Yeah.
It's a rare opportunity to get to go on Indiana Jones.
I also wanted to know.
You get snacks and you get to see sample hotel rooms.
That's fine.
And I'm a theme park journalist.
So I knew this was part of my job.
I mean, I want to go to Disney sea and I want to go to Hong Kong and stuff.
It makes, I mean, yeah, it makes sense.
It makes sense to do it.
If you're going to take like high level hotel vacations every year.
Right.
But they had, then you have to go to a Disney property.
You don't.
They have partners.
It seems like you learned a lot during this presentation.
I don't want to bore everyone.
The other thing is that they don't really push.
There's an aftermarket.
So you can buy people's points because it is a time share.
So Disney can only regulate it so much.
There's federal timeshare laws.
Okay.
So you can go to third party point sellers and buy points to use to stay at a Disney
property for cheaper than you would booking directly.
There's a whole secret sort of thing.
They don't like to tell you to about it where it's like Disney will buy it back.
They have right of first refusal essentially on your property.
If you want to get out of it, you have to offer it to Disney first.
Right.
They won't necessarily take it.
It's like a first look deal.
Yes.
Talk about this on your Facebook group.
Shout out to the Facebook group.
Yeah.
It's like the dues are like 28,000, you have to pay like $28,000 or something or maybe
$20,000.
A year?
No, no.
For like one time fee.
Yeah.
The one time fee.
And then yearly like $800.
You buy the points.
It's like.
Yes.
So it's like.
I'm so stressed out just hearing that part.
In 20 years, it's like a good deal if you keep it.
Yeah.
Well, it's like.
You can describe that way.
It can be good.
Well, it's the idea being like it is an investment.
It's essentially a vacation home that you pass down to your through your family.
Right.
And everyone gets a home resort.
Yes.
And that's how they're starting to screw people is like you your home resort.
If you didn't get in before a certain date, if you want to stay at the newer ones, that
has to be your home resort.
You can't use points for it.
Yeah.
But that.
Or some perks.
It's very.
I'm joining.
I'm going to do it.
You didn't even need to.
You did the last passes.
Just give it to me.
I have the email of the gentleman I talked to.
Oh, man.
I get the DVDs.
How long were you occupied by this presentation?
An hour and 15 minutes.
Here's the thing that is one of my biggest mistakes with the presentation.
At the end, he goes, do you need a ride anywhere?
And I said, what do you mean?
And he's like, like back to the parks or to a hotel.
And I was like, oh, no, no, I'm good.
I go, well, do people get rides places?
He goes, yeah, we can give you a ride anywhere you want.
I go, well, where does the where does it go?
Where do I?
Because it's over by the Disneyland Hotel.
And he's like, yeah, just like in the back, the back area.
And I should have.
I didn't know.
I don't know why.
Yeah.
I think I would have been able to take a golf cart backstage.
I screwed up.
I really screwed up.
I'll take it.
That's a lot better.
Do those pass?
You can't take the golf cart ride until 20 years from now.
And he can buy it back from you.
All right.
So Jason, I'll go down.
You'll go do the presentation.
You'll be my guest.
You know, you can come along.
You'd be my guest.
That's a good point.
I'll be your guest.
He's my brother.
He's my big brother.
We don't even have to go that far.
We don't have to go that far.
Oh, no, I like to have a narrative, so I have a character going in.
You could just be friend.
I love it.
I think it's better for my motivation if you play my big brother and we can make a joke
about how tall you are.
Guys, just be married.
It's OK.
Be married.
All right.
Fine.
Married and proud.
Pamphlets.
OK, so I.
Religious.
We should wait.
We should explain this.
OK.
If you're going to downtown Disney, then why are you?
How are you getting through any of this?
And second of all, you there is an area that's pretty like undecorated.
That's just like Ivy, essentially.
And one of the only things that's there besides the sporadic treat cart is just a table and
chairs where Jehovah's Witnesses usually.
But I think there are some others.
But we tend to see Jehovah's Witnesses passing out pamphlets.
It's very odd to see in a Disney environment.
Yes.
And you can see the park from the table where they are.
Yeah.
You're like very close by then.
And just the New Testament.
Not full Bibles.
Usually book copies of the New Testament and like pretty thin booklets.
Yeah.
And such that you can take on the go and that, you know, door to door people can take on
the go.
Also, too, when I walked up, it was two ladies in very, very like overdressed, not overdressed,
but like religious clothing, long sleeves, big skirts, umbrellas to shield themselves
from the sun.
It's hot.
It was hot outside.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's been a very hot summer.
And they were, yeah.
And they just sit there and panned out what I got, which is a copy of The Watchtower announcing
Jehovah's Kingdom.
It's the magazine of the Church of Jesus Christ Latter-day Saints.
Okay.
It's very thin, what you're looking at.
This takes me back to church, like the thin ass bulletins that I would grab on the way
out.
They're different.
The Latter-day Saints is Mormons.
This is Jehovah's Witnesses.
I see.
It's not bad.
Anyway, I'll just describe this magazine.
I read all of it when I was eating at my restaurant in the sector.
Wow.
You really did it all on top of each other.
I did.
So the cover just says, is this life all there is?
And it's a man standing in a graveyard.
And then the table of contents is the sad reality of death, the search for a long life.
We are designed to live.
Why do we grow old and die?
Conquering the enemy death, dot dot dot.
How?
How can you have more than this life?
Making the most of life today.
What hope for the dead?
And then the sad reality of death is just like, this is just a paragraph.
Imagine yourself watching a video about a celebrity, perhaps a famous musician who you
admire.
It starts with scenes of her childhood, her music lessons, and her endless practice.
Then you see her performing in concerts, traveling far and wide, becoming an international celebrity.
For a long time, images of her golden years.
And finally, as the video ends, she dies.
And so just about how everyone dies.
Oh my God.
This, by the way, is steps away from a store where you can buy a mini merchandise that
says rock the dots.
And she's, you know, she's clad in polka dots.
And you can read about the death of a hypothetical pop star from your feet away.
The anxiety of death in this thing is wild.
It's like the death is our enemy.
We cannot, we can't not die.
And we're going to get, we're going to suffer and die.
This is a hell of a way for me to find out in the middle of a, a mall series.
I know a man who rocked dots, two dots in his hands.
For our sins.
You'd be better at this table than the ladies.
Tie it into the environment.
Yeah.
So I looked into this a little and there's really not a lot online.
I reached out to a reporter friend and said, do you know anything about, do you know why
this is here?
And he's like, no, that's a good, I've never looked into that.
But all I could find was people complaining about it on Reddit.
I thought I'd find like an OC register article, but it seems to be, cause they see every now
and then they're at city walk too.
And I think it is, and I think the city of Anaheim ruled they can be there.
And I think it has to deal with public private spaces, privately owned property that still
acts as a public area, like a mall or something like that.
Yeah.
I've seen street performers at downtown Disney.
I once saw a guy playing a wild electric hammered dulcimer in the middle of downtown Disney
and remind me what a dulcimer is.
It's like a, a, it's like a bunch of strings.
It's almost like a zither or something, but you hit it with a hammer.
It's like a old school instrument and he had like, he had CDs for sale and stuff.
Yeah.
So I think as long as you fill out the proper application and I don't know if you have to
pay Disney like, so they can't reject because that was my question where it's like what
Disney wants to be so neutral on everything, right?
But is it like, just because they have open submissions for you to sell or street perform
they have to allow religious, I think they can restrict content a little in terms of
family appropriateness.
But I am wondering like where the religious freedom like constitutionally they can because
there's no Scientologist.
Right.
And there's no like Hare Krishna.
No.
Falun Gong.
Yeah.
No like really weird, like crazy graphic bloody signs that make me mad when I see them.
And they also, they do that.
The dance show is them.
I went to it.
Oh, you, oh, right.
Shen Yun.
Oh yes.
And they also, they also, they publish the Epoch Times, which is the sells more ads for
Donald Trump on Facebook than any other organization.
Because they think that Trump will get rid of the Chinese government or help them be
free of the Chinese government, which he doesn't care.
But if you go to the show really quick, there's dancing and then all of a sudden they come
out and lecture you about Falun Gong and then they do a dance number about a girl whose
eyes gets gouged out by the government.
And then eventually later in the show they do a number about like people looking at their
phones and two guys are looking at their phones and they start holding hands.
They become gay from their phones, from technology.
There's also an opera singer who comes out and sings a whole like opera song, which translated
about how technology rots the soul.
And then- Holy shit.
Can you like- Why do they, the billboards just make it look like there's like one person
jumping.
This is a lot more interesting.
Yeah.
Four people go.
And then there's like Billy and Jason Willner and the audience was just like at the Dorothy
Channel Pavilion, all just confused old people that did not know what was, it was so weird.
And yeah.
And the thing at the end is like, it's, they're all gay from their phones.
And then a giant wave with Karl Marx's face comes up and destroys the earth.
It like drowns them all.
What?
Wow.
How is that conveyed?
There's a giant like video screen behind them that they claim to have patented this
technology and it like, it just crashes up.
It's a tidal wave and it washes the earth clean.
And then- A lot happened in 5,000 years of civilization.
Yeah.
Their motto.
If this is an innovative screen, I feel like we need to renew it.
Theme parks.
Anyway, you guys should go to Shenyang or maybe don't go because they, they are crazy.
Maybe just- It's a cult.
Afraid?
Yes.
I'll do it.
Next time they come through, you should see it.
And then the next episode is you guys, or you trying to convince us-
Also the Chinese- To join their vacation club?
There's always- Bank of America flags your visa for buying Kevin Spacey and Shen Yun material
in one week.
I bought these coasters that say, I love Shenyang.
And my fiance was like, what the fuck is, what are you doing?
I came home with them.
He was like, why do you have this?
You're being tracked now.
I know where those things are going.
There's three companies or four maybe doing a Shenyang show at any time somewhere on earth.
Wow, really?
And the Chinese government follows them around and like slashes their tires on their vans.
It's crazy.
You can see that happen if you wait it around.
Yeah.
They get harassed.
Whoa.
Jeez.
Okay.
Okay, sorry.
So Disney- They're not there.
Well, Disney's not going to allow that because Disney has business with China to do.
Yeah.
So they aren't going to allow.
Well, I think it's interesting too that like the part of the Jehovah's Witness thing is
like you don't get birthdays, you don't get holidays.
If you knew a Jehovah's Witness growing up, they don't celebrate their birthday.
They don't do celebrations.
Prince didn't believe in birthdays.
Yeah.
Oh.
But I've seen- Wait, before he got religious though, I've seen the band lead a happy birthday
to him.
Not after though.
Not by like 95 or whatever.
So then you're not allowed so they don't get, you can't trick or treat at their house on
Halloween, all that shit.
But are they allowed to go to Disneyland?
That's a good question.
I don't know.
You can sit outside of it with a bowling table.
Has anyone ever walked out of Disneyland, met those ladies and gone like, well, that's
it for me.
Like, this is my new thing now.
Kids, we're Jehovah's Witnesses now.
It's only the line at Space Mountain had been shorter.
That's like the Comic-Con people that protest outside of like no false idols.
And you're like, is there one single person that like walked out of Comic-Con and went,
whoa, you're right.
And then like they were just- Jesus, the original Batman.
Yes.
They're right.
He is like Bruce Wayne.
Any comic characters came back from the dead.
His parents were murdered in front of him.
Yikes.
Oh, the other thing I read about the Jehovah's Witnesses at the table, they're not allowed
to approach people or talk to people unless you approach them first.
Oh, I talked to them.
Yes.
So you were allowed.
Wow.
Yeah.
How'd they go?
How'd they seem?
They were nice.
I talked to them, I think their name was Bethany and I asked her what her name was and I said,
how's it going?
Bethany.
I was like, can I have this?
She's like, oh yes.
And ask me, tell me if you have any questions and we're just spreading the word.
And I was like, cool.
There's one interesting thing in this death magazine that if you go to JW.org, they'll
come to your house and give you a Bible study.
You can like-
Did you arrange for that right now?
In here?
Come on in Bethany.
They're here.
Wouldn't that be a surprise?
They're all named Bethany.
It would be so fun if they just showed up right now.
Honestly, I would be delighted by that.
Yeah.
That we just, that's an hour of the Bible study.
Get them on mic, get three other mics out.
Yeah.
So just so you know, if you are looking around, I also texted Scott, I was like, I can't find
these pamphlets.
Oh yeah, that was fun.
It was like, ooh, this is going to be a fun episode.
Even making a point of finding the pamphlets.
I got a little book, more of a tiny little book called The Secret of Family Happiness.
I got two bookmarks in it.
So with some passages I want to read.
It is from 1996.
It is a family that looks disturbingly similar to my own.
Oh nice.
In you know, members, genders and floral button dresses.
So this is a bit of a, it's a bit of a flashback for me.
Let me see what I wanted to mark.
Oh right.
It's been the caretaker.
I, well, I didn't have time to read the whole thing.
There's a lot of pages.
This is 185 pages.
I just skimmed through it to find the word sex and I found it a couple of times.
God's view of sex.
Let's see.
The law frankly mentioned a number of sexual matters including menstruation, seminal emissions,
fornication, adultery, homosexuality, incest and bestiality.
Those last three of course all fit together.
Homosexuality, incest and bestiality.
Pretty much the same thing.
Yeah, pretty much.
That's a real 1996 religious attitude.
It's been crazy.
Looking back, don't you guys think it's odd how like now that we, now that the slippery
slope has happened and we allowed gay marriage, just how many of our friends are married to
the donkeys and the electric fans.
It's just, it's all other world.
I was then curious about the one that, I guess I know the word fornication, but I was never
sure of the exact definition and elsewhere in the book.
I looked at the like Amazon listing of this that pulled out some notable quotes and they
say, in the eyes of Jehovah God, living together consensually without the benefit of marriage
is fornication.
So we're in a house of fornication as we speak.
Uh oh.
Mike, I know she's, I know your girlfriend's coming on tomorrow, but maybe you should consider
marrying her before then.
Yes.
Before the episode.
Maybe on the episode.
Yes, that's fair.
Plus you've got that horned up dog of yours.
Oh, bestiality.
That's true, the dog humps my leg and that is I am sinning because I'm allowing it.
I think so.
Is that right?
She's shameful.
And a chick deuteronomy to be sure.
Because you have a messenger, there's a prince poster looking at us.
In front, there's always a witness staring at the dog humping your leg.
Yeah.
How dare you.
He's a Jehovah's witness.
And it's a room of false idols.
Yes.
Batman.
Leonardo.
The hat box ghost.
Ooh.
The cookie, the dog, the chef from Hong Kong.
Cookie from Hong Kong.
The hat box ghost.
Our Dr. T.J.
Echolberg looking down on us.
Judging.
Went over my head with that one.
The eyes and the great cat's feet.
Maybe if you did a little, I think you should do a little reading of that book and read another
book called The Secret of Family.
I was hoping when you said religious pamphlets, that would be Jack Chick pamphlets.
Do you guys remember Jack Chick pamphlets?
Oh, sure.
No.
Oh, there are these little comic books that this lunatic made by himself for like 40 years.
He died recently, but they're like little rectangular pamphlets and he's got his own
weird take on everything.
And he would update them.
Like he would, you know, he did one on how Harry Potter's a warlock, but they're just,
they're crazy.
Like there'll just be a, there's a really good one where it's like a rock band that's, that
signs a contract with Satan.
And then he's like, I've got a, I've got a gift for you guys now, some aids.
And so he gives them aids and then they, uh, there he is.
Yeah.
Never really evolved though past like the EC horror like style of art.
He always drew, he drew them, them the same forever.
But uh, here's one just of the devil saying you were wrong.
You didn't accept the Lord Jesus Christ as your personal savior.
Yeah.
He, it's always this like, I, I one time in college bought the full collection.
It was like $20 and I had like 150 chick comics and they were all the same.
And I immediately got really boring, but I was at the Albuquerque international sun port,
which they call the airport.
Uh, and I found one underneath a chair and I got really excited and I read the whole
thing and then I put it back where I found it.
And I was like, Oh, some kid's going to find this and it's going to blow their mind.
Like I did when I was 14 and found one, I was like, what the fuck is this?
And I showed all my friends.
I used to find them every now and then and laugh and they're so fun.
But then I think my little brother, like one of his classmates was like passing them out
at school, sincerely.
And he was like, what, what are you doing?
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I guess they could make you Christian or something, which would be bad.
Anyway, that's what I was hoping for.
But instead I got this death obsessed watch tower.
I have one more little passage, which is a, it's a, uh, it's basically about how, if you
are a single parent, a widow or a divorcee that you should not partake in sexual activities.
You should not experience the joy of sex if you've lost a spouse or gotten a divorce.
Not for you.
And it gives you a guide of how to get through that.
This isn't even a quote from the Bible.
It's just a Christian man said who?
It could be somebody who like bailed on it the next year or killed themselves.
Or Trevor said sexual urges are very strong, but you can control them.
When a thought comes in your mind, you must not dwell on it.
You have to get rid of it.
It also helps to think of your child.
Oh, that's good.
So the next time you're sad about your divorce and trying to have sex with somebody, think
of your child instead.
Don't cross those wires.
Yeah, I know.
Yes.
What a horrible moment there you're creating.
Also, if you were trying to deaden your appetite for food, would you read magazines featuring
pictures of delicious foods or would you associate with people who constantly talked about food?
Hardly.
The same is true concerning fleshly desires.
So you don't look at porn.
Yeah, I guess so.
Just like Sports Illustrated swimsuit edition.
Don't watch the Victoria's Secret Fashion Show.
Those delicious shows.
Don't watch Baywatch.
Oh, Scott.
Hey, no, stay away from Baywatch.
You're trying to dampen your appetite.
How have you watched that delicious show?
Everything you are describing is pretty much as a 12 year old Christian.
This is my...
Do you think...
That was all porn to me.
The most innocent.
Your epic rewatch of Baywatch that's going on right now.
Oh yeah, it's going to blast.
Do you think there's something in the back of your mind that's like, I'm getting away
with it finally?
You weren't allowed.
Like, this is my Christian rebellion.
Yeah, a little bit.
At last.
Well, there's still morality lessons within it.
Okay.
Although, wait, no, they deter...
Don't swim between the red flags.
I had very lax parents and probably full access to pornography or whatever.
And I spent all that time watching the Gary Glen Ross scenes with Kevin Spacey in them.
Being like, this is my guy right here.
I don't know.
Maybe he should have chosen porn.
The ref, his part where he destroys the Christmas tree and the ref with the fire poker because
Judy Davis is telling the story wrong and everyone's fighting.
So many wasted hours of my life.
It's so weird.
If we lined up all of your ex-boyfriends, are they all sort of like Spacey types?
No.
Not at all.
That's too bad.
If only, like, wait a minute.
I was needed a captain of all the teams.
Wow, really?
All the teams?
Yeah.
Like, cross and soccer.
Wow.
Pretty good.
We didn't have football.
I went to a hippie school, but I was dating Nick O'Donkers, the captain of the teams,
and I was lecturing him about Kevin Spacey movies.
Oh my gosh.
That's wild.
Go on, hustle, O'Donkers.
You got to get caught up on the show.
You got to get caught up on profit.
He ended up living on a tree platform.
What?
A tree platform?
Yeah.
Like in Santa Cruz?
People live in the trees in Santa Cruz?
He was, like, living on a tree platform, and I was like, are you protecting the trees?
He's like, no, it's just a tree behind an apartment I rent.
It's not even a tree house.
It's a tree platform.
Will you join me?
Will you be Mrs. O'Donkers?
Join me on the platform.
No, Nick O was his first name.
Oh, I thought it was Nick O'Donker.
Yeah, that's what I thought it was, too.
No.
Nick O.
How do you spell?
I'm disappointed by that.
Is it N-I-C-K-O?
N-I-C-H-O.
Oh, okay.
Oh, man.
Not Nick O.
Nick O.
Interesting.
Nice guy.
Sure.
He has no social media footprint, so I can't find out what happened to him anymore.
Oh, unless this somehow brings him out.
Yeah, Nick O, text me.
Nick O.
Nick.
When I thought it was Nick O'Donkers, captain of all the teams, that was one of my favorite
phrases.
I think that's a false idol right there.
He sounds like a superhero.
Come on, Donkers.
Pick up the pace.
So religious pamphlet.
And once armed with religious pamphlets and once you have a pure heart, you can make your
way to have some pretty good Italian food.
Oh, yeah.
At...
We're all thrilled.
Is it Naples?
Naples?
Yeah, Naples is the ristorante.
Is it new?
It's recently redone.
Because you guys usually go to Ovo Bar, right?
Yeah.
Which I'm sorry, Sector Keeper.
Yeah, yeah.
But it's closer and seems like a better selection of stuff.
Yeah.
Well, I don't think there was as much...
Did they even have the...
Is the bar...
Is the walk-up bar new or has that always been there and I just haven't?
I was just really impressed by their selection of local...
They had a lot of Green Bar Distillery Spirits, which is a local distillery, make refined
slow hand whiskey, the only LA whiskey, and it's pretty good.
Really?
Yeah.
And I was just like, the selection in general, I got a trio of Italian mules, like a small...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it was great.
That's great.
It was like they had different types of Amaro in them and they were just very interesting
and little tiny copper teeny mugs.
Oh, sounds great.
I loved it.
Yeah, there was a...
I think this is what the bar looked like before and it was just not as striking, you might
say.
This is tiny picture, I'm sorry.
Uh-huh.
It was just not as striking.
Yeah.
You could just pull up...
Our night before Galaxy's Edge, we were all hanging out out there.
That was a very chill, open air...
This is upsetting.
This is like one of the, I would say, better than fine places.
I had a blast and I just got a little minestrone soup and a shrimp Caesar salad, but they were
both great and my trio of mules was just so charming.
It was truly like the kind of drink you get inside a Disney park.
Yeah.
It's like fun and there's variety.
I liked my waitress.
She was sweet and I just had a...
I read my watch tower and I just chilled out.
Yeah.
Got some work done.
I like the pizzas.
My family is eating the pizzas there a lot.
I especially like they have the little pepperonis that are crisp when they cook.
That's a great idea.
If you look up hashtag pepperoni cups on Instagram, you can find people posting pictures of different
pizzas that have the little pepperonis.
It's like a whole thing.
I should have got that.
I think Farley Elliott told me about that.
I was describing it to him.
He's like, yeah, pepperoni cups.
Look up the hashtag pepperoni cups.
But yeah, the pizza's good.
There's a side of the restaurant that is just pizzas and salads, which is a pretty quick
in and out meal.
If you're waiting on...
If you got a fast pass coming up or something.
That's not Napolini.
I think, well, what's the divide?
Napolini is the quick service one.
It's the quick service.
Okay.
Really, this is three restaurants.
There's sit down naples.
There's just pizza and salads naples, which I think the bar is part of.
Yes, I think so.
Yes.
Maybe that's the only food you can get at the bar.
I've done the sit down and the sit down's fine, but it's like you're pretty quick in
and out with pretty quality food at the outdoor one.
And then Napolini is the quick where you do pizzas to go.
Where I bought two pizzas.
Yes, I bought two pizzas.
That's cool.
To Validay parking.
I know it's that.
You can also get beer and wine at the quick service.
Yes.
Oh, I wonder how's that?
Yes, and hard seltzer.
Oh, these are good tips.
This is the most like...
This doesn't sound like a compliment to call it functional, but for sure, you're right.
It's not that far from the parks.
You can get some pretty quality food.
The pizza I've had there has been great.
Not unreasonably priced beer and wine.
It makes you feel like you want to live five minutes away.
It makes this a place where you go.
Are you moving to Anaheim?
I say it a couple times to Lindsay once in a while.
I've wondered if Orange County somewhere is some kind of secret to happiness, but I don't
know where.
I don't think it's Anaheim.
Well, again, that Anaheim, the mythical Anaheim Hills, which I have not explored, but I've
heard tell of it.
So that might be it.
You just want to live at Tony Baxter's house.
You want him to adopt you.
Well, of course, I'd like to wait for him.
One of his houses on the block to open up, so we can move right in.
So you're next door neighbor.
My neighbor.
Borrow a cup of sugar.
Borrow original designs of the Alice in Wonderland ride.
Hey, Mr. Baxter, I'd like to trip a little light fantastic in your backyard, sir.
Does he live down there?
He lives down there, but he also installed all these lights from Mary Poppins Returns
in his backyard recently.
That's cool.
There's a big article about it.
Have you driven by his house?
No, I don't know where he lives.
I'm not insane.
You definitely don't know.
No, no, no, I don't know.
I don't know.
You described looking at Mary Poppins lights as tripping the light fantastic.
That's the name of the song from the movie.
From the new one?
Yeah.
Yes.
It's a killer joke if you knew it.
It is a good joke.
It's a good joke.
My mom just said she likes it.
He apparently was like obsessed with it and he put he decided to redo his whole backyard
to look like the lamp lighter scene, the iconic lamp lighter scene.
From the new Mary Poppins.
A couple years ago, I did this thing where there's this immersive theater company that
had a subscription.
I haven't talked about this on the podcast, but I bought into the subscription where they
were doing a play in my life for eight months and eight or nine months before they-
Oh, right.
You didn't know when they would show up.
They'd show or they would warn me, but they kept calling me down to have experiences
at midnight.
But they were in Orange County by Biola University, around by Knott's Berry Farm in this weird-
Yeah, I figured out pretty quick they lived there.
I see.
Because I kept having to go to this one area of condos and I was like, okay, you guys live
here, don't you?
I'd be like, so I'd have to drive down and it would take a while.
There was one cool bar that I would go to and get food beforehand.
It was the guy that now owns the Wolves downtown.
It was his first place he opened.
Anyway, but then I'd have to go up to a door and knock on it and then they would drag me
into a garage and interrogate me and then send me home.
I did that four times and then they moved away and they didn't finish my narrative that
I'd paid for.
I was like, I started lightly harassing them on Twitter about it.
They're like, okay, come back.
But then they made me go to Biola University.
So I drove down again to finish my story and it was midnight again.
Then they brought me into this conference room and they showed all my tweets to me that
I'd written or being mean to them.
They made you pay for your tweets-ins?
Oh man.
They really showed me.
Is there anything fun to explore around Biola?
I've never been there.
I like a good New Orange County thing.
I don't know.
I mean, I wish Puzzle Bar was still there.
You would love it.
But now the guy just has the Wolves, but all of his drinks were named after like, uh, animes
and stuff.
He made all of his own, but you just go to the Wolves now.
It's cool.
Same stuff.
La Mirada is where we're talking.
I would go to La Mirada maybe once a month.
And one time they came to my house and they arrested me for crimes.
A thrilling immersive experience about your life that is convenient for us to travel to.
Was it finished?
Did he get finished?
I did not feel...
Is it time to start harassing them again?
No, I will say that one of them came up to me and like apologized at the immersive design
summit for never...
He was like, we just got way in over our heads.
And I was like, it's okay.
I definitely got way more show than I paid for.
So they were, I was part of an experimental process.
Sure.
How many other people do you think were?
I, they said it was, there were a few more people.
But under 10?
Oh, under 10.
Yeah.
Wow.
And yeah.
Do you know the other ones?
There was nobody that I know.
Okay.
But I sat on a podcast and I thought it was just me.
And then they contacted me and said, there's a couple other people doing it.
No, no, there's others.
Anyway.
Wow.
But yeah, anyway.
So there are some nice places in La Mirada.
Okay, sure.
Sure.
But be careful of hijinks and get arrested.
Don't do that.
Other people in that condo complex, there was this one night we were all walking around
with monks robes, with monks, like they must've been so annoyed with the sprinklers kept going
off and hitting us.
They made me leave my shoes in a tree.
Man, it's one thing to use the rec room for an improv practice, let alone the costumes
and monk robes.
Oh my God, they're burning a witch puppet again.
It's going to stink for days.
Art collective.
We should talk a little bit about the, this is the first of many restaurants we'll encounter
that are part of the same shadowy restaurant group called the Patina restaurant group.
Oh yeah.
So Patina has a iron grip on Danta and Disney.
What else is there?
Stratia Joe's, Catal, Uva Bar, we'll be covering all of these.
They are behind the upcoming Epcot space restaurant.
Right.
Epcot Italy restaurant.
Oh, okay.
It's Annapoli.
The Annapoli.
The space is a collaboration, I believe, between Imagineering and the Patina group.
Oh, finally.
If you go to the restaurant in Disney hall, that's a Patina restaurant.
Yes.
And then you have the music center like by the Mark Taper.
That's where, that's a Patina.
Okay.
Black Moon.
Yeah.
They're in a lot of museums.
And Big New York.
Yeah, they were in the Norton Simon cafe.
Okay.
And then they have restaurants in the Empire State Building and in Rockefeller Center.
I will say that a Patina group sign inspires confidence in me.
Wow.
Right, so a place I can feel like I can get a reliable little nibble and probably like,
yeah, they probably have a nice glass of wine, something like that.
Sure.
Is that Norton Simon in Pasadena?
Yeah.
I re-ordered it wrong.
I started saying New York.
That's a good museum.
Yeah, that is a good museum.
Shout out to the Norton Simon.
They've got a bunch of Warhol crates in the basement.
Well, you're right to trust them because they are interested by Hollywood's second biggest
night, the Emmy Awards, to cater.
Do you guys know this?
No.
Patina caters the Emmys, Governor's Ball.
Wow.
Okay.
The people, well, there's two people primarily involved in Patina.
Nick Valenti, I'll get to him in a minute, but Chef Joaquin Splishol is sort of the main.
Same.
Yeah.
It's like, yeah, there was never a Wolfgang Puck, right?
Just has a ring to it.
Fictional character created.
Nancy Silverton invented him.
He's like Chuck E. Cheese.
Yeah.
In a lot of ways.
Is there a little book that tells me his best story?
Wolf Entertainment.
Yeah.
Puck.
Pucky Cheese.
He'd, you know why the, as we record this, the Emmys have just occurred and this year
was no exception.
He did the catering and the, there's a theme every year.
This year was brilliance in motion, which is why they had mini milkshakes and street
corn ravioli.
Ooh.
Brilliance in motion, I guess.
Wow.
I want that right now.
It does sound pretty good.
We just all gotta get nominated for Emmys, I guess.
If they open a podcast category, let's see what we can do.
Let me see what they, oh, it's very decadent stuff at that.
One decadent dopamine releasing spoonful of the pot de creme, a fashion by Lint.
It's topped by a tiny gold bar decoration sprayed with edible gold.
A quote from a Natalie dressed attendee.
This is why they hate us, she says, smiling wickedly.
Are they terrorists?
I think so.
Anyone out there, MAGA people, anyone outside of Hollywood.
That's a good thing to say when you're eating gold.
Very cool.
I think that maybe that refers to like all the, like 90% of lower tier members of the
writers guild.
I think that's what that's about.
I'm so tired of edible gold.
Yeah, yeah.
We just get it all.
It grows on trees in LA.
All the damn time.
Also this year they served a thousand calorie gratin.
Why would, why is it the calorie?
Why is it called that?
Yeah, why do they push that as in the title?
Is that just like very rich?
But like all gratin is already incredibly rich.
Right.
Isn't it already approaching a thousand calories?
Well, it's like you spent all this time getting into your little dress and you ate your little
packaged meals and then you lost to like Jason Bateman.
He won best director.
The best director we have.
So this is, you're the person who didn't win for directing Game of Thrones and then you
were like, fuck it.
I'm going to eat this thousand calories.
You needed it.
It's a baby bottle.
Yeah.
To nurse the wounds.
I know, you know what's fun is when those award winners, they don't go to the fancy
ball.
They go to in and out with their award in hand and then they get back in the car immediately
because it was a stage photo opportunity.
It took a minute and a half to.
I worked in a reality show back when I was a reality show person that was called Pageant
Place and it was like about pageants.
It was anyway, I was backstage at Donald Trump's Miss Teen USA pageant and the Pasina City
Civic Center and they put me in the losers room to interview losers, which was horrible.
But they kept eliminating these girls and they'd come back and there was just all this
pizza in that room and the girls would just be like stuffing pizza in their mouths because
they hadn't been eating and they're teens.
But anyway, we all remember that lady, that Miss South Carolina who talked about maps.
Oh, an early viral sensation video.
Yeah.
So she was that year.
So I was in the loser's pit watching all these girls eat pizza, watch that happen and they
had lost and she was still in the pageant and they all just like, there was this like
howl like this weird guttural howl.
Of just like rage and like, that I saw firsthand because they told us the pageant people took
us, well this is a spoiler, this is a secret probably, but they told us she was going to
win.
Oh wow.
And over there like she's probably going to win so you should be following her a lot and
she was like, so she came to the pageant as like the probable winner and then she did
that and she lost.
Oh my gosh.
She had it in the bag before the night.
She had been selected probably by Donald himself as the winner and then she was such a dumb
dumb they couldn't give it to her and this other girl won.
Selected by Giseline.
Yes.
Yes, Jeff and killing.
Speaking of in and out photo opportunities.
Do you guys know that I have shared a name with a character from the Epstein verse?
Oh yes.
I saw you posting that.
This is so weird.
I'm sorry.
It started popping up under like YouTube videos or like mentioned, like it'd be like, is this
the Eva Anderson who took the Lolita Express?
And I was like, what?
And then I, and it turns out it's with two S's.
She's like an ex girlfriend of Epstein's and she's in the black book right above magician
David Copperfield.
Whoa.
Who's also in the black book.
That's right.
Oh boy.
And you have magic connections.
I know.
Yeah, you've crossed paths.
So they're probably thinking.
He came to my house when I was a kid.
And he would come by and like buy shit from my dad.
Oh my, police monkeys and have them draw pictures of you.
To be fair, have you ever done some sort of train immersive that was called the Lolita
Express that's unrelated to the plane?
There was like this whole chain on, I found on Twitter where they put my photo up and
they were like, was it a childhood photo of you and your dad?
Yeah.
And they're like, she was on the Lolita Express.
And then, and then someone underneath was like, isn't her dad an admitted warlock?
Yes.
That's the thing about the, about conspiracy people is like, they are afraid of the dark
arts.
They are afraid of black magic.
But then like on this chain too, I found it was from, I was Googling my own name guys.
Someone corrected this woman and was this QAnon woman and was like, that's not her.
She's it's a different person.
QAnon to the rescue.
But I tweeted, but the picture of me had been shared like 60 times, like repeated 60 times
with my dad on it and everything.
So I tweeted at the lady.
I was like, Hey, that's not, that's wrong.
And she was just like, I was corrected already.
Just look at the whole, read the whole chain, please.
And I was like, okay.
Not a sorry, not a sorry.
I said, you went on the Lolita Express to the island where they think there's like a
temple with tunnels where that I went in the tunnels and got like Adrena Chrome with Hillary
from a screaming child.
I've already been yelled at a bunch of times today.
Last thing I need is a warlocks daughter bugging me.
Wow.
So I'm part of the Epstein verse.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I didn't know Epstein had such an elaborate Island, much like Copperfield.
It's probably what they bonded over.
Oh yeah.
There's a temple.
Whoa.
Did he build the temple?
I don't know.
And the Zorro Ranch in New Mexico from the earlier photographs, it looks like it has
a maze, which I find very interesting.
That's his ranch.
Right.
He had his own Neverland type, like he had his Neverland fun, like amusement park back
behind the house.
I meant to look up how far apart Mousha K and Little St. James are.
Is that how they know each other?
It's just like chartered flights to the islands.
To their sex island buddies.
To their evil islands?
Yeah, possible.
Didn't we say we think there's an underground tunnel probably to the islands?
Oh yes.
Oh yeah.
Or like the, yeah, the whatever it was.
The tunnel, what's underground?
What's the?
The tunnel.
Is it the tunnel I'm thinking of?
Something like that.
There's like a tunnel between.
Did you ever do, Jason Walliner and John Daly and I did a tour of Jalil Barajan's house.
Barajan's collection in Vegas, which is like an old.
Oh, I wanted to do this.
You told us about this.
We drove up to the house.
Okay.
Because it's the house where Michael, one of the last places Michael Jackson lived.
The Thrilla Villa where he like lived after he was exiled from Neverland.
And the reason he bought this house was it was made by, it was built by some entertainer,
some guy who like ran a bunch of shows in the fifties or whatever.
But he built a house with tunnels connecting all the rooms, which is not a good thing for
anyone.
Everyone needs tunnels.
No.
Alone.
Michael Jackson.
Well, he needed it so that paparazzi couldn't fly over and see him.
So we would never leave the house.
But it was crazy because you get a tour of the Thrilla Villa and the first.
So they're walking you through and they'll be like, you'll be in a room.
They'll be like, it's this really elaborate, like a room full of oil paintings.
Like all these oil paintings are on loan from the French consulate.
When Michael lived here, all we know is that this whole room was painted black.
The windows were blacked out and there was a single chair in the middle of the room.
Okay.
They just say weird things like that.
And then you go into these tunnels underneath and you and Liberace's collection is down
there.
Oh my God.
Underground.
Under in the tunnels.
Yeah.
And you're in it.
Also, like the reason I didn't do it is because you just, you told me a little more and you
said like, yeah, that guy like picks you up in your car with lukewarm champagne in his
car rather.
Yeah.
Like, Hey, come on in.
And he's got like lukewarm just bought champagne from Ralph's.
He bought market sushi.
To take you to a, to Michael Jackson's tunnel.
I think I looked into this and it wasn't running, but there was a, there was something.
You would love it.
It's fantastic.
I would really like to do it.
The guy who does it is the consul to Monaco and he's a whole character as well.
Oh great.
And he just tells you all about, he'll tell you all these secrets.
He told us like a bunch of weird secrets.
Just he's trying to, we got the feeling like if we had asked the right question, he would
have gotten us literally anything we wanted.
Like, cause he kept plying us with cheap champagne and sushi and being like, so what else guys?
Like he just kept trying to keep the party going and being like, so any questions about
anything?
In my fantasy of it, the guy who hosts the tour is a Josh Agabor's husband, the Prince
man.
Oh yeah.
I went to her estate sale and he was there in the room with us.
I think we may have talked about that.
Celebrity estate sales.
Oh yeah.
Jason.
I mean, we're, we got to get on the same mailing lists.
So yeah, I, I missed it.
I couldn't squeeze in the Jack Webb one.
I was really sad.
Jack Webb just had an estate sale when he had, did you see that?
I tagged even Molly Lambert.
He had nine TVs.
He would watch all the TVs at once when, when Dragnet would be on.
He supposedly, when he moved out, he packed one suitcase and walked out with everything
still in the house.
That's a crazy, that gave me goosebumps when I read that.
What was, what happened?
I don't know.
Like what happened to that man?
Just the facts please.
That's what I want.
Jesus.
I don't want any of this shit.
Do you guys know that my parents bought the first, the house that I was the first raised
at the first three years of my life was bought from my parents.
My parents bought it from Jerry Mathers.
Yeah.
Like it was like that, like that was a, that was a handoff.
Jerry Mathers.
You just moved up in the celebrity rankings in my mother's head.
You're now 25.
Another layer of the onion.
After the Beatles, the Monkees, David Cassidy, Bobby Sherman.
And now it's Scott because he lived in a house that was bought by the Beaver.
I grew, I was, I crawled around a room the Beaver lived in and then they were selling
the house not that long after.
And there was a plaque in there like the Beaver house.
Oh my God.
It was just a place where he lived and didn't.
The Beaver house.
It's still called as the Beaver house.
That sounds.
It's a great name for it.
The Beaver house.
Is that why they had a priest bless it?
Because like God knows what sort of business Jerry Mathers got up to in that house.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, my parents, as I've said before, had every house blessed so that it couldn't get
lit on fire.
Anywhere I lived would be blessed by prayer.
I should text my mom this right now.
Oh yeah, let her know.
I lived in a.
Oh, sorry.
I was just, the other thing about it, the one thing is that there was a hole in the
wall of the master bedroom that then my parents moved into.
But that apparently wasn't fixed before they got in there.
There was a hole in the wall that was distinctly a fist shaped hole.
Oh.
So.
He punched the wall because he was so mad.
He wanted to punch his wife, but he's like, punch the wall instead.
Oh, so actually I, you know, my whole life I've thought like, does that mean he was an
abusive guy?
But if it saved somebody from getting abused.
Yeah, you can't abuse a wall.
Yeah, you can hit them all you want.
Yeah.
Hit all the walls.
We lived in Michael Landon's house.
Old house.
Michael Landon.
And he told my dad that he had like, there were a bunch of pets buried in the basement,
like weird ones, like an orangutan and an iguana.
In the basement?
Yeah.
And he took it off where Michael Landon was like, enjoy it.
No, it was like some people that lived there in the middle between some old people that
lived between, but then my dad met him at some sort of function was like, I live in
your old house.
And he was like, oh.
And he, then he told him this was like grim, creepy thing that orangutan had died in that
house or something.
Was it an unfinished basement?
Like how was it, why would it be buried in the basement?
I don't know.
Like in the floorboards?
Orangutans.
This isn't Michael Jackson's house.
Right.
Yeah, I don't know.
It's like, I don't know.
It's weird.
It is weird.
This is reminding me something I saw, someone sent me a few weeks ago, there was tour.
Okay.
There were ghost tours, but they were advertising it as like ghost tours of Walt Disney's own
old house.
And it's not as famous like Homeby Hill, like his big house.
He lived in like 10 places in the Los Feliz area when he first lived here.
So it was a house, but very slyly the ghost tour operators put in like, and then the house
was also owned by the LaBiancas.
And I was like, oh my God, did Disney live in the LaBianca house?
No, it was just another house that the LaBiancas lived in before the house where they were
killed by the Manson family.
Different.
Wow.
Which you, yeah, that's not right to call it the LaBianca house.
You know what that means.
It's a LaBianca house.
It's a LaBianca house and a Disney house, but it's not the in either case.
Just think about it, guys, if Manson had just come a bunch of years earlier into a different
house, he could have killed Walt Disney.
Walt Disney.
Well, if he'd crank through it all a little soon, like there's maybe a little slice of
time where he was like on the prowl and doing drugs and stuff and Walt was going to die
in like a couple of weeks.
He could have gotten in there.
Yeah.
Just read it along.
James L. Roy wrote this book for sure.
It's like a crime conspiracy novel.
In a hundred years, this is what we'll think happened, like when all of history jumbles
together.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Manson killed Disney.
The 60s died when Manson killed JFK and then Disney.
A quick update.
I did find so Moosha Kay is in the Bahamas.
Little St. James is more between the British Virgin Islands and Puerto Rico.
So kind of a decent, decent distance.
The shuttle is big.
It's a big shuttle between the two islands.
They definitely visited each other's islands though, guys.
Yes.
For sure.
All right.
And now to unfavorite little St. James lest I get trapped.
Oh, yeah.
Don't keep that pinned.
I had to.
Yes, I had to get the pinned so I could see it.
Ghislaine like got put in, like got sawed in half, like giggling and a like a little
like trick and she was like, oh, David, like you're funny.
Would you like my monkeys to draw you?
You know what?
I've only ever drawn one person and it was Jeffrey Epstein.
Oh, when they're like digging through the remains of Moosha Kay in a Jurassic Park,
nature has been reclaiming it and then they find an old drawing.
Wait a minute.
And wait a minute.
And also there's been all these questions about how did Epstein just magically evade
the cameras, evade the security guards?
Maybe he had the help of a magician.
David Copperfield helped him fake his death in the prison.
We just solved it.
That's what happened.
That is honestly you're right.
It is what happened.
And maybe he's still alive.
Maybe he dug like a channel or something.
Do we know what what Epstein's father did?
Where did he work in the military?
Oh, do you have a question?
Did he also have a little friend that helped him?
So David gave.
OK, so David, of course, broke into the prison.
We're also, by the way, referring to things you have to listen to the Patreon.
Do it, the Copperfields episode is worth it.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, thank you.
He gave Epstein his time stone and sent Epstein back in time.
That's where.
So if they want to find Epstein, they got to go to the bath.
They have to go to the bath.
They got to go to a park where Epstein's dad is kissing Epstein's mom.
Love, Jeffrey.
The answer is love.
The message was love, Jeffrey.
There's a picture of Trump Epstein and Blue 32 hanging out.
Oh, man, I was going to get you guys those blue 32 pouches.
They're so ugly.
I was like, that's not cool.
I would spend one hundred and fifty dollars on that nice blue.
Like if they really just if they made him, I want it so bad.
I need blue.
Donald competing over the same pageant contestant.
Yeah, sure.
She's hot.
Donald.
Make sure to stick with her.
She's going to win.
It's honestly like they're the same sense of humor like Trump making fun of somebody
who can't speak English like Blue did during the Copperfield show.
Like, I can't understand it, David.
He drinks a lot of root beer.
Trump farts root beer.
I bet you know how his farts smell.
Please.
Oh, my God.
If you're confused by any of this, please seriously go to the Patriot and listen to
it.
OK, winding down, we should talk about the other figure in all of this in the patina
group.
Yes.
Nick Valenti.
And you know what's funny?
We've been talking about this.
We're in our this research has been going for a little while.
The first time I ever checked the website, it said founder and CEO Nick Valenti of the
patina group.
Now it just says founder because guys, he's out.
Whoa.
He's out of the company.
It used to be the patina group that runs all these restaurants used to be a two and
a half year old founder.
Nick Valenti hit the bricks.
I'm not sure what it happened this year is like like within the last few months.
Let me see.
He's just an external adviser through his company, Simple Hospitality LLC.
He works on special projects for this other not unnerving name for a company, Delaware
North.
Definitely not like a scammy.
Love board in that state, half run by DuPont, half run by credit card companies.
Sure.
Totally fine.
North Delaware?
No, no, not North Delaware North.
North.
Flip it around.
And then also, I think it's so it's been a tough little run for the patina group because
they've also recently been kicked out of Rockefeller Center.
So if you're if you live listening to this, you live in New York and you're a fan of patina's
Sea Grill Rock Center Cafe or Kuchina and Co.
It's well January 2020.
It's all out.
It's gone.
Wow.
So patina something's going I couldn't find any more information about the drama.
Right.
But Joaquin Splashall, king of the thousand calorie gratin has there's there's been the
split with with old Nick Valenti.
And I don't know what does this mean for their future at 1010 Disney?
What does it mean for the future of the company?
Yeah, that's a good question.
I mean, there's something we have to answer, obviously, on the next or downtown Disney or
deal.
Yes.
Two years maybe.
Yeah, or deal revisited.
Yeah.
It's good.
I was looking at all the list.
I will real quick.
I just want to praise them.
They don't have a lot of repeat name restaurants, which I like.
That's impressive.
The Disney Naples Napolini via Napoli is a little confusing.
Look, I'm just saying there's not they're not doing the they're trying to do different
concepts, which I appreciate.
That's anyway.
So we don't know.
There could be some shadowy things happening.
Yeah.
Evil.
I don't want to say evil spirits are involved in the patina group, but maybe something is
going on.
Interesting.
Maybe he was trying to propose less or more calories in the thousand calorie grotten.
Yeah.
And he was shouted down and stormed out never to return.
We don't even know what kind of express plane he's been on.
No.
A man with that power.
Right.
That's all he is went through to get to an island.
He's described everywhere as like a major New York restaurateur.
So yeah, who knows?
We know what's up in the New York socialite.
Yeah.
Hmm.
We're on to you.
Well, this is something we're going to have to just keep exploring, I guess, and for further
episodes because we got a lot more patina to go.
But for now, I guess we've went our way to the end.
And so we get to say, Eva Anderson, you survived.
Hey, where did Eva go?
What happened?
Wait a minute.
Guys are I seeing something or like we're looking over.
I looked at my notes to say goodbye and remind myself of Eva's name.
And then I looked up and she's not here anymore.
I looked down at my computer to remember Eva's name as well, just to make sure on the way
out you got it right.
Because you wouldn't want to say the name.
But she's gone.
It's just a puff of like marinara sauce, red smoke, which is different from the kind of
water vapor like buffalo ink flavored water vapor that the Sector Keepers been vaping.
Right.
Yeah, right.
Distinctly.
Huh.
But him being a vapor expert, maybe he could tell us what's going on or just explain what
the we've never had a guest to just not make it through the I say you survived.
I guess the ride.
This is the first time it hasn't worked out.
Yeah, I mean, there's been guests who like clearly like wanted to leave because they
were bored with us.
But they never actually disappeared on us.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Well, then maybe we need to bring in vapor expert and evil spirit.
The Sector Keeper.
We weren't planning on having him.
He just popped in to tell us where we're going this episode.
We got to get him in the room.
Hey, Sector Keeper, what the fuck's going on?
Boys, boys.
Sector Keeper.
What the hell's going on?
What happened to Eva Anderson?
I don't know, boys.
Things aren't good.
It truly is an ordeal.
I mean, I guess you said that there were evil spirits around these parts.
Is that what was the evil spirits?
They're nearby.
But what?
Boys, no, no.
What's happening?
He's changing.
The Sector Keeper is more.
It's Nick Valenti over here.
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Fuck you.
I'm trying to open restaurants over here.
The Sector Keeper has been demonet possessed by New York restaurateur Nick Valenti.
Oh, this makes sense at the end of three stages in a video game.
This is like a boss.
This is what the boss is talking about.
This is the boss.
This is Nick Valenti.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm walking over here.
Oh, my gosh.
He's a real New Yorker.
That is no place.
That attitude is no place here in Anaheim and the Anaheim Resort District.
Look at me, Scott.
Look at me.
I'm a man who opens restaurants, okay?
I was a goddamn CEO selling pizza, pasta, et cetera.
Yes, were.
You were.
That's the key word.
And you're not part of Patina anymore.
But I should be.
Yeah.
A snake.
There was a snake in the grass and he took my place.
What are you talking about?
Joaquin's fochal?
Joaquin's fochal.
Everyone knows.
It's his recipe.
He's the mastermind behind this whole thing.
Anyone could get in the kitchen.
Who are you?
You're my goddamn mom.
No, we're not.
We're Scott, Jason, and Mike.
I don't even understand that.
No, we are not.
And we respect the craft of the cooking of chef's.
I don't even understand that.
No, we are not.
And we respect the craft of the cooking of chef Joaquin's fochal.
And I don't respect you.
You know, New York businessmen are running amok through this world.
And it's about time that people like you be stopped.
If I could get my friend Giuliani on you right now.
My best friend.
Whoa, your best friend is Mayor Rudolph Giuliani?
More like brother.
That's the kind of person you hang out with.
That's not a person you want to be associated with today.
Listen up, you three little assholes come around.
Carefully, he's got a pizza paddle.
That's right.
I got a pizza paddle.
Oh God, to put in the wood burning ovens?
He's going to spank us with the paddle?
I'm trying to spank over here.
Oh God, he barely missed me.
Oh no.
Hey, sit still.
Okay, now I'm going to spank you.
No, I don't want to sit still.
Move your toys off the shelf.
Let's sit on the shelf.
Jason, why are you pointing your butt at him?
Do you want to get spanked?
Well, I don't know.
I don't want to be a distraction.
Anyway, we've got items.
We've got items to stop him.
Oh, that's right.
We've been getting the sector keeper whose body you are stealing right now.
He gave us things to help us.
We're going to defeat that paddle and we're going to defeat you.
What do we have?
What do we have in the inventory?
We have three black aprons from Starbucks and a side loaf of sourdough bread signed
by Nancy Silverton and Mark Peele.
Let's put on the aprons as protection.
Everyone put on the aprons.
Silverton and Peele.
I'm trying to open restaurants over here.
Are there other restaurants you're opening now?
Are you partnering with Rudolph Giuliani in any way?
Yeah, me and Rudy are going to open a restaurant.
Where?
Downtown Manhattan.
Wall Street.
Rokers only.
Oh man, you're going to kick some good old fashioned porn theaters out and mom and pops
will be out on the street.
We're cleaning up the city and we're serving pizza to the top one percent.
Only for the one percent.
Gold leaf pizza?
Gold leafs instead of pepperonis?
Is that what we're talking about?
That's right.
In that famous street, Wall Street located in downtown Manhattan.
Manhattan, Wall Street.
Never heard of it.
Yeah.
Buy sell, bitch.
Jesus.
Yeah.
You're probably going to have oregano that's shaved off of rainforest trees.
You probably scorch the Brazilian rainforest just to get your oregano.
Oh yeah, I live for that shit.
What is Giuliani going to actually be doing at this restaurant?
He's going to be tossing pies.
You're going to be able to watch him through a window.
It'll be like a little show.
He'll make the pie in front of you.
And if you say Rudy, Rudy, he'll wink at you and give you a finger gun.
Whoa, really?
Honestly, that actually sounds interesting to me.
It's a better thing than being a lawyer.
I think you'll be better at it.
Every dollar spent there goes to a super PAC to reelect the greatest president.
Oh no.
No.
All right.
So beyond saving Eva, beyond saving ourselves, we've got to save the world.
Trump's going to get a third term if we don't stop this guy.
Yeah.
Okay.
Abrons on, boys.
Abrons on.
Tie him on tight.
Someone beam it with this sourdough bread while I stick my little bottom out.
Jason, yeah, toss him with your little bottom.
Oh yeah, look at that little bottom.
I want to spank it with my pizza paddle.
Oh, he's leaning in.
He's leaning in.
Take the bread, Scott.
I'm going to sneer and give it to you.
The bread, it's crusty on the outside and stale, so it's extra hard.
I like you.
You smell like pizza.
Well, usually.
All right, here we go.
Right on the back of the head.
Oh, Scott, I'm going to get it again.
Again.
And again.
But we just got to be careful, though.
This is actually the sector keepers body.
That's right.
Oh, no.
Okay.
You can.
Wait, I'll use it.
Wait, I'll use the crack it open.
I'll use the sourdough inside to patch open the parts of the sector keeper that I split
apart.
Good as new.
Sourdough.
I love him.
Hey, quick question.
What was the name of the restaurant you were going to start with him?
I just wanted to know really quick before your spirit left the sector keepers body before
to do it.
He wrote is really good.
It's good.
It's really good.
Good name.
These are teas.
D. Yeah.
Yeah.
Hey, I'm dying over here.
Boys, boys, boys, what happened?
I'm not sure.
You seem fine.
I don't think anybody bangs your head in.
My skull is half red.
Yeah.
We do.
You sort of spazzed out and we took it.
It's an enhancement.
A lot of people are doing these days.
They're using dough.
It's actually safer than skin and skull.
Boys, boys, are you okay?
You look shaken up.
You're wearing the aprons.
Yeah.
The master brewer aprons.
We use to take down somebody who doesn't respect the work of chef.
Yeah.
Jason, you can not present your little bottom anymore.
Just use it now.
This one's wearing only aprons.
Well, we didn't have to strip.
Yeah, you stripped.
Well, I suffer for my art.
What are you going to do?
Okay.
The point is, Sectorkeeper, you were inhabited by a ghastly being and it's so good to see
you again.
And I just, are you feeling okay?
Can you count to 10?
Is everything you're not seeing crooked?
I'm feeling okay.
Okay.
In fact, for some reason, you've given me strength.
Well, so it was actually, I helped him actually.
Yeah, I guess it was 10.
Good.
We seem to have dissipated somewhere.
I don't know where, but they're not gone, boys.
Oh no.
But I have an inventory item for you.
I just received a text message from the level keeper.
Yes, the level keeper.
He or she had one text message left today from their cricket wireless prepaid phone.
Their precious last text on us.
What an honor.
Guys, I grant you two pizzas.
Wait, there's a little note, a little post-it note.
It says I grant Jason two pizzas from Tootie Rudy.
What?
Wow.
The defunct restaurant Nick Valenti and Rudy Giuliani were going to open?
Yes, just for you though.
Beta tested pizza.
That's great.
Wow, hand tossed by Rudy Giuliani?
That's what I was going to ask.
Guess so.
He could put his hands on this pizza, I'm interested, but we can't eat, Scott and I
can't eat it.
We can't have the pizza, we can't have Rudy's pizza?
No, no, just for Jason, but for you two, I have two pamphlets about the dangers of fornication.
God damn it.
That's not as good.
We just have to read a pamphlet while Jason only eats two pizzas?
But look on the back, boys.
It's endorsed by Rudy Giuliani.
Well, that's good.
He's been divorced so many times, he's no one to scold us about.
Oh God.
But look, he is America's mayor.
He is and always will be.
The future events don't erase that.
All right, well I honor him with this and I'll read every word.
And Jason, you ate every bite of that pizza.
Not a problem.
Wow, guys, we did it.
We survived our first boss.
Yeah, how about that?
Geez, it wasn't so bad.
No, it was pretty scary, but you look like you were having like a lot of fun.
Honestly, we Scott, when you were when I was doing whatever I mean, the sector keeper and
improving the state of his skull, I was just going to like say like maybe like talk to
someone because it seems like there's some anger.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I feel perfectly calm and I direct my anger correctly.
This one has sourdough on his hands.
Usually it's Jason.
I know.
And like like you were white knuckling it too.
Like it's under the skin.
Well, I guess Jason's lust for food is only matched by my lust for blood.
Fair.
We're all lust for something.
I'll consider trying to deal with this.
But hey, keep in mind, if you need me to be violent with anybody for the rest of the rest
of the ordeal, I'm your guy.
You're like the bear Jew in Inclerious Basterds.
You're the guy with the baseball bat that comes in.
You're Negan on The Walking Dead.
Hell yeah.
It's a new addition to your character.
All right.
Yeah.
Fuck yeah.
Well, all right.
Well, next time, next time, maybe next time we get some of these items, I'll like strap
some to the other and yeah, you know, like nails on a baseball bat.
I'm going to fuck somebody.
I don't know who else is coming up down this down this in this ordeal, but future bosses,
watch out.
Yeah, let's just call.
Actually I need to hear that.
I need to calm down.
Everyone needs a hit.
What flavor we got today?
Today's oh, today's flavor is oh, I'm dizzy.
Today's flavor is fun dip.
Nice.
That's fun.
Scott's going to take some too.
Mint.
Fund it.
Yes, they all have to be mint now.
Lust for blood decreasing.
Whoa.
Whoa, man.
Pass it down.
Here you go.
Hey, Jason.
I got food in my mouth.
Bring it back.
It's all right.
I can't do it.
I wouldn't do it.
All right.
Well, who we survive.
Oh, man, we survive podcasts.
The ride down to San Disney ordeal level.
What we did.
This is our first time.
Guys, yeah, we made it out.
All right.
So tomorrow we move to level two and we'll see what waits in store.
Who knows if anything scary happens, I'll make him fucking bleed.
Yeah, I.
Hey, so hashtag DDO hashtag save the level keeper and hashtag cricket wire.
And hashtag cricket wireless severance.
No, sector keeper cricket wireless severance.
Tweet that at cricket wireless.
Not at us.
Much appreciated.
Well, let's keep let's keep hitting this shit and I'll get recharged for tomorrow.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Forever.
This has been a forever dog production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe
Cilio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.
Facebook.