Forever...
...Dark!
Darkness falls out on the street, Evil is its head.
Get your crazy shake to go, And your fried doughnut bread.
Beignets.
The villains threaten this sacred place, This downtown shopping mall.
We must defend the Lego store, And the Splitsville bowling balls.
The Downtown Disney or to you, We must protect our AP discount meals.
The Downtown Disney or to you, With secrets does the Earl of Sandwich conceal.
Boys, boys, my cousin has been taken by evil forces that have inhabited Downtown Disney.
In order to find them, he will need to thoroughly discuss every aspect of them all.
Stores, restaurants, both of the Starbucks.
We have 15 daily very necessary episodes and much to do so. I will be there to guide you and keep your conversations from getting too off topic for...
...boring.
The Downtown Disney ordeal. Why do we do this to ourselves?
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Downtown Disney ordeal, Level 1 Stage 2.
This is our second day of our newest daily event. I'm Jason Sheridan here with Mike Carlson.
Our newest daily event. It's new. It's still very new. Day 2.
What you said is right. It does suggest that maybe we will just really expand the daily events soon, I guess.
Scott seems to be making noise. That's Scott's character suggestion.
Mortful Scott character.
The daily events.
A daily event. I try not to be a grouch, but a daily event is a lot.
Every once in a while is a little treat. It's been a treat so far, but it's only day 2, so it's hard to say.
Hopefully it will be a daily treat for everyone listening and not a daily chore.
A chore of deleting it from your podcast menu without listening.
That's a good point. Make sure to make room for this.
If you have albums like Apple Music or Spotify, delete those albums. You can stream them.
Also, here's the thing. You can go into your podcast app and if you want to make sure you have an episode marked as un-listened to because you want to listen to it,
but you want to delete the file, click on the little dots or click on the expand options, and you can delete the file but still code it as a new episode.
That's what I've had to do when stuff has gotten backed up.
Delete other shit so you can hear things like that.
Tips about dots.
But you also listen to this daily series and you get the presence of everyone's favorite ghost spirit who guides us through dining and retail locations.
Give it up for the Sector Keeper.
Boys, boys, you give me strength.
Hi Sector Keeper. Hello. Good to see you again.
Good to see you. Day two of the newest daily adventure.
One of many daily sagas. Good to see you. You're doing well.
Hey, you're hitting that PB&J vape that we went out and picked up together.
See, Uncle Scott hooks you up.
Uncle Scott maybe isn't the Uncle Danny.
Danny. Oh yeah. Yeah, all right.
Oh, I'm gunning for Jesse.
I think maybe that's kind of the subtle thing we can be doing throughout is like...
Character development?
Yeah. What I mean is that we have a rare chance to calibrate how cool we are.
We have a cool youth in our presence.
And I think right now I'm up points because I went and bought a jewel for him.
By the end of this, maybe you can make a determination which one of the three of us is kind of your coolest uncle.
Wow. That's interesting because for a while Jason was our barometer for the youth culture and terminology.
Sure, but he never put it into practice. He's never been a young kid here.
But now we got a real young kid, somebody really connected to youth culture.
Yeah, sure. No layers of irony with him. He's all in on it.
No layers of irony is what he said.
Oh no, yes, yes, of course. No layers of irony. Everything earnest for me.
Yeah. That's what people love about you.
So when you say throw up a dab, you're serious.
Always. Yeah. Yes.
Dabs are not to be joked about.
Right. Of course. Yeah, that makes sense.
Well, I think, you know...
And when I say bae...
Right, earnest.
Earnest.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, because I think we say it with a twin.
Yeah, and if you say you stan something...
Then I really stan it.
Right, earnest.
Earnest.
Yeah. And you caught up really fast because you were locked in an eternity cage for a long time.
Yeah, Toby, my boss at Cricket Wireless, he would tell me some stuff.
He tossed off, so he caught you up on the coolest trends.
Some stuff, yeah.
Was he younger than you or was he an older guy teaching you youth stuff?
Much older.
We're always going to be failing in comparison to Uncle Toby.
Yeah.
Like you, but older.
Okay.
Interesting.
Huh.
He really took you under his wing, huh?
Mm-hmm.
And gave you jewels constantly.
Introduced me to jewels, yes.
But now I get my jewels on my own.
Yeah, sure. Yeah, yeah.
Give me some credit.
He helped you get the peanut butter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, don't forget about what old Uncle Scott's...
And maybe if these guys bail on it, just you and me will go see Good Boys together.
Whoa, Good Boys, yeah.
I'm lobbying hard to be the coolest older man here.
Hell yeah.
Yeah, the podcast's coolest older man award.
And you know what's great about what you got me?
It's peanut butter going in...
And jelly coming out.
Oh, he did a ring.
He did a ring plume.
Wow.
Oh my God, a jelly ring.
A jelly ring?
Oh, that is so...
That is so funny.
A jelly ring.
That's a youth thing, I think.
That's so...
Yeah, youths yell out jelly rings, and I let him do it.
Man, you and me, SK, thanks for making the room so fragrant with your jelly rings.
Of course, of course.
But boys, boys, it is after all stage...
Other way.
Level two, stage...
He's jeweling.
Give him some weight.
Other way.
No, it's level one, stage two.
Level one, stage two, yeah.
There we go.
Yes, yes, boys.
Where are we heading?
That jelly jewel gets in your eyes, you know?
It's all foggy in here.
It's all foggy.
Level one, stage two, boys, are you up for it?
Do you have strength?
Yeah, yes, yes, we do.
Yeah.
Okay, boys, your mission today to discuss and review, to help find my cousin, the level
keeper.
The level keeper.
Level one, stage two is Starbucks, Sunglass Icon by Sunglass Hut, and of course, Curlsurf.
Curlsurf, yes.
All right.
These are all real places.
We need to get all as much, a high amount of interesting info about all of these places
out so we could save your cousin.
Yes.
And boy, do we have a fascinating one today.
Starbucks, a Seattle-based coffee chain.
You may have one in your neighborhood.
Take a peek, see if you do.
Lots of them everywhere.
This is a, this is one with a very tall ceiling.
Yeah.
High ceilings, yeah, man.
Maybe the, I mean, for sure, I think the highest...
Really high.
Yeah, man.
Highest ceiling one I've ever seen.
I don't know if it exists, but is there, are there two-story Starbucks?
Do we know?
No.
We don't know.
We don't know the answer.
We should have looked into it, but this is very high ceilings.
I like that.
It's very wooded in there.
Beautiful.
Wooded, beautiful.
It's a well art-directed Starbucks.
Yes.
Yep.
I'll say that.
There's some nice foliage, good tree and plant situation.
The courtyard's built around an old ficus tree.
Oh, yes.
I know that.
We're going to get that cousin free real soon.
What with interesting facts about old ficus trees.
Ficus tree, beautiful tree.
Good place to get some work done, I'll be honest with everyone.
I roam around the resort sometimes with my laptop doing some work.
I feel like you name checks like 10 plates.
You just plant and then move and then plant and then move.
Well, here's what I do.
Okay, I'm going to let the listener in on a little bit of a secret here.
So sometimes when you're a childless man in his 30s and you're trying to get some writing
done and maybe you're depressed being in the apartment, you go somewhere where you're not
depressed.
The Disneyland Resort, I drive down when it's not that crowded on the freeway and I will
do this.
I will try to get about an hour, hour and a half of actual work done.
Then when I hit a roadblock, I pack it up, put it in my backpack and go on a ride.
I will then after that leave the ride and go at a different place in the resort and
do try to do some more work and I will repeat as long as I have time.
Do you want to tell the listener, where do you think the strongest Wi-Fi spots are?
That's a real crap shoot.
Is that a secret?
No, I'm not going to hide that from the listener.
Starbucks is pretty good.
The hotels have a lot better.
Yes, the hotels, I like the formerly whitewater snacks, whatever it's called now, I forget.
It doesn't matter.
It's not part of the district.
No, I know.
I'm just saying that's good Wi-Fi in the hotel.
Yeah.
We're not supposed to be talking about this.
It's a little out of bounds.
All right, all right.
But the Wi-Fi at the Starbucks is pretty good and I will sometimes go over to that Starbucks,
you know, get a green tea or something.
What you're saying is there's a Starbucks with Wi-Fi where you can get work done.
Yes, but it's in the best place on Earth.
You can pay a buck more for everything.
Downtown Disney.
For beverages out of a little carton.
Yes.
Remade ice cream.
And like they're not day old baked goods, but they may as well be.
That's sort of the feeling.
I mean, I like a Starbucks cheese danish, you know.
I don't not like it, but it all isn't fresh.
No, no.
It's not fresh.
I'd rather just go to a local.
I like the coffee, but I'd rather just have a local donut shop.
Do you go?
It's not an option.
Mom and Pop say.
Not when you're here.
No, for sure.
Is that number one or do you like Danish?
That kind of depends on the establishment and a Starbucks Danish for sure.
Sophie's choice.
Yeah.
Yeah, I would say that a lot of like mom and pop places in L.A.
if you don't get there early enough, the date, the like croissants are gone like that.
OK, so so OK, you had a really doughnut.
You add a donut shop.
Donuts, of course.
But like a bakery, I like to see what their specialty is.
But sharing cheese danish is usually my go to if that's available.
It was an establishment where they made everything pretty much of the same quality.
We're talking then donuts, cheese danish, croissants.
What is the number one?
Oh, gosh.
Do you think you would go to if they're all of the same quality, if they're all the highest caliber?
No, I mean, it kind of depends on how hungry because I could eat a donut if I'm not that hungry.
But a danish could be kind of big.
A danish or a croissant could be kind of big.
OK, so it sounds like donut is sort of the winner.
Yeah, it can be big.
Some places make it kind of big.
Yeah, but it's fluffy, though.
What do you put?
You put something on it, but it's buttery.
No, you just eat it plain.
Well, no, I usually gravitate towards either an almond croissant or a chocolate croissant.
I noticed that you I think I pointed out years ago that you call them croissants.
And then I realized a couple episodes ago you said it and I was like, oh, he's not saying it like that.
But I think you fell back into croissant.
Or a cream cheese croissant.
Well, my mom used to because she took French in high school.
She trained me to say croissant.
But then I feel like I sound like an asshole when I say that.
Yeah, very much so.
Yeah. So I guess I've tried not to do that.
Yeah, sorry.
What do you guys lean towards for your breakfast treats?
Doughnut.
Doughnut?
Yeah.
I don't eat the treats ever.
You never have a doughnut?
Almost very rarely.
Really?
Sectorkeeper?
Doughnut, yeah.
Yeah, doughnut.
I'm working in an office right now with this free doughnuts every Wednesday and I don't ever do it.
Whoa, what?
Yeah.
The free thing.
I'm breaking young hearts here.
Doughnuts every Wednesday?
Yeah, yeah.
I haven't.
Interesting.
I don't know.
I have like a quarter of one if I am.
If you get the right ratio of like a sweet doughnut and coffee, you're almost high because you can really slow down.
Like when I was younger.
Whoa.
Riqui and montage of grabbing doughnut.
I would eat a doughnut like in the morning for breakfast and be like so sluggish because I would have it with like orange juice.
And it's just like so much sugar at once.
But if you have caffeine, if you have a decent coffee and sugar, you balance out to the perfect equilibrium.
You can ride that high or not, baby.
I mean, you just start the day off feeling great.
You are I think are the most affected by sugar of any of my friends, I think.
Because like I don't I would always know the kids would say like, oh, you get a sugar high.
And I even when I would eat candy, I never felt a difference like caffeine.
For sure.
There's a difference.
I don't know if I noticed the high.
I noticed the crash.
Hmm.
I mean, if I if you drink a sugary drink, sometimes my stomach will feel a little weird.
But in general, I don't feel like hyper from or I don't feel like even a big crash.
I got the hyper part.
I love it.
Well, you love course.
Every time I have it, I want more of it.
Sure.
They say it's a day.
It's very addictive.
Yeah.
I'm worried that you're going to start that that sugar is going to be a gateway drug and you'll start getting different kinds of high.
No way, man.
Well, that's good.
You seem like you seem like a good kid.
Just just my jewel.
Does that make it to you?
It's OK for now.
I mean, I'm worried we're going to find out some bad things about what jewel does to you.
But for now, I guess you're OK.
Oh, Scott, we still scientists still have not found out the long term ramifications of diet coke.
So it's going to be a lot longer for a jewel.
We don't know what type of like artificial sweet.
He's saying if we don't know about diet coke, there hasn't been enough decades of research.
Like, oh, it takes like a long time.
It takes a long time.
OK.
Hmm.
What about a bagel, Scott?
I've become a little more bagelish.
Yeah, maybe it's bagel.
Is it an aversion to it or is it just sort of that part of your routine?
They're not out for breakfast.
You know, I'm way more likely to be out for lunch or dinner.
Sure.
That's what I mean.
I don't have going along.
I'm not going to bakeries.
Yeah, I don't have donuts a lot.
But if I if I if I'm out or something, you are.
I feel like you're popping into the weekends.
Yeah.
You go to Dunkin or you go to you have a couple of donuts a week.
A couple of donut spots.
Not a week.
Maybe once a week on the weekends.
OK.
You live the life I dream.
Yeah.
Ice cream, ice cream, tummy aches whenever he wants.
Yeah, I actually I recently I haven't Danish in years.
I had a day a cheese Danish from Starbucks while I was waiting for my laundry to dry.
They're nice, warmed up.
Does he live the life that you dream?
I relate to this one.
I mean, two points adjacent.
Yeah.
So so so.
Oh, we talk about the screen.
Yeah, there was a fun digital chalkboard.
We had so much fun together.
We do. We were with the sector keeper in this particular Starbucks.
And I want to just let everyone know this is the Starbucks closest to World of Disney.
It's not the other Starbucks.
We need to make that clear.
Regular Starbucks on the eastern side.
And you know what?
I don't think I said in the last episode that I I watched this video like the what you watch in the hotel from 2003 that tells you what you know all of all of the night spots and everything to do and then Disney.
And they used some term that they don't think apparently this whole area that we're in right now is the Eastern Garden District.
They don't really do it anymore, but it might help us since we have so many areas to worry about.
So we this is so it's that we're in the Eastern Garden District Starbucks.
OK, got it.
Yeah. Cool.
Jason's writing it down.
Writing it down.
Eastern Garden.
Yeah. So not the and this is the larger of the two.
It came in there right around when Disney was beginning its its Starbucks partnership because you got Starbucks in the parks as of like 2013 2014.
The Market House on Main Street in Disneyland, the Fiddler, Pfeiffer and Practical Cafe in California Adventure, which if you want your Starbucks to take if your complaint is it's not slow enough, then go to Fiddler, Pfeiffer.
If you want your Starbucks to take six times longer than any Starbucks on the face of the earth and to pay a dollar fifty more.
This is the Starbucks for you.
That one used to have a full hot sandwich menu, too.
That was very good. And it took forever because essentially they're serving two restaurants.
They were serving a full service Starbucks and a full service sandwich restaurant.
And it was kind of a mess.
You know, it's a nice thing that really helps with efficiency.
So especially if you land from a drive where you need some caffeine, do the mobile ordering of the Starbucks while you're on that, you get on the parking tram.
Oh.
Make sure you pick the right one because you might get delivered near a totally different Starbucks.
It will automatically sense your location if you don't select otherwise.
Yes.
Yeah. So be careful there. Pick the right one.
But getting off that tram and there being a Starbucks beverage waiting for you is a real treat.
That's great. I love that tip.
Obviously, I'm a big mobile order guy. You cannot mobile order Starbucks in the parks yet.
No.
Which, yeah, that's a big problem.
You can use your app and get your stars and points.
Yes. Can I? I'm going to complain real quick about the app.
And this is not just Starbucks. Don't get donuts.
This is too. They won't let you just add the amount you need.
You have to buy a ten dollar gift card to reload.
If you're making a mobile order, am I wrong about this?
No, you can add it in the app. You can select the amount.
I just think I think they Starbucks, I think, said it.
So the lowest amount you can do is 15 Duncan.
You can add 10, but you can add value within the app.
But you can write specifically the value or am I just getting tricked by some generic default?
I think it's just a couple options, but I think you can write that.
Well, here's what I'm going to do. I've loaded them both recently.
I'm going to investigate this.
Now, I try to drink coffee at home primarily, but when you're out and about in the big city...
You're raising your voice.
Now, let's now, don't tell me I worked coffee out.
I think we should investigate this. I will bring it up on the next Starbucks episode, which is only a matter of days away.
I don't want to say that, but I want to settle the Duncan.
Because I just have a few. I feel like they try to make you.
It's just sort of a trick to make sure that you come back.
They'll make you put like $10 in or something as opposed to just reloading the exact amount you need for your purchase.
I'm so confused. You said so many words just now. My brain just floated.
My current balance.
Only Jason and I are on the same page right now.
My current balance is $7.35.
It does seem to be interested in both of you checking apps to save different money amounts.
Right, boys?
Okay, so Duncan specifically says $10 minimum, $100 maximum.
$10 minimum. That's what I'm saying.
You can only put $10 at a time.
Meaning instead of just driving up and saying you want like one donut and that's $1.50.
Basically, you have to put $10.
You want to add $1.50 and spend it and then add another?
What it's doing is perpetually making you come back over and over again.
But I'm going to perpetually come back anyway.
You both are. You think you're going to just stop after the $1.50?
No, I don't, but I don't quite like the idea that they're doing a little trick.
They're trying to trick me into.
How are you having this many thoughts while you order a fucking coffee?
I'm a thoughtful man who thinks about angles.
I think about angles on things.
You know what? I'll say this. I'm going to meet you in the middle. I think.
Hey, welcome to the middle.
I think I think when you are like a buck or two short, when you have a balance,
like let's say it's $5, but you only have like three bucks on there.
I think it should prompt you.
Like, do you want to add the $2 to even it out?
Yes, that's what I'm saying.
That I think is reasonable.
You have to load 10.
So say I'm $2 short on my balances in the app.
It makes me reload another $10 and I don't like it.
I don't like the feeling of it.
If you go to the cashier and I think you will be spending, by the way,
you're definitely spending the new coffee place or a new donut place pops up.
I never go to Duncan again.
Has that happened?
Not yet, but there's a chance though that maybe I don't want to ever want to use it.
Maybe I have a bad experience at Duncan.
I think the host of this show never go to Duncan again.
I don't know. I'm saying I don't like the idea of it.
And I think I'm not alone.
That's my feeling about it.
I don't know if I'm wrong.
But do you carry the cards?
Do you still carry cards?
You just have it in the app.
It's just in the app.
Okay.
So I have cards just in case it's down.
Gift cards?
Yeah.
You always have multiple gift cards?
No, hold on.
I have a Duncan card and I have a gold Starbucks card in my wallet.
Really?
Wait a minute.
What?
Yeah.
You carry hard cards.
Wait a minute.
Wait.
The Duncan card is not a gift card.
It's just a physical representation of your app.
Well, when I first put credit, they weren't pushing the app at the time.
Right.
So I just got a card.
I put $10 on it.
And that's how I racked up points originally.
You got your Duncan platinum.
So I just put that in my wallet and it's just still in my wallet.
So you have backup cards in case your apps fail.
Sometimes the apps are down.
Okay.
Interesting.
How many cards do you have in your wallet in general?
A lot.
Like this ballpark?
Like at least a dozen.
Okay.
That's not as many as...
Credit and debit cards, health insurance, dental insurance, prescription card.
Donuts.
Donut card.
Coffee card.
Those are the basics.
One or two like a Barnes and Noble gift card with like some credit left on it in case I'm
out and about.
What's it called when you're a spirit and it feels like your spirit left your body?
A double ghost.
Like a spirit we've checked out.
And you and me, we've checked out.
SK is number one right now.
I can tell.
Why don't we say to be continued at Starbucks West?
Of course.
We'll talk a lot more about this in Starbucks.
And obviously the listeners will chime in and say, do you like the psychological effect
of having to load more money on your card than you're actually about to spend?
We'll see.
The time that's wasted in caring about it.
Yeah, that's true.
But this show is all about wasting time.
I mean, that's very true.
This is certainly true.
You know, I don't know much about software design, but I do notice user interface, user
experience changes.
But there's something...
And I like to toggle.
Here's what I'll say.
This is my final thought on the matter.
There is something psychological when you're thinking about getting a coffee that if you
know you already have $8 on a gift card, you might psychologically want to use that more
because you've already spent it.
So you will go to that place over a different place.
And I don't care for it.
Do you hold...
When you get the rewards, do you hold on to it until you're like, I'm going to get a real
big one?
No, I like to just sort of do add-ons.
Oh, you do the...
I say I don't really do add-ons.
I like add-ons.
I'm like...
We'll talk about that in the next one.
Talk about it next time.
Because we're going to have my order.
I know that.
Hooray.
Yeah.
We're going to have our order.
That's...
Amen, brother.
All right.
Not complicated enough.
Let's talk about the screen.
Wait, wait.
We stopped talking about the screen.
Yeah, the screen is really cool.
It's a home screen.
The screen is cool.
It's like a living chalkboard.
You can write things on it.
You could take a picture where it looks like you're a chalk drawing.
Yes.
And it seems like there was a function that was broken maybe that we could see what was
happening in Florida.
Is that what...
Yeah.
It seemed like they were trying to flash to Florida.
A postcard to Florida.
Or we were sending our postcard to Florida, but we didn't receive any from Florida.
Yeah.
We didn't have to receive a Florida postcard.
What time were we there?
Could that Starbucks have been closed?
Because three hours ahead.
I think you're right.
We might have been there at nine or 10.
Yeah.
So perhaps...
No, not earlier than that.
Eight maybe.
Yeah.
Who knows exactly whether the function was broken.
But it was cool.
I didn't even really realize it was in there until we were there.
I mean, the funniest thing, there was a little fly crawling along it.
So right.
He was adding little dots.
It was on interactive video screen and you could draw things and write things on it.
And we saw the cutest thing in the world.
It was a little fly and it was drawing on the screen.
And at first we thought there was a problem and why are these little dots showing up?
No.
But then I see what's making it.
It was a cute little fly.
In an eatery.
The place you want them.
He had just taken dips in each one of the coffee with his little fly feet.
And then he decided to fly over to the screen and draw.
And he drew for a while.
Yeah.
He made a big design.
We were watching a fly make art.
Yes.
Or as Jason frames it, maybe that's Bugmane making putty sauce.
Could have been.
That's what he said.
Yeah.
So we were delighted.
That was wonderful.
That was a highlight.
And then we did a lot of, hey, the Sector Keeper, we made some fun art with you were
writing our name and posing in the photos.
So people look closely at the photos we post on Twitter.
You might be able to see what the Sector Keeper looks like.
Yeah.
For me, it made Starbucks fun.
Because do you like any of this?
Because coffee, are you getting into coffee?
You're getting older.
But coffee still, I mean, I guess teenagers, that's when you start getting older.
Getting into it, and especially the really like, you know, the froufy drinks.
Sometimes if I have too much vape, I'll soothe my throat with coffee.
Just pure black coffee.
I don't know.
I think any health problems you encounter in your coughing and what have you might be
self applied.
Hey, Sector Keeper, this is the first appearance of a business that's present at both downtown
Disney and CityWalk.
Yeah.
We have Starbucks at CityWalk as well.
I would spend time there every once in a while.
Sure.
Both get really busy.
Very busy.
I can't imagine why you'd go to either of them.
Maybe the Disney one because of the screen.
But other than that.
Or the tall ceilings.
Or the nice smells.
The possibility of seeing a fly.
Riveting.
I would say maybe bring your own fly in and unleash it on the screen to see what we're
talking about because there's no guarantee you're going to get to see an adorable fly.
Trap a fly, go to Disneyland.
Let it loose in Starbucks.
If you get it in a plastic container, you can bring it to security.
I don't think there's any metal in a fly.
The interior of this Starbucks is apparently partially made with reclaimed wood from old
railroad boxcars.
Wow.
Which made me wonder, Jason, does it make you flash to some past life when you were
a hobo boy riding the rails?
Just hiding from the yard cops.
Hiding from the Bickerton's and their Shillelies.
That's a stressful memory.
Yeah.
That's not fun.
We were imagining a Little Rascals type situation.
I mean, once it's moving, it's fun.
But once you get to those yards.
They start scraping the sides with their batons.
Yeah.
You could end up on the wrong side of it.
Come on out.
Come on out, you lot.
You lot of you.
You lot.
Come on out.
That's right.
You and your officer O'Brien.
It's officer O'Brien and O'Malley's here too.
One of my ancestors is in the boxcar.
The other ancestor is outside about to beat the hell out of them.
There's one more thing about this particular Starbucks.
We sent out a tweet and said, hey, if you have any memories or facts that we might not
know about downtown Disney as we head into the ordeal, please let us know.
I did that partially due to a dearth of interesting information I was finding.
And Sam on Twitter wrote back, that Starbucks is one of the only ones where everyone is
allowed to wear black aprons.
Especially it's only certified coffee masters who don't wear green.
Wow.
And we got a number of responses to that tweet.
I think that is the most interesting one.
And I noticed a lot of people had memories of downtown Disney Orlando.
Way more.
This was a and some of the stories were just like, I think somebody was like, I went on
a Tinder date there and it didn't go well and I left.
Like that's what that these are the cherished memories of the place where we have to live
for 15 days.
Apron colors.
Yeah.
Yes.
A little dry.
I really like searched.
I didn't even find the wood that would thing.
I was like, whoa.
When you just said that would think I was like, holy shit.
I'm pulling it out.
So that was impressive.
I think that would ficus tree.
Yeah.
You got a an outdoor wall designed with a thousand native plants in the shape of a coffee cup.
What are you doing?
Y'all.
We stand.
Yes.
We stand big up.
You truly when I was thinking like, oh, city like City Walk really seems like we were talking
about some of the greatest moments in American history compared to this at this point in Episode
two.
It's also recent.
A lot of it's recent.
That's the problem.
And it's all it's all since 2001.
So you don't have any like particularly awkward genre throwbacks.
So everything's stuck in time, but in this exceedingly dull time.
Yes.
Disney still has a relationship, though, with that Joffrey's coffee, which I think is supposedly
all right at like a Joffrey's location.
But when it's brewed within the parks, like at restaurants, people are like, this is dire.
This is very bad.
I don't have any opinion on Joffrey.
Do we know who Joffrey is?
It's a coffee.
I think it's Florida based.
I mean, who he is.
It's not the Toz R.S. Giraffe, I'll tell you that much.
No, Joffrey.
Much less likeable Joffrey.
No, Jeffrey is the name.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's all right.
It's all the same way.
I think I say more like Joffrey because of the GEO.
This is J-O-F-F-R-E-Y, right?
Yeah.
Well, let's get to another topic that's much more interesting and has so much more information
that we could talk about.
Here we go.
The next one, of course, is icon.
Son glass, son glass icon by sunglass, by sunglass hut.
I have a lot for this.
You do?
Yeah, I do.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, lead the way.
Okay.
So I mean, well, our experience with it.
I'm just gonna say how.
We all went there together.
We were gone in two and a half minutes.
Well, we stood our experience directly is we stood outside and it was there were two
salespeople inside.
Oh, that was I'm thinking of Pearl Surf.
Okay.
We didn't go in, did we?
And no, we were too intimidated to go in.
It was not enough people.
They would have talked to us.
Yeah.
Bad times.
This is a fun moment where we get to, as I'm sure will happen a lot on this series, examine
the parent company.
So sunglass icon.
Here we go.
Here's where we learned about how the glasses industry is one big con.
So Jason ruins glasses, sunglasses, sunglasses icon by sunglass hut is clearly owned by sunglass
hut.
Sunglass hut is owned by just grew a couple inches.
Sunglass hut is owned by a company called Luxottica Group.
Luxottica Group owns lens crafters, sunglass hut, apex by sunglass hut, Pearl Vision Sears
optical optical, I med vision care plan, glasses.com Ray Ban, Purcell and Oakley.
They make frames for the brands that for designer brands to Chanel Prada, Giorgio Armani, Burberry,
Versace, Dolce & Gabbana, Mew Mew or mid Mew.
I can't.
I just got to fuck up.
And then Turt and Turi Birch.
So in 2017, 2018, they merged with a company called Esselur, becoming Esselur Luxottica.
Esselur Luxottica is responsible for creating the very first progressive lens and combined
this company controls one quarter of global eyeglass sales.
One quarter of global eyeglass.
What's the next biggest eyeglass company?
I don't know.
I think it gets smaller after that.
Are you saying that?
This is a monopoly.
I was going to say they have a monopoly because they own different parts, different stores
and they supposedly compete against themselves.
I remember growing up doing this dance at the mall.
My mom would be like, we can look into lens crafters, but we'll get a better deal at Sears
optical.
But it was all the same.
Usually the price points were a little lower at Sears and that's probably why she wanted
to go to Sears.
But yeah, I mean a lot of these like Ray Ban was just a solo company and then just got
bought up at some point.
So you're kind of blowing the whistle on an eyeglass monopoly that's happening.
We don't like whistle blowers.
No, that was a month ago.
You used to call them spies.
That was a month ago.
He's obviously out of office right now.
I'm sorry.
I gotta forget we're pre-tabbing.
Everything's fine.
Yeah, so and also this isn't cheapy eyewear anyway.
This is like designer.
No, the cheapest.
I looked.
Did you look?
The cheapest eyewear is $50 here and I'm going to complain because sometimes you step on
your sunglasses and you break them and you need new ones and go in and get a $10 pair.
It's vacation.
I don't know why.
Again, they're catering to high end customers exclusively.
I guess in the parks there's spots where you can get like a cheaper pair of glasses.
Maybe the hotel gift shops.
Maybe there's a rack.
Yeah.
I just think there needs to be like a clearance rack in here.
Yeah, for sure.
Put a clearance rack and dress it up.
It doesn't have to look shabby.
What's your guys' eyeglass, let's say sunglasses.
Oakleys.
Set up.
You're an Oakley boy.
Okay.
I love one day I want to own Oakleys.
You want to own Oakleys.
I hear dream.
Yeah.
But you just got laid off.
Yeah, I know.
But one day I'm going to be wearing Oakleys and playing in the big leagues like Robin
Ventura.
I hope so.
Yeah, I hope so too.
Yeah.
Not without sunglasses.
You need sunglasses first.
They'll never accept you.
What about you guys?
Well, when you lose your sunglasses all the time, there's only one brand for you and that's
Panama Jack.
Oh, sure.
They're going to be cheap ass CVS sunglasses because they will be gone in six weeks.
Panama Jack.
Mike.
How much are they?
20 bucks.
I've never worn sunglasses more than $20.
I don't even, I'm trying to, I'm looking actually at what the name of it is.
I will generally go on Amazon and buy like a lot of like $10 different color wayfarer
type.
Yeah, cheapy wayfarer.
Very cheap depending on, and they're usually under $10.
I think one time like five years ago, I just bought a box of 12 for like $25.
Yeah, I used to do that.
So and I break them all the time.
I'm still, I have these multicolor glasses I got for a freebie at Comic-Con two years
ago.
There's like 18, it says AT&T on the side, but they're like multicolor.
I like those.
This is a thing where I am the one who is splurged the most because I have real Ray-Ban
wayfarers and they are one of the most single most expensive items I own because they are
prescription.
Right.
I was going to say you have your glasses.
So you have, that's a concern.
Yeah.
I mean the frames alone were like a hundred bucks or 120 and then the lenses and all the
coatings and like my insane least strong prescription.
And I had good eye insurance when I got these and it was still like 250, 300 out of pocket
or something.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Dollars?
Dollars.
I mean, I have more money than anything.
Did you make like, were they paying you like sub minimum wage at a cricket?
Were you in like the, is it like four, four bucks an hour?
They were paying me an experience.
Oh my God.
You were a cricket intern and they laid you off?
Yeah.
Jesus.
It's like a comedy theater or something.
You're gonna have to do audition to get in the cricket?
Yes.
You just had to do like sample wireless.
I took cricket classes and then once I got through level seven, I got into the advanced
cricket intern program.
You got onto a Palm pilot team.
Yes.
Geez.
I don't.
I had to pay my boss.
You had to pay to work there like essentially?
Yeah.
Doesn't make any sense.
It's a community, right?
If anyone tweets about, in anger about what happened to you, I feel like it's just going
to be a big old mess that never gets solved.
Yes.
I, I, that's why I hopefully you all use the hashtag, hashtag sector keep, sector keeper
cricket wireless severance.
Yeah.
Right.
We will.
Not at the show at cricket wireless.
I'm not going to crack the Twitter account, cricket wireless.
I don't know how you feel about this insane training program.
Yeah.
I found this, I can get eight of the sunglasses I buy for $13.
That's what I used to that or just buy them on the boardwalk like down the beach.
So that's basically what I do.
You and I, our sunglasses money in two years combined doesn't equal what Jason had.
Yeah.
Well that makes sense.
My constant anxiety that I have forgotten them or left them somewhere.
I leave mine everywhere.
I break them constantly.
So it just, I've never ever invested in any sort of.
I can't have nice things.
Expensive.
Yeah.
I know what will happen.
When I, when I had like smaller, thinner glasses, I would buy, you had to put cheapie wayfarers
over top.
Uh, but these are, when I got big thick glasses, I had to get the, get the prescription and
it is nicer.
It is good.
I like it.
Yeah.
So, uh, what else we got on the sunglasses?
Yeah, that's it.
It's all just one big, it's all just one big shell game.
It's all just one big con.
I have question.
Yes.
Why is it called sunglass icon?
Oh, yeah.
We haven't really covered that.
So it is a sunglass hut.
So it's the only, there's only two sunglass icons around and they're in Disney on both
coasts.
Right?
Am I wrong?
Another double coaster.
And I honestly, now that I don't know if I came upon why they call it sunglass icon
is it Mickey?
Are we talking about Mickey?
I think it's like they're trying to like, like it's a special, it's special like Disney
world and Disneylanders, but this is a special sunglass hut.
Who would you say is a sunglass icon?
I'm sure there's a very, dreams Dean slide deck.
Elwood blues.
Sure.
Uh, that's something for later.
Ferris Bueller.
Yeah.
California raisins.
Man, dad who left them on, on the credit coaster.
They have Mickey, they have a brand of a Mickey specific sunglass thing that they're pushing
in the store and online, um, of sunglass icon, but I don't know who does it, does anyone
ever use that phrase?
Boy, what a sunglass icon.
Like what is it even with the right sunglass?
You just haven't, nobody's wearing their perfect pair yet.
I guess so.
Yeah.
The idea is like a exclusive destination downtown.
The classy word icon mixed with the word hut and the double also a brand name with a one,
a word in it twice.
Yes.
McDonald's cafe by McDonald's restaurant.
Well, that's McCafe and it's really an experience more than, yeah, well they named it, look,
they named it correctly.
If they'd called it McDonald's cafe by McDonald's restaurant, that's stupid.
So I, yeah, it seems they're just trying to be classy.
They're trying to make it seem like it's a classy thing, I guess.
Cause that is what the whole idea of, I think downtown Disney is like a sub scale, you know?
It's interesting.
Similarly, uh, we didn't get, I had info and we didn't get to it when we were talking about
Carthay circle, but the, what Carthay circle replaced was, uh, the, the, you know, the icon
of the original California adventure, the big gold sun, which were the actual name for
it was the sun icon.
Really?
I never knew that.
The sun glass icon was really near sun icon, which is by the way, the flattest.
Yeah.
Cinderella castle, the spaceship or spaceship.
Sun icon.
The thing that haunts and plagues us here in Southern California.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
That's getting worse and worse.
It wreaks havoc on our life.
And in California venture also, there was a dinosaur with the sunglasses that sold sunglasses.
Am I wrong?
I believe so.
Now though, yeah, those were a little cheaper.
So those were cheaper, but that's gone now.
And I still remember forgetting sunglasses once and spending like 20 bucks for a shitty
pair there.
Yeah, sure.
It can be done, but not at sunglass icon.
No.
By sunglass hut.
Which I think we've determined.
High rollers.
Is a monopoly, a waste of money and time.
So there's two things I want a future president to do.
Number one, pass a law that says you can't make people load up a gift card for more than
they're going to spend.
That should be outlawed.
And number two, break up big eyeglass.
That's what I want.
Elizabeth Warren's talking a lot about breaking up tech companies.
Talk about big eyeglass, Ms. Warren.
Does she have a plan for these things?
We don't know.
Shouldn't we be talking to definite candidate Joe Biden instead?
Yes.
Who is for sure still in the race.
Listen here.
By the time this comes out.
I grew up with Mr. Sunglass and what I really liked was how much he said I was great.
Thank you so much, dear.
He's taking money from the sunglass hut.
He's in Ray Bans pocket.
Joe Biden bad.
Oh, you don't like Joe Biden.
I met him.
Really?
Where?
In the 90s or recently?
Purgatory.
What?
Did he die once already and come back?
Every once in a while, he'll die.
God.
And he gets resuscitated?
Multiple times.
Then he comes back.
Whoa.
That's how it seems.
Watch closely.
Does it happen like mid debate?
Yes.
Like if the camera's not on him, he'll nap and then that turns into death?
If the camera is on him.
Oh, that explains it.
His teeth start to fall out.
So he came and popped in, said hey to you.
Yes.
Yeah.
He'd be in and out in the holding area.
Did he ever like pull you close and put an arm around you in a way that you didn't approve
of?
Always.
Oh, man.
I knew it.
Did he ever briefly dying to inappropriately put his arm around?
Did he have a nickname for you?
Yeah.
Corn pop.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he did.
He did.
He called me corn pop.
He just re-recycled the name.
When he talks about corn pop, that could be any number of many people he's known on earth
or in purgatory.
He calls everyone.
Yeah.
He just tosses it around.
It's like saying like you or hey, what's up, slick?
Like anyone you can't remember the name of.
You didn't even take the time to learn your name.
What a son of a bitch.
He doesn't get along like you and me do, SK.
No.
He's like, yeah.
Yeah.
If he takes money from mom.
Oh, yeah.
Jelly rings, jelly rings.
Yeah.
I think you gained like an inch in diameter there.
Nice.
Noise.
Am I even cooler because I said noise?
Yeah, feels good.
Yeah.
Feels good to get my fix.
Are we ready to move to Curlsurf?
I think so, yeah.
Yeah.
Well.
All right.
Curlsurf dinner, nanana.
Curlsurf rules.
Let's show it the proper respect.
Yes.
As you know, the full name.
You have it.
I don't.
Do you say it?
I'm not sure.
Yeah.
The full name of this establishment is Curlsurf by Sammy Duvall.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I do have that.
You, man.
There's only.
Just be a name.
Only two of these exist.
Two of these exist.
Where's the other one?
Disney Springs.
We don't need to go to Disney Springs.
It's all the same shit.
But there's probably differences in the way that the stores are laid out that we really
should we should talk about.
So say OK, you go.
You go first.
No, no, you go now.
I just want to get that name out there.
So Scott, did you look into Sammy Duvall at all?
Oh, I miss this.
Educate me.
Oh, man.
OK, here's what I find interesting.
And there's not really a lot of answers.
Is that Sammy Duvall?
Sammy Duvall.
You summoned a photo of like a painting of Sammy Duvall with jet skiers under him.
Sammy Duvall is a jet water skier, an Olympic athlete, a child prodigy, a child prodigy.
And he is he has been connected to Disney for 25 years in some capacity.
And I this is shocking to me.
Yeah, I didn't know any of this.
So I was looking at Curlsurf and it's like it's a brand that basically like you go in
there and you can buy like Billabong and you can buy different skating.
O'Neill, Oakley.
And like good stuff.
Well, yeah, Oakley, sector keeper Oakley.
Yeah.
And I want to play in the big league.
So I was looking around and I was like, you know, I like clothing, whatever.
But I didn't know anything about Mr. Sammy Duvall.
No.
So Sammy Duvall has two stores.
I'm like, how did he get involved?
Because like these are the only two stores.
Sammy Duvall had something at the Walt Disney World Resort called Sammy Duvall's Water Sports
Center.
I just got to it.
Sammy Duvall was there for 20 years, I believe.
And this is the place where you would water ski or parasail over Bay Lake.
Oh, yeah.
He took over my beloved Pablo Cruz water sports zone.
Yes.
OK, from the Contemporary.
This closed or it closed like a year or two ago.
OK.
And it was there for 20 years.
So anytime you were doing any of those water sports at Disney World, it was Sammy Duvall's
branded water sports, essentially.
Yeah, I did it.
You did.
Yeah.
So you water skied or you parasailed or?
Uh, water skied.
Sure.
And it was expensive.
I looked it up, it's like 150 bucks to do that.
And you could.
Did you make it?
Did you get a lot of water in your mouth and your face?
Was it pleasant?
No, it was fun.
Yeah.
I always wonder if you if you go to Disney World, why do that?
Because you do whatever your heart did.
A dream is a wish your heart makes when it's fast asleep.
So you do whatever you want.
I think it's very held over from the 70s, like it's a vacation destination.
That's why there's got to be golf.
There's got to be an equestrian thing.
It's for dad, I think.
That's I think a big selling point, especially the 70s and 80s.
Dad would go there and he'd be like, I don't want to go on this stupid ride.
And you go, well, do you want to get in some water skis?
And he goes, oh, no, you're talking golf.
Yeah, no, I'm not going to sound like this.
Early marketing for Walt Disney World was like, this is a vacation destination resort.
You know, put on a suit for dinner.
Go parasailing, go water skiing.
Put on a suit and go parasailing.
Yeah, put on a suit and do that.
There's a great, I think it's called the history of Disney World in documents.
And it like catalogs like a lot of old tourism brochures and documents.
It's great.
Like I would love to fully like go through like the early days of Disney when they were
like, well, you'll go to the park.
Sure.
But then you also want to have a buffet meal and see some Broadway singers and then take
a putt-putt boat out.
And the plans for like the Persian resorts.
Yes, the Persian resorts, which looked very beautiful.
And then the Islamic revolution happened.
So the funding disappeared.
Yes.
They should bring that back.
Yeah, they should.
I mean, it would be a great olive branch.
Boys, boys.
All right.
Just to Sammy Duvall.
I just got a text from the level keeper, my cousin.
He said back to Sammy Duvall.
Okay, back to Sammy Duvall.
So on the Curl Surf website, this is direct copy from it.
And this is very succinct about Sammy Duvall.
Who is Sammy Duvall, you might ask?
He one of the most accomplished water skiers in the world.
So there's a typo.
So it's he and then one.
And both words are capitalized.
And this is like.
We here for you.
We're.
He one of the most accomplished water skiers in the world.
I just could not stop laughing.
And I copied it.
I copied it because it's kind of in like a.
It's like a same copy.
I have the same and I put it in the notes just to make sure I wasn't seeing anything.
I have it in here and it just says he one of the most accomplished.
He one of the.
He one of the most accomplished.
He one of the most accomplished water skiers in the world.
It's just a little too long to put on a t-shirt, but it makes you.
Or to fit into a meme because that's what I'm picturing.
He was a child prodigy and won more than 80 professional championships throughout his
career.
He was sponsored by brands such as O'Neill, Oakley and others.
Oakley.
Yeah.
So kind of brand agnostic.
This has a lot of different brands.
They got those Herschel backpacks that are like seventy five dollars and kind of chintzy
when you start to open them up.
Those little backpacks with the dragon on the back that I don't know how to pronounce
in the name, but they're all the rage.
Mm hmm.
And it it says that he's built on those relationships to develop the ultimate retail experience.
Yeah.
So I'm just like, when did he get involved?
Did he talk to like people at Disney about opening up only stores that are at Disney?
Like he's in the family.
I think it's going to keep happening.
Well I'm just like, who else is affiliated with Disney?
And then like they're just in the family.
They're like, you know, we got to find something new for Sammy to do.
Did Sammy come in with schemes?
Like you know, you got to.
What if I sold a bunch of skate shoes?
You know, I don't know.
I'm just interested in this guy who only can get a store open at Disney World.
That's a hard retail space to have.
Very specific.
And it's like, I'm just, I couldn't really find, I was like, I looked up Michael Eisner,
Sammy Duvall expecting like them to be water skiing together in a photo, but I didn't find
it.
And maybe I just need to do more digging.
But I couldn't.
He's like a young man.
He's not old.
Yeah.
Sammy, Sammy Duvall's water sports center.
That sounds to me like one time I played golf at a Lawrence Welk golf resort.
Like I would have, I would have expected that Sammy Duvall like died in 1979.
Water sports center.
I like, you know, I like old timey crap, but when I would stay at my grandparents sometimes
if they were watching us and they would watch the Lawrence Welk show every night and I was
like, oh man, even I have my limits.
That's exactly the line I think is like that.
That's the exact example of like things that don't cross generationally at all.
Yeah.
I liked Matlock.
Okay.
I liked Matlock and diagnosis murder because they're mystery, they're mysteries and like
crime, but they were never too stressful.
Never too exciting.
And those are younger guys you can relate to.
Yeah.
I got life in them.
I did have a very good Pizza Hut personal pan pizza at the Welk resort and took a photo
next to a Lawrence Welk statue.
It was a good time.
I don't know what that is.
It's in San Diego County.
So they would check out Welk resort.
They would sell Pizza Hut at the Welk resort.
Wow.
Cause they, they sell Pizza Hut in one of the, I forget which like a Hilton hotel near Disney
that I've stayed at with my family.
So they do have like a Pizza Hut express.
So it's interesting to know that the Lawrence Welk family.
Interesting to know.
It is.
Your boy said everything reboot.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
Will they reboot Lawrence Welk?
Sarah Lawrence Welk Jr.
That seems, I don't know.
Maybe, but maybe there's a way to, what would that look like?
I get, would you like polka music and bubbles if it were played by 17 year olds?
What would you?
Yeah.
You're exactly.
You're the young audience.
We can focus group on.
Yeah.
So you'd get into polka.
So you like bubbles flying around like you're back in the bowl bath as a kid.
There's bubbles flying around and music.
Yeah.
That sounds fun.
Wow.
All right.
So new Lawrence Welk.
There's a new Lawrence Welk out there.
There's, there's a new service called Quibi.
You could pay me pitch that to Quibi.
Yeah.
I, as long as Quibi is still around by the time this episode comes out.
Well, no, it hasn't launched yet.
I guess you're right.
So, but it's, but if you're listening to this, if you're listening to this in May, 2020,
then you're listening to it on Quibi podcast because they bought us out because they are
all entertainment now after a month.
Yeah.
That's a good point.
They're all Quibi employees and they also, which actually was purchased by that big eyeglass
company.
Oh, Luxottica.
Luxottica owns Quibi.
Esselord Luxottica.
And we have to plug their eyeglasses.
Yeah.
While we were talking, while we were talking just now, I went back to my photos from when
I went to the Welk Resort in 2014 and I found a sign in the window of a beverage they serve,
almond champagne, the Oh My Gosh champagne.
What?
I don't know.
Oh my gosh.
I want to try it.
I do not remember I had this photo.
The Oh My Gosh champagne from Wilson Creek at www.gotalmond.com.
Whoa.
Gotalmond, which just combines into Gotalmond.
Got a lot of questions.
I mean, they've got to reboot this.
Reboot almond champagne.
Get the kids drinking.
You get off the jewel in a second if you had almond champagne.
Is the Welk, is that place still there?
The Welk?
I think so.
The Welk Resort in San Diego.
Yeah.
Let's all have it down there.
Maybe after we go to that rock place that invited us.
We got invited to a fake rock factory and we haven't taken them up because it's far
away.
Is it by San Diego or is it more by?
It's weird San Diego County.
Oh it is.
Like you're in like Temecula.
Okay.
Yeah.
So we can go down some almond champagne and then go see some fake rocks.
God, that sounds great.
You're invited.
You're coming along.
Yeah, I'm in.
Yeah, yeah.
Bring some almond jewel too.
So Sammy Duvall has got some relationship with Disney and I'm just, I want to know what
does he have on them?
What dirt does he have?
What does he have on them?
And it's like, yeah, I mean.
Is it Wide World of Sports?
That's different, I think, right?
The Wide World of Sports was a different.
Yeah, that was a different part of property.
Yeah.
Did he participate?
It's a good question.
I don't know the answer to that.
I feel like this was his own thing.
I think he stayed in his lane, his water lane.
But I think, but he got a cut, I'm sure every time any dad went up in a parasail, you know.
Grumpy dad.
Yeah.
Whenever one of your boat drove her dad around in the air.
Sammy Duvall got a taste.
The custom stores that are only in Disney Springs and downtown, is it like a couture?
Like they're like, well, you can't get these anywhere else.
Is that what the idea?
I don't know.
I'm so fascinated.
This is a, City Walk has its own version of the surf clothing store.
That must just be a thing that sells well.
Billabong.
Right, Billabong.
Billabong still going strong.
Element closed.
So I don't know if they saw like.
Sorry, sir.
Whoa.
Remember what a great time we had at Element?
Never again.
I feel like it's been only months.
All of these places closed.
I know, and post our show.
Yeah.
It's like we didn't get the tourism up there.
Or we did and they bungled it.
It's like I left and it started to crumble.
You were holding on to all the calories.
Kind of, yeah.
That is what happened.
Maybe we have to go back.
Oh no.
We're only in episode two.
There's only like one new place.
The rest are just empty storefronts.
You're going to send us a fucking 11 more missions by the end of this?
Yeah, it's really going to be our newest daily series.
One a month now.
No.
Malls, reviewing malls.
So yeah, Sammy Duvall, he's a man of mystery as far as I'm concerned.
Maybe they just saw an opportunity where like we need a surf shop with surf type clothing
and they go, you know, Sammy would be perfect for this.
Let's get Sammy involved.
Sammy's got any ideas?
And he's like, yeah, get all the brands in one spot.
I've developed a relationship with all these brands from my time as being a world champion
water skier.
And they're like, this guy's perfect.
And they got him in.
They brought him into the tent and it makes a lot of sense.
So let's see.
Very nice scene.
This is a very polite business transaction.
Sammy seems like a great guy.
We like the stuff in the store.
I think we all like it.
Sammy Duvall has great taste.
So I am interested to see if Sammy Duvall's Curl Surf can expand past the downtown Disney
and Disney Springs areas.
Can we see?
I don't know.
There's not a lot of language.
Get him on Shark Tank.
It's like a water thing too.
Hey, that's great.
Yeah.
So here's a little tease.
A Shark Tank cast member will factor into a future stage.
Great.
Get your hopes way up for how interesting this is going to be.
Edwin literally popped up.
He first said that.
Yeah.
Who's it going to be?
Cuban?
You don't know.
Damon?
Time will tell Edwin.
I don't know.
So anyway, I'm out of interesting things to talk about.
Me too.
I've come to my end.
Yes.
Out of uninteresting things to talk about.
Exactly, that's not totally true because I went to gotalmond.com and it redirected me
to almondchampaign.com which informed me that it is no longer known as almond champagne.
It is now almond sparkling wine despite the web address being almond champagne.
Well, did it redirect or it's still our almond champagne?
It's still almond champagne.
Is it fermented?
It redirected from Got Almond.
Oh, okay.
Is it just a brand of champagne or is it champagne made from fermented almonds?
I can't.
There's a whole story.
I don't know.
Who knows?
But they keep reiterating that it is the, oh my gosh, champagne.
Oh my gosh.
But I'm getting ahead of myself.
We'll deal with the walkers later.
Boys, boys.
Yeah?
You've done so well.
You give me strength.
And we did still because I feel like we meandered a lot.
But if you consider that strength, then I'm happy.
There was a little bit where I think I dozed off.
That's fine.
But you didn't meet Biden in purgatory.
Yeah, I did meet Joe Biden in purgatory.
Not long enough for the nap.
But you did so well.
Yeah.
And I've just learned that by giving me strength, my cousin, the level keeper, he's texted me
and you've given him or her strength as well.
Great.
And I have something to add to your inventory, an item for completing.
Next boss.
What was the name of it again?
It was level one, stage two.
Level one, stage two.
I reward you three black aprons.
The aprons from Starbucks.
And we get to wear them even though we're not master brewers.
Yeah.
You've earned them.
Whoa.
We did something else more valiant than cooking a good cup of coffee.
For those who didn't know, you one of the greatest of all time.
We one of the greatest.
Wow.
Cool.
I'm pretty honored by this and I'm excited to store up these aprons and hopefully they
can protect us from a boss, which that is what's around the corner tomorrow.
Yeah.
Because we will encounter our first boss and I'm nervous about it, but I'm invested enough
thanks to the kindness of your cousin and we'll try to help him or her out.
Yeah.
So you've survived Pockets the Ride, the downtown Disney ordeal level one, stage two.
And if you want to do more of this, follow us on Twitter, Instagram and Facebook.
Hashtag DDO, hashtag save the level keeper.
Hashtag at Cricket Wireless, hashtag sector keeper.
Cricket Wireless severance.
Great.
And as always, three bonus episodes every month.
If you subscribe to podcast the ride, the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the
ride.
So get a good rest.
You're going to need it.
We're going to need it.
Boss tomorrow.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever
dog team and liking our page on Facebook.