Forever...
...Dark!
Darkness falls out on the street, Evil rears its head.
Get your crazy shake to go, And your fried doughnut bread.
The villains threaten this sacred place, This downtown shopping mall.
We must defend the Lego store, And the Splitsville bowling balls.
The Downtown Disney or to you, We must protect our AP discount meals.
The Downtown Disney or to you, What secrets does the Earl of Sandwich conceal?
Boys, boys, my cousin has been taken by evil forces that have inhabited Downtown Disney.
In order to find them, you will need to thoroughly discuss every aspect of the mall.
Stores, restaurants, both of the Starbucks.
You have 15 daily very necessary episodes and what's to do so. I will be there to guide you and keep your conversations from getting too off topic or boring.
The Downtown Disney ordeal, Why do we do this to ourselves?
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, The Downtown Disney ordeal level 3 stage 1.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Jason Sheridan.
Yep.
And Mike Carlson.
I'm here in this level and stage.
This is this makes day 7 of what is if you're just joining us for some reason or just need a recap or refresher.
I do.
I'm lost track for any number of reasons.
Yeah, I know.
And we're all discombobulated from our run in with Rick Wetzel.
So we're thrown.
So to remind everybody what's happening, this is day 7 of a 15 part daily series where we explore every store and restaurant in downtown Disney, which is, of course, the outdoor shopping mall outside of Disneyland, outside of Disneyland, between Disneyland and California Adventure.
Yeah.
If all of this sounds a little trying, that's because it has been.
I'll be honest about that.
My voice cracked as I said it.
And there's, by the way, if you don't, if this is too much, there's plenty of episodes about rides you can go back and listen to.
Yes.
Go take a break if you need to.
If this is bothering you, yes.
Go get the taste of the regular.
Two feeds.
Two feeds worth of attractions.
Yeah.
Listen to the Haunted Mansion one again.
Lots of dry info there.
But here we're doing it.
We're doing a different thing.
It has been our deal, but I'm excited because today, tonight we are talking about my favorite thing in downtown Disney.
And doing it with one of my favorite folks.
Returning to the show from Saturday Night Live, Kyle Mooney is with us.
Kyle.
Hey, Captain.
This is great.
I know.
Yeah.
It's great to see you guys again.
Likewise.
I love hearing your voices all the time on your podcast.
Thanks.
Oh, man.
Thank you, Kyle.
Thanks for listening.
Thanks for checking it out.
Yeah, of course.
And for returning.
You came here, I mean, not directly, but you were at Disneyland.
Today.
All day.
Yeah.
So what time is it right now?
Do you tell that to your listeners?
Do you not like to reveal that you have?
It's not like the talk show thing where you tape it earlier.
It's a good question.
It's like, I guess if we don't say it, it's because we want them to think it's like live.
Like even if they know it's not like intellectually, they kind of want to feel like it's live.
We can kind of say.
I was at Disney, I think two or three hours ago, essentially.
That might be one of the quickest ever.
It's like full nighttime.
Yeah.
Which and this being this is an episode.
We are now in an area that at one point in some article I read, this was called the Wine
Bar District where we are in this stage.
And Kyle, you brought champagne.
We're drinking champagne.
We're sipping champagne.
Yeah, I brought some bubbly.
You know, I try to treat my boys good.
Hashtag spoil.
Thanks, daddy.
Please call me daddy.
Oh, no.
Got into his disturbing rhythm in this episode.
But you have an assignment now.
I call Kyle daddy.
All right.
I have to do at least several more times.
But I owe you, you know, for the champagne.
You never owe me.
I'm excited to be here.
But yes, I warned I warned Scott that I would be in maybe a particular shape.
I feel like I'm maybe fine.
I don't know.
I can't.
I'm doing fine.
I listen to this after the fact.
Who knows what I'll determine.
But you feel I've been drinking since 1030 in the morning today.
Damn.
Hell, yeah.
You started that or like you got there.
I started my house.
I took an Uber with a couple of friends.
That's a way to do it.
That's a good way to do it.
So all that.
Well, that's great.
You're speaking my language.
The point was, though, to research for for this.
Of course.
Yeah, yeah.
For what we're doing.
Good excuse.
Which, by the way, look, I called you daddy.
But really, we only during the series answer to the great one, the sector keeper, who now
we will pause so that he can tell us what we specifically are doing today.
Boys, boys, today's stage contains the bar in Ballast Point.
Good luck, boys.
All right.
So, yes, two fantastic liquor dispensing locations, Uva Bar and Ballast Point.
And you hit up.
Did you hit up both of these today or you have at various?
One of them, at least.
I did today.
Yes.
And I have prior to today.
Nice.
Hell, yeah.
Yeah.
So we have a lot of posture.
Oh, wait, really?
Like, so you had like a drink and stuff?
So wait, so you have like a drinking problem?
Hell, yeah.
Drinking problem.
Pure bars.
No rides.
You didn't do.
Scott, you have described Uva Bar as one of your favorite things at Disneyland property.
Yeah.
Not even within the.
Yes.
I'm a big fan of Uva Bar.
List the things, the rides in Disney and California Adventure that you like less than Uva.
Oh, this probably is the best.
I probably a ton.
That's what I mean.
I mean, the ones that are jumping out are like Star Wars Launch Bay and or like the watch
on those Star Wars movies.
Easy.
But like, what's like a major one?
Casey, I like you.
I like going to Uva Bar more than going on Casey on the train where you're trapped in
a cage.
Yeah.
Takes all kinds, I guess.
Throw in one if you would agree with me.
Throw in a throw a ride under the bus if you wish or don't.
I'm just inviting you in, Kyle.
I'm trying to like goofy sky school or I really like that that much.
I'm one of the I think most people don't like that.
I do like that ride.
Goofy, really?
Hmm.
People think it's too like jerky, right?
Well, it's scary.
It scares me.
I don't like a slow moving thing that's high up.
I can't.
I'm not allowed to do it because everybody who's ever been on it doesn't want to do it
again.
Oh, really?
It's a wild mouse, right?
The one that makes you feel like you're going to go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Those drops are you feel like very naked in that they're like very sudden and exposed.
Yeah, yeah.
Kyle, with you and alcohol, I overcame some fears of some rides, both in Credit Coaster
and Guardians of the Galaxy Mission Breakout, which thank you for your encouragement.
Man, I just like kicking it with you, dude.
Oh, jeez.
I mean, you don't I don't have to like overcome goals to impress you.
To me, it's just all about like being with the boys and.
All right.
Cheers again.
Like, this has been a great night.
Hey, we're too far from each other to actually cheers.
Oh, yeah.
I also I mean, another one we did that I don't I don't want to put you on the spot here,
but from that Guardians experience, I seem to recall I feel like you do a pretty good
job of it.
Whoa.
Is right.
I have heard you guys do rocket on the podcast.
Yeah.
Can you give me a moment here?
I've got to like I'm getting my hair back to like kind of get into character.
Roll your sleeves up like you've been working on.
It's like digging up wires.
The problem is, OK, now what does he say?
That's the stuff that it's like when this when the Simpsons actors have to improvise
as well.
Mark, what are they?
The gantry like what we do.
Your hand.
Yeah.
My hands.
I don't want to give you a reading.
I know that's sort of against the actor code.
You can all do it.
Yeah.
Let's see those hands.
That's what he says.
Makes you start.
Oh, yeah.
He says, let me see your hands.
Let's see those hands, people is what he says.
Let's see your hands, people.
Yeah.
The problem is my hands don't scan.
Yours do.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
Something in that world.
Yeah.
When I do and I was on that, I took that I did that ride today and I just repeat that
phrase over and over again in like different versions.
Like basically like my hands don't scan.
My hands don't scan.
Yours do.
And I like I see this little puppet above me.
Every time he's like he's about to say my hands don't scan.
I just mean I love it.
So awesome.
I feel like you alerted me to the oddity of that moment and it is very addictive and yeah,
we've been doing it.
Well, I like I think usually what I do to correct me if I'm wrong is we're walking through
the after we're out of that room and I just go gantry lift.
Yeah, you say gantry lift again.
Gantry lift.
My hands don't scan.
It messes up my gantry plan.
Gantry.
My plan involves a scan with your hands.
My hands don't scan.
Does it ever do?
Is there a super fast version?
Is it all you can?
My hands don't scan.
It's kind of it is like yeah, if you're I feel like you guys being comedy people.
I feel like you've mentioned before this.
I don't know at some point I remember you guys talking about this voice that comedy
people do.
They'll kind of like the like, hey, here we go or something like that.
I don't know.
I don't know when you guys said this.
That's like old radio voice.
At some point you said that like it's like a voice that all improv-y people do or something.
Like an old timey voice guy.
Yeah.
But I feel like that rocket raccoon voice is almost something that is all is very approachable
to any person who like does comedy if that makes any sense.
Yeah.
It's a little James Cagney.
It's like, well, do what you think James Cagney sounds like.
So the idea of just being able to be like my hands don't.
I feel like it's not far from a character I do on Saturday night.
Like Bruce Shanley.
It's like almost what that is.
And you give it that gust that like you're really proud of yourself with every word.
Yeah.
It's I told you about it.
The Epcot preview center that's happening currently.
It is why we talk about it in a future episode, but the moment when this part where you get
that vibe, but in a different place in Florida when there's this boring thing happening and
then he says boring and unplugged.
And it's really, I don't know.
I feel like it went from something that seemed a little silly to me to like, I'd love to
watch like rocket unplugging anything I don't want to watch.
Is there a lot of that just generally in that?
I feel like are there multiple unplugs and plugging?
You mean the new moon in the gardens of the galaxy ride?
What they did is it starts off in the ride and they just re use the silhouette element
in this preview show video.
It's clearly the same.
Yeah.
Like coming soon.
But he, when the robot unplugged something, right.
And then you get on the ride and then the silhouette on well, rocket unplugged, he mutes
the collector, right?
Is that what happens?
Yeah.
Well, he, yeah, he says, let's mute this guy.
And he says that in the pre show.
And then right before the car takes off is when he goes, when rocket unplugs you and gets
things rocking.
Is that what he says?
I think he says, and gets things rocking or something.
Something like that.
Yeah.
Let's jam.
Let me see those hands so we can jam.
Did you guys, sorry, go ahead.
I was just going to say a rocket.
Its voice is like the universal studios, New York performers.
Hmm.
Yeah.
Like what are you doing down there, sweetheart?
Let's see those hands.
I respect Bradley Cooper so much as an actor and I'm not going to get on this.
That's assuming it's him.
It is.
I think it is him.
Is it him in the ride?
I believe it's him.
Yeah.
I think it's him.
Cause they all did their, they're all in it.
Hmm.
So it would make sense.
Now you guys, I know we're now not talking about the subject we're supposed to talk about.
Thank God.
Yes.
Has there been, I know this exists, I'm sure on Reddit or something like that, but like,
do we know all of the songs that are a part of the gardens of galaxy ride?
Yes.
Yeah.
There's six.
It's not that many.
Six of them.
And then the like death metal one in monsters after dark.
Have you done monsters after dark?
No.
Just Halloween specific, but that guy, one of the guys who scored the movies wrote an
original metal song called monsters after dark, which is the best of all of them.
It's the best ride profile.
Wow.
So does that make it then the best in any of the towers anyway?
Is that the best thing you can do in a tower of terror or a gantry?
That's a good question.
Depending.
Uh, uh, yes.
Wow.
I will say yes.
As far as just the lift itself, but not the pre-show.
If there was a way to combine moving car in Florida with monsters after dark.
Here's the ultimate tower ride.
Customize it like a Taco bell order.
That's what I'm going to do.
Uh, it's the, it's the, uh, Tokyo tower.
Pre-show that story and all the story, all of it up.
Then add the fourth dimension room from Florida.
Cause it's not in the Tokyo version.
And then it's the guardians of the galaxy, uh, monsters after dark drops.
Yeah.
Doesn't make any sense, but that's the most thrilling version of the ride.
I think it's good.
I still like hit me with your best shot.
Really?
Yeah.
We had today.
Do you have a favorite?
I think parliament, uh, tear the roof off.
Parliament's really exciting in the, in this little Epcot show.
That's cool to hear and to see the model like spaceship, little mini spaceship birth light
up with like funk colors.
Good stuff.
Jackson five.
Yeah.
Want you back.
Controversial.
Let's not, let's not go saying anything.
It's still on the ride.
It's after dark here at, uh, monsters after dark takes on a new meaning.
Um, I, okay.
Well to get to go some steps over back over to, uh, back to this 2001 era bar.
I've been drinking since 10 30 in the morning.
Was that a full 90 minutes?
How long have we been just talking right now?
Let me look, let me look.
You're really zonked son.
It's 12, 15 minutes.
We were talking about, we were doing the voice of rocket record for 15 straight minutes.
This is how we've time escapes us.
Sometimes when the episodes are two and a half hours, we honestly don't know.
It's true.
It's like Jack White.
Jack White says he, um, when he gets off stage, he doesn't really like, he can't remember
what what exactly like, I feel the same way when I go on stage.
I don't remember.
Like a lot of what I've done.
Yeah.
I've killed, I've killed.
No, no, I've killed again.
Um, uh, so, uh, who bar was one of your destinations today?
I, okay.
So yes, I'm very fond of a bar.
I could probably, there's probably a bigger list.
I may be probably monsters, ink thing.
I'd let's rather go on.
There's probably a lot of rides I'd read.
I'd less, because if I'm at that property, probably a good 45 minutes hour to have a
bar is on the, on the short list.
Uh, I lit, I fit, you mentioned it when you were here before, which I was, I think part
of like a, or it was like your salvation in like a bad scenario.
Right?
You talked about this, right?
Yeah.
I took like a stem of mushrooms, maybe.
It was when star tours, the initial incarnation of star tours was closing and, uh, the three
friends I went with decided to take mushrooms.
I, I'm not, I don't typically do, uh, hallucinogenics or psychedelics.
And I did it in this case, I did a very small amount and it was a bad scene for me.
Uh, but at some point midday, probably about, I would imagine four or 5 PM we left Disneyland
into downtown Disney and got a beer at uva bar.
And like it brought me to a place that I was like, Oh my God, now I, I can breathe again
if that makes any sense.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's beautiful.
That's what this place offers in a much more minor way.
I just, that's how I feel if I'm just like, uh, tired slightly or got too sweaty or something,
but that's what it is like a breath of fresh air.
Uh, and I'm trying to figure out why, like, cause really, I mean, it's like not the greatest
place you've ever been to, but I think within the Disney property where you lower your expectations,
I think the fact that it's, uh, that it's outdoors, it's very mellow, it's not themed.
You can take a break from theming and just be at like a, be at a nice relaxing place.
Uh, good beer and wine and dry.
I haven't like covered the gamut with the menu or anything.
Uh, cause I'm just doing a chardonnay probably.
I have a lot of affection for that early 2000s logo, that uva bar logo.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
Kind of like squiggly.
Yeah.
I was going to say that's one of my least favorite things about it.
I figure, yes.
I'm font picky.
But I, I mean, in terms of like choosing aesthetics, no, but I do like when things from the past
had like Florida, when we were down in Florida, there's some stuff that it's like the nineties
never ended in this.
Oh yeah.
In this thing.
It's like a city walk entirely.
So I like seeing like different decades of stuff, like little remnants of different decades
of stuff.
We'll trip back to 2001.
Yeah, absolutely.
They're bad fonts though.
They're bright, but you can be nostalgic for, yeah.
That's basically what I'm saying.
Like you acknowledge that like aesthetically, if you were designing something, you would
say that sucks.
But the katal font is more taste is more tasteful.
Sure.
Very similar.
It's kind of similar.
But isn't there just like a blocky or letter?
Am I wrong?
I'm just kind of like a, the katal fonts.
We really, should we get back to doing the rocket raccoon voice?
I don't know.
Was that more fun than that?
So what do you think then about the flute?
Cause you, I only learned recently from you telling me that the champagne flute planters
surrounding uva bar.
That's what, when did you notice this?
That's when you're in uva bar, there's some big planters and they go up in kind of like
a funnel shape and I only knew this cause I looked at an article that said there's supposed
to be like big champagne flutes.
No, I did not notice that.
I think we, and we're on the upper echelon of people who like and have thought about
uva bar and we've never noticed that.
While we're speaking generally about it before we, if I don't know how deep we're going to
dive into this, katal is the name of the restaurant that's essentially attached that it's a part
of.
That it's connected to, which we covered a little, I don't remember when.
I don't either.
It's a whole yesterday, a day before.
Yeah.
You can't even tell that it's attached to a restaurant.
It's very, to me it's its own thing.
It's weird.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's not like there's no connecting.
The first thing I think of is when we were last, last year in the city walk saga, we
were at the Hall of the moon at city walk and there's an outdoor section of, of the
piano bar, how the moon, but we had to have a waiter surf our drinks cause you're not
allowed to bring a drink onto the sidewalk.
So there's a man who was standing there whose job was to take your beer from you or your
big blue bucket of alcohol, put it on a tray and he would have to walk it over.
Like a sidewalk.
Six feet.
Width.
Yeah.
But like really that does give those two things some continuity is my point.
There's not, there's nothing, what you're saying, there's no continuity between the
restaurant and the bar.
There's like two separate entities.
Yes.
So I want, maybe I want someone to serve liquor back and forth.
At least you would know.
What are you talking about?
You want someone to carry, you want an inconvenient liquor carrying hand.
But at a nice restaurant, like I've eaten at like had a drink in the bar at Spago.
And then when the table was ready, they put their like sir, they carry it.
They carry your drinks for you.
Spago.
I've been to Spago.
Is that even around still?
It is.
It's tight.
Yeah, it's great.
It's really good.
Recently remodeled the last few years.
Have you been?
I've been four or five times.
Four or five times to Spago?
Yeah.
I've known you for like 11 years.
When did you go to Spago?
My dad, when my dad comes out.
The first time I, when I was first out here for school by.
My hands don't scan.
Yeah.
That was one of the things my dad knew.
It's like my car doesn't scan.
My car doesn't swipe.
Did you say my car doesn't start?
My car won't start.
Spago was such a thing in popular culture, like as a reference point, like a name check
for years.
You know who founded it?
Wolfgang.
Yeah, Wolfgang.
He founded it with his hands.
So but now it's like, it's not like the, it's still very popular, but it's not like a place
anymore.
It's not like.
It's still very popping.
It's popular.
It's still popular.
I don't know if it's popping.
I don't know how you gauge that.
That's a tougher, it takes a, yeah, it takes a pretty.
I do like that place a lot because it feels like 1989 Beverly Hills and like such a cool
way.
It feels like.
Also Wolfgang Buck, if he, if Wolfgang Puck is there, he will come out and shake your
hand.
Yeah.
Like I have shaken his hand.
I have shaken Wolfgang's hands.
You did once?
I didn't know this.
How many times?
Just the once, just the once.
Oh, dude, does it do his hands scan?
His hands do scan.
He is a friend of Rocket.
Okay.
I just wanted to know.
Wow.
I'm really impressed now.
I do, that's familiar.
I've heard you, I've heard you tell tale of shaking.
Of shaking Wolfgang Puck's hand now.
But I guess.
Wolfgang's hands.
Man.
I want to, I'm sorry.
The problem is Wolfgang's hands don't scan.
He's speaking about Wolfgang Puck's hands.
Yeah.
The problem is me and Wolfgang's hands don't scan.
I tried to get up the gantry lift.
Didn't work.
Then I've got my buddy Wolfgang.
Guess what?
His hands don't scan.
So let's try you guys.
I don't know.
We should treat ourselves sometime.
It's not terribly expensive.
You want to go to Spago?
Yeah.
It's fun.
Let's go.
I'll go.
You never invited me.
Okay.
It's a him and his dad thing.
I never thought it was.
It's a him and his dad.
It only comes out.
Actually, yeah, you have him.
Will it help grease your palms if I call you daddy?
Huh?
A lot of daddy talks about that.
Hey, last time I was there, they, I don't know what, it was something where it's like
the weight was a little longer than expected, but like by like five, like no one would have
noticed.
But they came around to a bunch of the tables and gave everyone like free pizzas.
And they're like, we're so sorry for the delay.
You had the pizza with the fish on it?
Yeah, with the salmon.
They have a pizza.
They're like one big thing is like an interpretation of lox in pizza form.
So it's kind of like a layer of creme fraiche and then salmon and capers.
Delicious.
It sounds good.
Yeah.
I would eat it.
But you guys want somebody you have to carry your drink to?
Well, I'm just saying, I'm saying what Kyle is saying.
I kind of, it's.
I felt immediately uncomfortable, honestly, but it was kind of neat.
That is cool in a fancy restaurant, but I think it's good that it's a separate, it doesn't
feel like you're in some overflow of the better.
Katal and I couldn't get into Katal.
You want to like I like more than Katal.
I've never sat down in Katal.
The food, though, is seemingly coming from the restaurant.
The layers have to navigate a pedestrian walkway to get to the bar from the kitchen.
So shout out to them.
Yeah, that's full of peril.
And I will say I have eaten the food there.
I don't know if you guys have.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel like I've had some sort of flatbread or something, right?
Yeah, everyone is.
They've had chicken.
You know, I prepped today.
I did some I did some work.
I got I did at least four things off the menu, but I've eaten there quite a bit.
Yeah.
Oh, geez.
What's shout out some stuff?
No, that's off the table.
I love it.
I'm a man of research.
So it's nice knowing you guys.
Today we had the.
I will say I definitely recommend the corn are rapes.
Yes, that's on my list.
I go back.
These are good.
I think this is good food.
I think that's yeah.
Yeah, that's not even like for theme park.
Yeah, those are really great.
I'm not sure I had had a rapes before.
I don't I never get that anywhere.
Yeah, I wait.
I wrote down what it is from the fried corn cakes.
Top of the day, I think it's a little bit of a
fried corn cakes topped with pulled pork, guacamole, cilantro and red onion.
Good stuff.
I was about to say the same thing.
It's very important that I read it.
You can just imagine what it is.
I think there's a lot of things to do with that.
I have like the little like I don't like little shaved pepper topping.
Anything with that?
You're looking good.
Do you feel like you just like plugged in holes with food here and not at any rate?
I don't.
Yeah, I feel like it's just like snack wise.
I've never sat down for the proper uva bar meal.
I've had drinks, certainly.
Yeah, which is always a nice time.
I feel like uva bar at night is the time to do it.
I feel like I don't feel the magic during the day.
Interesting.
I don't think I've ever been there when it's gotten fully dark.
I mean, it's obviously like everything is better at night at Disneyland, obviously,
for the most part.
But like it's a good daytime spot.
It's not bad.
I don't want to trash.
I'm not trashing it.
It's a good spot, too, like if you want you want a little like respite from the parks.
I mean, if you guys want to hear the rest of my order, you can.
If you don't want to, I'm cool with that, too.
I'm interested.
I would like to hear it.
Yeah, I want to hear it.
I would like to.
Well, we got the corn rapist.
Yeah.
I didn't even know if that's the right way to say that phrase.
Yeah, and I meant to look up a pronunciation.
I think we you know, we had them at Jurassic World.
They serve it in the Jurassic World at Hollywood.
We're good.
The little corn cakes.
Yeah.
I think I like that item.
You don't see it that often.
Yeah, I do like it.
Yeah.
We got the happy hour barbecue chicken flatbread.
I think I've had that.
That's the one I've had, which is kind of like a kind of California pizza kitchen.
Ste is if that makes any sense.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure, sure.
It's fine.
It's good.
We got the guacamole.
We got the you got chips with that.
Comes with chips.
Cool.
There's a bowl with spoon.
Loose guacamole.
I guess it's not another.
We got the buffalo wings today is the other thing we got.
OK, they're good, but they're very like fluorescent in color.
If that makes any sense, they're like super.
I don't want to say orange, but like just very bright in whatever that color is.
Yeah.
But I've had these to have these things, these like street fries, which are really good.
And now I think they have carne asada fries, which maybe are the same thing.
But I think they used to come with chorizo.
But I do.
I think the food there is good.
I think it's yeah.
Yeah.
It's like a quick stop gap.
Like we'll go out of our way to go.
And lines not usually crazy, which some of these newer downtown Disney places they can
be and sometimes deservedly so.
There's some spots in there now.
But yeah, you can pop in there without a big weight and pretty chill, pretty relaxing.
It does have like an elevated look to it, kind of like the new the new bar at Naples.
Like, it's very well lit.
It's very well lit to trick you into thinking like, oh, this is nice.
This is fancy, but not terribly crazy.
Yeah.
It is nice.
But like that, no, it's like bar rescue tricks, I'm saying.
Like, you know, perceived value, they say in marketing.
But it's not terribly more expensive than most stuff.
Is it a full 360 bar?
Is it a full 360 around?
It is right.
I think so.
Pretty much.
Yeah.
So that's something special.
Yeah, you're right.
There's no corners.
There's no corner seats.
Something feels cool about that.
I will say today, I'd never experienced this before.
Like we were in a section, though a lot of sun coming through.
OK.
So there are some non shaded areas.
Yeah.
OK.
I'd never, but up to that, I've been going to this bar for maybe a decade now and never
had that experience.
But the boys I was with, you know, I was new to them.
I said, like, I'm trying to impress my podcast friends.
All right.
What did the boys think of it?
They all were kind of doing their own private reviews.
They're like, yeah, actually, they're pretty good.
But then one of them was like, I don't know, I got to say, I'll tell you later what I really
think.
Like he like, give the full review while we were there.
I think I think he had some he had some some.
Did he not ever tell you?
No, I don't know.
I think he thought the food was just like, OK, I think the food because we all eat like
theme park food.
I think this is I think this is better than.
To me, it's like, yeah, than normal.
I think so.
Yeah, I think I think it's better than most.
OK.
Anything in the parks that could compete or is better, it probably requires a reservation
or a big old wait.
Yes.
That's what really notches this up, that you're just in there and it's it's happening.
I also want to share a really specific menu item that sounds really mundane.
And yet I like it a lot, which is the trio of Mediterranean dips.
Yes.
You had the trio of Mediterranean.
Yeah, it's great.
Really good.
Yeah, it's I mean, like, OK, hummus and wait, now I'm not sure which is the one I like.
Hummus, Baba, Baba, Baba, Ghanoush and then Mohamara.
I don't think I've said it out loud.
And I think maybe that's the one that I like.
It's like darker and kind of purplish.
And that is a remarkable little little little hummus you can get anywhere.
But whatever that one is, whatever the mystery third one is, it's so.
Mohamara is a hot pepper dip.
I bet it's spicy.
Will you show me a pic?
Do you got a picture?
This is just the Wikipedia picture.
It kind of looks like a chutney.
Is it?
No, it's a hot pepper.
It is.
We typically get the dips.
The dips are great.
Yeah, it's like a good look.
You know, what we keep doing it for is like if we feel like we've indulged too much or
had some big too crazy of a lunch or something and we need like the theme park equivalent
of toast, just something simple just to settle the stomach.
Yeah, something quick before we get on the road.
Oh, traffic died down.
This is perfect for that Aleppo pepper ground walnuts, bread crumbs and olive oil.
Oh, for sure.
Walnuts.
That is instantly familiar.
Yeah.
A protein kick to it is so good.
Now that I've I need to get Mohamara, I'm going to make a big deal out of Mohamara like
if you like doing Nutella instead of peanut butter.
Do you think they have the uvibar referee?
I will get topped off.
Hell on the heck.
I mean, if there is some, I'll have it, but I don't want to.
I'll let you get there pouring right now.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a rare drinking episode.
This is only like the third drinking episode.
But it makes.
This is the time to do it.
We're a week into this thing, but we're getting close to it.
We're almost like we're not that far from halfway through, which feels less.
It's so much less punishing than city walk so far.
This is where we're at.
I don't know.
Like in workout, like it feels like I am not winded and we're almost at the halfway point
and that feels great.
Well, I mean, we do seven up.
If you're talking about we do a three episodes on Patreon.
So we do seven episodes a month regularly.
Oh, you're right.
So this is about seven.
So we just have to do it again.
Yeah.
So much better than the 19.
So much better.
Yeah.
Yes.
I wouldn't just kind of I wouldn't recommend doing 19 daily podcasts in a row.
I don't know if you've had the pleasure or will have the opportunity, but I don't know
what that entails.
Like that means like every day you're recording something.
What does that mean?
Well, we just I mean, it was spread out over a long amount of time.
It felt for I feel like the city work started took forever.
In my mind.
Are you guys really though?
You go kayfabe or not?
Oh, you're like digging through.
I don't know what that way.
That's a wrestler wrestling term.
Real life or fair story.
It's like story.
Or is it and how much are we playing up?
Yeah.
That was because we were just doing a little cave.
We could give you the real.
We'll give you.
You're just asking about us.
Maybe you're in Cape in general or his friends or that's what I was asking.
But how would I be?
I'd be fake like I'm not really trying to add on another bit or something.
I'm not.
I think he's asking how tight of friends are we?
Oh, that's all it was.
Right.
Essentially, like I think so.
Yeah.
I thought that we were asking for like the real schedule of like how we were doing this.
I think what Scott was saying, I think you were digging for psych.
You're digging for for Marin stuff is what you're asking.
I'll answer all any question.
I'll answer both of those.
Don't care too much.
We have taken the lessons of our foolhardy early years of podcasting and tried to go
a little easier on ourselves.
That's not answering the question, though.
I don't think I think it's a fair answer.
No, I mean, we're friends in real life and we just had a big, big great trip to Orlando
together.
You know what?
I think the biggest thing, because it's a bummer, is that we now I feel like we hang
out for podcast purposes because there's so much of this to do.
Yes, I agree.
And then we don't make a point of let's just hang out, not know.
It's why the trip was wonderful to hang, even though it still is all we had in Rick.
Well, we hadn't recorded on Saturdays in a while.
I feel like when we tend to record on Saturdays, we'll get a bite to eat or get a drink after.
So we haven't done that in a while, though.
Yeah, it is.
We got to remember to like put in the time.
What was the relationship prior to the podcast starting?
Well, you know, what's interesting is they were Mike and Jason.
You guys are an improv team.
So we you know, you have to make that blood oath for better or worse.
And Mike and I were friends separately and then we'd all hung out as a unit.
But I do think the podcast has resulted in specifically the Scott Jason friendship.
Yes, I would say so.
The beginning, yes, we just hadn't had the chance, right?
So it has the last line in the triangle really forms.
I. Yeah.
But it's pretty cool, right?
It's great.
It's pretty touching, right?
I love being creative.
Sure.
No, it is.
It's awesome, obviously, to meet people and to form friendships.
And that's so vague.
I'm so sorry, but like, I think that's true.
Making adult friendships is a difficult thing.
So that's awesome.
Very difficult.
Yeah, they say especially once you get into your 30s, like, yeah, it's even harder.
That's correct.
And I yeah, I will say this podcast especially has been a reason to like, yeah, these are
like yeah, like, yeah, you guys are like much more recent friends.
Yeah, friend that I've had.
You're making us.
You've got to like sweet, genuine things here.
Well, cheers.
Yeah, it's very.
Yeah, it's.
I brought the whiskey to.
Into the champagne.
I'm not going to take a little.
We may go back down.
We may go back down to a bar after this.
I mean, I think it's a ballast.
All right.
Hell, yeah.
Mike, please do not mix it with your champagne.
That's gross.
That's horrible.
I can do it.
I'm going to do it.
That's horrible.
I can do it.
I put tequila in wine at Dave Ferguson's bachelor party and I got very sick.
So don't do that.
Like immediately sick or sick later?
I'd have both.
All the guys.
Yeah, that's.
You poured your tequila into the wine.
I was like, I think I'd been like really pent up and I'm going to really I'm going to be
an idiot this weekend.
It's good.
This is I don't.
So Mike just took a pug.
I want to say a pug is a thing.
A pug.
It's a dog.
A plug.
You have a dog in front of you.
He's driving me nuts.
He's about to knock over the whole area.
I don't know where it's from.
This was in my house.
A pug.
You took a pug.
I feel like that's a thing.
Like I took a pug.
Like I took like a little like a shot of it out of the bottle, but maybe I'm making that
up.
I don't know if that's a phrase.
I've never heard that before, but it's like it's a cute little three cent or three word.
Mike just took a pug of the whiskey over there.
In context clues, you understand what it means.
How do you feel?
Are you do you?
You're well, you're more of a sipper that you probably aren't like, you know, do you
like to throw him down too often?
Yeah, I'm more of a sipper.
I think I can I can handle it.
Like I think I can still go if we need to go.
Like, go if we need to go.
You mean, no, no, no.
If we like all of a sudden, start like hard drinking.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Like we had to.
I don't really want to because like it's, you know, it's a weeknight.
Yeah, but you're at home.
Yeah, I got my week off, dude.
I'm chilling.
All right.
Yeah, you've got the rare week off.
You were very intense.
That's what your job is.
There's a Buffalo Wild Wings.
It's open 2 a.m. very close to here.
We can go right after.
That's Mike's superpower.
He knows any anywhere he is, he knows where the closest Buffalo Wild Wings.
Yeah, absolutely.
If you guys want to hang at the I'm down for whatever I have nothing to do.
We'll go right there.
I'm ready.
I think I think it's open unless it's only maybe they're open one on the weeknights.
There's also a Barney's Beannery.
So to be an asshole.
But if the Buffalo Wild Wings is not open, I don't want to hang out with you guys otherwise.
You know what?
It's important to set boundaries.
I understand.
No, that's that's the attraction.
That actually speaking of friendship, that you just opened up a window.
You just by allowing me or inviting me into that, you're saying like you'd be down to
extend the extend this past this thing, which to me is very meaningful.
Yes.
No, of course, I would be happy to extend.
I'm extending the pass.
Yeah, for sure.
No question.
And did I just make this awkward?
No, I'm just made it weird.
I think I'm seeing two AM.
I'm seeing two AM.
It's when the Buffalo Wild Wings closes.
Just saying.
Do we need to move to balance point?
Maybe.
Possibly.
I said everything I needed to say.
Look how much talking about it put us in this great mood.
Like and now we just are like I feel like I'm at Uva.
Have it like.
Yeah.
Having a glaven.
We are in that kind of circular.
I guess that's yes.
360.
Just like Uva.
I will say I think the last time I was here and I could be fully misremembering this so
I apologize if I am but and I remember telling this to you Scott that like Uva I swear specifically
used to have a specific soundtrack that was like old school R&B.
It was like Earth, Wind and Fire, Cool and the Gang, Shaka Khan, like kind of that steez.
Really?
And now I think is it right that Downtown Disney is just all like kind of the same Disney
soundtrack?
Pop music.
Oh there's more Disney than there.
I think that it's like not even like individual stuff.
I feel like you're hearing whatever they plug throughout the entire zone.
I think maybe they're keeping the theming going like as soon as you get on property.
Because we were there today and I think it was like maybe even Christmas music but it
used to be I feel like Uva by I remember specifically like oh it's cool they're playing like Earth,
Wind and Fire or something like that.
Yeah.
Didn't you see you were down there and you saw like a band that was you saw like a covers
band of this kind of thing or.
I don't know if that was at that might have been at California Adventure.
Yeah yeah yeah that's so yeah.
You know Donna band maybe or what are they called like hmm during like Food and Wine
Fest like.
We saw Yachtly Crew.
You were with us right?
No I wasn't.
Oh I sent you pictures of Yachtly Crew.
Not okay with me.
The first time of this of two times that I've seen Yachtly Crew.
Oh man.
In different spots.
That's the whole thing.
Yes.
I think this was that same.
That stage.
Period.
And like that was like I love all of that stuff because it's like you hear like some
Bruno Mars tracks.
Yeah.
Not much more to say other than the fact that it's cool to hear that.
Well and that's a Disney escape.
Hopefully it isn't just they aren't just playing Someday My Prince Will Come in the mall because
you need a I don't know I think you need those escapes so you can dive back into the immersive
Disney-ness wanting more.
You were saying Scott I think you did Grad Night at Disney.
Yeah.
And they played pop music on Main Street.
Oh no yeah that I didn't like.
Which you said was bad.
Yes.
But then I.
My high school Grad Night where you're hearing like Usher's Yeah.
Oh yeah.
In Frontierland.
It's not a fan.
I think that's so bizarre though for one off night though.
It seems fun.
I think I don't know if everyone here got to experience the show during the summer of
Mickey's Mix Magic which I think I declared we do an episode and we have not done an episode
about yet.
I'm sorry.
But Mickey's Mix Magic has an original song about Mickey getting getting your ears on
is what they say.
You know that's a phrase they're using.
I think to me enjoy yourself.
Come on everybody get your ears on.
That's like.
Come on everybody.
Either getting hard or cramming.
That's how Mickey says it.
I think it's both.
Mickey talks a bit.
I think you have to get hard to cram.
So but at Halloween he says let's boo this.
Yeah.
And then and that means cramming.
A lot of things Mickey says means cramming.
It's all in there.
It's all there.
But there that's a very look that's like a very modern song to hear on Main Street.
And I loved it.
I was so excited.
Now wait a minute.
Did you when we were in Orlando did you catch any of move it shake it mouse could dance
it.
I know what you're talking.
Dance it I think is a war crime.
Someone needs to be held responsible for the copyrighted phrase mouse could dance.
I did not see it.
We we.
I walked by it.
I would.
There's a lot of things we missed.
They were definitely mouse could dancing.
Yeah.
We you and I both experienced a thing we didn't know existed.
Yes.
The rainy day.
Oh, because it rained very hard this one day.
Yeah.
In Disney World.
And so and so what happened.
Characters come out and they're slickers like umbrellas and stuff.
And umbrellas and they have a song.
They have an original song and we'll Lindsay and I are walking down Main Street.
That was the last thing we did before we left for L.A. and we were we loved it.
We were so excited about it.
So some characters just in their regular outfits, which they didn't have.
Look, not every character had a slicker.
Not every character.
It's yeah.
So I agree on the word slicker together.
Well, I noticed Jason said I noticed that is funny.
If you want a little peek behind the process, Jason said slicker.
I went, oh, slickers funny.
Yeah.
Keep saying it seriously and everyone will enjoy it.
That's trick.
And I'll say, yeah.
And some characters had slickers.
That's what we learned.
And you know, that's how you do the trick.
That's once is a phenomenon, twice a coincidence, three times a pattern.
We took improv five.
And that's how comedy works.
Chad Carter in 2009.
We learned that 10 years ago.
That's tight as hell.
So you got the drunker you guys get, the more you name check improv theories.
Yeah, that's right.
Man, hell yeah.
Hell yeah, daddy.
So all right.
Ballast point.
I have some ballast point stuff.
San Diego in the house.
Yeah, that's the thing.
Yeah.
You must have been when you find out this was your stage, you must have lost your shit.
Uh, yup.
Speaking of third time is a pattern ballast point like Sanuk and a sunglass icon by Sunglass
Hut.
This ballast point in 2015 joined the Constellation Brands family.
The beverage magnet Constellation Brands bought them for one billion dollars.
Wait, those other places are also Constellation Brands?
No, no.
In terms of like Sunglass Hut is part of Lux Optica, if you'll recall.
Sanuk is part of a shoe monopoly.
Constellation Brands is another.
Constellation also owns Corona, Modelo, Pacifico, Spedka Vodka, Paul Mason.
Oh, Paul Mason.
Oh, the French.
I'm sorry to interrupt you.
Oh, that's good.
But that was, and I don't claim to be an expert by any means, but that this was controversial,
I think.
It was, yeah.
Within the craft beer community.
Yeah.
But yes, like I'm, I'm from San Diego and like they, we kind of claim craft beer is
a thing for like, that's a thing about our city.
Dallas Point started there.
Yeah.
But when Dallas Point essentially like, yeah, when they like kind of were sold to this company,
like then I think even like people within that culture and community turned their backs
on it.
It felt like a sell, like a corporate move, if that makes any sense.
Also I have bad news and it seems like consumers have also turned their backs on it because,
and I do have to give away my connection to this.
This is from the website, Good Beer Hunting, an article written by my college roommate,
Brian Roth, an award winning beer writer, wrote an article about some of Dallas Point's misfortunes.
Production fell by about 110,000 barrels between 2016 and 2018.
And the first half of 2019, the Dallas Point family of brands had sold just under a third
of the packaged product it did in all of 2018.
I want to, I want to get ahead of this and say like, first of all, like I love you, Dallas
Point.
I love your beer.
Truly.
Like I'm not believing the hype.
Like you guys are doing your own thing.
Go ahead, Jason.
I'll say.
The Dallas Point location, downtown Disney is always packed.
I think I had a beer there once because we've gone before and we haven't gotten it.
Like it's just too crowded.
I haven't gotten in there.
I haven't gone to this place.
We've tried it.
Why are you guys doing a podcast about this thing you've never been to?
I've been.
I've had a beer before.
We are punishing ourselves.
Yeah, we have been.
I mean it's good.
We tried to have a meal a couple of times and the line is out the door.
It's insane.
It's like a yourself get a number sort of thing.
It was chill today.
That's good.
You got in there today.
I genuinely think the beer there, the sculpin is the, is the name, is the most maybe famous
like around beer.
And so they've got like a pineapple sculpin.
They've got a grapefruit sculpin.
They've got the regular sculpin.
I think this is a beer I love actually.
I will like go to my, I wanted to bring you guys a six pack of the grapefruit sculpin
because it's one of my favorites.
It's my favorite beer.
Yes.
That's great.
But that is a $15 six pack.
And that's true.
On message boards.
People are arguing about a beer he likes.
The price is $15.
It's good.
You, Mr. Spongel is upset about the price.
There's a lot more craft brewers than when Ballast Point started.
And there is a lot of cheaper craft brewers doing the same quality at the price point.
I will say right now, like I walked into this scenario knowing that we were going to talk
about Ballast Point and I did like zero research and I'm realizing like you guys have not done
any research about your craft beer.
Wait, wait, Ballast Point grapefruit sculpin is $12.
That's a big difference.
I have to know a little stuff about this because like it is from where I'm from.
So I have to like at least like pretend to know.
It's like, yeah, sure.
It would be like deep dish pizza.
Yeah.
It's like part of the culture and like which it's like probably one of the primary San Diego
culinary things.
Besides like California burritos or like carne asada burritos or something like that.
Sure.
I'm just, I'm looking, look, I'm looking it up just now on Target and you can get it for
$12.
$12 is a difference.
Well, Jason's right.
It's super expensive.
It is expensive compared to similar craft beers.
Grapefruit?
Who gives a shit about grapefruit?
What are you talking about?
Grapefruit is the deal.
Grapefruit is the important thing.
Jason's so sad.
We're talking about fun beers.
Golden Road right down the road sold to a similar amount to Anheuser-Busch a number
of years ago.
You're raising your voice, Jason.
A cheaper price point.
You're raising your voice.
Because I'm right.
You're doing that thing where like why are you doing that?
Like it is true that it's super expensive.
I think you're too upset about a fun beer.
I'm looking, okay, I'm going to look up grapefruit beer.
But I will say like, wait, why are you looking up grapefruit?
The price of citrus isn't comparable.
I'm comparing.
The price of citrus is now the best.
We're talking about grapefruit, the best of all of these.
I mean, that's my favorite of the sculpin flavors.
Of the sculpin.
I'm talking about Southern California IPA centric craft brewery.
That's what I'm talking about.
Take a deep uva bar style bread.
Hey, give Jason a swig of this whiskey, I think.
Oh, I don't like that.
I'm driving after that.
That's all.
You're all good.
We're going to Buffalo Wild Wings after this.
You'll have a couple of beers to calm down.
What do you like about the beer?
You like the beer.
So here's the thing.
I'm almost embarrassed to talk about this stuff because I don't feel informed in the
way that I would love to feel informed.
But I do like quote craft beer.
And San Diego, as I said, is a spot that it's like, I don't know, San Diego, Portland.
I don't know.
There are like a few of these craft beer cities.
Were these when you in like your early drinking career did not until I was basically outside
of college, did I realize that San Diego, I went to college in L.A.
I didn't even realize about Ballast Point's existence until I was probably until it was
like already a thing.
Sure, sure.
And then it had to be 21 anyway to go to the places.
Company which I'm sorry, I forgot the name of.
Oh, Constellation Brands.
Scott, they also have they bought Robert Mondavi for one point three six billion.
I knew of it like before it sold to that company like probably two years or three years before
that, if that makes any sense.
You ever go to any of the San Diego restaurants or to like they have a they have they had
a spot in Scripps Ranch, which is where I'm from in Miramar.
And Scripps Ranch is truly like my neighborhood.
And I did go there and I heard about it before I ever went there.
So it was a thing where I was like, oh, there's a craft brew place called Ballast Point.
And it was kind of a zone for people to meet up at and hang out at.
And so I knew the name and I don't know the Mid-Aughts or whatever.
Sure, sure.
Yeah.
They're like pretty good aesthetically.
I've only seen pictures of this restaurant downtown.
Or like, I don't know if you can speak to the San Diego ones, but it seems like they're
like cool inside, good graphic design.
Very cool and I will say we hung out at the Ballast Point in downtown Disney today.
And the dude who served us, very nice guy.
They have specific beers they're brewing just for that downtown Disney zone.
Wow.
And I believe the guy's name is Chris Klein, who is who is the head brewer at downtown
Disney and Long Beach.
They have a Long Beach spot as well.
But they have beers that are only being brewed for just that Ballast Point in downtown Disney.
Wow.
And these people, the way the dude spoke to us, like he cared about beer seemingly.
And I don't know if that matters to you or to people, but like it was nice to hear.
Like he seemingly was like, is there something I'm into?
And like, yeah, they make this, this guy who came up with this recipe used to be a lawyer
and he decided he wanted to brew beer and this is the one he came up with.
Wow.
Which is very sweet, I thought.
Yeah.
This is the first brewery at the Disney property.
Right.
Or in downtown Disney.
So the first like, you know, they're obviously plenty of places you can drink, but the first
place where beer is being actually made on property.
So that's cool.
And a fun, I think it's an interesting like sign of the times that build a bear workshop
is replaced by, I think it shows who's going to downtown Disney and Disney.
It's sort of like less kids, a little and more, more young adults and people who want
to get drunk.
You can take, there are six pack or like tall boys you can take to go.
So if you're like staying at a hotel or even if you just want like a broader selection,
then what's at your grocery, you can get it to, you know, take and have those in the room.
Yeah.
This pre our overnight for excited talking about that.
I feel like I got too excited for this show.
No.
Yeah.
Then that was all that was all pretty sincere.
I know we're like, I feel like I'm a beer and wine fan, but I could not like, I couldn't
like talk about a flavor for more than five words.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Even that.
I feel generally defensive because like this brand specifically represents craft beer,
but they got a bat, like, and they're from my city, the city I grew up in, but they sold,
they like, you know, became, they sold to like some major corporation or whatever.
And thereby like people who love quote craft beer, then started talking shit about it because
it gets like, they sold out.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Which I think a lot of this happens a lot.
This happens a lot in life these days.
Sure.
Yeah.
But I think in the craft beer world, it happens a lot because like beverage distribution is
like, there's only like two or three like main distributors.
But I'm saying that's why you can't get like yingling this far west.
It's like difficult.
So when places of this size, like of a craft brewer of ballast point or golden road size,
when they want to expand, they need more resources.
Like you need to hook up with a bigger.
Sure.
Or also like the people who started those brands have the chance to make a lot of money.
Oh yeah, they also make some scratch.
Thing I'm talking about.
Make some scratch.
Yeah.
You got to get it.
You got to cash in baby.
You know, you don't know how to be mad about it, Jason.
That's all I'm saying.
No, Jason, I'm mad.
What am I mad about?
You were raising your viewer.
Are you mad at me?
I don't understand what you were saying.
Oh, the price is too expensive.
It's too expensive.
It's a higher like they, and they position themselves too.
Like there's a season of Top Chef where like it's, it's like the California season and
like every other shot someone's drinking a ballast point and in the other shots, everyone's
drinking Perrier.
So like they're trying to like.
Oh, be the bump up.
Be the bump up.
I see.
Sort of option.
The with beer in general though, I like, I think I'll drink whatever.
I don't really care.
It doesn't.
The boy is back in town.
I could maybe identify, oh, this is a stout.
This is an IPA.
I could say this is better than the other.
But I do think, cause I like, you know, look, I like a sugary drink when they got the fruit
in the beer.
That's when I, I go crazy.
You go a little crazy.
For me at least, which is what crazy for me.
You had a little more of a pug.
How's that pug hitting you?
Oh good.
I feel, I have that warmth, that like whiskey warmth that you get.
Nice.
But.
The kind that Jason refuses to have.
Yeah.
Come on, Jason, do it.
What?
Get a little swig.
Pug.
I think that's a sparkling wine.
Get a little pug though.
Is this a new word?
Yeah.
You created a new word.
I thought it was a thing, dude.
Swig.
Swig is the thing you're thinking of.
Is it like you take a plug of it?
You take a quick pug of a, of a booth.
Hold on.
Maybe.
Maybe you're right.
I don't know.
I always say, I swear.
I'm sure you guys are right that I'm.
Swig is the word I always would use.
I know swig is a word.
I know.
I'm not saying you didn't like the sound of pug.
I like the sound of pug.
I know I like the sound of pug.
Pug, swig.
Both G's at the end.
Do you have fun as also for also theme park, San Diego beer brand, Carl Strauss?
Love it.
But that's like, I knew of that.
That's a different, and these are all abstract thoughts.
Like I knew of that when I was growing up and like, Oh, that's a place that has a brewery
that exists here.
But Ballast Point represented like quote craft beer in a way that Carl Strauss didn't.
Does that make any sense?
Like, yeah, yeah.
It's like, like IPA or whatever it was that they were doing.
Well the appraisal.
Just felt like not too far away from Samuel Adams or something at her.
Oh sure.
Yeah.
I don't know where Carl Strauss is from, but I've always known Ballast Point is from San
Diego.
Like I know it's like a hometown.
Like they put it on the cans and bottles and stuff.
It was like, this is a hometown thing.
Is it worth going to those San Diego ones?
If I'm in the area?
I was at the Little Italy one this July.
It was cool.
I think anywhere in San Diego is worth it to go because San Diego rules and we love
what you guys are doing.
Keep that spirit alive, San Diego guys and gals.
Not a lot of people are repping San Diego these days.
You know, Tony Gwynn passed away, but he killed it.
He was one of the best hitters of all time.
Lindsay Katys from San Diego.
Yeah, that's right.
Lindsay, I'd love to talk to you about that.
She's upstairs playing with a dog.
She's got his track.
Then we'll find a minute.
Do you not like me?
I saw Padres game and after the at Jack Murphy and after the game, Beach Boys with Stamos
like with part of the same ticket.
I think I saw the Beach Boys play there too.
I think I saw the Doobie Brothers post Michael McDonald.
Okay, but post Padres?
Post the show.
That was a thing they were doing.
I remember knowing, I'm just having this thought now, knowing that you, I like that music.
We shared this.
The soft, the yacht AOR.
I remember this.
I was not super into that music per se when I was in fourth grade or whatever.
Sure, yeah.
I remember being at a Padres game and there was a concert after the fact and a dude who
is sitting next to myself and my father being like, oh, the Doobie Brothers is playing?
Michael McDonald's not a part of the band anymore.
He really like firm.
So fuck these guys.
So he knew it.
He knew.
He's like, it's not the same.
Michael McDonald's not in the band.
It's not going to be as soulful, but we still might get like the pre.
I've heard it quantified as like, I've even heard people say like, you know, good Doobie
Brothers and then Michael McDonald Doobie Brothers.
Are you out of your mind?
People treat that like, oh, Blackwater.
That's probably, is that pre Michael McDonald?
I would never listen to that.
I need, but like a live album where he's doing it with them.
You got that distinct voice.
Was he with the Doobie Brothers?
Like 77, 78.
Oh, it's a very short, right?
He made his mark as a Steely Dan backup vocalist.
Right.
Yeah.
Plucked in via Jeff Skunk Baxter and just really shaped the band.
Keep rolling.
Just really, you know, Latter Day Edition who made a big difference, just like Bill Champlin
in Chicago.
I know that's not what this podcast is about.
But it also is.
It can be.
And you know, that's, you guys, you get talking about improv theory and I get talking about
session musicians.
Let's talk more about that.
What we learned in Chad Carter's class, Jason.
What did everyone think about the fish, the sculpting fish itself, the big fruity fish
is on the wall in the restaurant.
I gotta say that's hashtag finding Nemo.
They painted them real big though, like wall sized in the restaurant.
It's a little, it's like the primary and like everybody in the restaurant has t-shirts with
like that.
Yeah.
That there's a specific artist who's doing all of that work.
Yes.
And I think it's kind of cool.
I looked, I watched a video on their website because I was like, why did they choose a
sculpting?
And the answer, and this is a direct quote, deceiving delicious, but be careful.
That was his answer of why they chose to name it a sculpting.
Hmm.
So that implying that the drink might have like a bite.
Yes.
Because it does have a 7% ABV, which is kind of high.
Which is true.
I do, that will happen that you have the beer with the higher alcohol percent.
Yeah.
You forget.
Especially with IPA.
It's only a beer.
And then you were like, how did I get so messed up?
I like a session IPA.
So you get a little of the flavor, but you get less of the kick.
What's your favorite beer, Jason?
I like a Golden Road, like the, the either the Wolf Among the Weeds.
LA.
We're talking LA.
Yeah.
Big slight.
Watch out guys.
I'm glad I'm between you.
Wolf Among the Weeds or this, which is the double IPA, uh, or the Wolf Pup, which is
the, uh, session IPA.
Wolf Pup's good.
Sure.
Wolf Pup is good.
I like a, uh, Knott's Berry Farm, Boysenberry Cider.
Boysenberry Cider.
Or Boysenberry Beer.
A tradition like a beer.
They have it as well.
I think that's too sweet for me.
Yeah.
I think I can only do one or two, but I do like it.
Sure.
I can't do five.
I gotta say I'm one of those guys who will drink anything and get fucked up however much
I can or will.
You've made a lot of finger.
You're going, you went from four, one to four fingers really fast.
So anything.
I'll do whatever I can.
Turpentine.
Drink whenever I can.
I'll make fun of whoever the fuck I want to.
I'll spit in their face.
I'm kidding.
I'm sorry.
Jesus Christ.
Wow.
We've been with a monster this whole time.
Oh my gosh.
Algesh Curieau is my infamous Curieau.
Oh, interesting.
Algesh Cider.
I've never.
I don't know what that is.
That's it.
Well, I used to think it was a little more like rare.
Like you had to pick a place that had it, but Yard House has them.
Oh yeah.
Really strange.
Is Yard House open until two?
Probably.
I think so.
Yeah.
Mike got so excited.
That's a bigger bite than that sculpin because that's a 10%.
Watch out.
You know, tiny little goblet.
But a big old bite.
Yard House open until one a.m.
So good.
How late is AMC McGuffin's open?
Because we could.
I can be here all the time.
I can just do your podcast with you guys for the next week if you need like a.
Just you can.
Ed McBrand style.
You're going to do a residency?
I'm not good the way you guys are.
You guys are so good.
You don't have to put yourself down like that.
You're great.
Anthony, what are you?
I.
You do a very difficult job.
My hand.
But the problem is my hands aren't skin.
But at the end of the day, none of our hands are.
That is true.
The podcast, your hands do have to scan.
You got to scan.
Are we done?
Maybe we're done.
I mean, I mean, I'll take a little hug and then I can be done.
All right, I'll take a.
Give me a hug and I'll take a.
Oh, my God.
Mike, you're really going for it.
Can I describe to the listeners what's happening is there is a bottle of rye whiskey that I
inherited.
It's Whistle Pig 10 Year.
It's a reputable brand of rye.
Yeah, that is now being passed around and we're deciding whether hugging is like just
taking a sip of whiskey or not.
Nobody's told me whether that's a bigger ones on me.
It's hard to get a measure in a champagne.
Yeah, yeah.
You got a pub, too.
Well, Kyle's going right for the pub.
Oh, geez.
Yeah.
Well, that was more than a pug, maybe.
Well, I don't know.
You said you tell us what a pug is.
He created it, Scott.
Let him measure it out.
Well, pug on three.
Pug on three.
One, two, three, pug.
That's for the listener to like kind of visualize what we were doing.
All right.
I mean, noise.
And with that, Kyle Mooney survived podcast ride.
One of the funner episodes, I think, of the series.
Certainly very cutting for our other episodes.
I would go to record.
I'm saying all of that fun.
But like this one, we're having pubs.
You're really mad at me, though, during the episode.
So you know, we got started talking about citrus.
Like you start talking about the grapefruit.
You got mad at me.
Answer.
You started talking about citrus.
But this is like an old this is like a trick.
Like we know how to gas each other up a little.
This is that improv trick.
You know how to get so far from that nice stuff.
We were in a class in 2009.
I do remember Jason and I talking about theme like it was theme park very quickly.
So to talk about earlier of like.
But then you got in that huge citrus fight and the whole friendship never got off, almost
never got off the ground.
Jason and I fight about citrus a lot.
A lot.
That's a lot of problems.
I love to I want to know more about your guys friendship.
That's something I want to know.
But maybe that's not this.
Do you have one more?
Do you have another like one more question?
We can go out on a question about our friendship.
Any of us, whatever dynamic you're giving me like truly like 30 seconds to think.
Absolutely.
Sure.
Yeah.
We need a week here.
Wait while you do here, just don't pay attention as well.
I said that.
But I'm still going to say your proper goodbyes.
But the so for more of what has just become, we realize the downtown Disney district.
So we use make sure you use hashtag DDD.
Oh, that is a district ordeal.
Hashtag save the level keeper.
Hashtag sector keeper cricket wireless severance.
Tweet that at wireless and not at us.
And for more of the downtown Disney ordeal and the rest of level three, follow us on
Twitter, Instagram and Facebook.
And of course, we will be back tomorrow.
And hey, three bonus episodes every month that podcast or patreon.com slash podcast
the ride the second gate.
That's what it's called.
Not the web address is patreon.com slash podcast.
Right.
I think this pug is getting to me.
So that being said, that's all of our business.
Thirty seconds.
Kyle Mooney, have you formulated a question?
Hold on one second.
One second.
An item is appearing.
Oh, you're right.
It's really nice.
Yeah.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Satchels.
Oh my God.
And it is a oh my.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
It's a it's a medium sized sculpin.
So it's not just a little tiny guy that can't do anything, but it's meaty.
It's like bigger than other sculpins.
So he might pack a pretty serious bite.
Yeah, we could do some damage with that.
That could really come in handy with whatever boss we're going to face.
We face bosses, Kyle, at the end.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm nervous as hell.
You don't have you don't have to.
You're about to get out of here.
Unless you stick around all week.
But that's up to you know, you should try to get out before there's bosses to face.
So OK, well, hopefully that sculpin can be kind of our attack dog or attack fish.
Great.
Kyle, what have you got?
You don't have to ask me.
You can also just say you're Twitter or whatever.
I can turn it off right now.
I can turn the recorder off right now.
What do you think?
I guess you guys met each other like what while you were working on the same improv
team.
They these two.
Well, we were around.
We were we met each other in an improv class.
And then a few years later, we were put on the same team.
I think because one year later.
Yeah, it was a few.
I think it was 2009.
We put on the team in 2010.
OK, that's right.
Is there more to the question?
Yeah, are you just clarifying some getting timelines right now?
No, I just I. Yeah, that's what.
So yeah, we were in class together first.
We improvised together.
And then I think because of our association with each other, they put together a team
of people that at all like a couple of different little groups together that had worked with
each other.
And so was there a moment where you guys felt like you clicked or got along?
I mean, I think in general, it was I remember we had a class on Melrose.
Yeah.
And I do remember very quickly, like like this guy.
I remember that moment.
I remember, too.
Yeah, you guys are pointing.
I don't remember what I don't remember.
Like the day of it, I just remember very quickly being like, oh, yeah, this guy.
I remember that you I think you did a scene of a man breaking down like in a Taco Bell.
Well, that's it.
You're bringing this up.
It was going to be very interesting for the listener when it really a revelation in my
improv was when Chad Carter had me do this scene.
And that's Chad Carter.
Now you now you just a daily show, former Daily Show writer.
Does he work on the detour?
Is that still around?
I think he's a producer on that.
Yeah.
OK, anyway, let's hear the credits.
What else has Chad done?
I don't know.
He's funny.
Funny guy.
Oh, yeah, of course.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Anyway, you had a now you just have mini breakdowns every time you go to talk.
For years and years, I did a scene about having a breakdown of talk about now I just live
it out every time I go.
And now you get now now you guys all you've met at USC and you formed a group.
You started putting videos on YouTube.
Jason and Mike.
So I remember when we were there, I remember we all got together and I remember thinking
like you were like I was like this guy.
I remember thinking that.
So I don't know if maybe you don't remember that.
Am I getting my groups confused?
So tragic.
My mythologies are getting tangled.
Kyle, let's exit to the gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to plug?
You got to check out this new stuff.
Let's go.
I don't know what to say.
You don't have to.
We've been drinking.
I've been again.
You don't know when this show is recorded, but it's now probably I imagine midnight or
something.
No, no, it's like 1040 and 40.
It's at least 12 at night.
But daily it's just happened, though.
So it is later.
I also came from New York.
I'm now on the West Coast.
You've been drinking for 26 hours.
It is like three in the morning for you.
I just want to say these guys are some of my best friends and they really do great work.
And please check out their other podcast episodes.
Thank you.
Whoa, that's very nice.
Thanks, Kyle.
Oh, man.
Well, I said all the other stuff so we can just get out of here.
Yeah, I guess we're done.
All right.
We'll see you tomorrow.
See you all tomorrow.
Let's Pug it up.
Pug it up, Daddy.
Pug it up.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm, Joe Sileo,
and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts,
Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram, at
Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.