One, two, ready.
There was darkness on the street, Ralph Brennan, he had won.
He summoned the power of his jazz, and the podcast boys were done.
Now we're in the underworld, and I can't lie we're scared.
Ghosts of stores are all around, like the ruins of a builder bear.
The downtown Disney ordeal, a shuttered hog and does how must Jason feel?
The downtown Disney ordeal, what ghastly secrets does the house of blues conceal?
This is podcast the ride, the second gate, the downtown Disney ordeal, level X, stage two.
We're staying strong, we're surviving, I'm Scott Gardner, Mike Carlson's here, Jason Sheridan hasn't quit yet.
Still in the underworld.
We're still in the underworld, things got pretty hairy yesterday as you heard.
Yeah, I did not do any dip with Nick Mundy.
I wanted to, and I texted him later, I would have done the dip with you afterward, and he said I know.
And then I tried to get him to go to a Steve Miller band concert with me in Vegas.
Like that day?
Well, like in a few days, and he goes, any other weekend.
Which I still don't believe, but still it was a nice thought.
That would have been a hell of a place to dip.
He has a baby, but he called me then he goes, I was looking at ticket prices for a Steve Miller band.
There's no other way you could see Steve Miller, but the rarely seen in public Steve Miller band.
Yeah, so anyway, we're surviving, I'm thriving in a way, I guess.
Yeah, and I guess we just got to see what's in store for this.
That's the thing with these episodes, we don't know where exactly we're going yet.
We were surprised to see Mundy, and I guess it's a question of who we'll run into next down here.
Boys, boys.
Wait, was that the Sector Keeper?
Wait, that was familiar.
I don't think it was though.
Oh, okay, let's follow the voice.
Wait, behind all these destroyed RC cars.
Behind this stack of custom RC cars, move them out of the way.
Oh my God, it's Eva.
Guys, it's me.
Eva Anderson.
Oh my God, I've been down here.
We've been so worried about you.
You just disappeared at the end of level one stage three.
I got kidnapped by Nick Valenti.
That's what we thought, we knew it.
Oh my God, yeah, well, that was absolutely crazy.
We did battle with him right after that.
Oh my God.
So I think he's not going to be a problem anymore.
I think we can set you free.
But he banished you.
Yeah.
Right?
This is where he sent you.
He sent me down here.
I've been in the basement of the ghost of the Norton Simon Museum restaurant.
He's been feeding me thousand calorie gratins.
Oh no.
Trying to fatten me up.
Is it gratin?
Was I saying it wrong?
Jeffrey Epstein is here.
Oh no.
What?
We thought this was the Underwhirl.
He took me out.
This is the Underwhirl, I guess.
He made me go on the Lolita Express, the Ghost Lolita Express, and so it's true about me
now.
Oh no.
He made the story of the QAnon story real.
Jesus.
Underground Lolita Express, the trained version.
Oh no.
And on the other one.
Yes.
Oh my God.
One S. Eva's been on there.
If I go back to the planet Earth, then it'll be true.
QAnon will be right about me.
Oh my God.
Then you'll owe that lady an apology on Twitter.
The worst thing you could have to do, apologize to a QAnon member.
There must be a way we can reverse this though.
There must be.
There's got to be, and get you back up there so you can make that apology as soon as possible.
She deserves an apology.
She really does.
My father was a warlock.
Yes, well that was never in question.
The time you hadn't been on the Lolita Express, but now you, how was it?
Did you have a good time?
Oh yeah, they have like a, it's actually catered by Patina.
Oh, wonderful.
The food was fantastic.
As many gold lip bars as you want.
And then my granny gave me a foot rub.
Oh, okay.
It's upside down the Lolita Express.
Turn about his fair play here in the underworld.
Oh yeah, you're holding a drawing you did of your favorite characters, Homer and Bart.
Yeah, those are my favorite characters.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
He signed it.
He said, thanks for letting me touch your beautiful feet, he said.
I'm going to go to Gelada and distract the wait staff so no one else can be served.
That's what he said to me.
Give them a photo of Homer and Bart too, their favorite characters.
Okay, well there's got to be a way we can bust you out of here.
And if I had to guess, it probably involves something that the Sector Keeper knows.
Probably continuing to talk about the Fallen Brothers.
I think thoroughly discussing and reviewing the Fallen Brothers will get you free.
The Fallen Brothers, you mean all these closed shops?
It must be.
Well, let's find out to what end and how many. Sector Keeper, where are we going today?
Boys, boys, today's stage contains Ride Makers, Build-A-Bear, D Street, Disney Vault 28,
Fossil, Star Abilias, Club Libby Lou, Studio Disney 365, Anna and Elsa's Boutique,
Basin, Compass Books, Islands Charters, Kits and Kids, Haagen-Dazs, Blink by Wet Seal,
Little Mismatched, Apricot Lane Boutique, and Anne Geddes. Good luck, boys!
Jesus Christ. That went on and on.
Guys, it's too many.
That's a lot.
That's staggering.
Fuck, the last one was only like four and we ignored most of them.
Normally I'd say we could skip some of them, but we have to rescue Eva and find the Level Keeper.
It's going to be longer than Dogpatch.
Well, it could be. There's definitely a risk of that, but I had a feeling that down here we were going to encounter an extremely long time.
I knew that we were going to face some weight and some rambling, so I thought there's got to be a way to keep us in line.
So on the way down to the Underworld, I downloaded a special alarm app. We don't have to stick with it exactly,
but it will let us know when we've been talking about something for five minutes.
I'm not going to have a hard cut off, but I think it'll be good that it reminds us that five minutes is a long time.
If we truly did more than five minutes about all of these topics, we would be here forever.
The reason I downloaded this specific app is because you can put a custom sound on it.
I was trying to do this off of a podcast episode, but it wasn't clean enough.
There is a sound that I've been obsessed with since it occurred, and I want a clean version of it.
The sound is from our recent Castle Cake episode. Jason was talking about gnawing,
and I was hoping you could recreate the sound that I enjoyed so much, the sound of gnawing.
Would you be willing to make this the alarm? So when we hear the gnawing, then we know that it's time to move on.
So here we go. Hopefully this will record fairly cleanly.
Okay, here we go. And three, two, one.
Wait, I missed it. Okay, here we go.
Okay, how does that sound?
Okay, great. So that will let us know after five minutes.
Now, how do we turn the rules here? Say we were supposed to be talking about the Disney Vault 28,
and we went off on a five-minute Kevin Spacey tangent, and we haven't even discussed Disney Vault 28.
Does that count as the Disney Vault time?
Uh-oh, I hadn't accounted for tangents. I don't think this app has any information.
You've got to save it for the Patreon guys.
I appreciate keeping us on track, but whatever it takes.
Whatever it takes to get us out of this underworld.
Yeah, and if tangents are the way.
Well, I don't know. I think it does. I think as soon as the store is said, it will be on me to start the...
And again, we don't have to stop. I don't want to cut off good coverage.
I just want the sound of gnawing to let us know we've been talking about something for an ungodly moment.
I like it.
Okay, so thanks for recreating the gnaw. Let's kick into it right now with Ride Makers.
Ride Makers, okay. Timer started.
Ride Makers was sort of like Build-A-Bear, but for RC cars.
And Build-A-Bear is kind of like Ride Makers, but for Teddy Bears.
Does that make sense?
Did you guys know?
Yeah, I got it. Yes.
That since they closed at Downtown Disney, that the only existing locations for rides are in Pigeon Forge, Branson, Myrtle Beach, and Destin, Florida.
God's country.
So they're all like spinning distance, a very interesting, some Christian...
All theme park, all weird, the home of Hard Rock Park.
You could take your rides to the Yakov Smirnov What A Country breakfast show at Branson.
Oh, we haven't done that.
The magnetic trays that stick to your table.
Oh, does it have that?
Your seat has like a lecture hall, a college lecture hall, it's a swing out...
Have you been to Branson?
No, I haven't. I've just seen video where he talks about the magnetic tray.
I want to go.
I want to go. I want to see. I don't know. He might not be doing it anymore, but I want to see Barry Williams is like hits of the 70s show.
Oh, man. Let's go to Branson and then we go to Dollywood.
Okay. I mean, yeah, we have not cracked how to do Dollywood.
Dollywood is a frequently talked about topic, but we got I think we have to go there.
I almost went there by myself over New Year's, but I couldn't figure out how to do it.
It's complicated.
Yeah, it's hard to get there.
Pigeon Forge isn't exactly...
Do we have enough listeners around there to get them to do like come to a live show around Pigeon Forge?
That's a good excuse.
Maybe that's it. Or Branson. Is there a theater in Branson? Are we too dirty for Branson?
We might have to clean it up. Yeah.
Honestly, we could clean it up easily.
You could review stuff in Branson and then...
Yeah.
Oh, that'd be so fun.
That's definitely fun. And then we and of course, we can visit one of the remaining ride makers because I didn't get to do this.
You didn't get to. I chose not to do this when it was there.
Even though I was here. What was it? You build your own remote control car.
Well, you built a car and for an extra 20 bucks, you could make it remote control.
So you just wanted a car and they had licensing. So you could build like there was Marvel in DC, Disney's cars, of course.
But then apparently they had agreements with Dodge and Ford and GM. So like, I guess you can make a Mustang sort of thing.
Do you guys like remote controlled things?
Well, Rex is remote controlled over there.
I used to do this thing where I'd drive around a parking lot, controlling a remote control car from our real big car.
That's fun.
That was a lot of fun. I forget why, but we called the little car Ruben's Speed and the name of the game was Ruben's Speed.
It's like try to not run over your own car.
Yeah, yeah, which we did not. We never because you can never play again if you if you run over it.
Yeah, that's really fun. It was a blast. Yeah, extremely. You need a really open space.
I think we did like take it onto a regular road once and almost get in some trouble.
There are some neighbors who were glaring at us.
These are some questions that are from the FAQ.
Right. What is Ride Makers?
TM. Ride Makers is a fun car customizing experience where kids with a Z from four to one oh four create cool one of a kind rides.
Who owns Ride Makers? Ride Makers is privately held by a group of investors.
Sweet. Whoa, that's radical.
And then I didn't understand this one.
Will Ride Makers accept Build-A-Bear Workshop coupons, gift cards or points?
Build-A-Bear Workshop stuff for stuff club reward certificates may not be redeemed at Ride Makers shops, locations or Ride Makers dot com.
You may not earn stuff for stuff club points for my purchases.
Build-A-Bear Workshop coupons and or gift cards cannot be redeemed at Ride Makers.
Like are people trying to do this all the time?
Because it doesn't seem like the same people own both things.
Even though we should explain the Ride Makers at Denon Disney was on the bottom floor of and Build-A-Bear was on top.
So I guess I didn't even realize they were affiliated companies.
They were sick of people trying to use their Build-A-Bear stuff first stuff points to get rides.
Having enough like write an FAQ and I assume everyone.
Just put it on the website.
Yeah, everyone read the FAQs before coming in the store. Guaranteed.
People got confused because the signs were so close to each other they'd wander into the wrong one and try to use a gift card they got.
You make toys. My kid wants to make a toy, custom toy.
And they would like build it the whole thing first and then get to the register and put down the wrong card.
The Build-A-Bear card?
Could you put a Ride Makers motor in a Build-A-Bear bear?
And just have it roll around on the ground?
Yeah, sure.
Just flop around like a fish.
Drive a bear around.
Like it's having a seizure?
Yeah.
Probably.
This is one of the only things that I wish I kind of had made a rides when I was reading about it.
I was like, oh, that'd be fun to have a rides.
You didn't want to make a rides.
I thought about it for about 10.
There was a rrrr.
We got it.
Again, doesn't mean we have to move on.
It's just letting us know the.
Do you have anything else you want to say about rides?
I also wish I had made a rides.
It does look like fun.
Honestly, I don't even know that I ever went in.
I went into Build-A-Bear a decent amount of times and never built anything.
But I feel like I never went in the ride maker.
When you go in and not.
Yeah, I wanted to see what new outfits they had for the bears.
As you know, I have.
There's a whole controversy because Duffy, some people put Duffy in Build-A-Bear clothes.
Oh, that's weird.
And for a while when they were pushing Duffy in the park, Build-A-Bear was active.
So you had your choice of customizable bear options.
Yeah, and it was controversial.
A lot of people didn't agree with it.
I didn't do it, by the way.
I just was interested.
That's like, that's an affront to God.
It's trying to mate a dog and a cat.
Yes, yes, it's playing God.
To put your Duffy.
Yes, to play to place your Duffy in Build-A-Bear clothes was against the Duffy message board.
A lot of the people really had strong feelings about it.
But he fits, they fit each other?
They were around the same size.
And also, I think Disney was trying to get in on the Build-A-Bear action with Duffy.
Yeah, as well with all the outfits and stuff.
The Duffy message board seems super chill.
Just like a rad place to hang.
It is about 30 of the angriest people.
Really? Is it on Reddit? Is it subreddit? Where is it?
I'll send you the link.
Okay, I want it.
It's so micro-focused that I don't even want to say where it is.
How active? Still active?
Still pretty active.
There was one central figure who was, I read a little bit of his work on the Duffy episode.
The gaudy of the worst stuff.
The gaudy of the, and he is, honestly, he is less active recently.
So I wonder if he's fallen out of love with it.
But he was the one who was getting on everyone's ass for not spreading the gospel of Duffy.
We are not doing enough work.
Did you ever do a thing where you like search just generally for whatever his screen name is and see if he's on any other boards on other topics?
Yes, but he had Duffy in his name.
So I think he had a Duffy-specific name.
Okay. And you never got his first Christian name?
Clarence Dufferman.
I need to know everything about this guy.
I don't believe so. I went really deep on the message boards though.
And I really got some of his backstory.
And it really like, it did, you know, it was like Magneto in X-Men.
It's like a tragic upbringing.
And I started feeling bad about it.
I started getting a full picture of him and his...
Might have made him a Duffy tyrant.
Yeah. And it was a simple, he was a sympathetic villain.
It's Todd Phillips's next movie.
Oh man. He's a... He's a pill Duffy man.
Yes.
By the way, did any of that count as the start of the timer for...
For Build-A-Bear?
I think we should start it.
Alright, let's start it now.
Start Build-A-Bear now.
Great.
I'm going to put it in my shirt pocket so the audience can hear the rubber.
That's good.
Build-A-Bear again. I never bought anything in Build-A-Bear.
But the idea of it is really good.
It's a really good idea.
The only thing that's a little morbid is that you are actually stuffing your bear.
Which I find odd.
Taking its skin, putting it on a tube.
Yes. You would literally go get loose skin from your bear and stuff it.
You could decide how stuffed you want it to be.
Yes, you could make him extra stuffed.
Like if you want to make him a bladder bear or a stuffy bear.
Could you just keep the skin loose?
Well...
Like a bear rug?
That's a good question.
Why so?
Would they just sell you a loose skin of a bear?
Too weird.
No way.
You could just have like ten of them and just put them out like the little rugs around.
Or they could be rugs for your other characters, your other stuffed animals.
Like your stuffed animals, your Duffy sits on a Build-A-Bear's flesh.
It's like the flesh of his enemy.
It's like he killed and disemboweled his enemy.
Then you could stuff it with like anything.
Yeah, a newspaper.
We did this thing in college.
We bought a pinata and then we went to the 32nd Street Market by USC and just bought all this organ meat.
It was an Elmo pinata and we just filled it with meat.
Then we convinced a birthday guy who was drunk to break it open.
Oh no.
It was full of meat.
Literally like tubes?
Yeah, like hearts and livers and stuff.
But it was funny too because we couldn't hang him up because he was all damp and heavy.
So he just like was sitting under a street light out on the street, like under a pool of light.
Then we gave the guy, our friend, a bat and we're like, do it.
Go to town.
Then the meat came out.
That's something you could do with a loose Build-A-Bear's skin is put meat in it.
Again, your college experience, very different.
You could drive around throwing Build-A-Bears full of meat at people.
Yeah, that's a fucked up thing to do.
Have you ever written meat pinata into a script?
No, and I don't know why.
I've got to put that in something.
Prior patch season two, meat pinata.
They had Ninja Turtle Build-A-Bears, which I was very excited to see.
Can you still order those?
Well, they still have Build-A-Bears.
So it's a good question if they're still on the website or they're still in the stores.
Did you guys know about in 2018, Build-A-Bear held an event in the United States and Canada
where patrons could pay their child's age for a bear?
I don't know.
This attracted massive numbers of people, overwhelming the franchise stores.
Shopping malls where Build-A-Bear franchises were located.
This is from the Wikipedia.
The event prompted a surge in public awareness of the Build-A-Bear brand, according to a subsequent poll,
nearly all of which was negative.
That happened last year.
Oh my God.
Also, did you guys know this, that Build-A-Bear is starting an in-house production entity this year?
I did not know that.
Build-A-Bear entertainment.
From Chicken Soup for the Soul.
Oh, guys.
So Build-A-Bear entertainment.
The first planned movie is to be called the Honey Girls movie.
Everyone get your packets ready.
There's two movies in development for the Hallmark Channel.
Yikes.
Wow, of course.
A movie where built bears hang out.
That's interesting.
I think they definitely had a split from Disney because I can't find any of the Marvel characters that they used to have.
The bears would be able to dress up as Marvel and now it's DC on Build-A-Bear website.
And you can get Joker Bear.
What?
Yes, here, let me show you.
But where?
Here he is, Joker Bear.
Oh, he's a little pal.
He's a little pal.
He's pretty cute.
He has green hair and he has ha ha ha written on his face.
So he's kind of like the Jared Leto.
He's got a tattoo.
Do you want to know how I got these stuffings?
And a condom full of stuffings to his friend.
On eBay it's $180 for one for a Build-A-Bear Joker.
Wow.
And then there's a bear and I don't know if I'm wrong about this.
There's a bear that's just wearing glasses and he has a jeans and a t-shirt.
And I just looked at him and I immediately thought, oh, it's Jim Gaffigan.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
He's kind of an emo bear.
Pleasant, well doughy.
I've never been inside a Build-A-Bear, but now I kind of want to go.
I haven't either.
I mean, I appreciate how it was a little Chuck E. Cheese-ish and as a kid I would have really.
Uh-oh.
Again, it doesn't mean we need to stop.
Sorry.
If it fucks up the flow.
No, no, that's okay.
That's okay.
I just want to hear it better.
I just keep thinking something's wrong.
Maybe I just need to keep it held up to the.
Well, you can just turn the volume up and leave it there.
If it's just a little in the background, it might be.
Do you know that the stores also carry something called barofinalia, which sounds like drugs
or sex.
Yeah.
And it's just candy, greeting cards, jewelry, stationery, stickers and t-shirts.
I like that they made up a word, but it is a creepy word.
Barofinalia.
Yes, for a place where you stuff dead skins.
They have, I see on the website, they have their honey girl section.
So this is what honey, honey girls honestly look like.
They have the same color palette as brats.
Okay.
Oh yeah.
So this is like what it's going to be.
Let's, what are their names?
Well, of course, like we've, we've talked a lot about IP here.
Store IP.
More friends.
Yeah.
Honey girls, Tegan, honey girls, Risa, honey girls, Viv.
I'm also creeped out by the term, the name honey girls.
Like, isn't it?
Cause isn't there a word similar?
Like, I don't know.
Like if you're a honey trap or something, what's the.
Honey trap is a.
No, honey.
Honey.
Yeah.
Honey pot.
Honey pot, honey trap.
Same.
Yeah.
Honey girls.
Sugar babies.
They're like sugar babies that get paid for sex.
Yeah.
It's a creepy term.
I know.
I think that's probably what the, it's about them posing as, you know, prostitutes to lure
other stuffed animals into different.
Yeah.
This is all Tinker, Taylor, soldier, spy shit.
They're all.
Guys, Epstein's around.
Be quiet.
Don't let's not give him any ideas.
He's going to go back to earth, get these bears and prostitute him.
Honey girls.
Jesus Christ.
I made it candidate Epstein is down here with you.
Yeah, you did.
It was to tell her if we meet another guest, that's going to be unfortunate news to break
to them.
So welcome.
And by the way, Jeffrey Epstein's here.
The honey girls.
Okay.
So you told me he committed suicide.
Oh, you.
It was a copper field.
It wasn't.
It was just a big misunderstanding.
Oh, okay.
He had plenty to be sad about.
Yeah.
He's a razor, I guess.
So.
I can't find any honey girls movie on IMDb.
I don't think it's happening.
I want to see who the casting was, but.
Do you think maybe they're they were deciding to go with some of their other IP, like the
Berry Fairy Friends?
Oh, they're cute.
They're cute.
Pink Unicorn Fairy Friend, Pastel Bear Fairy Friend.
They don't have any names.
They're just describing them.
The other IP I like, the Horses and Hearts Riding Club, which is all just outfits for
your bear.
If your bear wants to ride a horse.
If your bear wants to do dressage.
Yeah.
That's an affront to God as well.
Honestly, these are on sale right now and maybe I should buy Duffy little riding pants
and little riding boots.
But not from Build-A-Bear.
Are you crazy?
Don't do it.
I worked at this in college.
Jason, I worked at this really weird, creepy, like souvenir store on the Santa Monica Promenade.
And one of the things that we sold, it's called Blue Wave, was WWF shirts for children with
Tasmanian devils, like screen printed onto them after the fact.
Whoa.
Also wrestlers?
Yeah.
It was like it started with a wrestler shirt for like an infant and then it would either
be Taz or like Tweety Bird just kind of in front of the wrestler.
And it cost like $27.
Wow.
That's what I feel like putting Build-A-Bear on a Duffy is.
Cause it's not a wrestler shirt.
It's not a Taz shirt.
It's like a, it's cheap.
They don't belong together.
The kid gets made fun of when he goes out in it cause he knows it's, everyone knows
it's not a real shirt.
I think it's a good value for the kid.
I mean you got Tweety Bird and Mark Henry, the world's strongest man.
You know?
There's one that had the Undertaker and Taz on it and it was for like a one year old.
I was like, I don't like this at all.
Oh my God.
You know, we got, honey, we got you a shirt where Taz is being taken to the grave.
Taz getting choked slammed.
You'll spin no more.
Let me look up the return policy and like, maybe I can just like try the clothes on Duffy
and see if they look good and if not, I'll just return them if it's a generous policy.
I also have to retract.
They do have, they have a very small Marvel section and it's just bears with A's on their
stomach and then one Thor bear, but that's it.
The pick is a slim.
No Spider-Man.
No, they don't have much more DC stuff.
I don't like Build-A-Bear.
It's ugly.
Did you see?
I don't, you know what I don't like?
I, both ride makers and Build-A-Bear, I'm glad they're out of downtown Disney just because
their signs were ugly and their logos are ugly.
And part of the recent beautification, beautification sort of, it's a little more appealing of a
place to me because there aren't so many horrible logos all crashing, clashing, including a
logo for a little girl's makeover boutique that we'll get to in a little bit.
I just have one quick other thing I want to bring up about Build-A-Bear.
Their affiliation with the Girl Scouts of America and they have a whole line and Jason,
you're going to be very interested in this.
So keep those ears open.
Let me read some of the different bears you can get.
Is that?
No.
Yeah, go on.
Thin Mints Cookie Bear Doodle Print Gift Set.
Thin Mints Cookie Bear Junior Gift Set.
Thin Mint Cookie Bear Cadet Senior Ambassador Gift Set.
Thin Mint Cookie Bear Daisy Doodle Gift Set.
Thin Mints Cookie Bear Brownie Gift Set.
Does the mint, does it smell like mint?
I hope it does.
Ooh, tell the sector keeper.
It's his favorite kind of jewel.
And just Thin Mint Cookie Bear.
So these are the Girl Scout bears.
God, they're like electric blue.
They look like a mint lifesaver color.
They look like they were incorrectly dyed or something.
Like they went and they got in the wrong washing machine.
Yes.
If I got that toy as a child, I'd be so angry.
You had my curiosity, but now you have my attention.
It's like we're going to hear the nom nom nom and it's not going to be the alarm.
Yeah.
It's got thin.
You know how Duffy has the Mickey on his little paw or his little foot.
It says thin mints and it's the picture of a cookie's on his paw.
Is that, am I like just imagining this as the bear like thinner than a normal bear?
Like a little malnourished.
It's like lean.
It's been leaning out.
It hasn't had protein, just sugar.
Yeah.
It's like that starving polar bear we all had to look at that one day.
I can confirm that you can add fun extras like thin mints cookie scent and plush thin
mints cookies.
So you can smell a cookie or you can just get like a cookie doll?
A doll of a cookie?
Yes, I think you can get like a little cookies for him to pretend to eat and then it's $4
to add the scent.
So a box of Girl Scout cookies worth.
Can I get that now?
Can I order that now?
Could we just get the scent?
I want the scent on another thing.
On a ride maker?
Yeah, I want a car that smells like a cookie.
Here's what the cookie, the fake cookies look like.
You can wrap him around his little paw to make sure he holds onto the cookie, which
it's just going to look like he has like a little handbag or something.
Or like a little turd.
He's a shin in his hand.
A little turd handbag.
What are the other varieties?
What are the Lord of the Dunes?
What are the Caramel Delights?
This is the website.
I wish I had more variety for you, but it's all.
I hate this toy.
If you want me to read the six, I'll read the six again.
No, please never.
I don't want to get out of here.
I don't want to get in there anymore.
No, stop it.
Get him out of here.
We have Epstein's around the corner.
He's going to get us.
Monday's not here to unplug my mic this time.
No, I wish.
Frank, can he come back magically?
Let's stay in Carlson country though.
Tell us about D Street.
And let me start the timer.
All right.
D Street was definitely them thinking like they imagined in their head a consumer that
looked very much like me was of my age at the time and they're like, what does this
dickhead want?
And it was like vinyl toys and Marvel and Star Wars t-shirts.
And they thought that they should make the store a little darker, you know, like literally
like visually darker, I think.
Cause you know, it's cool.
This is for the, this is for your millennial.
I'm still a millennial by the way.
So it's like a hot topic.
It was, it wasn't that aggressive, but it was closer or like kid robot.
Yeah, kid robot.
It was Marvel toy.
It was like for your like Disney fan who like likes the obscure characters, but also might
like the action adventures as the things they bought.
So I would go in there and buy vinyl figures generally and a shirt once in a while.
What's the best thing you bought there?
That's probably a park star.
They sold, I think they sold them in there.
I think so.
And then I, for a while I did have some Marvel vinylmations that I would buy.
But then I did sell them cause I have too many toys.
Yeah.
So I would buy, I would buy those in there.
They weren't great.
You, you got really into buying the full park star set.
Yes.
And I would just, I like to chase.
I would buy the individual box.
But at a certain point, if you want all of them, it made more sense for me just to buy
a box of whatever 16 or 12.
So I would get each one.
I think all of them is so many.
It is.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I have them, the shelf is crammed upstairs of all of them.
Google park stars, it just tells you how to go to Joshua tree and look at the sky.
That's the first thing that comes up.
Who cares?
That sounds dumb.
And was he a toy?
Show me your rides.
Yeah.
Z, did you use a Z?
I found them.
Okay.
They look pretty fun.
Yeah.
I bought them on eBay for pretty cheap.
It all depends.
That orange bird I have is still, is still expensive.
I could sell that for.
These are cool.
Under bucks.
Yeah.
I only have Rex.
I have a baby type.
Yeah.
It's, it's very cost effective to only like one character.
Yes.
Um, keep his expenses down.
Yeah.
But when that character is Betty boob, she's on everything.
Jason, you, here's your favorite characters, Betty boo.
Jason and Simon.
Cannon.
Just when things were starting to get cheap with Jessica rabbit, she's on nothing nowadays.
You're not buying nothing but little tin lunch boxes, mounting them near walls.
It's not enough lunch.
I went to something at the new Bevan.
They showed a Betty boob cartoon before it and it was super funny.
Like old Betty boob cartoons are trippy and cool.
They're, they're like from that really early.
The Fleischer company.
Yeah.
They're fun.
Why were we just talking about Betty boop?
Was it for something that hasn't come out yet or for so many of these?
I heard you guys talk about it.
Just about.
She's so highly sexualized.
Yeah, sure.
You may come up.
Were we offended by her?
I think you were.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Yeah, that sounds right.
But no one should be offended by her who so solemnly paid tribute to the heroes of September
11th.
Did everyone see that on Twitter?
Was that recently?
Yeah.
Like the, with the corporate Betty boob brand said, never forget in a photo of the freedom
tamper or like maybe, or the two lights, I think that replaced the.
I was trying to find the picture of Mr. Met like doing the nine 11 thing, but he's smiling
on the, like the head is smiling.
So it looks like he's happy about it.
My plan.
Someone showed me this.
He's like, it worked.
New York city, still best city on earth.
Can't help but smile.
What more D street or can we?
I mean, there's not a ton of D street, honestly.
I, you know, I did some window shopping.
Yeah.
I would, I browsed a lot in there, but also they'd still never get as I, as I've said
before, they've, they've still not catering to the hyper obsessive niche retro nerd retro
market out there.
Like you can buy stuff online sometimes, but they're still, you have to go to D 23 to buy
that stuff.
Not even D 23.
Like they were doing a whole series of shirts that were really obscure that we bought a
couple of and then they stopped it because obviously like the, maybe the market's not
there for that.
I think they realized if they go a little obscure, they can still mass sell it and get
it on Instagram as opposed to going like hyper obscure and 50 maniacs buy it.
Yeah.
You gotta go to, you gotta go to like Etsy or you gotta go to like a T-pub, like people
legally making these shirts now.
A lot of good bootleg stuff out there.
Nice.
Oh well.
Do we beat the timer?
I think we did.
Whoa.
Yeah.
I wish it was easy.
Yeah, we did 17 seconds to go.
I wish it was easier to do like rollover minutes.
Like, oh, we're actually seconds, 17 seconds for this next topic.
I guess.
Okay.
Disney vault 23.
Let's start it.
Disney vault 20.
I never went in here really.
And looking at pictures, it's like, you can buy a lot of floppy hats.
You can buy a lot of like, like straw hats, home goods, home.
Yeah.
Home goods, but also some t-shirts and also just like flannel shirts, like not Disney specific
flannel shirts.
I just like this Yelp review.
Shopping or not, you gotta enjoy these beautiful places.
I love the look of these places.
Shopping is not the most important thing.
Looking around at the amazing decor and finding the hidden gems around.
Just enjoy the love that is put into these places and realize it goes further than just
a place to spend money.
What does that mean?
Buildings, rooms?
That really sums up like so many of these closed shops, like because a lot of them do
make you go, how many people bought something here?
Or we're just browsing around for the three years it was open.
It reminds me of like all those places in city walk, like what's that woman's name?
Francesca's or whatever.
Yeah.
It's just like, it's just a.
Also the name Disney Vault 28, every time I would walk by there, I would have to remember
that it's clothing.
Not a cool thing.
Because Disney Vault is of course the mythical place where they put their movies when they
don't want to sell it to you or they want to withhold the movies from you.
Yeah.
It's not where you couldn't walk in there and find the original print of Song of the
South.
Right, which is what it sounded like.
Yeah.
So like the idea, and it feels like the door was a big vault.
Was it ever cool?
Doesn't seem like it.
I don't think so.
You could go in and buy a flannel shirt and that's it.
But you got to enjoy these beautiful places.
Look.
Shopping or not.
The number one thing is.
The beautiful door.
They really made it.
It really is there.
You have to enjoy this.
You have to enjoy these beautiful places.
You love to see it.
Folks, we love to see it.
You love to see these beautiful places.
All right.
I'm going to reset it.
We're going to go to Fossil.
Fossil.
We better not use the five minutes on Fossil.
Fuck this shit.
It's a Fossil.
It sucks.
It's gone now.
It's gone.
What am I mad about?
It was one of the City Walk cousins.
It was one of the, you know.
What would you buy there?
Sunglasses?
Is that where you go to get some sunglasses?
Wallets.
Watches.
Big watches.
Big boys.
What's the biggest watch you have?
I just have a couple basic Timex face watches.
Hmm.
Have we done?
I got a really small wrist, so I can't go too big.
So do I, friend.
Yeah.
Oh, you do, don't you?
Oh, man.
Wait a minute.
How, who's, is my wrist big?
I think it is, comparatively.
Yeah, comparatively.
I used to be able to wear a children's watch.
Huh.
The children's little.
Let me see your wrist, Jason.
Sorry.
I'm just really fascinated.
Like, think about my proportions.
Like, yeah, let me see your.
I guess you're right.
Yeah.
I just never noticed you had an incredibly narrow wrist.
Let me see your hands, Jason.
Please.
Bring them this way.
I'm far away from the couch.
I didn't even know.
I got one that I just.
I always thought I had a skin, skinny wrist.
I mean, wrists are skinny in general.
Yeah.
I think if you had a fat wrist, it wouldn't even mean that they're like, the rest of you
was, had a problem.
It's a bone structure.
Yeah.
It's all bone, yeah.
I think it's, you might have like a specific, like maybe your wrist is sick.
See, I have, I have small wrists, but I have much, I have smaller fingers, I have short
fingers.
Interesting.
Do you ever find, do you guys find these, these little issues ever that come up or actually
bother, are you bothered by short fingers?
Has it ever been a problem in any particular way?
It's a weird, like I have friends who are pianists or whatever.
Oh, that would be a problem.
Sometimes their fingers are twice as long as my fingers and that's creepy to me.
Whoa.
Oh, yeah, twice.
You ever have a typing issue?
Do you ever not be able to reach or go from shift to.
Not that bad.
I know I don't think so.
I can type on a standard, I can type quite fast.
I can type pretty fast, but I can tell when the typing lessons end it, like when that
class end it, cause when it starts to get to the shift number categories, I gotta look
down.
I, when I was learning how to play the guitar and I was testing out different tabs, I saw
it, there was a Dave Matthews band song I was trying to play and I could do this crazy
chord that he plays like with his, and I was like, Oh, my fingers, I guess are long.
Cause some people said they couldn't do it.
What was the chord?
I can't remember what note it was.
I can't do closeup magic.
Oh no.
Yeah.
But I don't want to.
Oh, good.
Cause you're not a warlock.
I'm not a warlock.
Like anyone who does closeup magic would be called deemed a warlock.
And admitted warlock.
He said it.
Look, he admitted it to everyone.
Warlock is to which, right?
Yes.
It's just witch and warlock.
Weirdly though, also, when I was a kid, the national inquirer published a story about
how my mom was a witch and they included a spell that they said she had done.
She'd done a spell.
Is that where they were getting it from?
Or is that just a coincidence?
My mom was a Wiccan.
Oh, so a witch then.
But they also said she'd cured someone's cancer with a spell and then they published
the spell and none of that wasn't true.
So anyway.
Wow.
So you say.
I know.
That we know it wasn't yours.
But I mean, don't let the QAnon's find this out.
Well, this is, we're behind the paywall, so they won't know.
This could be a lot of our audience could be QAnon.
People willing to pay for a theme park, Patreon, paywall.
Let's be real.
A lot of the Q&A stuff is crazy, but the EPC and stuff, I don't know.
Some of that.
He's listening.
Oh, God.
He's always a few stops ahead.
Peeking around the corner.
I feel like he got out easy that he's not in hell.
He's in the underworld of he's in like some weird parallel theme park mall, which is inherently
more fun than hell.
And it has a club Libby Lou in it.
It has a club Libby Lou.
Is that where we're heading?
No, I think we're heading to.
Starabelias.
OK, let's be proper with the order.
This is another thing that sounds like a sex act or like a sexual like.
Kind of like a starabelias.
Or just like you say, like fecafelia starabelia, like it's just like I can only fuck big movie
stars.
Oh, my life.
This is a perfect example of the don't even worry about buying anything.
Just look at these beautiful places.
Yeah, because I feel like these kinds of movie memorabilia stores that were so big in the
90s and in this case, the early aughts, I never saw anyone at the register going like,
yeah, I want this Scarface signed Scarface thing where this here, this is autographs
of all the James Bond's.
OK, they're all signed ace playing cards.
OK, and they're mounted.
How much does that cost?
I couldn't really find a price, but I'm sure expensive.
If this a review from 2007 says that an autographed eight by 10 of Lindsay Lohan is six hundred
dollars.
Wow.
Madden Framed.
Yeah, the starabelia that was in the downtown Disney, now Disney Springs in Orlando, got
caught up in a scandal for supposedly selling a five dollar bill signed by Babe Ruth that
was not authenticated correctly.
Oh, likely would have been a fake.
Because there's all this fighting in these articles about like, well, this and this authenticator
hadn't been certified like they should have used this a different authenticator.
It's a very, can you like a very weird world?
Yeah.
Member signed memorabilia world is strange.
Autographs are weird also, and they're certainly not what I desire anymore.
But it made me think, do you guys have autographs in some form that means that mean a lot to
you?
No, mean a lot to me?
No.
Or do you just think it's cool?
You weren't even there for it seems so strange to me being like, yes, I have someone got
this signed.
Trying to think the autographs I realize.
I mean, I have some signed comics.
I have somewhere we got Mark Grace, Chicago Cub, Mark Grace to sign something.
I have the last time I had somebody autograph something it was at Comic Con.
I had Jim Steranko, who is a very fascinating character who we should probably do an episode
about who was like a Houdini ask magician in addition to being a writer and artist.
Cool.
In addition to being like the guy who did all the art, like the Indiana Jones concept
art, Blade Runner 2.
This guy sounds cool.
He's a mad man who like claims that there's people that are like he's he carries a gun
on him in the hills of Tennessee because there's people that want him dead.
Cool.
And like he slapped Batman creator Bob Kane for disrespecting him.
Which is great because everyone hated Bob Kane.
It was at a Comic Con where like Bob Kane disrespected him and he came up to him and
like pulled like a glove out and like snapped like.
Yeah, yeah.
And he did like a little like rich guy slap and the next day Steranko saw him and like
stopped an elevator and like hit him full on.
Anyway, I have I have a picture of him like Houdini like a young man because now he's very
old.
He's like Houdini and he signed it.
And I love that.
I the only time I ever did that was I was working on a shoot for a Comedy Central show
that was like promoting the movie, former Dickie something, former child star, Dickie
Roberts.
Oh, yeah.
So we had all these different former child stars that we're bringing in for like a it
was a really weird shoot day.
OK, so side note, there was this convention for I had to drive around Emmanuel Lewis and
I had to pick him up at his hotel and drive him to set and then drive him back.
And he was he was like a 9-11 conspiracy theorist.
He was very strange.
And when we got to set and there were all these other child stars there, everyone was
like, are you guys going to the are you guys coming to the from the TV land convention?
Because I guess there was a TV land convention at a nearby airport.
And it became clear that Emmanuel Lewis had not been invited to the convention and everyone
else had.
Man.
But he didn't but he didn't care.
And then also at one point, he like called me into his trailer.
He's like, do you have a second?
And I was like, yeah.
And he like then he just like pulled up this paper and he's like, welcome family to our
reunion.
I hope you have a great weekend.
He read me like the intro letter he'd written to his family for his family reunion and asked
for notes on it.
You're a writer.
So then also so at the end of the day, I was supposed to drive him back to the hotel and
he's like, we're driving and he's something like, you know what, I think I'm going to
rent a car.
And I was like, oh, well, okay.
And he's like, pull over around here.
I I'm going to rent a car and I'm just going to be mobile or whatever.
And I was like, well, I'm supposed to take you to your hotel.
I kind of got those instructions like just just do it.
Just do it.
So I dropped him off and he like ran into this hotel and then I realized it was the
Nick at Night Hotel and he was just like, he was just going to the TV land convention.
He just was going without being invited and he just like ran into the convention and lied
to me.
What he was crashing.
He was crashing the convention and he knows they'll let him in.
It's me.
So he tries me Webster.
Yeah.
So then the other thing that happened was that I had Barry Williams was there.
Oh, Brady.
That came up on the last episode.
And I had a DVD of the Brady Bunch Variety Hour, which is it's my favorite thing ever.
Oh, we've never talked.
And I oh, we should do a whole you should do a whole episode on that.
And I got him to sign it, but I turned the cover inside out and I didn't show him what
it was.
Oh, and Casey.
And he signed it.
And then he asked me what it was.
And I showed him and he went, fuck you.
Really?
Yeah.
And so now you're doing something on it.
I was being a dick and I was at my job.
It was like a shitty thing to do all around.
But what do you have not signed it?
He hated.
He hates it.
Yeah.
But he's still like us like a singing court like it's so embarrassing.
Now come to my 70s songs of the 70s show and show.
So that's the only thing I got autographed.
Well, all right.
I have two quick autograph things.
Once I won tickets to an advanced screening of Frost Nixon.
And at the end of it, there was a Q&A with Ron Howard and everyone stormed the front
of the theater to get Ron Howard's autograph.
And I was like, well, I guess I'm getting Ron Howard's autograph.
Like I just followed the crowd.
So I have an autographed Arclight ticket stub.
You're not not going to get his autograph.
I'm not going to not get it because he was very gracious.
I mean, he wasn't really rushing out of there and everything.
So then we were like I went to the bathroom and he was in the same bathroom and some guy
was just like, great job, Ron.
And he's like, oh, thank you.
And then just like walked out.
Weird.
Yeah, weird in the bathroom.
Great job, Ron.
You really peed.
The other weird autograph thing is that Mike and I worked a horrible gig once like 10 years
ago or I guess only like eight or nine years ago.
And they didn't pay us, but they gave us a bag of swag at the end, which included an
autographed OK, go city.
You got paid by that.
We got paid by that.
It was only Ashton Kutcher and HP, the printer company.
They didn't have any money.
They couldn't swing a hundred dollars.
A band that's not known for its CDs.
Yeah.
Right.
Or known for its members, pretty frankly.
Oh, also a giant book about the way the future will go from the head of HP.
Definitely will crack into this one.
Guys, this is great.
We rushed the table to get a picture with Robert Evans.
Oh, yes, we did.
That's cool.
We have a picture of us with Robert Evans.
We have his book signed, but he had pre-signed it and they said no pictures before.
And then everyone rushed this old man and took a picture with him and we did too.
That's cool.
You got that?
Yes.
I have an autograph from Emmanuel Lewis's friend, Michael Jackson, which my friend David
gave to me.
He was working out of Beverly Hills office where he was going for doctor visits so frequently
that my friend got bored getting autographs for himself and got an off the wall autograph
for me.
He gave it to me.
I was very moved by it.
Oh my God, you're kidding.
That's insane.
I appreciate this so much and boy, I love off the wall of Michael and then he died the
next day.
Whoa.
I have something that he touched in his last week alive.
That autograph is canceled and that story is canceled.
Conrad Murray.
He may have been looking back.
Maybe he was going to see Conrad Murray.
Conrad Murray.
Yeah.
Those may have been the visits that.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
And then he like flimply touched his album cover.
I wonder why Dr. Murray had been giving me such a great deal on visits.
I went to Michael Jackson's funeral.
You did?
Yeah.
I won the raffle and I got tickets.
What?
The Staples Center one?
Yeah.
Wow.
I just entered the online raffle and then I got two tickets.
You saw John Mayer play human nature in a eulogy way.
Yeah.
What was insane at that?
I don't remember.
Magic and Kobe spoke.
People were just eating McDonald's at the funeral.
What?
In the stands.
So that was weird.
Wow.
Holy shit.
Oh yeah.
Because I guess the McDonald's at the Staples Center.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
It's still open.
Yeah.
Sure.
The Phelps, Fred Phelps people were picketing it.
That was crazy.
God.
Jesus.
Anyway.
Okay.
So that all counted as part of Starbillias and more.
Did we hear the gnawing noise?
It did go off.
I just missed it.
No, it was, yeah.
I guess it's far away from, I don't know if the listener heard it.
I'm not sure.
I have my headphones on.
I'll just, I'll do one myself too.
Anyway, you could buy a Texaco gas pump there or a Ty Cobb autographed baseball for $10,000.
Why don't you do that?
Don't do that.
Ah, the history's most racist man, Ty Cobb.
I don't think I know.
Oh, I once, someone in the stands yelled at him and he climbed into the stands and beat
the man to a pulp and they, yeah, like stop beating him.
He's handicapped.
Like, oh my God.
Yeah.
That's fun.
Wait, just now or before?
Because I know he is now, but.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
Still in a war named after heaven.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Yikes.
Okay.
So I know now we are, this, now it's going to be hard to obey the time even more so as
we enter Club Libby Lou.
A children's fashion retail environment that encouraged celebrating being a girly girl.
And experience at Club Libby Lou always began with a wish.
At the front door of every, at the front of every door were fairies, which would grant
your, their wishes of people of all ages by sprinkling fairy dust onto guests as they
walked into the store.
On a beautiful day, girls of all ages sat in front of a pink colored heart shaped mirrors
listening to pop music and they becoming rock stars, princesses and favorite celebrities,
including Miley Cyrus and Ashley Tisdale.
A makeover cost between 25 and $60, depending on the package of choice, included a full
hair updo, nail polish and makeup.
In addition to playing dress up for the day, Club Libby Lou VIPs, very important princesses,
were guided by their club counselors over to various stations, including a potion bar
where a VIP could make their own lotion, perfume, fairy dust or lip gloss and a pooch
parlor where the guests could own stuffed animals of their choice.
At the end of every experience, each VIP was encouraged to join the free club and was given
a friendship bracelet.
In early 10th of November, 2008, parent company, Saks incorporated announced that due to the
dismal state of the economy, they would be closing all 98 locations.
Dismal.
It's nothing to do with us.
We're this model is sound.
Hard Rock Park and Club Libby Lou victims of the recession just died.
Oh, awful.
As I said before, horrible logo.
Disgusting, but just made the entire area look like trash.
Uvabar fonts.
Yeah.
I pine for Uvabar compared to this one.
That's so gross.
Girls, like I looked up some Libby Lou makeovers and there's just like slutty, slutty little
girls.
What I read was that like what they showed you in the look book wasn't nearly as slutty
looking as what they came out with.
Because I think you probably have like less talented makeup artists day to day than the
people providing the samples.
So it's just broad strokes.
Bright lipstick.
Here you go.
The girls looked insane.
It is the potion, the potion bar and the pooch parlor are very fun, but when you Google them,
they're not quite as magical as you might.
You'd hope they would be.
It's sort of just like as if you're getting like soap, different soaps out of.
Oh, there's pumps.
There's like pumps for like body glitter or they call this body shimmer, which I think
is body glitter.
Am I wrong?
Thank you for clarifying.
8.50 each, which is just like, what do you get?
A cup of body shimmer?
I want to make my shimmer.
Get it.
I haven't finished my shimmer.
Get out of here, mom.
Yeah.
So it's like, it really is sort of like a, maybe it's like a Terry Gilliam style, like
nightmare in a weird way.
Like there would be in Brazil or something.
Oh, like these designs in the way, the way things are literally not shaped.
It just feels like perverse.
The whole thing is like, would be in a parody of this where it's like, see what we're doing
to these kids.
It's in the opening tirade of studio 60 or the newsroom would include, we're making up
girls to look like little whores.
Club Liddywood.
You know what it reminds me of is Lindsay, who just walked through, would know what I'm
talking about.
Hi Lindsay.
Barbizon.
Oh.
Yeah.
So there's this modeling school that advertised in all the teen magazines and there was like,
they had them in every town in America in the eighties and it was like their model was
trained to be a model or just look like one.
And so you take classes there where they teach you how to be hot and then you get like a
modeling portfolio at the end, which you wouldn't be able to use for anything.
Yeah.
All the gens in my middle school got their own.
Oh, Lindsay, by the way, you just entered the underworld briefly.
We found Eva.
That's where she was.
She was in the underworld all the time, but watch out cause Jeffrey Epstein's here.
Definitely.
Oh yeah, get out.
Bye.
She's well, she just walked out the door.
Why do we have to, how can we have to rescue Eva with store after store?
I like being here.
I wanted to be caught.
Classic warlock.
Yeah, this is horrible.
There's like a really nasty blog about it that's titled, where do you take your ugly
daughter so she can be fixed up?
Club Libby Lou.
Oh my God.
You know, it's sarcastic, but it's just like, that's what this is selling to all these girls
that they're too ugly to be in the mall.
They need a makeover.
It's very funny that it's owned by, it was owned by Saks.
Yeah.
They bought it.
They like bought it and over franchised it.
I think it, yeah.
This isn't the last thing for women that was added to Disney, which was founded by like
misogynists.
You'll see, you'll see it's coming down.
No, kind of progressive in terms of like boy store, girl store, boy store, girl store.
Racers.
Club Libby Lou.
This also isn't, I mean, not to spoil it, but this isn't the last place for makeovers
for little girls in this sector.
Well, they were all in this location.
Sectors are for city walls.
Sorry.
I think the alarm, we can like ignore a little bit because these all bleed into each other
a little bit.
So, but before we move on from Club Libby Lou, I think you also found the crazy story
on the Wikipedia of what happened in a Club Libby Lou contest.
Unless we're looking at the same thing.
No.
You tell me.
Oh, nevermind.
So, in order to win a Hannah Montana contest where you got a makeover and four VIP tickets
to see a Hannah Montana concert, there was a, I don't know, there was just something
where you said why you deserved it and a six year old girl talked about how her father
died in Iraq and then she won.
Yes, I saw this.
She was in the middle of getting the makeover when somebody came up to her mom and said,
you know, we looked up your husband's name.
We checked your husband's name with the military and no one has ever served with that name.
So, this mother forced her six year old to tell a fake story of stolen valor to get Hannah
Montana.
Libby Lou's stolen valor.
This truly is the underworld.
It's only getting grimmer.
With this specific, he died via a roadside bomb.
They tell him, honey, tell him it was a roadside bomb.
I looked up video of a wreck.
That seems like the kind of thing that's there.
Tell him it was a roadside bomb.
Oh my God.
Outside Mosul.
And it blew up his whole body, his whole skeleton and any identification that he had on his
person.
You look like a hamburger helper.
Looked like a bunch of organs came out of a pinata.
The E was decimated.
So horrible shit here.
Disney, I think, seemingly decided they wanted to have something like this, but not do business
with this company or maybe they just fell apart entirely.
So the same space got converted into something called Studio Disney 365, which is similarly
ugly.
But Mike, you're going somewhere with this.
Not one of these beautiful places.
Hold on.
It's not a beautiful place.
It's not, don't appreciate it.
What are you heading for?
Did you come across Sweet and Sassy?
No.
No, what's that?
Which is another company that I'm trying to figure out now if it was fully.
So Sweet and Sassy is a little kid's spa.
It seems like it's the sequel to this.
But it's for pampering the little girls.
It's a little bit, yeah.
So it's not quite as gaudy maybe or tacky.
These are some uncoordinated shows we're watching.
But there's still some, like, she's being injected with something.
I know it's her ear pierced.
They're getting their hair, it's a salon, so they get blowouts or they get their hair
cut.
Something like that.
So I'm looking at the website and it says, this is her story, the Sweet and Sassy story.
While researching national competitors, she found the woman who found a retail and party
store for tween girls called Club Libby Lou.
The handful of stores that were started by a Chicago businesswoman were later purchased
by Saks Fifth Avenue.
Dixie who started Sweet and Sassy saw how the unique tween items such as room decor,
bath items and accessories were selling at Libby Lou.
This reinforced her idea that the retail party concept for this segment of the market was
already successful.
Although the Libby Lou parties were good, they were not great and customer service was
lacking.
These parties took place in a cramped 30 square, they're trashing Club Libby Lou in their facts,
in their origin story.
You know, we read ads on our podcast and sometimes it'll say, don't refer to competitors because
we want to say we're better than the other products, but we get these little notes that
we don't read to you, the audience, saying, but don't like trash another thing.
This is like just pure trash.
Does Sweet and Sassy still exist?
Yeah, yeah.
Sweet and Sassy, I think is thriving.
So Dixie saw the opportunity to provide a better experience and then they go another
mile, like an extra mile here and says, in parentheses, Saks closed Libby Lou due to
branding issues related to girls growing up too fast.
Sweet and Sassy learned from this and made adjustments in its early years to keep make
crazy, to keep makeup light and glittery and to keep girls little.
He injected a drug to all girls and to provide costumes that do not show tummies or anything
that shouldn't be seen.
Oh, it's Christian.
So they were like offended by this.
Yes, I am Dixie.
Another woman known as Dixie who's founded Sweet and Sassy, the chain for little girls.
If I walk into a Sweet and Sassy and just like slam down $200, they got to do my hair,
right?
Yeah, I think so.
Give me a makeover.
As long as you don't want your tummy to show.
No tummies.
My money's as good as these fucking girls.
Nothing that shouldn't be shown.
Make my party great.
There is, I'm trying to find, there are no Sweet and Sassy's.
I want my choice of lotion scent.
Here are all the Sweet and Sassy's countrywide.
They're all on the right side of the country.
They're all on the right side.
Let me, uh, Branson.
Starting at Texas and moving east from there.
Where does Dixie live?
Dixie, are you listening?
She is listening.
Where are you?
Sweet and Sassy of St. Louis, Sweet and Sassy, let's see here, Branson.
I probably should have put the timer on the topic that isn't in downtown Disney.
That really nasty ugly girl's blog was about the St. Louis location of Libby Lou.
Okay.
Wow.
Not there, which I'm sure the Disney one was classy all the way.
Dixie saw the same thing that woman saw.
Yes, she did.
There is one in Branson.
See, everything's in Branson.
Or wait, it's, you know, it's actually closer to St. Louis, but that's.
You can get your ears pierced at Sweet and Sassy.
That's kind of crazy.
Yeah.
That's where we move.
It's closer to St. Louis, but still it's not far.
So where, what now?
Cause I, there are two paths.
Well I, what I think, I've made a change the grouping of what you're looking at, but it
seems to me to make sense to move over to what replaced Studio Disney 365, which is
Anna and Elsa's boutique.
So they, they may, they changed it from a generic Disney makeover place to a Frozen
specific makeover place.
You could choose from many different hairstyles that were Frozen inspired.
It mostly involved a tiara, hair extensions and hair glitter.
You could pick your own hair glitter.
If you were a boy, you're not locked out of the fun.
You get to be an Olaf.
I saw, I saw a picture of an Olaf.
I don't know that I would know that it was an Olaf if he was walking around.
I'm going to pull it out.
Cause they didn't just paint the kids white.
They didn't just like douse them in white paint.
It's that you had spiked hair with quote snow flurry tips.
What does that, so you look like Smash Mouth guy basically.
That's what you look like.
That's true.
Who does kind of look like a living Olaf.
He does Steve Harv, what is it?
Harwell?
Not Harvey.
Harvey.
Yeah.
No.
There, oh, look at that little Olaf.
Yeah, it's an Olaf.
Yeah, it looks like a real Olaf.
Oh yeah, that kid is Olaf.
He's having fun.
He's a little, he's my seed.
Look at my little Olaf.
He's my seed.
Look at my spiky hair.
Okay, so you can be an Olaf here, which means spiked hair.
I don't know, like you were saying, it's one of those like, let's jam frozen into the every
like any vacant spot in the parks, let's get frozen in there.
Yeah, they did not know it was going to be a hit like this.
Totally.
Why did it close?
So many singalongs and was it just to get some other store in there?
I'm discombobulated.
I don't know what this time I didn't look up what retail location all these places were.
I don't know where we are.
This one was right next to the entrance, the hotel entrance.
Okay.
Now that area is kind of sprinkles in the void.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, I think we got there and we can move on to on my list.
It is Basin, which is a bath bombs kind of place before.
Still going strong at Disney Springs.
We got and we got another bath bombs place coming up, but there's a Mickey Mouse inside
that was carved from a 250 pound block of soap.
That's cool.
That is cool.
Yes.
I don't think I ever stepped foot in Basin.
No, I didn't either.
There was an oversized sink where as many as eight guests could simultaneously try out
all the natural body scrubs.
They have this up at the city walk too though.
They had a big sink and they encouraged you.
They would say like, what do you want?
Like try out one of our soaps and like.
Get in our big old sink.
Get in there and mix it up.
They should just get a big tub and have you get in.
Oh, if only.
I have a thing in front of me that says, it's weird little soap balls with Mickey ears in
it and it says, soak and relax in this fresh scented bath and watch the Mickey shapes confetti
dance in the tub.
No.
Wait, what?
Like you would drop the bomb and then all of the Mickey confettis would be swimming
around you.
I don't like that.
It feels like he's watching me take a bath.
These there's many little Mickey's.
I see you.
Made entirely of parabens.
We're bathing together.
I'm big with the bath with you.
Little Mickey sperm.
But also yeah, like what is this like on the, on the city walk saga, I was concerned with
my bath bomb cause it had like glitter in it.
Confetti seems terrible.
Confetti seems, I guess it's bigger.
It'll just mess up your drain, right?
Yeah.
Is it true confetti or was it actually like something that would just degrade in there?
They're thicker.
I'm sure it goes down.
I'm sure it's just plastic.
Like the scrubs, like all the like body wash scrubs, there's little beads were just those
microbeads are like killing coral reefs all over the place.
Yeah.
Very bad.
It's all animals are choking on Mickey confetti.
Basin is now Sanuk.
Oh, right.
We're all saying it right?
Basin is now Sanuk.
That's how we get you out of here.
We repeat that mantra.
Let's remember that.
Everyone remember our mantra.
All right.
I'm ending it.
That's it.
That's Basin.
All right.
Compass books.
Oh, I loved Compass books.
This seems like a legitimately cool place.
Yeah.
I actually was reading about on Yesterland because they had a great affection for it.
I love a bookstore cafe.
It's funny because paper book sales are now up.
There was a dip, I think, as e-books were catching on, but now as people are so glued
into their devices and stuff, there has been a swing back to like people want physical
books.
Yeah.
But there's so few bookstores now.
There's so few bookstores and these little like outdoor malls, there always used to be
a bookstore cafe.
I mean, there's still a Barnes and Noble at the Grove and the Americana.
And this closed 2012.
Yeah.
So it stuck around for a while.
For a little while.
I got another store I don't think I ever went in.
How was the coffee shop, Jason?
I think it was fine.
I don't think I had much of a palette for coffee back then.
But when my parents, my family, visited, we would stay down there.
I would usually like walk through, read out some books.
I remember there was, they did have a rack and I saw this in the Yesterland pictures.
There was a rack of like behind the scenes at Disney, including I remember one book called
Tragic Kingdom.
Oh.
It was a body cast member stories, including one that was like the college program students
all live in apartments together and they hook up.
Oh no.
Yeah, they're college students like in one building together.
They're not married.
Yeah, they're not married.
They did not remember going to a presentation about like come do the college program when
I was in college.
And I feel like there was some sort of offhand remark about like curfew or something.
Why didn't you do it?
Because for most schools, it ran a full semester plus two more weeks.
So you had to give up half a break or part of a break and a full semester.
So I couldn't like do whatever winter break or summer break.
I would have had to give up a semester and part of a break.
Would you have taken classes as well?
There's like you take a couple of classes and then you work in the parks or somewhere.
Do you make money?
You do get paid.
Yeah, it is paid.
You would have just given up a, is really the issue here that you would have given up
a break.
Well and a full semester too.
Like as I was going to do, I did a semester in LA.
I couldn't do a second semester out and complete in four years.
Would you have, if you could go do it again, would you have not done LA and done Disney?
I don't, people I know who've done it said it was, they liked it, that it was nice, but
I don't think I ever got a rousing endorsement.
I think the people who really like it go into corporate or like stay with the company for
years and years.
I just dropped out and just hung out at Pleasure Island all of college.
That was my, that's my fan.
Every day is just posting to their Facebook group.
Just going like, man tonight would have been a great night.
There's a Pleasure Island Facebook group and they're all people that work there and party
there.
And there's this one guy who every few months will just be like, tonight would have been
a good night at Pleasure Island.
Weather's perfect.
He's just sitting in his house with his children, looking at them, going on the Pleasure Island
Facebook group.
I wish you were all nightclubs instead of kids.
I wish you were mannequins.
I am on the mannequins.
She had roller skates on.
I'm also on a mannequin specific fan page where people remember mannequins.
And recently a lot of people have been dying from Pleasure Island.
Well people are, yeah, if they were working there at this, yeah, they're getting older.
It's like the deaths of despair they talk about.
Yeah, yeah.
A little more Americans are dying, deaths of despair, which is like suicide, opiate
addiction, loss of mannequins, mannequins nightclub, sex plane ring being found out
about.
Yeah.
Jeffrey Epstein died a death of despair.
We're sorry, Jeffrey.
Your message was love and we didn't listen.
The message was love.
Love, Jeffrey.
Love.
Anything else on Compass?
Well, it was very big.
It took up like that whole stretch.
That's our love sandwich now is a big footprint.
Well, yesterday landed the caption wide store.
It also wide store big boy.
It also had like a very early California adventure.
Sun man.
Yeah.
How does sun man compass?
Very angry.
I don't like him.
Yeah.
Piracy kind of cranky sun man with a mustache.
Even though he looks like my favorite actor, Keenan Wynn a little bit.
Oh, he does look like Keenan Wynn.
He's Keenan Wynn.
He's like a grouchy guy who was in the beginning of Super Train and a movie called Laser Blast.
What Disney?
He's in like the love bug movies.
He's Ed Wynn's son.
Oh, okay.
Ed Wynn's son.
Great.
Yeah.
And then they start on a Playhouse 90 together about themselves.
Wow.
A story that's about their relationship.
Whoa.
A play?
Yeah, there was like some story about like Ed Wynn getting cast in a movie that Keenan
Wynn was in and he wasn't right for the part and he was struggling and then they made,
they played themselves.
You did that.
No, I did.
You touched that in the middle of my Ed Wynn story.
I have no way to do that.
You're talking about Keenan Wynn who I love.
That's true.
I wouldn't purposefully.
Anyway.
I have to start enforcing these because I have dinner to go to.
Beyond the metaphysical plane.
Right.
You have to get out of here and come back into the underworld.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Yeah.
Island Charters.
That's where I saw Epstein.
Oh yeah.
He's hanging out in there.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
The greatest island charter of them all.
Models and authentic leather flight jackets, right?
A lot of Hawaiian island stuff.
When I looked at it, I found the four square page four and the only picture was this man.
That's an unflattering photo of a man.
It's the guy in like a fedora and sunglasses.
It seems like they have boat reproductions.
Yeah.
Handcrafted mahogany airplanes from the Red Baron to the stealth bomber.
He could buy replica planes at downtown Disney.
This is a store for dad.
Yeah.
Right?
Island stuff, leather jackets.
Just thinking about a leather jacket he can't buy, but you know.
And a plane he can't buy, but he can buy a replica.
Or not.
He can't buy that either.
No, you can't buy that either.
Okay.
Let's go.
Another big footprint.
It's now the Wonder Ground Gallery.
You can buy any number of different size prints of hipster Mickey.
There are a lot of.
We'll get to.
Yeah, they are.
We talked about it.
You're right.
I'm so sorry.
I forgot where we were.
Yeah, they are.
We've talked about it.
We've talked about hipster Mickey and all the different.
The guys, Alice in Wonderland.
The J. Scott Campbell.
J. Scott Campbell princess.
Sexy snow white drawings.
We know.
We talked about it already.
We talked about it.
We did it already.
Let's keep moving.
Here we go.
Kits and kids.
Of course.
It's supposedly a celebrity sighting spot.
Well the main one, the Beverly Hills one was, is what I'm seeing.
But I think some people came to this one.
Some people came to this one expecting to see celebrities on Yelp and then they didn't.
There was a narrative about Kitson.
When I moved out to Los Angeles a little over 10 years or 11 years ago, I recall my mom
when she visited for the first time being like, should we go to Kitson to see the celebrities?
So there was some general feeling of like the celebrities go to Kitson.
So maybe that transferred to the downtown Disney location.
Just their reputation of being like, as if you were going to, you know, the Brown Derby
in 1965 or something.
Kitson.
Kitson kids.
Celebrity children.
Right.
So this is what, 10 years ago?
So what celebrity kids were big then?
10 years ago.
You could see.
Ally and AJ.
Mm hmm.
That's good.
Right.
The girl from Whale Rider.
Uh huh.
Yes.
That's good.
Aqua Marine.
I think it's all more than 10 years ago.
I don't even know.
What year is it?
What year?
It's from Leah Obama and Sasha as well.
Of course.
Yes.
Hayley Young.
True grit.
Hayley Steinfeld.
Yeah.
Quinjane Wally.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
And that's it.
That's it.
And that's just about it.
The ladies and gentlemen, the five famous kids.
That you would see at Kitson Kids.
The younger siblings from Wintersbone.
Lemonade mouth.
Oh yeah.
The cast of Lemonade Mouth.
They were always there.
Kitson Kids.
Yeah.
All right.
Moving on.
Haagen-Dazs.
Oh yeah.
I found this really sad story when they opened a Haagen-Dazs in India.
They had this promotion where you could only shop there if you had a foreign passport.
So they weren't allowing Indian people into the Haagen-Dazs.
No.
What?
And then it mimics like this British colonial thing where they'd have signs being like no
dogs and Indians.
And so Haagen-Dazs had to apologize to the country of India for their not thought out
promotion trying to get foreigners to come in.
Oh no.
There was a, I just typed Haagen-Dazs scandal into Google and that's what came up.
Oh my god.
Good strategy.
That's really good.
You should have typed that scan.
Did you do that for everything?
I should have.
I didn't think about it until right at the end.
Like Build-A-Bear scandal.
Build-A-Bear scandal.
I'm going to type it in.
Well, I don't want to speak positively.
I think Haagen-Dazs is usually simple flavors, simple ingredients, always very expensive.
Every now and then I get it on sale, but a little rich for my blood and like not crazy,
not satisfying enough.
Mike's excited.
What's up?
July 13th, 20 to 2018.
Build-A-Bear CEO apologizes for pay your age disaster.
That's the closest it is.
So I'm just excited that that came up for scandal.
How about kids at a Build-A-Bear party were forced to give their creations to the birthday
girl.
Yeah, I see that too.
Wrong.
Terrible.
Yeah.
So that's, I'm just excited that this, there's so many scandal things.
People were really mad about that.
There's a scandal in the next one, but I don't want to interrupt any Haagen-Dazs.
Has anyone here ever gotten Haagen-Dazs like from a, from a not at home, like a walk-up
location?
Never.
I have never done that either.
And they're in most malls, but I'm like, I can't imagine getting a scoop of Haagen-Dazs
on a cone is alien to me.
And it's, and I just go all the way.
I'd rather do like the Rite Aid ice cream and go all the way, go cheaper.
Yeah.
I'm a thrifty man.
That's good ice cream.
So sorry to do this.
Outraged parent blasts mother who hosted a Build-A-Bear party for her child and then
made all eight kids who attended give the toys they made to her daughter.
So the girl got all the pairs.
All right.
Anyway, her dad died in Iraq.
Childhood sympathy scandal as twin boys make Jack Ruby bear who takes out Lee Harvey Oswald
bear.
Okay.
I'm sorry to say that there is racial profiling involved in the next one, which is blink by
wet seal.
This is a, that's in, well, I don't know.
I might've added it later.
There was in the stones later, keeping the goodies.
Sorry.
They were blink might've been the list, but I didn't have a wet seal wasn't anyway.
It's less blink seems fine.
It's just some boring store where you could buy like a, like a very, we haven't gotten
there yet.
A sugar boot esque, uh, the sack that says infinite swag over and over.
So interesting that all of these, like every, so you have to have the same different 10
rest, like restaurants and we don't want to have our like,
Cloth inspirational spot.
Yeah.
So yeah, like they needed that.
And then, but like then you, it is interesting that like a build a bear is in there because
that is sort of an anomaly that comes around and it's maybe more of a fad, but then your
soap store and your sayings store and your glasses store or like those have to be in
every outdoor mall.
And then there'll be your fads that'll come and go.
Makeovers of your children in different slutty ways.
And then of course we'll come in waves, it'll be slutty for five years and then it'll be
princesses for the next.
It'll be Olaf.
Yeah.
Um, wet seal, the name came from the founder and his wife going to a runway show and the
founder's wife saying about a model, she looks like a wet seal.
So the name is like an insult.
And then I think this, it's only retail now.
It all went away and one of the nails in the wet seal empire was that they reached a $7.5
million settlement with minority plaintiffs who charged the company directed managers
to fire African-American employees who thought they didn't fit the company's brand image,
which is the Armani look, white blonde hair and blue eyes.
The Armani look.
Can they call that huh?
There's no other name for that.
I know when that starts with an A and then an R and then a Y.
And an A and an N.
Yeah.
Easy to get them confused.
Okay.
So he's just shopped there at the Glendale Galleria in college.
Wow.
Your college was so interesting.
What that part wasn't so much.
Did wet seal go under?
Yeah, they're gone.
They're retail.
I'm sorry.
They're, did I say retail?
They're online only now.
Good riddance.
Little mismatched.
Three socks that don't match.
I hate it.
It's driving me insane.
It's some shark tank shit.
I like this review.
I've got quite a few of these socks.
They speak to my inner child and make me laugh.
I always want to hold onto that youthful feeling even though I'm just now turning 30.
Again, LOL.
By buying little socks, you hold onto your youthful feeling?
Yeah.
She just explains that they come in three mismatched socks.
When I'm feeling, quote, kicky, I'll put on two from my favorite set, Fabulous 292 pink
and then match it with another Fabulous 293 mauve or Fabulous 294 green.
Yes, they have names on them.
I'm quirky like that, LOL.
You will always find the reviews that read like they're about to segue into I've killed
before and I've killed again.
Find me Mr. Police.
Which ones I choose depends on how playful I'm feeling.
You brought a lot of humanity to that performance.
You could have gotten like sort of like dumber ditzy here, but you're really, I don't know.
You made her seem thoughtful.
Socks don't match, but they have reverse color coordinations which kind of match.
If they were like two socks and one of dots and one of stripes, okay, that's fun.
But the three socks is driving me insane.
Like I can't, I would just buy two packs of three so I could have three complete socks.
This guy's this reviews eight paragraphs long.
Oh my God.
I also see the quote somewhere.
Little mismatched has expanded to include all elements of a girl's life from PJs to pencil
pouches, books to backpacks and wallets to water bottles.
Do they not match each other?
Three water bottles, three wallets.
And those are all the elements of a girl's life from pencil pouches to water bottles.
And that is a life.
That's that does a life make.
That is a life.
That and the Bible.
Learn to accept death now sooner than later.
Do not fornicate.
I, all right.
Is there anything left?
Well, yeah, wait, I have apricot lane boutique.
Oh, fuck it.
It's got a studded peace sign and it says simply become who you are.
Okay.
I did it.
Yeah.
Ten seconds.
Can't be mad at that message.
And here we go, the final going out with a bang and get ease and get a signature shop.
Yeah.
Flagship store.
This was her flagship store.
Has she is she in prison?
Did she ever hear?
Did she pay for her crimes?
She was.
I don't think she's ever been disgraced like Thomas Kinkade was.
Yeah.
I've been to Thomas Kinkade stores and seeing like a painting of a NASCAR for like $60,000.
Why?
Yeah.
It was inexpensive and like lush Hawaii settings and how can he afford?
Mill Valley or whatever.
Yeah.
He's dead.
He is dead, but the company lives on.
Yeah.
And here in the underworld, all the paint, it's all his paintings, all his new works.
I was in Carmel by the sea and I went into, I saw whenever I see when I got to go in and
the lady was like, this was his studio.
Like I was in his actual studio.
Oh, where he would paint and then Korean around the neighborhood drunk.
Sure.
He got a restaurant in Scottsdale.
Oh, yeah.
He got a restaurant in Scottsdale for drunk driving before he died.
Jesus.
Well, if you went into Ann Getty's studio, you might think it was a crime scene.
Look at this, like photos is in the store, a bunch of like sleeping baby dolls in East
Inn.
They're dolls.
They're dolls and they're all in little rabbit costumes, alternating yellow and white.
And they're all sitting in half shells, like kind of a creepier relative of the Osa Pia,
my favorite characters from Tokyo Disney.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
This is much more disturbing because it's a bunch of doll faces.
What is the Ann Getty's type of person?
It's like this was, it's like Ann Getty's exists to be a reference or to be like somebody's
job in like a baby mama kind of movie.
It's like you're not, it's like, I feel like the Ann Getty's type of person is someone
who's not allowed near a normal baby.
So they can just look at the picture of the baby and the pineapple or whatever.
And be like, oh, that's what it looks like.
Very distant aunt.
Is it like sort of how, you know, somebody who really likes to drink beer gets very into
craft beer and knowing about the hops and they have like different types of beer around
them all the time, where it's like somebody like just wants to always have a baby.
They have the baby dressed up in different costumes.
You sort of dress up some bizarre obsession that you have in your head.
Why do you think beer people are as creepy as baby costume?
Well, I'm just, I'm trying to draw a parallel between the thinking.
Making your own beer can be a weird thing, but yeah, people brewing their own beer, putting
a baby into a shell, drugging the baby so it doesn't move or just finding a baby.
And then it's perished.
And before the cops get there, you put them into like a ear of corn costume and then put
a little corn around it and then take it all away and be like, oh no, this baby is sick.
911.
Then start leaving a beautiful corpse.
You just have to, I think Aunt Geddes was born with this like nefarious superpower of
knowing where, when a baby has died.
It's almost like having a police scanner, but it's like a internal and psychic.
So she can race to the scene, climb through the window, do the little photo shoot, then
escape and take the costume with her.
And if you're the parent, you wander into that shop.
She also puts a spell on you so you don't recognize your own child in the photo.
So this shop is exhibit a, what you're saying.
It's a through beautiful photos.
The baby's sleeping.
Yes.
Forever.
Not a bad horror movie.
Yeah.
Honestly, not.
Luckily this is by the paywall.
So not too many people can steal it from you.
She has to take photos of the babies or else they'll come for her.
Like they'll, yeah.
Yeah.
So it's the only way she can stave off like her dark curse.
This shop had such a central location.
It's now the main Starbucks.
Oh, this shop also only lasted five years.
That's so weird.
Like they got it open and they went, oh no, what have we done?
When does the lease run out?
Like do not let her renew the lease.
This truly is the scariest photo.
It really is.
What are they in?
That's like an FX twin music video.
Oh yes.
They're like, it says like the photographer who put babies in flower pots, but it looks
like they're hatching from like egg sacs.
Yeah.
Like they're xenomorphs.
Like Baron Harkonnen from the David Lynch's Dune.
Yeah.
She's Australian.
And she's married to Kel Geddes.
Her husband's name is Kel, which sounds Kryptonian.
I hope to God he doesn't have a tequila brand.
I'm honestly, I've been trying to Google it right now to find out if he has a tequila.
Kel Geddes.
I don't see a lot.
Formerly Kel Mitchell.
He took her last.
Kel Geddes.
Oh boy.
People make fun of Stedman and like the ultimate, like, you know, lesser than the wife husband,
but boy to be Kel Geddes.
I think I'm very jealous of Stedman.
I found Kel Geddes on Instagram, but his account is private.
He is a branding and media specialist from a 30 year commercial television career and
he's a Vietnam veteran.
Kel Geddes.
I can't make fun of him anymore.
No, you can't.
This is interesting.
Geddes does not audition babies for use as models because she believes all babies are
beautiful.
Okay.
And instead she keeps in touch with multiple birth and twin clubs.
What?
Twin clubs.
Do you know anything about that?
And has thousands of photographs on file that parents have sent her.
Okay.
Oh no.
No.
What?
No, no.
No, don't stop sending the photos.
Send your, send the videos to America's funniest home videos where they belong.
I found another horrifying one.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, it's like they're rats.
They're rats in nests.
They're going to eat each other.
Oh, rat king.
It's a rat king for babies.
Whichever one eats the other will be the baby rat king.
Oh, these photos.
Oh, what a monster she is.
Why are you doing this?
Did anyone ever buy, and this is another store where it's like, did anyone, did it go under
because no one ever bought an item in here?
Like my roommates did have the calendar, the book that she did with Celine Dion where Celine
Dion is posing with all the babies.
No.
What?
I mean, as a joke, we had it around.
It was great.
Oh man.
There's a Celine and Kitty's collab.
Yeah.
It's like a baby in a flower pot and Celine Dion is there.
I know you have to leave Scott, but I just found the Anne Geddes dolls on eBay.
I really got to leave.
Like look at this.
Oh boy.
Anne Geddes dolls.
I don't know if they're making them now.
This is only $33 though.
When you look her up on Wikipedia, it says Anne Geddes MNZM, which if you click, what's
that you click on it.
It's New Zealand order of merit, but just the capital letters jammed together seem like
Nixxiom, the, the Ballyss and Mack cult.
She's got Alex Mack's name branded on her vagina.
Every baby, if you get them out of the shell, they're all branded.
Alice and Mack, not Alex Mack.
Not Alex.
She has powers.
I saw her in a, I saw Alice and Mack in hair in the, in Burbank when she was in high school.
I just found out.
She was in it in the, I saw my friend in it and then he was like, Alice Mack was the lead
in that hair that you saw.
I just saw her on a one of the worst failed pilots in the, in existence, which is it's
called Shangri-La Plaza.
And it is a show all about a strip mall, not too far from where we are right now, like
in North Hollywood.
And it's so it's like all the, like the tire store guys and the donut shop people and everybody
in the strip mall hangs out and it's she's in it.
Melora Harden is in it.
And it is all a musical.
It's a music.
They only made one.
It's see it's very, I wonder if one killed the other or something, but grotesque, horrible
and the worst things I've ever seen.
And I looked up who did the music.
I was so disappointed to find out the guy who did the DuckTales theme.
One of the greatest songs of the century, a show about a mall that's a musical and all
the songs are about the guy who did DuckTales.
It's so awful.
It's awful.
And Alice Mack is part of it.
So evil.
How about these dolls where babies are the flower pots and get these dolls.
You are about to witness a great becoming.
I want, I always thought it'd be funny to do like an adult flower pot photo shoot, like
shirtless, we'll do it.
We'll do it.
Get it together.
Just get the costumes.
We'll be there.
We got nothing better to do.
I'm worried that in we're like 10 months away from Mike going, you know what?
I kind of like the and get these photos full of and get these dolls.
You get a doll's doll meets a friend.
The dolls are more likely for them than the photographs, I think, because I'm going through
and I'm going, well, some of these I could, I could like, there's this one, like a butterfly
that looks good.
Show me that and then tell me again that it is good.
Hold.
I didn't say it was good.
I'm saying like, I could see if I could work my way into thinking it was good.
This is not going to help me this picture.
He's touching a finger.
No, it's like realistic wings and antenna.
That's not good.
I don't know.
I'm not saying I like it yet, but you're maybe we're not far.
We're born of booty sauce.
Um, sick, awful.
So the store went away.
The story is the store went away because Geddes is now concentrating more on photos inspired
by nature and pregnant women.
That's what they say.
And they were insistent that the store is doing very well.
It is not on a, we're not kicking her out.
She has chosen to go right because she's doing different photography.
It seemed a little insistent to stay, to say all that in a press release.
Bad.
Yeah.
Definitely not that only seven photographs were ever purchased.
I'm trying to find Anne Geddes scandal, but nothing's coming up.
It's all you got to be in New Zealand.
It's all, uh, uh, again, night islands where nightmares occur.
Does Anne Geddes have an island?
It's called New Zealand.
She rules it.
She's royalty there.
She's got the merit prize, which is worse than Nixxiom.
Some, uh, oh, so I'm on Anne Geddes website and it says 7 30 2019.
Hi all.
Some exciting news regarding Anne and her body of work.
Hi Kel.
Husband, of course, Kel Geddes.
Last weekend, Geddes LLC has gone on to be successful in this year's greater London enterprise
awards.
I am delighted to confirm that Anne Geddes LLC has been awarded the following most innovative
children's photographer 2019.
Ooh.
So she's still winning awards.
Is she putting them in new things like Minecraft towers?
I don't know.
The jewel sticks.
Uh, this is awful.
What?
We need to get out of the underworld as fast as possible.
Oh, there's an Anne Geddes credit card.
You can get the, now that's my way in.
What kind of rewards can I get for this?
I'm going to go to Japan on my Anne Geddes points.
You're not going to be allowed back in the country.
Anyone who gets this card is put on a list.
A childless man in his thirties carrying around an Anne Geddes credit card.
Sorry, you cannot come in the country.
These babies in the cabbage, uh, like in a cabbage patch.
I want it right now.
Welcome to Cabbage Patch Cuties.
The podcast hosted by one childless man in his thirties with an Anne Geddes credit card.
And I talk to myself too.
You still say I'm my girls and Jason Sheridan is not here.
I was there.
I was out here.
I left long ago.
But we're here father.
You must be perfectly still from the photo.
Take us out of the wallet.
No.
You'll never go, will you?
There are so many different designs.
I need a new credit card.
Oh my God.
And then there's a philanthropic trust cards.
We're watching Mike's turn.
It's happening.
It's going to happen way faster than 10 months.
Yeah, no, I didn't know.
I was high balling it.
Look at all of these cards.
Great.
It's just the visas.
Burn them all.
Yeah.
That is a lot.
And then there's black and white.
Black and white.
Those are the philanthropic ones where you like rewards go to charitable situations.
Yeah, and get his fucking bank account.
All right.
Let's get that.
We don't get to leave.
All we have to do is say goodbye to you.
I get to leave.
Oh.
So.
Are you sending me back to earth?
Yeah.
I think you have passed the test.
I think you get to go back there.
Two hours of talk culminating in creepy baby photos.
Now I can actually say, Eva Anderson, you survived podcast the ride.
I did.
The first.
Thank you for saving me.
We're so glad we made it feel like a more virtuous quest to talk about three sock stores.
And yeah, thank you for being.
Now you wait.
Now you can exit the underworld through the gift shop.
Hold on.
And Eddie's has her own line of costumes you can buy for the children as well.
I knew that.
That's the end of it.
That seems like a given, Mike.
Buy that.
Guys, you'll never believe it.
Put Duffy in the closet.
You'll never believe it.
Put Duffy in that.
Oh, that's a good idea.
We need to tip Lindsay.
Keep tabs on.
If you have the credit card login and you see the words and get ease with the with the
two hundred seventy dollars of spending Duffy in the mermaid costume.
Yeah.
That's a it's an orange mermaid.
That's with that's an awful costume.
Give me the business card.
You're not allowed to have it now.
Oh, God.
Put Duffy in a ear of corn.
All right.
Fair enough.
Anyway.
I'm glad you interrupted the item is appearing.
Oh, yeah.
Well, we have exit.
Wait.
Well, I don't know.
We can do them both.
Let's do them both.
Are you seeing the same one as me?
I'm seeing a thin mint cookie bear.
Full of organs.
Yeah, I'm seeing it, too.
Wow.
It's wonderful.
So we can use either the organs or the costume or the.
It's oh, it's scented, too.
Maybe we can use a we can.
Somebody spent the four dollars.
Yeah, I guess the sector keeper did.
Thanks, sector keeper.
He upgraded on he's holding a little and he's holding two little cloth turds.
So this is a lot of gifts and one we can see.
I'm sure we'll be able to use this against a future boss.
But Eva, you won't be here to see it.
We're going to send you on your way.
As I was saying before, we found out about a baby mermaid costume.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
Do they do makeovers?
All right.
Wait, we have to send it.
We'll send you back upwards with the mantra.
Basin is now.
And she's like that.
And she's gone.
We're still stuck here till tomorrow when we face the final boss in the under
worlds.
Keep following us.
Hashtag DDO, hashtag Save the Level Keeper, hashtag Sector Keeper, Cricket Wireless Severance.
And we'll see you back here in the underworld where you have very intelligently chosen to
pay the money to make sure that we're safe.
Tell all your friends who didn't come to the underworld to do the same.
We'll see you back here tomorrow.