Forever...
...Dark!
Darkness falls out on the street, Evil is its head.
Get your crazy shake to go, And your fried donut bread.
The villains threaten this sacred place, This downtown shopping mall.
We must defend the Lego store, And the Splitsville bowling balls.
The Downtown Disney or to you, We must protect our AP discount meals.
The Downtown Disney or to you, What secrets does the Earl of Sandwich conceal?
Police, boys, my cousin has been taken by evil forces that have inhabited Downtown Disney.
In order to find them, you will need to thoroughly discuss every aspect of them all.
Stores, restaurants, both of the Starbucks.
We have 15 daily very necessary episodes and what's to do so.
I will be there to guide you and keep your conversations from getting too off topic or boring.
The Downtown Disney ordeal, Why do we do this to ourselves?
Welcome to Podcast the Ride, The Downtown Disney ordeal level 2, stage 2, day 5, is that correct?
Yes, it has to be correct.
Alright, you've been with, we're back in another one of those grooves, you and I, the audience and us, I mean.
You've been hearing us for a lot of days in a row.
I hope you've enjoyed the inbox overloading and we're going to keep on blasting.
My name is Scott Garen here joined by Mike Carlson and Jason Sheridan.
Let's, I don't know, let's get to it.
I guess we can, yes, no fun banter up top.
Let's just get to the thing, let's just get through, let's help.
Let's not waste time with a bunch of stuff that isn't really anything.
No, and it won't happen during the episode.
Let's just be all business.
All business today, that's what we've decided for today's episode.
And not me, Andrew.
In the service of that, let's summon the Sector Keeper for one quick sec and then he'll go back to whatever no good shit he's doing.
Sector Keeper, where are we heading today?
Boys, boys, today's stage contains the Disney Dress Shop, Marzaline's Confectionary, and Catall Restaurant.
Good luck, boys.
Okay, thus we have landed at the Disney Dress Shop.
Gentlemen, let's talk dresses.
Yes.
And you, I think you said, because look, I looked around.
You made a point.
You made a point to go and you'll tell us what happened with that.
Yeah.
But other than that, like this is a fun place where you can buy a dress, a Disney inspired dress.
Some not inspired necessarily.
Some aren't inspired.
Some are not as inspired as others is all I'm going to say.
It is an official Disney store that feels like they're trying to make a buck on Disney bounding, which is dressing like in the style of Disney characters, but not wearing a costume, which you cannot do.
And also trying to make a little bit of a buck off the, you know, the mod cloth style of vintage inspired.
A little, yeah, pin up the burlesque isn't the right word, but it's like, it's all there's a retro.
I looked at the mod cloth website and read about the company a little.
I'm like, they started selling actual vintage stuff and then they switched to quote vintage inspired stuff.
You can even shop by debt like 50s, 60s, 70s through now.
I see.
Right.
Yeah.
So all retro flair.
It's all big skirts and collars.
I mean, you know, we're not going to, we're not wearing these.
No.
And I don't think that I think, you know, we probably have a lot of listeners who would wear stuff from this, from this place.
I don't think this would be, I don't think this is Lindsay style.
I don't think this is Aaron's style.
Hmm.
Yeah, probably not.
I think that, yeah, I don't think the bounding specifically, I think you have to be a specific type of fan to be more into it.
I think maybe the style of dress you would wear.
I don't want to speak for her, but I assume the style of dress, but maybe not the Bo Peep jumpsuit and convertible skirt.
Yeah.
I don't think Aaron would wear a dress with every Toy Story character on it.
And it's not knocking if you want.
I'm just saying, yes, I think you're right in regards to that type of thing.
I think the orange bird dress is kind of cute.
I wrote down orange.
I think that one is oddly more like the sort of like the what is that nature of orange bird?
The fact that it's like a little bit of a deeper reference and it could just be some odd pattern.
Yes, it could be kitsch.
It's very it's funny to me because orange bird is a Magic Kingdom specific character specific to one kind of specific to one quick service dessert place.
That also acted as a promotional item for like the Florida orange growers and stuff, but it has taken on a life of his own.
And like I have bought an orange bird button on Main Street in Disneyland.
So it does show up in the or they have orange bird like kitchen stuff or pillows.
I feel like shows up in orange bird merchant stuff.
And that's that's that's all cool.
Embrace of orange bird is cool.
Like the haunted they have this haunted mansion.
I don't know if this is all the same stuff they have in there, but they have this haunted mansion dress.
I feel like that's kind of cool.
Just maybe a bit limited in where you're going to wear it.
Is it the wallpaper?
Yes.
Yeah, I feel like that's it's truly where it's like buying clothes to wear in the parks.
Yeah, I guess it is really sort of for that life.
Yeah.
So in the park, obviously it fits.
But like, yeah, this is a hot more of a Halloween time thing in general.
So you can wear it to like Halloween parties.
I don't know if somebody's probably mad at me and say, you can wear this year round.
We wear like Epcot or country bear shirts.
Yes. And this is also the maybe hypocritical nature of what I'm saying even is because like I'm wearing a Mickey Mouse shirt right now.
And it's like, well, just because I'm not willing to wear his little red shorts, you think you're so much better like that.
So I agree that, oh, please don't start wearing Mickey shorts.
Mickey's little.
In three months, you've justified.
I like them.
I like the Mickey shorts.
Counterpoint, please start wearing Mickey's little red shorts.
You once played Mickey in a comedy show and you did not wear his little red shorts.
And I said, why are you not wearing his little red shorts?
And you like, I didn't even think about it.
Yeah, no.
Do you said little every one of these times?
No, it's a comedy podcast.
Supposedly.
It's really more about rantings and ravings.
But lately, yeah, well, this whole thing.
Yeah, boy.
What we're doing here is a whole different story.
We're going to be ranting and raving on the street by the end of this.
Yeah.
So if you do have the Bo Peep jumpsuit, that's fine.
I have 20 Mickey shirts.
I have so many Mickey shirts.
Bo Peep jumpsuit, that does feel like smart tie in.
Because he's wearing a jumpsuit in the movie kind of thing.
It looks exactly like your costume.
And jumpsuits are in fashion now.
Yeah.
I like, I didn't see this in the store.
I see it on the website, though.
Did they have this hat box ghost satchel?
Ooh.
Because I think this is cool as shit.
I like that a lot.
Well, that's all we should say.
I guess there's other stuff.
There's purses and backpacks and some very expensive items.
It almost feels like it's easier to get away with kind of more novelty accessory
than having the main item be.
Yeah, I don't know if that's just my sort of insecurity or not.
Yeah, but I know what you're saying.
I've actually never been the one to cosplay at.
I've gone to many a convention in my life, but I've never really wanted to cosplay.
But it does feel like I would carry a hat box ghost bag with me.
Sure, yeah.
That's fun.
Maybe it's like, maybe I'm describing an unwillingness to dive into the water.
Maybe just pins and accessories as opposed to just going full tilt.
What clothes relate to the obsession and you own it and you work it?
Yeah, I guess maybe the clothes, if I were to wear the clothes,
it would be reminding me of like I'm trying to pretend I'm still normal,
a normal person with white clothes, like shorts that don't have Mickey's face on it.
I don't own any shorts that have Mickey.
Don't have any shorts with big white buttons.
Not yet.
And on my socks, undergarments, no Disney, any of that.
That's all.
I'm wearing Spider-Man socks as we record.
He's a Disney prince.
Oh my gosh.
Yes, he is again.
Okay.
Yeah, well, and also I think I would feel, you know,
I love the Epcot aesthetic to an extent that's been described as fetishy.
Yeah.
If I was dating someone who wore on their own volition
or insisted on wearing a dress with the spaceship Earth pattern,
I think that might be a little beyond the pale.
I was going to say you'd be very excited, honestly.
I don't know. I think that's a bit much.
I think it would depend on what it looked like, honestly.
I think that dress does exist. That's why I'm saying it.
Right, so you're saying that specific one.
That actually feels like pretty kind of given to me because it is a pattern.
It's like a geodesic pattern.
And I feel like I've seen it like even in non Disney stuff.
But you can't deny that that would be the point where people knowing that I dig Epcot
and then like I show up with some arm candy wearing the spaceship Earth pattern.
That's the point where somebody goes, oh, all right.
I guess I guess if people knew, oh, I see it.
You see, it's interesting because I wonder if people would even know that dress is spaceship Earth.
Unless like if unless they were a nerd, they might show up.
I think it's interesting. This is what you're talking about, right?
Yes, I think so.
Yeah, I don't know. It's subtle enough.
I guess if you frame it in that way that it was like, you know, Scott's spaceship Earth thing has gone a little too far.
Does he want to have sex with the ball?
Yeah, I guess that that framing of it would make sense.
But honestly, if you were just an average Disney fan who wasn't obsessed with the ball
and you had and you were with a lady who had that dress on,
then perhaps it would be fine, honestly.
Now, if I made somebody wear the full a full like cloth ball, if you were no face, Jimmy Stewart and Vertigo sitting in with Kim Novak in front of like the hairdresser
and you were like, oh, make her the ball. You got to make her look like the ball.
More silver and like you were losing your mind.
We go to a hair salon and then it becomes that hair isn't even in the picture.
Yes. Cover the hair, the hair up.
That's why I make it a geodesic sphere.
That foil you put on when you were dying her hair. Put the foil back.
You just go all the way around.
Scott, you just love the ball. You don't love me.
Shut up. Cover her mouth.
Yeah, that would be.
I wish you were full of scenes about the history of communication and later storytelling.
Yeah, that's a that's an issue.
All right, so I'll try to avoid this.
I don't I don't think I will. Now, that being said, look, if we were all being brave, we all should have put on a Disney dress.
That's clearly what we should have done.
I don't think anyone did it. I would have tried. Sure.
Could have been done. Probably would have made for a fun photograph.
Well, I feel like I'm so hard to shop for menswear in general with my proportions, let alone women's wear.
No. So so look, we didn't cover that base.
I did go into the Disney dress shop with my wife, Erin.
Are there things in this store that she could wear and pull off?
Absolutely. Sure.
They even, you know, a dress with Mrs. Potts' face on it is a lot of fun.
I don't think I could see her wearing it on the town.
I just go to go to a movie, go to the art house. But we wanted to pick something that is the thing that she would the least wear.
Right. And I we definitely found it after some consideration.
It is very much the case that Erin would never go out in public dressed fully as Red the Pirate.
Oh, interesting. There's no world in which.
It feels complicated. I thought it was going to be Sally from Nightmare Before Christmas rag dress.
That feels like a lot. Also not up there in Sally.
That that makes the Epcot dress look more subtle.
Like, if you consider that, your other option is pirate dress or rag dress.
Does the pirate dress come with the hat? I don't know if it comes with the hat, but there is a hat.
Right. It might be a separate. I'm sure it's a separate buy, but there's a hat.
And Erin put on the hat. And I think the hat is the point of no return because I have a picture now.
The clothing is certainly something that Erin would not wear.
But there is no universe in which Erin goes out in a three corner hat with a feather on.
And one of her taxation is theft rams.
Now, she does, of course, you know, she'll she'll refer to us all in a hearty way as boys whenever we're together.
But otherwise does not embody the spirit of red.
Come on, boys, to the wine bar.
I'm going to show you a photograph of Erin in red clothing.
I don't think I've ever seen her so humiliated in my life.
The biggest pout that's a tiny hat. Honestly, very small.
That's the problem is the hat is too small. That's the problem.
That's the only problem. Well, wait, I don't know.
I think if you ditch the hat, it just kind of looks like a dress you would wear to a casual wedding.
Like a summer wedding. It is like a corset with a but with a big tie.
It's like a shoelace. I can't really see. I'm looking at it.
I didn't see the corset. It's this thing. Yes, that's correct.
With the kind of like multiple skirts. I think I think also I.
Is there a pose where she tried to be like, see, like she was summoning everybody
like when Red says they want the rum, the men want the rum.
I don't think she had it in her. She didn't want to do.
I think wearing it crushed her spirits. I think the hat 80 did 80 percent of the crushing hat should be.
Here's the red walk around performer. The hat needs to be at least this big.
You're right. She has a big hat because the tiny hat looks funnier.
Honestly. Yeah, no one should wear a tiny hat.
The tiny hat with it. I totally agree. Looks really funny.
If she had the big hat, I don't think I think it would have been worlds better
because the tiny hat makes it look like you're a little doll or something.
The tiny hat. I don't know. It just it looks makes it more precious.
It looks too far to me. You've been you've been trapped by some some like demented
toy maker who's turning people into toys. The Indian in the cupboard or something.
Like it's a doll. You're a little doll. And then you've been frozen.
So I can't make a lot of fashion statements in a sweeping way, but tiny tricorder hats out with tiny figures.
Yeah, for sure. Nature of fashion.
I do feel like, you know, that kind of string tie bodice like does come back into style every now.
Thinking about like red carpet photos or like going out trends of like the early 2000s, late 90s and stuff.
I feel like that does pop up every now and then.
Does it have skulls? Does it have skulls on the bottom? Is that right?
I mean, the skulls. Yeah, that kind of pushes it.
Some skulls and some like black and white drawings of red.
It's also with this one specifically, this does feel like you're going to be maybe it's more appropriate at a Ren Fair.
Certainly, yes. That's what it seems to Ren Fair people.
The line between inspired and costume is very thin, like inspired by that.
I drew my inspiration for my outfit from this and very first this.
I am wearing a costume of this can be very thin.
And I think the Disney dress shop, though it is in that Disney bound area and they aren't costed, they do still feel costumey to me.
And my recommendation to anybody interested in Disney bounding is try doing it on your own because it's going to be cheaper.
It's going to be more creative. You know, do a thrift store run and try to like it because if you can like represent the character with stuff you found
and not just fork over a bunch of money into the Disney dress shop, I think that's more fun and you'll get a more individualistic wardrobe.
That is my yeah, because I do think the Disney bounding thing was a fan created thing and a fan driven thing.
And this is very much feels like the company trying to make money off the fan driven thing compared to like when Mike and I were down there once.
And there was like the dapper days convention.
That's all just like fan or fan affiliated companies selling to other fans like that feels better to me.
That feels like people taking ownership of something. Yeah.
The positive. You don't like the corporate involvement with Disney bounding now that they're sort of making their money on it.
I don't know. I think I think it's kind of yeah, it gets a little dicey because yeah, they're they're jacking up the prices.
Sure, of course. I don't know. I do think it's more fun when yeah, when you piece it together from thrift shop or people sewing their own stuff.
I'm always impressed by that. I have no skill in like clothing creation.
Do you think I'm trying to think of like a Disney bounding thing I would do because I'm looking through it now.
John Stamos wife, who her name is escaping me at the moment is a pretty notable Instagram Disney bounder.
He has Disney bounded as Prince Eric. Have you seen these photos? No, no.
He's just wearing sort of an open white dress shirt and blue pants and a red belt. Yeah.
So is that all right? It looks all right. You wouldn't know exactly what he's doing, but obviously in the context of Disney that they're having fun.
And he's yeah, the shirt is a little, of course, too open for what I would be wearing, but I could see wearing an outfit similar to this and not and being OK.
I don't know that I'm going to do it, but I'm just saying you brought up your chest issue, Jason. I think that's my issue.
I don't think I have the chest to pull off Eric. Yeah, I say I'm not I am not, you know, I'm no I'm no Gaston.
I don't think I could be a Jack. Caitlin is John's wife's name. Caitlin McHugh Stamos.
I think one of the things when I said the corporate kind of co-opting of it is like we've been to Comic Con for we've gone to Comic Con a lot.
Mike and I Mike even more than I have. But like probably in 10 years, the shift of like, hey, fans, check out fan of central.
Like it's like, man, we're just a home for fans. This is where the fans come. This is for real fans. It's all the branding.
And we see Universal Comcast, Shine Heart, Wake Company, you know, we're owned.
We are owned by the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia. So like, do not do your fandom in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia.
But like this is where we get our money from, as opposed to like clubs and like Comic Con was like in the very early days, very DIY and then fan or reader driven.
Yes. And now all these corporations have figured out how to exploit the fan to its fullest by creating the fan community and cultivating it and monetizing it.
And emailing every other day. It's like, hey, it's Legion of Fans and we got the new we got that hot tip on the Jade, Sila, Bob, Reboot, Funko, Pop.
Like when I started high school, it was like I was never that insecure about liking comics or whatever.
But like geek was an insult. And then like after a while, corporations were like geeked.
We've talked, I think we talked about geeked them before. We're going to talk about it. I can't remember.
We were talking about geeked them essentially. And it's like it's a word now that's been branded and it's taken what used to be a slam and now made it into like this thing that they can brand.
And then they can like try to control your fandom. So now it's weird. It's weird how this thing is flipped around.
Yeah. Now we're being sold our own. Yes. So like being way into something was not a thing to be years ago.
It was not cool because corporations couldn't make money on it. And there's a real like they weren't monetizing it.
I feel like there's a very super fit. There's a clip Tom Sharpling always plays on the best show of Chris Hardwick's stand up, which I've definitely summoned an evil god with that phrase.
But like Chris Hardwick sucks. But there's a clip of him going like, I love I'm a nerd. I love comic books. I love sci fi. And like the example he gives, it's like I like Star Wars.
I like the Lord of the Rings movies like, yeah, I like this one billion dollar thing and this other billion dollar thing. And it's like so gross.
Is it where doesn't say where my nerds at where my nerds at least? I think that's the phrase. I mean, it was already already bad.
11 before it was clear he was a creep. But like, Jesus, how dare you speak ill of clip cup cast member Chris Hardwick.
Hey, he was nice then. You had a fun time with him then. Hey, different time. We didn't answer.
You know, I don't think I've thought about this like who would what's what's like a subtle Disney bound we could pull out.
Maybe we have to pose it to the audience. Hey, audience, dress us up. Yeah, what can we do? And I don't even mean like Jokey.
What could we like casually pull off? Yeah, that's because obviously we could all put on Donald Duck sailor suits all day.
Oh, my gosh. Yeah. And do. Yeah. I mean, because like the big the big five goofy.
I mean, I could wear a vest and like a pants pants with a patch on it. But I got a little red shorts.
I have minutes ago. I considered little red shorts. Yeah. Good. So that's on the table.
I'm just trying like what fits with your weights. Well, I don't know who we both wear like floral shirts and I like floral shirt polos.
What about Pete from Goof Troop? Does he does I feel like he wears fun stuff. Let me see yours fun stuff. I could be wrong. Let me see.
I don't want to be Pete. Oh, Pete's the dad. He's just a goofy. He wears like polos.
Oh, no, he wears the he wears like a dress shirt with a tie. I mean, that's an easy honestly.
That's not what I was thinking of. I'm thinking of a different character. Max is easy. Max is like 90s.
This is like Pete. If I was Pete bounding, I would wear like a that's another look I could pull off. I don't exactly look like Pete and I mean, his size.
We should all pull off different Pete's. You. Yeah. Your your steamboat willy Pete. Yeah. Right.
The different looks of Pete over the years. That should be all collection. The Pete collection. Yeah.
Like the John collection we were talking about earlier. Yeah. Yeah. Could I pull off like a casual cosplay of Dr. Nigel Channing?
Oh, that's an interesting audience. Anything with a suit like I feel like could be cobbled together.
I feel like even Dreamfinder, if you if you get these colors. Yeah. There's a bright like shirts tie suit.
Like I feel like you could color block that. You know what you would do?
Well, the Drake Mallard Darkwing Ducks alter ego cosplay, the sweater vest and the dress shirt. Oh, yeah.
You could pull that off. And I think that would no one would bat an eye.
I see this is the kind of thing I like because I don't know that you're going to walk into Disney and even some of your more hardcore fans are going to go Drake Mallard Darkwing Ducks alter ego.
But if you're wearing this, it's like that's my type of costume. I'm I'm I like an obscure thing.
Gadget jumpsuits and style. Gadget from Rescue Rangers. That's a real easy one. That's very easy.
But you'll that's right on the nose. Yeah. Like people will all gadget because you have the goggles. Chip and Dale.
Rescue Rangers. Leather jackets, Hawaiian shirts. Yeah. Dale. Dale would be cool. No pants.
Walking into Disneyland. Hawaiian shirt and no pants.
Well, if you have any ideas for us, let us know. But I you know, I did try on a little I did try on a little something.
I threw on a pink pink sparkly Mickey ears and a pink sparkly Mickey ear.
Probably many year backpack and with a bow. I think I'm working it here. What do you all think? Oh, yeah, sure.
I mean, that's pulling it off. What's the backpack? I can't see that far. Oh, it's you know, it's it's pink and sparkly as a bow on it.
Oh, those back. I like that. They're really I sure is pink, too. What company is that?
Is it Dunion Bork or is it the other one? There's one. It's a it's handwriting.
What does he has a Carly? Weisel had been posting a bunch of they've they've like a line of these tiny backpacks now of like a bunch of different stuff.
Well, I didn't buy them. Let me know if you think I see their present Dunion Bork stuff. Those person are really pricey. Yeah. Yes.
Well, this is one of the stores where Heidi Klum is selling six hundred dollar Minnie Mouse ears.
Oh, you know, with one hundred and fifty sparkling Swarovski crystals. Yes.
Those are it's probably sold out by the time this is coming out.
But as we speak, I believe actually yesterday as we recorded this, she was like at downtown at the Disney dress shop signing these taking photos.
Yeah, I did see that. I'm with another seems like a lot. Yeah, it's more than I wonder if they really had.
How many people went down for that for the Heidi Klum six hundred dollar years?
All the seal stands out there. That's correct. They're not married anymore, though.
Oh, then they went down to yell at her. Yeah, I don't think they're on good terms. I think they have kids. They do have kids.
I seem to know a lot. That's what I got about the Disney dress shop. Great.
Marceline's Confectionary. Confectionary. You know, I'm a fan. You know, I stan.
Yeah, Marceline's Confectionary. It's kind of like the candy restaurants you'd find on Buena Vista Street or Main Street.
Almost exactly the same inventory. Same offerings, same picture windows where you can watch them make stuff.
It's very much more of a minimalist design named after Marceline Mazura, where Walt lived as a young child.
That's what they say there. Yeah. They say Mazura. I like it.
I'm a big fan of the chocolate covered peanut butter graham cracker. They used to call it a peanut butter sandwich.
I don't know what they still sell that as. I've had that. That is very delicious.
I like to get the goofy sour balls as a gift or a big hit.
I haven't had the goofy sour balls in years, but I do love a goofy sour ball. Delicious.
I think I've talked before my favorite candy. And if anyone remembers this, they used to sell plastic containers with the characters' faces on it full of tartan tinies,
which were some of my favorite candies. And they would have sour balls in those containers. They'd have tartan tinies.
Both fantastic candies, but they don't carry tartan tinies anymore. Another company is making them. That's a whole nother podcast.
You did find tartan tinies. Yes, very excited. And had a conversation with a candy store proprietor.
Yes, he's worked at that candy store, owned that for like 25 years. And he's like, oh yeah, and he's like, why yes, we have tartan tinies, of course, as high as the eye can see.
He sang a song too about it. He was very happy. My tartan tiny kingdom.
I was like grabbing hands with him and circling the candy shop. Very small. It's very narrow. So you're knocking a lot of shit over.
You're the chosen one, Michael. It was always you.
I went to the tartan tiny factory after that. And OK, so.
Marcelines. Yeah, great. You know what I like? When we were there the other day, they have take a number like a deli counter right at the entrance.
Like, yes, it is very efficient. I don't think it's really in the theme style of the either Main Street or Buena Vista Street.
But you can. It doesn't matter at downtown Disney. They want to get people in and out and on their way.
Yeah, I had I had a thought and then I realized I was wrong to think it.
And I have a similar thought about the world of Disney. At first, I was like, it's kind of a bummer to me that all this stuff is available outside of the park.
Because in some ways you're like, oh, the special treats are for in the park.
And there's feeling of like you're on the main street and you're watching the candy apples.
But then I realized the park is so goddamn expensive that if you want to go and have some Disney magic and your Disney magic is buying a nine dollar candy apple with that looks like winning the poo, then that's nice that you can get it down to Disney.
So I made a reversal. At first, I was going to say like, it's kind of it's I wish the treats were specific to inside, but I was wrong thinking that.
And I'm glad that this exists here. Sure. And plus, if you're staying at the hotels and you change your mind, it's like, I think I want to go back for that.
Like, it's a lot easier to just go downstairs or down the street to downtown Disney and grab something.
But yeah, it's exactly the same, almost exactly the same treats you can get.
There's a shortbread cookie drizzled with a rainbow whatever it is. Fun frosting. Great. I've had it twice.
There's a type in the park. I ate a tiger tail and turn it. It was a Cheshire cat's tail and I ate it. There's marshmallow inside and I ate it. Yeah.
That's good. Yeah, they have that at Marceline's or version of it. That sounds good. Yeah, that's pretty good.
It's like a cookie ish on the outside and the marshmallow inside. Very love that. And then this is a great place. I buy a lot of, you know, holiday.
I buy coffee for the family or you buy. I've done that. Yeah. You buy. There's a tea set and everyone likes that and it's pretty good.
And yeah, Marceline's good. That's what I'll say. Good. Catal? Catal. I think you have the most experience with Catal of all of us.
Well, I've been there twice. Yeah, I think that's about right. I've had some drinks around there.
I've been to Uva a lot more than Catal. They're related, but it's confusing because what is this maybe where I think this is the official beginning of in.
I've been talking about these unused district names. Yes. And this is the beginning of apparently the wine bar district.
So now we're talking. But I go to Uva a lot more than Catal. We have, of course, separated them into different levels.
They're making things as complicated as possible, but they are pretty separate organisms, even though you go to the outdoor Uva bar and it all comes from the indoor kitchen at Catal.
I've only been to Catal twice. I think my general feeling is you're going to get the vibe. You're going to get the it's all seems good.
It's good food. But if you want, you know, drinks and Mediterranean tinged food, but you need to put a little speed on it.
Who was your place? Catal is probably a great place to sit down. I've enjoyed the meals I've had there, but I don't think I'm ever if you're in the mood for a sit down nice dinner at Disney, probably you're going to do Napa Rose or or obviously Carthay.
If you can get a steak, I think I think it's maybe trouble because it falls into the nether region of is it it's like pretty good food, but you can get better food very close. Right.
It does have some very specific food. Like I am like if I wasn't so tired last night, I was like, I wish I kind of want to go to Catal because they have a paella menu.
Okay, they have maple leaf duck, which I love duck. Wow. And then they have suckling pig and I'm like, and they even have paella with suckling pig.
And I'm like, I gotta eat at Catal. I gotta go to Catal. Paella with suckling pig doesn't make it down there before the end of the saga and update us. Yeah. I think you need to get some suckling pig before this is all said and done.
We can do addendums. Sector Keepers not here. Rules are off. All bets are off. So we'll come back to it. We're still pretty early in the saga. So I would like to take a minute to get some logistical. Sorry, the ordeal.
And it's levels and stages. Yeah, it's early, but it's getting to me. Hashtag Sector Keeper cricket wireless severance. So just some logistical advice for the listener.
Catal is one of the restaurants that you can validate five hours of downtown Disney Parking. Thank God.
Bray a bakery cafe, Naples, restaurante bar, Ralph Brennan's jazz kitchen, splitsville luxury lades and tortilla.
Joe's. Why go to a website when we could read the website to read it?
Catal also one of the restaurants that if you're staying at one of the Disney hotels, you have access to preferred dining reservations, which not just dining includes preferred reservations at the Bibbidi Boppidi boutique.
Blue Bayou Carthay Circle restaurant, Catal Goofy's kitchen, L'Oreal bakery, close in the alphabet, get to the Z's, Naples, restaurante, E bar, Plaza, every place, Ralph Brennan's jazz kitchen, tortilla.
They set aside some reservations if you are a hotel guest so that you, you know, it's a little make me wait like a second class citizen.
Look this. Yeah, there's a class system. It's classes. You get a case of the it's a perk. It's a perk.
You got to say get a case of the hungries. Get a case of the hungries.
I heard what you were going for. In case of the yummies. Case of the yummies. Very helpful if I have stayed at a hotel and unknowingly the next day there was a run Disney event and everything is a madhouse.
Did you accidentally get swept up in a run Disney mob? A group of people running? No thankfully because that's all at like four, four to six a.m. and the more it's crazy.
Which of us would be the, none of us wanted to run Disney. No, no. I could do a 5k.
Whoa really? It's only a few miles. Said confidently. I don't think I'd finish fast. We've got to volunteer. I think I'd do some speed walking for that.
We need someone to review a run Disney. We haven't done that on the podcast yet so I think you just sign yourself up. And there's run Universal too.
You can run all the parks. The Minion, it's a Minion run. Run Dollywood. I'm not much of a run. I'm more of like a walker.
Well wait a minute. You got to run a little bit. That's the whole thing. I'll run a little bit but you got to pace yourself. So you're going to walk Disney?
Why not? I don't think they put a cap on you. They don't. They're not going to come by and tell you. In fact there's all these photo stops anyway so I don't think you're really.
It sounds like you're going to walk the race track and then take photos. I'm going to briskly walk. The distance is. Alright you can still, we'll still send you.
You stepped way down from the initial confidence from a confident run to a briskly walk. I think I could get up to speed in a month to like. To walk?
No to get a little pep in my step to jog. To briskly walk. You have to prepare. For 5k. 5k or what? Right? There's different length tracks.
I'm sure there is. It just sounds like you don't need like a ton of physical fitness to do what you're describing. I don't think you do because it's like photo stops every few.
Probably accurate. Yeah. I think it's customizable. If you want to do a full marathon or half marathon. If you want to go for speed. But I think if they're like if you just want to come and like speed walk a little and then take a picture with the Cinderella, the mice.
Alright. You are welcome to. That's good. Alright well we'll send you. That's my cosplay. I'm Jacques. Jacques the mouse. Oh yeah.
I haven't worn a lot of cloth. Like kind of floppy hats in my day. Now's the time to start. Yeah. So take that anyway long and short. Know that parking advice. Know that preferred reservation advice. If you're going to visit downtown Disney.
And hey if you're really getting that five hours pop in the parks for a little bit. They can't find you. If you have an annual pass. What a bad boy.
Now I don't have a lot to say. I'm sure you would go to this place and have a nice restaurant and I think there's some seats where you can see the fireworks and I'm just more more of a fan of uva than Katal and especially let me look we had some rough stuff with the patina restaurant group a little while ago.
Yeah. So yeah. Another patina. It's yeah with what we've lived through. I don't know how much I want to push a business into them. But the Gambino family.
I mean, I'm not going to say the patina restaurant group. Our first boss. I was so rattled. But so but there is an event. I was like there's this thing like a lot to talk about is just because all seems nice and good probably and there's nothing. Is it an opening day restaurant? I think it is. Yeah.
The font would suggest that. Sure. That's a good point. I was saying that's like the like we when surveying everything like do we talk about this already that the Katal and uva bar font is one of the it's one of the most the biggest signs of 2001 of like sloppy shitty 2001.
Because there now are some cool aesthetics throughout Dandead. Different fonts on the vertical side than the horizontal side. A very 2001 move. The new Naples layout and stuff like that's like it doesn't fit next to this and some of the other new signs for sure.
It should all be that craftsman stage should all fit in with the with the Grand California hotel which is what Jason was saying. Yes. Or if you have to do something take the world of Disney telescope and the nephews and put them on top of the Katal restaurant.
At least do that. If you're going to make it gaudy like this at least have a giant gaudy telescope with the duck nephews go all the way. That's neither here nor there. He's so crazy. They built this whole district. Beautiful craftsman building behind it made a quarter of it.
Look in that style. Just extend the craftsman the whole way. Yeah. I think we'd probably be coming in a lot more like that's nice. That's nice. If everything was craftsman style because it's never really gone out of style. The way that they blew up Disney Springs and just gave it all the same style which is a cool actually thought through new style.
Yeah. Disney downtown Disney is a mishmash and I do no matter how good a restaurant Katal is the bits that that font is what you see. Yes. Face in the public gross. Are they doing a piecemeal though in downtown Disney because they can issue like they have a lot more structural control in Disney Springs where like well we can blow it all up at once.
Downtown Disney had to deal with the city of Anaheim. Perhaps that but also I wonder if the patina group is I wonder if they're figuring out if they're going to keep it this restaurant because stuff still closing stuff has been closing at a pretty decent clip. We're going to be at the 20 year mark.
We're going to be at the 20 year mark so I wonder if they're still I'm just wondering if they're figuring out like we'll put a new concept in or will we just re update everything that's going on here. It feels like with the redo of Naples though patina is at least leaving one foot in downtown Disney. Right.
Well I don't think they would redo a whole restaurant and go like anyway we're out of here. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. But I wonder like there's no other Katal restaurant right. This is the only Katal restaurant. No no no there's a ton of patina restaurants but they all seem different.
So maybe yeah patina has a new concept they want to try out. Could still be. So there's a possibility. There's a the imagination imagination of Joaquin Splashall knows no bounds. Yes I mean we all wait for Joaquin Splashall for his next concept and there will be a smoke signal from his apartment window and then we will know.
And then maybe Joaquin has an idea. Maybe Joaquin will just say you know make the font Papyrus. He'll just say that it will be Katal still but now it'll be Papyrus font not whatever this is. Only one way to make it worse if there was some font that merged Papyrus and Comic Sans into a new. Maybe he's trying to invent a new font.
Oh we don't get that. He's a font for the Avatar sequels. And the way that everyone was like oh you know once upon a time in Hollywood Tarantino clearly poking fun at his reputation for the foot stuff there's so much of it.
If James Cameron dug down of like oh you made fun of my Papyrus. Well what if I. Ha ha. James can't visionary filmmaker James Cameron is working with visionary chef Joaquin Splashall to craft an all new font that will define the 21st century and designer free agent Johnny I.
So but then all right so none of this is that fascinating with Katal and we're being mean about the font. But I'm going to go out on a positive note with something I don't I feel like it would come up by now if you guys had found it and I'm delighted to break it to you.
Okay. You know that every year at a Katal restaurant there is an event called Breakfast with Santa. No. Everyone's dream to have breakfast with Santa Claus. I definitely sure you sit on his lap. Like you would have milk and cookies with them but breakfast one day a year.
It is one I don't know it could be a recurring over a month and you sign up for times of it. I'm looking at some website now. Let me say go on sale in July. Whoa. Wow. I for all you know what they said is that there's a Christmas in July discount.
So you have a foresight to book right. We did not this year. So we're gonna have to wait with the masses to get have our cherished breakfast with Santa. Let me tell you what happens at breakfast with Santa. Adults are welcome to sip on bottomless mimosas.
I'm in while little ones are treated to a cookies little ones or grown podcasters are treated to a cookies and milk station and steaming cups of hot chocolate from the cocoa carts hot cocoa cart it says you got it hot cocoa.
So living polar express after they share their Christmas wishes with Santa he will gift every child with a stuffed animal and a personalized stocking Wow guest been make reservation today to enjoy this beloved Yuletide tradition that is sure to put a smile on every child's face and make memories of a last a lifetime.
I want to come out with the big papaya pan like that's what I want him to come as did someone order papaya with suckling pig. I think I know I think there's a little older boy.
I have something for you. I hear you've been very good this year I any many good podcast episodes is there what would you like perhaps something suckling yes that's right.
What a big new with some spice rice with saffron I don't know if you've been that good. Where's the little boy who enjoys duck. Which one of you is here blitz and get out here.
Stab your antlers into that tray and bring this boy some suckling big forthwith.
We've got to go to see Santa then we have to it looks like it's like the 7th of December through the 23rd 24th. Oh it's all month long. Yeah so it's at least three weeks.
Wow I didn't know I knew I it's interesting because you find different stuff like I didn't know up until a couple years that they did Thanksgiving every year at the Disneyland Hotel which we did which we really enjoyed so they do have these little weird holiday celebrations in different spots.
And we did we did Easter at storytellers which I was hoping was going to be this fun thing where everyone was dressed up adequately in Easter clothes like all the characters that is and they were just wearing their safari gear like it was a normal buffet.
But no bonnets I wanted bonnets I wanted like Easter suits your Easter finery Easter finery yes but it was Thanksgiving we were Thanksgiving and the characters were dressed up in some different mini header apron because she's making the food we were all eating. Yeah it was fantastic.
And he cooked for you she cooked yes the country bears of course they were in the regular yes that's the cousins from the old from the holler you know they're just coming they're bringing some shine and yeah they're they're music they're beautiful music they dressed up in their fancy clothes then they wouldn't be being themselves right.
I guess Henry has a dickie and tie a top hat he is the master of ceremonies. Yeah that's true also a good cosplay potentially or not a cosplay but a Disney bound a country bear Disney bound is maybe your best bet. Yeah that's a vest a lot of vests.
But not a tiny teddy bear that no that would be a big one yeah full bonnet yes. Sun bonnet like the sun bonnet trio I guess the answer is that we all need some bonnet trio bonnets. Yeah not currently available at the Disney dress shop and those country bears are going away a lot in a lot of places and I'm worried they're going away in Florida so this is going to be there we're not going to see any of this in the Disney dress shop we're not going to see I feel maybe in Japan because they're very popular there still.
Yeah so we'll get our bonnet to Japan. Well did we make it. I think we got it. I think oh my god I think we survived level two stage two and oh my god it's materializing there's there's the sector keepers item that he's given us to put in the inventory oh my god it's a pink sparkly backpack filled with suckling pig.
Hey me. So if we need to take it on the girl something for Scott something for Jason. I'll wait I'll put it over one shoulder and you can just eat straight out of it. Follow closely behind me. You didn't have to tell him twice. Suckle that suckling pig.
Suckling pig out of a backpack. That's like two items in one so I think thank you sector keeper thanks so much and we will repay you by finding that level keeper and and saving him so everybody listening make sure you use you survived Pugget's Red Dent in a Disney or deal hashtag DDO hashtag save the level keeper and keep following us on Twitter Facebook Instagram and for three days.
Bonus episodes a month go to Patreon.com slash podcast the ride back for day six tomorrow. Are we excited about day six. Oh yes. Well it's another day so we got to know we need some suckling pig strength.
We gots but hey there's you know this this fun snacks coming up and maybe some relaxing footwear. Great. So join us tomorrow. Bye.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson Jason Sheridan Scott Gardner Brett Boam Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey for more original podcast please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.