Forever.
Dog.
Live from the Lyric Hyperion in Los Angeles, California.
It's an intimate Christmas evening with podcast, The Ride.
Featuring appearances by Regis Philbin, Michael Eisner,
Danny Thomas, Marlo Thomas, Eric Roberts,
Ice Skater Scott Hamilton, Roddy McDowell, Mickey Mouse,
Chuck E. Cheese, and hopefully not for some reason, Chucko.
We take you now to Jason Sheridan's Gingerbread Cottage
in the Forest, where old man Jason is settling in
for a long winter's nap.
Really coming down out there.
Darn kids trying to eat my house.
I built it deep in the woods for a reason, for me to eat.
Now I can enjoy my holiday in solitude,
reading and studying.
Oh yes, what a time it will be,
eating gingerbread doorknobs and gingerbread hinges
all by my lonesome.
Oh, who could that be?
Come in.
Hi there, hi.
Oh hi.
Hello.
Hi.
Oh boy.
Really coming down out there.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
I'm really sorry to bother you.
Are you the new neighbor?
Well, it's been a long time since I've been the new anything.
Very, very, very good.
Listen, you seem like a nice man.
I don't want to bother you.
Let me just explain.
My name's Scott.
I'm the theme park podcaster from Up the Road.
Oh.
Well say I'm a theme park podcaster as well.
No kidding.
Really, really.
You get into some of the newer stuff?
Oh sure.
I think it's marvelous.
Some of it's real fine.
Real fine.
Wonderful.
Geez.
Well, you seem like a very kindhearted man.
I was wondering if you could help me
with my little predicament.
You see, what with the blizzard and all,
my power went out.
And I've got a sack full of theme park related
holiday clips.
And no one to share them with.
Well, that's an unfortunate predicament,
but sadly I can't help you.
No?
Really?
I came all this way.
All the way down the block.
I've got a lot of gingerbread house to eat by New Year's.
Interesting.
Well then I guess I'll also have no one
with whom to share these Tate's double chocolate chip
cookies.
Why don't you take a seat?
Pull up a chair.
Oh.
Change your mind.
Lovely.
Thank you so much, sir.
I'm sorry, kids.
Kids, I'm so sorry.
I'm just gonna,
it doesn't look like we're gonna have a house
to spend the holidays at this year.
Sorry, hold on.
Hold on one second.
I went into such credit card debt turning.
Shut the fuck up out there.
But the credit cards offered such lucrative rewards.
I spent us into a hole, kids.
I'm so sorry.
I don't think there's gonna be any sort of festivities
this year.
Oh no.
Well, if you're gonna make a fuss about it,
just come on in.
What's that?
Oh, thank you kindly old sir.
Oh.
Thank you.
The age, the wisdom you have in your eyes.
Thank you very much.
Is it okay if I bring my kids?
Up to you, your house.
Fine.
Okay, hold on one second.
I don't wanna knock anything over.
All right.
Well, it's hard to stay mad at a whole community
of characters who come with fully customizable outfits.
How many months is the bird?
He's a mailman.
Oh, so quite old then if he has a profession.
Yes, I'd like to introduce you to Duffy,
his non-sexual life partner, Shelly May.
You sure about that?
You're totally sure about that?
I'm totally sure.
So it's a Jay and Silent Bob sort of relationship?
No, it is not Jay and Silent Bob.
Two body, I think.
Two body, their love is wholesome and pure.
Fair enough.
Their love is a perfect love.
And of course-
The Christmas spirit said that.
This is a gelatoni and he does one thing.
He fucks.
Oh, how rude of me gentlemen.
This is my audience of 85 people
plus 10 give or take friends and family.
Oh sure, oh wow.
That's an unusual feature for a cabin, oh my.
Well, you know what, in addition to all the clips in my sack,
I do have some things that I could potentially share
with some of the audience.
If that's something, they'd be-
Sure.
Before I say what the thing is,
let me just see if I can get a reaction out of it.
Is anybody a particularly big Knott's Berry Farm fan?
Woo!
I should have known if I asked that to this crowd,
it would be a tie of 85.
Who traveled from the furthest?
This is an LA show, but-
I'm in the-
What?
Oh hi, wait, we met you.
Oh hi, what's going on?
Well, you know what, then to-
We gotta give you a-
Wait, let me ask a question.
Have you been to Knott's Berry Farm?
I wasn't really-
Once is fine!
Yeah!
Yay!
That works then, and it's perfect,
because what we have, this is actually Christmas related.
This is a Christmas ornament
from Knott's now closed iron reef
VR attraction.
Yeah, here, let me go ahead and answer this to you.
You know, I'd like to get in on this gift-giving fun,
because I-
Yes.
Cleaned out some garbage from my gingerbread house.
It's just your thing?
While we're on Knott's Berry Farm,
any other Knott's Berry Farm fans here?
Who thinks they've been the most?
Oh.
Not a great-
I see a hand.
Oh, you work there!
That's going a lot.
Says the person in the tiny Fuppet shirt.
What?
Calico River Rapids Poncho.
Yeah.
Take that.
Was that, wait, wait, was that worn by you at the press night?
Yes, it was.
Why didn't, wait, hold on,
why didn't you throw that away like Scott and I did?
You never know what'll come in handy.
And that's why it also comes with this hand towel from Club 33.
Oh!
Wow.
Any more garbage?
You do have more garbage.
Yeah, I got a few rounds of garbage.
Okay, this is, they send you Comic-Con badges
in these cute little boxes now.
And this is a pack of absolute carnage, temporary tattoos.
What?
We are now completely off of the theme.
This one's got Jack Ryan on the inside.
Who wants the tchotchke box?
That, she's enthusiastic there, I think.
This also comes with a Club 33 hand towel.
Oh, yeah, I think so.
Most Jack Ryan enthusiasm ever produced by anyone.
Okay, this is another year Comic-Con box.
What?
What the hell is this?
Are there any Brooklyn Nine-Nine fans?
Okay, this comes with a very tiny pin.
Seems like less, huh?
Go, oh, an Ifca man, all right, you get this.
Oh.
Hey, Jason, do you have any loose leaf
notebook paper for them?
Yes, I do.
Here's your box and your Club 33 hand towel.
These are my handwritten notes from being forced
to watch the Haunted Mansion movie.
And a Club 33 hand towel.
This was the first hand I saw.
And this is the last thing to wrap up
this interminable bit.
Okay, this is a shirt I have, but T-Public
sent me the wrong one so that I got the right one.
And they told me to keep it.
This is the five original X-Men
and the Helvetica ampersand kind of thing.
Does anyone like the X-Men and wear a medium?
There, there in the front.
Maybe, here's your shirt and your Club 33 hand towel.
Wow.
Wonderful, a little like surprise secret Santa
for all of our friends for this holiday gathering.
You know, I know we all just met, but also we were just
talking about how there's a special gift
for a special someone in the audience.
Do you want to pull people in on that?
Oh, sure, I mean, I think we have actually
a special representative here from a company
that we all have a lot of affection for.
Excuse me, Anthony Gio, is he around?
Woo!
Oh, there he is.
Wow, wow, through the gingerbread door, good to see ya.
I wasn't sure if that was the door or the chimney.
So yeah, I hear you actually have a new job.
Yes, so I'm happy to announce I'm the new brand manager
for Skull Chewing Tobacco.
Great, great, great.
And I have a little secret Santa gift here
so I'm not only here spreading good tidings and cheer,
I'm here to pack a mean lip as this.
Pack a mean lip.
And so on behalf of Skull, Skull,
a pinch better since 1934, I would like to honor
and reward this to Skull's Dipper of the Year 2019,
Mr. Nick Mundy.
Yeah!
That's it!
And just for social media, for social media,
we have to take a picture.
No, no, bullshit.
It's not yours, you don't do it.
Yeah, sir, do you mind?
Thank you so much.
He's gotta pack the lip before we take the photo.
Sure.
Not enough time, not enough time.
It's important for the audience to know that...
Anyone have another bottle?
Or like a tin can?
If any theater management can get Nick Mundy a dip cup,
if not, it's going everywhere.
For the key work.
You drinking that coffee?
That man is drinking that coffee.
For the audience at home, Nick's wife is thrilled right now.
Dipper of the Year, any thoughts upon getting this reward?
About goddamn time.
And for the tight end of the holidays, it is winter green.
Happy holidays, sir.
Nick Mundy.
And from Skull Magazine, Anthony Geo.
Good to see you.
Thanks for swinging by.
We should have you on the show more often.
All right.
Okay, so with those gifts being given,
the main gift now to give out is this sack full of clips.
Let me just, I'll just like rattle them.
Like the spirit of them will go up to the booth.
Here we go.
Okay, and I see them.
The bits and bytes traveling up.
Let's have a seat, gentlemen.
Let's settle in.
Oh, boy.
Duffy, oh, careful.
Oh yeah, sorry.
Is this seat taken?
Lightning McQueen man, huh?
My son is allowed to dress how he wants.
Hey, Scott here.
From this point on,
we're gonna be showing a bunch of Christmas clips.
So if you aren't sure what's happening visually,
or you just wanna follow along with us,
we'll be posting all of the clips to our Twitter
at podcast the ride and using the hashtag PTR sack-o-clips.
That's hashtag PTR sack-o-clips.
So we'll be posting all the stuff there.
Go check it out.
Yeah, well, hey, thanks so much everybody for coming out.
You know, we did an episode a couple years ago.
It was called the Christmas Special Christmas Special,
where we dug into the vast archive of strange,
inane Disney theme park specials.
And we wanted to dig deeper, you know,
find, you know, worse muck and scum,
aligning the walls of the Disney vault.
The stuff they're not brave enough to put on Disney Plus.
But we're happy to put on display for you here.
Sound good, everybody excited?
Wonderful.
Nice way to spend the holidays.
You know, he got a big shout when we were introducing folks
at the beginning, you know, it wouldn't be a true
Disney Christmas Special without an introduction
from a very special person, and that's Michael Eisner.
Yeah!
You know, Michael Eisner did a number of great holiday intros.
There's a lot to choose from, but there was this one
that I especially enjoyed, and I think all you need
to know about it is that it's in service of a lot of people
and that it's a special event is about ice skating.
That's all I need to say.
At tonight's Christmas show, we celebrate the holiday season
with some of your favorite Olympic ice skating stars.
Well, Michael Eisner and the Walt Disney Company.
During the holiday season here in Southern California,
we don't get much ice or snow.
So instead of ice skating, we're rollerblading.
It's a great way to get around the lot
here at the Disney Studio.
Gee, Michael, can you rollerblade?
Well, Mickey, just a little.
Could you show us?
Well.
The list card, homie, took out a red hat.
And sunglasses.
What a dink.
Okay.
Bye.
Bye, mom.
Be careful, Michael.
Yeah.
Gee, Minnie, homie got the...
He skated away.
Oh, oh, did we see that?
Ah!
Jump, spin.
Not the spin.
Spin.
Oh!
Gosh, that was pretty good for an old guy.
Oh, Michael, you were great.
You know Minnie, I'm a little out of practice.
Yeah, sure.
Enjoy tonight's show.
How about that?
Woo!
You know, I know the glasses and the hat
were to cover the stunt, you know, switcheroo.
But in the 90s, that glasses and hat combo communicated,
I am the Unibomber.
I am the police sketch of the Unibomber.
Wasn't the Unibomber, didn't he wear a hood over his head?
Didn't he have like a hoodie?
I guess he had the hood.
You're thinking of a different guy.
A different bomber.
I'm thinking of that drawing in those spam ads
where it's like thousands of people
dream this man every night.
Yeah, yeah, that's it.
That guy.
I mean, we all, we dream Eisner every night, certainly.
I think everyone here does.
The rest of that special I scoured for anything worth
showing to you guys.
And the, there's, it's not really worth sitting to,
this far too much Bronson Pinchot for my taste.
But this clip kind of, I think,
tells you everything you need to know.
Here, I got it.
Okay.
Here we go.
["The Unibomber"]
Donald and Pluto finally had the last point
of the magic snowflake.
The end.
For,
for the listener at home,
ice skater,
Scott Hamilton, joined by saxophonist, Tom Scott.
And that's how lame my music taste is
that I know who the saxophone player was in this thing.
Do you know what else he's played on?
I mean, and a lot of good solo stuff.
He was in the, you know, the 70s SNL band here and there.
He was Chevy Chase's band leader on the Chevy Chase show.
The greatest talk show of all time.
They weren't brave enough to keep it on
longer than six weeks.
So, Scott Hamilton ice skates up to Tom Scott
and blows magic out of his hand.
And then, you know, there was a laugh from the audience.
And so in case you couldn't hear it,
then Bronson Pinchot narrates,
and so Donald and Pluto had the last part
of the magic snowflake.
The end.
That wrapped up nicely.
I spared you all the other parts of the magic snowflake,
which were all attained via excellent ice skating.
So what does the magic snowflake do?
Well, I think Bronson Pinchot's niece
throws it up in the air, who's never experienced winter,
and then it magically snows at Disneyland.
Oh, okay.
The thing that it does, like, every night
during the holidays?
Yes, but this time for real.
It's real, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, for real.
Also in that special, Bronson Pinchot plays Jack Frost
in almost the same way that Martin Short did it later
in Santa Claus 3.
So if you're a fan of that and want to see
essentially the same makeup,
it's another place you could see it.
There you go.
So, you know, a Disney special,
the Disney Christmas parades,
Eisner set up the pins,
and then Regis Philbin knocked him down.
He was the king of these specials.
You know, so much broadcast skill and panache.
And let me make that especially evident with this clip.
This is from the 2002 Disney Christmas parade.
He is finishing talking to Eric Roberts,
who I guess was on some show at the time.
And he's introducing a musical performer.
And just from Regis and Kelly's description,
see if you just internally can guess
who the musical guest is.
And if I had more prizes, I'd give them to you
if you did figure it out.
Here we go.
Why don't you guys stick around for our next performance?
Yeah, he is a big rock star.
That's right, singer, performer, songwriter.
Yes, he's got the scratchy voice,
you know, the white teeth, got the whole thing.
You know who we're talking about.
John Resnick of the Goo Goo Dolls.
Sure.
He's here to make us sing his hit song
from Disney's Treasure Planet.
It's called I'm Still Here.
And then a little, here's a little taste.
This came up on the show recently.
Yes. Like you're a fan, I believe.
What is this song called again, Mike?
I'm Still Here, John's name?
Jim's theme.
All right, I'm so sorry.
I have seen the Goo Goo Dolls in concert twice.
Has anyone seen them more?
But twice.
Two, two?
Two, everyone two?
We've hit a stalemate on Goo Goo Dolls' concerts.
I saw them at the Hard Rock in Orlando.
Your personal bizarre concert series.
Pretty good.
Oh, we saw, Kate, my sister is right here.
We saw them, right?
Hello, my sister.
That's my sister, Kate.
Hey, hello, hello.
She didn't get any of the prizes.
Nope.
There'll be a big gift coming at Christmas, I'm sure.
Oh, sure.
And the gift of hanging out with your family.
The most precious things in the world to me.
We do another little Regis moment here.
This one's a lot of fun.
There was a bit on a lot of these specials
where Regis would get a little preview
of some of the upcoming attractions for the year
and future projects.
And so he would, he'd get a little behind the scenes taste
but then things would go a little bit awry.
This happened every year and this I think was the peak.
I think they might've stopped doing that after this year
because how do you top this one?
1993 or four, I believe.
I'm here at Disney's Future Projects Center
for a sneak preview look at an exciting new attraction
that's gonna be opening up in the coming year.
Come on in.
This must be the model.
Let's check it out.
Come on.
See, it looks a little scary, doesn't it?
Almost looks like a real thing.
The listener does an elevator door.
I wonder if these doors open.
They do.
What do you think, should I go inside?
I'll try.
Yeah, why not?
Oh yeah.
Ma, Ma!
Hey, what's happening here?
What's going on?
Holy mackerel, look at me.
I'm black and white.
Next stop, the Twilight Zone.
I don't like this.
The doors have opened.
He's screaming.
Full view of Disney Entertainment Studios.
Drop.
Listen, listen, listen to this.
I'm out of control.
What happened to him?
For the listener, he's one quarter his height.
Next year, you do the new projects update.
Right now, I got a whole lot of suits to alter.
And that's how Kelly Ripa got rid of Regis
and replaced him with Michael Strahan.
Sure.
She threw him into a broken elevator.
If I let him take the elevator too early,
an elevator surely would shrink you to one quarter
your usual height and make your voice be pitched up
four times its usual.
It would make your voice a lot cuter.
Oh yeah, a little Regis elf there.
Kind of adorable.
Now wonder they stopped doing it after this year.
They scarred Regis.
They like maimed him.
And he says the line, I'm out of control,
which is the Dana Carvey impression of him,
something he didn't actually say.
So they were like, say the line that you don't say.
Yeah.
Much like George W. Bush's beloved catchphrase,
strategic, not his own.
Right.
And not going to do it.
George H.W. Bush.
I'm not sure he ever said that.
Yeah.
All equally beloved figures.
Just nice men all around.
According to Ellen, yes.
Yeah, they're both pieces of shit.
That's right.
Strategic was also the name of George W. Bush's podcast.
Right?
What?
Was there a George W. Bush library podcast?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Was it called strategic?
Sound familiar to anybody?
The audience usually has Jason's back
on these kinds of things.
But there is befuddled.
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
But there is befuddled this guy.
That's just general support.
He just likes Jason.
And it means the world.
We'll figure that out.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll find the George Bush podcast.
It's strategic.
Oh, it's strategic.
That's what it's called.
Lindsay K. Tai is in the house.
Lindsay K. Tai.
The author.
The author of Jelatoni Fux.
Did you say that first?
I think you may have invented Jelatoni Fux.
Wow.
Yeah.
So she should hand for that.
It's going to be so many people's senior yearbook quote.
The rest of the time.
K-A-S, Jelatoni Fux.
Have a K-A-S.
Jelatoni Fux.
Let me see here.
I think elsewhere on the Regis front.
Let me see if I got this one.
Oh yeah, here we go.
For one year, and only for one year,
and we might see why from this quick cut down,
Regis was joined by his usual co-host,
not Kelly Ripa, but her predecessor.
And I'll show you this.
You know her face and love her voice.
Today it's Kathie Lee Gifford with a special holiday number.
Let's see what's happening elsewhere
in this fabulous resort.
First, someone that I think you know.
No, she's not here.
Kathie Lee Gifford.
She's everywhere.
With a couple hundred Christmas fans
at the Disney MGM Studios.
Merry Christmas, Kathie Lee.
Hi Regis, hi Joan.
Regis, you just can't get rid of me, can you?
Merry Christmas and happy holidays to everybody.
We are having a fabulous time here
at the Disney MGM Studios.
Yay!
Hi everybody.
Oh, they're so thrilled I'm here.
This is what the interior of a busy soundstage
really looks like.
And as you can see, the crew's really busy
getting ready for my big Christmas number.
I'm gonna sing my brains out.
I'll spare you the actual number, but I'm sorry.
You don't have it, do you?
I don't have it, no.
The booing does nothing.
Could you?
Could you sing?
Do you remember it?
I think it's walking in a winter wonderland,
is what it is.
But imagine it being sung,
imagine her singing her brains out on it.
So you gotta kinda astral project that.
I agree with Monday.
Oh no, now we've opened up,
now we got a peanut gallery.
He's all scolled up over there.
Ready to fight.
Scott, can I play a clip?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You wanna go to yours?
Yeah, yeah.
So, we love these clips,
but we do need to acknowledge these are from the past.
Long ago.
And as the young person correspondent,
I had to see what's Disney up to in 2019.
Now I want you to remember,
this is happening in 2019.
This happened mere weeks ago.
And this clip, this is a little longer,
so bear with me, I'll narrate some of it.
This is like a magic trick.
It's got three parts.
It's got the pledge and the turn and the prestige.
And again, I do need to reiterate, this is 2019.
So as you can imagine.
The goo goo dolls.
Only the hippest, coolest influencers are in this.
Scared grumble from the crowd.
Yeah, that's Sting.
Sting.
This rocks.
Of course he's gonna sing a current Christmas tune
or something, right?
He's gonna sing something very modern.
No.
This is an every little thing.
Okay, so here's the ballerina.
The ballerina has now come out.
And if you haven't picked up yet,
this is everything she does.
Every little thing she does is magic.
Magic.
Yikes.
Here's some butterflies.
Some high school theater butterflies have arrived.
There's a fireworks burst set up to the energy.
I like this.
Yep.
Apparently has a Vegas residency up
and that's why he's coming up.
That's why it's all over this.
So the turn is coming in just a second.
Again, I cannot stress that the year is 2019.
Shaggy.
Oh man.
Hey everyone, say his name.
Shaggy.
Wow, that was fun.
Why, where's Sting?
He replaced Sting.
Shaggy.
They have an album together.
Barely moving.
Yeah, they have an album together.
Do they really?
So they have a single, they have a Christmas single.
They did not open the show with that Christmas single.
They closed the show with the Christmas single.
Here is Sting's mostly, or Shaggy's mostly white dance crew.
He just said it's a reggae Christmas.
I was looking for a moment to go backstage
and get my wine and I think we were at that moment.
You can get it, yeah.
Shaggy is really grooving.
Is this the prestige or is that still coming?
Still coming, it's still coming.
We're in the second part of the magic.
Sweet Cabernet, take me away.
Oh shit.
What happened?
Well, we're gonna have to watch it all over again.
Okay.
Well, the ending is what you probably guessed.
All your favorite characters come out in tucks and tails
and they sway gently with Sting and Shaggy
tepidly, tepidly singing Feliz Navidad.
And then who are your hosts?
Why, it's Matthew Morrison from Glee and Baby Spice herself.
Again, 2019.
Disney, bring it out their best.
Baby's Emma Bunton?
Yep, that's right.
Wow.
What, does she have a Vegas residency?
I think she's just a host.
What, does some of y'all know?
Oh yeah, yeah.
Oh, sure.
Oh, for sure.
Yeah, so catch Sting in the new year
at Caesar's Palace, Las Vegas.
If he really gets going, some of those gigs go
for like 10, 12 hours.
He can go, he can go and go and go.
So the YouTube video I pulled this from,
there was only one comment on this video
from Gooch's mom.
And it said, oh, Sting,
I wish your arm would get better already.
Which apparently he tore a tendon in his shoulder
and had to have shoulder surgery.
So we wish him the best.
And Gooch's mom, most importantly,
wishes him the best.
Does Gooch too?
We'll never know.
Yeah, just his mom, I think.
Gooch likes current stuff.
We gotta get Gooch on the show.
Yeah, we gotta get Gooch on the show.
We've been trying to nail Gooch down.
Hasn't been happening.
Major topic, Pirates of the Caribbean with Gooch.
Special appearance by Gooch's mom.
New fourth host, Gooch.
Permanent.
Jason fired, Gooch hired.
Oh, snaked by Gooch again.
Mike and Scott willingly fired themselves.
Now the Gooch cast.
Forever dog changes to Gooch dog.
Forever Gooch is better.
I like that too.
Forever Gooch.
Unfortunately in 2020,
Taylor Swift's music does revert back to Gooch.
Sorry, Tay Tay.
Taylor Swift throws massive shade at the Grammys at Gooch.
Anymore?
Where do we take it from here?
I mean, Mike, feel free to throw in anything you want.
I've still, I could take us back to the past.
Yeah, take us to the past, I think.
I'll take you to the past.
After that disturbing look at 2019.
You know, I was,
my brain got poisoned as a kid
and I watched nothing but Disney specials and Disney parades.
And there was also this show,
did anybody watch something called
Walt Disney World Inside Out?
Worked my whole life to get into a room where
12% of people knew what the show was.
So this is,
this is from a Christmas episode of that show.
The host's name is Scott, incidentally.
I say that not to brag that I have the same name as him,
but you just, you might need to know it later.
And this is this host taking an attractive young guy
she, it's an attractive young worker.
That's all I can say.
I won't, I promise you, here's what I can promise.
I'm not gonna, I won't take this as far as Scott does.
As other Scott.
This is a tour of the shop in the Germany pavilion.
And let me bring her, here we go.
Hi Yvonne, how are you?
I'm fine, thanks.
How long have you worked here for?
I've worked here for six weeks now.
And where are you from?
I'm from Hamburg, Germany.
I'm from Hot Dog America.
Oh yeah?
So here we have a nutcracker.
And you can open it here.
You can put your finger in there.
And lose a joint.
Okay, that's good.
Why does Santa have sticks in his hand?
Because if you're a bad boy, he would,
wimp you, at Christmas.
It's kind of a cheery holiday tradition.
And of course we have a lot of glass ornaments,
like the one here.
All right, what do you call Santa Claus in Germany?
We call him Weihnachtsmann.
All right, and what do you call this guy?
Scott, but he's really cute.
Was that a, what?
Yeah, did we hear that?
Did we hear that?
Whoa.
Was that a boing sound effect?
Yep.
We have a boing.
That guy,
Scott got a boner.
I guess he did.
And I guess, I guess do we blame
some sound effects of department?
Or did Scott have a boner?
That was loud.
And made that sound, it was picked up on the microphone.
Scott has an extra springy boner.
Fun facts, that Scott is now
Secretary of the Interior in the Trump administration.
And you can hear it when he gets a boner from down the hall.
Yeah.
So it's still loud is what I'm saying.
Okay, so is that the last appearance of him in that special?
No, he's throughout.
He takes you on a tour of, he goes on Body Wars.
Oh no.
Body Wars, which was an Epcot attraction
where you get shrunk down and you go through
like the human bloodstream.
And they're trying to find a way to make that Christmas,
I guess, because blood is red.
And he like says like, oh, I think I just missed my,
you know, a little bit of an errant Thanksgiving stuffing.
Or some shit like that.
I don't like.
That's rough.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Do we know who he is?
Was he a host of any kind at the time?
Does anybody recognize him?
No, nobody.
Is anyone in his employee now?
Is Scott here?
If Scott, if you're here, you know what to do.
Let's all be very quiet for one minute.
Okay, he's not within a 10 mile radius.
Oh my God.
We got to figure out where Scott is too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, we can delve into, well, we have to do
the Scott era of Disney World Inside Out
and then the George Foreman era of Disney World.
The show, this was a monthly show taking you
behind the scenes of Disney World
that was eventually hosted by George Foreman.
The strangest things ever.
That's cool though.
Yeah, yeah.
He was excellent.
Better than Scott, but a much quieter boner.
Well, yeah, when you're a boxer,
you got to do everything quick and.
You don't want to give them a warning.
You're about to get a boner.
You remember that scene in Rocky
where Mick is telling Rocky
to not let them hear your boner?
Don't let them hear your boner, kid.
Don't let them hear your boner.
You got to put socks over that thing.
Muffle it.
Dampen the sound, Rock.
My hands don't scan.
You got to make your voices different, Scott.
You got to push them.
I wasn't critiquing you.
My voice was the same voice.
And it's just a hair away from.
Don't do inhalants.
Damage your brain.
My graph is more like this.
And then Rocket and every other character is,
hey, your hands don't scan.
Far from the shallows now.
Jackson Maine voice.
Okay, where are we going now?
Let me find the next thing.
I see you're going by phone.
Oh, here, let's do this one.
I didn't want to just represent Disney
with these specials because so many theme parks
and themed entertainment experiences
do have Christmas overlays and Christmas iterations.
And that includes this place.
Maybe I should just let this place
do the introduction for itself.
So much phone fumbling.
That was very embarrassing.
Okay, here we go.
Take over, guys.
Ho, ho, ho, mateys.
Christmas has arrived at the Pirates Voyage in Myrtle Beach.
Christmas at Pirates Voyage Dinner and Show,
the most fun place to eat in Myrtle Beach.
Enjoy a holiday feast to warm your hearts.
Travel through time with Captain Scrooge
and the mystical spirit of Christmas.
It's a spiritual journey filled with...
Here's the Nativity.
Celebrating the real meaning of Christmas.
Pirates Voyage Dinner and Show.
Yeah.
Wow.
Love that.
Pirates Dinner Adventure spends
all their budget at Christmas.
I think so, I think so.
Well, keep in mind, this is the Myrtle Beach one.
This is not the one we experienced,
which does seem like it's a pretty huge scope.
Like I've watched more clips of their Nativity scene
and it's like full line.
It's like every barnyard animal,
there's a big Noah's Ark procession.
Like there's two of every kind.
I have to think all the like dinner shows
and Branson and like Myrtle Beach are just like,
once it becomes Christmas time, they're like,
yes, time to cash it in.
Time to get baby Jesus up there.
I got the camels in here.
So the pirate ship transforms into Noah's Ark.
Well, Captain Scrooge.
Is that what it is?
Well, that's what you just described, right?
I mean, I didn't mean literally Noah's Ark.
I just mean there are so many animals
booked for this Nativity scene every year.
But like you're saying two of each animal?
I mean, not literally.
I just mean like it is such a massive parade of animals
that all have to live in this dinner theater
in Myrtle Beach.
It sounds a lot like Noah's Ark though.
Yeah, certainly.
A big boat with a bunch of animals.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the baby Jesus, the same story.
They also alluded to a Captain Scrooge.
And what appeared to be some sort of father Christmas
like mystical creature.
Set sail with Captain Scrooge, they said.
And then a ghostly figure appears.
So I guess it's a Scrooge that makes Bob Cratchbeard
work late on the ship that Christmas Eve.
And then various ghosts visit him
and show him journeys past.
Tiny Tim is ill, he went in the elevator,
he reaches Philbin went in and.
And this is the same Pirates Dinner Adventure
that's in Buena Park.
Or it's a different pirate show.
I'm not sure, they may be affiliated.
I don't know the ownership.
Cause there are Sister Pirates Dinner Adventures
in Orlando, I guess it's Orlando.
I think it's Orlando.
I think this is a.
Can anybody back me up?
There's Pirates Dinner Adventure Orlando
and then in Buena Park.
So this is a separate Pirate Dinner Adventure.
And.
Does Mundy know?
Do you know the ownership rights of the various pirates?
What?
Yeah.
Busy scrolling.
You know guys, if you think about it,
Jesus was kind of the biggest pirate of them all.
He walked on water, you know?
He threw the money lenders out of the temple.
He said, if you authority to like the Romans.
Keep going.
He loved that wine.
And like pirates, he ate fish.
He has long hair like Jack Sparrow.
He has long hair.
Is that we have to figure out,
in Buena Park they do do a specific Christmas pirate show.
I know they do that.
I just wonder if it's as hardcore as this looks like.
Let's all go right now.
Let's catch the 10.30.
But it's probably not pirates.
It's probably the naughty show, Teatro Martini.
Which is the real name of the bawdy show
they do down at the Pirates Dinner Adventure.
Has anyone seen that?
I have not.
Woo.
I have to imagine though, there's no seals.
I feel like the Buena Park seals would be sickly.
One thing to explain to the listener at home
is that what was happening there,
the narration says discover the real meaning of Christmas.
And then a baby Christ is held up high by Mary and Joseph.
And then pretty quick after it cuts to a seal,
catching a wreath around its neck.
The reason for the season.
That has to be illegal in California, right?
In Myrtle Beach, it's like a lawless place still.
Yeah.
You can do whatever you want, but in Buena Park.
You can do like, they'll do plastic rings here,
but you can't do a wreath.
It scratches up the seal's neck.
Oh, so the seal isn't the problem.
I know.
They'll still do seal stuff.
If it's a soft thing, it's a soft hoop.
Yeah, you can throw it at a seal during a dinner show.
You just need padding.
Yes.
OK.
Myrtle Beach just has too many.
So they roll right into the Christmas rush
into the seal culling rush down in South Carolina.
That's a real bummer.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I think I just remembered who is the owner of that Pirates
Theater, and I think it's Dolly Parton.
I believe this.
I think it is related to.
She does have a Pirates Intervention.
I mean, maybe that's hers.
That's probably it.
Yeah, I think her company was buying up
a lot of the theaters that were having trouble.
What do they know?
Why are they buying all the seals?
So Dolly Parton owns the IP Captain Scrooge.
Yeah.
So she's making these Netflix movies.
There could be a Captain Scrooge Netflix movie.
And they do need three ghosts.
So they need three actors of varying heights
to play the different ghosts.
I call it.
Well, no, Jason calls Marley.
Oh, he's Marley.
Oh, no, Marley's not one of the three.
That's going to be Monday.
In.
Do you have any more Kathy Leigh clips?
Calling out a request for Kathy Leigh.
He has not been the same since she left the fourth hour
of the Today Show.
He loved that fourth hour.
Is she just retired?
Yeah.
Well, I don't know.
She's taking a break.
That seemed like her and Hoda seemed like they're
having so much fun every day.
Yeah, but sometimes you just got to take a step away.
Honestly, it's healthy.
She made a movie.
Kathy Leigh made a movie with Craig Ferguson.
Well, Craig Ferguson and Kathy Leigh, two powerhouses
together for the first time.
Is it out?
It's not out.
Is it coming out?
Is it a Hallmark movie?
We're grilling you.
We appreciate the knowledge.
That's more than we needed.
Plenty of information.
Yes.
Yeah.
You don't need to know that.
Second gate coming.
Yeah.
Great.
I like to imagine the poster said like Ferguson, Lee Gifford,
and those big metallic letters at the top.
For some people, those are better than the expendables.
Yes.
Those are my expendables.
So let me go elsewhere in themed entertainment worlds.
This is our last official show of 2019.
And we're reflecting a little bit
on some of the fun we've had through the year.
And one of my favorite episodes of the year
was talking about Chuck E. Cheese with Jamie Loftus.
That was a ton of fun.
Thank you.
And Mike, what you brought to the table in that one
is that some of the newer Chuck E. Cheese music
is really fantastic.
If I may say, really quickly, yesterday
was Pasquale's birthday.
That is not a lie.
I'm on the Facebook, the Chuck E. Cheese Facebook fan group.
And there was a big graphic that said, happy birthday, Pasquale.
So just keep them in your hearts today,
because it's a birthday week.
And we all love Pasquale P. Pie Plates, his full name.
December 12th.
December 12th, Pasquale P. Pie Plates.
Is there a code there?
That's 1212.
I see what you're saying.
Is that something, a little Easter egg
that the creator put in?
Yeah.
Does that look like pizza cutting tools
if you lay the number?
I'm stretching.
I'm trying to figure it out.
Let's just say that, yes, if you draw 12 right,
it looks like pizza cutting tools.
So I think that's what it is.
Nailed it.
I knew it.
So anyway, the point is, we found some of the newer
Chuck E. Music.
And there is a newer Chuck E. Christmas song.
And I'm going to play just the end of it for you.
You can watch a full music video of this on YouTube
as sung by the puppet Chuck E. Cheese.
And we should say, RIP the robots, I guess, this year.
That's a thing.
Our personal in memoriam for 2019 is just those robots,
and who cares about anyone else?
Five sad souls.
Yeah.
They've replaced, like they're replacing all the robots
with a screen, right?
Boo.
Yeah.
I don't like our screens.
Robots are what you think.
The angriest the audience has been
is when I mentioned a screen.
Yeah.
What for?
Fuck screens.
Yeah.
That's a good rallying cry for our audience.
Yeah, so that sucks.
It's a barn.
We do have to look in.
None of us, I don't think, have enough money
to start buying up robots.
But not expendable robot money, no.
We'd like to.
Yeah.
We shall try.
We'll try in the coming year.
So these guys, I mean, these guys
will be up for auction soon enough
that we can get these specific robots.
I want to give credit to the, so these are robots
being filmed.
And all of the cuts and edit decisions
are from the YouTube user.
And I give him credit for it.
This is really nice.
And it has a little bit of a wonderful Christmas time vibe,
I think you'll find.
Here we go.
["Christmas Time"]
And now it's here.
Christmas time has come again.
Friends are near.
And that is all we need.
To celebrate this special time when we can come together.
Wishing for you joy, love, peace, and harmony.
And we'll have a very merry Christmas.
Yes, we're ready.
Merry Christmas, yes, we'll have APP Merry Christmas time.
And we'll have a very merry Christmass.
Yes, we'll have a merry Christmas time.
Merry Christmas time.
Merry Christmas, Helen.
Merry Christmas, Chuckie.
Wow, yeah.
Give it up for that one.
Listeners at home, somewhat the audience is responding to.
We'll post the video, but
first of all, at one point, some random kids just ran by.
They couldn't shoot it when the restaurant wasn't open.
Well, I think this is a guy just going in and filming.
Oh, this wasn't. Oh.
Officially produced video.
No, no, no. This is a fan film.
Yeah, that had higher production values than some streaming shows.
That's what I got confused because there's a they post on the Chuckie
Cheese YouTube so much content like songs, new stuff, well produced things,
puppet version, like little sketches and stuff and songs.
So I just assume that was just a little thing they put up there
because they love to make.
There's a separate music video that is better produced.
And this one is just like also some of what we were liking there
is that just a ghostly Helen, the bird
appeared in the corner of the lower corners of the frame
in sort of a like
Natalie Cole, Nat King Cole, like as if it was a posthumous duet.
I guess in my version of this, Helen has passed away.
Is it possible that Helen in this restaurant had been removed already?
Yeah. And she was singing to Chuckie from like a scrap yard somewhere.
They're the ones getting rid of the robots, not me.
This is what they're doing.
Do you realize a little bit that sink in
Twitter claps, some cognitive dissonance going on too,
because like there was a tiny screen in the corner playing the puppet versions
of Chuckie and Ellen and then like casual puppet.
Chuckie was on the Christmas tree.
So like this is reasonably recent.
Yeah, yeah, very recent as in Chuckie cheese.
It's not a Chuckie cheese.
If I can't see five different iterations of Chuckie,
she's sure all within one field of vision.
That's old. Hell, it's old, like 90s Helen.
But newer Chuck, newer Chuck with super new on the screen.
It's like the full Dr.
Manhattan being able to see your whole life at once ability.
Seeing all he's been and all he will be.
I love I by the way, I haven't seen that before.
I loved it. It's really nice.
Yeah, yeah, that was great.
Yes, we'll have.
Yeah, those are good.
Cheese, we said it on the episode.
The YouTube is good.
Like to look at all this, the songs like there's some good songs,
a lot of them parodies, but like
there's a weird one that sounds like Snoop Dogg.
But I love that one.
Another Chuckie day, you know, is another Chuckie day.
I like that.
I like the me and my friends, which is a Bruno Mars, Mark Ronson riff
where he lists all his friends.
And there is a dance that goes with it.
I don't know it.
Don't ask me to do it.
But if you know it's you do this and then you clap.
So it's four quarters and then you spin.
Oh, you just got Mayor Pete on the brain. Yeah.
I love his little dance.
What is what I think?
Honestly, we have talked about this at the show, if it's the same dance before.
But what if Mayor Pete went into a Chuckie cheese
and he stole the me and my friends dance?
And it was the scandal that sunk his campaign.
Happy something.
It's possible.
We have to look. We have to look into it.
But there's if you go to the Chuck E.
Cheese fan page, not the official page,
there's a couple of people that will post new versions of them
doing the dance weekly.
Oh, I don't know why everyone's making that noise.
I like watching it.
And then he'll dance like this guy, all his dance with Chuckie.
And I love it.
I go join it.
You do have to answer some questions to get in the group.
But it's nothing everyone here doesn't know, I assume.
The first question, are you OK?
And oh, send.
Come on in.
But there's no one doing recreations of Helen
just with just total mono focus during game and time, right?
Or she's just like, I got to play this game, like just ignoring
everything going on around her.
That's the song I like.
I don't know.
That's the other song.
That was the other song we talked about gaming time.
It's the Taylor Swift like table.
Yeah, yeah, it's very it's an intense.
I forgot that that's about sorry.
I'm sorry. We hung out to dry there.
Oh, that's all right.
I just didn't remember gaming.
Sometimes I'm being a dick and I'm doing it on purpose, but not now.
I know. I know.
That's the one the running joke in it is like Munch is like,
I'm going to eat your pizza, Helen.
And Chuck is like, knock that shit off.
Don't eat her pizza, man.
So, yeah, that's right.
So the song is she is just very excited about gaming.
Yeah, that is that song is pretty good as well.
That album is available, I think, for free on the Chuck E.
Cheese website. It is. Yeah. Yeah.
So very good. Very good.
You all have a lot of homework now.
Yeah. And it's our break over the break, though.
So and everybody have a dance video ready to go to show us.
We do need to make a Mayor Jason dance, though.
Oh, good idea.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll be workshopping that and I'll be ready in January. Yeah.
OK, as I'm talking about other episodes I've really enjoyed
through the year, another another favorite of mine was talking about
a place called Dogpatch USA.
And thank you. Thanks.
That was a lot of fun.
Chris Cantwell joined us, who went there as a child.
It is now this strange, dilapidated park in Arkansas
that's been through a number of owners, including most recently
a right wing patriot con artist, allegedly
named David Hare.
And I was hoping, praying that there would be some connection
between Dogpatch and David Hare and Christmas.
And what I found is that this man who you're about to see,
this is video from 1990 of a future failed theme park impresario.
This is a original musical that he wrote and produced and performed.
It's just a taste of it.
And then with the power of editing, it is going to flash forward
to the David Hare that we know via
Dogpatch USA YouTube videos today.
So we're going to time travel real fast from 1990 to 2018.
And here we go.
Christmas is here. It's the time of the year.
The jingle bells ring out, the carolers sing out.
Good cheer is about when Christmas is here.
So spread a little laughter with some good old Christmas joy.
Mix it all together for every girl and boy.
It's a special time of year.
So families draw near.
Gather together as Christmas is here.
You know, somebody buried the pool at the hotel,
and we're going to get that back up and running.
I don't know exactly when at this point.
It's not at the top of our list, meaning in the immediate, immediate, immediate,
as in people start asking me when it's not in that scope.
It is in the next few months. I don't know.
It's coming up. We're going to get it done.
But I'm not going to give any announcement
because I'm not ready to answer questions about it.
OK, is Christmas here?
I'm not ready to answer that yet.
I'm not I'm not prepared to answer that at this time.
So stop asking me. I do believe Christmas is coming.
I think we'll be here soon enough.
Will it be December 25th? I can't promise you that.
I don't know. I just I just don't know.
God bless this man. Oh, my God.
Who would have thought this man would go on to own a property
you can only call Dogpatch Fury Road?
This setup he has here
is so interesting to me.
He has his characters.
Well, what's the what's the first of all down in Dogpatch?
Do we remember the song?
From the episode?
No, it's my sister, I think, texted me after that episode
and was like, that song is a jam or something like she
like a legit a bob a bob.
Did you say Bob?
That's a term Jason and kids use.
But I mean, this is like he's got his memorabilia here.
So he is trying to sort of like make it like whimsical.
He's in front of like a picture of himself working on a green screen
and then a big mug of WC Fields and a Diet Coke.
And there's a cannon right behind him.
Oh, yeah, an old timey.
Hmm. Hmm.
An interesting man.
Go down the dog patch rabbit hole if you get the chance.
It's delay is that whole first part of the special online.
Yes, you can watch all of Christmas is here.
If you're curious, spoiler, a fifties car rolls on stage
and some greasers sing Jingle Bell Rock.
So you have that ahead of you.
I'm coming to the end of video.
Should I close out my videos or should you are like,
do you have one more, the one more we were going to end with left?
And there's one there's one for that.
Yeah, OK, OK, I'll get to this quickly.
This is OK.
This is a little bit theme park tangential, but I could not resist
showing this to an audience because it is related to Christmas
and it's related to animation.
How many people like and enjoy the rank and bass holiday specials?
Yes. Rudolph the Red Nose Reindeer and Frosty the Snowman.
So, you know, the 2D animation and clay mission.
A friend of mine, Brian Rowe,
got a box set of the rank and bass holiday specials,
and it's the ones that we know.
And then there's one that I didn't know called that was referred to as a lost
Christmas classic.
And this is something called Cricket on the Hearth.
Is anyone familiar with Cricket on the Hearth?
Aaron Gardner is just a good to see you.
A favorite around the Gardner home, and I'm so we get to share it now.
This is really exciting.
I'm more of a turkey in the straw, man.
Your favorite song, favorite song.
I will say that Cricket on the Hearth is old timey because it is based
on a Charles Dickens novel that is much, much less popular than his other
Christmas carol.
I'd say Cricket on the Hearth comes in at a distant two.
Stuff competition, very tough competition.
So this, yes, as I said, this is released on DVD and it's called
a lost holiday classic.
And I think the reason it was lost is because of massive animation errors.
I will give you an example of that right now.
A gasp at the design alone.
Wait till you see what he does.
I suppose you're all wondering what me a crick.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
Go back. OK, here we go.
I suppose you're all wondering what me, a cricket is doing here on Christmas
Eve with a home of me own.
See, I am a part of the family, as it were.
Oh, and it's a lucky household.
What has a cricket on the.
Oh, God. Indeed, I am good luck.
Or if it hadn't been for cricket, Crockett here,
why, there wouldn't be no blinking family.
I'll tell you how it all began.
So it is what we're watching is an elderly cricket.
And he the why the audience is gasping is because
strangely, in an extreme close up, one eyelid lowers
for like three full seconds, then opens back up.
Then the other eyelid lowers for three full seconds.
You know, the way living beings do, we see it all the time.
So that's one reason the cricket on the hearth doesn't stick around
to holiday after holiday.
But I think I know the biggest one.
And and it is this clip.
So about an hour into the thing, the cricket runs a fowl of some powerful people.
And they want him gone.
So a group is enlisted.
And the group consists of a dog, a monkey and a crow.
And these are they're almost like, I guess they're like bounty hunters in a way.
And they are going to round up this cricket and then they're going to
they're going to get a reward for it.
And that's all the setup you need to know.
Here's this.
Hello.
Now, where's our pay?
I've got your pay off right here.
Oh, I can tell you.
That's what Scrooge originally did to the ghosts of past, present and future.
I've got your lesson right here.
Holy shit.
It cuts to an exterior of a boat.
And there are huge colored gun blasts
implying that a human man has shot a dog, a monkey and a crow in the face.
I have dreamed of the day I could show that to a big group of people.
I was fun.
I don't know what to say.
Yeah, I don't have a witty retort.
I have nothing.
No observations will make it right.
We'll make it easier to swallow.
Did you see that when you were a kid?
No, no, no.
No, I like like 10 years ago and we watch it every single Christmas.
So much of it is so dreadfully boring.
And there's a part with like I didn't even want to punish the audience
by showing you the Mae West esque sexy cat.
Good.
What's the hell?
Truly scarring.
Incredibly scarred.
So you got to like fast forward, fast forward, fast forward.
Oh, good.
Now here's the part where the man shoots the monkey in the face.
That's worse than the Bambi scene.
Yes. Yeah.
Like much worse.
It's a good Christmas lesson about what the life of sin leads to.
Justice.
See justice.
The fairest of them all.
Internet.
Oh, my God.
So if there's a cricket in your house this holiday season, leave it be.
That's my video run.
Mike, take the wheel for a little bit.
We got a couple of things.
We're sort of running out of time, so I'm going to just roll through here.
This is just going to be a quick thing for everybody here.
I just want to show everyone some photos of my favorite Christmas seats.
No. Oh, boy.
This is Bugs Bunny from Six Flags.
Nice. And there's his seat.
Dang.
This is these are the reindeer in the Disneyland parade.
And there are their seats.
There is Reese's Pieces, man.
Hell, yeah.
Peanut butter cup.
Here is his seat.
You you had to get in real close to get this shot.
You had to be a real pervert to get this.
I have to run the joke for the audience.
It's the rapper. It's really funny.
It's a very funny joke.
How else will they know? Thank you.
And then the king of them all.
Here he is.
Check out that Christmas seat, folks.
That's that's my segment called Christmas Seats.
All right. So.
Wow. Wow.
I will say, though, you know, we've had a lot of fun tonight,
but it is a holiday time.
And as Jason said, some things, you know, there there is a reason for the season.
Yeah. You know, a very special little guy
that we all need to remember when it comes to Christmas time.
So I've made a little piece here and I just want to show it.
Hey, Scott, again.
At this point, Mike plays a video that includes many, many images of Baby Grinch.
And eventually Baby Grinch is interacting with me, Scott.
It is obviously very horrifying and should be viewed by no one.
But if you want to watch it, it will be available on our Twitter at
podcast, the ride and using hashtag PTR SAC eclipse.
No, no, no.
These blessings are down.
Yes, we.
And the stars in the sky
the town on Earth, it
living Lord, Jesus sleep
on.
Oh, oh,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
The cattle are lowing,
the baby of wings,
but live Lord Jesus.
How many are there?
I love you, Jesus.
I come from the sky
and stay by my cradle
till morning comes.
Hell yeah!
For lay the manger
the pit for a bed.
The little Lord Jesus
lay down his seat.
The stars in the sky
the town where he lay.
The little Lord Jesus
sleep on the hay.
All right.
Let's get a Randy Gerber
chant going.
Randy Gerber, Randy Gerber,
Randy Gerber.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let me welcome.
No, that's it.
Me and Monday are hitting the road.
We're fucking out of here.
Let's split.
Yeah, I can't.
I can't.
So, yeah, it felt good to pretend
for a second and you had my back
and I knew you would.
Yeah, I want to get out of here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I understood.
All right.
Well, we're well, now I will
really swear we are wrapping it up
the entire podcast that is.
Well, look, I just there's
is important that we remember
around Christmas time.
It's it said reason for the season
and I understand the joke that
that's baby Grinch.
But then you kept adding reasons.
The reasons are all things I don't like.
I downloaded this.
I didn't make this.
Hmm, I found it.
Maybe that that Chuck E.
Cheese videographer did it or something.
Yeah, do it.
Should we watch it again?
Oh, yeah.
We have to go.
No, no, no.
The lyric I period is famously strict
to end times.
Well, we'll watch it after the show is over.
It's called the greatest story
ever told for a reason.
A child was born to us
and then two bros made a tequila company
and they decided to spread the wealth
around in a series of briefings.
We have heard this story.
We have heard this story a number of times.
We're all millionaires now.
Yeah.
Mundy, unplug his mic.
Unplug his microphone.
Um, he'll do it.
He will do it.
Do it at the end of the show.
We're just making Mundy clean up now.
I paid seven dollars for that dip.
So he should earn it is what I'm saying.
Seven dollars.
Who knew dip was so expensive?
Did it used to be seven dollars?
In high school when I was like 14 now.
What was it?
Three.
That was like 1996.
Boy.
That's why we got to vote for Biden
and get this country back on track.
We got to go backwards.
Back to dipping.
Get America dipping again.
Take America dip again.
All right.
Okay.
Do you have other stuff?
Where are we at?
No, that's the most important thing
I could show.
Oh my God.
Thank the Lord.
Okay.
Then we're going to start winding it down.
But as we do, I mentioned that we did this special
a couple years ago where we showed old clips.
And those of you who've stuck with us for a while
and listened to this podcast for a while,
you might have heard it.
And there was this part of one of the specials
that we showed that was it as scarring as Baby Grinch
and Chuck-O, perhaps not.
But it was very memorable and stuck with me.
And that is this strange moment from an old Christmas special
involving Geppetto.
Do people remember this?
Okay.
So this was a Christmas special from 1978,
Christmas of Walt Disney World 1978.
And to reacquaint, or for the first time,
or to, for the first time,
acquaint people who don't know this moment,
an actor named Avery Schreiber is playing Geppetto.
And he is very lonely at Christmas because he is not
with Pinocchio this year.
And he is airing his grievances to pets and other toys
and really wishing that Pinocchio could be around.
So here now is this classic Christmas moment.
Merry Christmas, you boy Pinocchio.
That's nice.
You boy Pinocchio.
You hear that?
He's still my boy.
Pinocchio's grown up.
He moved to America, but he's still my boy.
What a crazy wooden puppet I make.
What a man he has turned into.
I remember Pinocchio when he was a little child.
What a wooden head he was.
Every time I get a splinter at the work table here,
I remember the time I gave him the only spanking I ever gave him.
This is going to hurt me more than it's going to hurt you.
Boy, was I right.
Do you remember the time that I gave Pinocchio the first bath?
Oh, was he scared.
He was so frightened.
What's the water?
I put him in and he floats.
Then I couldn't get him out.
He gets all soaked.
He gets the wood inside him.
He gets twisted.
He gets warped.
It wasn't funny then.
Now we can laugh about it.
All right.
Who's seeing that for the first time?
Just to get a, okay, okay.
Oh, very good.
Okay, okay.
So that gives you the, I mean, it's like way longer than that too.
He monologues to no one for a long time.
Really long time.
Talks to his toys and to fish and fondly recalls spanking a wooden boy.
And when he got the wooden boy in a bathtub and made him swell up.
And it wasn't funny then.
It must have been terrifying then.
The child was in pain.
But it's funny now.
Biden told that story out of stump speech.
Biden.
What a funny wooden puppet I make.
And I called him corn pop and Jill said, don't call him corn pop.
So then I called him Pinocchio.
So this goes on for a while.
Pinocchio moved to America, of course, as we all know that's Canon and he's.
He's bummed about it.
And then he decides he's not going to just take this loneliness sitting down.
He says, today.
I'm going to make a new friend.
And then he puts his thoughts into song.
And we played this clip a couple of years ago.
But I didn't think we should just repeat material.
We shouldn't just press play on this clip.
We had to elevate it.
That's why we're now going to perform this song for you.
All right.
So this is going to take a little a little bit of setup, a little bit of wig work on my part.
Coming up here while you pull it out on guitar, Mike Carlson.
On Gepetto vocals, here's Truly Scott Garen.
This is the honor of a lifetime.
And on wood block.
It Jason is Sheridan.
That sounded OK.
Is it sort of working for us?
It check it check.
I'm not just rifling in my pockets creepily.
I'm like searching for a mustache.
We will see if it will remain on for the duration of the performance.
Likely not.
It's actually a repurposed Santa Claus eyebrow.
Which interesting fact.
All right.
I'm ready to go.
We're ready to go.
Do we have a name for when we perform music together?
It's the good boy.
The good boy.
The good boy band.
Be that for now.
So here we go.
Let this song carry you into the holiday season.
Today I take some wood from an old tree.
Don't you worry Christmas tree.
Today I try to make it's company.
Today I try to make those clones.
Make it out of wood you know.
Today I tried to stop being alone.
That's hard.
Today I try to turn lead into gold.
Today I try to stop growing old.
That's hard.
But today I drink from life's renewing stream.
Today I wake to cop a dream.
In all the good kids there's the bad.
With all of the laughs.
Then it comes the sad.
And as the clouds of time roll by.
It's getting clearer to my eye.
Today I wept for they.
So long ago.
You hear me Pinocchio.
Today I feel inside of me.
For today.
But it's all the man has been made new.
Today I give my love to you.
I give my love to you.
I give my love to me.
Oh, well.
Merry Christmas in Gilberto.
You survived the podcast.
You did it, too.
Thank you all so much for coming out.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you all so much for coming out.
Thank you so much.
Thanks so much, everybody.
That is podcast the ride for 2019.
Thanks, everybody.
So much for coming and listening.
We've had such a blast all year.
I can't imagine a thing I've had more fun doing.
And thank you all for being a part of it.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to forever dog for having us always and for putting on this show.
Thanks to Brett.
Thank you to the Lyric Hyperion for hosting us.
Lyric Hyperion.
Yes.
And thank you.
You are free to go now.
Bye bye.
Good night.