Five, four, three, two, one.
Merry Christmas from Podcast The Ride, The Second Gate.
This is Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
Ho, ho, ho, it's me, Mike Carlson.
And ho, ho, ho, Jason Sheridan also here as per usual.
That's correct.
Hey, this is a little special Christmas treat
for all you Patreon subscribers.
We're opening Santa's mail sack
to address some of your burning holiday
and or Christmas questions.
Thanks for sending them in on the Twitter
and the Instagram and Facebook.
There's so many sources of questions
and we'll try to get through as many of them as we can.
If you're not following any of those things,
then follow them and then you can, you know,
throw your questions into episodes just like this
among many other treats.
And also if you're listening to this,
you may have heard the live show that we put out
that we did at Lyric Hyperion,
this little Christmas special that was a lot of fun.
If you were there in person, thank you so much.
It was good to see everybody.
People brought us presents, which is insane.
Thank you for.
Yes, thank you so much.
Yeah, thank you.
It's bonkers.
We're not setting the base of expectations
that people have to give us presents,
but it's all wonderful.
We don't deserve presents.
Well, look, we're good boys, but are we that good of boys?
I don't know.
Only Santa can truly determine.
But I just wanted to, I wanted to follow up on something
that happened in that show
and take it a little bit further
because I was digging backwards into our year,
into an earlier topic, which was Dogpatch USA,
this dilapidated Arkansas park
that we did a very long episode about.
Because I was trying to see if there was any
good Christmas connection to Dogpatch USA,
I was going back into the Facebook group of Heritage USA,
which is the weird company that took over Dogpatch
run by this guy, David Hare, who was this right wing guy.
It was like, had this agenda
and then the whole thing fell apart and he skipped down.
And this Facebook group was like a fan page for it?
No, no, no.
This is their official.
Yeah, this was David Hare's way of getting information out
to the public about how the building was going.
Is this how you tell us you're a QAnon guy now?
I saw a lot of cool ideas there
and I kept going down another rabbit hole,
a hair hole if you were.
Did you guys know JFK Jr. still alive?
It was his sex plane.
It's been wrongly attributed this whole time.
It is a very fun Facebook page in general
because he'll be posting about,
I got a new song on the way
and then there'll be a comment that's like, cool,
hey, could you follow up on something you talked about
in your last video, which is paying off all those debts?
People use this Facebook page to come after David Hare.
Is it active?
Is it like, is he posted recently?
No, not anymore.
Because David Hare, I don't know that he's like.
The lamb maybe.
I think he's on the lamb.
I don't know that he's officially in hiding,
but he certainly is not going anywhere near Dogpatch USA,
which there was recent stuff that the current owner,
who is this guy who makes dog bowls,
he's letting the property go.
So who knows what's gonna happen to Dogpatch USA?
This story keeps going and going
and we'll keep updating you.
But now let me get to why I'm bringing any of this up.
This came up in our live show, the song Down in Dogpatch,
which you talked about and your sister is fond of,
apparently, who was at the show.
Down in Dogpatch is a song sung
by the character Foxworthy, who's an animal puppet.
And he's driving kind of an old Model T car, I think.
A very Mr. Toad kind of car.
And it's a really catchy song.
And that is from a video that was meant to be part
of the beginning of a lot of Dogpatch,
Down in Dogpatch episodes.
I think he says one of three
and then the rest we've never gotten to see.
And you're left to wonder, what was this gonna be?
We met Foxworthy, we met Hubbell Hare,
the main mascot of Dogpatch USA,
but you didn't meet any more characters.
And when I was digging back
into the Heritage USA Facebook page.
What do you find?
Okay, sorry, I don't wanna get ahead of myself.
There is a character who would have been
in a subsequent episode that we didn't get to see.
And it is a dog.
This is from the Heritage USA Facebook page,
May 17th, 2018.
And just take a deep breath and get ready for this
because here is the post.
Heritage USA Studios, a new character joins the cast
of Down in Dogpatch, meet.
Sorry, I sneezed in the middle of this grand thing.
Sorry, so sorry.
A new character joins the cast of Down in Dogpatch,
meet Puppy Carlson.
What the fuck?
I thought about bringing this up in the live show,
but it was like too much to talk about.
Puppy Carlson, you are now both looking at a puppy.
There was a character, an original theme park IP character
who we never got to meet whose name is Carlson.
What the hell?
Puppy Carlson.
First off, I gotta say Puppy Carlson is very cute.
Yes, probably more so than Fox or the Huffle hair.
The cutest of the Dogpatch characters.
Puppy Carlson, if I Google Puppy Carlson,
would it even come up or is it just?
No, I tried it.
It's nothing.
This is the only source.
May 17th, 2018, just if anybody wants to check that date
and we'll post it too.
Michael, you've always been the caretaker of Heritage USA.
You've always been here at the Overlook.
Puppy Carlson, wow.
And it doesn't have any other explanation
for why he's called that.
No, it's so weird.
It's very weird.
Like of all the names and that it's a last name.
Yeah, right, like why?
Why?
I mean, obviously it would imply
that his owners had that name.
Yeah, maybe.
I mean, if it's the format of Hubble hair
and hair is he's a rabbit,
but he's also kind of named after David Hare,
the guy who invented him.
Did he know somebody named Carlson
and it's an attribute to him?
Maybe, maybe one of his right wing friends
is named Carlson.
Could be.
And he was like, I'm gonna name a dog after him
in honor of this great man
who believes the things that I believe.
We'll all learn of who this other Carlson is soon.
He'll like, you know, attempts to assassinate
Adam Schiff or something.
Then your last name will be associated with insanity.
But puppy Carlson isn't ready for this Christmas,
but puppy Carlson will be ready.
Hopefully by next Christmas,
guys, we're still digging out the poop.
Puppy Carlson, wow.
Somebody took puppy Carlson and buried him in the pool.
Okay, are we gonna fish him out?
Yes, when?
I don't know.
Do we currently know David Hare?
David Hare?
David Hare.
David Hare, do we currently know his whereabouts?
No, no.
There's no update in a long time.
Will we be the first to find out
when he comes after us for attacking him?
Possibly.
Scott, you helped me last night.
I was trying to find the Lou Pearlman document,
which is on YouTube.
They found him in Bali in a very funny way.
Oh, that's insane.
That guy is just like, isn't that, hey, FBI,
isn't that that guy, that boy band guy?
I think I'm looking at him in a hotel.
The tourist sent a picture,
and the FBI agents sent to arrest him
are also in the other side of the picture,
because they were eating breakfast at the same place.
Do you remember that?
They're just in the photo?
They got there too early, they're like, oh, he's not home.
You wanna go get breakfast?
And they know if they hang out long enough,
Pearlman will come down for one of his several breakfasts
for the day.
So I don't know what the more cost-effective version
of Bali is, but maybe check there.
Maybe check Branson for David Hare.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, man, he should, yeah, he, was he ever in Branson?
That seems like such an easy-
Given, yeah.
Or does he have it out for Branson,
because he's trying to be a competitor of Branson almost.
Or yeah, or they wouldn't allow him
to have a Hubble Hare show.
They rejected his bid for a theater show
for Hubble Hare or something.
Maybe he, maybe the next place he'll show up
is trying to peddle these characters to Trump.
Puppy Carlson could just very soon be named Puppy Pence.
Yeah.
He's trying to sell this lineup
to be the official mascots of the Trump administration.
We may need to buy the characters
to make sure they don't fall into the wrong hands.
I feel like he would sell them, and maybe for not a lot.
And it's your right, there's a dog named after you.
There's a dog named after me.
You're fond of- Dogs, yeah.
Of Gelatoni, wait, Gelatoni, no, Gelatoni was a cat.
Who's the dog? He's an Italian painter cat.
The cook is the, the cookie is.
Cookie Anne. Cookie Anne, yeah.
Cookie Anne, yes, of course.
So yeah, interesting, very interesting.
Very busy.
It asks, honestly, more questions than answers here.
Yeah, I'd have to say.
This is another opening up a box
to try to figure, like a mystery box,
JJ's mystery box here.
Sure.
Yeah, I don't know what to-
So we'll have to, I bet there's no answers, honestly.
I bet he just has a friend named Carlson.
But I'd like to think there's some sort of grand mystery
or something strange afoot here.
Yeah. Yeah.
But if, well, if also, if anyone's just like
looking at this doll, if anyone went and like
pilfered through what was left of Dogpatch USA
and like found this dog line around,
then please send it to us.
Let us know. Yeah, send it.
We'll pay top dollar.
Puppy Carlson.
Let's just, whatever, he's a, he's a mascot of ours now.
They're not doing anything with him.
Yeah. Yeah.
We'll make a shirt.
Sure. Yeah.
We are asking for a lawsuit.
Probably. Which would be funny.
Can we change it just a little?
Like pupper Carlson.
Can it just a puppy I-E-B instead of Y?
I see.
Yeah, maybe that's enough.
Could you just maybe a lowercase P?
Is that enough?
Could be. Lowercase.
Maybe.
We gotta consult with an attorney.
But either way, Puppy Carlson.
Edwin is Puppy Carlson too.
So, he's a real dog.
You think he'd be jealous of Puppy Carlson
if they were to meet?
Yes.
Or he would do what he does with other dogs
and humps them.
He would hump them.
Most likely.
Because that's what he does when he meets a dog he likes.
That's just him.
So that's that.
That's my whole present to you is awareness of Puppy Carlson.
Thank you for that Christmas present.
Your personal theme park IP.
Geez.
Now let's crack open Santa's Mail Sack
and see what you guys are wanting to know
about how we do the holidays and our holiday opinions.
Jason is ready to go.
So I think we should let Jason,
we're gonna each take a different form of social media.
Sure.
On Facebook.
Jason Sheridan.
Jason's reading the Facebook group.
I'm coming Facebook.
I, the very first question on Facebook,
I will get to because it's the big one.
We've been asked it a lot on all forms of social media.
But I'm gonna start off with Gavin O'Mara asked,
since Life Day is now canon,
when are we getting a Batuu overlay
complete with grandpa Wookiees?
Life Day of course is the holiday celebrated
in the much maligned Star Wars holiday special.
From the 1970s, kind of a 70s variety hour special,
which I have never sat down and watched all the way through,
but I've heard is like, oh, will this be so good?
It's bad.
But I think I were talking about on the Night Call podcast
of like, no, it's not what you want it to be.
It's not that.
Parts of it are.
Yes.
I can narrate you through how to watch it
as the way people do it.
Like once the Star Wars in this order.
I think you gotta watch, it's the opening is really exciting
just to hear the names of like,
of Chewbacca's family and Lumpy.
Just like watch that opening is great.
Yeah.
And then watch the scene that's just various Chewbacca's
going, rrrr, rrrr, rrrr, rrrr.
It feels like 10 minutes of pure Chewbacca noises,
not subtitled.
And then the Jefferson Starship performance is fantastic.
And then anything where Harrison Ford is on screen,
because he's like the most gunpoint.
And then there's a thing when he was on late night
with Conan O'Brien and Conan like kind of devilishly implies
like, what if I were to tell you that I have a clip
of the holiday and then he fake strangles him
and then settles down and says a quote that I love,
which is, I don't know, I've never seen it.
Maybe it'll be nice.
I love that line.
That's actually my attitude too.
Yeah.
I think the mystery is better to have.
Oh, I also like Leia singing this inane life day song.
But yeah, I think it's good for a skip around.
I think if you sat and watched it, it's pretty miserable.
But.
But in reference to like, it's now canon
because it is mentioned, like I believe
in the first episode of the Mandalorian.
Yes, Horatio Sans mentions it.
And I think pretty quickly once Galaxy's Edge was open,
a lot of people are going like, when Christmas is coming,
are they gonna do life day?
And I kind of think it would be fun.
You know, there's a saying in improv
that there's no mistakes, only gifts.
And clearly they utilized it.
Like they mentioned it in the Mandalorian.
And honestly, I think if they did it in Batuu,
they could make it really fun.
Honestly, if Disney made a really good,
they could probably save,
they could probably do a new Star Wars holiday special
if they really made it good.
But I'd worry it would just be Megan Trainor
and Sting and Shaggy.
But I think there's probably like a fun version.
Like why not do it?
I mean, pass gas Mary Holland is in a crazy
Star Wars children's game show coming out.
Oh, that's right, yeah, that's coming out soon.
That sounds amazing.
She's a droid and Ahmed Best is the host.
Is the host like this?
It's kind of a Legends of the Hidden Temple
sounding show.
Which sounds like a blast.
Like that sounds wild. It really does.
Maybe we're, as we've expressed,
we just were in this hyperspace Hoopla episode.
We'd want Star Wars to be fun again.
And we do have pretty specific opinions
about what is acceptable Star Wars fun.
But I think some version of Life Day.
What is it though?
I mean, I don't think it would be like goofy.
I don't think it's gonna be like how they do
Halloween in Cars Land.
It would have to be,
I don't even want them to do something super silly.
I'm just even trying to picture like how do you,
I mean the fireworks look so good back there.
We're just, I mean, just doing some holiday lighting
and some tinsel around the Falcon.
Yeah, well Star Wars-y kind of tinsel and hanging stuff.
Right as we were done with the ordeal,
they put up some lights at Downtown Disney.
Have you seen these?
Yeah.
The circular lights around trees.
Oh yeah.
Neon and stuff.
I mean like just stuff like that even would give it
a little bit of a festive-y feeling.
Yeah.
Just changing the lighting as you're saying.
The marketplace seems ripe for some kind
of Christmas lighting.
And I have thought before how,
we've expressed this thing of like does,
I mean that initial Star Wars Galaxy's Edge visit
is so overwhelming but can you just do it again
and again and again and again?
And even like Rex, I have thought like,
well I love this loop and everything but at some point,
I'm gonna kinda want more loop.
Yeah.
So Rex's Christmas show would be.
Yeah, oh the Christmas Star Wars music for sure.
Yes.
Yeah.
And I would request that he play
the Jefferson Starship song, Light the Sky on Fire,
which is not Christmas related at all
but I consider it an official Life Day song.
Sure.
And Leia's pretty horrible.
It is just, if you guys seen that part,
it is just the Star Wars theme but like,
and we will come together now.
And I.
Yeah.
So they own the rights to that already.
I honestly, my opinion is you could get away
with making it a little goofy.
You could like, at night you could just like,
unfurl a big like weird Wookie banner
over those First Order banners and like decorate.
Like in the way that they've,
like in the way that Avatar land,
they've taken all the human bases
and like reclaimed them for the Navi.
You could just like put stuff on the First Order
Kylo Ren ship, like you could put lights,
string lights up on it.
You could put banners down and you could have like
a weird band, just like a Starship style band playing.
And I think people would love it.
I don't think.
Like non-violent resistant,
like the rebellion is doing this for fun.
Rebellion is one in this and it's Life Day
and like that's the narrative of it.
And I don't think anyone's gonna go in there and go,
well, this doesn't make sense between episodes eight and nine.
Like everyone's just gonna be like, oh, this is fun.
The lights are cool.
I like being here.
Yeah.
And is that Mickey Thomas?
Did they get him?
He frequently plays Epcot.
I mean, I do think it is like a fun way
to keep it fresh and interesting.
When we did the live show in LA the other night,
I met a guy who had just flown in from New Jersey
and it just went for the first time
and was like blown away by.
And I have to say, I was jealous of like,
oh, that's so cool.
You got to experience it for the first time.
And the more I thought about it, it's like,
well, the reason we can be critical of stuff.
And I try to have a reason when I'm being critical
is like, well, if you keep upkeep, you do a lot of it,
you keep it up well, it does feel like,
it gets you close to that feeling
of feeling it for the first time.
Sure, sure, sure, yeah.
I think they did a great job in Galaxy's Edge,
especially like the art direction and set decoration,
which is why I think they could do a really cool,
fun, tasteful version of the life day thing.
But the big thing that pretty much everyone is saying,
it's like the metaphor I have been using
is it's almost as if they built a beautiful theater,
like a Pantages or a Nederland,
they build a beautiful theater.
And for the play, most of the sets are there
and half of the actors.
You need the rest of the cast to do a full production.
We haven't acknowledged that thing
that at the Rise of the Resistance opening in Florida,
that there was this amazing lightsaber battle
up on the catwalks where we were promised
lightsaber battles all the time.
And there was a lot of reaction on Twitter,
like, well, imagine if this was happening all the time.
That's what they said it was gonna be.
And the X-wing drones.
That's very cool.
Which I think I saw somebody said they're on a truck,
they saw them on a truck to here for the opening.
So that's exciting.
We gotta try to get in that opening, that's a side note.
I gotta remind me to send an email.
Yeah.
I don't think that's gonna happen.
They're gonna ignore it, but I'd like to try.
You could try.
I would like to propose an original holiday character
that is a, you just have to,
it'd be like the same type of droid as BB-8,
but maybe with one more circle on the bottom.
And that's like a snowman.
Oh my God, that's so good.
That'd be great.
A triple layer BB-8 rolling around.
That's a, for sure.
Frost-E.
Frost-3, the snow droid.
I think once, well, Rise of Skywalker is out.
I have seen it at this point,
but I think once the dust is settled.
No complaints, right?
Zero complaints?
I think that I have, it's possible,
honestly, all kidding aside, it's possible I loved it.
I don't know.
It's possible.
Anything is possible.
But I think once-
It's a ambiguous silence from Jason and Scott.
It's too long for me to get into the,
my opinions on all this stuff is very nuanced.
I'm not some sort of hardline hater,
so I'm just saying there's no way for us to,
it's too long.
We have Christmas questions.
It's too long.
I'm just saying once nine is done,
I think the reigns will be loosened up
on the narrative of this area.
I think they're very much in the sense of like,
well, the movies are still going on,
we must preserve the tone of the movies at this point.
Mandalorian is implying maybe what the next era can be,
or it's a little, if there was,
if all of these movies have suffered under the weight of,
we have to bring it back and we have to do it right,
and it's gotta be, maybe now, yeah, you brought it back,
so can we chill?
Right, yes.
Let's just have Star Wars and be a little,
let's crazy about it.
So, Snowman BB-8, yeah, what about a Christmas tree droid?
Also.
Sure, yeah.
Yeah, that's fun.
We may as well do that, yeah.
I was thinking this morning of,
I was like, when did Force Awakens came out?
Force Awakens came out 2015, is that right?
Yes.
In five years, we got three main story Star Wars movies
and two spin-offs.
That's just so much.
Sure.
It's so much, I was just like,
man, that sure was a lot of Star Wars.
Even Eiger is saying it's too much.
And a TV show.
Eiger is like, I think maybe we hit the throttle too hard.
And I am more of a Marvel fan since I was a kid
than a Star Wars fan.
And maybe it's just because it's new characters,
every movie that then meet the old characters.
I don't know, I don't know.
But I think people in general might just be,
it just might have been too much.
Well, that's a whole-
And also, there's so much of everything.
People's attention is so precious,
so divided nowadays and so valuable.
That's a whole nother podcast.
It's a whole nother podcast.
Let's get to something about cookies.
We should holiday it up.
Yes, but I think, to answer your question,
yes, there can definitely be a fun version of Life Day.
You know that special that you showed a clip of
with Sting and Shaggy did have Portugal the Man
performing at the Millennium Falcon?
I saw that, scrubbing through it.
That was a full hour and a half special.
I barely got through it.
It was, I mean, it's a cool place for a band to play.
I don't know if I liked that so much, but...
Yeah.
I don't know why I even brought it up.
I'm just saying, a band performed holiday songs.
That might've been the first real holiday thing
at Galaxy's Edge.
Yeah, that's true.
Also, Portugal and the Man, a little more timely.
Portugal the Man, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
All right, on to more questions.
Okay, do you have anything, Mike, or are you gonna?
Oh, I mean, I can, yeah.
Let me see.
This year we learned about Sheridan Easter traditions,
Jelly Bean Trail.
Are there any fun, which I, you know,
I brought that up to Erin and she was like,
oh yeah, we did Jelly Bean Trail.
Wow, really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I think Jelly Bean Trail
was not so bizarre of a thing.
I brought it up to a lot of people and no one else has.
I thought Erin's the second one I've heard
of a Jelly Bean Trail.
I mean, it makes sense.
Yeah, it's a good idea.
But are there any fun Sheridan Christmas traditions
is the question.
I wrote this one down too.
That was from BD on Twitter who we met the other night.
It was at our show the other night.
I was right.
She was crazy.
The main one that stuck to me,
we do hang stockings at the fireplace.
With care?
With care.
Because the stocking holders we have
don't stand well on this fireplace.
So if you fill them, they will fall off.
But the big one that I insist on doing
is leaving two cookies and a glass of milk out for Santa.
I've kept the faith.
Still?
Still.
Let me ask you this.
Do you sneak out in the middle of the night
and eat those cookies?
I don't, but someone does.
Oh, fun.
That's nice.
I don't insist on having to buy a bag of carrots
to have something for the reindeer.
They'll just have to wait for another house.
We used to do that when we were real little.
I think we may have done a carrot one year,
but I don't know that.
My mom probably forgot.
Maybe we did it more, maybe I'm forgetting.
Yeah, we would leave the cookies and milk out.
Also, we insist, Christmas day snacks,
you gotta have the little smokeys rolled up
in like Pillsbury dough, like crescent rolls or biscuit roll.
With the little sausages?
The little sausage hot dog things.
For Christmas morning?
No, for like Christmas afternoon snacks before dinner.
Okay, so like as appetizers for Christmas dinner.
What is your Christmas dinner?
Back East outside of Philly,
everyone kind of does the same sort of thing
of like meatballs in the crock pot, honey glazed ham.
Excuse me, green bean casserole.
You're salivating just thinking about it.
Kind of a buffet, like a little,
you make a little buffet, you make a plate.
What else?
I'm trying to think of, yeah, we do stockings.
We've talked about it before.
You would get a citrus in your stocking or no?
That was like my grandfather's thing.
He would give us all orange,
like the citrus in the stocking.
That was a real treat.
Or a tangerine.
We would get a tangerine once in a while.
Now, also very easy to forget
if you don't immediately empty your stocking.
If you leave your stuff in your stocking for a little bit,
you will get a second gift of a moldy.
Use the citrus.
I don't know that that ever happened to us.
Did you forget an orange in a stocking when you were here?
Yes, yes.
Really?
You're referring to.
Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, yeah, I usually do Christmas Day at my mom's
and then 26 go down to my dad's
and do Christmas there too.
So, divorced kid, you get two Christmases.
Double presents?
Double presents, maybe.
Was it truly double presents?
Yes.
It was.
So was the same amount you would have gotten.
So the same amount you would have gotten at once
and then literally doubled.
It wasn't that they.
Yeah, but I didn't have like champagne.
I just wanted books and comics and stuff.
You would say you didn't have champagne taste for Christmas?
Yeah, I didn't have champagne taste.
I feel like a lot of kids I went to high school with
were getting like computers and cars and shit for Christmas.
Cars?
Yeah, I know like, I remember kids in high school.
It's like, yeah, he like totaled that Honda Civic
but his parents just got him a new one.
And it's like, in what world did that family live in?
I mean, I would once in a while get a video game system.
Honestly, maybe that happened once.
Maybe I got Nintendo.
Every few years we'd upgrade the systems.
My grandmother bought Super Nintendo
and then I saved up money for Nintendo 64.
So maybe I got a Game Boy as well one year.
Well, you know what I got twice was
we're going to Disney World in a couple days.
I got that when I was seven and nine.
A quick turnaround.
Those were my first two trips.
They were both like surprise
and it's in a few days, so get ready.
Wow.
Surprise and holiday season Disney World.
Twice.
That's pretty good.
That's great.
The first one I was just so caught off guard.
I didn't even know how to process.
And the second I wanted to weep, I'm like again?
Like how can I be seven and nine?
And then my sister who liked it a lot less
who was like much more overwhelmed.
She, I think the second year I was like, oh my God.
And she was like, no.
She cried because she had to go.
Oh no.
Oh wow.
So she needed consoling.
But I loved Disney World as much as like four kids
would.
My love was times four, any other child.
So that made up for that they were like terrifying
their daughter to have to go back.
Geez.
She made it through.
We all had fun.
Sure.
One more Sheridan tradition that I just do
to see how quickly my mom will notice it.
My one aunt got very into ceramics for a few years
and gave us ceramics like with like gift cards
a lot for years.
And one of them is what I call the Christmas seal.
And it's a seal that's painted all white
and it's got a little Santa hat on.
And a few times during the holiday season
I will swap that out with baby Jesus in the manger.
And Christmas seal will be in the nativity scene
until someone notices.
I do something similar to this in the last couple years
in the manger scene in my house.
I will find the beanie baby Hope that is praying.
It's the beanie baby that has its paws together
and its eyes closed.
And I will put Hope into the manger scene
next to Mary and Joseph and the wise men.
That's nice.
And I don't think it's that sacrilegious,
but I enjoy seeing a giant beanie baby
towering over everyone in the nativity.
That's fun.
I think as a kid I might've put Batman in there
and they were like, Scott, that's not funny.
That was scolded.
It's very cute that you like to do these kinds of things,
but not in this case.
Well, in a way Thomas and Martha Wayne died for our sins.
So Batman would protect us.
It's a good way to think about it.
I have one here.
I have a question from Rich McCarthy.
First question on the Facebook post.
And this came from a lot of people too,
but this is the first one I saw.
What other rides need a holiday overlay?
Well, we talked a little bit about this,
I think two years ago.
I think we were talking about doing the flight of passage
overlay where you would throw presents.
And I think we didn't come up with that.
I think our listeners said it should be called
like Feliz Navidad, which I think we were not clever enough
to think of.
So that one, I think the recap of that was that you would be
on the back of the mighty Akron,
but like there would be a VR component
where you'd throw presents as you were flying.
Oh, to distribute them to other.
So like Santa needed help and you were enlisted
on the back of the Akron.
So we got that one covered.
That's all I wanna say before.
Also on Twitter, somebody brought up,
Rich Uncle Skull and brought up King Kong
having a psanahat.
And he asked what would be the best goofy over the top.
I'm trying to think even like realistically,
cause there's like, what would they actually do?
Cause some of them, like I just mentioned,
I think that Halloween Cars Land thing is really adorable.
They do Christmas stuff too, right?
I believe so.
In the land, yeah.
Oh, they really deck out the land.
Not in the ride really.
There's been rumors of stuff on the ride,
but I don't think it's happened yet.
Well, in Credit Coaster and the baby Christ is lost.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
So, Edna is watching Christ.
And his baby's sitting.
Yeah, I'm not sure why Christ is in this,
or you just change all,
they're all like doing like an activity story essentially.
Yeah.
So Edna is like the innkeeper.
And so Bob and Helen are married Joseph.
So, does Christ just have Jack Jack's powers then
essentially and he is Christ giant at the end?
Yes.
Yeah.
Okay.
Cause Christ does, he has powers.
Jesus had powers.
And so maybe similar as a baby,
he didn't know how to harness them exactly.
And he was a mess and they're all coming out
in unexpected ways.
And I was not raised particularly religious,
but is one of Christ's powers a giant growing?
Is that, is he like giant man?
If you keep him in your heart and he grows big enough.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
So that's good.
The faith grows big enough.
Scott, I do have to say that is not funny.
I know.
I can never escape it.
Now that I'm thinking about it.
I'm sorry.
I do still have to watch the ride through
of this base mountain overlay they did with the,
the gridding with the green lights in Florida.
Oh yeah.
And they do tomorrow land speedway down there
and they get the jingle cruise.
I like the jingle cruise.
I'm sad they don't do it.
But the first year they did it out here was nothing.
Yeah.
And then the second year was just Santa hats on everybody.
But I think they went a little bigger.
What's the, did you know what the difference is?
I don't really know.
I mean, they do different jokes.
Everyone's got Santa hat.
There's pleasant presence floating in the water.
I don't dislike it.
I was just a little underwhelmed the first time
I went on it.
But maybe they're really doing it up in Florida.
You can work backwards from the name
cause jingle cruises.
So that's almost the main reason to do it is jingle cruise
is so good.
So like, forgive me.
I don't have this sorted out yet,
but it's like the rock,
the rocking around the Christmas tree coaster.
Oh yeah. That's good.
It's gotta be an Aerosmith version of it.
They would have to, did Aerosmith do any Christmas?
I think they must have at some point.
You would think.
Yeah. So that, that, and then you just make all the lights.
He's got a new hat, a Santa hat.
A Santa hat.
Check out Steven Tyler's Santa hat.
Yeah. And then you could change the radio station
to like Christmas radio.
That seems easy.
Yeah.
Anything where it's mainly music.
Oh, guardians.
Guardians I feel like, yeah.
The holiday overlay for that is one of my favorites.
Yeah. You just need to change the lighting scheme
on the outside to red and green,
which they change it for the Halloween,
which I think looks very cool when it's just purpley.
There's a lot of colors going on at night
for the regular version.
There's kind of like four color.
It's like green, blue, maybe orange.
I forget, but then it's mostly like dark purple,
which is real cool.
So make it red and green.
And then we just need a new narrative reason
to go back in, I guess.
Like there's maybe a Christmas tree monster
the collector has.
Teaching the collector about Christmas.
Like a grinch sort of angle.
Yeah, but you don't want, we can't get Benicio for that
to shoot more video.
So we need it to be just like a monster
like in the Monsters After Dark, I feel like.
So you can make Groot and Rocket CGI,
cause the actors, they're busy.
They can't.
Oh, like, yeah, they can just use those.
Well, is Groot a Christmas tree?
Very good.
Do you know how to stop a Christmas tree?
Oh yeah, maybe it's, yeah.
Should, okay.
Yeah, so Groot, maybe a rogue Groot
is like kind of overgrown
and looks like an evil Christmas tree.
And they have to get, they have to stop him.
Yeah.
And it's Rocket and Groot
fighting with a Christmas tree monster.
That's pretty cool.
Now, how about this?
The Guardians of the Galaxy holiday special.
And you go to a planet full of Rockets,
a planet full of.
Are you just pitching a TV show?
I'm trying, I think I can meld it into the ride.
I think like if you had to get Rocket
back to his family to celebrate,
like they're like kind of,
cause they're a little irreverent.
Sure, but you will pitch this as a show.
I mean, it could be a show,
but I think you can meld it into the ride.
I think there's a version of it in the,
like if the ride is making fun of the holiday special.
It's a little less exciting.
So you're just saying like,
instead of like exciting action,
we open up and then there's just a family reunion of Rockets
and then we drop.
You go to one floor only and then like,
Ma, I missed you Ma.
I'm sorry, I ain't always been the son that I wanna be.
Special on Disney plus seems like the,
yeah, the easier version of it, I guess.
I don't know.
I like your version where you go up in the elevator
and you just watch a special for 30 minutes
and then the elevator slowly goes back down.
And then to us, the child is born.
Yeah, and he like gives the-
Raccoon child, don't call me a raccoon.
Rocket Raccoon gives the Linus speech
in the Charlie Brown special.
Lights, please.
Yeah, and then you just watch it up there
and there's just no, it's not exciting at all.
It's just watching a nice little movie.
But they drop you once at the end,
like, oh, we're late, we're late for the friends Christmas.
We're late for the potluck on the spaceship.
They just drop you.
Well, I think it's different plots in every,
that's what's- That's good.
In one, it's still like an up and down.
It's inviting a tree monster.
And then the other, you slowly ascend
and essentially go to mass.
Let's take it all the way that it's like,
you with Rocket and his family attend an hour long mass
at the top of the tower.
And then slowly come back down.
That one has to be slow, just out of respect.
Because that's a ride that elderly people can go on
till you want all ages to be able to.
It's our first, like picturing roadie in front of something.
It's like, and this is our first attraction in Latin.
This is-
We all, the team of Imagineers all had to learn,
we all studied for three years
so that we could accurately write dialogue in Latin.
Yeah.
I like that we're putting a lot more religion
into the park with these two overlays.
That's the main thing we want, clearly.
Yeah.
Well, that's good.
What do we, hmm, what mall in Glendale
should you do your Christmas shopping?
Says Americana at brand memes.
Oh, come on.
Oh, very gay, you know, let's give the Galleria some love.
Yeah, the Galleria.
How about that?
I say Galleria, yeah.
How about that other, how about like the,
it's like the marketplace or something
that has like the Rubio's and the Michaels
and the Cost Plus, how about that?
How about we don't even go anywhere near your Americana
and your Galleria, take that Americana brand memes.
The Galleria's enclosed and we have rainy spells
and cold snaps and the winter here in LA, so.
Plus they've got a big old Dunkin' Donuts
in the Galleria now.
They've, they've, yeah, very good, yes.
Desserts and treats, I'm sure there's nowhere
to get those at the Americana.
And-
We won this argument, great.
Mike, what do you have on Instagram?
Anything over there?
I'm looking, a lot of people asking about the overlay.
This is not, well, this is not a holiday question.
Have you ever tried to sneak alcohol into the park?
This person, Frank Potts, 81, did on Halloween.
Answer, no, I've never tried it.
A friend of ours tried, brought it in
and a couple months ago when we were there,
I won't out-hood it was.
What?
We were with a friend of ours.
Was I there?
I believe you were there.
And he had like a soda bottle.
And you're not gonna out him even though this is a thing
that no one could possibly get in trouble for.
I mean, I will.
It's not bad to do.
I will, it's Andrew Grissom.
It's Andrew Grissom, yeah, yeah, I thought so, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I was like, oh wow.
I think Kyle brought it up when he was here.
I think they'll still sneak bottles in.
I don't think it's that crazy.
I only haven't done it because I look forward
to Disney's beer and wine selections so much.
That's right, me too.
McCarthy Manhattan.
We figured out how to make McCarthy Manhattans.
Could I just take a thermos of them around the park?
Sure, would that be disgusting?
Probably.
That honestly, that is the dorkiest reason, but it is true.
Why sneak in alcohol when I could enjoy what they have?
I don't think since I've been handed my undergraduate degree,
I've snuck alcohol into anything.
Not like a movie theater.
Sometimes I'll like, if it's a theater
that doesn't offer booze,
because movie theaters will always give you
just a cup of ice and then you can,
then you're not paying some $19.
Oh, I suppose, yeah, maybe.
But honestly, I hate fiddling in the dark at movies.
I like to get everything,
I would rather have a drink beforehand
or something beforehand and then go sit down.
I like to be, I like to sit very still and watch a movie.
So I like to drape my coat over, like myself,
like a little blanket and then if I have a drink.
You drape a coat over yourself?
I get cold very easily at movies.
Yeah, I turn my coat around and I have a little blanket.
I've been to many movies with you.
I don't recall seeing you snuggled up in your own coat.
Well, it's usually more mild out here.
Why not wear the coat?
It's not the same effect.
It's not the same, I like to be cozy.
It's cozier.
If you go backwards with it,
it's more like a snuggie or something.
Yeah, kind of, I think I feel.
But if you zip the jacket up,
wouldn't it be the same as far as keeping in heat?
I suppose, but I think it's a psychological thing
more than it's. It is, like, yeah,
no, I'm not disputing that.
Yeah, but if I have candy or,
I like to get that set and not really,
I turn my phone all the way off.
I don't like to fiddle around in the movies.
But do you ever have,
but do you ever just have a drink with you?
Yeah, I have a drink.
Like movie, popcorn or soda or candy is,
I'm okay with that.
Or if I'm passing something back and forth,
that is the maximum amount of fiddling.
But when you're in a movie and you were to sneak alcohol
in which I'm trying to even think of,
I've done it maybe, maybe,
you wouldn't be sneaking a flask in and out of your coat.
You can just put it in the drink.
No one's coming by to sniff your drink.
I guess so.
Yeah, and you can, and if you're just,
if you bring just a beer can in,
that's just a quick pop.
That's not like a.
It's like drink, like in the middle of the movie.
All right, drink inspector here.
Some guy goes up and down the aisle,
like sniffing every drink.
When we went to go.
You with the blanket jacket, you're busted.
Get out of here.
Honestly, I think when we went to go see like end game,
when we went to go see a slightly out of focus end game.
Yeah, oh yeah, that was out of focus, yeah.
The projector bulb needed to be changed end game.
And we went to McGuffin's and I got like a Jameson
and ginger ale.
I think that was the first time I had a drink in the movies.
At McGuffin's, yeah.
Really, they have it wait anywhere?
Yeah, I've been to like an Alamo draft house style one
and I think I just got food.
I just need to drink, at least have some water
during the movie.
Like I drink a lot of water during the day
or else I get a headache.
So you aren't movie drinkers.
No.
I mean, I go to McGuffin's,
I know I've had a drink from McGuffin's I'll bring in.
I don't recall if I've snuck.
I don't think so.
I did sneak alcohol into a wrestling show.
Although now that I think about it,
I just sort of drank it quickly on the street, like a bum.
Oh boy.
Because I didn't wanna get caught.
The prices were.
You're a little too worried about getting caught.
Well, they pat you down sometimes at the show.
So I just didn't wanna have,
that might've been an issue.
So this one was just mostly like,
it's so expensive there.
If you're, I think it was a battle of Los Angeles
where it was like three days in a row.
And I'm like, if I add up like beers,
I'm just like one of these days,
I'm just gonna be a scumbag one of these days.
A scumbag.
It's your scumbag if you sneak alcohol in
and you didn't wanna out our friend
for having a water bottle with two sips of rum in it.
I think I was being nice to him.
Too nice maybe.
You can argue that, fair.
But no, he's a scumbag.
He's fucking scumbag.
He's a scumbag like me.
He makes a point of not listening to the podcast
even though it's in the Facebook group.
So hey, somebody listening to this who knows him,
pass along you and your alcohol water bottle.
You're a scumbag.
Yeah, yeah, let him know.
Let him know.
I have a general hotly question I told you.
Question for you guys and also for the listeners.
Something that I got on, I've always wondered,
but especially yesterday,
I tried it at Trader Joe's.
Do your guys' family, do you know what panettone is?
It's that sort of, it's Italian Christmas bread
and it's the one that comes in a little box.
No.
Have you ever seen this?
It sounds familiar but I haven't done it.
So every Italian deli back east
has boxes and boxes and boxes of this stuff
for the holidays and Trader Joe's
has giant displays of it nowadays.
And I have some here.
I got a mini one yesterday.
If anyone wants to try any,
but it's literally just like kind of a sweet bread.
Like I cut a chunk off.
You just have a little tin foil.
I have a little tin foil.
A tiny amount of bread.
And it's got like candyed raisins,
like raisins and like dried oranges in it
if anyone wants to try any.
It's not the most appealing display.
No, it looks gross.
It does look great.
It looks gross.
But it's like-
If you really want us to do it, I will do it.
It's kind of nothing.
And I think it's like a holdover.
I think it's a tradition that's like a holdover
before people figured out how to make like sweets.
Like it's fine.
Try it.
Just rip off a piece.
All right, fine.
It's like, this isn't amazing.
But if any listeners like was a panettone-
Has this been in your car or was this in-
It was just on like a kitchen counter.
And then I put it in my bag.
It kind of reminds me a little of Pan de Muertos,
the bread of the dead from day of the dead,
but without the liquorice kind of flavor.
Oh, wait, I forgot you had wax paper like an idiot.
I don't know.
Do what you will, Scott.
Oh, I made something similar to this.
Yeah, I guess it's the Italian equivalent of fruitcake.
All right.
That's fine.
But it's just so-
Why are we eating this?
It's so ubiquitous back East.
I was just wondering like if you guys had done it,
cause I was just like, it's, again,
the Trader Joe's display was huge at the Burbank one.
Okay.
And multiple flavors.
I mean, I think they had like,
this was just the individual sized one
and I didn't want to get a giant like,
I'm sure the caramel one or chocolate one
is a little more fun.
Uh-huh.
Scott, any thoughts?
This was all your attempt to make that
a panettone of the business expense.
You can write it off.
This one-
Talked about it on the show.
199.
Yeah, it's out of it.
You said that.
You like made, you sent a special email to an accountant.
Every two dollars.
So just so you know, when you see that $2 charge,
that is, we did talk about,
and here's a file and I'll also give you a free month
on the Patreon so you hear it.
All right, are we done with the bread?
Yeah, that's fine.
But listeners, tweet at me, like, if you're like,
no, this was a big thing for us.
This is a big,
clearly it's called Italian Christmas bread.
So clearly it's a thing that some Italian families,
but it just seems so odd.
It's like, here is a cake in like a box,
like a cardboard paper box.
There's somebody on Instagram, Mel Schneff,
who is asking us to review something called
Text Me Merry Christmas,
which is a Mickey and Minnie friends show,
maybe at Disney World that I don't know about,
which I think we should just put a pin in to look into.
Text Me, yeah, that's the way, that's a live show.
I believe that she's, she's been costuming the show
four times a night since rehearsal in mid October.
Okay.
So we'll have to look into that.
Yeah, yeah, well that requires some research.
You have something?
Not, not especially.
I mean, I have another thing.
It's not holiday.
Sure.
Rate Hall of Presidents, Carousel of Progress,
and Great Moments with Mr. Lincoln
based only on animatronic hotness,
asked by Coward, Coward Lantis.
Wait, wait, what were they again?
Hall of Presidents, Carousel of Progress,
and Great Moments with Mr. Lincoln
based only on animatronic hotness.
That's weird because there's so many for the occasional.
You know, you wouldn't, okay,
Hall of Presidents has to go down there
because like, while I, while maybe Lincoln himself
is a little handsome, Lincoln is,
obviously we all agree Lincoln is very handsome.
Yeah, of course.
But Lincoln has his own thing, which is in the list.
And then like, when you think about
who is like kind of a handsome president,
if you consider Obama a handsome president,
the animatronic is not.
That's a really, that's a particularly inaccurate.
And would I be the first ever to point out
that the Trump animatronic is creepy?
I'm not sure anyone's made that observation,
but I will. I have noticed.
So you got to dock your points for that.
And then like hotness, I got to include Carousel of Progress,
which has like miners in it.
Well, you don't have to rate the miners, I guess.
Let's take them out of the equation.
Take the miners out of the equation.
Are we just mainly talking John?
I mean, we're talking John.
John and his wife.
And his wife is very fetching.
Uncle.
Uncle Orville.
The drunk who's drying out in a bathtub.
Hot.
Is he, is Orville hot?
I don't know.
I think John is maybe era appropriate hot.
I think he's the least hot in the last scene,
in the 90s scene.
He looks creepy.
The daughter's in college in one scene.
She gets to college.
Well, I still don't need to talk about
a college girl's hotness on this show.
Yeah, it's probably that.
Well, and that whole attraction is full of the dad
kind of like offering her up to be ogled.
So. That's true.
We got to stay away from that.
So.
Let's just, what era of John is the hottest?
Jason, you should have an opinion about this.
Yeah.
I mean, he's kind of a little more of a,
a little more distinguished in the last one,
a little older.
You like him in the 90s.
I think he's the least hot in the 90s.
I was going to say, I think he's too clean cut in the 90s.
I think kind of like the 50s,
there might be a little bit of a Don Draper kind of
more vibe to him then, you know?
I don't know.
They seem pretty identical to me,
but maybe if style supports hotness,
then probably more fifth,
it's not in the 50s, it's more like 40s, right?
Whatever era he's not like waving himself with a paper fan,
because I don't think you could be considered,
well, you're literally hot.
He's literally, yeah.
When I think about what is a hot man,
I don't think of like, oh my, the vapors.
I don't associate that with hotness.
90s Sarah in like her business casual glasses.
Sure.
I gotta say.
Wait, is Sarah his wife?
Yeah.
Jason loves John's wife on the carousel of progress.
He called her fetching a minute ago.
Fetching.
She's fetching?
We're trying to just write John and he keeps calling,
but yeah, but Sarah, have you seen Sarah?
I think the two of them together.
Oh, you want to do a three thing.
I might be the unicorn.
You have these things threesome, snail.
Have you heard about her work?
Sarah and I are thinking of joining a polycule.
It's a triad.
We're looking for what they call a third.
Anyone out there?
Sarah and I are on this thing, bumble.
Yeah, you can put in your specifications
of what you're looking for.
One of these things, key parties.
Usually use that bowl to make a jello mold,
but I guess you put all your keys in it
and that's how you figure out
how you're going to have sex with someone.
Sure.
Say to my lady friend, this is John and Sarah
and we'd all go out to dinner and have some drinks.
And what do you guys do?
Oh, we're animatronics from a revolving robot show.
I thought you looked familiar.
Yeah, that's me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're a senior.
Do you know the song?
I'll just do the song.
There's a great big.
Oh, yeah, of course.
You don't have to do the song.
We don't want to put you on the spot.
I'm looking through John's looks
and a lot of the closeups are a bit harrowing,
a bit terrifying.
But as far as his look that maybe now makes
is like the most modern is definitely what I think the 50s.
He's got the sweater, the dress shirt
and then he's kind of got kind of a neckerchief thing
going on it looks like, which I appreciate.
But yeah, this one, that's kind of too old timey for me.
That's the fan, a Niagara Falls fan.
Yeah.
I'm gonna say no on that.
I do like this look.
I think that's the worst look, honestly,
is the, and then this look is the first one,
which I like, but maybe not that hot.
A green sweater.
It's a smoking jacket.
Yeah, smoking jacket.
So I do like that look.
And then the 50s is this basic sweater combo
with his neckerchief.
Anyway.
Let's, we don't have too much more time.
I think we should do some quick hits.
I think there's a couple of questions
or Jason R Gallagher is one,
but there's a few variations of just favorite song
from Country Bear Christmas.
Country Bear Christmas.
Here's honest, the truth about Country Bear Christmas.
I haven't watched it all the way through
because I wanna be fresh when I see it one day.
I have not watched all of it.
So I cannot give you a good assessment.
I may have to watch it if we do the full,
no, we don't have to.
We don't have to do all the Country Bears.
So I will try, I'm gonna try to see it in Japan
at some point, which I know is crazy
because how often am I gonna get to Japan?
You have to go to Japan during Christmas.
That's true now that I'm thinking about it.
So maybe it's dumb
that I haven't watched it all the way through,
but I could not answer that question.
I can answer the, yeah.
Saving it.
Let me see.
Anybody saying anything you like?
A couple of questions of favorite Christmas treats.
I'm a big chocolate chip cookie guy
and I like pecan pie.
Oh, and eggnog.
Kind of just eggnog.
We always had eggnog growing up without the liquor.
I really drank it with the liquor,
but I am an eggnog fan.
Chocolate chip cookies, yeah, I like them.
My mom makes like, she makes usually four cookies,
chocolate chip, snickerdoodle,
which I've never been a huge fan of,
though maybe I need to get into,
maybe I need to try again this year.
Then she makes something called melting moments,
which are very good and I've always liked.
And I should.
What are we talking?
I honestly, I'm trying to think they're,
let's see what the recipe is.
I'll just read that on the air.
They look like this basically.
They're like kind of butter cookies essentially.
They look like these.
Oh, sure, yeah.
Which I've always been.
They're a little rich, so maybe you can't have too many,
but those have always been my favorites
in addition to the chocolate chip cookies.
But I'm not, I don't have a ton.
If people are having eggnog,
but it's not like a thing I need.
I don't need it.
Beth Strutz asks, best Disney Christmas special?
Movie, TV show, episode or whatever.
I, every Christmas Eve watch Muppets Christmas Carol
and skip around because the video cassette
has a song in it that is literally called The Love Is Gone
that Ebeneezer's young fiance,
when she breaks off their engagement, they sing.
Oh, that's right.
And it's brutal.
It was left out of the theatrical release,
but then put on the home video one.
And the Ghost of Christmas Future sequence is terrifying.
So you skip those?
I usually skip the song,
but I will watch the Ghost of Christmas Future
unless it's getting late.
I wanna go to bed.
Sometimes you get tuckered out.
I don't know if you'd have called this
an official Disney Christmas special,
but they probably own it to some extent.
And you know when it was aired, I think,
in magical world of Disney kind of slot.
Muppet Family Christmas, my favorite thing ever.
That's my favorite Muppet thing literally
where Sesame Street comes and Fraggle Rock
and they're all part of it.
And especially we're recording this
just in the wake of Carol Spinney's passing,
the person who played Big Bird and Oscar the Grouch,
and that's very sad.
And just like every once in a while, I will remember,
and I was recalling this right before he passed,
how the part of the special where the Swedish chef
is trying to cook Big Bird,
but then Big Bird gives him a bird seed
that's like a gift because your family's
all the way back in Sweden.
When Big Bird is actually taking the time to think,
Swedish chef is here alone in his Swedish family,
he doesn't get to be with them.
I've never considered the family
of this very broad, silly character.
And then they sing, have yourself a Merry Christmas,
but he sings it in blurgy, blurgy.
But it is such a sweet, wonderful,
great Carol Spinney performance,
the reveal when the turkey goes like,
get a load of this, and then there's a lightning strike
and he sees a giant bird and salivates.
That whole scene is written very funny,
performed very funny in RIP Carol Spinney.
Yeah, honestly, that was my answer,
even though it might not officially be Disney.
But just that, the meeting, and that's the only saddest,
I mean, there's been little crossovers here and there,
but that's the big, that's the end game crossover
that you want.
Like I've said it before, no movie where people
from multiple worlds meet is as fun and as satisfying as,
and something like that, what an unexpected character team up.
Why would you, you don't need to service,
Big Bird has to meet the Swedish chef,
but it is so funny that it happens.
And that's the fun of any of these things,
these crossovers, you know?
Like, so yeah, early on, I think Flintstones
meet the Jetsons I really like too,
but I think this one was even more impactful to me.
When somebody asked Muppet Christmas,
Paul Reagan said Muppet Christmas Carol,
Muppet Family Christmas or other.
I watch and love both every year, us too, apparently, Paul.
I thought, I remember laughing so hard,
my stomach hurt once when I first saw the Swedish chef.
I thought that was, he, as a character,
him like crazy cooking, trying to get a bird,
like I thought he was so funny.
And honestly, it is still very funny to me.
Like it still holds up.
We're probably gonna wind down here.
Anybody seeing anything you're dying to get out?
Let me see.
A few questions about the fake snow in Disney parks.
What about it?
And other play with fans, I like it.
I think it's fun.
Fake snow?
Like the fake snow coming down on Main Street.
Is it soap?
What is it?
Do we know?
It's kind of a soapy.
I think Disney's is fine,
but I feel like I've been amidst other fake snow
that is unpleasant.
So you just gotta be careful
what you're making it out of.
Oh, here's a quick one from Jeff Stewart.
Is Christmas shoes the worst Christmas song of all time?
Yeah, it's a little grim.
Yeah, I don't know.
There's no way it's the worst, though.
Yeah.
It's entertaining.
It's a journey.
It's something.
Yeah, I don't know.
You have a favorite Christmas song, maybe?
That's a good question.
As a kid, it was always like
rocking around the Christmas tree, I think.
I always liked the ones that felt more modern.
Yes, yeah.
I had a little playlist going at the live show
the other night, and I think my current answer
has to be Ray Parker Jr.'s Christmas Time Is Here.
Oh, I don't even know.
I don't think I've heard that.
It was such a delight.
It's one of the only legit, good, smooth R&B.
There's also this new edition Christmas album
that's fantastic.
Six original songs all done like super Casio synth.
I gotta hear that.
So, Elb 6 are a delight.
Christmas rapping by the waitresses I've always liked.
I like the McCartney.
Me, too.
Yeah.
It's nice.
I think some people don't like that.
I can't believe it's an argument.
Why am I blanking on it?
Wonderful Christmas Time.
It's so nice.
What?
There's a big, she likes just the 20 songs
that play at Christmas, and I'm always trying
to find other stuff for, I found Back Door Santa.
Have you heard this song?
No.
It's, hold on, let me find it.
It's really not much of a Christmas song.
It's really about Back Door Santa coming in
and having an affair with all the mothers in town,
but it is on the Christmas compilation.
This is by Clarence Carter, who did the song Stroken,
and it's great, and I love it.
What?
It's here, you'll hear a little of it.
The way I described it makes it sound worse
than it really is.
You know, I think, oh.
Oh, this song, wait, this sample is famous.
Yeah.
Is this the sample in the Ren DMC?
Oh, maybe.
Oh, this song, okay.
I mean, it is.
I thought it was a novelty song,
like a redneck comedian singing,
like Back Door Santa, get to the outhouse.
Like I was worried that's what it was gonna be.
No, no, this is a soul.
This is soul, baby, this is funk and soul.
I have an oddball.
I always, at the church I grew up going to,
an older guy every Christmas would sing a solo
of Oh Holy Night and would just belt it,
and it was always like very moving.
And most versions of that are not like belt it,
but this guy like had the deepest voice.
And it was, yeah.
Oh, Johnny.
And was not a professional singer,
but was just naturally very gifted.
And yeah, that was always nice.
There's a Kenny Rogers, Dolly Parton album
that I like, Christmas album that I like.
Full album?
Yeah.
There's a Bare Naked Ladies Christmas album that I like.
You gotta respect the whole album.
The whole album.
A big song.
They have their song from the Grinch,
it's called Green Christmas,
which is a pretty good original Christmas song.
Some of them are covers and a few are original.
This has not aged well.
I think people have covered this
and fixed the one word in it,
cause it's so brutal,
but Fairy Tale of New York by the Pogues is a great song,
but there's one moment that is just so awful.
Like that is aged.
But I think when people do covers of it now,
they take that out.
They slide something out,
but a very complicated song.
I wanna give some love to the in sync,
Merry Christmas,
happy holiday.
Yeah, that's kinda nice.
That reminds me of Christmas at the mall.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Having a nice time shopping.
I just found a music video for it
that is the cheapest shit.
In sync was spending a lot of money on music videos
at the time,
and for this one it was just like,
oh God, we got three hours, crap.
There's a Gary Coleman cameo,
he's like an elf,
and then it's all them flying on a green screen.
It is such a green screen closet.
I don't know why they couldn't have done this better.
Video's terrible, song's wonderful.
They did a whole Disney Christmas special,
they performed that in front of the Chinese theater.
I think the newest song,
I was listening to Country Christmas,
and there's a George Strait song.
Probably, maybe it's a cover called Christmas Cookies,
that sounds a lot like Red Solo Cup,
which is a song I legitimately think is good.
A very fun song.
And maybe he just ripped it off, I don't know,
or it was the opposite,
maybe Red Solo Cup ripped this off,
I have to look into it,
but Christmas Cookies by George Strait.
It's good, it's fine.
I'm quite familiar.
I feel like I wanna go out with one more audience,
has anybody seen one?
Yeah, so many people asked,
thanks, sorry we didn't get to everything.
Yeah, thank you for asking.
Country Bear questions.
Let's see here.
Oh, oh, you're in.
Blair Kuhnsmith, sorry I'm butchering your name,
do you all put out any parks related Christmas decorations?
If so, what is your favorite?
Don't I have a lot of,
my Christmas tree ornaments are a lot of key chains
that come from theme parks.
Oh, that's cute.
Yeah, actually I think I got a key chain
from Galaxy's Edge on opening day that's up on the tree now.
Oh, that's fun.
My mom gave me a, it's like Christmas,
Disney World 1989 that she found at an antique store.
And that's good.
My dad has a Lucy the Elephant Christmas ball.
Man, we should do a quick second gate on Lucy the Elephant.
It's a giant novelty elephant,
like three story elephant built on the beach
in Atlantic City that has been at multiple times,
like an eccentric rich person's house,
it's been a hotel, now it's a tourist attraction.
If you see picture of like Atlantic City
as like a quick mention that's often the image
even though it's right outside of the city
and it's a big elephant with the thing you ride in on top
and you go inside of it, there's different rooms in it.
Weird, I don't know about this.
It goes back to the novelty,
when novelty architecture was very big.
But it survived multiple hurricanes and ocean surges
and that sort of thing.
Wow. Yeah.
Yeah.
Holiday ornaments?
Yeah, I'm trying to think.
It's usually just stuff I already had displayed
in a different way.
Last year I put Swing and Teddy Bear
at the top of the tree.
Oh, that's right.
But Lindsay was like, it's too big.
So now she's just at the bottom of the tree.
But it's usually just repurposing stuff
I'm already displaying in the Christmas presentation.
A friend from college once sent me,
this isn't theme parky, but it's kind of adjacent.
It's one of our adjacent ones.
I think it was bought at the Cracker Barrel gift shop
and it is Santa in a bright orange hunting vest
and a woodland camo.
And that's insane.
That's a very American Christmas sort of it.
How about this?
This is, if I want to go ahead on, from Ryan Ritter.
If the Universal Studios stairway, Starway,
had a Christmas overlay,
much like when it becomes the haunted stairway,
what do you imagine it would be like?
Like, hey, you know, like, hey, you know,
tinsel and Christmas trees allowed,
but other kinds of green, keep it in your pocket.
That includes me.
I was going, I'm gonna go the traditional Christmas route
and it tells you the story of-
Back door Santa just started playing.
Back door Santa's sneaking back into the podcast.
Because it is a little long,
it tells you the story of Joseph and Mary
returning to Bethlehem for the Roman census.
He tells his story.
And then the ride back up is them trying to check in
to the inn and there is no room at the inn
and then the wise men arrive.
So instead of the regular Billy Bush,
it's like, but please, my wife is with child.
Every room is full, but you can go to the barn.
And then you arrive and like,
You arrive.
And don't forget to check out the Simpsons ride
and Cletus's fried chicken.
Try the crazy milkshakes on the lower lawn.
So that is another, we want to put more religion
in the park.
Yeah, there were some questions
about how you can relate to the park.
Yeah.
So mainly that it's the, yeah,
the starway should be a place of prayer.
Can't it be both?
Can't it be that voice with jokes
while he's telling the nativity?
Oh, there you go.
But he's also being like, a savior was born.
Isn't that crazy or whatever?
Gold frankincense and can't smoke that shit.
I am totally forget.
I fucked this up.
Okay, on the way down, it's the entire,
the greatest story ever told.
It's the story about the birth of the Christ child
on the way back up.
It's the Maccabees keeping the candle lit
for eight days and nights.
It's the Hanukkah story.
We have represented Hanukkah very poorly.
So yes, great.
So there's some like very small representation
of Hanukkah in the parks.
Somebody was asking on Instagram and I can't find it.
So I apologize where I can't see, I can't find your name.
But he was saying that he was wondering
if there's a better chance they'll see life day
in the parks than an actual like Hanukkah celebration
or true representation.
Because that's our generation's religion,
Star Wars.
Star Wars, yeah.
Good point.
Guaranteed.
It would be nice to get more Hanukkah,
more blue and white in the parks.
Like that would be very fun.
Although I believe in the Jewish tradition
is not one of the major holidays,
a second more secondary holiday,
but it's kind of replaced Christmas.
So why is it only Grinchmas?
Why can't we also celebrate Grinchica?
Grinchica should happen.
Yeah, both.
Why not?
There's plenty of time in December, do both.
Yeah.
That's, yeah.
Is that, would they?
That's crazy.
Would people be happy about that?
I don't know.
The Jewish church be upset?
I'm not sure.
I mean, if it's the same deal
and he's like trying to steal Hanukkah
and then who teaches him why Hanukkah is nice,
then that's good.
That encourages more participation in Hanukkah.
Okay, you're right.
Yeah.
All right, so get on it, I guess.
Grinchica.
Yeah.
I'm going to loot all those temples.
Yeah, you cannot.
He's stealing the candles on the menorah one by one
as the song plays.
Chocolate coins.
I'm going to flush them down the toilet
and not enjoy them myself.
If it's them teaching, yes,
it has to be them teaching him the importance
and the wonderful story of Hanukkah.
He cannot be, he cannot be Jewish trying to stop Christmas
because that gets very problematic.
Just so we're clear, he is learning that Hanukkah,
like the story of Hanukkah,
just as he learned the story of Christmas.
This isn't a sequel where they say at the beginning,
oh, so something we forgot to tell you last time,
the Grinch is Jewish.
Yeah.
No, none of that.
I haven't, unless they're not doing it this year.
Last year, of course, everyone remembers
I did a heart-stopping interview with the Grinch
around Christmas time at Universal.
I know I haven't been invited to another one,
but if for some reason I get an invite last second here,
maybe I will ask him, what do you think about Grinchica?
Propose the idea of Grinchica.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
And that is when you are quickly ushered out
because the parts did not take a firm stand on any
world religions, political events, and it's,
we're the best.
I've been waiting.
Grinchadon.
I've been waiting to get kicked out of a theme park
and that'll be the first time.
That'll be why.
God, see him.
What is your opinion on God?
Is God real, Mr. Grinch?
Decide once and for all
for the sake of the Universal Movie Company.
Then they, if he could throw him down the char way.
Well, you know, God is dead.
Throw him down and don't even give him an ounce of weed.
No weed.
All right.
Well, Merry Christmas, everybody.
We'll be back to you soon in the new year,
very soon in the new year to celebrate a little anniversary.
We've got a fun thing.
I think we're at the very beginning of 2020
and it's going to be a great 2020.
Enjoy some mediocre Italian box bread
with your loved ones and-
Take your jacket, snuggle up and see a nice movie.
See Rise of Skywalker if you haven't.
Turn your jacket around.
Snuggle up and thanks for surviving podcasts
throughout all year with us.
We'll see you soon.
Happy holidays.