Forever.
Dog.
Warning, this episode was recorded months ago and references the Scorsese Marvel war that
sadly never went away.
But don't worry, we also talk about Shrek's children, Farkle, Fergus and Felicia.
PTR legend Griffin Newman joins us to talk Shrek 4D.
Better out than in, it's podcast, The Ride.
Welcome to podcast, The Ride, the only podcast presented in digital stereophonic ogre sound.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan, thank you.
Hello.
Mike Carlson.
I'm Jason Sheridan, I'm a director and I'm in ogre sound as well.
Yeah, I'm always, not just this episode, we're always in ogre sound.
Because today we are continuing the 3D film symposium and I'm so happy we get to do it
and that our guest for this series is back once again from the Tic and Blank Check, Griffin
Newman.
We're closing out the trilogy, the wait is ogre, one could say.
Wow, yes it is ogre.
That was the tagline for one of them, for three or four.
I think so, yeah.
Because you did have to wait, there was three years in between each Shrek movie.
Animation takes a while.
It takes a while, it took even longer when this first one came out.
I heard a crazy stat which is that Katzenberg was, you know, anytime they found any degree
of success with any Dreamworks property he would just milk it from every angle possible,
as quickly as possible.
And they went into production on Shrek 2 two months after Shrek 1 came out.
Geez.
Wow.
Which I wonder if they were so confident that they had a script ready or if he was like,
you have two months to give us a script that is ready to start animation.
Or he just walked into the animators and was like, start animating, what do you want us
to do?
It doesn't matter, Shrek's involved, he farts and the donkey's there.
There is a story that I think it's Dan Harmon talked about on an episode of his podcast
I want to say.
Or it might have even been, he wrote like an article about what it's like to write on
an animated movie.
Where he came in to Kung Fu Panda and they showed him like all the storyboards on the
wall and they were like, you can only change 30% of this.
So you can pick 30% overall of the story to throw out or you can change 30% of each scene.
Oh because they were measuring 30% in dollars.
Right.
For example, in Shrek they threw out $4 million worth of animation when Mike Myers wanted
to come back and redo the lines in a Scottish accent.
We're going to get into all this but Shrek is kind of fascinating as like the Titanic
of CGI animation where it was the one where they kept on funneling money in and it seemed
cursed.
It saved DreamWorks.
Yes, and it saved them.
Yeah, it saved them.
It made them a player when they were not previously so much.
The road to El Dorado apparently almost killed them.
And Sinbad comes out I think the year after Shrek and like if Shrek had not worked, Sinbad
would have fully folded everything.
Shrek is sandwiched in between two hand drawn boys adventure films.
Oh yeah, dictating that this is what we do and no one was biting on those.
Well but the weird thing was the exact same time is Disney doing Treasure Planet and Atlantis.
Like early 2000s was everyone being like fuck, CGI is a thing now, we're not going to do
princess musicals, now it's like boys adventure films and hand drawn animation.
What triggered this?
Why did everyone decide that?
No idea.
Well it's probably because like stuff in Disney was starting to fail a little bit.
Their like formulas were failing so I think they were probably just trying to figure it
out.
I don't know this to be a fact but this is a guess.
They had their formula for the early 90s and then it sort of started to taper off.
Tarzan I guess was a bit of an upswing in terms of box office performance from the couple
before so maybe they took that and ran with it.
Right, it was like okay they like boys adventure now, that's what everyone likes.
But it's weird that like Disney did like two sci-fi like futuristic movies and then like
DreamWorks did these two like swashbuckling like boys will be boys movies.
It all merged in my brain.
I'm like seeing a Frankenstein of characters from all four of those movies and not individual
characters from the I don't know who's El Dorado versus who's Treasure Planet.
But you know the John Resnick song from Treasure Planet.
I'm still here.
Why did we talk about this?
We were talking about the rockinest moments in theme park history on the Patreon and he
performed that in Disney special.
We did not declare that.
But check out the Patreon, we did not declare that at the rockinest moment.
I'm still here.
Jim Parentheses, Jim's theme.
I think you made a joke on the episode that was like who even knows who played Jim?
Like you were like Jim I don't know who Jim is, who voiced Jim?
Assuming that it was some Disney star of the moment that was sort of like the tone in which
you spoke of it.
Can I guess?
Is it Tom Kavanaugh?
Jim was played by Joseph Gordon-Levitt.
Whoa.
It's kind of a Kavanaugh.
Kind of in that skinny like guy.
Maybe hadn't like broken ahead of the pack.
It was weirdly, it was like right after like Third Rock from the Sun ends and in the period
where he was like I question whether I want to keep acting and I walked away from acting
for three years and then he came back with like brick and mysterious skin and was like
a serious actor.
But like Treasure Planet was this remnant of his like child star days that just didn't
get released because of how long the animation is until he was like I don't know if I might
leave this.
Wait we also, oh no sorry.
I was going to say I think the thing too with animation because this is this sort of parallel
thinking or like two things coming out simultaneously.
Like people jump studios and companies so much and like oh they didn't really use this
kernel of an idea I pitched for this project so I'll do it over here.
And that like happens in animation, that happens in comic books too.
Like they're relaunching the X-Men at Marvel and they're relaunching the Legion of Superheroes
at DC.
Both involve characters in different ways who have seen like alternate time.
Like if you do this, this is what's going to happen.
I've seen it and I'm living a different life now but if we do something different something
else will happen.
Both of those.
Captain America and Batman both like died within six months of each other like ten years
ago in college.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's very weird.
Well and Dreamworks and Pixar were like notorious with that where you have like Ants and a Bug's
Life both in 98.
The furthest apart one is Shrek and Monsters Inc in 2001 where they're very different movies
but they're both like CGI monster movies.
They're bulbous creatures.
And then it's Finding Nemo and Shark Tale.
And then I think there's one more and then Dreamworks kind of went like we got our thing.
We can stop picking the same like sandbox that they're in.
They did the Unbelievably next to the Incredibles.
Right.
Hey wait while we're I realize we well you mentioned the references we made to animated
films in passing.
Yes.
I emailed you about this.
We stepped in.
I think one of us, Madame and me, I don't remember.
Somebody said no.
You said this.
I remember and I hold it against you.
Sorry it's coming.
I'm scarring you with something coming from my voice.
I said something about nobody cares about paranormal.
Right.
In the Amanda Lund episode she said that she had played paranormal at Universal and you
said wow you probably care more about paranormal than anyone else in the world.
You might be the only person who has strong feelings about paranormal.
Which sounds really harsh when you quote it.
It didn't feel harsh saying it.
That was a light jovial tone and I was not I don't think I came on aggro.
No not at all.
We were emailing about schedule this and I just said look Scott I want you to know I
happen to consider paranormal to be one of the ten best films of the decade period.
Wow.
No genre qualifiers.
Did Jason and I trash paranormal or did we not say anything?
No comment.
Both of you guys came out clean.
Thank God.
No comment.
I feel like in a very early episode of this podcast there was a paranormal joke run but
I don't remember the context.
I don't remember anything about it.
It might have just been about how Universal had the maquettes of paranormal out for a
while at that part.
I just had a flashback when you were saying that to when Doug Jones when I had made a
listener and a guest Doug Jones so upset by saying Pizzeria was bad.
Well and he was like oh no.
You reopened the wound.
That was the thing.
I invoked it when I came on the show but that episode hadn't come out yet so then I confidently
doubled down on all the things I didn't know you had said and then I felt so bad for Doug
who I have not met.
I don't know.
He's great and it's like yeah you didn't really you weren't like trying to like throw
gasoline on the fire.
Absolutely not.
And then my episode comes out like a week after that episode where he comes on and
defends Pizzeria so valiantly and look in my defense I did not go to the disco.
Yeah.
And now we know and we're well by this point we will have been to the disco.
Oh wow.
Oh yes.
We may have even.
I'm not going to eat there but I will walk through it.
I don't think that's even what it's about.
It's about theming not about.
So not by time not at the moment of recording but by the time this episode comes out you
will have done your your Orlando stop.
Yeah this is way in event.
We also will have survived the downtown Disney ordeal by the time we're jumping way ahead
here.
Yeah this is a future one.
It's we're different people.
Also we are by the time people are hearing this they will have also heard our journey
through another Eddie Murphy vehicle the Haunted Mansion.
Oh good point.
Which is.
We haven't recorded that yet.
I am on my second cup of coffee tonight because I have it from the library at home.
And you need to watch the clock is ticking before we leave for Chicago and I'm like doing
it on a plane.
Oh no it's library.
It's a library DVD.
If push comes to shove.
Yeah I'll just read it.
Perfect library DVD.
Perfect free.
Oh we had a working lunch and right afterwards I walked to the library and got it.
But then that night I went into my backpack and freaked out because I'm like what's why
is there a fucking DVD in here and I pulled it out freaked out.
Oh the Haunted Mansion.
Why did you freak out.
Spooky DVD.
Haunted.
Like you know when you're like I kind of know what's in this bag and you feel like.
I would be like oh that's interesting there's a thing in here I didn't know.
Not.
Oh my god.
Spooked by the contents of my own backpack.
All right well I was exaggerating for the sake of you.
All right that's fine.
You didn't jump up in the air you didn't leave a puff of smoke that was in your shape.
No it was more like what the hell.
Your hair stood straight up.
Yeah.
Can I tell an embarrassing anecdote about the Haunted Mansion movie.
So I went to see it.
The Friday it came out.
My high school the theater I would get out early my freshman year of high school I think
was when it came out and I had an early final class on Fridays and there was a matinee pricing
at the local theater so it would be like if I'm out by lunch I can go see a movie at like
one o'clock and it will only cost me six dollars.
So like whatever the Friday thing was I would I would go see it.
So I went to see Haunted Mansion with my friend Charlie and about halfway through the movie
just about when things were starting to get haunted because there's way too much wind
up in that film.
Yes that was exactly I don't want to spoil for since we still have to do the episode
but truly I don't know if you've watched it yet as we record this but like not yet there
is a yeah there's my wife and I had this big run of time we're like what nothing's happened
it takes it far in our way and it was like a ghost.
Yeah there's no like plot point.
No it's just slow real estate intricacies it's a lot of fucking shoe leather.
Get rid of it.
It's a lot of real estate bullshit.
But I'm sitting there I'm like finally ghost ghouls goblins this shit's about to get good.
And then my phone starts blowing up and I forgot it was my father's birthday.
And I was supposed to meet my family for like an early dinner or whatever.
I don't I don't know what time it was I guess but I was supposed to meet my family to go
have dinner.
And and so I always forget when my father's birthday is.
Everyone else my family birthdays are in quick succession.
They're they're very close to each other.
My father's birthday is at the other end of the year and I always forget when it is.
So I always need to check the release date of Haunted Mansion.
When I need to like which is I call in I believe.
Oh yeah I'm putting you on the spot.
Yeah you have to relook it up.
Usually I look it up.
I believe it's November 26 2003.
I'm sorry it is not October.
Why is it not October.
Way late.
It was like a Thanksgiving release.
Yeah yeah it was a Thanksgiving release.
So I think it's the 26th.
I know my father's birthday is within that week.
Yeah it's within that span of like between the 22nd and the 29th.
My mom's is just an unmemorable date.
Like my dad's is more like math symmetrical.
So I remember it.
My mom's is an unremarkable set of three numbers.
My mother my grandmother my two siblings and I are all born within between January and
March.
So those are like easy to remember because it's like every two weeks another birthday.
And my dad is like this like Haunted Mansion loser all the way back in November 26 2003.
Back to paranormal.
That's an amazing statement.
And I have not seen paranormal.
I have no problem with paranormal.
I just did.
It's ignorance on my part.
We're my my co-host on Blank Check David Simmons and I are big fans of making lists.
And so we're preparing for next year.
We're going to do our like best of the decade episode.
So I've been like actually running through year by year and trying to call and like
coming up with rough draft lists and nothing is locked in.
But I will say every version I've come up with so far paranormal is in my top 10
period for the decade.
Which you know I would say it's not an unpopular opinion.
It's just an opinion not wildly widely held because I feel like most people have not
seen it.
Sure.
But it is for my money the best American animated film of the decade.
Wow.
Yeah.
Oh so it potentially is like there's a world where it's on the list and the only
animated film on the list or one of two.
As of now I think it's the only animated film on my list and I'm a big animation fan.
Geez.
Are you a Lica fan?
I'm a huge Lica fan but that's far and away my favorite.
OK.
I love them overall but that was the one for me where I was like oh shit they're
cooking with gas.
Aesthetically it's my favorite and I also feel like it is it's tough to talk about
because the thing I like about the movie so much is like half of the way through
you're like oh this is about an entirely different thing than I thought it was.
Whoa.
OK.
And not in sort of like a plot twist way but like a thematic like deepening way.
And I think it is about a very weird nuanced thing that very few films try to
tackle let alone family films.
OK.
And for me the moment where I just realized like oh shit this is what this movie is
expounding on.
It kind of blew my mind.
And I think it's about like morally murky shit in a way that like doesn't back
away.
In you know I love Pixar but I feel like it is a less tidy package than any other
American animated film I've ever seen in terms of dealing with a really fucking
complicated thing.
Geez.
Wow.
I don't want to over sell it.
I will see it.
I would like to formally apologize on behalf of Scott when he said that Paranorman
is not cinema.
And that it is a theme park ride.
And that'd be the ultimate compliment for me.
Were you guys offended when Scorsese said that because it was demeaning to theme
park rides?
That occurred to me.
He can say that about Marvel films who gives a shit.
How dare he denigrate the enchanted Tiki Loon.
I was surprised how many people I saw like on like comedians on Twitter going
that theme parks are fun.
Like I don't really like Marvel movies but theme parks are fun.
I was like oh people starting to show their theme parks are good.
Oh right.
I like this.
Yeah.
He I mean honestly I was just like yeah yeah he's right and I like all of that.
Our friend Ryan Perez doubled down on the defending Scorsese and like went a
little further and insulting the broad appeal of theme parks and I was a little
like hey he's a friend.
Sure.
We'll get in and we'll corner him on.
Yeah let's get him in here and really rough him up.
I don't want it all to be theme parks.
No.
I also want it to be Martin Scorsese movies.
I think that's the valid point and that's why I appreciate him doubling down on
it because he's like no I shouldn't like get fucking like roasted for saying I
don't like these movies.
It's not like he came out and gave like a stump speech.
Someone asked him in an interview do you watch Marvel films and he was like not
really.
This is the truth not unlike my paranormal debacle here.
You pull the quote out and it does seem like oh boy that does seem harsh.
If Martin Scorsese like gathered the press and said I have a statement Marvel
films are like it's just something he said during.
I have that problem with like click bait articles in general.
Like it's not as if he like you know what I'm going to do I'm going to shout this
from a hilltop.
No I mean my big takeaway from that quote blowing up the way it did was oh no one
should do interviews ever.
I love interviews like I am such a fan of interviews.
I feel like I grew up reading interviews.
I feel like you guys are probably the same as like we're the same type of obsessive
dork who want to learn everything about the things we love.
Oh yeah.
And the best way to like more valuable than any film school or education is like
really like getting into the one I realized like oh yeah let me get into the
head of a creative person.
I really yeah interview magazine or like in comedy the and here's here's the
kicker and oh yeah.
I said is it great.
Yeah yeah yeah yes.
Very good.
Great.
Yeah.
Like I love shit like that.
That's like the cornerstone of podcast and right.
It's not just like oh here are the anecdotes about how this thing got made but
you're like hearing the person speak in their own words whether it's transcribed
or an audio so you're getting like their version of the thing uncut.
Yeah.
I love it as like a medium and I have become increasingly convinced that it is
in no one's best interest to do any interview promoting anything like it just
feels like it nine times out of ten fucks them over.
Well yeah because now especially because in the old like if you go back and look
at magazines with interview like with any music people or actors or directors.
Yeah.
In the old days you'll find insane stuff.
Insane shit.
No one even talks about it because it was just in a magazine and everyone went huh
that's weird.
Put the magazine aside.
But like every all these film places are like Martin Scorsese talking about Marvel
is yeah make everyone nuts and they're right.
It did make everyone nuts.
Yeah.
He didn't think too other than going like I'm annoyed that there's too many of
these movies in the theater.
Right.
He didn't really think much past that.
But some of it was all like him saying you know that these these movies have to
appeal to ages eight to 80 international audience.
Yes.
The stuff that theme park stuff has to do.
Right.
Which is a different skill and process than making like Bob and Carol and Ted and
Alice like making a grounded like.
Which is the nuance of what he was trying to say that got totally lost which is
like he's not saying that they're bullshit.
Yeah.
He's saying that they're not cinema in the way that he considers cinema but like
that's that's not as much a judgment of quality as it is sort of like a reflection
of process and their role in like society.
You know.
Well I think the other thing is that is bad about the maybe wider bigger picture
is bad about the Marvel movies is what you were saying about Katzenberg like
milking stuff is yes when people saw these interconnected giant movies universe
movies every idiot tried to do like dark universe.
These giant app and you have to have so much like as much marketing as production
budget it's just like huge you have to have so much money to get something made
now.
And and you know to to I don't want to get off the tangents but to just re center
some for a moment before we go back to tangent the ogre in the room Shrek for me
is a perfect example of that where it's like Shrek the first one is like doesn't
hold up great kind of innocuous but my my sort of perception of Shrek is so
negative now because everything Shrek rot and not just the sequels but just you
got like 10 years of every non Pixar CGI movie being like one arched eyebrow like
pop culture reference.
The main character looks like the actor playing the dream work space.
All that shit and then like every other studio starts their own animation studio
trying to copy dream works like that becomes the template that everyone's like
these movies that we don't think about anymore that don't exist.
It also seems like that's where we went from.
We've certainly talked about animated films veering to celebrity voices who know
who who cares about who cares if it's a celebrity or not.
But anyway how Robin Williams opened the floodgates on that.
But there was a time OK so even still Robin and then it becomes maybe there's
one big star star and then the rest are very good voice actors Shrek is where it
becomes the big the list.
Those are four titans.
I mean the main poster was just 90 percent white text Meyers Murphy Diaz Lithgow
and then Shrek at the bottom.
There were little photos of their faces but the main Shrek poster was just name
name name name title credit block.
And that leads us to today where there's like two separate stints in each trailer
where they were like here's now here's our nine celebrities.
And then here's our nine more celebrities.
I think that's sort of a sub issue I'm realizing within the celebrity stunt
casting is like we need to listen to this needs to be fucking crazy.
What child Vito Martha Stewart Dr.
Cornell West.
But now it's that weird thing also of like right.
It's like OK so there was like the occasional like Robin Williams stunt
casting.
And then there are things like even in the 90s when Katzenberg is like starting
to put bigger stars in Disney movies there are things where you're like oh right.
Mel Gibson was John Smith and Pocahontas.
Yeah.
It was not really a selling point and no one remembers that the chicken and
chicken run.
Those are the heist ones.
But then like those movies like everyone else in the cast is like chicken run is
just like British sitcom actors.
Yeah.
You know like the rest of the cast of Pocahontas is like voiceover actors or
like theater actors.
And then you get to like you'll have this weird balance where it's like hunchback
of Notre Dame is like Demi Moore and Kevin Kline who are like big at that
moment and then Tom Holtz.
Or you're like Tom Holtz is the lead of this film 15 years after Al Mudeus.
Why is that him.
He's good in it.
He is.
There was like still a balance of like oh let's get people who are like the right
person for the role.
Or let's get like David Odgen Steyer who's like a voiceover pro.
And then some big like 90s movie stars.
And then Shrek is just full stop like it's four huge names.
The movie sold on their names.
The trailers have the footage of them in the booth holding the one headphone to
their ear like it's We Are The World.
Now it's Nen.
But now none of this is a bad thing I don't think because I don't think any of
them are phoning it in.
No no.
Clearly Myers not for going I need to re record like he's invested.
I think they're all very good in it.
But it certainly leads to no shit.
This SNL guy has like an hour and a half between movies.
Let's grab him.
Let's add him to the list.
All right.
Throw him in the wood pile.
Shark Tale is the nadir of it for me where I just remember the poster being like
18 names including Mr Scorsese where it's like oh it's a blowfish that looks
like Scorsese it has the eyebrows.
The shark looks like De Niro it has the mole on the face like the fish looks like
Angelina Jolie she has the lips.
The Will Smith fish has the ears like everyone's like fish is some weird Mr
Limpit abomination of their like persona mapped on to some sort of sea creature.
And everyone's just kind of doing their own voice because the whole bit is like
just do your fucking thing.
Do the thing that you do.
And it's like it's like fucking you know it's just cashing in on the brands that
we all know.
Now I feel like when you do the 18 names in like the opening you know in the
trailer it's like largely like wait that was Rami Malek but he's got a German
accent.
What do you gain by hiring Rami Malek to do an accent different.
Like now I feel like it's big stars wanting to be like but I don't want to do
my own voice.
I really want to develop a character for this.
Yeah.
Is it like I think it's also like in the way like like I remember feeling like
doing digital like web video things going like why is there why are we even doing
web videos promoting this dumb thing.
That's what it doesn't it doesn't matter.
It's to show some boardroom guy and we're doing a internet video.
OK very good.
I think that the the litany of stars is is to show a Logan Rowe Roy kind of
person all the way up the flagpole.
And you see we have the very good.
Well that will bring in.
It's not for audience or even the makers of the film thinking it's a good idea.
Well I think there's one area in which it is for the audience in a weird perverse
kind of way.
You know what.
No it's not even really for the audience.
I think the other element to it is and Katzenberg is the first guy to really
weaponize this because like famously that the Robin Williams Disney falling out is
him being like I don't want to be promoted.
I just want to do the film and like Katzenberg slapping his name everywhere and
putting him in the trailers and everything and him being like fuck this.
This is fucked up.
I was just trying to like be a part of the Disney legacy or whatever.
But like by Shrek it's like oh they're on the red carpet like they're doing late
night talk shows like they're promoting a voiceover role as if it were their live
action movie.
Oh yeah.
Right.
Maybe that is Shrek like almost the first.
I feel like that's a turning point because even like it's it is truly my favorite
movie of all time.
But a beginning of the end moment is the Toy Story 2 poster is Hanks Allen Toy
Story 2.
Was Toy Story 1 not?
It was not.
It was like no names above the title.
And like Toy Story 2 was like two last names.
Because it was a risk for them.
That first one was like could have been a lie.
If that tanked like they wouldn't want to be associated with it.
And it was like Hanks before both of his Oscars and Allen like Home Improvement
had just premiered but wasn't like dominant yet.
Oh wow.
And for both of them it was like this is kind of corny like we don't want to do a
musical like they like talk about how they had to be sold on like this isn't
going to be like.
You recorded.
Your grandfathers.
Yeah sure sure.
And they recorded versions that were was like where things were bad.
And they're like maybe we don't want to be part of it.
Which ties directly into the Shrek stuff.
Should we before we get into the meat of Shrek 4D should we talk about.
And there's so much to talk about.
Well sure.
Well as usual the story behind it is more interesting for sure in this case
because the genesis of Shrek period I had forgotten that it was like a picture
book.
Which rules.
It's a great book.
It's William Stig.
Stig.
Yeah.
He's like one of those guys if you if you like if Jason you hold up a picture of
it if you have like a photo of it you'll recognize his art style as like he wrote
like kind of like the weird like edgy children's books.
Like he had this really kind of like scribble like almost like Roz Chast art
style and his books were like a little subversive and the whole hook to Shrek
was like it's like a fucking it's a fairy tale book about shitty things.
It's like an ugly monster who lives in a shitty place and everything's bad for
him and the book is really dark.
Yeah.
Oh there you go.
Oh wow.
Geez that's and that's pretty like specific and odd and grotesque.
Right.
Which is not the rounded off dreamers.
They took the color and the ears.
Yes.
Not the clothes.
The clothes are very bold and very 90s in fact.
So that came out in 89.
Spielberg options it for Amblin in 1990.
That long ago?
And the first names attached for it Bill Murray as Shrek and Steve Martin as
Donkey.
Whoa.
And they were debating at different points.
Is it like live action with like a couple CGI characters?
They thought about doing a dinosaur style where the characters were all animated
but all the plates were live action.
I want that now by the way.
I think that's still possible.
We have to find a reason to talk dinosaur.
Well there's the ride.
It's so weird.
Yeah.
I was playing this game the other day which was now that Disney is just like
the most dominant box office force and they almost never miss and like a miss
for them is like solo making 200 million dollars domestic.
It's funny to go back from like 97 to 2008 and look at Disney's box office by
year and you're like oh 2000 Disney's highest grossing film was dinosaur.
Geez.
A flop.
Yeah.
Today and today we lived them just tweeting out images of stuff that's going
to be on Disney plus and it's the same where we started recording.
It worked.
It fucking worked.
That's all everyone talked about on Twitter all day.
Even if they were mad they talked about it.
Of a lot of dog shit like so many years of so much dog shit.
So many oddball live action.
I would like look through year by year and you'd be like they have one movie out of
eight that did well and stood the test of time.
And you go through.
Bring down the house.
You're like that's like their highest grossing film of 2003 or whatever or like
1997 I think their highest grossing film is ransom.
Wow.
Yeah but it out grossed hunchback of Notre Dame.
Yeah those those movies are like bomb.
Yeah.
Disney animated films going under 100 million.
Yes.
That's that weird period where it's like Hercules and hunchback all do like 96.
Geez.
Wow.
Same for the part now that the parks are all these.
Well I guess we dipped a little bit this year but like you know like mega properties
you know you know attendance or like you know entrance fees go up and up and up.
And like late 90s early 2000s with you know your superstar limos and bad California
adventure and light magic and all that shit.
Yeah it was like it's hard to even imagine.
Disney being shitty.
Sort of risk proof to an extent that like the worst they can do is like the nut
cracker in the four realms.
Sure.
That's probably the last time we're going to get a movie like that for a decade.
I don't think they'll even take that much of a risk again.
And yeah if something falls through the credit they will of course correct and
like that's the end of that.
We're not going to try five more.
It's never going to be something that isn't a pre-established brand.
Well Jason brought up the point of like now they have Disney plus to like get
metrics totally.
So as soon as like the Tim Allen shaggy dog does very well.
Yeah.
Disney plus maybe there'll be a new Tim Allen shaggy dog if we're lucky.
And we'll never get to see it.
We'll never get to see the metric like in the way that like Nielsen ratings are
reasonably public.
It's so like oh god I don't even care as someone who could work on this shit.
I just want to know like what are people watching.
I'm just so morbidly curious.
It is the most bizarre thing to be like for years everything was running off of
the Nielsen ratings which are like the least accurate system in the world.
Grandma and grandpa have to take a booklet.
Right.
And write down in the booklet.
Yes.
Like when I've spoken to people who like were Nielsen families and they were like
at a certain point we just stopped doing it.
We stopped logging it or we just hit random buttons because it was just like I
don't want to I want to flip through and see shit whatever.
And now it's like the data has never been more precise and we don't know any of it.
We just know that every Netflix movie gets 30 million views in the first 24 hours.
Every Netflix film is the most popular film of all time.
Every Adam Sandler movie decimates 10 pre- Adam Sandler movies we all like.
Not just Gone With the Wind.
Paul Rudd doing Us But Funny is gonna blow away any other Paul Rudd project.
Just like all these things it's like yeah it's very odd.
And also like I'll say you know a couple of years ago Disney was like maybe we
need to go back to making like lower budget stuff again and like original like
family comedies and this and that and they produced a bunch and then all of them
just went weirdly quiet.
Like I know people worked on them and I was like whatever happened in that movie.
They'd be like I don't know.
And now a bunch of those are the things.
Premiering day one at Disney Plus.
Or those are all tricks.
Or are they for the next year.
That's what happened.
A lot of like that Anna Kendrick like Christmas movie.
The Bill Hader one.
Oh yeah.
Was shot like two years ago.
I believe Bill Hader was not a co-lead at the time.
They upped him post a train wreck.
And yeah.
Very.
Yeah.
But like that was one where they were like we want to get back in the business of
making like a 60 million dollar live action comedy.
Like low risk you know like high upside.
And then they watched all of them and they were like not worth the energy.
Keep it on a shelf.
We'll have a streaming service in two years.
There's an Adam Devine Magic Camp comedy.
That was shot three years ago maybe.
That's written by Steve Martin or co-written by Steve Martin.
Based on when he was a magician at Disneyland.
What.
That's just been sitting on a shelf.
I believe Jeffrey Tambor is also in it in the mentor role.
Which is maybe another reason.
That far after.
It's in the vault.
Geez.
We're post transparent finale where he's been killed off.
Is this how we finally get the day the clown died.
I cried.
Is this how we cried.
Yeah.
Right.
OK.
Somebody posted that joke on Twitter.
It was.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
Oh really.
Well that and this all happened six weeks ago.
Yeah I know.
Everyone's like wow this is current.
What a Disney plus talk.
I know.
It's out right now.
We're listening to people.
Now we're living in it.
Well here's the thing I noticed I want to see if you guys picked up on this because I'm
sure you scanned that thread as thoroughly as I was like the fucking Wi-Fi I need to.
I can't give up.
I need to hit the last tweet in the thread.
200.
But a couple of the old Fox movies that they've now.
Oh yeah.
Hired they slapped the Disney logo on it but not all of them.
So like in the Twitter thread like classic miracle on 34th Street was Disney's a
miracle on 34th Street.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I saw that.
Home alone wasn't.
It's weird because it feels like that somebody go through it and go which movies feel
like we would have made them.
Right.
Like there's almost some like determination of like well miracle on 34th Street so
wholesome and wonderful and home alone is fun but it's a little too you know.
Apparently a lot of like their weird Netherlands test with Disney plus was it the
Netherlands.
Yes they were testing it in the Netherlands because someone was posting walkthroughs
of the navigation.
It went up only in the Netherlands like two months ago and there was a bunch of weird
shit on there and it felt like it was them being like what breaks the Disney brand.
So something like Adventures in Babysitting which was like Touchstone but now is a
little too raunchy.
They were like but we remade it for the Disney Channel so it's kind of nice to have
both of them on there.
And it was like up there and then gone 72 hours later.
And it felt like there was Adventures in Babysitting not going to make the cuts.
That's what it seems like.
Whoa.
They're just filtering and they're being like what isn't Disney.
Like what doesn't pass.
This is funny games.
You're out.
Funny games.
U.S.
remake.
Right.
Staying.
Yeah.
Like Disney.
This is like Disney legend Jack Kirby.
Yes.
So it's like rewriting like OK that's comfortable.
Right.
Now he's been retconned into our museum is totally going to be retconned as a Disney
property.
Yeah.
And like Home Alone will as well which is why they've already said they're going to do
the news.
They're making a new Home Alone on Disney Plus.
Like they've identified the Fox properties.
The Dire of a Wimpy Kid I think is another one where they were like this is Fox and it
feels like Disney and we can just juice it up.
This is very very odd.
It's very weaponized memory hole.
Yes.
Like we will in like five years we will just think Disney made Miracle on 34th Street.
I saw someone tweet this and it was either terrifying or a perfect Twitter joke but
someone tweeted like it's crazy reading that thread having evidence for the thing I've
been trying to tell people for so long.
Colon Disney was making largely horse shit for 40 years and was constantly on the brink
of like going under like between like 50 and 90.
Yeah.
It was like so up and down and they were like how few movies between 50 and 90 are
like really canonical you know.
Yeah.
And someone responded either with a perfect joke or the most terrifying like Mandela
effect possible saying what are you talking about.
Star Wars was in 1977.
No.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Either way is interesting.
Right.
Good joke.
If it's a joke.
Right.
It's either you get the Mark Twain Prize for humor this year or humanity is over.
I don't know.
I mean that that's sort of like realizing that yeah there's a lot of garbage in 50 to
90 makes the stuff coming out of imagineering that more miraculous.
Yes.
That more incredible that the epic is when they're making their worst movies.
Yeah.
That's their most of the creative juice in the company is going towards the theme
parks at the time where it's all the live action movies that showed up in that thread
where you're like what.
Yeah.
How many Bill Cosby comedies did you make like a big Thunder Mountain occurs to me
too.
I'm sure like the two years surrounding Big Thunder Mountain were all horseshit for
Disney movies but then like iconic perfect right.
Yeah.
Crazy.
The one that's in my head from Twitter is that they won't leave my head even though
this was six weeks ago.
Now the there was a Disney Channel movie that I guess they have determined is Disney.
This will remain Disney.
And somebody tweeted this just with just the tree was just oh no.
And the and it was a like basketball player a twin girl basketball player movie
called Double Team.
Nobody thought the double team was a problem even then when it came out.
This wasn't OK.
This that's not a new phrase.
That wasn't OK in 2002 either.
It's not the Van Damme Rodman movie double team.
No no.
Right.
Which is great.
It ends in a big like the fucking the Roman Coliseum explodes.
Oh yeah.
There's a bunch of like soda machines in it and the branded soda machines go flying
at the camera.
What.
Yeah.
It's really funky.
And Mickey Rourke is the villain in that.
Is that right?
I think so.
Yeah.
I believe so.
I haven't seen it in a while.
Yeah.
Gosh.
Mickey Rourke when he was in his Disney between 1950 and 1990 period.
Yes.
Yeah.
Who owns double team.
Does Disney own double team.
Oh my.
Double double teamed in double team.
Team up.
Let me look it up.
OK.
But here's another link.
It's fascinating then that I feel like so much of sort of the cultural knowledge of
Disney becomes the theme parks becomes like it's a small world becomes like jokes
about like expensive food and whatever.
Sure.
Like that's when people are doing like Disney humor.
It's so often theme park based and merchandise based.
Yeah.
And it's not until the 90s then when you like OK they've revived the princess thing.
There are new tropes here and that's combined like the white washing of the fairy
tales with the theme park sort of price stuff.
Oh sure.
Which then what is Disney in terms of pop like the cynical pop culture.
Because Shrek is all about cashing in on that cynical pop culture perception of Disney.
Oh yes.
Yeah.
It is so much Katzenberg being like I'm I've defacted.
I'm like an expat.
Yeah.
I have a chip on my shoulder and now I can finally make the jokes that everyone else
has been making about me.
Sure.
I can do itch and scratchy land.
Right.
Yeah.
Now that I'm at this ruggedly independent I do what I want.
But can I make it a family film.
Like can I have my cake and eat it too.
Like can I do the jokes that make all the adults go like yeah yeah totally.
Disney is fucked up.
Also sell a bunch of dolls.
Opens with like it says stand in for Tinkerbell almost getting eaten by a frog and then
it ends with that same fairy getting shot out of the screen into a speaker and the
same gimmick as in Philhar Magic with Donald Duck's little seat like legs waggling around.
The fake Tinkerbell is like sort of.
Yeah I forgot that was in.
This is a thing with me.
I forgot what the four D's were because you can watch water.
Yeah pretty much.
I mean that's the only like sort of like theater environmental thing like that.
Well in the seats there's a lot of like a lot of seats.
She's on a bumpy road.
You're on a bumpy road.
And then and there's a rat gag.
Yes.
Which I think we all hate.
They did the honey.
I shrunk the audience.
Yeah.
And the ankles.
You don't get poked in the back though like bug do you.
I don't think so.
I feel like something like something does happen on the seat.
Am I wrong.
I feel there's a lot of carriage riding and I remember a lot of smells like I
remember that being the one sort of redeeming aspect of Shrek 4D was like
they were really kind of because even I was rewatching it on Netflix.
The weird form it exists in.
The yester world YouTube channel pointed out this is the one theme park ride you
can watch on Netflix.
Right.
Yes.
Because even like you have like oh like Back to the Future I'd like on the
Blu Ray box set but it's like presented in a context of like here's like a time
capsule of this one element of this thing.
Yes.
And this is an example of like they fucking broadcast this on television.
They sold it multiple times in home media.
They sold it to other theme parks.
Yes.
This was at multiple universal theme parks and also at what are they called movie
worlds Warner Brothers movie world Germany and Australia movie park in Germany.
Yeah.
It is I have to say it is no matter that despite being oddly also at a Warner
Brothers park and other parks it is no match for the most horrid out attraction
in all of theme parks.
Sponge Bob Squarepants in 4D.
This is a.
This replaced.
Oh that's right.
Movie.
Yeah.
Oh wait movie park Germany.
Let me just say really fast because I didn't really I was in my head that like
things just being really really tossed off to other parks.
So that's like that's Sponge Bob thing.
Then I looked it up.
Sponge Bob Squarepants in 4D has all told in its history played at 42 different
locations at Six Flags parks at Paramount parks and aquariums at museums at zoos
at Madame Tussauds at the Excalibur in Las Vegas.
Wow.
I assume there's porn booths somewhere where one of the options is Sponge Bob.
Yeah.
I've been I feel like to a weird amount of Six Flags parks that have it and it's
always anomalous because it's like you have no other like Sponge Bob Nickelodeon
presence you don't deal with them.
The Paramount parks did have Paramount via com did work was in the Paramount
parks for a long time Nickelodeon was in those parks for a long time.
And that makes sense.
It was built originally for that.
Yes.
But then at a certain point it became like Sponge Bob has just like never dipped.
It has only grown.
It lasts generations like it still plays.
So it becomes this safe bet.
If you have some if you got burned building a 4D theater at your like Six Flags
franchise or movie world and you're like I did fucking robots 4DX you know like I
did an original story open season and smell a vision.
Right.
And now like Sponge Bob is a safe bet.
Like I'm not going to replace this in 18 months.
Oh sure sure.
Yes.
It'll get dimmer and dimmer.
Right.
It's impossible to look at but people will come in.
That is a bet that I think Warner Brothers movie world may should have taken because
there Shrek 4D replaced Marvin the Martian in 4D or 3D.
Marvin the Martian in 3D it ran for eight years.
Yeah.
Then Shrek lasted only five years and it was replaced by Journey to the Center of
the Earth 4D Adventure.
Oh yeah.
That's this really bleak thing where a bunch of theme parks once 3D like studio
film releases started becoming like more prevalent would just take like a show reel.
They'd take like a 10 minute section of a wide released 3D movie put it in their 4D
theater and just show you a thing you could have seen at AMC with a couple extra effects.
Well this is we're living this currently with you know Star Wars Path of the Jedi
and this junk that they fill all of the empty theaters with that used to be teaming
with 3D films Disney parks.
At least Phil R. Magic is in there now.
Yeah there's finally a God all those they have like maleficent previews and all that
shit. Oh my God.
I mean I just want to contextualize like this is a trilogy obviously we are completing
a trilogy here.
Right but there could be other trilogy.
There'll be other trilogy.
Right for me you know my my sort of role on podcast the ride I want it to be a sort
of loosely connected series of interlocking trilogies.
I love it.
A series within the series.
We got a lot of them going now.
Oh and thank you again for announcing it at PTR 23.
It's very delightful.
I got to say you asked me to do the video.
I was happy to help.
I you know stepped away from a very busy you know career.
Flicked on the fluorescent lights in your kitchen.
Not even in the hallway outside my girlfriend's apartment.
Because she was on a business call and I was like don't mind me.
Couple power players.
Right.
Record seven takes of me pretending to be Zachary Levi.
Oh yes.
Announcing nerd HQ.
I love that.
You asked me to do it like day of.
I was happy to do it.
I sent it to you.
You were like thanks.
And then the episode comes out a week later and I was sitting there listening and you
started to almost say it and I was like wait a second is he going.
No he's not.
And I truly I got full body chills at you in a sort of tossed off way going well yeah.
Yeah why not.
OK.
Yeah.
Well I'm going to say he is a podcast the right legend.
Oh that's right.
I forgot we haven't seen you since we made since a technicality made you a podcast.
I was chills.
I was I was walking around a five below and I started beaming the hairs on my neck.
We're standing up and no one else could.
I was like I want to grab someone and go do you know what just happened.
I've been inducted.
I forgot we haven't addressed this.
Yeah.
Forced by a slideshow.
Worst for me.
We did it we could have objected.
We didn't object.
No the setup was there was a table and I was running the computer right.
It was like just that our arms reach for every time I had to really lean in.
Yes I think I feel like I hit hit it twice right.
The button twice you went past Choco to me.
And I ended up sneaking my way into that designation.
That show was chaos.
That was like preparing for the show.
Yeah I was joking.
We were at a bar for like my birthday recently and someone went oh how was your.
You guys did a show in Anaheim right.
I was like yeah it was great.
Putting it together was chaos.
We were Jerry Reagan stuff on the ground.
Hurry go.
We had a table.
I watched your whole video until it was playing and I got a sense of it.
Like it worked great.
He's wearing a forky hat.
It's fine.
Yeah it is.
Welcome to PTR legend.
Even you saying it again I just got chills again.
To a PTR legend.
Such such an honor.
I do want to say though I feel like it didn't happen because she was the guest on the episode.
But I feel weird being inducted and Jenny not being in because I feel like as a fan first I'm like that's clearly the best running guest you have on the show.
I would go to go to go to be in the larger conversation.
But for me it's inarguably Jenny is like the fourth good boy.
Wow.
You were both though the people yelled at us the most on the internet mega-foe and it's like have them on the show.
Oh really.
Jenny Nicholson and Griffin knew that.
Yeah.
I mean look I'm happy to be in the same general zip code but Jenny's at a different level for me.
Sure.
She has the experience and the insights and I just want to say I as a fan will be angry if she's not inducted next year.
She will be inducted I'm sure.
I'm just saying you're selling yourself short.
I wouldn't do that.
You're up there.
Once again I'm happy to be in there.
So we'll do it in the way most inconvenient to when we could have done it with her right there.
Right.
We will do it in some.
Yeah she'll be somewhere else and then she'll find out from a third party.
So it's oh it's Chaco Marvel McFay.
No not Marvel.
Marvel's not there yet.
Maybe should be.
So then you know what Jenny is actually in pretty good company being right on the outside because she's going to probably get inducted in the next class.
Chaco.
With Marvel.
It's Papa Steve from the Bread Factory tour.
Ice cream sundae I like.
Right.
It was the Hollywood's next big star poster.
Oh yes.
Poster outside of the bathroom in California Adventure.
The guy on like actor magazine or whatever it is.
There was another idea that didn't come to fruition and I'll tell you about off microphone.
Yeah.
Oh boy.
You guys know it.
Yeah.
Well just within viewing this as a trilogy.
Right.
You know I've come on and covered two of what I think are the finest American films for me.
Yeah.
The 3D Terminator 2.
Judgment Day 3D which I think both work incredibly well as theme park attractions and as movies.
And when we were like what's like the third one to close it out we were like I guess kind of by default.
Because like if he did.
Honey I shrunk the audience.
Yeah.
Shrek 4D is the next kind of logical one from that era.
Well and I mean the one that's looming there is a major 3D film made by a major film director.
But I don't think anyone wants to touch it with a 10 foot pole.
Yes.
Which is heartbreaking because boy do I love this film.
I know.
But I don't think we've made you do it.
Right.
You're doing that or nothing.
I've also I've embarrassingly only seen that one on YouTube.
I missed it when they released it.
I went so I like got a hotel room.
Yeah.
The night that it came out.
That's how.
Can I say a very dark thought.
Uh huh.
I don't think this is going to be dark in the way people now are fearing it will be dark.
I'm about to get kicked out of.
I guess the right legend.
Get out of this room.
I had this feeling after watching Leaving Neverland where I was like I wish I had seen Captain EO before this.
Yeah.
Like I wish I wouldn't like I would be able to compartmentalize it now.
But in the way I'm like I'm happy I saw certain things made by monsters before I knew they were monsters.
So now I never have to watch them again and they're sort of sectioned off in my brain because the memory is you have at least a pure memory totally to remember it.
And just in terms of like being a person who wants to have like a knowledge of pop culture and whatever.
Sure.
Yeah.
But to like invest in it now.
Right.
Seems like an odd thing to do.
Like I remember my friend and I like five or six years ago were like we should really see like Bill Cosby live before he died.
And then when like all the stories came out I'm like dodge a bullet.
Glad I didn't see Cosby live give him my money.
Sure.
But then part of me is like I wish I had seen it and then found out that he was a piece of shit and felt bad that I'd gone to see it if that makes sense.
Yeah.
Like I wish I just had in my brain the experience of seeing old angry half blind.
I'm going to yell at everyone in my audience Bill Cosby.
And go for like longer than this podcast.
His sets are through three and a half hours.
And be like oh I got a bad vibe from this guy.
Yeah.
I did see I saw R Kelly during the window where like everyone forgot before they remembered again.
And it was something that was the captain you know thing like it was like post Jackson death.
Everyone was like oh we're just like we totally love him now.
Completely pulled out of the parks.
If you look at the timeline when it started getting taken out.
It was trial one and then we and then he died and then just like never mind.
Fine.
It's fine.
We all agree it's fine.
Right.
It was a nice it was a nice era to live in.
Not it's not good that everyone was ignoring it.
But it was like terrible.
Yeah.
Horrible that everyone's ignoring it.
But sort of like you know fingers and ears ignorance.
Yes.
It's not ignorant.
Right.
I had that feeling like after watching Leaving Netherland where I was like they're never going to put it back in the parks again.
Like I'm never going to get to see it which is for in the grand scheme of things for the best.
But oh boy.
Oh the seats danced.
Now that's shaking.
You can take all if you could just take them out and digitally put is there a way.
Well and can we do an episode that avoids aesthetically speaking is it's mostly going to be about Hooter the elephant.
The alien elephant.
I know it's first in there.
Right.
Major and minor domo.
And we know that's what we'd be taught.
I'd be I would have spent 20 minutes on the plastic egg that's lying on him.
Yeah.
You know what.
That is the question.
This is the big moral question.
What did fuzzball know.
You know what I'm saying.
Like was he complicit.
This is all also making me realize I forgot I never watched the Theranos documentary that came out like right around that time.
Oh yeah.
About HBO.
And I'm like oh shit I have that at home.
That thing's like you're just thinking of other movies to watch while we're talking.
You don't want to talk.
We don't want to watch fighting there like it seemed unpleasant.
You're going to end up watching a mansion at 5 a.m.
I am.
Yeah.
You want what you're saying is you want Alex Gibney to make a documentary about what fuzzball.
Yes sure.
Yeah.
But but like honey I shrunk the audience.
Captain Muppet Vision Terminator 2 3D are all examples of like this feels like a theme park attraction.
You're not just sitting in a theater and watching a 3D movie.
Yeah.
And it's a thing that like the resurgence of 3D which was largely spearheaded by and ruined by Jeffrey Katzenberg.
Like Jeffrey Katzenberg is by all accounts and for all intents and purposes the man who killed the golden goose like this thing that was briefly like reviving theater like ticket sales.
Now allow me to say this that at this exact week that we're recording this I'm working on a Quibi show.
So I would just like to say Quibi we love you.
Any comments that have been made in the past were incorrect.
I've been proven wrong and I'm not saying things that Griffin is saying.
And Scott I would like to add that in a few weeks I will be pitching to Quibi.
This is not a joke either and I would like to say my opinion is that Quibi is probably great.
We haven't seen it yet when it's launched but I would like to.
Katzenberg killed the golden goose because he had so many more golden geese to raise from babes.
That golden goose was it was going to die of old age anyway.
So these new young golden geese.
If you guys need to step out of the room for another few minutes Griffin and I can continue this conversation because I don't have anything like that.
I've been trying to get a general with them.
It's a blast.
Yeah a lot of fun.
The general sounds so much fun.
I hear the meetings you can have.
Fuck.
I see.
I was going to say you can have the meetings standing up vertically or lying down horizontally.
And it's got to work both ways.
Yeah.
It's a golden goose of an idea.
That is such a crazy thing.
I have heard that corroborated by so many people and I have also talked to so many friends who are actors on Quibi shows and they're like that can't be true.
But.
They were on the set and they're like that it's not going to work.
Well no they weren't like technically that's impossible.
They were like that seems weird that no one would tell me that.
I think that's not complete incredulity.
That is I believe out the window.
Really.
No no no.
I'm in a room on a thing.
They showed us a chart.
Really?
They said remember to frame.
They said to me a writer not involved in the technical aspect at all.
To remember that the frame.
So I shouldn't write anything that says a very wide frame opens up.
I heard somebody there's a show that's being made that they were like yeah we're not doing that.
Maybe maybe some of the bigger creators are getting to just that is what I'm talking about.
Well it's like they have like news.
Does the news flip formats.
I guarantee you the news flips format.
Yeah the news.
Anything's going to be the news.
I was talking about this the other night too.
Do you know about the shining like the the aspect ratios like when Kubrick shot the shining the monitor.
He could see what it would look like in 16 by 9 and 4 by 3.
Yeah that like the 4 by 3 video release you saw like other stuff in the scene.
Right.
Yeah that's like Dark Knight.
They did that and those all the Imex.
It's cool if it's done intentionally.
It is insane the way that they're planning on doing it but also.
You don't think Antoine Fuqua is like look you don't think the key for Sutherland Fugitive.
They're like all right let's make sure when he's running through this tunnel.
I'm astounded by how many Kweeby shows are remakes of movies.
Like it feels weird that even at that level they're like well we need a baseline IP here.
We need something.
No nowhere.
Key for Sutherland Fugitive made me feel like no that already happened.
Yeah.
Did it.
It feels right.
It feels like a perfect equation.
It feels like.
So many fugitive shows.
He did that on CBS right.
He must have.
It was seven seasons.
Eight seasons.
That was designated survive.
24.
Wait a second.
Well that means that we do over.
Yeah.
Let's eventually we gotta get to.
Well what I was gonna say right.
I feel like Shrek is an example of like all the shit that is sort of more theme parky and
experiential to being in that specifically constructed theater at any one of seven theme
parks where it was playing are so gimmicky and hollow and less successful than the things
like Muppet Vision and I struck the audience and T2 and Cranter now where it's like more
fully integrated into it.
Yeah.
And it speaks to the fact that they like made a movie that can kind of work without the
theme park.
Yeah.
And that is the fact that they could repurpose it which you couldn't do with the honey I
shrunk the audio you can just be watching that on a DVD.
But it's like an ultimate neither nor where like I remember seeing Shrek 4D at Universal
and being like this is a bad 4D movie and then watching it on Netflix being like this is
a bad animated short film and in either format I'm irked by things that were clearly done
for the sake of the other format.
There's some cognitive dissonance because the pre show is very theme parky.
Which I think is the most successful shit.
Yeah.
With like Gingy banging on the camera and then making jokes about like this is what
happened after the credits.
And it being like dungeon security camera.
Yes.
And it helps because Shrek the first Shrek is so much.
And the pigs are in the cages.
The just eyes of you can watch the video you can watch that the user cow missing who
releases all the like good raw material of all these pre shows and everything has like
video feeds of every individual set of pig eyes.
It's pretty cool.
They're good.
I'm glad you brought that up.
I do like the pre show.
And the show building is good.
It helps that like Shrek has set up that the whole kingdom is like a riff on Disney
World that's already baked into the cake.
Yeah.
So like that's fun to see.
Like it's like oh I'm walking through the real thing because in Shrek there are
turnstiles and there are weird like sort of like velvet ropes you know and there's
like a scene in Shrek where he like gets in a fight with like a dude in a Farquaad
mascot costume where he's in like the ride queue line.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Oh sure.
So seeing all that stuff like replicated in real life is like kind of fun.
I was gonna say the Singapore location that opened up to the other ones.
Yeah.
That facade is crazy.
It's like the full castle.
It's barbed wire.
Massive scale.
Yeah.
That was rumored to be in the new one in Orlando but I don't think it's happening.
It's not at least in the pictures.
There is like sort of medievalish but that's maybe how to turn your drink.
Yeah.
That's the people think.
But there was yeah it was gonna be a full like reverse Magic Kingdom.
Shrekified.
Both of those are kind of weird.
Like I mean.
I think how to chain your dragon they must have tested well enough that like OK
that's a trilogy.
There's three.
There's I think there's a spin off TV show and people still have goodwill towards it.
They are very well regarded.
They're probably the best reviewed Dreamworks franchise top to bottom.
And the ancillary stuff has done well for them.
But it also like all three how to train your dragon movies each one makes less than
the previous one.
Sure.
Like they go down whereas like the other crazy Dreamworks franchises you're like
Madagascar 3 made that much.
For sure.
What would have happened though if they had made the other alternate Shrek's like
Nick Cage Shrek.
Or you didn't get to all these.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Janine Garofalo as Fiona.
Whoa.
There's like Farley recorded 95 percent of his dialogue.
That much.
Yeah.
And then find that online.
And it's just him doing voice but it's it's him just doing his regular voice and
his sounds very endearing.
And then people they had a 3D model that looked more like the illustration.
Yeah.
And it was Farley's.
That's a whole other.
Oh yeah.
Completely different character.
And apparently I would so so curious to learn more about this.
Like Mike Myers did not know he was replacing Farley and did not know there
were recordings.
Whoa.
When he was.
They kept that from.
He claims that he asked that when they showed it to was this on his Marin
episode that when they showed it to him he said.
It seemed like he had a feeling.
Was Farley doing this at some point.
Yeah.
And they said no.
Because they had like storyboarded it to his voice.
Like they had like the animatic like showreels of like which I guess they must
have showed him and then put in some scratch voice of like someone at the
Dreamworks offices to cover it up.
But the whole character had been defined by like Farley's performance.
Like they had it all like sort of blocked out.
I mean I as like a weird broken child who was like a reading variety distinctly
remember them announcing that Chris Farley was going to be the voice of Shrek.
But I guess Mike Myers probably just didn't ask didn't care.
You know or when he asked he had no outside like reference.
He hadn't heard anything.
It just seemed like it.
But yet it's like right.
Spielberg wanted to do it his own maybe his live action maybe his hybrid do it at Amblin.
The Dreamworks bought the rights from them.
Right. Right.
Once he formed that and it was like this is the big idea.
And then they just kept on like resetting it over and over again.
And then like Farley dying and then Mike Myers did it all in the voice of Lothar
from the Hill people from SNL.
That was the first where it's like hello.
I am Lothar.
And he was like he went in and first of all apparently Myers demanded a page one rewrite
per his notes his like control freak stuff.
He like they rewrote the whole script is like sort of interest.
I think they brought in a bunch of his like SNL guys who were uncredited on it.
Michael McCullers I think worked on track but didn't get credit.
And that is what took out all that was the final nail that killed all the Farley.
Right.
And he's thing hanging on.
Right. Right.
Because I think it was like I want to make this thing my own.
It feels like this is some remnant of some other movie.
You don't even like what then what is Mike Myers.
I mean for sure that thing that's reprised in Trek 4D of is he compensating for that.
I can't do Scottish panel.
Is he is far quite compensating for something.
There's a few penis jokes in the movie.
There's some funny.
Obviously he loves that's his favorite.
Yeah.
Trek 4D has a number of callbacks to the first movie like what it is.
Second beats that don't necessarily pay off.
He just made it like body.
He made it body with like in his body body.
Right. And then his his thing was he was like this is too arch.
I'm doing a sketch comedy character.
It doesn't work.
There's no emotionality to it.
I want to redo it with a Scottish accent.
And he was like my my like one of his parents was Scottish.
He'd done the voice a bunch of times.
And that's that's so Harry Dax murder and fat bastard.
Right.
And he made this argument to like I think it's a soft accent that's also hard.
Like you can sort of balance the warmth and the monstrous side of him and pitch them on it.
And in like one of the rare instances I've ever heard of like Katzenberg choosing the more expensive option was like fine.
And they threw out like six million dollars worth of animation to start over.
Do we think.
With timeline is that the difference between like what he can request pre Austin Powers and post Austin.
Like is he like does Austin Powers put him in a position where it's fine.
Spend the money because we'll get it back.
Yeah.
I mean you go like in between like Austin Powers two and Austin Powers three.
No one's going to say no to that guy.
Yeah.
But then that whole fucking crazy Deeter debacle is part of all that.
And is that dream.
No that's universal universal.
But that was probably about the same time as this.
You know.
Oh and Cat in the Hat was the fallout.
Right.
That was his punishment.
Make good.
Yeah.
That was his make good.
Lock him in a suit.
One of my favorite phenomena.
I would love to like curate a film festival that's movies where actors were sued into being in them.
Which is like Mike Myers and Cat in the Hat.
Edward Norton in the Italian Job.
Oh yeah.
Which is why he clearly doesn't want to be in that movie.
David Cross in third.
Yes.
Alvin and the Chipmunks.
Emily Blunt and Gulliver's Travels which she was forced to do because of an option on the contract she signed for Devil Wears Prada.
And because she was forced to make that movie she dropped out of playing Black Widow in the Marvel Cinematic Universe.
She was signed and announced and Fox was like no we got one on you.
Jesus.
She's probably had a more interesting career since.
Totally.
Oh totally.
But it's still a crazy thing to think about.
And she'll get in there.
Yeah.
Yeah that means she's available.
Marvel will devour her.
I have to say I was trying to think back to 2001 when Shrek did finally come out.
And I have such a weird association with it because I was like between sophomore and junior years of high school.
Yeah.
And this is when a couple friends got cars and driver's licenses.
So this was the summer that like we don't need our parents to take us anywhere so and so can drive.
Which resulted in me seeing Shrek twice.
Oh I thought you were going to say 20 times.
20 times.
I think I did see it with my family and then I saw it with friends because there was a friend who saw he was obsessed.
He got obsessed with Moulin Rouge that summer.
And every time we're like well let's go to the movies.
He's like I want to see Moulin Rouge.
Let's go to Moulin Rouge.
We'll see Moulin Rouge at this point.
And he's like on number four or five screening.
And it's like no it's not in theaters anymore.
But Shrek is somehow still in theaters.
Let's just go see Shrek.
I'll see it again.
Fine.
I'll see Shrek again.
And it was fun.
It was fun.
We liked it.
Summer of Shrek for Jason Sheridan.
This is an insane stat that I'm embarrassed to share and I don't think I cannot think of another example of this.
I believe I saw Shrek three times opening weekend.
Whoa.
I believe I saw it Friday Saturday and Sunday.
Wow.
Because I just could not get enough of this fucking thing.
I saw Red Dragon twice.
Because like I saw it with my dad and then friends we were going to go see something else but got the times wrong and they're like we could go see Red Dragon.
And I'm like yeah OK.
But a lot of people I like in that.
Yeah.
That's Ed Norton too.
Ed Norton.
Mary Louise Parker.
Yeah yeah.
Hoffman.
Yeah.
Well the circumstances were there was a kid in my grade named Mack Shrek.
The villain from Batman Returns.
And the actor Mack.
Yes.
Right.
Nels Feratu.
But at the time that was flying over our heads and we were just like yo dude they made an animated movie about you.
Like it was the best joke and he owned it.
To his credit Mack Shrek owned it.
Wore it like a badge of honor.
Had a Shrek birthday party.
Oh.
And we were like 13 or 14.
But he was like we're going to buy Shrek party supplies.
We're going to like everyone buy me Shrek presents.
Like I'm owning this.
This is my movie.
So that was like Saturday was going to be Mack Shrek Shrek birthday party followed by a sleepover where I distinctly remember at Mack Shrek's apartment watching the cowbell sketch.
That was it.
Yes.
That was the weekend that Christopher Walken does cowbell on Anson out.
I also remember where I was when that sketch.
The whole room.
Yeah.
Truly.
It just you could kind of I feel like for for the four of us as comedy nerds if you were watching that live you were like this is something.
If you're going into comedy enjoy this curse.
This is going to be something.
The guy who hired me and a lot of my friends at Funny or Die was a guy who wrote there at the time Andrew Steele and he at one point said you realize everyone in this building is here because of the cowbell sketch.
Yeah.
Like this would not this building isn't here without cowbells specifically.
It's not.
Still sounds bizarre but it's true.
It's crazy also because I remember I was like I guess I was like 13 at that point 12 or 13 and for years it had been my dad would tape SNL on a VHS and I would wake up Sunday morning and have a bowl of cereal and watch SNL because I could.
Take me to church.
Stay off.
Lord is my pastor.
That was my synagogue was watching SNL with like corn pops on Sunday morning but that was a rare one because it was a sleepover where I was like Max's parents let us stay up and I watched it live with three other people.
So I was watching other people laugh at SNL which I didn't usually get.
Oh usually the social experience.
Yeah.
You spoke of nerds watching them lose their minds.
I was like this is this is something.
Yeah.
I did not think it would become the most dominant.
But like primary if like if we have to explain what is sketch in a thousand years.
It's the thing.
We only have room to remember one sketch.
I guess it's that one.
It's the thing we put in the time capsule.
You know it's what we buried outside the Nickelodeon hotel.
We're so close to where we're recording this to the time capsule.
Yes.
Yeah.
Closer than we usually record.
Oh wow yeah you're right.
Steps away.
I can feel it.
Oh no where you say sorry.
Well my other thought on Shrek is.
OK.
Two ideas on that one.
They say the first few years of a new decade are closer to the previous totally.
So 2001 still a little 90s the.
Yeah.
My I am wondering is this does Shrek mark the end of the 20th century or did the
matrix do that.
I think in a certain way it's Shrek and the matrix.
And here's another thing I'm going to say.
I think Shrek despite the fact that the franchise continued for another decade.
I think Shrek is so specifically a movie that only could have come out in this
warmly received this successful this beloved the less than five months before
September.
Yes that was the other thing.
This is the end of innocent.
This is totally the end of innocence.
I think there's something to Shrek coming out in those final moments of like you
can't fucking touch us.
America's on top.
Hollywood's like it's big stars big movies.
Anyone can come on a lot without a ton of screening and a certain type of irony
starts to get questioned right after 9 11.
There was that whole thing of like is irony dead.
Have we been living in this like sarcastic society does like sincerity need to be
embraced again.
It's an overnight like entire sea change.
But I do feel like Shrek even when the sequels were doing well and people were
watching it later.
Some of its success was tied to remember nine months ago before the greatest act
of like international terrorism that our country has experienced in decades.
It's a different movie but we were all singing.
Hey here we are now entertain us Shrek.
Yeah we were singing it along to Moulin Rouge.
There's something hedonistic about track.
It's also funny.
It's a little mind blowing.
The trick came out the weekend of the cowbell sketch.
Because also so that puts it at like that the cowbell sketch is happening and then
five months later Rudy Giuliani and the firefighters with ashes on them.
And we still be funny.
Five months later.
All of this is like this is important cultural content.
Can we still be funny is at least a joke as opposed to like the other tragedy.
How do you know there wasn't one joke.
You're right.
Right.
Wasn't a joke at that point.
The tragedy mashup or their new biggest recurring or or saying to sir with love
when Obama's term ended.
Once again these comments are not my comments.
Yeah.
It's great love.
By the way can I just put in this is not part of a trilogy.
I just want to throw in my name into the ring.
I would love to do the entirely behind the paywall Jimmy Fallon episode.
It's hard to say no to that.
You threw it out recently that maybe that's the way you can finally talk about race
through New York the fact that you notice that I have so many thoughts on that ride.
That might have to happen.
I and if you're willing to go outside the trilogy then yes.
And if you're willing to jump into the lion's den I mean obviously you won't hear it if
you don't go by the bill obviously will only say nice things.
Yeah.
But you could.
Because that is like they try to build that as a ride but it isn't more of a 3D film.
This is my argument.
That would be the scorpion king to this the Brennan Fraser mummy trilogy.
Oh you know it's like a little great.
I love that.
I agree.
Perfect analogy.
Well yes.
Now I just want to we're recording this very late.
I just want to roll straight into that right now is the problem.
I can be able to do it for a while.
Now I am thinking about our day upcoming day at Universal and going oh if we blitz
her original unit Jesus we got we got to make time.
I do it.
Yeah.
I've done it but I haven't done it.
I don't know.
We have to do it.
Oh that's why we have to experience.
We couldn't do a bang.
That's the reason we can't right now.
I have to experience fake 30.
So that's the thing.
So much of it is the fucking Q area.
Oh but Dapper Dan what are they called.
Oh shoot I can't remember.
Doodles.
The camp down racers.
I am more excited for the today show cafe.
But the weirdest thing is just like the Q area being like the front desk that you
used to check in when you have an audition for an NBC pilot.
Yeah.
That's all.
And then the tiny little Conan tonight show display.
It's my favorite.
Yeah.
Steve Allen has a huge case.
Everyone's got it and then it's like a little tiny.
It's somehow more disrespectful than if they had removed him entirely.
Yes I actually yes I agree with that.
There's this should probably be behind the paywall but there's this video of Jimmy
Fallon like talking to Steve Martin in that he's facing that display and saying to
the display as if like a beyond the grave Steve Allen Steve we did it Steve.
We did you ever ride Steve.
God he would have loved this.
And then it just pauses and doesn't cut and it's like a comedy cut again.
No I can't make I can't defend that one.
Watch it.
All I did was describe a video.
Yeah I didn't say anything that wasn't in the judgments and everyone become a
Patreon subscriber that you get your five dollars worth.
I can vouch for the quality.
Speaking of Shrek also I want to say Shrek premiered at the Cannes Film Festival.
Huge thing to talk about.
11 minutes standing ovation.
Shrek competed for the Palm or the first animated film since Disney's Peter Pan.
Everyone sat down at Cannes and one of the first things they heard was somebody.
And people were like it might win.
Like I remember there being the buzz of like Shrek's a solid contender.
Like it's like first animated film Oscar Shrek and Donkey in attendance at the
Academy Awards.
So on a technological marvel.
I think that's the one year where they animated the animated film nominees in the
audience and like before the animation studios were like this is kind of like
infantilized.
That would be nice because you know Jack Nicholson is not always there anymore if
they just every year animated Shrek and Donkey in the front row.
Shrek wearing the Nicholson sunglasses.
Coked out of his pants.
There with Bill Adler and Donkey.
Yeah throw Shrek in the Lakers game audience.
Crowd.
This.
They should.
Shrek should just occupy when Nicholson passes.
Yeah Shrek should take his seat.
They like kind of bow to the seat and then wave Shrek in.
Honestly.
The big the theater shakes.
It would be good if they just sort of like treated Shrek like an actor.
Yes.
And he's just in movies.
So like Shrek is.
Well that's this thing like Universal buys Dreamworks and they already have
illumination which is doing so well for them and has been doing better than
Dreamworks for the last five or six years.
And apparently the whole thing was like Chris Melandari who's in charge of
illumination was like I'm not going to leave my post.
I want to keep illumination going.
These minions are like printing money but we got to figure out something to do
with these Dreamworks characters.
And by and large like the development of new Dreamworks movies has slowed down
in the name of like these apparently constant meetings of like fuck what do we
do with Shrek.
Like everyone's banging their head against the wall going like do we do a
sequel do we do a reboot do we do live action.
Like what do we do what do we do.
We got to do something new with Shrek.
Dark Shrek which will win.
That'll win Venice.
Right.
But that's why I'm like.
Just put Shrek in other movies.
Yes just put Shrek in other movies.
Just like in but like not like period like just a romantic comedy with Kate Hudson.
Right Shrek and Kate Hudson are in a movie about her working in a magazine or
something.
He's like a new he's a new Vinnie Jones.
Yeah.
Shrek's like a villain in a Fast and Furious movie.
Like what's in the Universal stable.
Like he's a little Shrek.
Yeah.
Shrek is a Guardians of the Galaxy cast member.
Yes.
It's interesting you bring up illumination because the way this all played out Shrek
one comes out two years later.
11 happens.
Yeah.
11.
Two years later Shrek 4D is placed in the kind of opens almost
simultaneously not totally simultaneously.
I think Hollywood opened first then Japan and Orlando opened on the same
day and for both of them there the attractions opening within like nine
months of when Shrek 2 is going to come out.
Yes.
And it's such a unique phenomenon of not like we're making another like entry but
like we're making a bridge entry between the last theatrical movie and the next
theatrical movie knowing full well that Jeffrey Katzenberg was like we're going
to make six of these goddamn things.
Yeah.
But in 2003 as a theme park goer I thought this is cool.
Right.
It's a picks up right where the first movie left off.
You can't see it anywhere else and it's like an important piece of it's important
piece as you walk out there.
Well there's a poster in the exit that says coming in 2004 Shrek 2.
That's what happened.
So literally what that is my memory of it.
But it's so weird for this attraction to be like still running after Shrek 4 came
out.
Yeah.
Oh yeah.
Because it's been like I don't I'm not up I haven't seen two through four so I
don't know what happened but I imagine character things are like irrelevant or
changed.
Things change.
Everyone starts having kids.
Shrek's life gets really complicated.
Growing up is tough.
I'm sure with those Shrek's kids.
So like I haven't seen the films.
I haven't seen three or four.
Donkey and Dragons kids are cute.
Oh yeah.
Donkey and Dragons have kids.
Yeah.
Oh and there's a statue in Singapore of the the the the donkey dragon kids called
the dronkies.
Yeah.
It's a pretty horrifying statue and I didn't recognize them because I haven't seen
the films.
I got the official bug main ruling on the Shrek's.
He said two and four.
Oh.
Two and four.
Two and four are the best.
So he says I don't know.
And can anyone vouch for that or not?
Four. I will say this.
Four is kind of interesting.
It's a it's a wonderful life.
Yeah.
Essentially.
Oh wow.
I think I saw two and three.
I cannot remember any.
Whoa.
The parents.
Fiona's parents show up.
That's two.
Three is like abysmal.
Three is like memory holding.
I am like reaching for this.
Three is like it feels like it's 60 percent about selling the idea of Justin Timberlake
as a movie star.
Like the same time as Love Guru or whatever.
Yeah. When is Puss in Boots shows up and gets spun off.
Also so Fallon you could also be called the Fallon episode is the Puss in Boots of the
3D movie.
Yes.
That also works.
Separate but real.
Compare this arc to like Illumination.
Yeah. Secret Life of Pets comes out.
Huge hit. Secret Life of Pets 2.
Not so big.
Big drop.
Secret Life of Pets the ride coming 2020 after the big drop.
Yeah. Right.
A different arc.
Right. Right.
That's why the the how train your dragon thing I think aside from the fact that it's
like a good world and it's the kind of thing that like you see a weird amount of how to
train your dragon at like conventions and stuff.
I think people like cosplaying how to train your dragon and all of that.
But it is like a franchise where the numbers dip every time.
And usually I feel like people like to get in like you know when it's hot.
Right. It is interesting with the way that what supposedly the four lands which are
the Nintendo for the new theme park in Orlando Nintendo how to train your dragon.
Fantastic Beasts but I would be not surprised if it's just Harry Potter land three.
Right. They could just do any other area.
Right. Yeah.
So that might be what happens and then Universal Monsters which is great.
But the monsters and the how to train a dragon maybe they're just letting them
imagining imagine you whatever they're called.
Greeners are people do stuff they want to do.
No of course it's not.
It's not possible.
That's how to drag in a cool world.
It could inspire cool attractions.
Yeah.
But also in my head I'm like oh man imagine a dragon riding.
Oh well that imagine dragons ride.
But that's the problem.
Well I first I'd love to see an imagine dragons.
I'd like to hear an imagine dragons ride.
But when I'm like oh it would be cool to do like a ride where you're on the back
of a dragon and then I think oh that's that's Pandora.
That's like they've already done the great American dragon ride.
Sure.
Unless it's a true like coaster somehow.
Which they.
Dueling dragons too.
They just move it over.
Can I bring up this thing of you were talking about the connection like it's it's
like a vital connection between one and two.
How.
That's what I went in rewatching it and I say this not knowing too.
So maybe I just don't know.
But I remember them making a big deal out of that at the time and thinking that
was cool.
But now I'm looking back and like OK so Fiona's in Ogre now.
What else is.
Oh I wouldn't say it's vital.
It was just like that's what they said.
I'm not putting it.
Oh yeah.
I'm not criticizing you Jason said.
No I remember that was such the angle and now I'm just going back to like what
made them feel like nothing that happens.
In Shrek 4D has any bearing on the following three Shrek movies.
No.
Nor the following eight Shrek TV specials.
Yes.
Ghost Farquaad though.
Never ever acknowledged ever again.
I guess the fact that they did pick it up from it's not a reset they do.
That's the one happened in Farquaad is dead and Fiona is an ogre.
But also like the fact that it starts with them like in the onion carriage.
That's like the ending of Shrek one and that it ends with them at the hotel for
their honeymoon.
That is the beginning of Shrek 2.
Like it fits in very tightly.
That's a little neat.
Okay.
Right.
Between the two.
So it's not that it like is important to the story at all but it's so specifically
between those two goalposts.
And it literally is how they move from one location to the other.
I guess then it becomes so strange that it's like it is so specifically not a
Shrek 3D movie but a 3D movie that is a sequel to the first Shrek.
While they're like spinning their wild plans of like a Christmas special, a
Halloween special, you know, like all of this.
They're making this like thing that's going to, you know, it stuck between as
opposed to T2.
It doesn't feel as weird.
It's clearly between two and three.
But three feels like such a different thing.
It's like one, one, two and T2 3D are one item for sure.
Right.
And it was like Cameron's final statement at least.
Like even if they make these other entries because they're not Cameron, it's
like, well, that's not canon and it doesn't really count and all that sort of stuff.
But all the Shrek is all it's all Shrek.
I'm trying to think of like if there was a Star Wars 3D movie in between
Force Awakens and Last Jedi.
That's what it's like.
The Saber.
Yeah, sort of.
We're in a, this is a land between Last Jedi and Rise of Skywalker.
Yes, it is.
As it stands now.
Will it stay that way?
I don't know.
That's technically what it is currently.
Yes.
So pop culture is just a land between like all of pop culture is Shrek 4D now.
It's just a little connective unnecessary bit.
Rogue One is Shrek 4D.
It's plugging in pieces.
Right.
And taking you right up to the room where the next one's there.
It's right.
That's the Shrek 4D thing where it's like you can start at the original Star Wars
and everything you need to know is in the body of that film.
And Shrek 4D is being like, wait, wait, wait, no, you need to understand how they
got to the hotel.
And certainly you can get on Star Tours and not know one fucking thing.
Right.
So I find it weird how plotty it is in that sense that it's so directly in
dialogue with the two movies.
There's this crazy stat where we watched the same Yesterland video.
Oh, yeah.
Good video.
And I also watched a iPhone video of it on YouTube where for the pre-show it was
vertical. Then it went horizontal.
A Quibi style.
Quibi style.
Yeah.
And it was obviously a little blurry because it wasn't 4D.
I think I can summarize it real quick.
Shrek and Fiona are on their way to their honeymoon.
Shrek wants to take a shortcut through a scary part of the woods.
Then Ghost Farquaad shows up and him and Thelonious kidnap Fiona.
There's a chase scene through the scary woods.
They want to kill Fiona so that she can be his ghost bride.
Yes.
There is a statue with Farquaad on a big pillar killing the dragon.
He's rewritten history.
That's how they get the...
In his death, he's rewritten history somehow.
He's somehow rewritten history.
That's where we get the second reference to see a compensator for.
But the end of the first Shrek is Fiona and Farquaad are getting married and Shrek
rides the dragon through the stained glass of the church and has the dragon eat
Farquaad alive and then is like, we're getting married and runs off.
I'm a believer.
Cut to credits.
Right.
Yeah.
It's the graduate ending.
Right.
Kind of.
This movie has this weird thing where it's like somehow in death Farquaad.
And this is a fairy tale universe.
Right.
Yeah.
You have all sorts of magical creatures, but there's no sign of the afterlife in
the first Shrek and like Farquaad is this very well connected ghost who's in
regular conversation seemingly with his living henchmen, Thelonious, and is
planning this multi step, like lure them to the forest with this statue that was
built to correct the narrative of my death.
Which didn't that just happen?
Just happened.
He hasn't missed a beat.
They're on their honeymoon.
Yeah.
He hasn't.
There's been no problem.
Like it's just he went from one form to another and it's just business as usual.
And just immediately started talking with him.
He has as much power as he ever had.
Right.
He's the most powerful ghost of all time.
He inhabits the stone dragon statue, brings it to life.
So then there's a dragon versus dragon chase sequence.
Right.
Wouldn't it be real?
I'm just thinking out loud here.
Wouldn't that be nice if that is how it worked?
You just like all of a sudden you like died and you were ghost and it's just like
normal, but I'm around and I can talk to my friends.
Yeah, everything's fine.
I just keep doing episodes.
Yeah.
It's all into a go past her day.
Isn't that going to be like one of the tossed out ideas for a Ghostbusters
sequel was like Bill Murray helps train the new Ghostbusters.
But he's a ghost.
That was sounds so much better.
And also with Farley part, maybe his whole thing for years and years was they'd be
like Bill Ghostbusters three and he'd be like, I don't want to do it.
I'll only do it if you kill me off.
And that was just his way of saying like, fuck off.
Right.
I don't care.
And they like teams and teams of writers over 15 years were like, OK, so act one is
Bill Murray dies, too, is he comes back as a ghost.
Like everyone was constantly trying to crack the like Bill Murray dies in the first
act Ghostbusters movie, they would have called him and he would have been like,
no, that's not right.
I meant, don't bother me.
But there was one that was like it was pointedly like it was him mentoring Oscar,
the baby from Ghostbusters to as a ghost.
Was that the year one guy's script?
I believe that was that.
Yeah, I bet he died.
I bet they've cracked it in the new one and he does die.
Bill, you think he dies?
I think he gets a Han Solo like noble.
So I bet.
But other but Answer the Call universe, Bill Murray is still around.
Whatever.
No, he died.
He jumped out a window.
I didn't see the movie.
He's dressed like Paul Feig and he jumps out a window.
They killed him.
Oh, yeah.
So that's the joke in there.
I realize now I saw like a grainy video of Akred's cameo, but not Murray's cameo.
So I contend that Murray's cameo was the good one in that movie.
I think Sigourney Weaver's is a good one because it makes sense.
You know what? They're the good two.
The other ones are all like fucking stab me in the eyes.
I'm a big Answer the Call defender.
I like it a lot as a movie.
But any time they have someone come on and say the inverse of the line they used to say,
I want to murder myself.
Which Dan Akroyd pioneered in Casper with when he runs out of the house.
Who are you going to call?
Right.
Somebody else.
Also, we should have of course said at this point, we've defeated boss Dan Akroyd.
Oh, we've already.
Oh, yeah.
It's funny to be talking about this post defeating a ghostly.
These are major spoilers.
For you, not for a listener.
You know about it.
We're in the underworld and we fought and defeated Dan Akroyd.
Of course, as one does.
Yeah, yes.
It's all ironic to be talking about this.
Yeah, we survived and you can listen to it at patreon.com.
Slashbox guys are right.
The underworld episode.
That's one of those things where I'm like watching this.
I'm like, I found this so I would have found this so funny as a 12 year old.
And right now it makes me want to vomit when when Donkey says didn't.
Oh, I know you died in the first movie to Far Quad's ghost.
It's not a self reflexive.
If you decide you're that early on.
Right.
Wayne's world knows it's that, you know, pretty quick.
Totally.
He's talking to you pretty fast.
So that's a but you can't if you've never done anything like that, you can't do it
in the 40 theme park movie.
And there's a weird amount of fourth wall breaks where like Far Quad's ghost like
pops out and like shushes the audience.
Like, don't tell them I'm a ghost.
Fiona does the Matrix jump kick spin again.
But Philonis gets her this time.
Right.
They like there are a lot of pop culture references.
But oh, he says I see dead people.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Like there's so much stuff that's so like it's it's dated both in terms of where
they're placing it within the larger Shrek mythology, and it's dated in terms
of every joke they're making there.
This is I'm side noting too much.
This really all of this makes me think that
Deadpool really deserves a 3D film in a theme park.
Deadpool almost is is being short shrifted
by only getting mainstream theatrical movies and not theme park attraction.
Yes.
That is Deadpool's ultimate medium.
What if also that's the first time we made it out of this before, if you get
carted in a theme park attraction for the first time.
It's not a bad idea.
All these, as I said, all of these theaters are all husks in the Disney parks.
You turn them at that Tomorrowland when the former EO turned that into a 17 and up
only Deadpool attraction as soon as a kid sneaks in, though they're screwed.
So the 12 year old comics are technically like PG 13.
Sure.
There's like one or two runs.
OK, you could listen to that.
That's more.
You can still make some of his like cutting pop culture remarks.
You call somebody Rosie O'Donnell or something.
You can know that he's part of a theme park attraction.
He can reference how much the tickets cost.
Right.
And he would also say like he would say,
maybe I can't say the words I normally would say.
Right.
So there's that.
I can't say it's a lot of Bob Chapek.
Yeah.
And of course, call up parks ahead of consumer products.
Call out the recent loss of themed entertainment,
themed performers in the Bob Chapek, the Farquad of Disney parks.
Yeah.
He'll be bugging us past his death.
There's a weird there's like another there's like stuff that like Donkey calls
himself a noble steed, which I think is a call back to the first Shrek movie.
When he flies away, he yells about waffles.
And Fiona's like, what was that about waffles?
And Shrek's like, oh, it's a long story.
Right.
And it's like that doesn't really pay off.
There are callbacks like that that don't even function as like jokes.
They're just kind of victory laps.
Yes.
Also, like you remember this thing from a year ago that you liked?
Like Donkey was well, I want to know the logic of the travel itinerant.
Like Donkey was coming on the honeymoon with them.
But then at the end, he goes home back.
Let's go home, sweetie, to the dragon.
And it's like implying they're going to make waffles and fuck.
And like Shrek and Fiona are like, OK, now we can fuck.
But then there's a big party.
So then there's a party that Donkey and the dragon are not at.
But the three blind mice are there.
I have not seen Shrek 2 since I saw it probably three times in theaters when it
was released. But from what I remember, it starts on their honeymoon,
opening credit montage of them enjoying their honeymoon set to
Accidentally in Love by Cannon Crows and Academy Award nominated song.
I remember that performance.
And then they're like in bed, like post-coital.
And Donkey like pops up in between the two of them.
Like, I remember Donkey's introduction to Shrek 2 being a joke that he is
showing up out of nowhere in an intimate moment.
I'm all but certain that's how Donkey's introduced.
So they need to explain why Donkey isn't with them for the latter leg of their trip
to the hotel, but also can't make a movie without Donkey.
So they have to explain why he's going with them on their honeymoon to a point.
I feel like the movie is also
is what happened that they go on their actual honeymoon, which is quickly wrapped
up and then it's getting past the honeymoon stage of the relationship where they start
to go through challenges and tribulations.
And it's like the honeymoon is over.
You could argue the honeymoon is ogre.
And that is kind of the main conflict of Shrek 2.
Yeah.
Does he in that where you end up at the end of Shrek 4D in that honeymoon suite
hotel, whatever is that does he get her pregnant in that?
No, the babies come in at the end of Shrek 3.
Oh, not for all.
OK. How many babies does he have?
I should know the names of all of his babies.
Like you should.
Seven.
OK, I do like them.
I don't know their names.
I don't know what they look like, but I do well say I like all seven of them.
I like the baby Grinch.
Of course, you are like baby Grinch.
Baby Grinch is they all have very distinct names and they have like such extensive
merchandise lines of like these are their different personalities, like Shloopies,
like the sporty one, you know, like things that are not in the movie at all.
But it was so clear they were like, this is like our Cabbage Patch kids.
We can sell a green base and they're multiples.
Oh, Scott, you're going to hate them.
Yes, they won't see this.
No wonder three is the worst.
They're fucking shitty.
Yeah.
So they why did you like them?
Contrary, I like them.
Yeah, I like them.
I met them.
They're like my own children.
I like to be the picture of one of the ogre triplets.
No, it's a big thumb.
Are there only three of I could have sworn there were like this is ogre triplets.
There's three, but a handful of that is like seven Shrek father, Fiona mother,
unnamed paternal grandfather, unnamed paternal grandmother.
Sure.
Why do they list that?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Shrek's parents never show up.
Yeah.
Oh, well, that really four movies and Shrek's parents.
There's no Meet the Parents with Shrek.
Well, Shrek 2 is Meet the Parents with Fiona's parents.
Meet the Fokkers, we should say.
You never get the Meet the Fokkers, which would have been Meeting the Ogres.
The Shrek book is largely about, from what I remember,
I know this was a big part of when they did Shrek on Broadway,
that Shrek was born so ugly, his parents threw him in a ditch.
Jeez.
And that was part of the anime movies for so long in the various incarnations
of this film before the first Shrek comes into existence.
Like Max Shrek's friend, the Penguin.
Correct.
That it was a Penguin-esque backstory, and that's why Shrek became so grumpy.
Hmm.
Farkel, Fergus, and Felicia.
Oh, Fergus.
Everyone say it with me.
Farkel, Fergus, and Felicia.
We got to make Farkel and Fergus and Felicia shirts.
Oh, the ands ands.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And unknown paternal grandfather.
Why not?
Farkel and Fergus and Felicia and Griffin Newman.
Oh, my.
Shrek and Fiona's four children.
So my memory is right.
Shrek 1 is the courtship.
Shrek 2 is the honeymoon, them getting over the parents.
Shrek sort of overcoming his sense of inferiority about being lower class than
Fiona, she of royalty.
Shrek 3, she gets pregnant at the beginning.
And then most of the movie is him being like, oh, fuck, I don't know if I can
handle this. And he goes on this weird road trip with Justin Timberlake playing
King Arthur, but he's like a brat.
And most of the movie is just like, we want you to buy Justin Timberlake as a
movie star.
And then the babies are born at the very end.
And Shrek 4 is like House of Handfuls.
I can't take this.
I don't have a social life anymore.
Remember when Donkey and I used to hang out the good old days.
So he wishes that the previous Shrek movies hadn't happened.
Oh, that's why.
It's a wonderful way.
OK, OK.
So Shrek 4 ends with him being like, I do want to be in this franchise.
OK, franchise over.
And yet, yeah, then it disappeared.
So that we have to explore the children in the next movies, however they come out.
They could be grown now.
That's the question.
Farkle goes to college.
Well, maybe a movie.
A movie for each triplet.
We should see all of their college adventures.
They all go vastly across, far, far away.
Where do they live? Is that right?
Three kids just like the Roy.
Shiv and Kendall and Romulus.
Fighting for the Shrek fortune.
Shrek star.
Shrek session.
That's it.
That's the reboot.
I found a People magazine article from May 1st, 2007, exclusive Shrek's babies
revealed. So Shrek had a baby reveal.
He sold it to the media, to people.
What a whore.
I graduated college.
Shrek had babies.
2007, hell of a year for all of us.
So just a little odd little fact I found reading about this that kind of ties into
running stuff into the ground.
The voice actor who was the voice of Pinocchio and the three blind mice.
I thought I had his name.
I've lost his name.
I don't have this connected to Wi-Fi.
He also directed Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs 2 and Open Season 3.
Did you guys know there were three open season?
No.
I think, are there not four now?
Are there four open season?
I feel like there might be a fourth now.
I'll have to look this up.
Yikes.
I have something to say about these.
Me not being a particularly big Shrek fan.
I think it's often a ripe area.
The voices that are clearly done not by a famous person, but by a behind the scenes
member of the animation team.
Joe Ranft as Heimlich in Bugs Life.
That was the big breakthrough.
Brad Bird as Nemoad.
Some fantastic characters have that equation.
Most infamously, Walt Dorn as the voice of Rumpelstiltskin in Shrek Forever After.
Walt Dorn.
Good pull.
I've got a Dorn head over here.
I feel bad.
I don't want to insult these specific people who are clearly great directors and everything.
I can tell.
I think there's something that bothers me about Shrek.
All of the pigs in the gingerbread myth.
I don't love them the way I love Nemoad or Heimlich.
I feel like that trick doesn't work that well.
The animator doing the voice.
I feel like it's like, voices anybody could do.
That's actually, by the way, very accurate.
I've tried that once at home and that's it.
It's not very practiced.
So it goes to show.
You can just throw it out.
I don't know.
That's just, I think, a criticism I have about this attraction.
I watched it and I'm like, oh, and these are animators who worked on the movie.
I know this is...
Cody Cameron.
Okay.
There were three open seasons and an open season, Colin's Scared Silly,
which I think was a Halloween direct to video.
Because we should mention on Netflix, where a form of Shrek 4D is currently viewable,
it is filed under Shrek's Spooky Tales,
which is a little Netflix subheading for DreamWorks Halloween specials.
Can I really quickly...
It's retitled The Ghost, The Tale of the Ghost of Lord Farquaad or something like that.
The Ghost of Farquaad.
I have the breakdown.
So this was released on DVD with Shrek 2 as Shrek 3D.
Yes.
And it's a DreamWorks spooky story as the Ghost of Lord Farquaad.
It aired on Nickelodeon as Shrek's never-before-seen adventure,
despite coming after several of these airings.
And that was aired right before Shrek the Third came out.
It was in the drum up of Shrek.
Okay, okay.
Shrek Third.
And then also as part of something called Shrek's Thrilling Tales.
And it was published as a comic book by Dark Horse Comics.
So this has been...
They've just fucking beaten this one thing into the ground.
Is there any other prominent thing like this,
where they showed the 3D DreamPark movie on TV and on Netflix?
Captain Eo showed...
There was a Michael Jackson marathon on VH1 in like 97.
And it was the only TV airing of Captain Eo.
And that's the only reason anybody could see it in any way,
because that was taped off TV.
During a Michael Jackson A to Z, they showed everything.
Wow.
But like a non-3D, a 4 by 3.
And that's how people...
So it wasn't the ultimate...
Is that why people even have it on YouTube?
Yes, exactly.
Yeah.
Or they would have to...
That's why it has like credits and stuff you don't see in the...
But like, right.
Like Shrek was released...
Like Shrek 3D was released as a DVD that was packaged with the first Shrek.
When Shrek 2 was coming out,
it has its own case that Shrek wearing red and blue 3D glasses...
Oh, and they give you glasses.
...comes with red and blue 3D glasses.
And you could watch it DVD quality at your home.
It was a disc with just 12 minutes on it.
DreamWorks was very candy about this.
They had the full team back.
They had like the A-listers working on the Shrek 3D, 4D.
They working on that movie.
Katzenberg oversaw the same thing.
They retained the rights.
That was their whole thing.
Which is how they were able...
We would love a Shrek attraction.
They're like, we'll make a Shrek attraction and give it to you.
And that's how they were able to sell it as a DVD and sell it to other theme parks too.
It would be great if we knew how much money Shrek 4D made.
I would love...
What if it's the most successful film of all?
That is what I'm getting at.
Per minute, it certainly could be.
12 minutes.
But that's nuts to me in terms of just the beginning of the end of things becoming a little less special.
You go like Shrek 4D opens at two theme parks in the United States of America
and a year later is available on DVD.
Yeah, that's the part.
The attendance stayed high for a while, but you're just like...
Fucking bloom off the rose.
We're two movies past this in terms of chronology.
It's available in four home media formats.
It's airing on Nickelodeon.
Like, what is this?
It's unrelated theme parks in Germany.
And it's so bad, minus the 3D effects.
Like, there are so many sort of like super sweaty, like someone throws a thing at the screen.
Someone pokes their finger in the audience's eye.
That is one of the worst ones I've ever seen where Shrek goes to the carriage.
That might be the worst 3D in your face I've ever seen.
They were also like these were all sent out.
Like all these tropes have been sent up already.
Many not even just in Muppets or something like just other places.
I think that's what's so embarrassing about it is like Shrek is like trying to get off on being like the Deadpool of its time.
Like, look at us.
We're acknowledging the frame.
We're calling out the bullshit of this other like family entertainment, like the tropes of fairy tales and everything.
But then Shrek is earnestly doing the hokeyist 3D movie tricks without any self-awareness.
Yeah.
And it's like you want at the very least Donkey to be calling out like that would look good in 3D.
As much as I wouldn't respect that comedically, I would respect it artistically as part of an attraction.
It would be more in line with what the franchise is.
Totally.
And that they do it once and it's a bad thing.
It doesn't need to be.
He doesn't need to say you died in the first movie.
He probably does need to say, aren't these some cheap 3D tricks?
Right.
Because otherwise, like the pre-show stuff is all like talking to the audience.
Like the magic mirrors talk in the audience.
The pigs are talking to you.
They're explaining that they need to keep you in lockdown to interrogate you.
Like the premise is that they're going to lock you in a room to interrogate you.
And then just a movie starts and the movie just occasionally characters look at you.
You're not like part of the narrative in the way that like T2 3D.
It's like very clear of like they're hacking the system and now you're getting a glimpse into the future.
And they're here at the Cyberdyne presentation and all that.
Muppet Vision is a show for you.
But it begins with the Kimberly Duncan and everything to get.
And then like, and now we go to film shots.
But then you get live action people coming in as well.
Like it's moving back and forth.
Muppet Vision is a show for the audience.
Like Honey, I Shrunk the Audience is a presentation for the audience.
I wonder if they just worked backwards and we're like, all right, we need like the seats will move.
So we just need a place where they like going fast through something.
And we need a place where and they just like, just throw some jokes in there and no one's.
But also, nonspecific enough that you can probably transfer it to parks who don't want to pay for the full modification.
Yes, that's true too.
Yes, that you can sort of do that.
I mean, I think that's like pre show.
I think a lot of the success of that SpongeBob movie is that like the brand is strong and they have made it in a way where it works in any.
For the theater, you know, like basics, there's not yet.
And they don't have to build the theater to do it.
If you have smells, then maybe they can put water in there.
Water spray.
I mean, this has bubbles.
But it's not like totally reliant on it.
It would be funny to look at like the list, the a la carte list of all the additions for Shrek.
If you were buying it and like, do you want his fart smell?
OK, that's going to be an extra two thousand dollars a month.
Because he farts a lot.
He farts a lot.
Because there's drag, there are bits in this where I was like, why is this happening?
Like the extended like, you know, in a 12 minute short, a full minute devoted to like Fiona crying in the onion carriage.
Yeah.
Like what? You're only supposed to be depressed after you get married.
You know, years later, whatever.
Like a great marriage.
That's all the Shrek franchise just becomes like fucking Kevin can wait.
Like that's what sucks is they just become like fucking middle aged like animators griping about how much
they hate their home lives.
Well, also this the arc of this that you really follow is Gingy just experiencing trauma.
He's locked up, manages to escape, builds a beautiful home and that Shrek and Donkey fuck it up.
Another horrible joke, when they run, when they drive through the gingerbread home,
it looks like Shrek has Austin Powers teeth.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
That's what that gag is. I reround it because I was like, what are they doing?
And then I realized that's the bit.
It's that the filling, the cream and the gingerbread now resembles Austin Powers mouth.
Wow. I don't know if I've ever picked up on that.
I thought it because that's just like a Looney Tunes gag too with the piano.
Right.
But it clearly looks off.
It's too specific.
I was like, there's something going on here.
I'm not getting I reround it because I was like, did it play into an effect in the theater somehow?
And then that thing with the onion carriage was like that where I was like,
why is this much time devoted to this?
It doesn't really have any bearing on the rest of it.
It's not like there's any emotional arc about like because she says like,
no, I'm not crying about my marriage.
I'm crying about the onion.
I was like, oh, right. I think there were onion smells.
It's really stagnant too.
And you can barely see her.
Why are we just watching a half visible?
I think it was a smell.
I think it was a smell thing from my memory where they're like introducing the scent
thing because there are a couple other moments like the farts or whatever.
We're like, that was clearly a smell.
Yes.
You know, I'll say this.
Some things I like about it.
One great spot to cool down for 15 minutes.
Great spots to cool down for 15 minutes.
There is I'm trying to think of what the other gag I liked is,
but I like the gag where Thelonious and Fiona are on the raft and he cuts the rope
and Farquaad is yelling, you idiot, you're still on the raft.
And he's like, oh, like he's floating away.
Oh, that's a solid gag.
And then you get a crotch hit and then you get a crotch.
You get a big crotch hit.
Yeah, so much dick stuff.
Yeah.
Pinocchio's nose is the boner at the end.
And that doesn't really make sense.
That doesn't really make sense.
I caught that the last time we saw it before it closed.
Nose grows.
But it's like, what's what?
Because they're all talking like he's going to have sex with the dragon.
And then Fiona and Shrek are also, I think,
what they're saying something to each other about a honeymoon or whatever.
The joke is like he wedges in between the two of them.
They say, what are you doing here?
He says nothing.
And then his nose grows.
Right. He's horny.
What the fuck?
The implication is like he's there to do something salacious.
Yes.
That is the illusion of a joke.
He's going to jerk off because he's thinking about either Shrek and Fiona or the dragon.
He just drooled the people and rented the room next to theirs.
Yes.
It is the dirt.
Hiding in the vents.
It's the most nonsensical dirty joke in a theme park, I think.
The rules of ghosts in this world, too, are that the dragon saves them at the end,
can shoot a fireball at this ghost, and then it becomes little tiny ghosts that dissipate.
Yeah, what the fuck?
That's a bit of a leap for me.
The resolution of this movie is, oh, they kill the ghost.
Shoot it with a gun.
What are you talking about?
That's the problem that you were saying, Mike, that if you just died and were a ghost
and everything was the same, don't forget about second death.
Yeah.
Right.
Yes, that's true.
You're right.
So the first one hurts so much.
No problem.
You become Ghost Mike and you're so much more powerful.
You have all the same relationships you had.
Your friends are there for you.
Second death, you become like a thousand little Mikes and they suck and they can't do shit.
Yeah.
You're just heads.
They should really.
So wait, Farquaad never came back.
No, no.
He's like a quick fantasy.
No, he is not like the grand villain of the Shrek franchise.
It's weird that they were like, oh, we're going to make the Shrek theme park
attraction specifically be the Farquaad resolution, the Farquaad epilogue.
That is not necessary because the first movie ends with the Farquaad being eaten alive.
Yeah.
So maybe the new Shrek movie is just called Farquaads,
and it's about all the ghosts, the different ghosts.
We'll hear briefly.
Yeah.
Isn't it?
How much does it not land?
The moment of he's back like they yell in the pre show that Farquaad's back and that's
supposed to hit you right in the chest.
Yeah.
This iconic villain.
He's like, who care?
And why would he be?
And so here's the funny thing that later for me is reading about this movie is they
were all paid like 300,000.
Great.
I'd just rather bring this up.
OK, yeah, go ahead.
No, no.
The first Shrek movie, $300,000 for the four of them, right?
For Lithgow Myers, Diaz, Murphy.
Right.
300,000, which at the time was pretty good.
No one gets paid that much for being a voiceover in an animated film.
They had no sequel contracts.
So for the sequels, which they're starting production like two months later,
they got to strike while the iron's hot.
Murphy, Diaz and Mike Myers each got $10 million.
$10 million.
But then baked into the contract was you got to do Shrek 4D.
Like that's pro bono.
Like that's part of the deal.
Whereas Lithgow, they were like, hey,
can you do us a favor and come back and do this theme park?
Right.
How much does it suck to be John Lithgow?
Where everyone else, the theme park thing is like fine.
That's just like icing on the cake.
Whatever.
I'm going to buy four new homes.
They got to have tossed him like a few hundred thousand.
Yeah.
He got scale.
Right.
He got theme park money.
Oh, no.
We've heard it's not good.
Nothing seems to indicate that it's good.
Myers and Murphy did go to the premiere.
They were at the universe.
Shrek 4D?
Yeah.
They came to Universal Studios Hollywood and were at the premiere.
And just really quick, other people there.
Too notoriously anti-social, like anti-press.
It was weird to see them hanging around with Katzenberg.
Also at the premiere, Christine Lottie, Michael York, Austin Powers buddy.
Then married Bradley Whitford and Jane Kaczmarek.
Richard Schiff, Keenan Iverwey, and Donald Logue, Michael Gross,
and Richard Dean Anderson and Childs.
Wow.
Starst...
Yeah, very strange.
And Childs.
Yeah.
Most of the Getty Images has like 400 photos of Richard Dean Anderson and his kid.
And Childs.
So...
Ferkel.
Ferkel Dean Anderson.
That is the very end of 90s coupled, Kaczmarek-Whitford.
Yeah, right.
Star of Malcolm in the Middle, Star of West Wing.
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
They were ruling like prime time at that point.
Yeah.
So on Blank Check, my podcast, we finished recording them, but they're still coming out.
I guess by the time this comes out, they'll be done.
But we were doing all the Miyazaki films.
We went through his whole filmography.
And in our episode on Spirited Away, we started out talking a lot about Shrek,
because I was like, this is a really interesting counterpoint.
Like, Spirited Away versus Shrek, they both technically come out the same year.
Oscar nominees against each other?
Spirited Away doesn't get released in the States until the following year.
So it then wins the second best animated.
Holy weird, Shrek then Spirited Away.
Right.
So Shrek wins the first year, Spirited Away wins the second year,
but they both are released everywhere else in the world in 2001.
And they could not be further apart as films.
And our guest, David Reese, has not seen any of the Shrek films.
And I was trying to explain to him, like, there was a movie that won an Oscar
that was like very seriously in the mix to win the Palme d'Or con that opens with
Shrek ripping a page out of a storybook to wipe his ass,
the sound of flushing in an outhouse.
And then he kicks open the door to All-Star by Smash Mouth,
which had already was two years old for Mystery Man.
It's already in a movie.
It's the weirdest thing.
And this was taken very seriously, this film.
So that started this whole jag about, like, how much worse Shrek has aged
than Spirited Away, which some of that is the runoff of, like,
the shittier versions of Shrek.
Because I think the original Shrek is, like, half good.
I think there's half respectable qualities to it.
Yeah, sure.
I think it is weird in that it is so much existing in sort of like direct response
to Disney that it just has the least appeal in color palette of all time.
Well, I knew you're portraying all those other things.
They're having to show all of the Disney characters, but not Disney-ify the princesses.
They're just uglier versions of all those character designs.
Yeah, those choices.
And it's that weird balance of, like, the humans are a little too photorealistic.
Like, they're not really stylized enough.
Their facial hair is gross.
But it also, like, that movie has, like, a color palette that's entirely dirt and split pea soup.
You know, like split pea soup.
It's all, like...
It's very pale. It's a pale film.
It's very pale and, like, earthy in a bad way.
But there's stuff in it that's respectable.
There's some basic storytelling fundamentals.
It works as a thing.
It has, like, emotions in it, unlike the later entries, which become so, like, just gag bullshit.
But there's the half of it that ages so badly, which is just, like,
hey, we all agree that Disney's, like, bullshit.
Make fun of the theme parks.
Make fun of these stories.
Have Fiona, like, sing, but her singing's so bad it kills a bird.
Like, all this shit, right?
And, like, the movie star personas and all of that.
And when this comes out, I'm, like, 12 or 13, and my sister's a bunch younger.
So I went to see Shrek with her when she was, like, four.
And she loved Shrek.
And a thing that I didn't think about until we were, like, a couple Shreks in was, like,
oh, my sister did not grow up with the Disney classics.
Like, Shrek came in at the point in time when she would have started watching those movies.
She was three, maybe?
And so for her and a bunch of people of that generation,
their perception of the fairy tales was the versions from Shrek
over the versions that the Shrek versions are just riffing on.
Wow.
Like, it's this weird copy of a copy thing
where, like, you're getting the cynical version of the thing
rather than the earnest version of the thing.
And they're all too young to remember September 11th.
Right.
So it's a really warped point of view.
My sister thought that was just a big fire.
It was visible out our window in New York City.
They went, that's just a big fire.
Did Farquaad do this?
Yes.
That was her first question.
Was it visible out your window?
Yeah.
But this was, I said, I didn't get into that sort of detail,
but I was talking about how poorly Shrek has aged.
And it became the most controversial thing I have ever said on my podcast.
People were irate.
And I was like, I just think Shrek, like, no one has fond memories of Shrek.
And I said that confidently because there's such a fucking culture
of weird Shrek memes that feel like kids who grew up with Shrek,
who are now 24, looking at Shrek and being like, Shrek is weird,
and then meme-ifying it.
I assumed it was a whole generation rejecting.
It's like the first, we just realized that things can be bad.
And this is the sacrificial lamb.
That Shrek is kind of like cynical and gross.
And like, let's make fun of how cynical it was by, like, having Shrek
make out with Hitler or like whatever.
And do it like the 10-hour loops and bizarre and Shrek speeds up every time they say Shrek.
The same thing as B-movie, where B-movie also feels like,
oh, this is so weird that we watch this as children.
But is it just that they, like, our generation has meme-ified
The Simpsons to death and we love The Simpsons.
Are they doing it to Shrek because they love Shrek?
That's what's weird is it does feel like there are people who still have...
And look, like, we're dudes who are super nostalgic
for a bunch of things that people think are dumb.
And all of us will stomp and like stand tall and argue for eight hours
why the things have merit and artistic integrity.
So I'm never going to like shit on anyone else for liking a thing
that I think doesn't age well.
But my underlying thesis was like, I think it looks bad now.
I think it's a very product, very much a product of that time
in CGI animation and the capabilities.
Whereas, like, Pixar was more stylized.
Shrek was going for a level of detail that now just looks kind of crappy.
And also that the film is so cynical, I'm like, I can't imagine
you would have like emotional, like, well, you know, like Shrek and Fiona
and Donkey meant a lot to me, like, growing up.
You know?
Right, you'd watch it now and you'd be like, these characters suck.
Like, I liked them at the time too.
Like, I saw these movies, I saw them with my sister,
but I don't feel like my sister has any sort of like lost love for Shrek
where she does for other, like, Daddy Daycare was like her movie
that she watched all the fucking time.
And she's got this weird childhood, like, nostalgia for Eddie Murphy.
But it's like, it's that, you know?
Like, that's her one.
But are you saying people were upset with you because they do
legitimately like Shrek?
Yes, I guess they were upset with me saying, I don't think anyone
legitimately like Shrek, which I agree was maybe a little bit too broad of a brush.
But I was reacting more to the the meme culture, like it.
But I think it is what you were talking about.
Some, I mean, people are, I feel like I read a couple things saying,
like, the new Joker movie is not, it's less about the Joker,
the comic book character, or it's about trying to process the Joker
as cultural icon in the last 10, 15 years.
It's processing the Heath Ledger Joker.
But like, Spirited Away, a movie I would call haunting, moving,
exhibit, archived in film archives, shown in museums.
Cinema.
Cinema, like cinema.
You know, not in the park.
Not paranormal.
The same thing showing it to anyone at any age, at any time.
Like it will always have a power.
Subs or dubs?
What did you guys settle on?
We mostly did subs.
The only one I watched with dubs of Howl's Moving Castle was because I was tired.
Which they sometimes get like dubs for those Miyazaki movies are star studded
affairs like Shrek.
And feel like Kiki's delivery service.
He's the cat.
But they very much feel like, oh, who are the people in the Disney stable?
Or who are people who are big at that specific moment?
Where like Shia LaBeouf is like the sort of innocuous young male love interest,
I think, in Nausicaa Valley of the Wind, where you're like a year later,
he was a leading man.
Yeah.
You know, and a year, like two years earlier, he was even Stevens.
And that's the one transition, like the greatest game ever played zone
where he would do that.
But the Shrek thing, yeah, it's very bizarre to me.
And I also just feel like now Disney has sort of so reclaimed their territory
where they've like even like more greatly perfected the Princess musical.
And I've made. Oh, yeah.
And ones that don't need to be like they don't.
We don't have to make fun of the tropes of damsel in distress and that kind of
thing. We can make fun of ourselves.
All the princesses show up and wreck it, Ralph, too.
And like in What's Her Name and Frozen, she burps.
Totally. Yeah.
That's the thing.
They took the wind out of Shrek sales.
They were like like Tangled is like self aware, but sincere, you know?
Yeah.
So then that for me just makes Shrek feel like completely obsolete.
We don't need it. We grew out of Shrek.
Yeah.
But for a certain like the prequels for a certain generation,
that was their special thing.
Totally right.
Which, you know, it's like I'm a little younger than you guys.
I was like the upper end of middle school,
which was like, you know, and you're at the beginning of high school.
No, for Shrek.
I'm saying.
OK, right.
Yes.
Yeah.
And that's like the zone where you were like, oh, it's like this one's actually
kind of edgy. Like we can like all go see this together.
Sure.
And then I feel like Shrek 2 I saw and it almost felt like nostalgia.
And by Shrek 3, everyone was like, we're not seeing this.
Like all my friends my age were like 16.
We're not going to see this, you know?
But your sister being younger and staggered with Shrek in a different manner.
Yeah.
How does she feel about the later ones?
I feel like she only ever saw one and two and she was like all in on the first Shrek,
like had Shrek toys and everything.
And then I feel like just diminished returns like, you know,
some other franchise came along that she liked more.
I think, you know what?
It wasn't a franchise. It was Devil Wears Prada.
She realized she could watch movies about women having careers.
And my sister was like, oh, no, no, this is the thing I like.
Oh, my sister always was just from a very young age into movies where people have
to like navigate office culture.
That was like we're like divorce movies, like rebounding after divorce.
So if Shrek was in the Devil Wears Prada.
Love it. Oh, yeah.
It would be perfect.
Now, too cheap.
Yeah, the bricks.
But it was there was a weird thing where like Shrek 2 was at the time of its
release, the third highest grossing film in history.
It was Titanic, then original Star Wars.
Counting releases and then Shrek 2.
And of course, now it is each.
It's Adam Sandler's Murder Mystery.
Right.
Is that the name of it?
What's it called?
It's just called Murder Mystery.
They're working on a sequel, apparently.
Yeah.
Untitled Murder Mystery.
Murder Mystery grossed what?
Like seven billion hypothetical dollars.
And you love to see it.
We love to see it.
Success in America.
I just had a cursed memes.
Originally were known as viral ideas.
And this might actually make us sick.
Shrek comes back, but it's like Watson and Holmes.
And it's really topical because you can like do CGI quickly now.
So like Shrek is making Trump.
Oh, it's a self photograph.
Well, this is what I want to say.
I don't know if I'm jumping ahead here.
I mean, we got other stuff.
But if we're going to talk, plus it up.
Let's let's do it.
I think we're veering into longest episode territory.
I wouldn't mind Shrek 40 being longest episode is pretty perfect.
That's a good very fun.
Well, I don't want to declare.
We'll see where it goes.
We'll save the parking garage Shrek.
We'll save the Shrek musical for another episode.
I think we have to.
Brian Darcy Daines is a true talent.
Yeah.
Yes.
There's a farting song.
So this obviously right.
They've replaced this with the Dreamworks animation theater, which feels so shitty.
Just in Hollywood.
Still running in Orlando.
Yeah.
Shrek 40 is still in Orlando.
We can go see it.
We're going to go see it.
This thing they bring up in the yesterday video.
Well, you should.
Yeah.
I mean, get in for Falon's before one track for that takes priority.
This thing they bring up in the yesterday video was that even as late as like 2007,
I think attendance was so high for Shrek 40 in Orlando.
They built a second screen, second screen.
There were two theaters so they could double the amount of people seeing it every 20
minutes. In 2015, they upgraded the ride in Hollywood and built a brand new queue
like planters and stuff so it didn't look like shit.
The you know, while when Harry Potter was going to open.
Yeah.
And then they closed it down in 2017 anyway.
What?
Why did why bother?
I don't know.
I wonder if it's like a J.K.
Rowling thing where she's like, nothing around it must look like shit either.
She just hates Shrek.
Yeah.
She just doesn't like Shrek.
She thinks it's cynical.
We didn't even touch on the weird
meet and greet with robot donkey that was operated by someone who was almost
always white.
Well, yeah, you're talking about the waffle cart.
Yes, that's the.
Well, no, there's this other thing where eventually the queue became that there
was a they stopped doing the pigs in the cages.
Yeah.
And there was a donkey who could interact with.
Yeah, you're talking about the donkey in the park.
Yeah.
But there was one that was the pre show as opposed to what you're talking about,
which is also there, which is the donkey outside the attraction waffle cart.
And isn't it?
But that I'm saying the waffle cart is still around.
Am I wrong?
Yeah, I think so.
I believe Wal-Mart is still part of the DreamWorks.
Shrek is still you can find him.
You can find him.
You find the farting troll, you know, all your favorites.
Isn't that so lame, though, that they're just like, oh, in terms of like theming
that now there's just an attraction that is, oh, look, it looks like the offices
where they animated Shark Tale, you know, the actual show.
The office is all our friends are constantly fired from.
Right.
It's like the same thing as like the Fallon thing where it's like,
I understand like Rugfish Center at least is more iconic.
Yeah, that's at least something you might recognize.
Like, oh, I saw this on TV.
Totally.
Well, for a long time, Disney,
Disney Studios in Florida has been like part of it is like you're at the Pixar.
Yeah.
So this is pretty common.
That's yeah, that is what the comparison is.
The mythologizing of the people who make the thing that the rides based off of.
The Quibi offices will eventually be the home of a
there, but what they call minimal office.
We just wanted to do something a little minimal.
And then you walk in and like, this is the nicest place I've been in 14 months.
The Quibi shavers, the Quibi barbershop quartet will sing to you.
My favorite Quibi, Clarence.
Quibi boy.
They are going to go back to some more traditional carnival, like fun house
techniques where the offices like when you enter fun house, the spinning room,
the offices will be long waisted and spin horizontally.
The first room they all change aspect or is this haunted room actually changing
formats?
Well, this is what I was going to say.
So obviously, you know, Dreamworks Theater now, I think the whole idea was
they were like modularity.
We can replace it and add new things that are not specifically themed to one thing.
And I guess have any of you gone on the whatever the country we all have done it
together? We went to preview.
I live close enough by we get preview tickets sometimes to stuff.
How is it?
Would you say it's better or worse than this?
I have not seen it.
It's better because it's new and it looks sharp and everything, but it's a lot of
the same bullshit.
It's the sheet.
The seats shake.
There's a couple effects that are cool.
At the end, there's a cool effect.
It's better because it's brighter.
Right.
Sure.
And there's like it kind of invades the walls a little bit.
I feel like if Trolls World Tour does well, it will be rethemed as a Trolls
attraction within a year.
Maybe.
And that's a smart thing to be able to switch those out because that feels like
the DreamWorks thing that's on an upswing rather than like winding down.
OK, sure.
But here's my like plus it up idea hypothetically, knowing that the thing is
already out of commission.
Sure.
Talking about track, the topical references, the coarseness, right?
The thing to do would have been to replace Bill and Ted's Halloween Spectacular
with a slightly less dark, family friendly pop culture Shrek show.
Oh, that's great.
That is great.
I didn't have that specific thought, but I also as we're doing this, this is very
similar to the Genie from the California Adventure Live show, and it would be perfect.
Get the Genie.
He's out of work.
Bring him in.
Give him a four year contract to play Shrek.
He knows that I have paint on bright color paint on his face.
Yeah.
He's bald.
He knows he knows how to dress up like that.
He did the fat bastard voice at parties so he can do that voice.
I'm sure.
Yeah, there's no doubt.
I'll even I'll say turn the theater, make a new 3D movie.
Yeah, because now that it's passed a little time, he's been around for a little
while the roast of Shrek, all of the characters, all the fairy tale characters
give him what for and then he gives a right back.
What I would love, since it is the DreamWorks theater now, is if it were the roast of Shrek,
featuring a dais of DreamWorks characters outside of the Shrek franchise.
Oh, because there are other characters do factor into the pre show of Kung Fu Panda,
which is a little interesting.
They do start to emerge.
Shrek makes a little appearance before.
That's right.
And there's a cool effect that is sort of exactly the same effect from Guardians of the Galaxy.
The character picks up things.
And Shrek asked to see your hands.
Yeah.
I can't do the voice.
I know I was about to try.
I don't think it's going to be more of the Gingerbread Man.
My hands don't.
No, that's just rocket.
That's rocket.
My fingers are too big.
Hands don't scan.
My hands don't scan.
Fart.
Get in my belly.
So the roast of Shrek.
That's Jason's idea.
And it's live puppeted so that we can reference.
Oh, yeah.
Like, you know, that you look worse than Giuliani.
It should be like 45 minutes long.
Like, it should be like a full people leader kind of show.
I think that is good.
Everyone weeping at the end because it gets hard.
You know, ever since Fiona passed away, I am a single father of three.
I just have a plus it up.
I want humans playing the characters in the next movie.
That's what I want.
My plus it up to the movie franchise is do a live action, live action.
Cats, it's cat style.
But I mean, I want to cast, but I truly don't want any CGI.
You want a fully practical live action.
Fully practical Shrek.
That's the musical.
So get Brian Darcy James back, which again, we'll do a Patreon on this whole musical.
I get Sutton Foster.
All of them are in there and it's just practical Shrek.
I have worked with people who like costume people who worked
in the costume department on the Shrek musical.
And it just sounded like the worst fucking thing in the world.
Like that poor man was just baked inside of this thing.
He couldn't hear.
He couldn't see.
He was like dripping with sweat.
The thing they told me was that they placed
sanitary pads all over his body, in between his flesh and the suit so they could absorb the sweat.
Because it was impossible to take off any part of it.
And what's so weird about it is like at that same point in time,
like Disney has so many musicals running where their costumes are so much more
representational and the Shrek musical, they're like, he has to look like he stepped outside of the fucking cartoon.
SpongeBob musical.
He's just got a hairdo and shorts and shirt.
But you look at every other person, like if you get a photo of the Shrek musical,
everyone else in the cast has like a representational costume.
Only Shrek is stuck.
Me poor Brian.
Here's the thing, though.
Sorry, Brian, you're going to have to do it all again.
And if it's a hit more than once.
So Pam, I don't know.
I'm fine.
I was told it.
I think let's declare it.
Griffin Newman, you survived podcast, The Ride, the 3D film trilogy.
Thank you for bringing this mini franchise to us.
And it does feel like this is the end of an era in a certain way.
You know?
Well, I like and we do move from like what it's late 80s, early 90s to mid 90s to to 2000s.
And this is 2003 and a couple of years later, 3D becomes a mainstream thing.
And also Ride start utilizing screens more with movement.
Sure.
This kind of like sit people down.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, though they still have them.
They don't feel like the events.
And the DreamWorks theater feels so incidental.
Let's put something there.
Right.
Like sit down.
We're watching this.
Yeah, maybe it is the last.
Because the Minions Ride and the Jimmy Fallon Ride are both like the one step
beyond it just being a 3D movie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It does move, but like in a big just a big blunt kind of way.
And Jimmy Fallon.
Yeah, I think we got to do.
You're brave to volunteer and
miss Hagrid's.
We miss the window when there's not a thunderstorm shutting down Hagrid's.
We are on Fallon, an indoor ride we could do all day.
Yep.
Seven times to do for all the new ones.
But let's exit through the NBC gift shop.
Is there anything you'd like to play?
Yeah, Blank Shack with Griffin and David is my podcast.
By the time this comes out, we'll be doing the films of Jonathan Demme.
Oh, that's cool.
Very weird.
Set up for that.
Boy.
And I am on our cartoon president.
I play Jared Kushner on that, of course.
Typecasting.
It's a weird conflict of interest job because I like keep on wanting him to get removed.
Yes, like for the sake of the world.
Right.
But then every time he does, and I'm like, no, another 10 episodes.
Here we go.
Another pick up on the contract.
But if he goes, if he went to jail and there's plots to have him in jail.
Oh, please.
I have pitched that to the writers.
Oh, yeah.
Because I'm like, look, I want to have it both ways.
I want him to get arrested.
And I also want to keep on working on the show.
Yeah.
And then people can still watch the tick on Amazon.
I keep on plugging it because I'm terrified at some point it's going to disappear.
All the all the streamers you do worry.
But I say that to people and they're like, oh, do you know something?
I'm like, no, but I just feel like all of like anything that isn't outright owned by a streamer.
I think in five years, there's going to start being weird purges that people take things back.
I also think there's a weird like we were talking about it earlier with Disney and their stuff.
Like, you know, it feels like the company could have failed.
I still think things are going to fail left and right.
Like, we don't know what things look like in five years.
I think three of these big streaming services are going to collapse in a spectacular fashion.
The book is dead out the door.
Not Quibi.
Not Quibi. Never.
No, no, no.
It wasn't Quibi.
Quibi was 10 tall.
What are we talking about?
Since we said this real quick, I don't know if you guys know the Griffin.
I don't know if you know this.
There's a bunch.
You can just watch a bunch of movies free streaming on IMDB now.
Yes.
Like Shutter Island, the Hey Arnold movie and a movie you're in Draft Day.
Now available on IMDB.
Now on IMDB.
So double feature Draft Day and Hey Arnold movie or Zodiac Draft Day.
IMDB?
It's like turning its own streaming service.
But then it's related to Amazon's, but it has a separate...
I think it's very weird.
The interface is weird.
Does it make your star meter go up when you watch it there?
I don't know. I'm very curious to see.
You know, the Draft Day residuals always tell an interesting story.
Much like an NFL Draft Day in real life.
Well, that's the thing.
I will always get one disproportionately large Draft Day check a year and go like,
whoa, and then I'll remember that is the period of time processing after the actual NFL Draft.
It's like that's the residual check two months after when the actual Draft happens,
where I think it plays on TV more and people like rent it digitally more.
The other big bump I saw was when it went onto airplanes
and I got a crazy residual check.
Airplanes play, really?
It was insane.
I made... This is no exaggeration.
I made more money in one check when it was only playing on airplanes than I did for doing the movie.
Now, that is... I got paid scale for the movie.
Okay, so I'm supposed to...
So it wasn't like an insane...
I didn't get like $120, $1000 on an airplane, but it still was like,
oh, this one check, it has not come out on home video yet.
It is not available for digital rental.
The only place it's viewable is on airplanes.
And I got a check that outnumbered me working five weeks for scale.
Wow.
Yeah.
Whoa, that's nuts.
It was crazy.
So I'm hoping...
These places can't help.
I need to be feels like it might be the perfect platform for Draft Day.
Like there's certain...
You have luck with unorthodox...
It works well in certain areas.
A big flop wasn't even released overseas, but huge on planes.
Watch it on a plane then.
Yeah, folks, watch it on a plane.
Demand Airlines, acquire the circle.
You ever watch the circle?
Are you in the circle?
I am in the circle for like 10 seconds.
Gotta watch the circle now.
Demand it from your wherever, planes, I guess.
Get on a plane and yell, where is the circle?
Where is the circle?
This again?
Another plane full of circle heads?
Call TSA, drag him off the plane.
Well, all right.
So yeah, watch...
Demand the circle to watch Draft Day on an airplane or an IMDB.
That's my big plug.
I'm wiping my previous plugs.
Just watch Draft Day and IMDB.
I want to test the residual structure for IMDB.
Sure.
Yeah, you got to focus the play.
You've brought too many things.
That's going to be the only thing I promote for the next six months.
Good idea.
Just as an experiment.
Perfect.
Well, but we'll side promote Patreon.com slash podcast,
the ride, the second gate where we will eventually do.
I think let's just agree to it.
Race to New York with Jimmy Fallon, with Griffin Newman.
The second you threw it out, I was like, I need to put in my...
Yes, me.
You came off the back wall in the press show.
Me, hello, hi.
I'm in.
I have made so many people unwillingly watch it.
I have taken out my cell phone and gone,
you need to sit here and watch this with me, the ride through.
Come on down to Orlando next week, brother.
I attempt it.
I'm very fascinated with it for reasons I will save for a paywall.
Yes, very much so.
Well, and there's side material.
There's so much to talk about.
There is very, very much to talk about.
So that'll be there eventually.
We also, stemming from Shrek, we should have coordinated it.
We got to do Father of the Pride.
We also announced that at PTR.
We're the do Father of the Pride.
And that's Katzenberg's height off of the Shrek supply.
And that is an example of what you said you wanted, Mike.
Donkey is just in an episode of Father of the Pride, playing Donkey from Shrek.
Yes, thank you.
Yes.
Existing in our universe.
That's the best.
You know why we haven't done it yet.
I think we do have to do it because we said multiple times we'll do it.
I don't think we, anyone's had six hours to carve out to watch a full season.
No, we've been busy.
Yeah, I know.
And I think we do have to, unfortunately.
We do.
That does seem like the premise of the episode.
You should just binge all six hours tonight before you watch Haunted Mansion.
High five, AM.
You know what?
After three hours of podcasting, I'm feeling great.
And we'll definitely follow through with that good idea.
Boy, that first half hour of Haunted Mansion is going to be like more caffeine.
Yeah, like straight into the veins.
Energy. I'll be up for days.
It takes half an hour for them to enter the house and another half an hour after
they enter the house for anything spooky to happen.
Yeah, it's a rough one.
Get ready.
Anyway, happy birthday to my dad.
Oh, yes.
This is always coming out around his birthday, I guess, probably.
Something a little bit past.
Yeah.
Happy anniversary, Shrek.
Happy Shrek-a-verse.
All right.
Well, we've been going for, you know where our things are.
We'll talk to you later.
Bye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production.
Executive produced by Brett Boehm, Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit ForeverDogPodcast.com and subscribe to our
shows on Apple, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter and Instagram
at ForeverDogTeam and liking our page on Facebook.