Forever.
Dog.
The Dead Speak.
Podcast The Ride is back with resolutions for 2020.
Occasionally accurate Harry Potter specifics
and magical creatures called bees.
Lots of bees.
It's the economically named
Hagrid's Magical Creatures Motorbike Adventure
today on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the podcast about theme parks that will, in 2020, cover the Country Bear Jamboree.
I'm Scott Gardner, joined by Jason Sheridan, who is on board, correct?
I am, I'm being a little, starting the new year off blind side.
Yeah, yeah, that's right, coming in hot.
We gotta do it, a lot of you are doing a big ride today.
And Mike Carlson, what do you think?
What?
First of all, I'm a little under the weather.
I'm not prepared for something like this to be railroaded.
I know, I was worried about launching that on you,
considering your health.
I'm being railroaded here, is what I feel like is happening.
But you're being, here's what I'm, you're being railroaded into doing.
Your dream.
This is like, why would you avoid doing,
talking on your podcast about your favorite thing in the world?
People have been waiting, I think it's time.
Yeah, that's true, huh.
I don't know, you know, I think it just like, it feels like,
I think I've said this before, I wanted to go somewhere
and sort of meditate on it and think about doing Country Bears
and feel like if it's the right year to do it.
Sure.
Is 2020 the right year?
I guess we have 12 months to figure out which month it is.
That's what I'm saying, we're at the very,
we're at the very, very beginning, which gives you 11 months
at the, you know, extreme of meditation.
So that's a ton, that's a ton.
This is the most shocking.
We could devote all of December to it,
however you want to frame it, there's so many options.
This is the most shocking start to something
since the rise of Skywalker when we said that,
it's at the Dead's Peak and Emperor Palpatine.
The bears sing.
The bears.
Wow, okay.
Yes, and shocking as a broadcast from a cave.
Oh my gosh.
Yeah, it's, I know, I knew it was gonna throw you,
but I think it's a big year coming in hot.
I have to travel to the Country Bear version of Exegol,
the Sith planet, to talk to.
You're the bad version, you're Palpatine?
No, I'm not Palpatine, I'm Solo.
You're gonna discover dozens and dozens of bears there
waiting for you.
Roar, roar, roar, they kinda like mutter or something.
Built by crowds that are guys or ghosts, eh, what is it?
We're not sure exactly what they were.
I don't know, and thank God we didn't have to find out
much more, because if they had done something,
that would have been, tariff,
that would have thrown me big time.
Yes, we shouldn't spend so much time on Exegol.
We probably will get there on the rise of the Resistance ride.
Yeah.
I assume it goes to Exegol.
I assume you'll be on Exegol.
We're gonna talk about Exegol a lot this year.
I will declare this, Exegol will be the planet
we discuss the most in 2020.
Exegol exclusive.
Good space name, a lot of Xs in it, that's very spacey.
Yes, and I will say I like Exegol, honestly.
I think there could be better uses of it.
It's the planet where there is always lightning.
It is the only all strobe planet.
Uh-huh, there was warnings about that movie
that if you were sensitive to strobe lights,
you shouldn't do it.
No kidding, yes.
And it's Exegol.
Entire scenes.
Well, that's the new Star Wars planets.
The five sets from The Mandalorian were all CGI light.
In pitch black.
That's the reigns.
That's Star Wars, baby.
Disney ain't doing well.
We fucked up.
Uncle Billy, Uncle Billy lost.
Lost Disney's $8,000.
So they have to.
They spent too much money on Rise of Resistance.
That's where all the Star Wars money went.
Which we'll cover soon, we'll get there soon.
But here, yeah, I think you need to be like Rey on Exegol,
summoning all of the spirits of Bear's past.
Be with me.
Right.
Again, in black voiceover.
Just yeah, you'll hear all their voices.
Be with me.
Don't use the footage.
Don't use the in costume footage
that is shot and on a hard drive.
Supposedly.
Supposedly, that was good.
Wait, really?
Yes.
There are so many rumors.
There are so many rumors about Rise of Skywalker reshoots
right now.
Wow.
There are rumors.
I would love to know every,
I would love to do a pop-up video
and see every frame, what was a reshoot and what wasn't.
I will send you multiple reddits,
and some of them could be total bullshit,
but there's versions of the rumors
where Matt Smith is a full character that was cut out.
He was the villain of the movie.
A full on Doctor Who.
They, it is possible that Disney could have promoted
the new Star Wars bad guy as the Doctor Who y'all liked.
And I don't know any of the,
I don't know how true any of this is,
but if you go back in April,
there's like Matt Smith is in this movie reports.
So it's not like this is completely out of the field.
But there's versions, yeah, where there were,
spoiler alert, I guess,
Jedi's at the end, Jedi ghosts at the end.
Because I had said, we shouldn't talk about this.
This is for the Star Wars episode.
It's approaching our level of conspiracy theories.
I love conspiracy theories.
Anyway, let's get to this in the Rise episode.
Rise of Resistance.
Yeah, yeah.
I think we'll have a ton to talk about.
I don't know if we're gonna want to go over the fucking movie
during that episode.
I will guarantee in 2020,
we'll work on our communication skills.
We'll work on taking turns.
The next episode, Mike will tell us what we're doing.
And then I will surprise us with what we're doing.
Well, I like declarations.
I think I wanted to get it on.
Like, okay, so will you commit?
Will you commit to Country Bears 2020?
I have to commit now.
Yeah, you do.
Okay, okay, okay.
Let me think here.
Let me think.
I'll commit, but I am prepared for it to be
Irishman level.
That's fair.
Irishman.
Of course.
Let me just summon.
Let me see if I can summon.
Oh, surprise guitar, apparently.
Well, no, that was supposed to be like a,
sort of an otherworldly.
Oh, that's right.
Yes, I will commit.
Yeah.
I've been tapped on the shoulder by Big Al.
Oh, he appeared.
Yeah, that was him.
He was with you.
I should have actually just played one string
on the guitar there.
Ding, bong, bong.
That's good.
Yeah, oh, there he was.
I felt his spirit.
Wow.
Yeah, exactly.
However you want to play it, as many hours as it takes.
It's going to grow.
Like, I caught some of Bugsy on TV.
Not our Bugsy.
No kidding me.
Some of the Warren Beatty Bugsy on TV.
A movie that is just about a casino budget
slowly going from $1 million to like $6 million.
And Ben Kingsley and Joe Montegna
is just getting more and more mad.
And then any goodwill I had for the movie
immediately thrown out the window at the very end credits
where it says, written by James Toback.
And I was like, oh, man.
I forgot.
Man, what the heck.
The guy who, pure stats-wise, is maybe the top dog
of Me Too.
James Toback.
Although we don't know.
We don't, I don't know.
Stats-wise, I don't know.
There's people maybe putting up even bigger stats.
Toback's also, his shit was like,
his shit was like, just like, walk up to you
and like rub himself on you in a crowded place.
Jeez.
My God.
Just really, I don't even know what to.
Creepy as old grandpa Palpatine.
But we'll get to that on the.
We'll get to that on the Warren Beatty episode.
On the Toback episode.
It's Toback slash Thought Sunrise of Skywalker.
But that's incredible commitment.
I love it.
It's a New Year's resolutions.
That's how I feel.
Anything else we're excited for in 2020?
Oh, yeah.
At 2020, I mean, rides-wise,
we got Marvel Land opening in the summer
that has been confirmed in the last couple weeks.
There was some speculation of like,
maybe that'll be pushed, but no, apparently not.
Because it's another in the series of,
the land is opening.
Not the big ride, but something as a restaurant.
And that hasn't even started construction.
The big ride.
That's God knows where we're gonna get that.
But you know, I can only think of Rise of the Resistance
because it opens here in.
Yeah, which all we can say is we'll try to,
we're gonna do it as soon as we can.
But my fear is we're all gonna go
and then it won't be open.
And then I don't know, I hope we get to it in January.
We're gonna try, right?
Yeah.
That's all we can say.
Oh yeah. Yeah.
I think it's like what we're covering today
could be a lot of problems.
Not guaranteed, Hagrid's I'm saying.
The big rides of late have been fraught with peril.
Complicated.
I mean, higher and higher expectations,
but they're also reaching higher and higher.
And when you just keep adding on different drops
or launches or all of that,
it's just more technical issues.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And well, you know, and speaking of reaching higher
and higher and you know, climbing to ambition growing,
I wanted to say towards the top here,
everybody check out the podcast, the right YouTube,
which we've been putting up things
a little bit here and there.
Mike, I was gonna ask you, we gotta put up the,
it was on Twitter, but the video you sprung on me
at the live show, the baby Grinch reason
for the season video, I'll put that up.
But I wanted to get people to the YouTube
because I have done a new cut of the,
maybe a highlight of 2019,
at least for me personally, the Michael Eisner hello video,
which was acknowledged by Michael Eisner himself.
I collect in that original video, 67 hellos
from various sources due to a new channel I found,
Walt Disney Introductions, credit to them.
And one from the Imagineering story,
there is a hello, I noticed, I've only seen in the image,
because now I know all of them, I know where he's standing,
I know how many characters he's with, is he by a lake,
is he by a different lake, which version of poo is he with?
What I'm getting at is I've done a new cut, Hello 2020,
and it has gone from 67 hellos to 104 hellos.
Oh my God.
So that is only on the podcast, the right YouTube.
That's incredible growth, that's over a third more,
I forget the percentage there.
Is it too long to put on Twitter as well now?
No, I think it's still, because it is paired to just hellos.
I think it's still, yeah,
I think I could still throw that out,
or I could just do the new section.
Well, the Twitter one, because I, yeah,
when we were saying 2020, one of the things,
we haven't talked, we haven't done really a powwow meeting
yet about guests and stuff, but Michael Eisner is,
maybe guest, like, wanted guest number one.
Yeah, yeah, that was so, well, we were texting about
the country bears thing, because there was a thread
on the Facebook we noticed that was like,
what do you want for 2020?
The top two things were Eisner and country bears.
So we, yeah, we should talk strategy
about how do we do this.
Is it a petition?
Is it another round of Twitter,
like tweeting at him with a video,
because he famously has retweeted us once
with the original hello video.
But I think that, first of all, there's no DM option.
I think Twitter, I'm not sure that a Twitter campaign
will be heard.
Eisner's DMs are not open.
They are not open.
You cannot slide into Michael Eisner's DMs.
Goodbye.
So I don't know, I mean, like, I think tweeting,
I love that when he tweets, like, he tweeted his
Rise of Skywalker opinions, which was fun to see.
Nick Mundy had our back and immediately responded,
go on podcasts, a ride, got a lot of likes.
If he's noticing what's getting likes,
I also, I was checking the stats when he retweeted
our video, which if you haven't seen it,
it's a super cut of every time he says hello,
introducing Disney movies.
I was checking his stats like a crazy person.
That was one of his 10 most popular tweets of all time.
Sure, wow.
Like, and that wasn't like a retweet or,
like of like original content Eisner tweets.
I mean, it demolished most tweets about the soccer team
he owns, no offense to the soccer team.
But our video is more popular than,
if we took up a British soccer stadium
and just played that montage in a loop,
we'd sell it out way easier than whatever
the soccer team is called.
Right, we are more popular than the soccer team.
Yes, absolutely, yeah, yeah.
So he's gotta do it.
And with that, but with things like putting down
the soccer team, I'm sure we're definitely
gonna get him here.
You're already gonna get like hit with a bottle
by Arsenal fans or whatever.
Oh no, they're gonna find me in America.
Or throw it so far from me.
Throw it so far.
They're so good at throwing bottles,
it's gonna hit me in the valley.
Is it a petition?
I don't know how many listeners we have, honestly.
I think a polite email is probably usually the life.
That would be my, I mean the real answer,
yes, is that.
I've sent a polite email.
I did it without.
But where?
Maybe you shouldn't say, but.
Yeah, not to a direct channel,
but somebody who should be in the circle.
No response.
Maybe it was the wrong email.
Maybe we should send it to multiple emails, though.
I think like office culture email,
you sometimes do need to send five,
of the kind of banal, like hey, following up,
checking in, the stuff like individually you might hate,
but like in a corporate culture,
that is kind of the dance.
I think that would work.
I honestly think.
That is the dance.
We just stay.
Yeah, I think so.
The dance of death.
Well, and maybe we have to try,
we have to get multiple of these emails.
We have to find, if anyone has some way to,
I'm on IMDB Pro, and that didn't get me any closer
to having info for him or his company,
because I think it's like some PR representative,
and we threw some stats their way.
That's what the angle I did.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, do we have new stats that would be?
Like stats that like, is he like, oh wow,
the downtown Disney ordeal did a certain amount of numbers?
Like it's hard to tell what.
I mean, the stat is 18 stages.
Oh really, 18 stages.
Well then I gotta see what these guys are about.
18 stages, oh my God.
They made this.
I have to talk to these men.
They have respect for La Brea Bakery.
Edwin, meet me at Catal.
No.
The Eisner table at Catal.
My table at Catal in the back.
We'll break all the rules.
We'll don't, if this episode,
if he only gives us 15 minutes, that's okay.
Oh yeah.
If we have to record it while he's like jogging
or something, we'll do, like, however we need to fit it
into his schedule.
If he just wants to talk about the football team.
Yeah, that's fine.
I mean, it's not my favorite, but.
Club, I think you say football club.
Football club, you're right, you're right.
FC, FC?
You're right, yes.
This cow will trick him by knowing all of his phrases.
Footy, Michael, do you wanna come on
and talk a little footy?
Your footy club?
Your footy club.
Do you think we ask, like we do another episode
with Tony Baxter first and we go,
Tony, could you drive us to Michael Eisner's house?
We knock on the door?
I think the answer is no.
Okay, fine.
That's presumptuous, but does he know,
and you're saying he knows where Eisner lives now?
I don't know.
I'm not sure.
I don't know anything about that.
I know where his, I've gone up to Lake Arrowhead
a couple times and I took the boat tour once
that just like goes around the lake
and they point out houses and like,
that used to be Michael Eisner's.
I know where Mike Love lives now.
Whoa.
Around Lake Arrowhead.
Wait, in what city, in Arrowhead?
Whoa.
There's also, there's a kind of an infamous house.
And good vibrations coming out of there.
I think the residents hate him.
Is it Hagar?
Some like 80s rocker bought two big houses
next to each other and connected them
to make like an architectural monstrosity
and the townsfolk hate him.
Geez.
Yeah.
Sammy wouldn't do that.
It seemed like a big like 90s, like place if you had money
because they were like, that used to,
either that is or used to be Eric LaSalle's house.
And that was the one with a 20 car garage Jay Leno bought.
I think a lot of these have flipped a couple of times.
Sure.
But like.
I don't wanna side check too much.
Have I talked on the show about seeing Dennis Rodman's house
in Newport Beach?
No.
Okay, so this is in the 90s.
I spent a lot of summers down there
and my dad and I were on a bike ride
and he's like, now I've heard Rodman moved in around here.
I wonder what is the,
I wonder if we'll be able to tell,
I think it's in this neck of the woods, we'll see.
So we're like on this bike ride going, I wonder is this?
And then suddenly we see a,
the biggest Hummer I have ever seen
more than blocking the bike path.
It has his face massive on the back.
The pattern on the hood of the car
is a bunch of airbrushed naked women.
Oh my God.
All drawn to have breast implants
and they are all touching themselves.
And the car, the license plate has an abbreviated version
of this and the car says it really big, wool patrol.
What?
Which I guess is some, it's like about pubic hair.
That's what I, I guess?
He loves, Rodman loves wool.
Good, just wool.
I mean like getting warm with some wool.
God, I've never even heard that before.
I think it was a coincidence.
He hired a decoy to throw people off the trail.
Yeah, he lives across the street.
He lives in the ocean.
He's like in some underground pod house.
Oh yeah, yeah.
You gotta take a submarine to get there.
No, but then driving back the other way,
we watched him coming out and plumes of smoke
and a smell that made me for the first time in my life
say, dad, what's that smell?
So that was the very, what a cool way
to discover the smell of wool.
Dad, what's the wool patrol?
How do I join?
It's much different than the paw patrol.
This car is a famous thing too.
If you Google Dennis Rodman Hummer,
you will discover, you gotta see this for yourself.
It's unbelievable.
I guess I gotta do it right now.
I will guarantee we will do
the Dennis Rodman Hummer episode.
I wish it was a car you could ride.
I wish it was, if that was an option
on Radiator Springs Racers.
Yeah, you got it.
Oh, it looks like shit.
It's really stupid.
It's stupid as hell.
I mean that obviously sounded stupid and bad,
but this looks like shit.
No, it's not a cool kind of,
it's very similar to when Tom Green painted sluts
on his parents' car and it said Slutmovie.
It's like that variety of just super trash.
But his, I'm not sure if his was funny on purpose.
I don't think it was.
It doesn't seem to be.
All right, so yeah, full Rodman Hummer episode coming.
Back to, real quick to Eisner.
Iger supposedly, Bob Iger supposedly leaving as CEO.
Is there any movement to get Michael Eisner
back in the CEO position at Disney?
Are there rules about this?
So there are term limits.
Can you go back like Jerry Brown
as governor of California?
I think you can.
And I think maybe with some like Lieutenant CEOs
with Mr. Eisner, three to be exact.
That's right.
With Eisner at the helm and three Lieutenant CEOs
of the Disney corporation. The Knights of Mike.
Yes.
Faceless, faceless, characterless man.
Faceless, developed, developless.
He's wearing the wear hoods all the time.
And he'll just, yeah.
Oh, hello, hello.
Hello, hello.
Gosh, we've really added to the IP of the show today.
Yeah, yeah.
So that, yeah, maybe that's it.
Maybe we push for Eisner.
Jobs went back.
Jobs went back to Apple.
Yes, Jobs went back to Apple.
Izer was, yeah, Izer can go back.
I don't think there's any sort of term limit.
He's gotta save it.
Just like, Choms.
He's gotta save his ailing company.
That's right.
I don't know if that's accurate.
I think it's doing great, but like,
it's ailing in my eye,
because there aren't fun specials anymore.
Yeah, he needs to host the specials again.
We need direct to DVD sequels of all these movies.
We need him back.
Oh, you're saying, so not like Lady and the Tramp.
We don't want live action Lady and the Tramp on Disney+.
We want cheaply animated Lady and the Tramp 4.
Yes.
That involves time travel.
If you really are being honest with yourself,
what would you rather have?
The boring same movie that's just live action,
or like some bizarre thing where
Lady and the Tramp go to space?
Of course.
Lady and the Tramp go to space.
It's better.
Hell yeah.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Well, Disney Plus allowed me to see for the first time
Aladdin 3, what's it called?
The King of Thieves?
King of Thieves with his father, right?
Yeah, yeah, with his hot dad.
Yeah, that wasn't overhyped.
Williams comes back, doesn't he?
But number two is Castellaneta.
Yes.
Right?
So crazy.
And you get in Aladdin and King of Thieves
something more memorable than any of these boring,
if you only do shot for shots,
you're not gonna get dynamic things like
the genie transforming into Mrs. Doubtfire.
Yes.
Incredible, historic moment.
Like that one thing is more interesting
than live action Beauty and the Beast,
Aladdin, like all of them put together.
Yeah.
Well, there's only one solution is bring back Eisner.
Reinstall Eisner as CEO.
Let's get crazy.
With three youngish lieutenants.
Youngish.
On the CEO scale, there's not a lot of CEOs our age.
Yeah.
They're all Palpatine.
Youngish fixers, youngish hooded, Eddie Mannix kind of fixers.
I think, yeah, I think we have the two year
track record of ideas to prove that we belong there
at this point.
Yeah, we're tossing them off left and right.
I can't remember the rest of the water.
I could only remember Haldeman.
I couldn't remember the rest of Nixon's lieutenants.
You were trying to name.
Haldeman, Kissinger. John Dean.
Yeah, Dean.
Who else was in there?
I don't recall.
Rumsfeld.
I don't know.
Rumsfeld, yeah.
Young, re- young genie.
Roger Stone.
Stone, yeah.
We do have the back tech, too.
We have the Eisner back tech.
Yeah, yeah.
Like Stone is the Nixon.
We gotta get him on just to show him our Eisner back tech.
Yeah.
And I'll show him the prototype of my action figure
I created forever.
Man, we got it.
Okay, well, if anyone listening has any ideas
or any like ins to get him, please let us know.
Yeah.
Anything else you wanted here on the show this year also?
Please, we're excited.
I think there's a lot of fun stuff coming.
We got a lot of stuff in Orlando now we can talk about
that I've been again that we all went recently.
It's sort of what we're doing today.
I don't know where it lives.
We did a McGruff episode.
We unlocked a Patreon episode.
There's a Patreon if you're just new to the podcast.
You can, there's three, every four episodes
for free every month.
There are three extra episodes you can pay $5 for.
We unlocked in one of those episodes last week
about McGruff's singing career.
Yeah.
And I think we can also promise for 2020,
probably on the Patreon, but I don't know, is McGruff 2.
Well, we're announcing it.
We're saying it's McGruff 2.
There's some exciting developments
that we don't want to tip too much.
It's really good.
And I think we can say even we haven't heard.
McGruff 2 will consist of things we have not yet heard.
Yeah.
Thanks to some help that we're getting.
And I don't want to say much more.
And I'm working on some other leads.
I'm hoping those are gonna pan out.
Wow.
It's exciting.
It's very exciting.
Let me ask Jason, let me ask you a quick question here
because this is totally a sidetrack
and we shouldn't do it because we're already behind.
It's come to my attention that there is a misconception
among human beings that McGruff's first name is Scruff.
Okay, I fucked that up.
No, no, I'm not.
Twice now.
I'm not even trying to accuse you
because Lindsay, I was talking to her last night
and she also thought that his first name was Scruff.
Scruff, of course, is his nephew.
But then there's a famous jingle,
Scruff McGruff Chicago, Illinois 60652.
Did you also think his first name was?
Yes, and I think we talk about this on the episode.
Do we?
I think I brought this up on the episode
and when we unlocked it, I just went back into my notes
and scheduled a similar tweet to the first one.
So both times you called it Scruff McGruff?
Yes, I forgot my own lived experience.
Wow.
I may have thought that at one point in time
until we sat and discussed it at length.
But McGruff has one name like Madonna.
I think the jingle is what got me
because you were supposed to address the male
to Scruff McGruff.
Why do you address it to Scruff?
Because Scruff is his name.
Lindsay is shouting from the kitchen, why would they say it?
It's because in the commercial,
Scruff is a little like Robin Muppet style little dog.
When did addressing it to Scruff McGruff begin
and why would you send it to the network?
When is it addressing it to Scruff begin?
I think that's later, that's in the 90s
when they created the IP of Scruff
and added like, they probably thought you needed a child
to sympathize, that was your way into the McGruff world.
You sort through the mail,
I don't have time to do this shit.
As a kid, I loved getting mail.
It was very exciting if there was mail for me.
So the answer is they gave it to Scruff,
they send it to Scruff because kids like getting mail more.
It's more of a novel thing.
I think so.
I'm not convinced that it was Scruff as secretary.
Well, it was to both of them, I think that was the idea.
It was to both of them.
Yeah, you were sending it to Scruff McGruff.
And it'll weed through the creepy ones.
People send in McGruff their underwear or whatever.
Scruff will throw that out.
Keep them coming, ladies.
Oh, no, that's the mail I want.
Sniff, sniff.
He's a pervert, apparently.
Yeah, in the commercial, he go, he's talking to his nephew
and he goes, this is my nephew Scruff.
So like he lays it out there, like he explains anyway.
So McGruff to he's going to get the paper cut.
So I don't got to
coming in 2020 McGruff to.
Well, to some part, I don't know which part of it.
We'll see how epic it is.
That's OK. If that's not a good enough
indicator of what's going on at
patreon.com slash podcast, the right.
Yeah, go subscribe to the second gate.
And we'll remind you that at the end, too.
Lots of fun stuff coming. Yeah.
You want to talk about this thing? Yeah.
Now let's get to the main.
There's a lot of fun business.
I'm glad we had some business.
But now we have this business of Hagrid's Magical Creatures
Motorbike Adventure, which we were fortunate enough to go on
several months ago while in Orlando.
This is a this is a big one.
This is a good one. This is a hell of a ride.
Yeah.
I don't know. I think of the stuff that opened in 2019, maybe
the thing I enjoyed the most.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, individual attractions.
I'll say well, because you're sort of like
Galaxy's Edge is this huge, this amazing experience.
But that's a full land.
Yeah, I think and not complete in my eyes yet,
because I haven't done Rise of the Resistance.
Yes. And that and if that truly is the like real showstopper,
then we haven't gotten to do it yet.
But yeah, the the showstoppers we were fortunate enough to do.
This is well, it's a good and we could, you know, we could say right away.
I wanted to get into this notion.
Mike, you brought this up.
It was it was it's a bold statement, but I think I might agree with you.
Best ride in Orlando.
Oh, did I remember bringing that's a good question.
Yeah, I having thought about it, it's like this is certainly in the top
five, maybe at the very least pretty quickly out the gate.
Most expensive, I think, in Orlando.
The real ever rough budget is three hundred million dollars.
Is that right? Yes.
Geez. I did not come across that number.
It's the longest roller coaster in Florida.
It has it has seven launches, which I sure will get into.
That is the most worldwide.
Wow. That's the most launches anywhere anywhere.
Well, only the second in America to have a drop to.
Yeah, which oh, well, here, spoiler.
If I want to say this is maybe an episode you should not listen to.
If you want to be surprised by this ride as we as I got to think as we all got to.
Did you guys know what happened on this thing?
I kind of knew what happened.
I read about it. I was foolish.
I know too much about Rise of the Resistance to what I'm trying to stay away.
But I did know a little too much.
So I'm trying to stay away from Rise of the Resistance.
I knew nothing.
And I think if I'd known some of the things that this ride does,
I might not have gotten on it.
I might have said that sounds too scary.
So I'm really glad I didn't do it.
But truly, if you're concerned about spoilers, maybe skip way ahead on this one,
because this is it is it's really something if you don't know what's coming.
And they do a good job of keeping you surprised.
Like I don't there's so many things on this where it happened.
And I was like, what? How crazy?
It seems like this and then Rise, from what I know about Rise of the Resistance,
are like really going to play with your expectations in a very cool way.
And that's what this one does.
I guess we can say it now because we've spoiled her.
But like there's a drop there.
The track drops on this roller coaster.
Yeah, which is crazy.
About two stories, I think.
I saw 18 feet. Yeah, it's not that.
Yeah, which is equal to the other ride in the world that does this.
Which another spoiler, if you want to be surprised,
if you don't want to hear what it is. OK, here.
Now go away. OK, now the ride is at Busch Gardens Williamsburg,
and it's called Verbolten, which is a snazzy jazz up of Verboten.
The word the German word for forbidden.
It's like a crazy like German forest.
It's like sort of a cousin of Hagrid.
Interesting. Yeah.
Beautiful Park, Busch Gardens Williamsburg, built in the woods and built on water.
Like it's really cool.
My family went there a few times, grown up. Oh, really?
I don't I didn't know anything about it.
I watched a little of the ride through of this thing.
And yeah, it seemed like when you're like like the big drop on this thing
where you're sort of like looking over the forest.
Yeah, seems wonderful.
I think the premise of that ride, or at least the initial teaser video,
was that like you were racing down the Autobahn and then got struck by lightning.
And I think that's pretty rock and roll.
I think that's pretty fun.
Hell yeah.
Well, and then you end up in like but then it's like
then it's kind of like magical creatures stuff.
So it's like a like is it that the lightning takes you to another
like you're just on the regular German, the awesome German freeway,
and then you go into like fairyland?
Oh, sure. Yeah, that probably adds up.
They have like a VR fairy theater thing, too.
So there's a lot of like interesting stuff in Busch Gardens.
They call some what are the big like body of water there?
They call the Rhine.
So it is like a little mini German area.
That seems cool. That does. Yeah.
Yeah, I mean, what else like stats?
Why there's the stats are crazy for sure.
That's the longest coaster in Florida. Yeah.
Almost a mile long.
Oh, top speeds of 50 miles an hour.
Really good. That's great.
Yeah, it almost doesn't.
It is fast.
It's I'm trying to think like my my feelings on it was it's not often
I feel like that you get on something ride wise that really go.
Oh, I don't I've never felt this before.
Like like because, you know, you go on roller coasters and sometimes
they're similar, like even like Radiator Springs Racer, which is like before.
Is that the big last big ride before Millennium Falcon opened here?
I think so. Yeah, it's great.
It's fantastic.
But it's not unlike a sensation I had felt on a ride before.
It's sort of the bones of test track. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Once you realize there's crossover there.
Yeah, this thing is so I imagine like rearranged it like, yeah,
I guess there was technically a drop on a coaster before.
There's like a couple of things that have been done, but they're rearranged
in this really surprising way. Yeah.
And down to like, you know, I got I got fooled by things so easily
like the Indiana Jones adventure before it, where you feel the sputter
and the motor. Yes. And you forget.
Well, that doesn't have right.
Yeah. Like any like errors in the old dusty car are manufactured.
And it's similar with the bike where it's like motor sputtering and shaking.
And they made all that up.
And doesn't happen in the minor. Yeah.
And roller coaster and feeling the great beast
breathe between your legs on the flight of passage is not actually the mighty Akron.
It's it's just an illusion. Yeah.
Yeah, it's Avatar. It's Avatar.
But yeah, no, I yes, it's there's just like little those those little touches, really.
The ride vehicle is a motorbike and a sidecar.
Yeah. Which is two different experiences.
Oh, yes. Right. Which is a very, very cool.
I is that unprecedented? Do we know where there's like different?
Because it's a different level.
It's a different level.
I have to say, I I messed up.
Well, boarding this is very interesting.
I thought I did the motorcycle first, and I thought that was such a
I've never ridden a motorcycle in real life.
And I was like, holy shit to be on a roller coaster track.
In that posture, going that fast was very exciting.
The sidecar is good, too.
But I wish I had done the sidecar first because it felt like a D heightening to me.
Yeah, yeah, I did the other way. And I agree.
I think I yeah, I mean, I think sidecar is cool in its own way.
Yeah, for sure. It might be.
Yeah, motorcycle might be superior.
Have you not been on any other coasters that are motorcycle ish,
like Tron, which is only in Shanghai? Yeah, I haven't done Tron.
We did a bunch of times the Pony Express at Knotts.
Oh, yeah. That's if you're riding a horse.
That is a similar, unique sensation with much more unique restraints.
But that is like you're sitting, you lean forward and even just like roller
coasters, your brain, you just get trained to like lean back.
And these you have to lean forward and just like white knuckle any handles or whatever.
Yeah, it's pretty exciting.
And you get pretty tricked.
It feels like you're driving the thing when we did.
I got front row, I think, too.
I was in the front row at Haggard's. Yeah.
And Haggard's, which is just like there's nothing in front of you, obviously.
So like you really your brain starts to go like, I can drive a motorcycle pretty well.
That's pretty cool. We should maybe address a little.
It's probably not. It's a tiny elephant in the room.
It's a baby in the room.
How did we get on this thing?
I will only I don't want to I don't want to say much,
except that I will recognize this is a very hard attraction to get on.
And I want to recognize and acknowledge that we got onto this
because of podcast privilege.
Yeah, we pulled some strings.
We pulled. So we got to pull some strings.
Thank you to people who.
Time we've ever done that. Yeah.
Yeah. And work. What a place to do it.
Oh, my God.
Thanks, people who helped magical creatures.
You thank you Haggard and friends.
Yeah, thanks, Haggard.
Haggard. We know Haggard.
Boys. Hello.
Boys. Boys.
So full disclosure, I did have to go back and watch a bunch of videos of the queue
to try to get some perspective on that.
So sorry, everyone.
We are in the line and we got to skip the line.
And then we got to it.
For completeness sake.
It was so nice. It was like, OK, so do it.
Motorcycle and then do it. Sidecar.
We got to do both in a row right away.
It was unbelievable.
And sorry to anyone who hasn't gotten on this thing.
But hey, I don't know.
You get something for women.
Entertaining people for a little bit is nice to reap a little reward.
And it was it was great.
Thanks for helping us.
Yes, that was wonderful.
Yeah, so that's I don't think it would just by happenstance.
So I got to go front row, I think it was just.
Oh, yeah. And sometimes it just works out.
I didn't demand that.
No, I wouldn't be that bold.
But that that brings up a good point.
The loading of this for a roller coaster is very unique.
It's a continuously loading, moving platform similar to
Haunted Mansion or Forbidden Journey.
It's kind of a stressful entrance.
I know, like, go, go, go, guys, go, go, go.
Like we I don't think we you're sort of dilly dallying.
What should I pick? And then like, no, get on.
Yeah, it is a little it's a little jammed in there.
There is even there in the queue.
There is a video
saying like, here is how to get on.
Don't stop walking.
Get on the motorcycle first and then get in the side.
But like they and kind of done.
I reminded me, I think, on purpose of like an old British
informational pam, like sort of like not quite the look around you aesthetic.
Yeah, that's the that's the show I'm thinking of. Right.
Yeah, yeah. It's very dry.
Yeah. But kind of done in that in a drawn
pamphlet information pamphlet style. That's cool.
I missed that one. I actually watched that.
Yeah. Are you that's that different?
Because in the queue, there is also like Hagrid explaining sort of
that is different. Yeah.
So there is like that digital
like projection projection, like like how Harry and the kids are in Gringotts.
They have the same like and in Hogwarts, you know how like you see them
kind of come out, but they're just like a projection.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's sort of like that.
It's Hagrid and Mr. Weasley, Ron's father.
Did you watch that video, by the way, which the the the them talking,
the pre show a little bit. Yeah.
It's I thought it was very funny because I feel like the actor
playing Ron's father is giving 110 percent.
And I feel like Hagrid is a little sleepy.
All right. I'll contract says I got to do this.
A little green screen at like when he's swinging the umbrella around.
I'm like, oh, come on, man, give us a little work.
I know when you're that tall, you you it's you know, move that fast.
But I'm like, wait, he's so lively in the movies.
How tall is he?
Right. We're talking about Robbie.
Yeah. Robbie Coltrane is the people from the film in both cases.
Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah. It is.
Coltrane and I have Robbie Coltrane and Mark Williams.
In fairness, they may not have been there the same day.
Yeah, who knows? He's only 6'1".
Is he? Yeah, I'm taller than him.
I'm two inches taller than Robbie Coltrane.
I'm taller than Hagrid.
And I move around. OK.
Why you had to let us on the ride?
He thought you'd beat him up.
Hmm. I'm not. How am I sleepy?
Do I? Because I'm so tall.
Just I mean, today.
I'm very sleepy today.
I always say I don't think you've had a good night's sleep since I met you.
Yeah, but that's not that's not my height, though.
That's true. Yeah.
Yeah, that's anxiety.
No, it's fine. I'm just teasing a little because like it's
it's hard to do green screen acting and squat a pixies that aren't there.
And sure. Well, an all in one take.
The nature of this kind of scene.
Yeah, they have to have a little projected scene.
You got to do it all in one.
Just like Aerosmith and Ileana Douglas.
Mm hmm. I think they really I think the animation of the bikes
in that little sequence is wonderful.
It's like really like blunt, silly,
you know, physical gag.
What is the wait? I have a little bullets of what that is.
So this is explaining the premise of the ride.
So Hagrid is going to take you to a special care of magical creatures class.
You're going to board a bike and
he's going to take you to see some creatures.
Arthur Weasley is like doing some work on the bike
and he's going to magically duplicate it, which happens.
But then Fang Hagrid's Borahound releases
Cornish pixies accidentally who fly around and blow up the other.
It's pretty crazy.
Full on explodes. Yeah. Yeah.
It gets pretty extreme.
But seeing those seeing the bikes like clang up and down and fly and move
in this really it's like very silly and fun.
Could communicate to people who don't know Harry Potter or the English language.
It's it's great.
And and they fit in a little universal spray gag.
They got a splashy in the face.
Yeah, they have to do it, which is what that's Hagrid like.
Like there's something like he has to spray us.
Mr. Weasley is putting out the fires with water sprays from his wand.
OK, yeah.
And then what is the like the the is it?
Is it my correct that they didn't completely change the cue of
what was there before, which is a one point dueling dragons
and then called Dragon Challenge?
Yeah. This was an original
ends of adventure ride.
You know better than me, probably. Yeah, yeah.
So they this is the second time they have retrofitted this cue.
They changed dueling dragons into dragon
challenge to make it fit in with Wizarding World stuff a little more.
Kind of taking it from lost continent, from the next land next door
and sort of absorbing it into the Harry Potter land.
And when they did that, they they retrofitted the cue a little
and kept that that small stone, the loading building.
OK, and then they did it again for this.
And there's a video online actually Universal Orlando put it
on their official channel.
They did a full cue walkthrough.
Mm hmm. In like very clear, like 4K.
I guess the idea being we'd prefer you not bring cameras onto this ride.
It did not stop people from strapping GoPros to themselves
and recording ride throughs.
But I think to build excitement and it's a long cue.
Like it is very long.
It goes through all this wooded areas and then through the building
and then finally to the loading area.
And then once you get inside, there's lots of little
there's like broken up dragons, eggs and little cocoons and like other stuff.
Because Hagrid is, you know, he takes care of the animals
and it's the groundskeeper at Harry Potter.
And please don't yell at me if I don't have that language correct.
But yeah, not 100 percent.
I'm trying. Totally trying my best.
Yeah. So it's been retrofitted a couple of times.
It was interesting because I watched one video that showed like the
what what Dueling Dragons, Dragon Challenge
look like compared to what Hagrid's look like.
And in 1999, lower expectations for landscaping.
It's like it's just metal. It's just beams.
It's just a coaster. It's just coaster and empty lots.
There's no attempt to dress up the area around it compared to Hagrid's,
which is like hidden.
And they actively tried to hide the ride.
And they planted a thousand trees in this area to make to simulate the forest.
It is such an insane campus.
Yeah.
So much and such a like actual they made it such actual nature
that among the many problems this ride has had,
there was at one point a couple of months ago, a bee infestation.
Yes.
And I maybe heard that a little and I was like, what?
So there was a hive and they had to get rid of the hive.
It wasn't much crazier than that.
You guys are a little far away from this picture, but I found this photo.
All of the black specks of this photo are bees.
It was like a really nuts bee infestation.
And I think the type of bee, whatever it is specifically,
is a protected species in Florida.
So to get rid of them was a whole process.
Yeah. Yeah. I missed all of this stuff.
This wasn't just some sort of like opening day idea,
like the ice machine that would an Indiana Jones that would drop like,
rock debris on your car.
This wasn't an idea like maybe we'll try live bees.
And then if it doesn't work, we'll have lost control of me bees.
Well, control me bees.
He doesn't sound like that.
He doesn't sound like it doesn't sound like Shrek.
Oh, arg.
We don't really have a Hagrid.
No, I don't at all.
No, they weren't drones.
They weren't put there by the part.
They weren't little little be tiny be drones.
Good idea, though, they just raise bees and unleash the man.
Like they should genetically engineer bees without the stinger.
Oh, so then you get the noise and then you can unleash bees
on different motorcycles during the ride.
Sure. With supplies, even vented flies.
Yellow yellow flies.
If you paint them. Yeah.
Yeah. That's like little dye drops on each fly.
Mm hmm. That's the next level that I've heard actually rise to the resistance.
There are genetically engineered bees to keep the weight, to scare people away.
Keep the weight times down.
Mm hmm. Also, though, Emperor Palpatine unleashes
a bunch of bees on you in one of the scenes.
I just didn't pick up on that.
Just like I was texting you the other day, like that first scene
was supposed to be Mustafa.
That's true. Yes.
Rise of Skywalker, the first scene when Kylo Ren is like wrecking guys.
He's just killing guys.
That's supposed to be the planet that Vader's castle is on the planet.
But it's supposed to be cooling.
So that's why it's not.
Oh, that's not clear at all.
Pick up on that at all.
Anyway, anyway.
Bees. So there are no bees now.
They got rid of them on this attraction, but there are many wonderful creatures.
You want to talk some creatures? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, the big I didn't realize all the mythology of this
and some early Harry Potter person, but the big deal
in this attraction is that you get to see the blast ended Scrooge.
And that is a creature that was never seen in the films.
So it's the first time it's ever physicalized.
Yeah, I saw it's in Goblet of Fire, apparently. Yeah.
So yeah, this was this.
This is the physical debut of this creature is on this ride.
Kind of terrifying. Yeah.
Like a scorpion with no head that also shoots fire.
It's a weird like it's just it is like just like a shitting machine.
It looks like a weird like only a butthole. Yeah.
It's like if you got if you got cursed by a genie or something in a bad way,
it's like I become a blast ended Scrooge, a blast ended.
And I made it a genie, not a magician.
I had to bring genies into this. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, it's a magic, right?
Well, we were talking about genies earlier.
The genie also magicians.
Harry Potter is not a magician.
I know. Oh, technically wizard.
Harry Potter is a magician.
It would be. Oh, man.
The whole thing a lot.
It does make Hogwarts into like the Magic Castle,
which makes it a lot less interesting.
I like the Magic Castle a lot. Don't get me wrong.
I'm just saying that like this is a place where kids go to learn magic tricks.
I wouldn't send any kids to the Magic Castle.
No, I'd be careful about that. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But if Harry Potter could cross over with the Now You See Me universe.
I mean, well, he kind of did.
Daniel Radcliffe showing up. Oh, that's true.
Playing Arthur Tressler's son.
Yeah. Spoiler alert.
Spoiler alert for everyone's favorite franchise.
Well, I forgot about Daniel Radcliffe being in it till very recently.
That was that I watched the film and it just like left my brain as soon as it entered.
Yes. That speeds as fast as this coaster.
The creature kind of reminded me of the tremor, like of a tremor.
Oh, yeah. Tremors with like a molten lava asshole.
Like that's the only way I can.
Sorry. Yeah. How do they eat? Seat hole. Seat hole.
Great. I fixed it.
Fixed my vulgarity again.
I always can fix it.
But they yeah, they they glow with many different colors and are just steaming.
And this is a this is a bad creature to be.
This is like the weird, the horrible,
you know, like the limbless creatures created by KFC.
Who live in cramped cages.
That's the blast headed screwed is like an abomination.
Also, Hagrid made him like create genetically like.
So he's like a doctor.
Roe style. I actually don't know a ton about apologies about the Harry Potter.
He's always getting into miss.
Is that do you know that?
Yeah, I am saying that canonically, like he had a dragon.
He wasn't supposed to have a dragon.
So he created his dragon.
I think he's a I think he was breeding stuff.
Is this a fuck up on the way to drag?
Did he mess up and then go, oh, it's the blast
ended screwed?
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, that's the ticket.
I think I think there is John Lovett's is a liar character.
He loves it.
He's always doing something like he's not not supposed to.
I guess he is always like doing crazy stuff, like crazy stuff
out in the forbidden forest and his little house.
I didn't know he was playing God out there.
Well, I guess he is.
I I make a little mini version of himself who he plays the piano.
Someone draw that, please.
Hagrid and mini Hagrid, if you don't know, we're talking about
island of Dr.
Moreau, the Val Kilmer version, Marlon Brando in it.
And it's the basis for mini me for Austin Powers, too.
Oh, yeah. I didn't know I knew that part, but I didn't know until the
really great documentary about the making of Dr.
Moreau that it that the piano part was.
I thought that was full on Austin Powers and.
Oh, oh, oh, no.
Tiny piano. I know that.
It's Marlon Brando playing the piano.
And then there's a tinier version of him on top of the piano playing a little piano.
Yes. Yeah. And that is real.
Also, I've read that everyone in the movie is cursed that made that movie.
There's like a there's like a feeling that, yeah, like, yeah,
the whole cast got cursed by that movie, that there was just bad.
That's why Val Kilmer looks like Val Kilmer does now.
Well, yeah. And he had an issue with his health.
Oh, no. Your health issue. Yeah.
I didn't know that. And I'm making fun of him.
Shit. Well, you know, I meant Mark Twain.
That's right. Yeah, that's what you meant.
He looks permanently looks like Mark Twain.
But yeah, there's there's that movie is very interesting.
There should be some sort of experience based on that.
And Dr. Moreau. Oh, man. Yeah, that's who also, you know,
that's one of epic universes by surprise.
It's not Fantastic Beasts. It's Dr. Moreau.
It's Dr. Moreau. I think I read that book in school
and then I saw there was a movie.
So I watched the movie and I was like, this is very different.
Yeah. I honestly, you know, everything is IP right now.
So as I'm saying this, I was like, so much to make a new island of Dr. Moreau.
And do it like Superman Returns, where you take old Marlon Brando footage.
If it's a Marlon Brando property, we got to find all the footage we can.
Oh, my God. That's such a great idea.
Every movie he's ever made from like on the waterfront on,
you should look for his like B roll foot or like cut scenes
and piece it together in the new version of the island of Dr. Moreau.
So we like it. You can then you can tell an epic story.
Yeah. He was young and in black and white to when he's older.
All eras. Yes. Yeah.
You could repurpose what was shot for scary movie two.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, it is. And it became James Woods.
Andy Richter is in the scene.
Andy Richter, I believe, acted with Marlon Brando in a scene never released.
Right. This footage does exist.
So, yeah, you could take and him as an exorcist could be repurposed
to be him as a doctor. Yeah. Yeah.
I think that's also you could repurpose the footage of his interview with Larry King.
Was me an angel.
He like sings. They sing like 40s ditties together.
Yeah. And then they kiss.
Yes. Like a sweet kiss between Larry and Marlon.
Yes. Marlon is kind of antagonizing Larry the whole time during the interview,
which is kind of funny.
Then they sing some old standards together and then they kiss on the mouth.
This is the sort of abomination in front of God that only Hagrid
can cook up in the woods.
So twisted horror.
My strangest creature yet, Larry King.
Late in life, Marlon Brando in the tan suit from that one music video
and also the score.
You mean the Michael Jackson one? The You Rock My World video?
Yeah, right. There's got to be footage.
There's got to be extra footage from that, too.
Yeah. And do you guys you know about when he was at that
Michael Jackson concert right before 9-11 and he was just rolled on
on a couch in sunglasses and he rambled about like, kids are getting killed
with machetes and like at that Michael Jackson concert, you just got to see like.
All right. All right. So coming up, the Jackson five reuniting for the first time
in 20 years. But first, Marlon Brando saying whatever he wants on a couch.
I saw that. They didn't even announce it.
It was just they just rolled it out and he started talking.
I've seen that special, but I do not know.
Special. Oh, it's just like grainy.
Like somebody just had a camera.
Filmed it.
Well, Madison Square Garden.
This this does this sounds like a half remembered like
Dana Carvey shows or exit 57.
Like one of those sketch shows that I'm like,
yeah, I kind of remember that.
Yeah, yeah.
If this man, an old man on a couch like that.
Yeah, it feels like a sketch.
Like, where do we put Marlon? I don't know.
After Spacey oddities, maybe Brando oddities.
Oh, yeah.
Well, and I'm vouching for I'd love Travolta.
Who? Oh, man.
We both made the same.
Jason, I both made the same noise.
Oh, that's that one's too difficult.
Oh, no, I just like, yeah, yeah.
Have you seen every little step?
Yeah, of course.
Of course, I've seen every little step, please.
I watch it once a month.
Please look up John Travolta, every little step.
Oh, yes.
You've seen the like newer videos he's made with Olivia Newton, John.
That you're like low fi, like low res.
Yeah.
Like in like no budget.
And they're just singing.
I forget what song it is.
I found a weird one where he's playing a giant game of hide and seek in a YouTubers.
No, it's in his house, but he invites a YouTuber over to play hide and seek with his whole family.
Oh, my God. He has a GoPro strapped to his head and you get to hear all his thoughts about like,
well, I think they'll see me if I stay on top of if I stay next to the cabinet.
So I'm going to move over into the crawl space.
The strange like it's like being inside his head.
It's like a being John Malkovich.
Oh, my gosh.
You are playing hide and seek inside of John Travolta.
Not quite the most dangerous game, but it's some sort of game.
All right. Travolta oddities as well.
Yeah. Oh, boy. New episodes left and right.
OK, back to back to where the creatures are for staying on this.
We can also just like talk through the order of events of the of the ride.
Yeah, I have opening opening day stuff, too.
Sure. But yeah, what other creature?
Well, you see, well, here that takes us through the.
Yeah, OK. I'll go through the I'll go through the order of things.
So you get you get on the thing.
It starts sputtering.
It takes off and it's very exciting right away.
And there's good little moves right away.
But it's just a preview of what's to come.
But it is very exciting from the second from that very first launch.
Then you end up in a little hut and you see the blasted end of the screw.
And he glows and then he kind of breathes some smoke and you take off.
Oh, and the Hagrid animatronic.
Very good animatronic.
Garner Holt animatronics, of course, is a girl.
It is. Yeah. Oh, it's.
Yeah. The only the only complaint I have about the animatronics
is that we're not close to them like we are in like the riot
in the first Forbidden Journey, right?
Is that the way when I'm?
You mean when you're very close to a dragon?
Yeah, like close to the dragon and close to the spiders and stuff.
Like I just wish I could see them closer.
I mean, this is I can't do it.
I'm just like, yeah, they're like, oh, this awesome.
And it's a thing that elevates the original Harry Potter ride.
Yeah, that's an aspect only that has that keeps it essential.
That's all I'm saying. But it's really not a complaint.
It's just like I think it looks like they look awesome.
Yeah, I'm saying they're very cool.
So then the Hagrid animatronic, then you take off.
There's this this huge straightaway
that then goes up into a lift till and then through an arch.
And this and that section right after Hagrid, I feel like is the like
most exciting coaster part that it's a long, long stretch before more
like plot and characters happen. That's super exciting.
And there's big banks.
You go all the way like tilt all the way in a 90 degrees to the left and right.
It's like a sizably wide vehicle.
So when you go, I actually think the bank turns in the sidecar are pretty damn.
That's cool. Yeah. Yeah.
And an interesting thing to me, there's not a lot of like
catwalks or infrastructure.
Like, I guess you're not high.
You're not super high off the ground in the way that
Dueling Dragons was where they would need that infrastructure for evacuations.
So for the but it does help the immersion and helps the theming
that there's not a lot of like breaking the reality of zooming through the woods.
That's true. Yeah. Yeah.
And you're going so fast.
It is just this blur of trees. Yes.
Yeah, it's a very it feels like a forest.
And we were told we couldn't.
They're not running the ride a lot at night right now,
but we were told that the night ride is the ultimate version of this ride.
I assume because like there's big stretches that don't have much.
Some like don't have many lights.
So when you're zooming through, you're not seeing much of the track, probably.
Well, I know the answer.
Friends of the show, Carly Weisel, wrote an article about this.
The lights at night are the headlights on the motorcycles.
That's the lights. Right. That's it.
Yeah. So you really you can't you don't know what the hell's happened.
The suddenly it's Space Mountain. Yeah.
The other thing she pointed out any time, like in a natural
like a point in a roller coaster where you would naturally plateau, you launch.
That's yes. That's what kind of sets this apart.
Oh, that's a good way to put it. Yeah, right. Right.
That's the sensation that one of the sensations
I'm talking about when I'm saying like, oh, this is like new.
This feels new because generally on a roller coaster, even the craziest ones
I've been and I am not a coaster head.
I'm working my way up to it.
But even like the craziest ones I've done, the first part
generally is where you get all your energy built up
and then you're going through and you coast off of that energy the whole time.
And some of there's like one midway point.
That's right. An exciting surprise. Right. Yeah.
But this has what is it?
Is it seven seven seven launches?
Yeah. So you're constantly feeling this refreshment of energy.
It feels like it's almost like a three act structure a little bit.
Yeah. Yeah. Like it's sort of and then like a grand finale.
Like they save the biggest launch till the end.
But and then they're they're less intense launches too.
Like if you had, yeah, you could take kids on this.
Like there's a small there is a height requirement, but it's not super intense.
It's kind of slinky dog dash similar.
Right. Did that have multiple?
Yeah. Oh, there's a there's like it kind of I think it's there's
there's only two launches. There might be two.
Because there's the middle one is like sort of that on slinky is like
where they kind of reset and you go through those circle things.
Yeah. Yeah. And then you shoot up again.
Yeah. That slinky would be a good
coaster for like your first coaster.
I mean, they always we always say Big Thunder is a good term.
Like kind of even test for whatever, you know, if you're like 10 or 11
or maybe 16 or 17 and you haven't gone on things or in some cases with me.
How old was I last year?
I don't remember. I was ready.
34. I was actually OK.
So, yeah, there are seven launches on this.
I was again, as I said, there was reading about this.
It's a ton of launches.
There's drops and there's like a spike, quote unquote.
I don't know if I want to do this thing.
I'm so glad I became a launch queen as we've been recording these episodes.
And I was trying to do some math.
OK, so all right.
The biggest launch in this with most
intense, intense one is zero to 50 in three seconds.
In credit, coaster felt like a crazy one to me.
But now I've now I'm a pro.
That's zero to 55 in four seconds.
Rock and roller, I would call the most intense one that I've done.
That's how it feels to me.
It's not that much, but it's very fast.
It's zero to 57 in two point eight seconds.
Very significantly faster than these other ones.
And I mean, just hearing hearing like loud body rock and roll music also
just makes us experience so much more intense.
That is I mean, you joke, but that is a good trick like pitch blackness,
loud music, Hulk.
You go through like you can't see where you're going
and then you immediately twist coming out of it.
What does that launch?
We do we have an episode about this coming up.
I don't remember the numbers.
Zero to 60 in two seconds or three.
It's every time I talk about it.
I can't pull it off the top of my head, but it's certainly more than what we're
talking about. Certainly more.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hmm. Yeah. Coming up.
Stay tuned. Hulk coming up.
Yeah. The Hulk is I think I said it's more intense, but I said it gets away with all.
It gets the psychological stuff out of the way quick, which is my always my thing.
Yeah. It doesn't.
The buildup is always worse than actually the right itself.
So like Hulk, that's you have no time to think about any of the scary things on.
No. And this one buildup isn't even in the picture.
It's all so joyous.
Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. You're never there's not one part of this that well, no.
Hang on. Well, I guess I think we maybe are heading to the scarier parts.
Yes. You see fluffy real quick, right?
A three headed dog.
The three headed dog.
Is he a bore? Is that also a boar hound?
Do we know or is it?
I have a list here.
Where is it?
Oh, I don't have it right here.
That's where I think supposed to evoke Seribus, the devil dog.
Oh, sure. Headed devil dog.
Cool. I'm trying. Very cool. I'm trying.
Yeah. Then and then OK, just past that,
then you go through this like log, the kind of log structure.
It's like a little mountain or something.
And there's a car on top of that.
What's the Harry Potter?
What is this in Harry Potter?
The car and the pixies are dangling off of it.
Is that the Weasley car?
Yeah, that's the Weasley's flying car.
OK, OK.
The car and the motorcycle are like oddities in the wizarding world
because they don't really drive cars.
Oh, gotcha. OK.
And that car is in the queue for Forbidden Journey.
All right.
Yeah, some of them.
I think it used to be in this queue.
Did they take it out and put it over?
Maybe they put it in Hollywood.
I think it is. I think in Florida, it was always in this queue.
I see. But it's somewhere in the land sputtering.
Just right stopped.
OK, so you go you go through this like
like under this little rock structure where that car is into submissed.
And when you come out the other side, they do such a good job of hiding this.
That is what they use.
The Wikipedia calls a spike where, OK, it's described as a spike
that catapults guests 65 feet into the air at a more than 70 degree angle,
followed by a backwards drop in one movement.
You just go like straight up.
And that is that was the biggest surprise of it to me.
Like, what's this?
It's like a mini version, a very, very mini version of like the Superman.
Like, yeah.
But this is a thing I wouldn't have.
I would have been like, I don't know if I want to go on this.
So when I was when that was just happening and I'm just staring straight up,
that scared the shit out of me.
Luckily, you aren't there for very long.
But it's so crazy how they hide it behind that mountain.
And then you're like, what? I'm just staring straight up now.
And I went through mist like my like my face is a little misty.
Yeah, I surprised me in how
not just how sharp the angle is, but how quick it is.
Because Expedition Everest, you know, you come to the bent track part
and you you stop there for a while and then you go backwards.
This was almost like a pendulum.
You stop for a second and then you go backwards really quick.
Yeah, yeah.
And it's a similar moment in a in a in a coaster where they have to make a switch
behind you, because now you've got to go backwards
into a whole other section of track and into a like not the place you came from.
So that's really fast to be up there for a little track switch to occur.
Yeah, I would.
I did not look at a video.
I would love to see it happen.
Like I would love to see it.
How quick the switches, because, yeah, every time I've seen a video
of some sort of track switch on a coaster, it feels like it takes a little while.
That everyone feel like you have to stay there.
Sometimes you get delayed up there, seemingly.
Yeah. I make the switch.
And then you get delayed on that when you finally end your backwards descent.
Sometimes you get delayed there, too, because the tracks got to switch.
Oh, gotcha.
But yeah, both times we went on this part of it.
We did get delayed a little bit in one of the sections.
Yeah, yeah. But this part, yeah, was so quick.
Really? No sign of process.
So cool. It's really, really cool.
Yeah. And then you go backwards into a show building.
And you don't know where now you don't know where you are in this forest.
They're like, where was the show building hidden?
And that is like a that's like a cave.
And there is a again, I don't know, Harry Potter things.
What is the centaur kind of creature pointed an arrow at you?
They they live in the woods. OK.
Noble creatures.
But I like the standoffish.
I enjoy the woods.
Now that that I think is interesting because I think that's just a statue
that there's a quick lighting cue to illuminate.
Oh, not an animal trying.
I am not 100 percent sure.
It looked stationary to me, but I thought it was a it's a trick, right?
It's to distract you because then the drop happens.
Not quite that.
No, you keep going.
You're pretty that that thing's pretty far out of sight.
Because you have to go back into.
What is the it's the devil's snare, the devil's snare,
these malevolent vines that that get a hold of you.
So you go you keep going backwards and backwards and backwards,
and then you stop entirely and you look behind you.
And where do we go?
What happens from here?
And the room is getting covered in these vines.
That's creepy as hell.
They did a great job with that effect.
So where do we go? What do we do?
Suddenly drop straight down.
It is such a shock.
Did you guys both know about that?
Yes. Yeah. OK.
I didn't quite know how it was happening, but I did read that.
So but like I think I even read up the thing going up.
I read about that, but I totally like forgot about it.
I didn't look at any pictures or videos, so I knew it right.
Intellectually, I knew what was coming,
but I didn't know the order and I didn't know the execution.
You know what that feels like?
I didn't know what it feels like.
And I was shocked as Mike said, I was like very surprised.
Yeah. Pretty much all of this.
It takes a lot to surprise me.
And it feels like the floor just gives out.
It just feels like, yeah, it just feels like, ah, like a like a floor collapses.
Essentially. Absolutely.
You feel really untethered.
Yes. It rattles you.
And that's where we got stuck the first time,
which I was OK with because I needed a second.
I needed a breather. Sure. Yeah.
That and then you're just that was that was very unsettling.
Just being in this dark room and having done that big surprise.
But boy, then to get to do it a second time and experience the full effect
where you drop and then just immediately you're going.
It's nuts. Also. OK. So there's two of those.
There's two rooms next to each other. OK, sure.
So I think if one drop is not working,
they can still run the ride with the second room. Wow. Wow.
Yeah. So I think I think we saw I think you could see out the
like you saw the other room shooting. Yeah. Cars out when we were stuck.
Oh, one went ahead of us.
So I don't know what they did.
You know, they didn't fill us in on what went wrong in our version
or when we went to the first time.
But obviously the other one was either working or whatever.
So so cool. Yeah, very cool.
You power back up a huge flame shoots out of the wall.
Hagrid's narrating you through all this stuff.
He gives you a spell.
I think that's why the drop happens. That's how you get out of there.
Yeah, you get really. Yes. Yes. Yes. I think that's a second screw.
Is that supposed to be a second screw that's fiery and that always.
I don't know what that flame is.
I think so. I think he's like, oh, there's the other one.
OK, I believe that's what happened.
It's kind of hard to tell in the in the ride through videos.
OK, OK. So noisy. That's cool.
And then you do the fastest lunch. Then there's a zero to 50.
They save on a way that most roller coasters could not do.
You know, and like, yeah, think about in credit coaster, it's sort of like
Peter's out a little. I like those little drops and then the swirls.
I think they do a good job of ending it in a fairly exciting way.
But like this might be as a rare coaster where, you know,
one of the coolest things happens at the end.
Yeah. I mean, very few, very few, if ever.
Do you get on the coasters?
Do you get that launch at the end?
Like most I think most coasters feel like they do the trick when now they've
dropped you to the like the lowest part of the coaster and spin you
to try to get the last bit of the like propulsion out energy.
Yeah. And to make you feel like you're a little disoriented.
Like honestly, that last loop on the Incredicoaster, that's
other than maybe the the the loop.
When you're going around, my head kind of goes like it's almost
I feel like they're trying to do a different trick on you as opposed
to just like launching you fast and straight, which is what this does.
And it's a much more pleasurable.
Trying to distract you from the sandlot in the center.
Well, that boy funnel.
That is also an issue.
That's really that's truly put to shame by the thousand trees of this ride.
Right on the other side of the coaster, there are like there is dune grass.
And it's like, honestly, if you just plant more dune grass in the center,
that's all it would like.
I don't know. Just a little trick. Yeah.
Well, I can't believe in all of the renovations.
They didn't put some Incredibles or the big Jack Jack.
That's what we said.
I mean, I'm sure I am sure somebody proposed that.
But this is a giant Jack Jack trying to grab at the coast.
Like it just makes too much sense.
And I'm sure they put it some or an under minor burst into the ground.
That's not really the story, but I like that under minor. That's great.
That's fine, too.
That comparing the Incredicoaster to this where like, yeah, that centaur is far away.
So, yeah, OK, I'm not 100 percent sure if it's a statue or an animatronic.
It doesn't seem to be moving a lot.
But like one of those with a solid lighting cue, that's great.
All of them at the Incredicoaster are just stationary statues.
That's kind of a bummer. Yeah.
Well, it's it's again, we I want to just defend the image.
Of course they wanted to make something like move.
Yeah, but the budget. I know you're not running them down.
I'm just saying we know we know the budget.
Well, and we know what you're doing, shape back.
Well, we're here clearly initially must have come from Lasseter.
So it's another we can conveniently blame it on him.
Blame Lasseter.
I insisted on statues and not animatronics.
Mm hmm. I wanted to blame Chaypec.
And then I wanted to say that will the Mike Lysander Shadow Council,
the three of us will be put in charge of the parks.
Change your ways, Bob.
Bob Chaypec will report to us.
Do it because it's delightful, not because of the bottom line.
He is Bob.
Bob Chaypec has to go to our version of Mexico to go to talk to us.
That's how it'll work from now on.
But in this one, we win.
Yes, but in this one, we win.
Yes. Yes, that's the important distinction.
He doesn't get all of the spirits of past presidents of parks in his head.
He. Yeah. Yeah.
And our lightning wins.
We shoot him with lightning.
We shoot Bob Chaypec.
But it's like lightning.
It's an electricity of ideas and creativity.
Yeah. And then he becomes like spirits.
Is this the future of parks that will or may I still change my ways?
In instance, in honesty, if we were in charge of the parks,
would we bankrupt the Walt Disney Company within six months?
I think the answer is yes.
I think we would have green light.
So much stuff, so much cool stuff like the parks would be so good
for a few months before they had to close because we spent so much money.
That is what is cool about Eisner.
I think that it's going to be the Disney decade.
And then in two years, he blew through all of it.
Yeah. Well, now that second half was rough, but boy, we were flying high.
When I manipulate them into spending a billion dollars
to bring back both Touchstone and Club Penguin,
I'm going to argue with you on that one.
I feel like I don't care about that.
I was not a Club Penguin kid, but I am fascinated by it
because it does seem like some kids spend a lot.
Do you know this was like the online game?
Yeah. Pre social media thing.
I would advocate they like sell Fox back to the Murdochs, sell ABC,
sell so many different things they have that are boring,
that are boring, just as fun.
The parks. Yeah.
I mean, like, get the billions, get billions of dollars,
sell Star Wars back to George Lucas.
They can still I want to still be in the park, sell it back to George.
And then let's just use all the money to make Westcott.
And then the rise of the true source of power, the return of Go.com.
The Go.com never left.
Yeah, that's true.
Powering the servers, still powering the Disney servers.
I think what we really want is to be in charge of the Oriental Land Company.
Oh, my gosh. Tokyo.
So we could say, hmm, I think triple spending.
And everyone will say, yes, very good.
And then it'll happen.
I think we probably are needed the least there, but it would be fun to
be an easier road. Yeah.
Well, they just bought in Florida.
They just bought that chunk of property that has like a body of water.
Do you see this? Like Disney bought a chunk of land that does have water on it.
And there were some people fantasy casting online going like,
build Disney Sea, build like in America.
Yeah.
That's weird because like they did like they made up
with a body of water in Disney Sea.
It's not like it'd be like, oh, it would be very cheap to make Disney.
Well, I have here's one of my ideas that I would have pitched
or make Bob Chepik do, Disney Swamp.
Sure. Orlando Disney Swamp.
Tokyo Disney Sea, Orlando Disney Swamp.
I think that's you can still do a similar.
It is pretty good.
It's the Swamp Thing live there.
Yes, he does. They own.
No, no, it's DC. No, yeah.
They'll buy Swamp Thing in some sort of a train.
Man thing.
Yeah, they own an identical character.
There's a Marvel comics character, a man thing.
Great man thing.
He's from the swamp, I think, too.
You could do a ride where you like recreate how we meet Kermit
in the Muppet movie.
You like see him singing. Right.
Rainbow Connection. Yeah.
And like go through Kermit Swamp home.
Entire Emmett Otter world.
Yeah. Now we're Disney Swamp.
Shared universe with Pizza Rizzo and the Regal Eagle barbecue.
This is too soon to call for Regal Eagle barbecue.
We should probably do an Orlando Disney Swamp shirt
that looks like they start seeing him in the parks.
Yeah.
I would wear the Disney Swamp shirt.
Sure. Maybe we need to do an episode where we flesh it all out.
That's a good idea, too. That's coming in 2020.
Yeah, great. Yeah.
We'll design all of it.
So you get through the fastest launch and then you land and you see
a beautiful unicorn and as Hagrid says, Oh, and look, she's a mum.
She's a mum.
Ain't she?
You know, a little baby unicorn.
That's wonderful. Very cute.
Yeah.
In the pre-show video, he's talking about all the creatures.
You'll see it at the very end.
He like this very, very funny, odd delivery where he goes, and if we're lucky
or if we're lucky to lure one in a unicorn.
I was just like, I don't know what it is about the delivery,
but he just like leans forward a little like he's telling you a secret.
And I don't know why I found that so delightful or just so interesting.
But I was like, it's kind of cute.
Like he's telling you a little secret.
He's telling that's 100 of his closest friends.
The secret.
That's like a different version of my thing with Optimus Prime,
where it's like he's addressing you and you feel like special.
There's a restaurant called Howlin' Rays in Los Angeles that we've been to.
And one of my favorite things is that if the owner is there,
oftentimes he'll do a thing where he goes like, I gave you extra pickles.
And then he puts like his finger to his mouth like he's don't tell anyone.
And you feel like you're like a free side.
Yeah, like here's some free fries.
And he goes, and then you're like, wow, he likes me.
This is cool.
I know. I like we have a secret now.
And it's what Hagrid is doing with the whole with every guest.
Yeah, like we know we're in on it now.
It makes you and look and like dig deep into the sidecar.
There's a couple of pickles for you.
Shh, keep it quiet.
Don't tell the motorcycle driver.
That's the way to make the sidecar a better experience is there's secret pickles.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
Secret pickle compartment.
That is that would be a true innovation.
I've heard actually, though, on Rise to the Resistance, there are secret pickles
in the vehicles. Oh, wow.
So I mean, food service in a ride is a whole other
arena hasn't been tapped.
So that would be I mean, if is that is that the secret at the end?
Do you get to eat a meal amidst the bad ads?
Oh, yeah, maybe. Maybe you.
Yeah, I think that I don't know the end.
But yes, you have a full three course meal served to you in the right vehicle.
And they're eating big burgers themselves.
Oh, wow. So it's so.
Yeah. So all the all the bad guys are all eating and you're eating too.
And then the resistance comes and they it's sort of like a Thanksgiving
where they bring their food at the end.
That's the end of the ride.
It's sort of a rebels and first order Thanksgiving.
How did we not?
I mean, it's a spoiler to say this isn't the end of the Skywalker story,
but it it does not end with a Thanksgiving style reconciliation
between both sides. That would have been a nice ending.
That would be the evil people turn good and they break bread.
They break self rising bread.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, why haven't they have the self rising bread in the land?
That's like when everyone likes the self rising bread in Force Awakens.
Well, portions. Yeah.
Possible to do not with the wizards and imagineering.
Anyway, we should probably talk about Harry Potter some more.
Yeah. I mean, that's the ride.
That's things that happen.
And they're yeah, it's amazing.
What can I say? It's just like it's it's full of surprises.
And you really got to do it.
I think it's the epitome of a our friend, Andrew Grissom, was saying, like,
I've watched the right through and I don't really like get it.
It does. I've watched the rise, the resistance right through.
And that seems very exciting.
This one I don't get. I'm like, because you got to go.
You got to feel those forces and zip through that forest yourself.
I've heard from other people that they were like, I watched it.
And it looks a little bit underwhelming.
But it's like it's just it's not.
It's not. I could I could see.
I think my sister watched it, too.
And she was like, well, it seems like there's not a lot of stuff in between.
But it's like this the zipping through
with these launches on this specific vehicle is so fun and thrilling.
Sure, it would be nice if it was loaded with robots,
but it's like you're so excited to be on that little. Yeah.
Like it's still a roller coaster.
The story coaster like this is also like the only like
there's only a handful of I mean, this is this is sort of ringgits
was kind of the precoast cursor to this.
And Guardians will be the next big one.
I think that's coming.
That'll be there. That's really the test is if that tops this.
I don't know.
I don't really know what's in it. So it's hard to say.
If you are going to go on this, I'll say this.
Do check the operating hours.
So this is a big thing.
Universal kind of hedging their bets with this.
I looked up in the app a few days ago, like on the first or second.
And in the app, the page for Hagrid's does still like have a disclaimer.
May open later and close early,
which is sort of what they were doing when we were down there in October.
It's not like they were expanding hour by hour.
But at the time we were there, they were only running at five hours
in an operating day. Yes.
And I think they were.
And part of that was it wasn't operating at full peak capacity.
They were like you can run multiple trains running at once.
At different parts of the ride.
But they were still trying to get up to that level.
And the blog Orlando Rising got data from touring plans
or friends of touring plans.
So on average, the month of November was the most successful month of the ride.
They had it broken down by percentage of operating day that Hagrid's was open.
November, the average was about 72 percent.
So if Islands of Adventure is open 8 a.m.
to 8 p.m., 72 percent of that day, Hagrid's was up and running.
But the first month or like the first few weeks of like end of January,
it was only open 46 percent of the operating day.
And if they're not running it at full capacity,
that's why you would see multi hour lines opening day.
The lines were estimated eight to 10 hour waits.
She's and I tried at some point you wouldn't be able to.
If you got in a 10 hour line at noon,
you're not going to get on.
Yeah. And this is it's an interesting.
It's a conundrum because like, well, if you try this is one way to open a ride.
And what you get is news stories about people waiting eight to 10 hour rides.
And guests go, that must be a really good ride.
But then Disney, when we were at Galaxy's Edge opening day, pretty smooth.
And then you get a lot of guests posting on Twitter and Instagram
and Facebook having a good time.
And people go, oh, that must be a pretty good thing.
So I don't I don't know that one is better than the other.
Well, you mean as far as a like a line is always a good marketing tool. Yeah.
That's what like that's what that place,
Hall and Ray's, who I was just talking about, always has a line.
Always has a huge like hour long hour, two hour long line.
So, yeah, as far as you're like marketing is concerned,
like when you go 10 hour line, I got to do it.
I got to go and do this thing.
So you think it outweighs that there's people who are certainly upset
they didn't get on this thing.
I'm not saying that.
I'm just saying that it's an interesting it's interesting
that Universal has opted to continue the sort of old tradition of that,
whereas it does look like with what Disney's doing in Florida,
at least for Rise of the Resistance, it's like it's all
first in the first thing in the morning, joining a boarding queue,
like when they opened the land and they were in.
So you got to get there immediately.
That's how it's working.
So they've done it a couple of different ways.
They've switched it up.
They've done in Orlando.
They've I think they started out just doing it where as soon as you got
into the park, you would be added into a queue.
And now I think they're doing it where it's completely sort of random.
It's like you get a reservation. Come back at this.
So, yeah. So basically, like there's no incentive now in Orlando
to get there very early.
OK, you get there, right.
You have to be there right when it opens.
But it's like it used to be there was like at least like they would form
some sort of a line starting, you know, what, at 2 a.m. or something.
And then you would sort of just join in the virtual queue
and then it would tell you to come back when it was open.
But it's interesting that they're universal is not doing that
because they could they have.
And in early promotion for this ride, they said it would use the virtual queue
system that they have set up for multiple rides.
They still have not put that into place.
Yeah. So it's interesting because I don't wonder.
I wonder if any of the galaxy's edge, like, quote unquote,
disappointment in the summer for Disney was that they never
they organized everything too well.
If it was like they had just made it like a crazy, you know, Mad Max style line,
like insane insanity, if he would be like, oh, my God, you wait for eight hours
and then you get in the light.
This has got to be the greatest thing.
And it would have made it like more exciting to people.
I don't know. I'm not exactly sure.
Is it equally? Yeah. Are people upset by a giant line?
Is there ever a 10 hour line?
That's is that one of the biggest in the history?
I mean, Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones, Star Tours.
I mean, well, I knew as much as Indiana Jones.
I think I may have waited in a three hour.
I waited four hours for Gringotts, I think, opening summer three and a half, four hours.
We waited really long for Guardians.
We we we got in a line that said 90 minutes and I think we waited
like three and a half hours.
Yeah. Do you remember how soon after Indy opened or was it?
I was there pretty soon. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
It gave me plenty of time to cry.
Because once I saw a video of what it was going to do, I was like,
I don't want to do it now.
And my dad was like, we're not going to go backwards.
And like, get the fuck out of here.
Did you like it, though, still? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I just saw that video, the video in the line where it's like
shaking mildly, I was like, no, I was like screaming.
My screams echoing across the temple.
You mean you mean 90s night vision isn't like particularly appeal.
Like that doesn't draw a child in the shaky like half lit.
That's what scared me. Yeah. Yeah.
I thought it looked like I was worried I was going to be in a cop's
esc experience.
You're going to be arrested.
I'm just thinking about it now.
Hagrid and Sala are very similar in their folksy friendly kind of like sidekick
style, and they talk to you while they're on the ride and they kind of
guide you through the journey.
True. Yeah. It's like sputtery vehicles.
And they they're you're kind of they talk to you while you're on it.
And it's a little wonkier than maybe they expect even.
But you get through.
They kind of have. Yeah, they kind of have an apologetic like at one point
in the ride, Hagrid does say it's hard to hear.
He says, I never was very good at magic,
which you never want to hear in a magic class.
You never want to hear.
Really hear that.
There's also, of course, a great overlap and crossover
that this is a ride at Universal Studios where you are in line
and they tell you and you're in a forest and they tell you you're going to get on
some magic flying bikes and have an incredible and see incredible creatures.
It really is a cousin to the adventure.
That's good. I never thought it's a soup.
It's a souped up adventure.
It really is. They could soup up.
If you know Harry Potter goes out of style, if J.K.
Rowling keeps tweeting weird stuff.
Yeah, she has not tweeted since her transphobic shit.
Don't tweet, please.
A few weeks ago.
Let us think that you're OK.
You know what I found out about her recently, because I haven't read those books.
I do remember this character from the movies is not into that much.
There is one Irish character in the book, like explicitly labeled.
And his name is Seamus Finnegan.
And he likes blow.
He likes explosions.
And the books are set in the time frame where the troubles in Northern
Ireland would still be going on.
And it's like, oh, come on, man. Really?
Oh, that's interesting.
I did not know anything about shame.
It's finnicky. They may as well called him Patty O'Malley.
And it's like you Irish, you like blowing stuff up.
Like that is wonderful.
Thank my heritage. Great. Well, well, I'm saying, yeah,
I'm saying if Harry Potter likes just goes away, you can maybe just
re theme this to T.
Oh, just move all the robots are this being just like a mega
mile long version of the T adventure. That's pretty good.
And that show building is like that's the dying planet.
And yeah.
I mean, when they make when when all the principle, when everyone in T dies,
who made it, E.T.
to or the remake of E.T. will happen.
And we got E.T. to this.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
We didn't even talk much about that.
People were tweeting that at me and us. Mm hmm.
There was a lot of commercial.
I woke up and there was so much stuff.
I was like, did they do something with botanica?
So you kidding me?
And then I checked in like, oh, it's just regular E.T.
Boo. It was a cast, right?
Comcast. Yeah, yeah.
I kept seeing the abbreviated one back east because both my parents have Comcast.
E.T. comes back home and then you watch and then the guy like
scrolls through an app and old show E.T.
old episodes of The Blacklist.
I don't understand why, like Spielberg is like no sequels to E.T.
But if but yes, a 10 minute cynical commercial for
fucking cable.
He's like, yeah, well, it's also seemingly OK with the Jurassic World franchise.
Well, he never cared about that as much, though.
He was there was always there were always he made Lost World and I mean,
he made a yeah, he made a hero and then three.
So I think he was never that precious about it.
But that's I'm just wondering what the deal was with that, where it's like,
oh, yeah, we'll make a 10 minute commercial, but I don't want to make a bad movie.
I mean, he doesn't have to direct it.
But but I'm saying I'd rather have a bad movie than that commercial.
Sure. But with the Green Planet Botanicus.
Yeah, that's the only way to do that.
The only way to do it. Yeah.
What I like about this ride, too, I was reading like they're saying that
this ride will only get like cooler and more immersive because, you know,
the trees will grow out, which I think is pretty cool.
Like in 10 years, like the forest will be like, you know, very whatever.
What is the word? Full grown?
Yeah. I mean, California adventure.
You look at the trees and the, you know, by Grizzly River.
All of those have grown quite a bit in 20 years. Yeah.
And you know, there's not a lot of Universal Studios that you would call beautiful.
That's not the word. A lot of it is exciting and thrilling and fun.
You wouldn't call it like, wow, that is like.
But all of the Harry Potter stuff has been so photographable. Yeah.
What is it looking so?
I think the greener, I mean, this and Pandora and the resistance
forest in Galaxy's Edge, like the greenery, greenery and water features.
Like I do have an extra like oomph for me,
just because I think naturally humans like green space and like water. Yeah.
And like some of the best parts of theme parks from the very beginning,
from the Jungle Cruise and for sure Disneyland in 1955.
What's the most successful stuff?
I think the Jungle Cruise and the Rivers of America.
And yes, there's always a place for that.
So it's a proud tradition.
Yeah. Sorry. Oh, no, no, no, no.
I was just going to say, I mean, just looking through,
I know we we did not go walk through the queue, but the queue like has
like much like, you know, Flight of Passage and Indiana Jones.
And it's got a lot of different like parts to it,
which are really cool and immersive.
I don't know. We don't we don't need to talk so much about
because I didn't walk through it, but I just want to highlight that as well.
Sure. Yeah. A little bit of like and there's like these cool,
like cozy little rock parts of it.
And there's a little room right before you get on and you look up the ceiling.
It looks like the motorcycles on top of the building.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That's very cool. Video projection.
I think, you know, they they truly Disney has
they had to do Galaxy's Edge and they had to do Pandora
because if we're in a little arms race here, I think the addition of this thing
now you add the the the the two campuses with the train in between
Hogwarts Forbidden Journey, the train, both of those train stations,
which I've seen in person, they're they're so cool, so immersive.
That train attraction is great.
Gringotts is amazing. Diagon Alley is amazing.
I mean, the the full Harry Potter campus, I think you have to say is
I'll say is better than Galaxy's Edge.
And that's a little unfair because it's further along in it.
Yeah. Yeah. And it is this multi park thing.
But like, like, I feel like this ride, I don't think they had to do this ride.
I think I know like the Harry Potter campus was
both of those lands were incredible already.
And you put this on top and it's like, I don't know.
I don't think I think they're winning the war right now.
Yeah, they definitely had to retire Dragon Challenge because that
I wrote that in 2017 a month before they took it down.
It was feeling pretty rough hurting people. Yes.
Yeah. And that was the one that was injuring your decapitations.
And yeah, yeah.
They I mean, we'll see a rise to the resistance, I think, is going to go
a long way in satisfying things that people don't necessarily feel about
Galaxy's Edge. But don't you feel like rise to the resistance?
You add that. OK, now Galaxy's Edge equals
original Harry Potter Hogwarts side. For sure.
Like, I don't I think the fact that there's this entire double section,
which I think maybe doesn't need that.
Maybe maybe the hotel will make it like, oh, now it's like an undeniably.
Yeah, I know so much there.
I mean, it's this a whole other podcast, but it's it's a it is a difference
between using an exact thing from the properties also,
which I think goes a long way to for Harry Potter to be so successful.
But like I'm saying, like, it's actually Hogwarts and you've seen it from the movies.
You've seen it from the books.
And now you're there as opposed to Galaxy's Edge, where there's elements
where it's like the Millennium Falcon is there and you know that.
And that's I think I would say arguably the probably what everyone likes.
The best in the land is just seeing the Millennium Falcon.
Yeah. The thing, you know, the thing, you know, you know, in it now,
I think you do have to give them credit because like, where would they put it?
Like, where is the where's the Falcon been parked?
That's grander than those spires.
Yeah, that cove that they built like, like, while you're right,
that it's the fact that it's the thing that we know,
and that's what we love to take pictures of it like it's not the same.
Like Tatooine is like sad, you know, yeah, like desolate.
And you don't want to be there. Right.
So, yeah, I I mean, we've had this discussion before.
I do think that it's a mix of like it's not what we haven't seen this before.
It's not beautiful.
Like like there's something obviously with with Hogsmeade and Diagon Alley
is a little more like perverse.
And I mean that in a good way.
But like Hogsmeade is so charming.
It's a little town and like just like the visuals of it are so appealing
versus just Galaxy's Edge when you're like in the first order area
with the ship, with the Kylo Ren ship from the Colin Trevorrow
script ship, which I'm talking about is that that ship
that Kylo Ren comes off of was from the Colin Trevorrow version
of Episode nine that didn't get made because early on in the process,
they said, well, do you have a ship that and he goes, oh, I have this Kylo Ren ship.
Does it look much different than the ship he is in in Force Awakens? No.
Looks like a TIE fighter shuttle cross, like what they've been combining
the same five designs for years. Right.
But if you like, if you go like over that area, you go, oh, OK.
All right. There's some like, you know, fascist banners
and there's a big ship and the ship is cool.
But like, yeah, you don't get you don't get a feeling like you get
going into Hogsmeade, which I do think you would get either way.
You would get that feeling whether you knew Harry Potter or not.
You'd go to like a quaint little town with a cool castle in the distance.
Sure, sure. So I'll give it up to especially let's let's take it to night.
Let's add fireworks into the mix when fireworks are going off around the spires.
Oh, yeah. There.
Yeah, I think it's unfair to say it's not beautiful.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There is that area.
So it nature to a couple parts of Galaxy's Edge.
But we don't want to say there isn't anything.
No, I'm not trying to.
I'm not trying to put down Galaxy's Edge as a failure or anything.
We'll talk. Let's we'll talk more about this on the rise episode.
Sure. To see how we try to do as soon as we can.
Now, Reiser's has to throw this argument because it's open in Florida
and we haven't got to do it.
Maybe that's the best right in Orlando now. Yeah, right.
But do we think it's this is it is it is it currently Hogwarts taking rise?
I think it's definitely the most technologically advanced.
And I think it's a good preview for the direction Universal is going in,
because like Secret Life of Pets say what you will about that second
movie not doing very well.
That ride has pets animatronics on it.
Sure. They're on. They're talking about that.
They're building a city street facade.
They're going there.
They have heard it seems like they have heard some of the criticism of like
too many screens. Yeah.
Yeah. Need some robots.
And I've seen it's like, yep, here's people posing with the robots.
Here's universal people.
Yeah, that's good. That's yeah. Yeah, you're right.
That's a start.
Physical stuff, because you can take pictures of it.
Yeah. Screens.
I don't know. I still really like Spider-Man.
I was thinking it could be.
Maybe it's Spider-Man still.
Spider-Man still up there.
That also technologically innovative, like new grant.
So like, yeah.
So this is my this is in my top five.
I really have to sit down and think about what the order is.
Sure. But it's it's really great and really both.
Like you got a lot of cool stuff to look at.
You get a cool vibe from it.
And the ride system is super, super fun.
Yeah. Anything in Walt Disney World better than Hagrid's motorbike?
I don't know. I really like I really like Everest as far as thrilling.
I really like Everest.
This does rank this higher because of more and it might be that higher.
But I do like, yeah, that's it.
That's such a tough question, because Everest itself is so impressive.
The Tower of Terror was the thing, I think, like kind of fell in that all over.
It could be that last time there.
I'll say this, too.
Hagrid's when I checked like Friday afternoon, down to 90 minutes.
So they're getting there.
That's good.
I ran in the corner.
But truly, if you want real insurance about getting on a startup podcast,
do it for a couple of years.
See how that audience grows and then maybe someone will help you.
And then Hagrid will reach his hand out and cast a spell.
Boys. A line cutting spell.
And I've got a secret for you as well.
Pickles. McGruff's name is Scruff.
The nephew is named after Maine McGruff.
You were right all along.
He's Scruff Jr.
That's his name. His nephew is Scruff Jr.
Well, does that do it?
Did we survive the first podcast the ride of 2020?
Big stuff coming up.
And thanks for listening.
If you want to follow all of it, then go to our Twitter, to our Facebook
or to our Instagram.
And as I said, go to YouTube, the expanded Hello Supercut.
More hellos than ever before.
And for those three bonus episodes every month, sign up for Podcast
the Ride, the second gate at Patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
I think by now we've put up a pretty fun episode about the Disney
World Millennium Celebration.
Yes. The bullshit they were doing around ninety nine, two thousand.
That's a fun episode.
We're going to talk a medjaneering story.
And of and of course, soon enough, a bunch of stuff about Marlon Brando, I guess.
Was the other thing we said long ago.
It was a real idea.
What are you to them, this episode or before? Yeah.
Yeah. Well, we talk about McGruff too, obviously.
Oh, McGruff too. Yeah, that's it. Yeah.
Yes. Yeah. McGruff too.
Probably on Patreon, unless it's just too big.
Yeah, we'll see.
To be contained.
I know we got to lure people.
I mean, yeah, that's true. I forgot about the other
developments in that there's been two or three different developments in that.
So multiple McGruff multiple McGruff.
What a way to start 2020 iteration.
So we'll see.
And none of none of what we're getting has been attained illegally.
None of it is bootlegs. Right.
Don't buy counterfeit cassettes or write a fair sale.
That's the legal. Right.
Yeah, I think the FBI warning is important.
Don't skip past the FBI warning on any videotape.
If you fast forward through it, you're as bad as the worst murderer in jail.
And make sure to stand and salute the FBI warning on all analogs.
And watch the national anthem as you watch and read all of the copy
and make sure to watch Jack Ryan on Amazon video.
Thank you, Jack Ryan. Thank you, J. Edgar Hoover.
Thank you, John Krasinski for your portrayal of Jack Ryan.
True patriot.
Uh, hey, thanks for listening, folks.
We'll talk to you next week. Happy New Year.
This has been a forever dog production executive produced by Mike Carlson,
Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Sileo and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit forever dog podcasts.com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest forever dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on Facebook.