Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast contains murderous hippos,
free ads for Pluto TV and seats,
both the kind you sit in and the kind you sit on.
Danny Jelanick joins us to sip tropical drinks
and talk about Trader Sam's Enchanted Tiki Bar
on today's podcast, The Ride.
["The Ride Theme Song"]
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, a podcast about theme parks
with hosts who would gladly buy a $300 leather-bound
coffee table book called Letters from Short Round.
I'm Scott Gerner, joined by Jason Sheridan.
The Short Round, I can't.
Yeah, it's something.
I mean, I would, I also would buy that book.
Oh yeah, come on, like the little,
I say that because that's a thing that exists in this bar.
Of course.
It's cutting a little deep, Mike Carlson is joining in.
I'm here, I would have to buy it.
If it's in the parks and it's a very obscure thing,
no matter what the inappropriate level is,
I'd have to own it, I think.
That's the way that my collector brain works.
But there's nothing, the letter itself
is just from a child's brain.
There's nothing inappropriate about that.
Sure. I understand that.
Yeah.
But everyone's uncomfortable with Short Round,
is that the?
A little bit.
Even though Temple would do my favorite of the Indiana Jones,
there's still some issues maybe in the 2019 context,
but we don't know.
I would imagine, I haven't seen it in a minute.
Yeah.
I would imagine roughly two hours of issues.
No, when they're in the mine cart, there's nothing weird.
The mine, there's like five minutes
where everything's fine.
Though I bet if you watch it, I don't know.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe you're right.
Oh, there's all that problematic stuff.
Oh yes, okay, I get what you're saying.
Okay, let's veer away from all this.
Kate Capshaw does a terrific job singing
Anything Goes in Mandarin, Cantonese.
Oh, I forget.
I don't know.
I forget, I don't wanna say something wrong.
And then I will be canceled.
For not knowing the language?
Yeah, now I'm on edge.
Anywhere, like Indiana Jones and traps.
You have to avoid with every step.
Let's veer away from this and let's bring our guest into it.
He's a friend and collaborator of so many
of your favorite podcast kind of people.
That's accurate, what did he say?
He's currently a director for Jimmy Kimmel Live
and previously of Comedy Bang Bang,
Children's Hospital and Lords of Synth,
live at the Necropolis, it's Danny Jolenek, hello.
Hey everyone.
Hey Danny.
Welcome Danny.
I was also talking to all of you out there in Podcastland.
Oh yeah, that was interest to us.
And they all said hi Danny at once.
I'm just gonna say one just for them right now.
Okay, only them.
Hey everyone, glad to hear it.
Okay, and that was for them.
You've said one clearly for us.
I'm assuming they said hi Danny, we're good.
That's why I said glad to hear it.
I don't know if they said those exact words,
but potentially, but you left the correct amount of space
for them to say those words.
Then I followed up with an incorrect response.
Yeah, because somebody could have said like,
oh I'm doing horribly.
Glad to hear it.
Not so glad to hear it, and then you're a villain.
Perfect, just as I wanted it.
Should I do one for the people who are doing well?
Yeah, do one for the people who aren't doing well.
Hey everyone, sorry to hear it.
All right, great, that works really well.
Except that you said hey everyone
and then that would have required them to say hi Danny,
I'm not doing so well.
Yeah, same.
They had to fill in a lot into that gap.
So you did one for the people that just sort of offer up
what their life is like right now.
You should actually do one, maybe two,
say hi everyone, how are you doing?
And then, you know what, let's do it later.
That'll be sort of supplemental.
I just wanna get out of the way.
Okay, yeah, don't forget.
Hey everyone, how's it going out there?
Glad and also sorry to hear it.
Hmm, so that's like if somebody has two pieces of news,
one good news, one bad news.
They can just pick.
I just got a new job but my car has been totaled.
So that's good for that.
Or I just got a new car but my job has been totaled.
This is like the Dana Carvey sketch
where he's Tom Brokaw or Dan Rather?
Tom Brokaw.
Tom Brokaw and he's trying to,
well he's on vacation,
he's gonna get all the different options.
Or the possibilities out of the way of a great sketch.
A very good sketch, yeah.
If there's a way to do like glad in one ear
and sorry in another so that you can shift binaurally
to whichever one was gonna apply to you.
Right, there's gotta be a way.
It's really complicated.
This one's just for the left ear listeners.
Sorry.
We know what you did, we saw it.
You thought you were alone but we saw it.
You think you're ahead of us left ears.
Circling back, double check, it is Mandarin.
It is Mandarin.
Oh okay, okay.
Great, good to know.
All right.
Everything has been correctly said
and we did a perfect beginning into this.
Danny, thanks for being here.
I'm a clunky to you all.
I'm a clunky.
Happy, happy, clunky, yes indeed.
Yeah, I'm sorry we're here.
I'm sorry we're here.
We're gonna recount a outing we had now a while back.
We got delayed in doing this but maybe this is
a good little memory test to recall every step
of a very fun outing.
Oh yeah, this would be a good exercise.
Yeah.
Or a memory test as you say.
How good is our memory,
especially when you mix drinks into it.
Yeah, mixed, mixing in mixed drinks.
Mm, yes. Sorry.
It's a precarious little cocktail here.
Yeah, we all went down, or not all of us went down.
Mikey didn't go down.
I didn't go, I forget why, too long ago, I can't remember.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, something lame and bad,
some audition that would have been bad if you got it
and was bad to try to do it.
Yeah, probably, I mean whatever it was,
it was a waste of time.
As are all things that aren't podcasts, the right.
Yeah, that's true.
I feel for us, not you Danny,
you do a lot of things that are not this.
This is the first time you've done this.
Oh yeah, this is the first time I've done this, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, so it'd be unfair to judge that waste of time.
It will show.
Yeah.
If it hasn't already.
No, not at all.
Yeah, well it's good to have you,
and you're a person who,
you're not a mega theme park obsessive as we are,
but it seems like you have a lot of appreciation
for the finer points of these places.
I feel like you're like a normie who does go to these places
and like them and find unique angles on them.
Yeah, I feel like including you guys,
I know other people who have highlighted
the finer aspects of a theme park,
and I used to appreciate the artistry of something
like Cars the Ride at Night,
just like on a pure visual,
like wow, this is beautiful looking
and took a lot of work and things like that.
Yeah, yeah, there's a real.
And I like the history of Disney,
like not like,
like of the artistry, the history of the artistry.
Sure, sure, yes, yes, yes.
I'm not just like.
Plenty of corporate intrigue as well, you know.
What's that?
I said plenty of corporate intrigue
in the history of the company as well.
Oh yeah, it's all very interesting, a lot of history.
I don't know, I just like, I like being there, it's fun,
but I don't go all that often.
Yeah, but you made it to DisneySea before.
Oh yeah, I did.
I mean, that was just like amazing
and a totally unique experience in my opinion.
Just, I'm sure you guys have talked about it
at length and everything, but.
Really have.
It's really so cool.
Even without having done like specific episodes,
just when Mike and I both came back from it,
it's just like, okay, blah, talk,
and then we both had two and a half hours of stuff to say.
There's so much there.
Yeah, well, peace, we're gonna,
we'll do three hours on each ride.
Yeah, eventually.
My favorite ride out there is the water one.
Oh yeah, oh, Aquatopia.
Aquatopia.
I love that you came back
and were really high on Aquatopia.
Yeah, you don't see anything like that anywhere else.
It's like you're gliding on water
and it's an incredible ride.
It's such a, and I didn't know what to expect,
cause I guess I kinda knew the aesthetic of it,
but I didn't know what it was once you got on it.
And then it's like, I don't know,
it's a weird little whirligig.
Yeah.
Spin around, it's just this little rock.
If there was no water there,
it would be pretty normal,
but just adding that layer is amazing.
It's so, and like beautiful to watch,
even if you're not on it,
just watching these odd little vehicles
just kind of push and sweep
the little thin layer of water around.
Yeah, and you don't know which route you're gonna get on.
You have no idea.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh wait, of the two sides,
but then once you're on it,
you don't know what it's gonna do.
There's that illusion that like the wall,
if you like look on beyond the ride,
there's like a little wall
and then beyond the wall, you see the ocean.
Oh, yeah.
The wall is just high enough to make you think,
it's like such a perfect illusion of like,
oh, just beyond the wall,
the wall's holding the ocean back basically.
It's like really cool.
And it's around there where there's like a fake leak
in the wall also,
like where there's water pouring through,
which really makes you feel that way.
Such a great detail.
If you get on the monorail,
that's back behind that wall.
So there's like a service road,
there's a ton behind that wall,
but it's that infinity pool effect.
It's so cool.
So best parts of Disney see that level.
Although it's all.
I was gonna say like it's all.
How can you choose?
Yeah, yeah.
Our friend Matt Mazzani just got back.
He just went and I saw him this morning
and I got that mojo from him.
How's it going, Matt?
Hey.
And what if Matt's-
Great to hear it.
Yes, great.
I think he might've picked up and responded.
He might've developed the pattern.
Sorry.
No, no, no.
No, you did perfectly.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, he did immediately like I'm going,
I'm gonna go back.
Yeah, he was, yes.
Yeah, like how quickly can I possibly?
Yeah.
Did you guys eat in the cafeteria there by chance?
Near Aquatopia?
I don't remember.
Actually, I shouldn't go into this.
I don't remember what I ate or where I ate.
I just remember-
Do you remember any keywords?
I just remember the dessert was good.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I had a Nemo colored churro.
That was awesome.
That was wonderful, cause that's sort of a Nemo zone.
I was just gonna say,
I didn't realize I didn't say this on the show,
but now that we've,
there's been a little more attention to Donald Duck's seat,
as we call it.
I ate a Donald Duck seat Sunday.
What?
With like his little like feet
and the ice cream was like his seat.
The dessert was, we're talking about his butt.
We keep- The seat?
Yeah, we have this thing,
this new thing that we are doing,
where we call it his seat.
Well, he used to have a really big seat back in the old days.
He still has a pretty large seat.
No, but in the 30s, his seat was huge.
Was it bigger in the 30s?
Yeah.
Was Donald's seat bigger than the 30s?
It was.
I just watched it.
I just watched a Donald Duck,
or it was actually a Mickey cartoon
that Donald's sort of like a Woody Woodpecker type in.
On Disney Plus, it's like this one where Mickey's conducting
an orchestra and it's an incredible piece of animation.
Obviously, it's like 30s Disney, whatever.
But Donald the Duck, as I like to call him.
He probably was that at some point.
I couldn't help but notice the size of his seat.
So even you, we didn't,
we hadn't even talked to you about this whole seat thing.
Us and our fans, we're all admiring this duck seat.
Why would you call it a seat?
Because we're, I forget why it came up,
but we're all very, we poke around swear words
in the most goody two shoes way.
And that seemed like the least offensive way
of saying rear quarters.
Hindquarters.
Piney.
I mean, I'm looking at,
this is an evolution of Donald picture,
but not as like completely on his seat,
not showing his seat.
Yeah, number two is jutting out more.
Yeah, yes it is.
And his beak is longer too.
He's got a longer beak.
This is the Donald Duck seat I was referring to.
Pretty big.
If you're Google imaging at home,
I'm looking at the, it's a yellow background
and it says Donald Duck,
and he sort of has this look like, I'm fine with myself.
It's funny that Donald, vintage Donald, I'm proud.
Text me that photo of Donald's seat
and I will put it on the Twitter.
I'd prefer they just Google it.
Put it in your file.
Labeled DS.
I'll print it out.
Code for Donald.
One for social media, one for iCloud.
Password protected, encrypted iCloud.
What'd you Google to find that, Danny?
Donald Duck's 30s seat.
No, no, just Donald Duck 30s.
I believed it for a second.
Somebody labeled it as such.
Wow.
This is one of those Google things
that we can affect possibly.
We had a thing a couple months ago, Danny,
that we were really delighted by.
Mike is a big fan of Avatar
and the Avatar experience in Florida,
and he, for many episodes, has talked about
when you do a journey, a ride on the mighty Akron,
and so many times you've said that specific phrase
when you feel the mighty Akron and he breathes between you.
And then once Google searched for mighty Akron
was actually done, it was just Mike.
Oh wow.
That phrase had never actually been used.
It might not be in the movie.
I may just have made it up.
Wow.
I mean, Akron is obviously what's in the movie, but mighty.
30s Donald and 30s Daffy both have very long bills,
I feel like.
They both evolve to fatter.
They evolved concurrently.
The way cartoon ducks evolve,
the beaks shrink and the seats shrink a little.
But Daffy does not have a thick seat, correct?
Oh, that's a good question.
Does Daffy have a thick seat?
Will you just give us a read on that?
Yeah, hold on.
We should look up Howard the Duck.
Yeah, Daffy's seat has never been big, I don't think.
In no point.
There's here's one where he's kind of sticking it out,
but in general, like that's just his posture.
Yeah.
Daffy got that Hank Hill ass.
Oh yeah.
That's straight down Hank Hill.
It's a little, it's not a bad seat by any means.
It's just that it's never been Donald's.
You're now wondering what podcast have I entered into?
I like it.
Talking about seats for this long.
Seat.
Yeah, there's Donald's seat.
We had some plan about, we had a tangent in an episode
about ranking the seats, like doing a tournament of seats.
And Erin listened to it, my wife Erin,
and she was like, that was very funny.
Please don't actually do the seat tour.
Okay.
The people demand.
What people?
Look, we've got five ranking.
We've got five tournaments to do this year.
But all right, they demand it,
but I'm gonna get a fucking divorce
if I do this two hour seat episode.
I mean, that seems like there's another issue at play
if that's all it takes.
I'm only one seat podcast away from a divorce
at any given time. Oh no.
But maybe she needs to hear it first.
So we'll record it for two hours
and then if she doesn't approve of that,
then we won't release it.
Just crying like Sally Erie hearing Mozart's like,
it's beautiful, I can't be mad, it's too beautiful.
Scott, I was wrong.
I was wrong. You needed to do this.
The world must hear this.
In fact, to do another two hours.
It's not long enough.
You didn't investigate the seats enough.
Boys talking about big theme park butts.
All boy butts though.
Did you hear when Scott said butts,
it actually made it real what it was
and it was too much for you.
That's why seat, Danny,
to illustrate what we're talking about here.
That's why seat is so important to this conversation.
I think we should just do the tournament of seats right.
Right? Now.
Do you have any others in your head?
The tournament of seats.
Do you go to another character with a seat
from theme park or not?
Oh man.
I mean theme park preferably.
I'm gonna not answer it.
That's a very put on the spot.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Brer Bear, of course, Splash Mountain.
Brer Bear, yeah.
Dream Finder, a bigger fellow.
I feel like no humans.
No humans? I feel like it's only animals, yeah.
Not even a literal imaginary,
not even a fictional imaginary.
How about R2D2?
Well.
Mm.
If he's all thick is the issue.
He's the same amount of width.
Is he Disney canon?
Yes, he is.
Well, he's owned by them now.
He's owned by them.
And was already from the rise.
He's all seat.
Actually, looking at your Rex toy,
Rex technically, his bottom part is bigger.
That's true.
But I don't know, but it's bigger all around.
That's like he's got a big seat and a big,
you know, an equally thick pelvis.
And hips.
It's like a hoop skirt.
I think it doesn't work.
Pelvis makes me uncomfortable.
Is there a better word for pelvis that's a little safer?
Pouch.
No, no.
Front?
Front.
I guess front.
Like grill.
I think front is the best.
Yeah, front.
Front.
He's got a thick front.
But let's be clear, front isn't your like,
No, no, no.
It's like, it's just your front.
That's all it is.
No.
There's another, we got to dive.
How about front seat?
Yeah.
It does help explain.
But who, no.
You guys don't sound like you agree.
It was just a pitch.
Oh yeah, no.
You don't have to be polite, cause I'm a guest.
I could just say, no, that doesn't work.
That's exactly why we had to be polite.
No, no, no.
Don't just think of me as if I'm not here at all.
Well, if we do that,
you won't be speaking for the rest of the episode.
That's fine.
All right, that's it.
And you'll sit patiently while we talk about Trader Sam's.
Yeah, we all went down to Trader Sam's a little bit ago.
Now this is a, we, this was your topic suggestion.
And of course we had to do it.
This is a great thing to talk about for a little while.
Did we have to go do research?
Probably not.
We've all been, we remember it well enough,
but how delightful it was to do research.
It was great.
It's nice.
It's such a dark restaurant to go into
on the middle of the day and just pretend it's night.
We did it at opening.
Yeah, like 11 a.m.
To make sure that we got in
because it can get a little crowded.
And you can end up out on the terrace,
which is plenty pleasant,
but that's not what we're gonna talk.
It's not what we wanted to talk about.
We wanted to see the effects.
Never sit on the terrace.
Don't ever do.
Demand perfection.
It's better to wait in the non-waiting area by the door.
Yes. Yeah.
You always want the indoor experience at Trader Sam.
Well, unless you want quiet.
And then the terrace is usually,
like they have like spruced it up over the years
and put an outside bar and.
They have some musicians though.
So it sounds like so quiet.
It's nice. I like it.
I would never say don't sit on the terrace.
Yeah.
Maybe if you want the terrace, go to the terrace.
But if you're there for Sam's, it's a pretty big let down.
Yeah.
I mean, if you're going to see Sam's
and you don't do it a lot or you've never done it,
you gotta do it inside.
Yeah. It's like immersive.
Sam's is chaos in the traditional,
like happy hour nighttime.
Oh yeah.
You have to like stalk seats together.
Yeah.
And seats, literal seats, not butts.
Literal seats, not butts.
Chairs.
Those chairs are not part of the tournament.
Yeah.
This episode comes with a key.
Yes.
The way I say seats.
Assault key.
Assaults that matters.
I say them in different ways.
In my head at least.
You kind of glaze over at seats.
You don't go.
Seats.
And the same applies for front seats as well.
Yes.
In this context.
There's no front seats in the restaurant
unless you turn it around and sit on it
in the cool teacher way.
You see Slater.
Which is how I sat.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah, yeah.
You're like check this out, guys.
Guys, let me show you a trick or two.
There's this new way to sit.
I don't know if you know about it.
It's pretty rad.
We should say, by the way, just in case you don't know.
So there's two Trader Sam's establishments.
One is Trader Sam's Enchanted Tiki Bar,
which is at the Disneyland Hotel in Anaheim.
And then there's Trader Sam's Grog Grotto,
which is in the Polynesian Hotel in Disney World.
Yes.
The first opened May 2011.
That was the Enchanted Tiki Bar.
Grog Grotto came along in 2015.
And they're similar, but Grog Grotto has a lot more
20,000 leagues under the seats stuff.
Like a lot more. Under the seats.
Under the seats, all right.
You've upset Jason.
I'm sorry, Jason.
Yeah, so they've been around for a little while.
Sam. He's in the zone right now.
At the Disneyland.
All right.
We're done with the seats part.
Okay.
All right.
I love throwing this out. Keep rolling, keep rolling.
Yeah, all right.
Keep rolling, keep rolling.
You're doing fine.
I'm doing fucking research every fucking episode.
Come on, come on.
Go through the research.
So, you know, LA, home to a lot of Tiki bars,
influenced the Imagineers as they were designing all this.
Well, if you want to be saying,
why are you saying it's so tired and beleaguered
if you were excited to say all this?
Oh boy, this is always my favorite part of every episode.
You just said you're excited to say the research,
and you're like, LA is home to all of the things.
It's called Casually, Scott.
It's Casually.
You're staring into the corner of the world.
Anyway, keep going.
God fucking damn it.
Actually, man.
No, what did you want to say?
No, it is a full size.
I mean, it is like a Tiki bar,
and like to the size of a Tiki bar too.
It is very intimate.
It doesn't hold a lot of people.
Yeah, which is.
Brombrato a little bigger.
A little, yeah, but it seemed like,
now I did get to go down there in Florida,
and I walked around it,
but it was very super jammed in there.
There was no way I was gonna get a seat.
I walked past the hostess and like, whoa, whoa, whoa.
And I'm like, I'm not trying to get a seat, I swear.
I'm just gonna take pictures for two minutes,
and then I'm gonna get out,
because it's like a lot of competition
for both of these places.
Neither of them big bars by any means.
They have a better system, I think, in Florida of sitting.
Like they have a, like they're more.
There's a list.
There's a person that's in charge of the list,
and they will like a little bit facilitate that.
Oh, I didn't even,
that didn't even register to me as a difference.
There is no host.
Yeah, there's nobody.
That's why it's just around.
It's just kind of.
It's kind of chaos.
A lot of the Anaheim bars are kind of chaos,
except like Carthay Circle has someone with a list.
And that's a little.
But that's, yeah.
But this, yeah, for Trader Sam's is literally,
like you ask somebody, they just go, I don't know,
watch, watch if someone leaves.
People just like end up in a big pile at the door.
Yes, yeah.
It's a big pile of people.
Which is sort of a stressful time.
Yeah.
So I'd be better to be deeper in that bar, if you could be.
We were close to the door,
but I didn't feel the weight of clusters.
Oh, no, no.
I felt plenty relaxed.
We were there like really early.
Yeah. Yeah.
That helps.
And that might be the tip,
if you want to make sure that you get in,
that you actually, the tip is start drinking at 11 a.m.
I've done it once that early.
And I don't know if you guys had this experience,
but I'm sure I've said this on another episode.
I was working on something
because I was doing a show at WonderCon in a few hours.
So I was working at the bar and somebody came in.
The bartender went, oh, hey, his name was not Mac,
but let's say, hey, Mac, how you doing?
The usual.
And the guy was like, yep.
And it was like 11 or noon or something.
And he just pulled up and that was his usual drink.
And I was like, wow, this guy's doing it right.
Yep.
This is how it works.
If you at home want to play Mac,
we could do that.
You can just ask Mac right now.
All right.
Right now you're Mac at home.
Oh, no.
No, no, there is Mac.
And Mike will play the guy who says, hey, Mac.
So I'm the bartender.
The skipper is what he did.
And I will do the sound of the door.
Wait a minute.
You're kicking it off is what you're saying.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Mac, will you have the usual today?
Yeah.
Oh, do I say yes?
No, now you say very good.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
I fucked the whole thing up.
Back to one.
Hey, Mac, what do you have today?
The usual.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Wait, no.
Wait, that was right.
That was right.
They just told me some devastating news.
Yes, I need my usual more than ever because.
It's not going to fit in my car.
My car has been totaled.
Everyone I know is in a car accident, friends and family.
Oh, sorry to hear that.
19 people were on the usual.
19 people were in a bus to my birthday and the bus flipped.
So I decided to come to Trader Sam's anyway.
Sorry to hear that.
But you will you have the usual?
People really be able to make their own podcast, their own conversation.
We've had so many different scenarios now.
Yeah.
So leaving blanks is a nice.
That's what's great about technology.
Yeah.
One of the things.
That's the only one.
There's only one.
This is the first thing that's been great about technology.
So but, you know, it's an odd place to be a regular because the, you know,
if you're really wanting the full Trader Sam's experience, you want you're
probably getting big crazy drinks that are on fire and stuff.
Which if that's your usual, it's a pretty insane usual.
Also, having a laptop at that bar, they squirt water at you and stuff.
Well, I didn't have a laptop that day.
Have I?
I've never actually I've had my laptop down there at plenty of the hotels,
not at the bar at Trader Sam's.
I would have this place to do it.
I would hope they didn't squirt water at you because they can control that.
That's not a thing.
That's like a bottle.
Yeah.
So they're like shipwrecked right on your laptop.
Straight at the ports at the USB.
They light my computer on fire.
Volcano.
Oh no.
Doing pile drivers on it.
But that, hey, that's the fun stuff though of this.
If you don't know this place and you haven't been there, of course, it's a
tiki bar, of course the drinks are fun, but what you really go for are these
interactive drink experiences, which are not triggered by every drink,
but a lot of them, but you sort of have to know.
I mean, I guess it's kind of a fun guessing game to like, Oh, I'm just
going to throw out a drink that sounds good to me from this menu.
And then some do nothing, but some there's this crazy immersive show that
breaks out over the whole establishment.
It's fun.
It's a lot of fun.
Yeah.
I like these things a lot.
Like it'd be pot.
You could see going into a place like this and think, and then like, Oh,
they're going to do a little thing.
Is that going to be cheesy?
Is that going to be like Johnny Rockets when it's somebody's birthday or something?
But this is so thoroughly imagineered.
And even though all of the illusions are, are little, it's limited to this
window or that ship in the bottle.
They're so cool.
It's such real imagineering and probably the only bit of real
imagineering besides in the parks.
We've just done many exhaustive episodes about downtown Disney.
If you remember, I'm trying to forget, but none of it is really, some things
are cooler than others there, but none of it feels imagineered.
But Trader Sam's is so imagineered.
Yeah, it is something like you could, it's one of the few things Disney was like,
well, anybody can get into this.
So it's technically free.
Why would we ever spend money on it?
But they did.
I guess it's for the hotel guests, but like, this hotel got a big refurbishment
around the time Sam's opened.
Yeah, in 2011.
There used to be a Neverland pool.
There used to be this pool with like skull rock and the ship, the pirate ship.
This is what it looked like.
Which, yeah, it seemed to be beloved, but it was only opened in 1999.
That pool before that, this was still the Marina.
This was still like an in-ground place you could drive small boats around.
Yeah, isn't that weird?
That whole area that's pools now, you could like take a boat out for a real boat.
Whoa.
Yeah.
That's not that much space.
No, that's wild.
It feels, yeah, that feels so like 60s, 70s idea of you're on a vacation.
Very strange.
So they only put in like a real like kids pool area in 99 and then redid it
not too long after.
In 2011, which was that's when they got the e-ticket pool.
There's a monorail themed slide and then the e-ticket logo like at the bottom of the
pool, all of that and Sam's came along in 2011.
And it all ties together very nicely because with that old monorail and the
vintage Disneyland sign, now you've got a 50s, 60s retro thing.
And then Trader Sam's isn't specifically retro, but the general idea of a tiki bar
feels very 50s or even before even even 30s, 40s.
It caught on first when soldiers were coming back from the Pacific and like
bringing like drinks and ingredients and this sort of antique culture, like
souvenirs and that sort of stuff.
So that's when it really caught on.
Where it really required somebody to like personally bring it.
And like, I went to this place and here with I found this vibe and now I'm
bringing it to you.
There were people bringing back pot.
Like we went to Hawaii, we bought back back pineapples.
You know, the thing you can only get a couple of times a year or in a can.
We brought it back.
They're flush with them.
Yeah, there was like a brief resurgence, apparently in tiki bar
popularity in like the 90s.
I'm assuming with like the swing dancing, like all of that, it feels very like
accompanied by the cherry poppin daddies, cherry poppin daddies culture again to
the 90s. Same with smuggling pineapples too.
And smuggling pineapples.
People you knew you can get them wherever, but the thrill of the chase.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Something to go for.
Are you a fan of tiki bars outside of this, Danny?
Great question, Scott.
Which you may not have an answer to.
I mean, I I don't seek them out, but I'm always happy to go to one.
Yeah, when I'm in one, I'm having a good time.
I like them. It wouldn't be my go to.
I live for the closest bar to me is a tiki bar, but it's like
it's a little bit of an exhausting vibe to do all the time.
Do you want to tell everyone across streets?
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
All of them or I'll just leave a blank here.
I did say what you think I got.
He lives in the Disneyland Hotel.
Oh, I wish.
Oh, if only if only.
Um, I found a secret tiki bar in Las Vegas.
Oh, is that the the off strip?
No, it's actually in one of the hotels.
Oh, wait, really?
Which hotel are we not allowed to say?
No, no, I'll say it. Why not?
Nobody lives there. No secret anymore.
I think everyone probably knows about it.
A cosmopolitan hotel.
Really? Where there's like.
It's right by where there's like a Hattie Bees and a bunch of like.
That's secret. I've been there.
I've eaten at that place.
But then there's like a secret door.
Oh, I do know this.
I saw this and it was packed and there was no way we were going to be able to go in.
Yes, I did.
There's like a little secret.
There's a little secret.
Yes, that's the issue with tiki bars is that it's always it's impossible
to move around it. Yeah.
They're a little tiki bar in Clifton's Cafeteria.
100 percent. Yeah, not even that little.
It's yeah. OK. Yeah.
Upstairs. But isn't it hard to get in? It's secret.
There is one in Silver Lake, too, that's like open randomly.
And you can smoke in it.
And that is tea. That's tiki tea.
Yes. You can smoke in there.
Weird. It's like a private family owned
and it was grandfathered in of like as a private club or something.
And that's how you could still smoke into it. Right.
Until last year or two years ago.
I think now you cannot smoke in it further out in North.
I don't know why I guess I'm like saying, oh, I don't smoke.
I haven't smoked in a while, but I kind of like the idea
of being able to smoke in one bar.
They should let one bar. That's a little.
Yeah. Yeah. This one.
This private bar city, one bar should be one bar.
But if that's a tiki bar, then it's even more chaos.
Yeah. Yeah.
I saw a list from and it's an out of date list now
because it was a couple of years ago.
But I saw an LA Weekly list of the top tiki bars in Los Angeles.
And LA Weekly is like a little hip and a little maybe a little judgmental.
So for them to put Trader Sam's as number two on this list,
I was pretty impressed.
I think it speaks to that while it is the Disney fight version of something,
it is also legit.
The drinks are good.
And it's sitting on there with a tiki tea was number four.
Number one, I don't know.
Purple Orchid and El Segundo.
Oh, what is that? I didn't see.
Yeah, I read that list to beat Don Don.
The Beachcomber is on there on the beach, which now is closed since that article.
Don, the Beachcomber is the original.
That's kind of the guy who, you know, kicked off this whole trend.
There were a bunch of those around, I think.
And then there was one remaining and weird, like South Bay.
Tonga Hut is the oldest one in L.A.
that's in Van Nuys, Deeper Valley, which is a fun bar, but also but crowded.
Crowded. You end up in a deeply crowded to.
Yeah. Like, what's the Chicago place?
It's got like a guy's name.
Is it the place I literally went to a month and a half ago?
It's like a it's like a fake tiki, but it's like somebody figured out, like,
how to make a big TGI Fridays.
Oh, oh, oh, that I did not go to that one.
I know what you're talking about.
It was big in Chicago when I was little, at least at least to my parents.
Like my dad talked about it all the time.
He's like, oh, and they invented the Mai Tai, he used to say.
Oh, which I that can't be true.
It could have been that one.
Yeah. I don't know why my dad thought it probably was like
the first time he had ever seen a Mai Tai.
And my dad was like, they invented it.
Just lodged in his head.
Why not? Could have been that. Who knows?
There's a trader Todd's in Chicago.
Ah, the exotic South Pacific from Todd.
Well, let me tie it all together and say that one of my favorite
tiki bar experiences was on the island of Kauai.
That I was in a very stuffy hotel.
We went and visited a stuffy hotel where we weren't even getting service
because the hotel was being so judgy of and like everybody around us
was a fucking rich asshole.
It was so snooty.
It was beautiful air, but we want out of there.
We want a place for the people.
And I looked up, is there anything fun to do around here?
I think Princeville is the town.
And I and sure enough found, oh, my God, you're kidding.
I can go to a place called Tiki and Niki,
which is a tiki bar owned by Todd Rungren.
Wow. Yeah.
Favorite musicians in the world.
He has his wife mainly runs it like seems to really.
It's almost like somebody went back in time and put that there for you.
Yeah. Yes.
What would make Scott Gardner happy right now?
Well, I put it there for himself.
I did it. I'm saying like in the future, you like a wild stallion.
Save my younger self.
What all I'll have Todd Rungren open up a tiki bar.
I need to plant the idea in Todd Rungren's wife's brain.
And yes. Well, not only that, but it's also like and sometimes,
you know, it's a place that some of the the Kauai locals could stop by
and do a set like Walter Becker from Steely Dan.
What? Yes.
I don't know if that ever happened.
But anyway, if you're on Kauai, that place was fantastic.
I found out about it from an article called Aloha. It's me.
Nice.
Truly made for me. Very much made for me.
Articles called that. Yes, they don't have.
There's only one Todd themed drink, which is Bang the Drum Rum.
Oh, yeah. Kind of a later.
But yeah, they named it after his worst.
His worst.
But one of the more well known.
The big yes. Yeah, yeah.
What is his rock and roll part to it?
He goes back in time and plant the seed in his wife's brain.
About a Todd related drink.
What would it be?
Well, I don't have the drink ready to go,
but I would love if it was called a wizard, a true bar.
Hmm. After his album, a wizard, a star listeners, no wizard.
Yeah. His best album is best.
It's one of the top 10 albums ever made.
No one listens to me on this fucking rules.
A drink that I might need a minute on that one.
Oh, sorry. Yeah, I didn't mean to put you on the spot.
No, no, no.
Is that is that Todd Rungert's own type?
Is it is it just a rum drink that they make there?
Or does he have an actual label like a Sammy Hagar of his own?
Sammy Hagar, of course, has Beach Bum Rum,
which has replaced his Cabo Wabo, which he sold.
He sold. Yeah. Oh, really? Yeah.
I'm never drinking Cabo Wabo again.
What a loss.
Oh, wait, I have it.
It would be a drink named after one of his other best albums.
And it would have to be like a mojito, something with mint in it
so that it could be hermit of mint hollow.
That's great.
Of course, it is hermit of mink hollow, the real album.
Right, right. OK. That's really good.
Thanks. It just took me a minute. I'm sorry.
You know, so it's like maybe you could work the word mojito in there, too.
Hermit of Mint Hito.
Yeah, there you go. Spelled with a W.
Great. All right.
I'll close I'll self close the door on Todd Rundgren thoughts and see myself out
for more Todd Rundgren thoughts.
Stop me in person.
I'll do it happily.
Where were we, though?
Tiki and Tiki's and Todd's go together is what I'm saying.
Sure.
If you're a Todd, consider
getting into opening a Tiki bar, being at a Tiki bar.
That one's probably the easiest to do.
Yeah. Just go be at one. Just go be at one.
Do we know what the first trader something is?
Is it from is it Vicks?
Is that what it is? Yeah.
I think who redating actually may have invented the Mai Tai.
Is that something was invented at Trader Vicks?
Not the Chicago guy.
Not just the Chicago man.
Not this Chicago shiester.
Although what if it is?
What if I want to know the name of you?
I was going to Trader Ditka.
No, no, it's not him.
It's not him. It's a different one.
If we're wrong and the Mai Tai was invented in Chicago,
we always say people are yelling information at us.
If we're wrong on this podcast, let's do what you said and leave the space.
Trader Mai Tai's weren't invented in Chicago.
And that was a space where you could have yelled angrily at us.
And then you could say, oh, that's where they were invented.
Thanks, listener.
Oh, I guess we were wrong.
Unless they were right.
Oh, I'm glad you're agreeing.
You were wrong. Dead wrong.
Am I ruining your guys' podcast?
I don't think so.
Oh, no.
We do that all by ourselves.
Well, and also, this is unlike the one the we did some bars
during the downtown Disney ordeal, and we used it being about bars to drink a bunch.
And so this feels more coherent to me in that we're not drunk.
That's where the Mai Tai was invented.
Oakland?
Oakland. Oakland.
Thanks for letting us read it.
By Victor J. Bergeron.
Is that Trader Vic?
Did he?
Got to be right.
Whoa.
You'd have to think.
Wait, Bergeron?
Tom Bergeron, his grandfather?
Trader Tom.
Trader Tom?
Dancing with the stars is Tom Bergeron?
Wow. We got to look that up.
Let's look no further into it and just assume it's true.
Yeah, you're right.
Tom Bergeron is the heir to the Mai Tai fortune.
Oh, my gosh.
Do you think Tom Bergeron has any drinks that he's made up?
The Tom? Probably.
But the Tom.
It's just whiskey.
It's just whiskey and ginger.
America's funniest, America's bloodiest Mary.
America's bloodiest home, Mary.
Home, oh, my God.
Is television host Tom Bergeron related to Trader Vic?
Victor Bergeron is the founder of Trader Vic's and grandfather of TV host Tom Bergeron.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
No kidding.
So he doesn't have to wait for a table.
He doesn't have to wait for a table in West L.A.
Wow.
We got to just remember to do the research.
That's how he got the home videos gig.
He was just they've like, yeah, he sent his grandpa to loosen up those ABC executives.
That's a very bizarre fact.
It's nice when some of the research we just save and do it live in the air,
because then you get the joy of all of us together going, wow.
Hold on a second.
Oh, is it a lie?
Is this a snopes?
I was on Tiki Central, Tiki Room Dotcom, which is Tiki message board.
What's your name on that message board?
Michael Carlson.
Mike, the beachcomber, Mike, the beach, Carlson.
People are disputing this.
OK, that brings me.
So I also saw people disputing stuff on Tiki message boards when I was trying to figure out.
Oh, no.
Because I was trying to figure out what is in Trader Sam's Grog Grotto,
which is the base for a lot of the drinks.
OK.
A lot of the drinks say it's a mix of tropical juices.
It seems to be people have reverse engineered it.
And it's a lot of stuff that is used as like bases in tribal drinks.
It seemed to agree that it's passion fruit, orange juice, guava.
That's big and a Pog.
You see Pog juice.
Where the word Pog came from is passion fruit, orange guava, pineapple juice, lemon juice.
And then possibly add ins of this is other stuff that's in a lot of the drinks at Sam's.
Orgeat and Falernum, these are syrups.
Orgeat is an almond syrup, almond sugar.
I will correct you only because I wanted to compliment that item.
So I looked up the pronunciation and it is or-jot.
It's or-jot.
It is apparently.
I believe so.
And it's because I don't usually like the fruity stuff in these drinks.
But everything I've had with orgeat has been great.
And it's some combo of orange water and almonds.
Just got curious what it was.
And I like it.
That is like a sugar additive that is delightful.
Falernum, very similar.
Also has a bit of a bite from ginger and lime and either cloves or allspice.
So you see a lot of the drinks on the Sam's menu has orgeat or falernum.
Nice.
Allspice.
Yeah, allspice.
I hope not.
They just open a can and pour it into my drink.
I will correct you.
Yes, I use allspice.
That's why I always.
Oh, wait, it's not allspice.
It's old spice.
Wow.
Wait, oh, I thought you knew.
No.
Yeah, I thought you were.
No, that was not a joke.
I genuinely thought it was called allspice for a second there.
That's good.
That was like a natural A to C. You skipped the, oh, this sounds like old spice.
But I'll say allspice.
I skipped it by being dumb and thinking that the deodorant was actually
called allspice.
Allspice is a potent spice.
So it would cover up odors.
You could use it.
A lot of people do, actually.
It would probably irritate your skin if you're just rubbing allspice all over it.
The thing is, yeah.
But the thing that is debated is we're shocked in the Graug Grotto
because some of the drinks have it listed separately.
Their mix is called the Graug Grotto.
Or Graug, or Gorilla Graug, excuse me.
OK, OK.
Gorilla Graug is like their base fruity kind of fruit punch.
How hotly contested is this online?
Oh, one or two guys on a 5'3".
I'm just curious if it's like a bigger.
People trying to make it at home.
Oh, OK.
Who are wearing roughly identical shirts.
Yeah, everyone can agree on the fashions, that's for sure.
Yeah.
But it seems like Bergeron debated.
I don't, I'm doubting it.
There was a lot of people who said it was true on this Tiki room message board.
And then somebody said no.
And then I can't get it backed up on another site.
So I'm guessing no.
That would be delightful to think it's true.
I'd like to assume it's true.
Look, I've lost my faith in Tiki Central.
Open 24 hours.
Stay out of these message boards, everybody.
There are hotbeds and the info we can't always believe.
What have we had that we've enjoyed?
I don't know when the appropriate time to bring this up is,
but we missed out on a key feature of that bar.
But what is that?
The sinking stool.
Yeah, yes.
I did not know that.
Yeah, that's a real thing.
Like, it's a little prank the bartender will deploy, his or her will.
Wow.
They'll just push a button and very, very slowly,
the seat will start to sink over the course of a half hour or something.
And then the person's below everybody else at the bar.
It's a great thing.
If you order the shrunken head, I think that's the effect.
Oh, I don't know if all the seats do it, though.
But not all the seats do it.
I don't think ours did.
I don't believe that.
Because I actually was like, I asked the bartender secretly.
I was like, can you make one of our seats go down?
And they were like, oh, you're not sitting in the right ones.
It's only a specific.
OK, OK.
Oh, I like that you slipped in a little question.
I wanted it to happen.
I wanted to create a moment.
Yeah.
Should have given him a 20.
Does this change it?
Yes, actually.
If you would sit this guy goes under the seat
and just tries to move Jason's seat down with his hands.
If you would successfully shrunk in our seats without us knowing,
yeah, that would have been a delight.
Is that true, though?
You have to order that drink.
The shrunken zombie head is certain barstools
will begin lowering to the floor.
Same if you order beer, the draft eyes start to glow
and tiki drums and chants play.
And if they order, if they're doing a bunch of beers,
it will speed up the sound.
Wow.
Yeah, because all of the taps are tiki heads
and their eyes will glow red.
Yeah, OK.
So we should just say all of these effects.
So those are a few of them.
I got shipwreck on the rocks, as I said, with Orjat, Knob Creek
whiskey, dram, and pineapple juice.
Oh, wait, no, I'm sorry.
I'm reading the Spiced Island, which is what I had in Florida.
I'm fucking up again.
I don't remember what was in the shipwreck on the rocks,
but it was wonderful.
And that causes a ship in a bottle
to sink, which is up on the shelf behind the bartender.
Yes, that's from the Adventurers Club.
That bottle is one of the few props.
I read an interview with the head set decorator,
and he's like, that's one of the few props
we were able to claim for the Adventurers Club,
because so many of the other props
got sent to Mystic Manor.
Oh, but they're all around.
They're around.
Wow.
Yeah, but that bottle is original.
They redid the ship inside.
They redid the footage inside.
This might be a very novice question,
but what do you mean exactly?
What is the Adventurers Club?
The Adventurers Club was an interactive theatrical bar
and club in Pleasure Island in Florida back in the 80s.
There was an all night club district.
And it was just crazy set decoration.
It was like this, but two stories tall
with multiple rooms and shows and actors.
And that's closed now, and that stuff's just everywhere?
They repurposed it all?
They sent a lot to Mystic Manor, which is a ride in Hong Kong.
It was an early success of this Imagineer Joe
Rhodey, who's associated with probably some
of the more tropical adventure kind of rides.
Avatar in Florida and Animal Kingdom is him.
So this was an early thing he did insanely well.
Oh, cool.
He is referenced in the bar.
This is the nod to Joe Rhodey inside of him.
Oh, there is a big Tiki head, and it's kind of sloppily
labeled Joe.
And it has the earrings.
As part of our live show in Florida,
we put on these big dangly earrings,
which are what Joe Rhodey wears.
And so this Tiki head has the big dangly earrings.
That's awesome.
Yeah.
Wow.
And I think part of the desire to build Trader Sam's here
and part of the pitch on what the vibe was going to be
was, let's have some of that adventures club spirit.
Yes.
Let's have it be like a kooky funny place.
It seems like maybe there was a take early on in Imagineers
developing it where it would have been a little more stately
and classy.
Like a posh Tiki bar.
I don't even know what that looks like,
but I saw that mentioned too.
Yeah.
I'm not sure.
Maybe more in the Grand Californian vibe,
where that's like, yeah, it feels very sophisticated
if you're getting a drink at Grand Californian.
But it was this one Imagineer, and there's
a few interviews with him, Brandon Clayla, hopefully
I'm saying that correctly.
But he was a former Jungle Cruise skipper.
And he had just joined Imagineering
and found out this was happening and went and begged
to be part of it.
I've got the take.
This is me.
I'm a Tiki guy.
I know how to make this thing.
The place has a passion to it.
Oh, for sure.
There's nothing like.
Well, not only did this guy develop the backstory,
the notes, he wrote the copy of all of the notes,
short rounds note.
He came up with the drink names.
He developed the spiels that the cast say,
telling you what the place is.
He came up with the idea that this
is the place where the skippers from the Jungle Cruise
hang out during off hours.
That's the back story.
They aren't bartenders.
They're skippers.
And this is where all the skippers
go to hang out when they don't have expeditions to do.
That's really cool.
It's really neat.
And of course, what we haven't said
is that Trader Sam is a character from the Jungle Cruise.
So that ties everything together.
But then not only did this guy, Brandon,
develop all of this and really specifically
hammer out all the details,
he collected every prop himself in both of them,
in Anaheim and Orlando.
Wow.
Anaheim, I think it's estimated at 1,600 items in it.
Is it really that much?
1,600 pieces.
Yeah, it's super dense.
It's snow.
But you look around and what an insane,
to have the vibe of it's kooky
and things are exploding off of the walls.
How hard to populate that.
Yeah.
And the attention to detail to individual stuff.
I saw one of the interviews with that guy
and one of the things that brought him to,
seemed like in his career,
he made a documentary about the fan culture
around Indiana Jones.
Oh.
And as a big, scenes have a big love,
affection for Indiana Jones.
And when they were talking about like,
should we put Indy's hat and whip in there?
And he's like, well, that's ridiculous.
Indy wouldn't let go of his hat and whip.
So they, the attention to detail,
they're like, but maybe he gifted Sam a whip.
So that is how we square that circle of like,
there's a whip in here.
And it is a gift from Indiana Jones to Trader Sam.
So it's not like a,
like a hard rock where you're gonna get the original guitar.
The original.
100% authentic, all of those hard rock.
This is a guitar gifted from,
Yes.
Famous guitarist, Axl Rose.
Yeah, Gary.
Famously beloved guitarist.
Yes.
Beloved musician, Gary Glitter.
All the Gary Glitter stuff still on the walls.
That's awesome though.
Yeah, how cool of this guy to take the initiative.
The thought, the thoughtfulness of like,
well, Indy would keep his whip.
Let's not get carried away.
Indy would keep his whip,
but let's call the bartender skippers.
Like all the bartenders are referred to as skippers,
like the Jungle Cruise guides.
There's a lot of real internal logic to it.
Other Indy stuff, you've got the map
of the Temple of the Forbidden Eye,
mere feet away in Adventureland,
which is the same one that's in Indy's office in the line.
I think even maybe, I forget,
I think the one that had been in the line
got moved over here and they put a copy in Indy.
So this one is the original map.
Well, it seemed like they couldn't find
the original map in the archives
and realized it was in the ride, so they duplicated it.
And so the one is in the, I think it's duplicates now,
one in the queue and the other in the bar,
and the original is being restored,
because they're like, we probably shouldn't just have this
sitting in the line.
In a bar or a line, yeah.
And while we're talking Indy,
maybe it's a good time to bring up the short round letter.
Yeah, there's a letter to Trader Sam.
I feel like we've skipped around way too much.
Part of the theming of this bar is that there's artifacts
everywhere that Trader Sam is inherited
from friends all over the world.
As part of this guy Brandon's pitch
is that Sam knows everybody.
Everyone's stopped in his bar.
He's visited people, so he knew Jack Sparrow.
I like that detail, that Trader Sam
is hung out with Jack Sparrow.
This starts the precedent for mixing different movies
and Disney park lore.
We talk about the Guardians of the Galaxy ride.
Tanelier Tavon is a big Disney parks collector,
which I thought is funny.
It doesn't quite make sense, but also this is actually
the precedent for Indiana Jones knows characters
from the rides that aren't Indiana Jones related.
Yeah, and if they were in the bar at the same time,
Indiana Jones could hang out with Jack Sparrow.
Did you know Tony Stark sent Sam
the original code for Jarvis?
I didn't know that.
It's in there, it's in the bar?
The code, it's in the bathroom.
Oh, okay.
Only under-
Jarvis talks to you in the bathroom.
It's only in specific stalls.
You gotta pick the right stall.
The toilet seat opens its mouth.
To talk to you.
Hello.
I'm Jarvis.
But so he's collected letters and artifacts
and he got a letter from Indiana Jones' buddy
from Temple of Doom short round.
The letter reads, Dr. Jones said to give this to you.
He trusts you to destroy it so it not hurt him anymore.
Thank you, short round.
It's written in crown too, isn't it?
Yes.
Okay.
In crayon?
I think so, right?
Yeah.
It looks like it.
It's very-
Or grease pencil or something.
Scrabble Scrawl.
Yeah.
And this is referring to a voodoo doll of Indiana Jones.
Mm-hmm.
And I have this question, which is,
he trusts you to destroy it,
but if you destroyed a voodoo doll,
wouldn't that hurt Indiana Jones?
That would kill Indiana Jones.
Yeah.
I think that's why he's bequeathing it to Sam.
You know how to destroy this without killing him.
Sam knows the ways.
There's only one way.
There's one machine.
It's like disposing of waster needles.
Yeah.
There's only one way to do it and have it be safe.
Sam knows.
And only Sam knows.
So if you have a voodoo doll you need to destroy.
It would also stand to reason though
that Sam then knows how to use voodoo dolls.
So he could do that to anyone at any moment.
He is a shrunken head salesman.
Yeah, that's true.
Should be careful what we say.
Yeah.
It's true.
Yeah, Sam, you think right on the line.
I don't know how much longer Sam is to kick around
in his current form.
All this stuff is a little bit-
All this stuff is a little right on the line.
It'll be-
No, I meant I didn't want to offend Sam.
Oh, okay, excuse me.
Oh, I see what you were saying.
You weren't talking about that we're gonna stumble
into saying something offensive.
No, I was saying honestly,
in all honesty, I was treating Sam like the character he is.
You were worried that if Trader Sam somehow ended up
with a voodoo doll of any of us-
And he's like, I don't like those guys.
And Ethan, we say that a drink price is unfair
or that a tabletop wasn't sufficiently cleaned,
then we could all end up with needles in the chest.
Yeah. Sure.
I mean, we must respect Sam.
Yeah. We love Sam.
He's great.
And we also have to make sure no voodoo dolls get made of us.
That's true.
We'd all love action figures or plushes that look like us,
but how do you prevent one from being voodoo-ified?
Well, I know a guy named Trader Todd
that knows all about that type of thing too.
So maybe if Sam does something bad to us,
Todd will step in.
Todd can help.
If he can't, then Todd Rundgren can play the guitar real good
and cheer us up.
Yeah.
I feel like, oh, I found out I went to Lost Lake,
the Tiki Bar in Chicago, which was fun and very crowded.
This is the nature of-
It's the nature.
Look, they got that right.
Much like a Trader Joe's parking lot.
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Anywhere Trader is cursed, they're all shrunken settings.
Settings.
Like?
This is another, there's probably some clean paragraph
I could have read at the beginning,
but I want to make sure to say the backstory
that the reason Trader Sam's is doing a bar at all
is that he is this character in The Jungle Cruise.
He'll give you two of his heads for one of yours.
This line has been said since 1955.
He's got a bunch of shrunken heads.
Whatever technology and potionry and apothecaratricity,
that's the word, right?
Yes.
Whatever he's, Trader Sam is doing to make the heads small
also applies to mixology.
He also discovered via his potions
that he's a great mixologist.
And that's why he decided to open a bar,
but some of his recipes and trickery
and drink items, perhaps his gorilla grog,
part of like things that he collected for it
has angered the gods.
Some of his methods have angered the gods
and that's why those illusions happen.
Right.
So if the ship is sinking in the bottle
or the volcano goes off,
that means that the gods are angry briefly for 30 seconds
and things go back to normal.
And they don't really hurt anybody.
It's just sort of a fun show.
Yes.
Honestly though, with the volcano and the shipwreck,
it probably just kill hundreds of people on the island.
It's just we're so far away, it doesn't matter.
Like that in itself is a voodoo situation.
Yeah.
And though it's a fun little illusion to us,
hundreds of people are drowning.
Yeah, every time in lava, yeah.
Also come the holiday season,
that view of the volcano has snow going.
Yeah, it's fun.
Snow is in the window, it's fun.
Snow shoots out of the volcano.
Oh yes.
They switch it over to snow?
They switch it over to snow,
which I found a couple days, a couple years ago.
Also the shipwreck, first generation Tiki Mugs
sitting over here.
A lot of Tiki, a lot of Trader Sam stuff over on the shelf.
Yes, so you can buy the mugs.
They are very popular,
especially like that Hatbox Ghost one.
Oh yeah.
And that Nautilus one.
I paid premium eBay prices for those.
Did you really?
Wow.
Maybe I should, I got a,
what would you give me for this golden piranha I picked up?
Yes, you got one when we were down there.
I know what you're talking about.
I got it on a whim.
I was like, oh, people were there just to buy it and stuff.
And I was like, I guess I'll get one, I'm here.
It is cool, I don't have that one.
I have twins, I have two boys,
and I've decided like when something good happens,
like they win the spelling bee or whatever.
Yeah.
Tie, they tie together.
Two brothers win the spelling bee.
Or if one, like let's say one of them wins the spelling bee.
The other one wins the football bee.
It's gonna be like a cup that they get to drink from.
You will save it for a special occasion.
Or maybe like if they're sick, it's like a sick cup.
If one of them wins the acting bee, the Oscars.
The acting bee.
They'll already have a trophy, but.
Are you concerned that you will,
your children will associate piranhas
with something positive?
Like if they then travel the world
and they're like, careful there's piranhas,
and they just hopper on him.
No, they're like, yeah, piranhas are good.
Very cool.
Do you know a lot of people die from like hippo,
get eaten by hippos because people think.
They're friendly.
They're friendly, partially because of like Fantasia,
I would imagine.
Oh, that's a good point.
But yeah, people think hippos are cute and stuff,
but then so they get too close and then they get eaten.
That's a real problem.
They are killers, yeah.
It's a real problem.
They don't think of.
And I know this is a Disney podcast,
so I think we should just tell everyone like,
hippos are dangerous.
Yes.
I mean, if anyone, I don't think I knew.
All the Disney hippos are a lot of fun,
but you should also think of hippos
ravenously eating marbles.
And in the game Hungry Hungry Hippos.
But the cartoon on that would make you think,
oh, they only eat marbles, not bones.
Yeah, but bones are kind of like marbles.
And your skull is kind of like a big marble.
That's really what those hippos.
With a brain in it.
I've had a hippo once.
Oh my God, you live to tell the tale.
Yeah.
Wait, what'd you do?
I pet like a hippo.
How big was it?
Full hippo?
It was a full hippo.
I went behind the scenes at the Philadelphia Zoo once.
And they were like, oh, come here, he's out.
That's scary.
In captivity, the hippo is very friendly.
I don't know.
I wouldn't trust that hippo.
Almost like inches away from the mouth.
We were petting.
The hippo was licking some people.
Yeah, I've read articles about how they're killing machines.
So gosh, the hippo must have been drugged.
Oh yeah.
Oh, I think when their food stuffs are provided for them,
I think it was a rescued hippo.
We're sending a mixed message here now.
It was used to living in captivity.
Some hippos.
Some hippos who have been fed are okay.
Been fed and there's like multiple zookeepers
and like tour guides around.
I'm still advocating the listener not pet a hippo.
If the hippo's a friend of your parents,
Yeah.
That's all you want.
Don't let the hippo pick you up from school
if they're a friend of your parents.
If the hippo was a crossing guard,
does that make it okay to go with him?
No, it does not.
No.
Is it okay to talk to a hippo?
A strange hippo will bite your skull off.
There is in one of my favorite details and props
that I wrote down in Trader Sam's Anaheim
is a in case of hippo attack case.
Not sure what was in there, maybe a gun.
And it said in case of hippo attack, break glass.
And the glass is broken.
So implying some hippo attack that's happened in the bar.
Like a hippo burst in there one time
and they never replenished the case.
It recently happened probably.
Yeah.
Like in the narrative of the bar,
it like happened an hour ago.
Yeah, possibly.
It was like a hippo attack, yeah.
Unless this is a thing like Gordon Ramsay would yell about
and like the hippo attacked 90 days ago
and you haven't replaced the gun.
We're shutting it down.
Everyone, everyone.
Everyone.
We've been on the Gordon Ramsay kick lately.
He loves when he gets to like,
there's a drip of water on the chicken, shut it down.
I was gonna do by the.
I love when he goes into a freezer
and it's just like pouring like really scary liquids out.
Just like, look at that, look at that mush.
That was next to your chicken.
You guys like, it's good, it's good mush.
It's perfect mush.
No, no, that's fine.
That was from two days ago.
Yeah, it's fine.
I put that in a glass.
We serve it to the customers. Two days.
Yeah, yeah.
It's delicious syrup.
Sorry.
Kids love it.
Also just a quick plug for Pluto.tv.
Pluto, not the dog, Disney dog.
No.
But Pluto.tv.
They have like a station where you can just watch
like Hell's Kitchen and like Kitchen Nightmares for free.
I plugged Pluto.
I'm a Pluto.
That was great.
I'm trying to get word out.
Yeah. Pluto's good.
It's wild.
It's like there's so many,
it fills the need of channel surfing, I feel like.
Yeah.
Because there's so many different streams and channels.
Coming on the middle of something.
Vintage Nickelodeon stuff.
Like, yeah.
There's a value to coming in on the middle of something.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
That's true, yeah.
Just landed on something.
Yeah.
Sorry, I took us way, I veered us way.
No, no.
Sorry about that.
We're all Pluto.
Plug for Pluto.
And we're Tangent fans.
The other, I think another,
like a theme of the decor is implied danger.
A lot of like, that's probably like
one of the crazier elements of it.
But in the house rules, it says like,
blow dart guns are not to be used as drinking straws.
And cannibals may not serve people.
And like this, like part, the rules are crossed off.
You don't even know what the rule was.
Like they got to some point and like,
we can't even have that on the sign
because that's just gonna happen.
Yeah.
So I like this idea that like,
around any corner, a hippo could burst in here
at any minute.
A cannibal could lunge up behind me
and start biting my neck.
I like when Disney gets macabre or like a little dark.
Like, you see that in New World,
in Haunted Mansion and Adventureland.
I think they used to do,
they used to do that kind of thing more often
in the 50s and 60s.
Like way more implied danger.
And this feels like a throwback.
It feels like maybe they got away with it
because it was like less of a high profile thing.
It's like, oh, this is just a bar at the hotel.
We're not gonna scrutinize it like.
And if it goes over the kid's head.
Yeah, but you know what I mean?
Like if it was.
It's a bar, so kids are allowed in there,
but you know, it's mainly an adult audience you're playing to.
Right.
So they could probably get away with a little more.
Yeah.
I'm guessing.
Have at it.
You're gonna die today, it says.
It should be more clever than that, I guess, but.
Yeah, but that's the gist.
That's why Brandon's the bigger.
Now the sign that just says,
ask, answer, grass, no one rides for free.
I don't quite understand why they have that one up.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm.
I was just gonna say like the whole collecting culture
of the Tiki mugs, they have generations of them.
So Danny, you were saying you have the golden piranha.
I think they're, have they already done a new piranha?
They might have, I can't remember.
But they've done two generations of the Hatbox Ghost
they've done.
Because one, I don't think I've even paid attention
to these on your mantle, Mike,
that in one, his head is in his head.
Yes.
And in the other, it's in the box.
Yeah, now that's, the one with the head on the head
is from Disneyland, the other one is from Disney World,
which is why I had to eBay it.
That's really cool.
And then they've done another generation of those,
which are just slightly different colors
and might be different material.
Mm-hmm.
The shipwreck one I have right there
is the first generation shipwreck.
It's the green barrel.
The green barrel.
I have that too.
The first one, they've done like four or five of them.
Yeah.
And then that Nautilus there is from Trader Sam's Grotto,
which is first generation Nautilus
from like the year or two after they opened it.
That's a very impressive, I had no idea
that you were such a Sam's head.
I'm a Sam's head, I'm a collect,
I'm an exclusive collector's head too.
You're in the Sam's club.
If there was a Sam's club for Trader Sam's,
I would be involved.
Wholesale.
That is dangerous though,
like for different printings
or different generations of stuff like that,
that can drive you mad.
Yeah, I mean, it's a collect,
there's a whole secondary market for it obviously.
Like there's, I think the first generations are like,
vaguely, I don't know, $100 now maybe.
Yeah.
Do you think Danny's Golden Prawn
is gonna accrue in value or has already?
It is made out of real gold.
You know, I think it will accrue a little bit.
I don't know that that one had like so much demand for it,
but I will take a look after.
I might melt it down.
I don't know if it's real,
I don't think it's real gold.
I really like though, when you buy one of the mugs,
they take your dirty mug away
and give you a clean one.
Yeah.
In a box.
Also the, I don't,
did you write down in the drink I had in that by chance?
Well, I think it just was the golden.
Oh, is that what it was?
Wait, no, no, no.
It was like, it was the-
Was it the Piranha Pool?
Maybe, I don't know.
It was really good though.
It was like drinking like a grape slushie.
Was it a, does it sound familiar?
Strawberry vodka, pineapple juice,
cream of coconut, strawberry puree, blue curacao.
Oh man, I don't know.
My memory is telling me there was some kind of grape taste,
but it was just very sweet and sugary and that very well.
It's going for about $50 on eBay.
Really?
I don't know how much I bought it for, but it wasn't 50.
30?
I don't think I bought it for 50.
Probably 30.
Maybe I'll hold onto it a while longer.
This could be your kid's future.
This is like a-
You pay for college with one mug.
They drink out of it their whole life winning spelling bees
and then I'm like, all right, now I sell it.
You put away childhood things.
No, you can't, you're a monster.
Trader Sam's-
This was my financial plan.
Trader Sam's mug.
Why do you think I always line the bottom of it with plastic?
I needed to keep it mint.
You knew this was coming.
And tell you to not have like pins or needles near it.
It can't puncture.
You're drinking from your college right now.
I think my go-to is usually the Krakatoa Punch.
The Sailor Jerry Spiced Rum,
Ired XO Reserve Rum,
Orge Gorilla Grog and Hibiscus Grenadine.
That one's good.
What does that come in?
What's the mug?
I am not 100% sure.
How many mugs do you have Jason?
I have the barrel, the shipwreck one,
and then I have one that's like clear glass.
That might've been what it is.
It's clear glass and it's like a tiki head
with little wings on the side.
But that one is very similar to ones you just find
at like the 99 cent store tiki mugs.
Right, for sure.
In my research, does food set anything off?
It's only drinks, right?
So I don't think food does.
And also the menu, the menu,
so this bar shares a kitchen with Tangaroa Terrace,
which is now an outdoor bar,
but also the quick service,
one of the quick service spots for the Disneyland Hotel.
And this menu changes so fucking much
that when we went down,
like I had like the Kaluwa Pork Poutine,
and that was new as of like February of this year.
And shortly after we had been there,
they changed the menu again.
Really?
All the Kaluwa Pork stuff is gone.
And now instead,
because they had Kaluwa Pork nachos and poutine,
and now in its place is Tonkatsu Ramen, pork ramen.
Whoa.
Like a bowl of ramen.
Disney, that's pretty cool.
I kinda wanna try that.
I had ramen at Disney last night.
How was it?
Whoa.
For Disney, good.
For regular ramen, fine.
Yeah.
And they have Hawaiian,
they called a Hawaiian platter,
but it's a plate lunch.
You were at Disney then last night and the day before?
Well, no, I didn't go to Disney the night before.
We just were at nuts.
Where in LA, that's right, okay.
Where in LA would you put it ramen-wise if you're...
I'm not like a ramen expert,
so I couldn't give you a definitive ranking.
That's fascinating, though.
I would say, I mean, I would say it's like a B, B-.
I'm glad you tried it.
I wanna try this.
For Disney, though, good.
Yeah, yeah, you're great on a curve.
Yeah.
Disney getting into the pork,
like I feel like I see pork belly on menus a lot now.
And I think that's a thing where it's like,
well, pork is so easy to make in large quantities and cheap,
but I do in my head go like,
oh, pork belly, that's interesting.
And they can charge a little more the perceived value.
They can charge a little more for it.
Sure, sure.
But plate lunch, that's fun.
Also in the changing menu thing you were talking about,
I ordered poke, which I had seen a website say
you can order poke and the poke is pretty good
and it wasn't on the menu,
but I asked them and then they brought some out.
So I don't know, and it was good.
I would say if you're looking for food recommendations there
and you're with a group,
maybe just try that poo poo platter,
which we did as well,
which was just a big sampling of a bunch of stuff.
There's like fried asparagus on there.
The fried long beans.
I like those.
Tango crusted long beans.
Those were good.
Fantastic, yes, not overhyped.
And a good dipping sauce.
Yeah, that aioli was really fantastic.
Okay, officially on the menu, poke bowl officially listed.
Oh it is, okay.
Yeah. Gotcha.
What else do we eat, sliders or something?
You had the burger, you had the Hawaiian burger.
Oh yeah, yeah.
It was fine, I don't wanna say.
You're saying rougher maybe.
I don't wanna say anything about Trader Sam
and Fear Hill retaliate.
That's right, then you're gonna end up with a burger.
It was kinda like cold, it came out cold,
which I didn't understand.
The burgers are cold!
Yeah. Shut it down!
So I wanted to shut it down like Ramsay.
I feel.
If you had started yelling that
and people would have thought it was a tiki effect going off,
but wait, that's just a guy in the bar.
Yeah, that guy's just trying to shut down the restaurant.
Speaking in a British accent, he thinks he's Ramsay.
He said his burger's cold.
I don't know why it was cold, but.
You put that ring of pineapple on something
and I think that cools it down.
Oh, that cooled it off!
Yeah, showing effects.
It is good if you get it fresh.
That's right.
It is like bacon and pineapple and cheese, it's good.
I wasn't thinking that through.
They should warm the pineapple up
before they put it on there.
Hot pineapple.
Cause it didn't pan for a second, yeah, you're right.
You guess so, I think maybe that mix
is why I don't do pineapple on stuff more often.
You mean the cold and the hot?
Yeah, I think you do have a weird temperature balance.
It works with pickles.
Oh, that's true, oh, you're right.
But why not?
But pineapples are bigger.
They're big, yeah, you absorb more cold.
You're not getting a really thick pickle on a burger,
which doesn't sound good at all.
Cold pineapple's like an ice pack.
It is.
Yeah.
Yeah, no wonder that burger was cold.
I was like, how's this even possible?
You're winning this memory test
because you put all this together.
Yeah, I couldn't remember what.
I forgot we were competing.
I don't think I explicitly said that
we were competing against each other, but I guess so.
I just remember that I tried one of the non-alcoholic drinks,
which is just the Gorilla Grog and the hibiscus syrup.
And that was good.
I don't remember your guys' drinks.
I had like a coconut one or something, I feel like.
Yeah, I forget what that one is.
Jason, we skipped past that you're,
one of the things you typically get, crack a toe punch,
that is probably the one that triggers the coolest effect.
That's the volcano.
Yes.
Oh yeah.
That's where the volcano erupts.
I love that there's little streams of lava
that keep going down.
Like there's a projected burst,
which looks really cool against the sky,
but then the volcano itself starts changing color.
Like the lava's slithering down.
And then the room turns red and flashes,
and a rain projection, and that is super cool.
Am I crazy?
Is there a drink there that's like a shared drink
that triggers fireworks or something?
The oa.
Oh yeah, there's like a chant.
There is, they ring a bell,
and that is the one that causes the water spray.
Oh yeah.
That is where they take out a water bottle
and start spraying it real high in the room.
All the laptops, if they see a laptop.
Straight at the ports.
So long.
Firewire.
It's fun if you're deeper into the restaurant
and you feel the rain and you don't know
where it's coming from.
Yeah.
There's the delay of, is there just,
do they just have rain sprinklers in here?
You don't realize until you look.
The bartender.
It's the skipper.
Yeah.
Now that, if you do it in Florida, oh man.
This was the moment when I was like, as I said,
I, in Florida a couple months ago,
I ate outside, but I was like,
I gotta go in and see what all the artifacts are.
And I knew I only had a couple minutes
because it was crowded
and they were gonna push me out of it.
But literally the second I walked in,
somebody had just ordered the oa.
So it was the perfect time to walk in.
And I just got my camera out
because I wanted to see what happened.
And it's all the things that happen in Anaheim.
The guy spritz and rain, my phone was intact, luckily.
They're ringing a bell.
It's all really exciting, lights flashing on and off.
And it was really fun because I was just filming
and I didn't even see this
until my phone camera whipped around to it.
I turned around from the bar
and saw the big Tiki god, oa.
Whoa.
Yeah, it's this like amazing, like huge, scary.
That's cool.
What do you call it? Tiki doll?
What is it?
Idol.
Idol, sure.
Yeah, yeah.
As soon as I whipped to it, its eyes are flashing red
and I gasped like, oh my God, I'm so happy
I got the view of this room
where I didn't even know it was there.
So that is probably the coolest illusion in any of them.
I feel so lucky I got to see it.
And I didn't know the history of oa,
that oa is from Enchanted Tiki Room under new management.
Really?
Wow, I didn't know that either.
Didn't know it.
Wow.
A lot of history here for you, Danny.
Danny looks dumbfound it.
Have you been to the Tiki Room?
Like durr?
Um, no I haven't.
You haven't been to the Tiki Room?
Wait, wait, wait, is that with all the birds?
That's with all the birds.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Birds sing words and flowers croon.
That's actually a wonderful time.
It is really wonderful, just like so gentle.
It's like a great place to go and sit and enjoy.
It's great little, whenever you're taking the boys there,
that's a good little chill out.
It's gentle, yes.
Yeah, for a while it was not so wonderful.
Go on.
Yeah, so it has basically been the same show
in Disneyland forever, but in Disney World,
and we gotta get to this as a topic at some point,
at Disney World they tried to liven it up for the kids
and they changed it and they called it
Enchanted Tiki Room Under New Management.
And the main thing they did was add the big popular birds
of Disney's famous 90s popular birds.
Iago from Aladdin and Zazu from The Lion King.
Wow.
They're now flush with movie cash
and they are investing in a restaurant,
much like Todd Rundgren before them.
And they have bought the Tiki Room and they own it now.
And they're way bigger than the little Tiki birds.
They're like creepily larger.
Yes, you know those two bird characters
who yell at people in different ways?
Well, now they're yelling at the Tiki birds
for being out of touch and for not being good.
That is the boring.
Boring.
So it's the same show, but now with critics in the-
Yeah.
Basically, that's a good way to frame it.
Yeah, I haven't watched it in a long time, but yeah.
And that's considered like, yeah, this is fine.
Like this is, you guys don't like it.
Well, it didn't last very long.
No one likes it.
No one hated this.
It's gone, okay.
Because people hate when anything-
What a funny miscalculation.
Really, yeah, to bring 90s attitude.
It was a very poochy move, I feel.
Yeah.
We need some attitude in here.
And it was supremely annoying.
It was sadly because it was one of the few theme park uses
of Phil Hartman ever.
Phil Hartman was in it, I forget how.
But there was this whole section where,
because all the Tiki rooms have kind of like a rainstorm part,
but in this version, this character, Owa, rises up.
And I don't remember what she did.
I didn't get that far.
But this was a full animatronic,
and they took that animatronic and installed it.
Wow, I didn't realize.
Which, with Trader Sam's being a thing
that ties together all these mythologies,
I really love that they took something
from a universally agreed to be bad attraction
and made it work.
And named the big crazy drink after it.
That's great.
So is the original Trader Sam's in Disney World?
No, it started here.
As we said, they haven't been around that long,
not even a decade.
Even though it feels like it's always been there.
So is that ride under, or whatever that show is that now,
under old management again?
It's back to the old way.
Yes, yes.
Now the sign says under original, back to original.
It does say that?
No, no, no.
I just believed it.
Reverted back to original.
We heard your complaints.
We're sorry.
We apologize.
Oddly in Japan, that same show is taken over by Stitch,
and that one didn't bother me as much.
Stitch is kind of awesome.
No, and he doesn't really.
They love Stitch in Japan.
He's a rascal.
He's not mean.
And he doesn't show up for a long time.
He's in the regular Tiki room.
Finale, yeah.
I gotta find some YouTube of these angry birds.
It's really, but do you remember any other details?
I mean, we gotta just do this season episode proper.
I haven't watched it in forever.
I never saw it in person.
I don't think I did.
I saw it, yeah.
I was upset.
I wanted to see my friends sing their songs,
and then Iago is.
Shut up!
Don't say, shut it down!
Shut it down.
Did he say that?
Yeah.
The chicken is cold!
Oh.
Just hating on the show you all like.
Yeah.
There's like, they change the lyrics to friend like me
to like, we're out in this place now, that, that, that.
Like he.
It's very strange.
They are like, aggressively ruining it.
They're aggressively ruining it.
And they make the birds feel bad and different
because Zazu's more cutting.
They make the birds feel bad.
Zazu's more cutting, and then Iago's like just so big.
But I think eventually Zazu and Iago come around
and they're like, we can have it both ways.
Cause they then anger the gods with their hubris.
This is, yeah, we gotta.
We gotta get into this.
Are they truly flush with movie cash
or is that your addition?
It's like, oh they do it pretty good.
Well they buy it, right?
They do buy the room.
Yeah, they buy it.
So.
I think it is, it is that Looney Tunes world
where they are the actors who were in the movie.
And now like, they, like an assistant would be like,
telephone for you, Mr. Zazu.
Like I think it is that they are movie famous
and have money and are blowing it on a restaurant
like any movie star.
They're playing themselves in the movie.
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
And I, here, I just went to the Wikipedia.
I mean, we'll do an episode later,
but I can't not say, Jesus Christ.
It is that there's, it starts with two animatronic,
two can agents.
One is named William and one is named Morris.
Oh.
No.
Fuck off.
This sort of 90s.
As a WGA member, I'm walking out of this.
I do not approve this show.
The 90s self-aware humor aged immediately
compared to the 50s, 60s, like kind of couched body
that like couch goes over the kids' heads.
Yeah.
Which is still.
It's cheesy, but in a forever.
It's cheesy, yeah.
But in, and like the 90s, like they, they may have been
like kids are gonna listen to Tiki Tiki Tiki Room
on the Walkmans.
Like they may as well have said something like that.
It aged so fast.
William and Morris were voiced by Phil Hartman
and Don Rickles.
Oh, man.
Two greats wasted in a terrible.
And they have to say dialogue about like, I gotta go.
I'm going to sign Donald Duck.
No, well, I'm gonna, I'm gonna sign the Mighty Ducks.
Oh, wow.
Wow, Mighty, what year does this open again?
Like 97 or 98.
The Mighty Ducks.
98.
Oh, and they're pushing the new hockey team and stuff.
And the cartoon.
Do you remember the Mighty Ducks series?
That's another, we promised that as well.
The Mighty Ducks was in a cartoon, wasn't it?
Yeah.
They did a cartoon.
No, no, no, they were ducks.
They were ducks.
It was a sci-fi action adventure show about a duck world
that also loves hockey.
Oh, there's hockey.
There is hockey.
They all have guns.
They're ducky pucks.
Ducks who play hockey.
And they were like, let's see how far we can push
this Mighty Ducks thing.
We got a movie, we got a hockey team.
Let's do it.
Synergy, yeah.
And now a really irritating cartoon.
So it was bad.
Yes, well, we have to watch it and see.
We gotta watch it.
Is it on Disney Plus?
I like it as a time.
It's on Disney Plus.
Whoa, I gotta watch some Mighty Ducks.
I watched the Jefferson Starship theme song.
Weirdly, it's about a duck world,
just like Howard the Duck.
That's where Howard the Duck is from.
So they stole the idea of a duck planet.
Yeah, really?
From one of the most unpleasant films
in the history of time.
But now Disney owns Howard the Duck.
Yeah.
They own the 80s Howard, they own the characters.
They own the characters.
The Marvel characters.
Whoever owns.
The characters in a couple of,
it's in Guardians of the Galaxy, right?
Yeah, people cheered at that.
They should have a lot of affection for Howard.
I'd like it if they brought back Howard.
That'd be good.
I think they could do it.
They're doing a cartoon.
There's a Hulu cartoon, I think.
There was a popular run in the comics
in the last few years.
Oh yeah, definitely had a big seat.
70s Howard the Duck in the comics world has.
Definitely.
But he's moving right up, just, yeah, yeah.
But his, I mean.
We've talked about that.
Howard the Duck was very,
I think maybe I was moving past it
because Howard the Duck is an extremely sexual film.
Do you remember this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's nude ducks.
There's duck nipples in it.
Not for kids, basically.
This is why we sanitize with that word seat.
Because we know how far duck sexuality can be taken.
We know, we've seen it.
And that's, look, George Lucas pushed for that.
They're sexualizing the ducks.
He was producing the movie.
It was him?
There was a lot of duck fun.
I know for a fact, 100%, that George Lucas himself
crafted the duck breasts.
No.
I'm just kidding.
You lie.
And when he handed over to Eiger,
here's my ideas for episodes seven, eight, and nine.
It was a 500 page document,
but it was just, most of the pages are empty.
It was just one cover page that said duck tits.
That's why Eiger.
Eiger wrote about it in his book and said,
you know, we respect George
and what he's added to the pop culture,
but JJ wanted to go a different way.
And a reverent choice.
George complained to Charlie Rose about it.
Just didn't like the duck tits.
And the wills.
Anyway.
What are we gonna recover from this?
I don't know.
We're all lost now.
There is a fun version to do, Howard.
Howard the Duck kind of in comics regarded as like
after the big, like first decade or so of Mad Magazine,
Howard the Duck was kind of Marvel's like funny
like character and well-received.
Crumb inspired.
Crumb kind of, yeah, more a PG crumb.
And also some weird.
Yeah, a little bit of like a lethario vibe.
There's creators ownership issues with that too though
with Howard, with like the creator and Marvel,
like a little like Watchmen.
Who is it?
Is it Steve Gerber? Steve Gerber.
Yeah. Oh yeah.
I don't know.
He came back and did a new Howard the Duck series
a few years ago,
but I think there's still some tension there.
I'm sure they, I'm sure all those comics companies
will pay a really fairly for the characters they made.
I'm sure they'll treat everyone fairly.
They always do.
Anyway. Anyway.
Danny, I think they're implying something that they won't.
I don't know.
Yeah, that seems like a little.
We said a sentence.
Don't read into it at all.
Don't listen to Alan Moore.
I'm skimming my notes and I'm wrapping it up.
I don't have a lot left.
Oh, we've got, it's on fire.
They light the drink on fire.
They bring it, they light it on fire.
They throw some little stuff at it
that makes a fire flare up.
Yeah, like pops. Right, right.
Yeah, that pops and you cannot order it alone.
It is a punch bowl.
You have to have multiple people with big straws.
They don't want to kill anyone.
Yes.
That isn't what the regular,
that's what isn't what Mac the regular
we established earlier, hopefully is having.
Right.
Do you have like just a bunch of,
I know we saw like something from up there,
like a jug or something.
Do you have like, I'd be really curious if you.
Yeah, coin jar.
Where they're collecting,
like they're saving up for their big trip to Paradise Falls.
Yeah.
That the movie is.
I'd be curious if there's,
I know we talked about Indiana Jones,
but whenever I'm there, I'm like,
I'm missing a lot right now.
I've learned a lot today.
I probably have other ones.
There's a newspaper that says Indiana Jones wanted
by Honduran government.
I like that.
I like the aftermath of the press.
He's like wanted.
There's also some,
there's a note from Sala.
We're offering tours of our temple.
I'll come back on Tuesday to get the map.
So that like that map that he has,
like Sala is going to come.
Right.
But at some point.
And I didn't see this in looking through.
And I would be interested to know what
in the narrative of the place, what the date is.
Did you come across that at all?
Cause usually they do place like these places
in a specific time period.
So I would wonder if they actually have a date.
They probably do.
Obviously this guy's a nerd.
I think there can't be if up is in it.
And I mean, I bet it's,
I bet they're thinking it's 30s, 40s primarily.
With the Indiana Jones.
And that's what they turn the jungle crews into
along with Indiana Jones.
But as soon as like what year is Jack Sparrow happening?
What year is Jack Sparrow from?
Well, that would be, yeah, that would be very far back.
That would be, is that 1800s, 1700s?
But Jack Sparrow becomes a mortal in one of them.
He does.
Doesn't he?
Yeah, sure.
I feel like he gets like, he becomes a ghost in one of them.
He's got that Keith Richards blood transfusion.
That's right.
He goes to a Swedish clinic and gets a.
Yeah, a hyperbaric chamber shows up.
And then Charlie Jones are sitting
in a hospital room together.
What's up, Q?
It is a little ethereal, a little out of time.
There's letters and postcards
from Adventurers Club members in it.
And they are always celebrating New Year's Eve
of a certain year.
It might be the late 20s.
Oh, is this Pleasure Island?
There's a, Danny, when you were in Japan,
did you go on the Tower of Terror there?
I didn't.
I screwed up.
I didn't go.
You made a big mistake.
I skipped out.
I was like, I've been on the Tower of Terror.
And then.
No, you haven't.
And I hadn't.
I heard it was very different.
I'm sorry to do this to you.
I was like, I assume it's just Twilight Zone stuff.
And boy, was I wrong.
I'm sorry to do this to you.
I have to leave the blank space for the episodes to yell.
For the blank space for the listeners to yell,
you fucked up, Danny.
Okay, ready and.
Ow. Sorry.
That's okay.
I can live with that.
It's better than a voodoo doll.
Yeah, I'll take that over a voodoo doll.
Yeah, yeah.
Just verbal stings.
Well, I have something to say to the listener.
I thought this through it also.
Hey, listener.
And now I'm in my car yelling at you.
Oh. Oh, good.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
That was silent to silent.
Yeah.
Interesting.
You know what?
No, no, no.
I think you, no, you bested them.
You bested all of those listeners.
I'm in an inception type of a situation.
This is why you have the good jobs.
By the way, I just wanted to talk about this chair
for one second.
Yeah.
Since the moment I've sat in it,
I've felt like I've been looking for a seatbelt.
What?
What do you mean?
Not literally, but it's just, there's something
like about this chair that makes me feel
like I should have a seatbelt on.
Like it's a ride or like it's on a car,
like a moving car.
I don't know.
I mean, we should save this for after the podcast.
And I hope I haven't offended my hosts.
No, I think that people are gonna be very interested
into it, because we don't really talk about this chairs
where I was gonna say seats,
the chairs and couches were sitting on.
So I think that's actually probably an insight
the listener would like to know.
It is the hot seat.
He's sitting on the guest chair, which is green chair.
It's Lindsay's chair that she got from somebody
and almost got rid of it.
I think it's falling apart a little bit.
Maybe that's.
But that might be what it is.
You just feel like your job is a bumpiness to it.
I don't think it's a ride.
I think it's more like a car instinct,
like, oh, I'm right in.
Do you feel like it's sinking slowly?
All a stool.
You guys are really tall right now.
Maybe we played a little trick on you.
We hit the chair shrinking button.
Damn it.
And you thought you had the upper hand
with that car yelling trick.
Is it Jackie Johnson?
Is that from the did Lindsay get that from
past guest Jackie Johnson?
I feel like she mentioned it when she was.
It's not.
And I wanna point out, Jackie, this chair is great.
And I like this chair.
There's just something about it that I feel like
I'm ready to put on a seatbelt.
Maybe just being on the podcast,
we're coming at you with some of the facts
and quips and stuff that you feel like you need a seatbelt
to strap yourself in from this adrenaline rush you've got.
Yeah, you need sort of that harness.
You're on the edge of your seat.
But from all of this exciting information.
You guys talked a lot about Goofy's roller coaster.
Not at all.
His Sky School?
It's a great roller coaster.
We are a little freaked out by it.
It's like a scary, it's supposed to be for kids and stuff.
But it's actually a very, there's a scariness to it.
It's a wild dance.
It scares me way more than any of the big ones.
Yeah, it's a great ride.
You feel too naked on it.
Like you don't have a lot to hold on to.
And there's never a line you can get right on.
Yeah, because most people I think feel the same way we do.
I would think.
Because now it's never even a thought in my head
when I'm there to go on it.
I'll go on it right before we do the eventual episode.
Isn't that what Kyle said to us?
Like he has to convince people to.
You think so, yeah.
He can't get his full party to go on Goofy's Sky School.
It's an acquired taste.
It's a good one.
It's the scariest ride in the park.
I just like that there's no line
and it's a great roller coaster.
That style of roller coaster is called a wild mouse
because it makes you feel like you're going off the edge
at every turn because the seat turns after the wheels.
So you think you're about to fall off.
Yeah, it does have that feeling.
I didn't know that.
That's a good name for it.
It used to be called Mulholland Madness
and it was simulating what it was like
to be on a crazy LA road.
Really?
Yeah, to be like a drunk celebrity.
I'm glad I brought this up.
Driving all over.
Yeah.
Taking one last hell ride.
You're Mel Gibson pre-famous police stop.
Yeah.
It's also like the beginning of Mulholland Drive.
There's like a car crash, spoiler.
Oh yeah.
So it's kind of as close as,
it was like an unofficial Mulholland Drive ride.
It was like kind of a David Lynch.
There's no David Lynch theme park attractions are there?
Oh, if only.
There should be.
No, I don't think so.
Yeah, they should have him come into Imagineering
that once in a while.
Yeah.
Advise on something.
Something cool.
I was gonna say this,
I guess it starts sort of with Adventurers Club.
The whole little universe they've been building out
and it goes from like this to Tropical Hideaway,
which is in Disneyland and then Jock Lindsey's also,
which is a little less fun.
Which ties in Indiana, also in Indiana Jones themed.
Yeah.
And then in Orlando,
like this little universe they've built out
and continue to build out is very fun.
Will it make an appearance in the Jungle Cruise movie
with The Rock?
I've heard people say that it will.
I don't know specifically.
A Trader Sam might be in the movie.
I don't, something.
I honestly, I don't know much more than just what I said now.
So we'll see.
But supposedly there might be some little light references
to see, which is the Society of Explorers and Adventurers.
It's a whole thing.
So I like that.
I don't know, hopefully this movie won't ruin it.
Basically, Danny, there's all this stuff.
They're connecting a lot of rides
and even just restaurants and stuff.
They're establishing all of these figures
who are like the owners of some of the,
here's the guy who owns the Big Thunder Railroad
or what I was starting to say,
the Tower of Terror in Japan is owned by a particular guy
who went and stole goods from tribes and stuff.
Harrison Hightower.
And there's a letter involving him in Trader Sam.
So they're building up all of this
past 30s old timey.
They're all rolling it into one thing.
It seems like, Trader Sam is yet another piece
in them connecting all of these formerly disparate universes.
Yeah, so they'll be like.
And bring Jack Sparrow into it too.
Or even like there's an Indiana Jones.
They bring in a James Garner movie called The Castaway.
Castaway Cowboy.
Yeah.
Like they're pulling weird old 50s.
What's this thing called?
Castaway Cowboy.
No, this project.
Well, there's a thing called Sea Society of Explorers.
So like the Adventurers Club was where like
members of sea would get together.
And that was the place they get like hammered.
And then they had made up all these characters
that are like the owners of rides.
So there's a character named Barnabas T. Bullion
who's the owner of Big Thunder Mountain.
And they have references to them
and all these different attractions.
Their headquarters is at Disney Sea in Magellan's,
the restaurant Magellan's.
So they've slowly built out a not cinematic universe,
but a whatever theme park universe.
Like a ride universe.
And like it's just like as they were filling in details,
cause they have to fill, come up with all these
different details to make the place feel lived in.
They just started drawing the lines between them.
And it's like, this guy knows this guy
and this guy knows they're all friends.
So it's very fun.
It's kind of an Avengers a little bit.
A lot like theme park ride owners
who are not usually featured in the rides.
Yeah.
It's not.
We've all been begging for it.
It's also pretty subtle.
So like only if you're a maniac who listens to the show,
do you like care about it?
So like you're going through,
it's not like you need to know the name
of the owner of the ride before you ride
or else they won't let you, which would be funny.
Like you don't have to answer a quiz.
There's nods to imagine nears.
Yeah, yeah.
Sorry, back to the start.
Better brush up on your trivia.
A lot of rides have nods to imagine nears.
We talked about Joe Rodie being in this,
I will call it an attraction, even though it's a bar.
There's Banjo that says Banjo lessons from H. Goff.
Harbert Goff was a very early imagineer,
not often, sometimes not mentioned,
but was like a very influential.
I think they jokingly called him
like the second imagineer Walt hired.
The one who drew the layout of Disneyland
took that initial order.
Something like that.
He also is known for designing the very first,
the Glamour Trams, the first Universal Studios tour guide
trams back in the 60s.
The Glamour Trams.
The Glamour Trams they called them.
I missed that name.
Yeah, that was what they just, the tour you said?
Yeah, the tour trams, like the red ones.
I wonder when they lost that name.
Scott should have been on the Glamour Trams.
I would have loved to.
Yeah, yeah.
That's much better than the trams.
The only way to have made that job better.
Like the perfect job in my head.
That's the most grasses greeners.
I've like built up that job now.
That was the best time of my life.
Forgotten all the shit.
All the shit.
What was boring about it.
What could have gone wrong in the world in 2007, 2008.
Like those videos where they let John Lasseter
back on the Jungle Cruise to do one more round.
They should let you on the Glamour Tram
to do one more round. I mean, I agree with that,
but I cut off the first part of that.
Yeah, I'm just saying that was the best.
I don't think we could make that comparison.
Best comparison I could think of.
I am in a Hawaiian shirt right now.
You are wearing a Hawaiian shirt.
Maybe that's why I thought.
I think our Hawaiian shirts
different than Tiki shirts though.
Why are you looking at me?
Trivia, go.
You're back to the front line of this podcast.
I think yes.
Great.
I have nothing to back it up on.
Danny, you have a can of pomade in your hair right now.
I feel like you could answer this.
I don't know.
I feel like Hawaiian shirts has exploded
into its own thing where anything can be a Hawaiian.
You could have a bunch of hockey players on your shirt
or something like that.
Oh, it doesn't even have to be floral.
Yeah, I look around, I see Hawaiian shirts and all kinds.
So no, I would say.
I guess the answer is no.
I'm just trying to maybe distance myself from Lasseter
with that question.
That was why the urgency of it.
Right, right.
But I think we've pulled you right back in
in the associated issue with this question.
His wore more novelty shirts or bowling shirt-y.
He would have, yes, he would have like a Maeder shirt
and then he would have 50 different shirts
where Maeder would have different outfits on the shirts.
He was getting that stealth custom.
He still, I'm assuming he still wears those shirts.
They weren't revoked.
Bob Iger came to his house.
Turning your badge gun and shirts.
No, it's all I have.
Walk-in closet.
I have 400 of them.
Why do you have a gun?
Wear a badge.
Oh yeah, it's Disney guns.
All Disney cast members have a gun.
Oh, I didn't know that.
Oh wow.
So not to the old cartoons
where Mickey was always just pulling a gun out.
Which is not a joke.
It is, we've talked about the gun cartoons.
Did Mickey had a gun?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, as an evening.
Keep poking around on Disney+.
I bet you that's all not on there, right?
Yeah, maybe the gun stuff has to go.
I'm really upset that on Disney+,
I grew up a lot watching these like goofy training videos.
Like goofy goes swimming.
They're not on there, right?
Goofy goes to the beach and swim.
Whatever that one's called is on there.
But the how-to are.
There's a few.
There's a few, no, no, that one is a how-to.
But the one that I remember that's like seared in my memory
from watching it so many times is the skiing one.
Yes.
And that one's not on there.
There must be something in there.
That's what I was looking for.
There's something rights-wise
or is there some incredibly offensive?
We forget that in every frame of it
he was smoking a cigarette and shooting a gun.
Yeah.
I think they're probably doing.
Oh, goofy.
Like waves.
He didn't know what it meant.
Yeah.
What were you saying, Jason?
Oh, I think waves.
I think they're probably doing waves of content.
Yes, they are.
As people's membership year or six months are ending,
then we go like, and here's a bunch of stuff
to keep you around.
So I bet that stuff is coming.
We got the goofy stuff.
You could cancel or watch the seven-minute cartoon.
I saw it turned out to be a real click-baity article.
I thought it was a real website, but it was not.
But Disney has promised more adult-oriented content
is coming.
And I'm like, wait, how are you using that phrase?
Because I was like, oh, are they putting
all the touchstone stuff?
Or are they putting all the actual PG?
And then it turned out to just be marketing speak.
And it was just the head of Disney Plus going,
we're going to keep making original, great original
content like the Mandalorian.
And it's like, well, that's a PG-13.
That's not really what I was thinking.
So not porn.
Not porn.
Not porn of the Mandalorian.
Not even like Splash.
Not even like that sort of stuff.
Not high-end pornography.
Not high-end.
On the same sets as the Mandalorian.
But they can put any actor in there.
Yeah.
Peter Cushing.
Grand Waff Tarkin.
His estate signed off on it.
We have all the face scans, and we can just do it.
Yeah.
All the monsters, the raiders.
Tusken Raiders.
Yeah.
And it would be the third woman to appear on camera
on those sets.
A lot of dudes in that Mandalorian.
A lot of dudes.
That's the issue with making the XXX.
Yeah.
There's not a lot of people.
It's the raiders with each other.
I don't see an issue at all.
I don't see a problem at all.
Zuckus and Boss going at each other.
No problem there.
All Raider dogpile.
Yeah.
OK, what else about the Fun Tiki Bar?
We should start winding it down.
I said many closing thoughts not related to Raider dogpiles.
I don't know.
I had a lovely time.
It's a fun place.
It's great.
Yeah.
Packed with details that it would take you
dozens of visits.
None of this stuff that we witnessed and enjoyed
and talked about happened on the terrace.
No.
You got to go inside, wait, stalk a seat,
do all the things you got to do to eat inside the dark
restaurant.
You got to do it.
I disagree with Mike Carlson.
And this is the only thing I disagree with him about.
Look, if you're coming from the jungle
and you've got some scurvy and you need to sit outside
and get some weight and see from fruit juices,
you might want to sit on the terrace.
There's also other places to eat.
If you have scurvy, though.
If you have scurvy.
We'll do another episode about just the terrace.
So we'll talk about it then.
Just about the terrace?
Yeah.
Just about the terrace.
Oh my god.
You don't listen to this podcast enough to know we'll do it.
No, I know.
I'll be forced to do it.
Oh.
Oh, pity the boy.
That was terrifying.
That was like you turn into a warlock for a minute.
Well, now there are warlocks in the adventurous clan.
There are warlocks in sea, I bet.
Magic is going to come.
He turned into Norma Desmond in my mind.
The next time I say, I'm not sure there's
enough meat on the bone for that to be an episode,
I will just get an all caps text, pity the boy.
Pity the boy.
I'll have to sit in this place he loves so much.
I think pity the boy honestly might become the new who gives
a fuck about grapefruit or the counterpoint you are wrong.
I think pity the boy.
This is developing quite a cadre of terrifying phrases.
I think that people are going to like pity the boy.
Oh, pity the boy.
That's also what I'm going to get when I'm
getting antsy in an episode and showing it.
I'll get all caps pity the boy.
Pity the boy.
Yes, those little notes we pass each other.
Who would have thought that at the end of this episode,
another phrase would be coined.
I feel honored to be here for it.
Yes.
You helped create it by mentioning this terrace.
It's true.
There will, I guess, be an episode about.
Yes.
You don't have to.
Just because you said it out loud, do you have to?
I don't know.
It's up to them.
It's up to Jason and I.
I will.
Look, I'm not promising it in the next month.
We promised about 100 episodes so far.
And there's a lot of those I'd rather do than the terrace,
which we've all agreed is lesser than the bar.
It's not as good as inside.
That sounds like paywall.
I think that's the episode.
I think you just did the episode.
But there's.
End of episode.
There's a fire pit.
You just survived the terrace episode.
There's a fire pit you could talk about over there.
And there's different cups.
They don't want you taking it out in case you go by the pool.
And now we've survived the terrace episode.
I love doing the episode within the episode, guys.
I also think that I should sign up and try to become a performer.
I play acoustic guitar outside to see what that's like,
to really enjoy that experience.
I mean, I agree with that.
So if I perform there, too, let's try that.
That would want a terrace episode for sure.
I guess.
I actually.
All right.
I'm not too interested in you.
I'm not too interested.
Performer permits.
Pity the boy.
Pity the boy who must play for the people who enjoy his tunes.
Screw this up.
I worked myself into a shoot, as they say in wrestling.
Mm hmm.
Damn it.
Well, I guess in that case, we'll
start researching the terrace episode.
Danny Jelinek, you survived podcast.
Oh, wow.
Thanks for having me, guys.
Yeah.
Hey.
Thanks for having me.
No pity for the guest, because I think you had a blast.
I'm still smiling.
I'm still.
I mean, I didn't fall out of my seat.
You didn't, despite there being no seatbelt.
Despite no seatbelt, we talked about it all.
And listener, it was great talking with you.
And what you got to say back to me?
Oh, that's a shame.
Oh, that's harsh.
Sorry to hear that.
Well, I tried.
I'm not really great at being on podcasts.
So listener, I'm sorry you felt that way.
But just know I'm going to stop this bit now.
If you're man at the bit, it's over.
You never have to hear it again.
Danny, you're great.
Hey, you were great on the podcast.
And you're great at many things.
And working people could see you be great.
Let's exit through the gift shop.
That's what I say.
What would you like to plug?
Oh my.
I've recently started tweeting again.
I know.
I've been enjoying that.
But then I also have stopped tweeting again.
But if you want to read some of my old tweets,
they're still there.
If you want to see a burst from around October, November.
List generator on Twitter.
Yeah, list generator.
Just spelled just how it sounds.
And you're doing stuff on that Kimmel show.
Yeah.
Oh, I have a zoom.
Are you now worried that you are an ABC employee?
Are you now worried at all that this is fire?
I think I spoke very highly of Disney and all their property.
I just, hey, Disney, if you're out there listening,
put Goofy go skiing up sooner than later.
We'd all appreciate it.
That's my only critique of the Disney corporation.
When are they putting up Jimmy Kimmel live?
Oh, that'd be good too.
Well, it's part of the Hulu package.
No, no, no.
I want the archive.
I want all 15,000 episodes.
They're on there.
They're on Hulu.
Are they all?
I think a lot of them, yeah.
There's no way.
It's like every episode.
You can watch a ton.
I think you can actually.
You might be able to watch all of them.
You may be able to watch at least.
Start at one.
You got to start at one.
Making him alive is not going to make sense
unless you start at one.
You can't just jump in now.
Yeah.
The other thing I will actually plug as well is I
have a zine called Dipped.
Oh, yeah.
That you can get.
Dipped is delightful.
You can email me at dippedzine at gmail.com.
Me and Dan Abramson make that.
It's a zine that we make that we actually
dip into coffee, the first issue.
We're currently hard at work on the second issue.
And it's going to be dipped into something else this time.
Yeah, probably.
I don't want to spoil anything, but we're talking about wine.
Oh, interesting.
I think at some point, glue would be fun to make it.
It might be.
Guys, I didn't really come here to talk.
Is that something you would have to investigate?
Oh, I would test it.
OK.
But yeah, we just dip the bottom corner in each.
Sorry, I didn't plan on talking about Dipped.
No, we're talking about Dipped.
I don't even know if we have any more to sell.
But I think we have some left.
If you email us, it's like $7.
I think someone who's been on this podcast
must have written for Dipped.
Oh, yeah.
I'll do it in the future.
I don't think we're done with it.
If you still want to.
Oh, really?
I'm asking you on the air.
I'm asking all of you on the air if you
would like to submit to Dipped.
Sure.
Because I think you're all very talented.
I would like to buy it as well.
Oh, the audience is not invited?
OK.
Well, that's a lot.
They are strangers to you.
Fair enough.
We went off on a very bad note, and that's their fault.
And that is on you.
If you had said something nice to me in your car
and I had responded to the blank space positively, then yes,
you would have all been in Dipped.
Wow.
I'm going to stop talking about Dipped.
Anyways, I do think there's good.
You should check that out.
You would like it.
Audience.
Yeah.
Great.
I'll do something for it in the future.
Yeah, and for more Podcast the Ride,
follow us on Twitter, Instagram, and Facebook.
For merch, look us up on Tee Public.
And there's three bonus episodes every month
if you subscribe to Podcast the Ride,
the second gate at patreon.com slash podcast the ride.
And I guess we will then say the Kongaloosh doesn't apply,
does it, as a goodbye?
I don't think it does.
No, isn't that a little low?
It's kind of a toast sort of thing.
You can get it.
No, if it's a toast, then.
Oh, man.
You can order Kongaloosh's old style and new style
at Trader Sam's.
Oh, oh.
It's not on the menu.
That's the secret.
Oh, that's fun.
So we should say it.
Yeah.
All right.
So then a hearty Kongaloosh.
Goodbye.
Forever.
Dog.
This has been a Forever Dog Production, executive produced
by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan, Scott Gardner, Brett Bohm,
Joe Silio, and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please
visit foreverdogpodcasts.com and subscribe to our shows
on Apple Podcasts, Spotify, or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news
by following us on Twitter and Instagram,
at Forever Dog Team, and liking our page on Facebook.