Five, four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year, happy new decade.
We're right at the start of it and welcome
to I Guess the Ride the Second Gate.
I'm Scott Gardner joined by Mike Carlson.
Happy New Year, I'm Mike Carlson.
How special does it feel to hear it from us
and from Jason Sheridan.
Happy New Year and welcome to the new millennium.
The exciting innovations all around us.
The gates of time have opened.
Let us march forth and be one anew with the spirit of time.
Yeah, this is a bunch of nonsense.
I'm excited to talk about it.
And we've talked for a little while about kicking off 2020
by celebrating a new year from 20 years ago.
Because this more importantly
than this being the beginning of a new decade,
this is the anniversary of the very famous,
very beloved Epcot Millennium Celebration.
It was all of Disney World I guess.
But really, yes.
But very much anchored at Epcot.
Epcot was Millennium Central.
There was this whole pile of Millennium Celebration stuff
they did around 2000.
Should we take stock of it?
We'll talk about all of it.
Yeah, let's overview it first.
Yeah, to give us a little roadmap.
Yeah, I mean they rolled out a lot of new stuff
and under the umbrella of new.
So technically rock and roller coaster.
Okay, sure.
Is part of the Millennium Celebration.
Technically the introduction of fast passes.
They stuck as like, you know what else is coming.
Yeah, really.
Oh.
They put it like they folded it in
or they were just like, see what's new for the Millennium.
Well, they were at least in the TV special.
Maybe it had been around.
Well, I think.
Now that I'm saying.
But I feel like, yeah, there's a TV special
about the Millennium Celebration
and pin trading for sure was introduced.
Yeah, it was the beginning of pin trading.
The beginning of fast pass,
the horrible journey into your imagination
was part of this.
But those all seem like maybe they were kind of like
retconned into like, well, these things are going on.
So we'll sort of include them in the main stuff we're doing.
But the new things for the Millennium,
big illumination show.
Illumination 2000.
With the globe rotating in the middle.
The Millennium Village,
a little like addendum area to World Showcase
off by the UK.
The big 2000 on the Epcot.
But which began the several years of ruining icons
at Disney World.
We've discussed for a long time,
was the Castle cake ruining or plusing
and was various opinions on that.
But I don't think anyone really likes the big 2000
on Spaceship Earth.
No.
Oh, I guess we should wait till the time.
But I remember I was there before the Millennium
and I saw it being built.
Oh, okay.
2000 being built.
Did it make you nervous?
It was very big, so it did make me nervous.
I don't have the same big thing fear that you'd,
although yours is specifically in a big thing
in a small space.
Which is why I'm nervous about Rise of the Resistance.
Oh, when the 8080s?
Yes, yeah, yeah.
Oh, right.
I think it's gonna freak me out in a good way.
Like being enclosed.
Full size TIE fighter too.
Oh boy, ooh.
Yeah.
If it's open air, well, I've seen TIE fighters.
They're around, but outside.
Something about being enclosed.
I don't think it's open air TIE fighter, or am I wrong?
No, he's saying he's seen them outside.
Oh, I see.
This is in a hangar.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If they're enclosed, it's scarier.
I didn't mean nervous so much, like it's big.
So were you nervous that it was going to be
aesthetically poor edition?
I think at the time I thought, oh, that's cool.
But then I don't even think I liked it
when I finally saw what it looked like.
So I just have a memory of going,
oh, there's a giant thing in the parking lot next to it.
Sure, sure. It was being constructed.
At 13 or 14, it had been enough years of going regularly
that I was like, there's always gonna be new stuff.
And I don't think I was often going,
ah, that wasn't as good.
Or maybe going with Journey, I was like,
why did they change that?
That wasn't as good as the old one.
But I feel like I gave them the benefit of the doubt
of if one thing didn't hit,
there's gonna be another new thing that quickly.
But this was an era where a lot of the new things
weren't hitting.
Yeah, I know.
I don't know, I don't wanna detain everything.
I found this era to be sort of odd and unpleasant
in general.
I don't have a lot of fondness
for the Millennium Celebration.
And that kind of, among which, as I continue to list things,
the Tapestry of Nations Parade
that happened around World Showcase
with these big puppet things.
Yeah, I mean, I don't have much affection
for this time either.
What, the Rock and Roller Coaster
and the Tower of Terror,
maybe the last things that happened at Disney World
where I have a lot of nostalgia for.
Either this whole stuff, all of these things,
it's either like, I don't care,
or, oh, this is bad, this looks bad.
Specifically bad, yeah.
I mean, I think even when it wasn't something
I was wild about, it was still like,
well, I'm still at Disney World,
and we're still having a nice family vacation,
so I can't complete too much.
I wasn't saying that I was like,
Disney World sucks now or anything.
I don't know how critical I was at 14.
I couldn't also, I wasn't some articulate,
I couldn't be like, you know,
I can pinpoint exactly what's wrong with the ride now.
Oh, for sure.
I'm just saying that in hindsight,
it's all hindsight is what I'm saying.
Ahana, okay, the hand on Spaceship Earth
seems like a misfire,
but they could have very easily made that
a little more aesthetically on game for Epcot.
Like, if it was that Epcot font,
if it was 2000 and kind of a futurey font,
kind of makes sense, makes a little more sense.
But why was it this swirly?
Why was it the Sorcerer Mickey hand?
Yeah, so in case you don't know what we're talking about,
yeah, the Sorcerer Mickey hand was popping out of,
essentially, the ground, I guess,
and like enchanting Spaceship Earth.
With a wand.
Did he have a wand?
There's a wand, here, I'm looking at a picture now.
Wait, are you asking, did-
Did Sorcerer Mickey often?
I don't believe so. I think of the hat.
Like, and of course, the hat went in over at,
then, MGM Studios.
Yeah, I don't, in Sorcerer's Apprentice,
well, does he have a wand, like, in Phantasmic?
Well, he's a conductor in Phantasmic, so he has a-
He has a baton. A baton, yeah.
Maybe, and he does in Sorcerer's Apprentice.
Maybe it's not a magic wand, it's a magic baton.
Oh, interesting. That stars and
sparkles are coming out of.
That's interesting.
So he can conduct an orchestra with that.
Go ahead and Google, if you're listening to this,
and you've never seen it, Epcot 2000,
and that'll show you what we're talking about.
And also, I think my big problem with a lot of this,
some of this stuff, I mean, I saw, I was there.
I was there in, like, spring of 2000,
and I saw all of this stuff.
Yeah.
And so, I have an affection for the Millennium Village,
positive memories of the Millennium Village.
I have a lot to say about it with 20 years of perspective,
and some of the countries represented are a little wild.
But I remember being very excited for the Millennium,
and doing the research for this,
I kind of got the vibe of doing the research
for the Bicentennial.
Like, it was a big thing that everyone knew about,
everyone was all in on,
except the Millennium celebration had the edge
that the world could end with Y2K.
As a nervous child, I was concerned about Y2K.
Well, that's a good question.
Do you guys remember your Y2K night?
100%, yes.
My mom didn't want me going out,
because she thought the world might end, yes.
Uh, that's, oh, well, my mom didn't want me going out either.
That's why I didn't do anything that night,
not because I had no friends,
and nobody invited me to anything.
It was that my mom said no.
Sure.
Let me be clear about that.
Uh, I remember filling some extra pitchers of water,
and putting them in the fridge, just in case.
Wait, you put like two extra pitchers of water?
Two extra pitchers, like in case shit went down.
And you did it?
I did it.
And then, right when the ball dropped,
we were watching at the living room,
and it went five, four, three, two, one,
and my dad was standing at the back,
and like turned the lights off, and I was like,
oh, this is it.
And he was just like a lamb, and he got me.
He did get me.
That's a good joke.
Also, at the time, my dad worked in, did computer stuff.
My dad worked in software.
He was like, no, we figured it.
It's fine.
Everyone's figured it out.
It's gonna be fine.
That is, like, I hate to use fake news,
but they, like the media really ginned up.
Really?
Yeah.
The idea that that was very possible.
And it wasn't.
And everyone really on edge,
and maybe that's an early,
yet like the sensationalism of extinction.
I mean, every big company had to double check
their software and make sure all the T's were crossed
and I's dotted.
But the idea was that the computers,
the computers would all shut, think it's 1901,
and they would go back,
and it would just destroy every computer, right?
That's basically what they were trying to scare us about.
What was gonna happen?
Like, everyone's bank account was just gonna like,
go to figure out, or?
Right, because it would like think it.
Neck defense.
Yeah, it would erase everything,
because it would like start at the beginning.
Just stuff would crash.
That sounds like, in saying that now,
it sounds like somebody who doesn't have any idea
how computers work.
Yeah.
Like being like, well, what's gonna happen?
We didn't, like, when they made Windows 95,
when they were making operating systems,
there's no way that they were like,
well, let's only plan for five years from now.
It wasn't like these were made 500 years ago.
Somebody maybe is gonna correct me,
because I sound like an idiot,
and I often do on this show, I'm sure,
but I'm saying like, in hindsight,
the idea that like, oh, most of these computers
didn't prepare for after 1999 doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, it was not that-
It was like 20 years away.
Like, if a computer, like, mainstream, like,
home personal computers were like, what, 80s?
Yeah, and I mean, if you think about it,
when Windows 95, you click on the clock in the corner,
it brings up a tiny calendar,
and you can just keep going years ahead of time.
You can go 20, 30, 100 years ahead of time.
Everyone's worried the whole world
is gonna be like, Minesweeper.
It's gonna be bombs around any corner.
So yeah, I don't know what I'm talking about,
but I remember just not like being like, oh yeah,
but they didn't prepare for the year 2000
on all these computers.
And then there was the fear that was proven correct,
which was not Y2K, but Will2K.
Well.
That we would be, that we would end up
in not a millennium, but a Will-
Millennium. Yeah.
And that honestly, that was, surpassed my expectations.
Yeah, it has come true,
what with Will Smith's frequent YouTube presence.
I just watched him go to the robot restaurant in Japan.
Oh, really? Yeah.
Which is like a, it's a long video that shows you nothing.
And he's like, the idea of going
to the robot restaurant is so bizarre to him.
And he keeps like throwing other people under the bus.
Like, man, that was Steve's idea.
Steve was pushing this one.
What'd you get me into this time, Steve?
Going to a popular dinner show.
I don't, like, why is this so weird to you, Will?
I'm, well, I didn't know he was even doing that.
I know that Jada, his wife, has like a talk show on Facebook
with her mother and the kids.
What? And they talk, yeah, yeah.
They talk about like-
That's an official like Facebook,
like that's a show Facebook paid for, correct?
I believe so, yes.
But they like, it's like intense.
Oh. Check it out.
They have to go to Luntown.
Sex talk and like the relationship.
Well, there's a lot to develop into
when your marriage is false.
Well. Scientology arrangement.
Yeah, that does make it a little bit harder.
I don't think they ever spell that out specifically.
But there's pretty like, yeah, it's, anyway.
We don't have to do much more on that one.
I don't have to go deep into Will 2K.
Yeah.
Did I already say, one of my issues
with some of this Millennium stuff is, you know,
it started October 1st, 1999, sort of a nod to Disneyland,
or Disney World opens October 1st.
Yeah, everything opens October 1st.
Everything opens October 1st.
Also traditionally a lower crowd season at the time.
So that way stuff breaks the first month or so.
That's fine.
And it ran to January 2001.
But a lot of this stuff,
they did not exactly wrap up in a timely manner.
The hand stuck around on Spaceship Earth
and they changed the 2000 to say Epcot after a while.
In the worst font that's ever existed.
In Epcot Center, a home of beautiful fonts.
Yes.
How many years was that?
2007 and finally.
What?
Is that long?
Yeah.
It looks like, shit, it ruins the symmetry.
Epcot I think is all about symmetry.
Because you keep walking past,
either way you go left or right,
then it's an even amount of Future World pavilion.
Maybe not that, that might not be true.
But it's, you know, here's Spaceship Earth
and it's a circle, then Future World's a circle,
then World Showcase is a circle.
It's this nice layered circular thing.
And then like, why is this big thing over on the left
that can't be seen from some angles?
Like Epcot, like Spaceship Earth looks good
no matter where you're looking at it.
It like mucked it up.
Now a lot of views don't work.
Why not something symmetrical?
Why not, I'm trying to think of a good,
okay there was a Sorcerer hat in front of the MGM studio
in front of the Chinese theater.
There was, what was it, was it in Magic Kingdom?
Well, there wasn't, there was-
They really didn't have-
15 years before they had the cake.
Yeah, but they didn't do something for that?
Not really.
For Millennium.
Throughout the 2000s, they kinda added like little touches
or they would spruce up the castle or something.
So it was just Sorcerer's Apprentice themed.
That was the idea?
Two of the icons became Sorcerer's Apprentice themed
for two, for a watt, for most of the 2000s.
Forever, for MGM studios.
Well, and they kind of reconfigured to the icon
for that park being the Earful Tower, the water tower.
Right, but they moved it.
Isn't that gone now?
Is the Earful Tower gone?
I'm not 100% sure if the Earful Tower is gone.
I don't recall seeing it, but it might still be there.
I think because it was,
I think that was on the back lot area
that is probably now Galaxy's Edge.
Right.
Honestly, why didn't they just put a hat on it at least,
put on Spatial Birth?
Or at least both hands, the 2000 on the top
and hands on either side.
Or Mickey making like Jay-Z's or Diamond Dallas Page's
diamond cutter. Making the Illuminati.
The Illuminati sign over Spatial Birth.
Just as a reminder of who will ultimately be in charge
for this millennium.
Don't worry, the Illuminati snuck into the Millennium Village.
There's some spots.
If someone could Photoshop either Diamond Dallas Page
or Jay-Z making that sign over Spatial Birth,
I'd appreciate it.
Sure. Yeah.
That sounds better.
While we're in Spatial Birth territory,
Leave a Legacy.
Yeah. Oh yeah. Let's enter.
Let's enter.
And then when we get past all this,
we can decide which way to go.
But yes, you would have to enter through Leave a Legacy,
which are these big stone tablets, these big pillars
that you, where you could make an etching
that was a drawing of you or your family.
And those were etched into the stone.
Actually, I saw them referred to as megaliths.
Oh, interesting.
The term they were throwing around.
Because a monolith is just a big slate stone slab,
essentially. Like what's in 2001
of Space Odyssey. Right.
So these are mega, these are bigger.
Megaliths. And they are giant.
But they're not bigger than the stones in 2001.
No. No.
They are large. But there's more of them.
So they can't say monoliths.
Oh, right, because monoliths.
Because multiple monoliths is impossible
because it's mono. There's 32 of these.
So they could. Is it that many?
It is that many.
They could be multiliths, but megaliths sounds cooler.
Multiliths is probably more correct.
You're right. Yeah.
But megaliths is dumber.
Right, but funner.
Yeah, yeah.
These were, I think these like fit the old aesthetic.
These didn't seem like they like super stuck out
and didn't belong.
Well, they yanked the fountain for it.
Now, see, I don't remember a lot of this that well.
So there was like the fountain was like,
I didn't go a lot when there was the original fountain.
So that was like the glass.
The glass, which is coming back.
They're nodding to that.
Like they're sort of reinstalling it.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't know.
Looking back, I'm shocked my family
did not put ourselves on this
because we could have done all four of us
for under $120.
Wow, really?
It was like $35 a tile, I think.
And you could get. That's a great deal.
I mean, we would do that now if they could.
We would 100% do that now.
I don't think I would do that.
Why do I need my face on a tile?
The three of us.
I guess the three of us.
Yeah, it's kind of a fun little Easter egg.
Yeah.
Yeah, for content we would do it.
I think it was two per tile.
So you do like the parents and then the kids.
There's some famous people scattered there.
Like all of NSYNC is somewhere in here.
Yes. NSYNC, also if you knew where to look,
you could see all of NSYNC lined up in very like 99 era,
like a stylishly dopey era for NSYNC.
These were designed by John Hench.
Yes. That's interesting.
Who designed Spaceship Earth to begin with,
or is one of the people who did.
And so that maybe factors into like why it matches
and is okay.
It matches.
It does feel, I went to DC a lot growing up,
and it does feel like a little bit like a war memorial
for like, were we in the Falklands?
This is a memorial for like these six people who died
in like a car crash in the Falklands.
Do you think anyone walked into Epcot Center
and was mistaken about what this was for
and like solemnly prayed for all of the victims?
Yes.
Like these are all the faces of the dead.
Yes, of course.
I don't think that's a joke.
I think that happened.
Yeah.
Like some kid was like, hey, cool it, stop playing.
Moment of silence.
Yes, I think for sure.
That's what it looks like.
It does look a little solemn,
even though all the faces on it, everyone's smiling.
Yeah, but it seems like.
I mean, it's true that everyone in all of the etchings
will be dead within the millennium.
Yes, that's true.
So we should stop and pray for the future dead.
Unless something happens technologically or scientifically
medically.
Yes, and the new millennium is full of hope and opportunity.
So it very well could.
Stem cells keep us alive until we're in our 200s.
That'd be great.
We'd have to go way past the millennium though.
We'd have to, nobody's gonna make it a thing.
I guess you're right.
Unless the technology you're describing
is really, really good.
Really good technology, really fast.
I guess it would have to be like robots
and then you put your brain in the robot.
Yeah, our consciousness.
And then you could keep the, yeah,
you would just inject stem cells into the brain
to keep it alive and we'd all have robot bodies.
Or one more option.
We get cloned.
So when you're around 40 or something,
you clone and you keep a brainless clone of yourself
growing somewhere.
And then when the clone is about 18 or 20,
you take the actual brain from your old head,
inject it with stem cells to keep it young
and put it in this new body.
Are you describing the movie, The Island?
Yeah, I think so.
I think you were describing it.
There's a couple movies.
Ewan McGregor, Scarlett Johansson.
I think I'm describing probably a couple movies.
It's such a clean sci-fi premise you're describing
that I'm like, it feels like it has to be something.
I think it's a couple- That's a really strong idea.
Yeah, I don't think I invented it.
I think it's in probably a couple of things,
but it might be The Island.
How creepy, a lifeless body.
Oh yeah.
But they're doing where they genetically engineer animals
to eat, but it's only like,
it's like a headless chicken or something.
For sure.
Yeah, right.
So you're growing a weird caged version of yourself
and then you plan, and then maybe you can do that again
and again and just hop and hop and hop.
Yeah, forever.
Yeah.
I saw this movie called Get Out.
That implies a technology that we could all,
let's take the racial as a positive.
Yeah, I was gonna say-
If you could do it in a nice way,
that's an option for hopping from,
if you don't have to put anyone in a sunken place.
Yeah.
That was one of the things I thought about
because this is,
I don't think, there's a lot of stuff the millennium,
we could not have predicted.
One, how many countries are run by fascists?
Like how many?
Okay, America, Brazil.
Oh yeah, check it out.
Okay, it's-
How many have World Showcase?
At least America.
Well, Israel will get to,
the Prime Minister currently being charged with corruption.
Okay.
Yeah, but a lot of this stuff where,
we're all part of the human race.
Who could have possibly foreseen with accelerationism
that that devolved into all lives matter?
Who could have predicted that at the millennium?
That quickly.
Boy, how unfamiliar- Very quickly.
When you go back and watch this 2000 stuff,
how unfamiliar is it to you here in 2020?
Very hopeful, yeah.
Like boy, things took a turn real fast.
Well, cause some shit went down pretty soon
after the millennium turned.
Even at the millennium, I mean, 1999,
right after all this stuff started,
the battle for Seattle protests were happening
like a month later.
Yeah, rage against the machine.
Rage against the machine.
The rise of rage against the machine.
And I blame all of this on them.
Sure.
I think-
We need the machine.
I think rage against the machine will be playing
at Eat to the Beat at Epcot in a few years.
You know them four, bulls on parade.
Soon, rage against the machine will rock the lagoon.
Da-na-na-na-na-na.
Fuck you, I won't do what you tell me.
Mom's dance.
Yeah.
You'll be out on stage like breaking chairs.
All right, we'll be back at 7.45.
We did three songs.
Here are some other things
that we're probably not predicting at the millennium.
For Leave a Legacy, part of your purchase,
you got a website where you would see
your Leave a Legacy picture,
and you could add, if your family grew,
you could add more family members to your website.
That was of course built on the great website, go.com.
And Digital Leave a Legacy, no longer with us.
Oh my God.
We can't get to that?
It does not exist anymore, apparently.
The other thing is, so all of these,
the Megaliths are going away.
The metal sheets with the pictures
are being moved outside of the park
as part of the Epcot redo.
Apparently the contract people signed
said they would be around until 2027.
So who knows how long they will be
in that little area outside the park?
I have a guess, 2027.
2027.
And not a day past.
There will be a big dump truck full of Megaliths.
Unless they just are too lazy to take them out.
I guess it depends on the financial state
of the company at the time.
Yeah.
Like if they have, or they're flush with cash at that point.
We're gonna, the thing that they aren't accounting for
is that Disney Plus is doing well now.
Yeah.
But with the impending rise of Quibi,
Disney Plus could be crushed into the ground
by the end of this year, 2020.
When Quibi absorbs Disney.
Yeah.
Oh God, so then it's gonna be in the ultimate
Katzenberg left and now he's back
and now it's his hand lighting up Spaceship Earth.
And all the Mickey walk-around characters
have Katzenberg's head on it.
No, it's not Mickey anymore, it's Kassa.
It's Katzenberg.
He usurped, he really is get outing the Disney company.
Yes.
He's kicking Mickey's soul out of his own body.
I guess all the walk-around characters
have a big plastic Katzenberg head on.
So it's like Minnie in her dress,
but it's Katzenberg's head, goofy with the vests.
Well no, Katzenberg and Meg Whitman.
Oh yeah, you're right.
Oh yeah, yeah.
There's a boy and a girl.
Mickey and Minnie is Meg Whitman.
Yeah, you'll go to see those Duffy shows in Japan.
She's only, you know, and she deserves all the success.
If you fail to be elected governor of California,
tank a couple printer companies.
Keep going, keep going, go bigger, get promoted.
Are you really forgetting her observation
that young people watch content on their phones?
Like all of that is in the past
because she has made the most original declaration
that has ever been made.
So give her some credit and let her,
and let's put her on all the plushes in the parks.
I mean, the Q&A with the two of them
where the reporter is like,
I asked a millennial about this and they said,
Quibi look like a fam.
How do you respond to that?
They're like, what?
Like they're so caught off guard by there.
Like young person said, this is a stupid idea
and won't work.
How do you respond?
Well, that's just one.
Like, did I tell you guys about the,
there was a big article where Meg Whitman was explaining
like what young people,
like working with so many young people
has taught me all these terms I didn't know,
such as fam parentheses work friends.
Did the young people you work with tell you that?
Is anyone defined fam that way?
That fam, work friends?
Friends.
Huh.
They're like family.
You didn't choose them.
Fam means work friends.
Hey, well, you guys are weird.
This is work.
You guys, that means you guys are fam.
What up fam?
But not the audience.
They're not fam.
No.
They're listeners.
Sorry.
They're on the other end of the exchange.
They're not work friends like you guys are.
But fam, we would like, non fam, other word,
we would like you to click here, here, and here,
and to subscribe.
Mash that button.
How hellish is that?
If you guys got that about YouTube,
but now they have to, at the end of every video,
say subscribe and mash the button.
Like YouTube changed it.
So now all these YouTubers have to say, do two things.
Yeah.
Is it smash the button or what are they?
There's a phrase they still say smash that like button.
You'd have to ask Meg Whitman.
I only share it now.
Cause I don't know.
She's up on the phrases.
I do only, I mostly associate fam with, hey, what up fam?
Or on Twitter, people misusing it purposely to go like,
shoes look like a fam.
Which the joke being good.
Like, yeah.
It's purposely kind of wrong, purposely kind of off.
Like not, like you looked at a glossary of young people.
Yeah.
Anyways, yeah.
2027, in sinks going in the garbage.
It's the end of bye bye bye.
But yeah, if it's too expensive,
that's why the hand stuck around for so long.
Cause it's like, this is going to be so expensive
to disassemble.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I think very possible.
And like river country just sat there decaying for years.
I think they got rid, they finally took it out,
but it was there for years.
They honestly just sat there empty
until the snow-capped preview center.
So who knows how long they'll be there.
So we've entered the park.
We've passed the megaliths and perhaps
put ourselves on for future generations to see on go.com.
We've admired the amazing magic wand.
Yes.
Which way do we go now?
I guess, well, it's, hmm.
That's, it's hard to say.
I forget what times the parades were happening.
Well, and it's in three legs and it's,
it seems, it seemed like it was always happening
from what I remember.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, this is what I, one of my big memory of thinking like,
well, what is the aesthetic of the millennium?
And it's these large puppets and the score,
which it is a score.
It's not one song,
cause it's like a 20 to 30 minute long thing.
And the composer actively said like,
you know, the lyrics, there aren't really lyrics
because it's not a language, but it sounds like a language.
It's the impression of a language.
Oh.
And so I don't know if that,
it reminds me of the shaman of song.
Yes.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What we were doing in the live that very like,
Ha-ne-he, oh-he-oh-ha, ha-ne-ho.
Like, I do not like this kind of thing whatsoever.
If you take away from me that it's a real language
and I have to be differential to it and like,
okay, that's cultural.
Like if it's made up, get out of here.
I don't, I do not want to hear any hey-yah-ho.
If it was like an Ewok language though,
if it was a cuter sound like yub nub or whatever,
like a cuter language, would you like it better?
Or if the characters you had some affection for?
I don't know.
I do, well, I do like Lapti Neck,
the song from Return of the Jedi very much.
But that's, I don't know.
I think made up language chants are hard for me.
I think chants in general,
because I really hate, you know,
Imagine Dragon, 32nd to Mars kind of like,
hey, hey.
Oh, heaven don't have a name.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, oh.
Yes, well, who would have guessed that all of the 2000,
the entire millennium will be that kind of music.
It's never going away.
Never going away.
We're doing 20 years deep and it's all chance.
Really the Tapestry of Nations parade
set the stage for Journey Renner.
And Imagine Dragons.
All of them were there as boys.
That's probably why.
Yeah.
Like it's kind of their biggest,
like when their brains were absorbing everything at 14.
And Journey Renner of course is a 50 year old man.
So he was a little older, but at 30 he was there.
I mean, of course the Tapestry of Nations parade,
one of the big things was the marionettes
would touch the ground.
Like you could reach, they would reach out and touch you.
I mean, I like that.
But if you said, I don't like this,
and Birdman heard you, he would say that famous phrase,
I will kill you and myself.
That famous Jeremy Renner catchphrase.
Oh, oh, oh.
Uh.
I didn't know where you were going with that for a second.
I know, it was a long journey, but I think it was worth it.
You said Birdman, I was like,
are we talking about Birdman?
I was confused, yeah, for a second.
I was confused reading about this.
Okay, maybe we need to explain this
from the ground up.
Yeah, let's go through it.
If you've never seen it,
the Tapestry of Nations was the parade,
and it was kind of this like street show.
It was somewhere between a parade
and a little street celebration
that I specifically remember seeing around Mexico,
Norway zone of World Showcase,
but I think it was in other spots.
But that's where I associated with.
But it was these huge tall marionette puppets
that walked around that were extremely post-Taymor.
This was very post-Lion King Taymor,
and in fact, I think it was a mask maker.
It was Michael Curry, the designer for the Lion King.
How would you describe it?
Like tassel-y?
Like, I don't know.
I mean, I know that it's all like,
it's very disconnected.
It's all like parts kind of abstractly forming a human shape.
That sort of model, like human shape thing you can buy
to learn to sketch.
Like you can pose.
You know what I'm talking about?
That sort of like one foot tall,
a little wooden model that you would use
to draw the human figure.
Yeah.
It's kind of like that,
is that early Mr. Show sketch
about like a little dancing marionette doll?
Oh, Mr. Limb Legs.
Mr. Limb Legs ain't got no clothes on.
It's funny you said that because I wrote down Pitpat.
Oh, yeah.
The spokes thing.
They are all spokes that they're all in.
A pansexual.
Pansexual spokes thing.
That's extremely accurate.
Yeah, yeah.
But which, that sketch, yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm old Swirlo.
It's all, yeah, it's like weird.
It's like handcrafted art, but on this mega scale.
Lecivious.
Those are great.
Tanker Bell's having sex with him at the end.
I guess I was only saying Tassel
because there's that one,
and that one they made the Parkstar out of
has like hair that is kind of like hanging.
He looks like, he or she looks like
the Muppets newer friend from Muppets Tonight.
That's Discman.
Oh, yes, Discman.
Thank you, thank you, Discman.
These are nightmare inducing.
I hated these.
I hated them.
I hated this thing a lot.
I like them if they were like the villains in a movie.
Yeah. Like they're cool.
They're all like Slender Man.
Yes.
They're like the creature from Signs.
Sage of Time.
I like Sage of Time.
I can't believe. A little more specific.
I had no idea these all had names.
We probably all stumbled into this
and you're excited about this, Jason.
Or exhausted by it might be the word.
Wait, show me again which one.
I just want to make sure we're on the same page.
The Sage of Time was like the grand marshal of the parade.
Is this the Sage of, hold on.
Oh yeah, this is, yes, this is the Sage of Time.
I like these in a return to Oz kind of way.
Yeah.
Where I'm disturbed.
I don't like, I'm scared of return to Oz still.
Right.
Have you watched it on Disney Plus?
No.
We should do that.
Okay, sure.
Is that on Disney Plus?
Yeah, yeah.
I've never seen it all the way.
Well, nothing scared me.
Very few things scared me harder as a child
than return to Oz.
I remember watching it.
Dark Crystal maybe, it's in that.
Yeah.
But I remember just, anyway, the woman,
I forget the character's name.
She takes her head off.
She has a whole room of heads and I melted down and ran.
I ran from whatever my grandmas.
My grandmother's, what I think upstairs, TV room.
I remember just running away.
But I did, there was a morbid curiosity to it.
We watched it.
The 80s.
Body part in the 80s.
Yeah, we watched it a couple years ago.
And it's not like a great movie, but I like it.
It's cool and weird and.
Is it fair to say like,
if it was a friendly, cute puppet
that we saw when we were under five,
then we still love it to this day
and want every piece of memorabilia about it.
And if it was a slightly scary puppet,
then we still have nightmares about it.
And it's the subject of our therapy
and we'll never get over the fear of them.
Yeah, that lines up.
That's probably pretty clear.
Ninja Turtles, we love forever.
Jim Edmonds.
Sure, Spectro Man?
Yeah.
No.
No, don't even talk about him.
Dolphay Spectro Man.
Hideous.
This was, so all these puppets, again,
this is the whole thing at the Millennium,
was again, the human race.
It's kind of a melting pot.
They literally said like,
it's a melting pot of all cultures.
So it's everything and nothing.
Like they're abstract, quote.
They can be anything you want them to be.
But that can also be meaningless.
Like.
Scott's going home with the sage of time tonight.
I think I am.
He can be whatever I want.
He can be anything.
No way, man, I'm going with Wiggle Girl.
Yeah, fellas, you're either a Wiggle Girl guy
or an Angel Girl guy.
Every type of man is,
you could break them down by,
do you answer, are you the sprite?
Fellas, are you a Discman or are you a Hammer Man,
also referred to as Hammered Copper Man?
I gotta say, you know, hey, Wiggle Girl's hot and all,
but I look, I love me a three tiered tail.
But I'm sprite all the way.
They had love Wiggle Girl.
I mean, I probably the most upsetting is Reverse Marionette,
a large multicolored puppet
with a little Marionette being.
Oh, wait, do I get to look at this?
Reverse Marionette, what's it called?
That's what it's called on Wikipedia.
Reverse Marionette with a little Marionette.
Oh no, no.
I hate these ghosts.
But sure, do you have a picture of it?
Cause I can't.
I don't have a picture.
I still don't know.
I could have made the effort to learn which is which,
but I didn't want to think about these things
for any longer than we had to.
I saw the main ones,
but I don't know where that Marionette,
maybe I missed that.
I feel like that would lead the, in the video,
you can find it in the videos.
There's also, they kind of break the pattern
because one of the people is called Aztec Man.
That is incredibly specific.
That can't be whatever you want it to be.
It's an Aztec Man.
Yeah, it's an Aztec.
And also like, oh no, there was a DC,
there was a DC comics character named Aztec.
That's just called Aztec.
The ultimate something man?
Am I wrong?
Aztec?
Aztec the something man?
He was preparing to fight Quetzalcoatl,
the ender of worlds, the Aztec ender of worlds.
Aztec the ultimate man.
The ultimate man, yeah.
Created by Grant Morrison, anyway.
These are, I can't,
I couldn't believe these things all had names.
The most, I am obsessed enough with Disney World trips
that I do a podcast where I talk about it
multiple times a week.
All I've ever thought about these puppets was like,
hey, I remember that awful thing for a couple of years.
I can't believe that they all had names or backstories
and the people have cataloged this.
I'm upset by that there was,
I mean, I guess it's good they thought about this.
I mean, at the very least,
you need a name for props and wardrobe on the checklist.
Like just for stage managers to have a name.
So like, I don't know that the public was necessarily,
I mean, maybe on the maps or stuff,
they would mention some of them.
There's someone listening.
There's one listener who is stewing
that we hate these puppets.
Well, and these puppets were everywhere.
There was so much promotion with these puppets.
They were in the 2000 Super Bowl halftime show.
The Super Bowl halftime show,
which we have discussed before
because it also included Phil Collins
and had a little bit of Tarzan Rocks vibe.
And he performs two worlds and he's in dockers,
the two primary components of Tarzan Rocks.
So yeah, this Millennium Celebration vibe
probably had its biggest grandest stage
with the Super Bowl halftime show in which,
and I didn't put any of this together
until researching this episode.
That halftime show was narrated by Edward James Olmos
by just a creepy closeup of Edward James Olmos
in an ambiguous space.
And he says all of these weird word soups,
let us reach out and touch the stars
as we light the way to tomorrow
and bring us hope for a better world.
All this nothing, this meaningless jargon.
I didn't realize until now that everything that he says
was also the narration of the Tapestry Nations Parade.
He says all of the same copy
that a disembodied voice says.
Yes.
Including, he says in his copy,
there's something about like, okay,
a thousand years have passed
and the Sage of Time is once again upon us,
which I just heard and everyone heard
watching the Super Bowl and was like,
what the fuck, what are you talking about?
No idea that the Sage of Time is a character.
I don't think Edward James almost knew
what the hell he was talking about.
Just like, here's the copy, great go.
They never communicated the Sage of Time
is a character, a man.
He also says this really,
and the main parade says this really crazy thing about,
as it does every thousand years,
the gateway of time has opened.
Let us begin, or no, behold the great millennium walk.
And then the puppets all kind of shake around
and that's what that means.
They kind of just like, you know, jingle.
The gateway of time is open?
What do you mean, how so?
You explain.
You are about to enter a realm beyond pleasure and pain.
Gateway of time, it has?
And in this context of the Super Bowl halftime show,
the gateway of time opening up
meant that some puppets shook around
and then Phil Collins went up on a crane
and then back down on a crane.
If the Guardians of the Galaxy Cosmic Rewind
has the Sage of Time in any of that narration,
it'll be the greatest ride of all time.
Oh, you know what I flashed too when you said that,
that they're like dementors in the Harry Potter ride.
If suddenly the Sage of Time swooped down in front of you
by surprise, get me out of here.
I would scream and scream until they stopped the ride,
get me off.
But you'd have to appreciate that.
I could see one of these in the queue.
Because these are around, these are in stores.
I want them to be the villains on the ride,
as Scott is describing.
Only if I can shoot them in the head.
Oh, I don't know if there's a gun in it.
And they bleed blood.
You know all that Guardians of the Galaxy blood scenes?
And they give you, yeah, they give you just a handgun
on the ride.
Just a Glock.
Again, the speeding up of reality,
like just imagining the Adam Curtis hyper normalization
voiceover going, like showing the 2000s
Super Bowl halftime show.
And then something happened.
And it's Justin Timberlake ripping off
Janet Jackson's costume.
And then it jumps to like Lenny Kravitz's hog.
And like, plop, plop.
Like, plop it out.
It could have never predicted what was coming for them.
They couldn't picture,
they couldn't have predicted the nudity.
The nudity, the sheer nudity and the sort of like
the devolving from like educational,
like slash marketing halftime shows.
If only the Lenny Kravitz penis popping out of the pants
had happened not just in some random show.
So we just have cell phone video of it.
But if it had been part of a halftime show
and the shot with like NFL Phantom cameras,
like super slow mo that you could hire,
you could zoom all the way, it'd be fascinating.
It'd be like watching a nature documentary.
It's like, it's frame by frame,
the two minute version of the unveiling of Kravitz's hog.
Kids would study it in school.
I think I'm conflating two things.
Cause his penis did fall out at a show, right?
But then when he did the Super Bowl halftime show,
he was wearing obscenely tight pants, I think.
So you're just talking about his tight pants?
I was just talking about like his like,
Oh, you weren't even talking about the dick coming out.
I was covered a little by high def work at cameras.
Well, what about Prince's giant penis?
Prince's was a little more mischievous.
Yeah, it was his guitar.
Oh yeah, that's right.
With his silhouette, he used the guitar to insert it.
The big, it was raining, the big like,
whatever you'd call it, sheet shot up.
And then as we're using a shadow effect,
he made his pointed guitar look like his giant penis.
That's right.
This is a, well, the 2001 was,
it didn't have any of this filth.
Right. Yeah.
The puppets, the Sage of Time does not have genitals.
They did not, the Timur puppets did not come with that part.
So again, something happened
where the Millennium Celebration ends.
This parade is reconfigured to the Tapestry of Dreams.
The Sage of Time is-
Very important, we changed it from nations to dreams.
And you, but you can have the Sage of Time.
The Sage of Time splits.
He's fucking out of there.
He's replaced by the Dream Seekers,
Discovery, Magic, and the Unknown.
Jason, what are their names?
All I know is they represent
Discovery, Magic, and the Unknown.
Do you have the names?
I have names here.
Of the Dream Seekers, our favorite characters?
Leonardo Columbus, who represents
Discovery, Invention, and Genius.
This sucks.
Elfin, who represents nature, magic, and emotions.
And Cosmo, who represented space and the unknown.
Leonardo Columbus is my favorite, obviously.
Wait a minute.
Two of them have one name,
and then one of them is Leonardo Columbus.
Yeah, I know.
The other two are not as exciting.
I should have ended with Leonardo Columbus.
I recently declared,
I don't know if I said it specifically,
but I regarded a discovery we found
in the Schomburg episode,
DVC, a character made to promote
Disney Vacation Club purchasing.
That in my head was the new worst Disney character.
Like a physical location character.
I think now I have to declare it's Leonardo Columbus.
I believe this is a pic.
Have you seen Leonardo Columbus?
No.
I think I'm gonna unplug my computer here.
Hold on, let me get this.
Do you wanna just text it to us?
Cause you can record your text.
I'm gonna text, I don't wanna.
Text.
David, Leonardo.
We named the Ninja Turtles after great artists,
and one of them was Leonardo,
and they're like, do you think that bumps at all?
No, no, this Leonardo is gonna stand on its own.
And also, wasn't Columbus already,
you were starting to be like,
yeah, this Columbus might not have been a great guy.
Yeah, they're gonna change his name
to Leonardo Indigenous.
What's happening in this millennium?
All right, I've texted you a picture
of Leonardo Columbus, I think.
Open your phone.
I bet he's cool.
I've texted you a photo.
Oh man.
I looked up Leonardo Columbus,
it says Leonardo Columbus, tapestry of nations, Epcot.
He's not that well documented.
My man looks like shit.
He's like, he's Michael Sheen's fake Bowie in Tron Legacy.
He's kinda like that.
Oh, but mixed a little with, he looks like fucking Khan.
He starts like Khan.
Yes, he does look like Khan, yes.
Columbus.
Here is a pin.
There was an Epcot pin with Leonardo Columbus on it.
I like that you sent us a Flickr from the username Miko.
Flickr.
Oh!
Yeah.
Sucks, worst font, worst character.
He also, Leonardo Columbus looks like baby Billy,
like running through the house with a pickle in his mouth.
And also.
Simpsons baby Billy, you're right.
He looks like Dr. Zayas.
He's dressed like Dr. Zayas with the big gray vest.
He's like a Planet of the Apes character.
He's all of these things and more.
Leonardo Columbus.
Maybe I'm coming around already.
Maybe we need a full.
Obviously we need to do a separate episode
about Leonardo Columbus.
This is so, again, a hodgepodge of specific,
but not specific, not very, very non-offensive,
but what they end up with is pit pat.
Yeah, when you have some crazy Imagineer who sees,
for example, who sees Magnum P.I. and then thinks,
oh my God, and then he makes up a dragon character
and it's all for, it's a crazy idea from one guy.
And that's neat and cool.
Then 40 people all come together and have 20 meetings
and they land on Leonardo Columbus.
All right, I have one more photo to send you
of Leonardo Columbus.
In this photo.
He's real and he's my friend.
He looks like Tanelier Tavon, the collector.
And honestly, he looks so much like him.
I almost think maybe that the Marvel people copied
when they were, hold on, here he comes.
Sorry, I was just gonna drag him.
Here we go.
Here comes one more photo.
Coming through the gateway of time.
Leonardo Columbus.
No, dreams, dreams.
The gateway is closed at this point.
A different gateway.
Oh, here he is, sending you now, Leonardo Columbus.
Re-routing you to a new gateway.
Do you see him?
Not yet, the gateway hasn't quite opened.
Now, in this one, he looks like that me,
like when you see your boys and you're about to get wild.
He's a bro-ier Leonardo Columbus in this picture.
So sad, mine hasn't come.
There we go.
He also looks kind of like, he looks like he's almost a lion,
like he's a Zubali zoo.
Oh yes, another great comparison.
He does look like a Zubali zoo.
But in this, but here he looks like he's being portrayed
by like a cousin of Leno.
He's like a, he's a Leno relative.
Like a character from a one season kid show
where the toys immediately show up at the KB outlet.
Not the main KB toys, the KB outlet.
Yeah, yeah, the KB outlet, I hear you.
Straight to the outlet.
I have a picture of his full like rig, not his hog,
his rig, like what he's traveling on.
There, here, that's gone through.
But his hog, I'm sure, is Kravitz status.
Kravitz-esque, for sure.
Yeah.
I mean, the floats are all,
I think that's impressive.
He is so much, if you go back and look at a picture
of that now, after I've shown you Leonardo Columbus
over and over again, you look at the picture
of the Sage of Time and you go, oh my God,
the Sage of Time looks like some perfectly realized
character, so well designed.
I'm dying for Sage of Time.
And then you go back to Leonardo Columbus
and you go, what the hell, it's just somebody
who was rifling through a costume trunk.
Leonardo Columbus is like, the prince is heading out
on the road in 96 and he had agreed to name
all the band members and they were like,
the press release is going out right now.
You're just like, Leonardo Columbus, okay, I gotta go.
It's crazy this is coming a year after Animal Kingdom 2,
like a stunning, visually rich, detail rich park.
Well, you know, it's interesting.
I'm trying to think, yeah, I know what you're saying,
because in the context of now, it's like,
what is the example of something where like, whoa,
something amazing came and then it's like,
I'm trying to think, like Cars Line opens
and then a couple years later, it's the Summer of Heroes.
And it's like, basically the Summer of Heroes is
like Black Widow rides out on an ATV, not an ATV,
like an armored vehicle to some menacing music.
And that's like, you're supposed to be like,
hell yeah, Marvel Comics.
Yeah, Curved Metal kind of gives way to like,
the Marvel movie shield aesthetic,
which is not the fanciful like,
no, it's militaristic.
More militaristic.
Which is sort of still what's happening.
But I'm saying like, it may be an example of where like,
something like really well realized with,
well, like a ton of money in it.
And then it's like, well, we had less money
and we have to do this in a week
and it's Leonardo Columbus and yeah,
that white wig over there,
just put the white wig on that college student.
And yeah, that's who he looks like.
They stripped a costume, they stripped like a snowman
character they had lying around for Christmas,
took all the white fluff off,
pasted it on a guy's face and sent him out.
There was a thing Disney was doing around this time,
Tapestry of Nations is one of them.
Light Magic is one of them, which we gotta do soon.
And to a lesser extent, I don't just like this one as much,
but Lion King Celebration, which was a parade
that like stopped and there's shows.
It's like, it's not a parade, it's a street abrasion.
Bring back parades, fuck this.
You don't have good, not only like four people
have a good view of the street abrasion, it's boring.
A float is cool to look at as long as it will be gone
in five minutes.
Like if it passes by, then I don't have time to stop
and think like, this isn't that good.
So why all of these things that stop
and it's a party in the street?
I don't wanna party with these puppets in the streets.
Street abrasion contains a lot of the word aberration.
You can't spell aberration
without some of street abrasion.
The other thing you mentioned that the parades,
Epcot actively doesn't have parade,
like not designed for parade.
It's too tight.
I remember this thing just congested everything.
I have marched in a parade at Epcot though.
Wow, marching band?
Yes, I marched on Main Street and in Epcot.
Where'd you go in Epcot?
We didn't go through World Showcase,
but we just sort of marched around Future World.
And I'm trying to remember the exact,
I don't remember the exact route.
Little wider.
A little wider, yeah.
But it was not as scenic as walking down Main Street
at night, which was legit awesome.
I was in the front row.
I was in the front row of the marching band
down Main Street. Nice.
Pretty, that's a hell of an advantage.
Playing Paul Simon's late in the evening.
Playing the triangle.
Ding.
You know, Jason, you mentioned that the carriages
could touch you.
They put their hands on you.
It's a total liability, but it's in all the commercials.
Would they?
It would reach its hand down and you would touch it.
Was it like the Magic Mike Show Lindsay and I saw in Vegas
where it would be like the performers will come up
and touch you, but here's your safe word.
And if you'd say it to the performers,
they won't grind their butts on you.
I mean, I know because I think that show,
part of the appeal is that like.
But I think if you go to the Epcot puppet show,
part of the appeal is you get touched.
For me at least.
But they're not lifting you up.
Like the two puppets aren't lifting you up.
No, Discman isn't grinding on you.
He's grinding on you.
Calling you beautiful.
I'm gonna put a 20 in this age of times, butt crack.
This age of time like,
is just puts you up against a post.
Please let me go.
Please let me go, sir.
They were so pushing that aspect of it that in fact,
the main song that I realize now was not only used
in the show, but also then sung in the halftime show
by Christina Aguilera and Enrique Iglesias.
Hey ah.
Ah na na no no no.
But that was so much, I mean, Ferngully,
like so much of this in the 90s.
What I don't like.
And so many levels removed from any sort of actual
indigenous chants or world music kind of stuff.
But what I was heading for though,
there's a specific song called
Celebrate the Future Hand in Hand.
Oh, okay.
The chorus contains the words,
put your hands on the future.
Ick.
Weird.
Put your hands on it.
It's so close to that.
That's the same thing they said at Magic Mike.
So close to like the excess tech,
like alien encounters, sinister company,
it's just a little different.
A little, yeah, one notch on the dial.
One notch down.
Do we know?
I might not have it timed up well enough, but.
Put your hand on the future.
No, you, no.
How did I get it?
Put your hand on the future, baby.
Put your hand on the,
actually singular is the worst.
Sky Net is the beginning of a new era.
I mean, that's what I think probably.
Like I had seen the Terminator show so many times
at Universal, they show that clip of Judgment Day.
I was like, all right, gotta be ready.
Put your hand on the future.
Put your hand on.
Has anyone ever said that in a sexual lease?
Add to Magic Mike.
And then Pony started playing.
I think I would forgive the creepiness of this
if Pony was the score.
Can you imagine?
And they all, if when they said,
and now the Millennium Walk,
bow, bow, bow, they all shook around the Pony.
Now I'm in.
Is there a Disney Pony that they could make new lyrics
for it to make it not sexual?
Like Mambo number five, in the TV special,
which was just made by a local UPN,
you can find it, a local affiliate
made an hour and a half special about this.
They play a clip of the Lou Baga Mambo number five
where he names all the characters.
He's like, a little bit of Minnie in my.
Oh boy.
I don't know if it's the same special,
but there was a lot of,
I noticed some Fat Boy Slim and some Moby.
We are, that's, if you put your hand on the future,
the future at that time seemed like it was gonna be DJs
and trip hop.
South side, yeah, here we are now.
Yeah, yeah.
Maybe that's a little later, but.
But Moby turned out to be just the future of, you know,
tweeting things that annoy people.
Sleaze bag, yeah.
Well guess what?
Now the great Millennium Walk continues away
from this puppet thing.
As far away as we can go across the lagoon.
I think we should head over to the Millennium Village.
Yes.
The Millennium Village, which was a temporary indoor
like tenet experience that was sort of off
by the International Gateway sort of.
Yeah, sort of in between Canada and Britain.
And this was the thing that I kind of like suggested.
This is what kind of started us talking about doing this
because I was like, oh, we should do the Millennium Village.
Not forgetting about the parade and the hand and everything.
Not forgetting about putting your hand on the future.
That's really what Mickey was doing
in the spaceship Earth Ball.
Oh yeah.
It's putting his hand on the future.
It all ties together.
But so there was this temporary thing
for a couple years that in a lot of much smaller stations
than the World Showcase pavilions,
it was like, you know, a couple dozen different countries
not represented in World Showcase,
all with these little exhibits.
In some cases, it's very small.
It's like a desk and a representative from the country.
And in some cases, it's a much bigger themed experience.
And in one case, a ride.
Yes.
I did not go into this thing.
I never went to this thing.
It also really evoked the names,
it evoked like Olympic Village to me.
Yeah, that seems about what they were going for maybe.
Which the Olympic Village, I think now,
this episode's already a little sexual,
but the Olympic Village now I just think
is Olympians having sex with each other.
That's what apparently.
Which is what you hear about all the international,
like the international students working in Epcot
for the summer, that's whatever that dorm is.
Oh, right, right, right.
It's a crazy party place.
So it very well may have been, maybe it reached its zenith
when the, all the, like, oh boy,
here comes Brazil and Scotland and all the countries
that aren't usually around.
Hey, Leonardo Columbus is around.
Put your hand on the future.
I went to the Millennium Village.
I was, it was there, we saw it, we walked in.
We were very, it was essentially, yeah, World Showcase 2.
Do you remember being excited about it?
Do you remember like going, oh, we're gonna go down?
But I mean, like, do you remember like going,
I know about it, I'm excited to go do it?
Or was it just there and you were experiencing it?
I think we, that trip we stayed at the boardwalks
and we were coming in through that way
and did kind of have a little bit of like,
oh, what's this, sort of thing.
It was something you happened upon as opposed to,
was excited about before.
If you happen upon it, it was very like,
oh, there's a whole thing going on here.
And specifically, and I was trying so hard
to pin down which country it was.
I remember one of the booths, a very nice cast member
said, come in, sit down, I'll pour you all tea.
And he gave us dates and he was like,
this is hospitality in my country.
Like, and I cannot for the life of me figure out
which one it was.
I think it might be Eritrea,
but they said that was a coffee ceremony,
but that was a similar like, come sit, sit with us.
This is hospitality.
This is-
It must be, right?
I guess so.
I saw that in the special,
like that's a big part of their culture is, yay,
we're gonna offer you things and we wanna get to know you.
And it was this like newer country at the time.
Tea and dates.
It was probably a Middle Eastern country,
but I don't think they were doing that
in the Saudi Arabia pavilion.
I don't think, yes.
Which seems like one of the more expensive ones.
Yeah, Saudi Arabia, even at the time kind of,
Saudi Arabia is an odd country.
I mean, it is run by the House of Saud.
It is the family that, essentially one family runs it
and they subscribe to a form of Islam called Wahhabism.
And that is a far right fundamentalist form of Islam
that pretty much just like Saudi Arabia
and Qatar subscribe to.
That's it.
So yeah, it's a little bonkers Saudi Arabia was here.
Yes.
Especially with them essentially doing 9-11 two years later
and then killing Khashoggi very recently.
It's been a crazy millennium.
For them through the Saudi perspective, sure.
Yeah, but here they came and built a moving story book.
It was an interactive book.
I wrote down just like keywords
of what some of the countries had
and it's their driest bullets in my notes.
Scotland, a golf game, Saudi Arabia moving book, Sweden,
four 30-foot tall eggs.
So, okay, okay.
So the golf game, each hole would teach you
about a different innovation that came out of Scotland.
Like lasers.
So you putted.
You putted.
The ball goes in the hole
and then a story about lasers is told.
The four Sweden eggs each represented a different season.
Yes. In Sweden.
And with that, what's my note on that?
That, yeah, okay.
So they have, there's like keywords around of every,
you know, that are important to each season.
Like whether it's a spring or fall in Sweden.
And for summer, some of the words that signify summer
in Sweden include strawberries, joggers, crayfish,
herring and schnapps, and maple.
Herring and schnapps.
I guess so.
Like that was projected up on a wall.
Summer, time for herring.
Jason, herring, what's your feeling on it?
I haven't had herring that often.
I don't think I've ever had herring.
I like sardines.
I like lox.
I like sardines, yeah.
Yeah.
Keep them in the house sometimes.
That's more of a summer thing.
Herring summer for you.
More of a summer fish.
It's a herring summer next year, I hear.
The herring's been good this summer.
Cool.
Yeah.
Wait, I'm reading about the yurt.
There's a yurt where a bunch of central Asian countries are.
So too, there was an artisan craft area
and you would have to go through a big yurt.
That actually I think sounds badass.
I think that sounds great.
Like an actual yurt they brought over from,
I think it was the Krugas Republic.
Yeah.
Jason, do you have photos of yourself
running around this Millennium Village?
Do you know?
I don't know.
I'd have to look.
I think we only went like the first day.
It was a quick thing probably.
Like visit in and out.
I don't know that we revisited the Millennium Village.
You didn't take time to revisit the Saudi community scrapbook
where you pick up a phone and a Saudi Arabian tells you
their accomplishments, their dreams,
and what their lives are like.
Is that just a recording hopefully?
That wasn't like a phone line
in the middle of a town square or something.
I tell you, there was an open phone in Jeddah
that anybody could just pick up.
And it was like, there was instruction,
like you're gonna be talking to a tourist probably
in a Florida theme park.
And just explain your dreams to them.
Say nice things because we've got like a dozen
different secret police.
That's a good way to weep people out.
Yes. Yeah.
Monitor their call on the phone of dreams.
Sure.
Yeah, it's interesting.
I like, I mean, of course, like the optimum,
I like the idea of it.
Oh, we wanna represent more countries around the world.
Like the idea on its surface is good.
Brazil, there was like a soccer gate,
like you controlled a soccer game with paddles.
And they also told you about the rainforest.
Chile, I think this sounds cool,
gave guests an overview of harvesting fog
through a system of nets to convert it
to drinking water and for crops.
I think that's legitimately interesting.
But some of these were big, like we said,
were bigger than others.
Some of the smaller, some countries just crammed into
what fell under the Expo 2000.
So like exhibits from the Expo 2000,
which was a part of a display of exhibits
from the World's Fair 2000,
which happened in Hanover, Germany,
and seems like a disaster.
Like it doesn't seem like they went well.
Okay.
And this is the, it seemed like it was just confusing.
Like it didn't have a clear message.
Sort of like the, if you can,
listeners look up the Millennium Dome.
That was London's big attempt at a Millennium thing
that is now the O2 arena.
They built this giant Epcotty kind of thing.
There's a very good, very long Twitter thread
about the Millennium Dome.
And it's kind of fascinating.
But another thing that wasn't super successful
tried to be hopeful about the Millennium,
but tried to be everything to everyone.
And then that means it's just kind of directionless.
Sure. Yeah.
Like, you know, Fantasia 2000 around the same time.
The 2000 was an odd era of like, okay, so it's, you know,
international and diverse and the message of hope.
Okay, but why is it like good or interesting though?
Cause hope and stage of time.
Dreams, dreams.
And drop in dreams.
Okay. So get in there.
Magic. Go.
All the words.
Of course the Millennium Village is also probably
the most controversial part of the Millennium celebration
because of just as soon as it opened,
Disney immediately got flack for the presentation
of the Israel Pavilion.
Israel.
And this is probably the main thing to talk about.
Yeah.
And just the strangest thing of all of this.
This is wild.
I mean, this was probably the most intensive
exhibit represented.
I believe the state of Israel gave millions of dollars
to help start this.
That is why it is the only one with a ride.
$1.8 million from the Israeli Foreign Ministry.
Yeah.
And yes, there was a ride and there was a lot of,
it seemed like before the thing even opened
is when a lot of the concern came because there was,
I don't know if it was justified fears
or if Disney had put out something that indicated this,
but there was a lot of like, well,
is this exhibit going to call in,
is this going to call Jerusalem the capital of Israel,
which would be a problem to make that declaration.
I can't tell if it ever did.
So here, okay, the answer is twofold.
One, the exhibit when it opened did not call it
the capital of Israel.
It heavily leans towards Jerusalem is the heart of Israel.
Despite being a disputed city at the opening ceremonies,
the director general of Israel's Foreign Ministry
called it the capital of Israel three times.
Oh.
Three times to roaring applause.
Okay.
So now, disputed city between
I believe this is the Six Day War,
they captured Jerusalem from Jordan.
I'm not 100% exactly sure on the history,
but it's a disputed city.
And who could have predicted 20 years later,
failed casino magnet Donald Trump would make it a,
like would make the thing Disney was worried about doing
or Disney was getting in trouble for
moves the American embassy to Jerusalem from Tel Aviv.
Who could have predicted that happening at the time?
A man who at the time was like, you know,
trying to get laid after the end of days premiere.
He's just like scoping out like,
hmm, any models here at the city of angels?
And soon enough he'll be.
He's at like a Goo Goo Dolls concert or something.
Yeah.
Who could have thought like half of the country of Israel
now named in honor of Donald,
like buildings and neighborhoods.
Do you think this age of time saw it in a prophecy?
That's why he went away.
He did it.
He's like, no, I am out of here.
I'm going off the grid.
Once my dancing obligations are through,
I need to go off and think for a while.
I know what's happening this millennium
and it freaks me out.
Really strange.
The exhibit did call Jerusalem the capital of the millennium
and the heart of the Israeli people.
That is wild.
Like you cannot just build settlements
on top of the millennium, easy.
Like you can't just claim the millennium.
You can't just bulldoze the millennium and claim it.
Jesus.
Yeah, the capital of the century.
What do you mean?
That's a place on a time.
What do you, I don't get it.
And I mean, and of course,
like it probably goes without saying
there is no representation of the Palestinian people
in this pavilion.
There's like no mention.
Cause they didn't pay 1.8 million dollars.
You gotta pony up the money, Jason.
Well, sure.
But like Disney must have,
I mean, was the situation in Israel and Palestine
complicated in 1999?
Well, it was a year that ends in a number.
So the answer is yes.
Of course it was.
So I don't know how they thought
all of this millennium stuff is so like
aimed at being non-offensive.
That they didn't,
they were like caught off guard by this happening.
Why did they even wade into the waters here?
I get, well, cause then the money is the answer.
But the, it all backfired
because Arab and Muslim groups were called,
were threatening a worldwide boycott of Disney parks
and maybe films and more.
Yes.
And the threat of the, yeah, the full Arab boycott was,
it freaked everybody out.
So they made sure to back off of the language
and be more careful with it.
And apparently one of the people who pressured Disney
on this was Saudi Prince Al-Waleed,
Al-Waleed Bintolal,
who is the guy who basically bailed out Euro Disney
for a long time, owned the majority of it.
Oh my God.
Now owns 10% of Euro Disney still.
Wow.
He is also a major shareholder in Planet Hollywood.
I knew you were gonna say it.
Honestly, as soon as I was like, yeah.
It's all the dots are connecting.
Earl flashed in my head.
I go, is it gonna be an Earl?
It's gonna be.
I'm gonna, I wanna be in this story.
I'm gonna be in it.
And the thing I really associate Prince Al-Waleed with
was his announcement, complete with a press conference,
that he was starting a company
called Kingdom Entertainment,
which was supposed to be a theme park endeavor,
mainly driven by him and the King of Pop, Michael Jackson.
They did a press conference about this.
Like, I'm so happy to be with Prince Al-Waleed.
And not only that, as they got further now,
obviously they're, they, as you probably know,
Michael Jackson did not build a Saudi Arabian theme park,
but if he had, the rides were to be built by Gary Goddard,
evil son of a bitch, like allegedly,
tied up in Encino, Brent's Singapore pool party,
so there is a photo of Al-Waleed, Michael Jackson,
and Gary Goddard all happily shaking hands.
Amazing, amazing.
Wonderful.
Again, that sinister, with the perspective of time,
like a lot of sinister stuff going on in the village.
Wonderful.
Yes.
The journey to Jerusalem, yeah, I couldn't,
that ride isn't really documented well.
Not at all.
Did you go on the ride, Jason?
I don't remember going on the ride.
Okay.
I must, we must have walked through it.
A lot of these smaller, like the sum of all thrills,
the build your own, the design your own roller coaster,
any rides, like, ad hoc rides in pavilions
tend to have incredibly bad wait times.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah,
cause they aren't like built to be there forever, so yeah.
Oh yes, so you're totally right.
Yeah, I remember a weird temporary ride
in Innoventions out here that was like way too long
of a wait to just sit in a VR helmet
and get around in a chair.
So there is insanely one person I know
who for sure has gone, went on the temporary ride,
journey to Jerusalem, and defying all logic,
or perhaps the most logical thing,
that person is Bugmane.
Mm.
Our pal Bugmane definitely,
and he talked about this a long time ago to me,
and brought it up like, you know, the Jerusalem ride.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
You're out of your mind, but it did happen.
And I texted him to ask his thoughts on it.
Let me just read his thoughts.
It was a temporary simulator ride,
like if a fair tried to build a Star Tours really fast.
I asked him what happened on the ride,
because it is truly not documented, it's impossible to find.
And he said, you went into the pages of the Old Testament,
like into a parchment,
guided by a guy dressed as an Old Testament king.
Wow.
And then like, whoa, that's insane.
Come, come with me.
And then I said, and then you fly to Jerusalem.
And he confirmed yes.
I did see one other account of this
that said like, imagine if you were being shaken around
while watching already shaky camcorder footage
of the streets of Jerusalem.
That's apparently what this was like.
Bug went on to say, it made me sick.
Not because it was about Israel.
I was gonna throw, I was just almost gonna throw up,
because of motion sickness.
It was hot.
It was a muggy simulation ride
that did not sync up properly with what the chair was doing.
So that's Bugmane's thoughts.
And then he added buzz buzz, skittle, scattle.
Oh, great.
You said trademark.
So, our man on the ground back in the 2000s,
if that's not simulation, we're honest with a simulation ride.
I caught it, yeah.
So it sounds great.
Journey to Jerusalem seems like a winner.
When I Googled like Millennium Village,
journey to Jerusalem, immediately got half a dozen
different newspaper articles about the controversy.
And if one of them pointed out,
I think it was the Orlando Sentinel one,
that this is, you know, when they threatened the Arab League
and others threatened a boycott of Disney,
that hit much, they're like,
this is a season of boycotts for Disney,
because I don't know what happened
that would cause this reaction.
But like the Southern Baptist Convention
was like poo pooing Disney,
because I don't, Jane wore pants in Tarzan or something.
Like, I don't, but it was very clearly,
like they were very clearly trying to make the distinction
of like, yeah, one of these boycotts
would be billions of people potentially.
And one of these boycotts would be a couple
of religious nuts in America.
Like, so they literally said, like,
they have not been able to see if there has been any,
you know, big effect from the Southern Baptist boycott
or what have you.
But they had to take care of this
or else the hope of eventual Jerusalem Disneyland
was not gonna come to pass.
Yeah.
Like it's disputed now,
but it won't be disputed as soon
as they build a theme park there.
I mean, there's rumors of over the years
of them building in all sorts of places.
Yeah.
So who knows what, I mean, that was-
Sure there's feasibility surveys.
Yeah.
I think like, I mean, the Middle East
did not have a good showing at Millennium Village.
Like Saudi Arabia and Israel were the represented.
There's so many other countries-
Which caused due to their proximity
caused a powerful Saudi prince
who bought their European park.
Yeah.
The only reason it's still around, Saudi money.
He's like, hey, this is real thing.
Maybe don't go for it guys.
When Europe was in the dark ages,
Arab mathematicians were inventing modern mathematics.
Like this could have had an amazing represent.
Asia also very underrepresented.
Obviously Disney was just,
as we were saying, it was just money.
It would have been nice for like a total,
like full picture representation.
Yeah. Sure.
But like hardly anything from Asia, which was odd.
Well, they're all jammed into the yurt.
All the Asian countries get in the yurt.
Yeah, I guess it's-
All that way, that's no, Venezuela is also in the yurt
in Greece, there wasn't all Asian.
But the, now they did now,
there are one more description I found of the ride,
which was eight minutes long.
That's a very long ride.
You get to go through stories of faith
that corroborates the Old Testament thing.
A dizzying dash to scenes of Abraham and Jesus
and references to Muhammad.
Wow.
But you don't see Muhammad.
So that's interesting because is there,
and I'm trying to think of like on Spaceship Earth,
is there religious,
what's the closest thing to something being religious?
They mention Arab and Jewish scholars preserving-
Right, texts.
Texts after the burning of the library at Alexandria.
But like Jesus isn't in a ride anywhere in Disney parks.
That's pretty nuts.
For a couple of years, there's a ride
where you went to see Jesus.
That's what I'm saying, like-
And nobody thought to film it?
Right.
That's it.
I mean, did they just get so much money
that they were like, whatever you want to do in here
is fine, or just about anything.
It's interesting because I'm trying to think of another,
like Lincoln probably talks about God,
but it's not such a-
Some religion, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Like, and I'm sure it's like the general God mentions,
but nothing.
I mean-
There's no Jesus.
Could have been a very interesting,
like Christianity and Judaism and Muslims,
like all pulled from a similar,
there's more similarities than difference that like
there could have been something.
Yeah.
That'd be a nice message.
Wait, I did find more.
There's a tour guide, like somebody,
they do that thing where somebody's like not on the screen
and then they're shown a video.
And then the person in the video talks to them.
He appears amidst bright light.
He says he is David, keeper of the stories.
And there's so much stuff Jerusalem to explore.
And then the simulators take you through the city.
So that's, so there is a character,
David, keeper of the stories takes you to see Jesus.
This was a ride that was there that nobody,
that is barely, there's not even like a full recap
of what the ride was.
Does he have a tiny blue alien friend?
That's my question.
Who himself is Christ like?
Yeah.
Who was persecuted and laughed at for his message of love.
And his root beer farts.
Now that leaves blue 32 as the closest depiction of Jesus
in a themed attraction anywhere.
Oh yeah, I think that's right.
I mean, where there's probably like some Bible themed park
that shows you Jesus.
Outside of that.
Here's a question for the listener.
Is there a Jesus robot anywhere?
Oh, good question.
I mean, we should.
It's gotta be in the Holy Land.
I mean, let me Google it.
Holy Land Park in Florida.
Let me just Google Jesus animatronic.
I think so.
I just can't name it offhand.
And this is a thing, here's a whole area
we haven't gotten into guys is religious theme parks.
We have not done.
That's true.
We did Heritage USA, the bizarre collapse
of Dogpatch USA, but the real Heritage USA
Jim Baker's Park we haven't done.
Oh yeah.
There's a whole bunch of that kinda.
There's even in Costa Mesa, there's like a weird
like a virtual reality Bible theater you can walk through.
Wow.
We have not done any religious.
Yeah.
We gotta do that.
Probably time.
Any results?
It looks like maybe there's like a Jesus
that kind of comes out of the ground,
but it doesn't look like there's a full like arms,
head moving, talking.
There might be, you'd call it technically an animatronic
cause it like comes up and like.
Katy Perry coming from under the stage.
Yeah, it's like Katy Perry coming from under the stage.
Dollywood Jesus.
There's no way there's a full robot Jesus in Dollywood.
I think Dollywood is very religious.
I think there would be a.
I'm just saying like.
Good question.
If there was gonna be anywhere in the United States.
Yeah, I think.
Bye.
Bye Lindsey.
I think that Dollywood is very religious,
but I don't know that, oh, maybe I'm wrong.
There's, I wonder if anyone plays anyway.
Robot is a whole other level.
Yeah, robot I don't see.
I don't see.
But I think that what they clearly,
and also, okay, if they wanna get out of the controversy
of if Israel and Jerusalem are names that court controversy,
they should have called this thing Jesus the ride.
And then nobody would ever forget about it.
Yeah, that's true.
Yes.
No one has done that definitively.
Yeah.
Look, just this week, there's someone,
there was a lot of news stories about that Jesus video game.
Really?
First person Jesus video game on Steam.
Is that coming out or is that out?
I just looked up Jesus the ride and it's,
there's some songs, but there's no ride, yeah.
All right, it's time.
I mean, I think we can just talk to Mel Gibson about it.
He's probably got some sort of financier
who might be interested in that.
Anybody could front the money, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah.
All right, so they made a big mistake here.
But what an insane thing.
What a weird.
It's, yeah, there's many layers.
Many layers, political issues, money.
We're talking about the oldest dispute in the world
that's only a few hairs away from the Bryan Singer
and Zeno ring.
Yes, that's.
Like I said, there's so much happening in this little,
I think what we're describing right here
is the most disputed territory in Disney,
in all of Disney World.
Yes.
There's one more thing we haven't mentioned
from the Millennium Village.
The World Culture Game Quiz Show,
which was a game show where people were playing
and people would answer questions about games
around the world.
And it would be like Team Checkers, Team Backgammon.
This game show was sponsored by the World Bank,
a kind of shady, non-governmental,
international development organization
similar to the International Monetary Fund
or the World Trade Organization.
And these were the sorts of groups
that they were protesting at the Battle for Seattle.
So they sponsored this game show and it was constantly,
controversy just follows these sorts of groups.
Like the World Bank is run by very economic wealthy nations
but helps develop less wealthy nations.
And they did a fun game show.
And then they have a fun game show.
And they, at the end of the game show,
they tell you about different World Bank projects
that are going on.
It's like, that's okay.
This is a little sinister.
It's told us everything we need to know about the Millennium.
Like all the clues were here.
Yeah.
In this one building especially.
It is true.
You can, yeah.
As if it was like a narrative story, you'd be like,
well, they planted all the seeds
at the Millennium Village in Epcot Center.
The Sage of Time knew.
Yeah.
He told us everything we'd need to know.
Who was the host of the show?
Do we know?
I think it was like a cast member.
No.
But it wasn't a character.
Wasn't Leonardo.
It also doesn't, I couldn't really find
what the prizes were.
I guess the prize was you got to watch like,
here's the World Bank giving, you know,
small loans to people with a 200% interest rate.
Prize is watching chicks be handed out.
Yeah.
It's also apparently there's like a tradition
that the head of the World Bank is always an American.
And it's like, well, that isn't quite worldy.
Yeah, yeah.
I think it's because America fronts most of the money for it.
But it's like, it's a little ominous looking back on it.
Very strange.
All very bizarre.
There's perhaps no stranger time to be at Epcot.
They also did stuff in, you know,
Illuminations was special and there was the big globe.
I'll leave it up to you how much you want to talk about.
The big globe.
I would just bank it for an Illuminations episode.
There's some interesting technological innovation
involved in that one, but we'll touch on that in the future.
Hit Illuminations.
Yeah.
Okay.
So what did we learn?
Don't try to do rides, but disputed territories.
One little quick thing.
Discman is scary.
Yeah, Discman is scary, but we do,
I do like him as a villain.
They made for McDonald's in 2000,
they had Happy Meal toys for the Millennium celebration.
And I was excited because I was hoping
it was some of those nightmare characters,
but it's just the characters in the plush.
Did they have this logo?
This logo was everywhere to this 2000 Mickey ear logo.
It was on the room keys.
It was just, basically, you know how like
when you have a thing on your closet
that can hold your shoes.
Yeah.
I guess you would get that from McDonald's,
and I'm gonna again, text it to you
so I don't have to move my computer.
Yep.
And you would have room for all your favorite characters,
and there were a lot of them.
So I do like this, but it was not,
I wish there was Discman.
I wish there was like a Discman in a Sage of Time,
but it's just Mickey Minnie and their ball plushes.
And I can buy all of them for $50 right now,
if I wanted to.
The full set and the hanger?
I believe so, yeah.
Can you buy that Leonardo Columbus pin?
How expensive is that?
Oh yeah, good call.
Let me look that up.
I like these plushes.
Yeah.
I like all plush Cogsworth, and only him, not other.
You know, that's what I'm interested in,
like why do they pick these characters?
A lot of dwarves.
What the hell is little brother?
Where does it say that?
Is that from Brother Bear?
Is it Brother Bear?
I don't think Brother Bear was out yet.
And it looks like, look at this with me.
It's like little brother looks like he's got,
he's vomiting black cotton.
What the hell is little brother?
Jason, you're gonna have to do this one
while I'm looking up Leonardo Columbus pin.
Hold on.
Scott, you mentioning DVC reminds me,
I bid on DVC pins and did not win any of those options.
Disney Epcot Tapestry of Dreams Leonardo Columbus pin
went for $8 on eBay.
So if we can find another one,
I don't imagine it would be much more
to just get one of the greatest pieces
of collectible merchandise of all time.
Oh, there's a lot of them.
Okay, good.
There's a lot of Leonardo, when I say a lot, five.
And there's one that at 399 to bid start at.
You could buy it now for $6.
I don't know, should I just buy it?
Yeah, I think to own some Leonardo.
$6 plus $5 shipping.
Are the other ones, are there pins for the other one?
I'm sure there are.
You gotta get the full set.
All right, you're right.
Let's do that off air and we'll figure out.
Well, we'll start out logistics,
but when Leonardo Columbus arrives,
that will herald the dawning
of the gateway of podcast topics will have opened
and the Leonardo Columbus episode will begin.
Heralds the dawn of a new time of love and hope and dreams.
A bunch of shit.
A little brother is from Mulan.
It's Mulan's.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Somebody's so mad.
A bunch of people are so mad at us for not knowing that.
Why would we need to know that?
I mean, Mooshu is,
cause her horse is her friend.
I haven't seen Mulan in a long time.
I know Mooshu.
And the dog is a friend and Mooshu is the friend.
Sometimes there's too many friends.
Tangled has the lizard and the horse.
In this picture, yeah, they got confusing.
In this picture, you cannot tell that it's a dog.
Like it look like, are you guys looking at it?
It looks like a very sick man, barfing black
and like trying to shove it back in his mouth.
Yes.
Are you seeing the same,
would you agree with this depiction?
I know what you're saying, yes.
So I couldn't tell it's a dog.
Lay off.
In the spirit of millennium peace,
don't be mad at us for not knowing who Mulan's dog was.
In the spirit of the millennium, get off Scott's ass.
Cut him a break.
Damn right.
All right, we'll buy this pin and hey guys,
it's gonna be a great decade.
It's gonna be.
Decades worth of content coming at you.
A decade of content, the decade of content dreams.
Stay tuned here.
That's not right.
Stay tuned right here to patreon.com slash podcast,
the ride for all the action.
Yeah, excited for 2020 and more.
Yeah, three episodes every month
and you know where our Twitters and everything are.
You know it.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, let the walk of the 2020s begin.