Five, four, three, two, one.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the second gate where we begin our analysis of the Imagineering
Story and most importantly we begin mining Disney Plus for content. We've been so busy
we haven't gotten to use Disney Plus as an excuse to do a bunch of bullshit. Now we're
gonna do it. I'm Scott Garner, Jason Churin's here.
Yeah, I think this mine will lead to a very rich vein that will then, once we have mined
it, dried up immediately. Or not, I could be wrong.
Hard to say.
Yeah, I'm here. It depends if, I will say there's a low amount of parks content in general.
Yes.
There is. Yes.
Per my general interests, I mean now that I've watched all of the Imagineering show
and I have like three episodes left to The Mandalorian, I was like, well, I don't know
if I'll log back into that again. Like, I don't know when I'll watch something on there
again.
Did anyone do the year? Did anyone pay for a year of Disney Plus?
No, no, no, no.
Or five years or whatever the hell.
Three, it was three.
I get it for a year for free as a Verizon customer.
Okay, good, good, good. That's good. I'm just month by month in it. I like month by month
in all of these streaming services. It's a little maddening, I guess, but now on iTunes
it's all control. You just like click buttons on and off and if there's nothing on HBO now,
why am I gonna pay for HBO?
There's no new content coming, no like major new content or new shows until fall. I think
Mandalorian season two will be the next like-
Wandavision?
Show.
Isn't that coming? Didn't that get bumped up?
It was, did it get bumped up this year?
To this year, I think.
Probably the fall though. That was gonna be next year. So yeah, maybe like, you know,
if it's, if I take six months off, that's fine. You save a little money.
Yeah, I think so. I actually had retired it and I brought it back to rewatch The Imagining
Story, which of course I watched every episode as soon as humanly possible and I really enjoyed
it and we'll talk about stuff that we liked.
I didn't watch six because I don't want to have, see the rise of the resistance.
Did you not watch any of six?
I have no, I have no-
Carly put the time code up.
Carly Wazil was very-
And I stopped right at that.
Me too. You should do the same. You know what? It's also not that hard to figure out because
they do save it. So you're watching it, they get into Star Wars, they get into Millennium
Falcon and then it like shows the words rise of the resistance and then you know to shut
it off. You will not get bum rushed by anything.
ET says Michael, like he says it to me and to turn off-
Trouble.
I should say, did we say what we're doing yet?
Yes, we did.
Oh, we did. Okay.
We sure did. But I should say another thing.
Yes, please.
Which, so here's an idea. As we said with Disney Plus open and streaming and teaming
content, we wanted you guys to customize our Disney Plus viewing experience. Here's, I'm
going to refer to the, I gave this the, what I want to do, a little catchy name. You know,
we talk about rides and how to plus them up, but now it's your chance to plus us up. So
plus us up is what we're going to do where you tell us to watch something on Disney Plus.
We're going to send out a tweet or respond to it, use hashtag plus us up and by popularity
or by bizarreness of entry, if we think something is so unique, well, we got to do that. Please
make us watch something on Disney Plus and then we will do a Patreon episode about it.
And that could be anything. If you want, if you just want us to watch, you know, Little
Mermaid and want to know what we really think about it, then great. If you, if it's, if
you want to make us watch an episode of that's so Raven, just some random thing in the Disney
channel archives. If you're really dying to hear what we think about Martin Lawrence's
college road trip or the cat from outer space, there's tons of weird shit on there and there
might be something odd that we haven't thought of. A Latter-day Simpsons even. Yeah, sure.
That is such a weird, like the Latter-day Simpsons is, is this 20 year desert. I don't know most
of what happened and there could be things that it's like completely surprised me. Like
they've been to Iran or something. I don't know. Very possible. They went and met that
guy. They went with Rick Steves. Rick Steves showed them the beauty. Rick Steves. How about
it? Huel Hauser must've been on the Simpsons. I think he was. He was. Yeah. Yes, he was.
He put a plane or yeah. Yeah. Because there was a Huel Hauser esque character. Yes. And then in
turn he, I see that's completely possible. Maybe Rick Steves. That's actually a good candidate.
If there's a true, if there's a Simpsons episode that you know about that we don't and that they're
like, you guys, you don't know this bizarre thing happened. Um, I, yeah. So the, uh, I don't know,
send us somewhere. Make us, uh, make us watch something. Um, anything you guys are curious
about or any like seeds you want to plant? Well, Mighty Ducks, obviously we've mentioned before.
Yeah. The cartoon. Mighty Ducks. The adventuring cartoon about, uh, uh, uh, ducks who live on a
planet where hockey is very popular and sort of a super team Power Rangers, X-Men esque super team
that use puck guns. Yeah. And it's a real Anaheim and Dennis Franz is in it. There's a real like
police chief of Anaheim. Ooh, I forgot about Mighty Ducks and I have flipped through there.
If you want to like make us a Mighty Ducks cocktail, if you're, if you know what's the
good on that show and you want to point us to a specific one or like give us a good gargoyle.
Yeah. Love gargoyles. I never really watched it. Oh, I liked it a lot. People loved it and people
still talk about it. So I would be interested to see if that holds up. I didn't really, although
gargoyles and like Transformers and to his extent, Mighty Ducks would get, give me anxiety
more so that I liked Power Rangers or like, you know, X-Men and Batman were all just doing
their jobs. I did not like the shows where they're like, they have to fight evil so they can get home
and I'm like, when are they ever going to get home? Why was they live in exile? Like that was too
like just existential. I just knew it in the background of like, Oh God, like, like the
Animaniacs just go on adventures. Great. Rocky and Bullwinkle go on adventures. You want to know at
the end of the day, it's all going to be okay, but there's not this acquist they may never fulfill.
I, you know, the X-Men were hated and feared by those they protected, but they had each other in
their hyper secure mansion. Gargoyles had, you know, had each other too. I guess that's true,
but I think if they're fucked in the daytime, they turn to stone when the sun comes up.
But that's just part of their life. I guess so. I'm just saying that I feel like you were
stressed about everything. You shouldn't be stressed about X-Men. Yeah. I say it really,
they had it rough. Yeah, but they had each, they had their, they were, they had their family.
They were, they all had powers and they were all hot. Yeah. Yeah. That's one of my favorite things.
Hot weird people. They were all hot. As Grant Morrison said, hot, weird, weird looking people.
Well, he made them a little, because with the Frank Whiteley art, they were all squiggly.
But yeah, they were just hot. And in the nineties, they were just hot. Jacked. Yeah.
A lot of pouches. They're all a gladiator, like American gladiator. Yes. Oh, they do. Yeah.
The female styles are kind of similar. A lot of big hair. Yes. Yes. Yeah. A lot of big hair.
Were you stressed out by American gladiators?
They don't win the Jouse. They might never get home. I didn't like when people did not complete
their tasks. Yeah. Or like got beaned by the tennis balls by like, got shot by a cannon.
So you, because then pyro, if he got beaned, might not go home. He might not make it home.
Well, no, the pyro, no, the gladiators were like the bad guys. Right. The regular,
right? No, you kind of had the regular people were challenging the gladiator. Like they had to face
the gladiators. So you were rooting for the regular people. Yes. You're, you were ideally rooting
for the regular. I hate to get off on a sidetrack here. Do we, did we see the Quibi
Legends of the Hidden Temple for adults show? Is it literally legends for the,
it's the, that's what it says. Legends of the Hidden Temple from Nickelodeon. That game show
is coming to Quibi, but adults are going to be playing instead of children. This is revolutionary.
Revolutionary. I'm sure people will like leap to see this and not just like watch two minutes and
then leave. You're right about that. I do want to be on it though. Being on it is a whole other
thing. Yeah. Scary though. Cause we've talked about the guards, the guards on Legends of the
Hidden Temple scaring all of us. Production shuts down. Yes. Production shuts down. Production shuts
down immediately after the first person cold cocks the guard. After a seven foot tall guy,
just sucker punches a guard. He just fell. He falls off that massive open set like,
yeah. And just barely misses the foam pit. Oh, if he'd just been one foot over. Oh God. The,
the guard. The guards have to wear a headgear and boxing gloves in case it happens from that point
on. The guards also, they're much like the Mandalorian raised that way in a religious
manner and can never remove the helmet. This is the way. This is the way. Yeah. They have
made the Lawrence that helmet. And then maybe will they ever make it home? Not if they get cold
cocked. No. So, Hey, yeah. Tell us what you want us to watch in Disney plus, plus us up. We'll send
a tweet and give you a place to respond to that, but also just, you know, send it to us. Hashtag
plus us up. Tell us what you want us to watch. Oh, I have one more example of an oddity. Do you want
us to watch adventures in babysitting from 2016? Because the real one isn't available on Disney
plus until 2021. And yeah, they made the card to say that that is, but there is a one from a couple
years ago. What are you talking about? Yeah, I don't know what that's some, some deal they had
previously, I guess they maybe thought that that was such a high profile movie. People would be
like furious unless they explained when it was coming. I don't know. That's my speculation.
I got to give you credit, Scott. It took me about, it's a very good hashtag and it only took me about
three minutes to figure out why you had chosen it. It was awesome. Disney plus. And I was like, wow,
he's been really optimistic that there's some gold there. And then I'm like, oh, the name of the
streaming. So got it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. No, it's not, it doesn't quite, I mean, also I could have
just said, make us watch something on Disney plus. That's what it is. That's really what it is.
You use that hashtag too, but I'm just keeping it tidy. No, I think it's very good. So go ahead
and use that. But for today, we're going to talk about the thing that we, you know, had to watch
as soon as Disney plus is available. And that's the Imagineering story. Did you guys dig it in
general? Yeah, I mean, I did. I thought that it was, it's nicely put together. And I was impressed at
Disney at least like admitting like mistakes a little bit or showing slight. I mean, it's nothing
crazy, crazy, but just sort of like talking about like challenges and like on occasion, making
themselves look a little bit bad or like, yeah, fun necessarily. But like you think of Disney is
just like so protective of their image and they were at least like acknowledging failures or when
they may be overstepped or whatever. Yeah. Certain things as the narrative that we've certainly
regarded as the narrative and like here now there's kind of this decay after Disney Paris
and it gets real, real cheapo around Disney studios, Paris and California adventure.
Superstar limo as the like nadir is cemented. Yeah. Really put this out there for lay people,
for people who aren't obsessed with this, like us, they really have like, this is the story
and this will forever be kind of the Canon story. It's an interesting story and one where they do
admit a bunch of faults. Yeah. There's a, there, there was a couple weird moments, more than a
couple, but less than I thought. Yes. I'll say that I thought Leslie Iwerks overall did a good job.
Yeah. And she has like, she's part of a Disney lineage because her grandfather is a Biwerks who
designed Oswald the lucky rabbit and Mickey Mouse. Kind of a sidelined person Disney,
in the Disney story. Kind of screwed over. So it's cool that the family's like still part of it and
kind of that she gets to like, sort of like, you know, shine a light on their lineage, including
her father. Don Iwerks. Who's in the documentary. Yeah. And he, I see, I didn't know about him. So
that's good that she's got this platform to talk about it. Who is like, who got special academy
awards due to his contributions to film because circle vision seems very, like very much his
doing. Yeah. He seems cool. I, and she's cool. I liked the Pixar story not long ago, which has
been floating around Netflix for a long time and now I think is on Disney plus. I've not gotten to
watch her documentary about ILM, but that I bet that's good. She's, these are just like great,
clean. Yeah. Yeah. For sure. Very accessible too. Like I would think that if you just are
like a casual fan of Disney, very slick, you would go on. Especially very slick. Yeah. I think you
would, it would be an easy watch and you would know what they're talking about. And it's not
impenetrable like this podcast. I think under the, the big thing story-wise that was interesting to
me is that Disney is simultaneously the hero and the villain in this because they make
Imagineering look like a real underdog, but the people kind of putting the weight on Imagineering
is just another branch of Disney. It's just the money men. Yeah. Yeah. Sure. Or like executive
the taste. Yeah. The man upstairs, but that is, yeah, it is Disney. I, yeah, it's fascinating and
interesting to see both sides of the Eisner coin. That's what I think makes him such a compelling
character. There were the good years and the bad years. And, uh, uh, and where, you know, I've,
I've certainly seen the complaint about I, uh, Iger's, uh, presence in these documents where he's,
it's just sort of like, and then in the end, finally the great dependable CEO did everything
perfect. What? I mean, I, I, Izer shows up about halfway through and I have to give him credit
because he looks like a human being and he stands like a human. He's like laughing in photos. He's
like slouchy. It looks casual. His hair is messed up in photos. His hair is messed up. And I mean,
Iger, there's some shots where it's like, man, did you start your undershirt? What is going on?
Relax a little. You're on mainstream. You're like, he has the posture of David Copperfield
robotically doing his show over and over again. Perhaps wearing a back brace is what we've had.
Yeah. Yes. Yeah. Human shoulder, like a rubber, like what? Like a superhero. Yeah. Under his,
the George Michael from arrested development muscle. Yes. Yeah. Uh, Iger is the first voice
you hear in the, he's the first person. Maybe Angela Bassett narrating before that, but the first
interview is Robert Iger, which is a kind of an interesting note to sure start on to have not
an imagineer, but I think we're probably getting to the heart of this is like it was approved by
Iger because they never said anything bad about him. And like, they mean other people in charge
look bad. So he's like, yeah, this is good. I like the more of that. The only thing I wanted to say
about the, I don't know a ton about like the making of this thing, except that it's been going
for a long time. Yeah. I think it was supposed to be a feature. I think they were not planning on
having it be this long. Yeah. Which, so they were, yeah. Working on it since 2013 sort of with like
no exact what it'll be in mind. And then the streaming service becomes clear and that's the
perfect home for it. And apparently the notes from Disney plus in shifting it to that format
were about character making, highlighting characters. And I think all of these things
that I'm sure we will say we really enjoyed watching Bob Gurr go through the Matterhorn,
watching Tony go through his many rides and how great does he look in this, that episode. It's
just like another one, another one, another one. But I think all of those moments were more recently
done. And that's kind of cool that a note that notes can be annoying, but I think that note led
to some of the like real heart of this show and some of the more interesting stuff. Yeah. It's
interesting because it seems like from what I read, Disney plus exists because in 2015,
the cable revenue dropped. ESPN. ESPN like dropped a lot. Yeah. And Netflix was doing well
and HBO go or HBO now. Quibi's on the horizon. Yes. The rumbling. The rumble of the distance.
The Legend of the Hidden Temple on Quibi. When they heard, when it was just Katzenberg,
that's one thing. But when they heard Meg Whitman was involved, like, oh God, oh God,
we need a streaming service stat. The printer lady, the woman who tanked the printer company.
Failed governor candidate. Failed gubernatorial candidate. Is going to make shows for 12 year olds?
Hurry. Open a new line of business. Yeah. So I don't know. It's good. I think like imagine
this would be, I think too much for a feature. I think so unless it was like split into two
movies. Yeah. I mean, I can see a super streamlined version with, yeah, without that stuff you're
talking about, which make it even better. But yeah, I think a lot of the imagineers
that they highlight come off very endearing. Yeah. Yeah. And I really liked, especially in the first
episode and the second episode too, a lot, it really highlights a lot of the people who are,
there's some people, Bob Gurr, Raleigh, Roley Crump, I'll never get that right,
still with us. But a lot of the people have, Mary Blair, Mark Davis have passed away.
Well, even Marty Sklar, who's interviewed, has passed away. But he's all over this thing.
Yeah. They get some great, great stuff with him. So the first episode, still a lot of Walt.
Walt is still alive and a lot of what they're covering because they're covering from the
initial genesis of the idea for Disneyland. And I'll say this, the weirdest part of the series
happens to me in the first one, which is the Angela Bassett narration. By the end of World War
II, Walt grew tired of fighting labor unions and the rising costs of animation. That is the worst
myth making in this whole documentary because the animator's strike, skip that, that was so odd.
And it was funny when the two sentences later she refers to Walt developed eccentric hobbies.
Jason talks about unions and Mike has to turn the volume down.
You were blowing those speakers and levels out.
Sorry. No, it's good. You care.
The animator's strike lasted five weeks. It wasn't that long. It was five weeks.
And this was- Writers haven't had agents for nine months now.
For nine. Yeah.
It may never again.
But this first episode, it was a good reminder that there is Walt Disney the man and Walt Disney
the character that the company owns because this is Walt Disney the character. They did not feature
Walt Disney the man who described the writer's strike as having cleaned house at our studio
of the chip on the shoulder boys and the world owes me a living, lads.
Jesus, really?
Yeah.
Oh no.
And also a lot of those people that cleaned house of came back eventually, but he took it
as like hurt feelings. He thought it was a family and never trust an executive who calls
something a family. When the Imagineers describe the environment as familiar,
familial, I believe that.
Yeah.
But when executives say like, we're a family here, they are trying to screw you.
All of this is so complicated. I mean, one of the reasons animation costs so much
is because a lot of Disney animators joined the war effort and Disney started making war
film. It was complicated.
That saved the company.
That saved the company because he had spent all of the Snow White money building a state of the art
film campus in Burbank.
Yeah. I'm very interested in that line about fighting labor unions getting left in the movie.
I don't think that's an accident.
No.
That's like in there. If they didn't like that in 2019 or 2020, that would be gone.
There's no reason to put it in. There's no reason to even highlight a negative part of
Walt's history. They don't need to do it. They don't like to do it. So either it's bizarre.
It's so bizarre. They must just not think that's a bad thing is what I'm saying.
At the very least, they must just go, oh, yes, he was fighting with labor unions and that was
being portrayed as if that was one of the great struggles of his life.
That like a noble effort.
They must just think of that.
For five tough weeks until the National Labor Relations Board were like, just sign the
fucking contract. It was the FDR's administration, so they were reasonably pro worker.
Yeah.
But it was just bizarre.
It's bizarre on a couple levels.
In that.
There's a couple of like little reckonings they have to do with, like little nods. They do describe
Song of the South as an old problematic film.
Yes.
And as I think we've said before, EO comes up and they don't say the name.
They don't say Michael Jackson's name.
Right.
Just like, let's get it. They acknowledge it.
First 3D movie.
Good done. And also, but also with sort of events rearranged because it was before Star
Tours. It led the way to Star Tours, not the other way around. And they presented as like,
it's the aftermath of Star Tours.
Right.
They jump around a little bit.
Now, while that's a difficult situation they're in, I think they landed in a good place because
we didn't have to meditate. They didn't have to go on about Michael Jackson being great,
but we also got to see a cool picture of those robots and ID and stuff.
So I got my picture. We didn't praise a bad guy and it's good.
Yeah.
I will say something funny in this early portion, when everyone's skeptical of Walt,
is how much it was taken as a given by his friends and family that everyone hates carnivals.
Those places are so dirty and the workers are so unfriendly.
The consensus amongst society in the late 40s, early 50s were like, fuck carnivals.
They all cough up oil on you while you're on the ride.
Bumper cars all break your spine. And then the carny spit in your face when you ask them
for help.
Just that is kind of portrayed universally as like, no, this sucks.
Yeah. I mean, that's, that is-
It tastes like gas.
In anything, any biography I've read about Walt Disney, it's always like,
he hated taking his daughters to the carnival. He wished, like, he was just like disgusted with,
like, just a Ferris wheel and a carousel.
I mean, when you see those Coney Island rides, like the, like just slides that are bumping
people in full suits around, like just like maiming people in like full gowns and hats.
Yeah.
It doesn't seem like the greatest scene.
I don't disagree. It is just funny. Cause as a kid though, I liked the carnival.
I, I-
Sure.
But we don't know carnivals in the 40s.
That's true.
Well, but even in the 90s, like you weren't opening your pocketbook for that trip. Like
carnivals have always been inflated in price and stuff to make profit.
I'm just saying like, I guess it was from Walt's perspective.
I like Disneyland. That he kept from carnivals.
He liked one thing.
That he kept off charge.
I'm just saying from a kid's perspective, I knew, I, we knew it was funny. We knew that,
like, it was funny that this thing got set up overnight and that, like, it looked like
shit, but there were rides we liked.
Yeah, sure.
I liked the Tilt-A-Whirl.
You know, it was nice to hear the story. I don't know if you guys have heard the story before,
where Walt goes to the merry-go-round and he's with his two daughters and it's daddy daughter
day.
Right, right.
Again, perfect myth-making. Perfect character development.
Yes, yes.
It's the most used footage of all time.
And to that end, while of course these things come up and I roll my eyes because I've seen
them a zillion times, I like that episode one is the Walt era and that's it.
Because this is the stuff I, I mean, this is me. I've been watching specials about this
forever and ever my whole life. So I just, I didn't want to rehash all the same things.
I really like that pretty quick. We're off to Tony in the 80s. We're off to the weird decay
and what happened with California Adventure. We're looking at Disney Sea,
looking at the stuff they just did. I like that they like move through time pretty quick.
I didn't think that would be the case. I also didn't think that would be the case. It's like,
I don't want to spoil the movie Executive Decision, but they kill off Steven Seagal
very early in that movie. And it's very surprising because I didn't think he was
going to go that quick because he's a big star. And it's the same thing where Walt dies at the
end of right at the end of the number one of the first one, essentially. And he's out of there.
Genuinely in psycho. What's Kurt Russell going to do when he's on this plane with his crew?
Yeah. Kurt Russell also in this show briefly in this. Yeah, I guess that's a thing. My brain
immediately was there's so many streaming services now. I'm like, what is Executive Decision? What
is that? I haven't seen it in a while. It's from the like 97. Have you seen it? No, but I immediately
it's like terrorists on a plane. I'm sure probably like Air Force One, but they like it's not like,
is it British terrorists? Cause that's okay. You can have British. I don't think it's British.
They were really forward thinking by having it be wrong, but I heard I remember. I loved it.
Big reoccurring thing in this series. Every episode does end on a cliffhanger except the
last one. Actually, I don't. Well, I won't spoil that. Oh, I don't know how the last one ends.
Oh, it's a cliffhanger for us. For us. Yeah. What's funny is as much as we're complaining about all
this Walt stuff and the myth making or whatever, there'll be a couple of times where I'm still
like sucked into like the cartoon version of Walt that I grew up in my mind with. Yeah. That guy is
real. I think he's a complicated person. Yeah. I think Steve Jobs complicated man. I am also
and I don't, I'm also got this story of like Roy, like Roy, you know, like lethal weapon where
Murtaugh wants to retire and or really I find Roy is very endearing. He never gets. He's like,
I'm out of here. And then Walt dies and he's like, I won't retire. I must finish my brothers like out
of tribute. Like there's something so moving about it. I don't know what kind of guy Roy was,
honestly, but that always gets me. I was like, Oh God, he just wanted to settle down. It was a life
of stress for Roy. And then by the story of Roy. Well, I do think, yeah, I was wondering what it
is like to live in the shadow of your sibling. Like I've heard Roy, I feel like rarely got the credit.
I've heard some bad stuff about Roy's kid, Roy, but I don't know much about Roy other than he's
just constantly stressed out. Walt is making like we're doing this and he said, I don't know where
we're going to get the money for this. They're constantly on the brink of bankruptcy. It's a
literally like a life of stress because like in my kid brain, Mike Carlson sees a patron.
I'm like Roy. Yeah. I'm like the original. So they say the, the Genesis of Disneyland, someone says
if it hadn't worked, it would have been the end of the Disney empire. Like they put everything on
the line for this. There's a couple versions of that too, even with like movies and you,
yeah, absolutely. They made Snow White and then it was smooth sailing and it was not.
Well, I do wonder what is the point in the company history where you that,
I mean, cause they were having financial issues through the eighties and stuff. When does that
start to become not true? Is it after the, the boom of the nineties where it's like, this could be the
end of us. Like, cause that just won't happen now. Well, they've got to be, well, cause the, I mean,
the parks obviously struggled through the nineties, but the, but the, but films were taking off,
like then you're in golden era animation that Eisner era it like seemed to like said it,
obviously there was turmoil past that, but it was never like, well, this just won't be a company
anymore. There were those rumors of like Comcast buys it and then, and what's the other thing that
they almost lost Pixar. Yes. Yes. So there was that. That was very contentious. But still all of that
isn't like the company doesn't exist. Right. Right. I mean, but there's, it's funny cause like it's
now it feels like such an impossibility that it could go away. Yeah. But I mean, stuff like 10
years pass and some stuff happened changes. I mean, an aggressive, an unfriendly administration and
an aggressive federal trade commission could break up some of these larger entertainment companies.
Hey, let's do it. I mean, let's do it. We would forgo some Disney fun for to make
um, companies professionalize a little smoother. Should be broken up. All of them. Anyway,
uh, I love, you know, they, they of course more myth making about like the opening day chaos,
but I hadn't really heard the stories before of, uh, people kind of fucking each other up to ride
Autopia, like people pulling each other out of cars and then taking the car to drive themselves
before Autopia was on a track. Well, there's, there's the guy, there's the stories of the
ladders over the, I don't know how true those are. You, somebody would like charge you a nickel to
climb your ladder to get into Disneyland. Oh yeah. Yeah. I think they talk about that. Well,
there was a counterfeit tickets to the opening day. Then people dispute how much that happened.
Yeah. All these, there's another, all these myths about exactly what chaos happened. Yeah. In the
first day in weeks. Um, but yeah, they try, they, they, uh, they, uh, address a little bit of it.
All of the costume characters on opening day were people sneaking in. They,
Disney had not hired any of those and then it gave them the idea. Right. Let's have like a Mickey
Mouse guy. Three Mickey mouses just walked out. They all look different. Why is that 20 guys dressed
like the president? The president walker. Uh, and he had to choose between, uh, drinking water
and toilets. I think I'd heard that drinking water and toilets is very, yeah. Yeah. They do like the,
like the cement is cement drying people's like heels getting stuck in cement. That's kind of,
uh, renewed in this. Is it Disney world? Is it the magic kingdom? The next step of it where they are
using helicopters hovering to dry cement. That's a really good advancement of the cement. This
thing wasn't denying a month ago. Oh yeah. Oh no. Oh no. Flew straight here.
Trying to keep track of what's happening in the world. Every, every time they mentioned a year,
trying to think about what was going on in the world at the time is very interesting through
this documentary. Cause I feel like that's a thing I think about doing the podcast a lot
and they tangentially bring it up. Certainly in later episodes. There, uh, yeah, there was one part,
it does feel like, I mean, if it's a documentary about the sixties, you have to have,
but with Vietnam and Watergate and, but I think in this case, they seemed to, I think is it my
memory, right? That they frame Vietnam and Watergate as that's why they needed to get the haunted
mansion open ASAP. Cause any sixties documentary, you have to have your little quick helicopter
in a wide room. Um, which Joker uses by the way, that song in a movie still, still today.
And then we're going to call it wildly, wildly original film anyway. Well, how about credence
may pull a credence in there. Um, uh, Bob Gerr, we had said his chunk very endearing, um, where he
signs the Matterhorn. I also like him talking about, uh, designing physics, like learning.
He knew how to build vehicles, but then he had to learn trigonometry to figure out the physics of
the Matterhorn. That's insane. That would just never happen nowadays. They would, yeah, they would
have that person draw up the theoretical design and then have scientists or engineers come in
and finish it off. Yes. Yeah. You know, machines, you know, put a hair like weird, uh, the machine
like, uh, uses gravity and that zillions of people get on every day. Uh, Tony Baxter says
at one point in the thing, the, like the, the, all the kooks they hired originally would not be
hired in the current atmosphere because you have to get experts to do things and not this like crazy
band of misfits. They were like the original SNL people. Um, just as much cocaine, I'm sure.
In 1955, they didn't really go into the substance of future shoes of like who was like, man, we were
staying up all night to complete the tea cup redo. I was going to say there for sure are,
uh, like a 90 minute specials on each ride. Like there's, they could, they could easily expand this
whole thing and maybe if the ratings are good, they will. Do you think that might infringe on
what we're doing? Do you think they'll go off on long tangents about McGruff though in the 90
minutes? Yeah. That's what you come here for. That's the difference. I think. Yeah. Um, but yeah,
that Matterhorn sequence is really nice. Uh, yeah. Watch it. Just like, you know, it was really cool
is watching Bob Gurr like just walk into the Matterhorn with the familiarity of norm walking
into cheers. Yeah. Of course I know. Yes. Here's the door and I walk up and there's the, you know,
there's the basketball place and the basketball court we've heard wasn't remarkable and boy,
is it not. Yeah, boy. It's just a hoop. It's just a hoop cause I think storage shed up there.
Initially when I heard it was like, there's a basketball court in the Matterhorn and I was like,
holy shit, a court. I actually thought that it was like a secret, like pro level place where like
magic would secretly practice. That is actually what I thought when I was, I didn't think that
far into it, but I think I sort of thought, I thought at least it was like a half court
and like had, you know, a real nice floor and lines. And yeah, I actually, yeah, it was a little
misrepresented to that mythology appear. People really built that up. Look either through balls
in a hoop or you read a paperback book and that was your options to entertain yourself in between
your job and your breaks back then. If you were in your mountain climbing. Yeah. And your
mountain climbing. All right. Time to go back to climbing this mountain. So, but I mean, it was
great to see it. I'd still like to go in there. I would still love an invitation. Sure. They also
like, don't shoot a lot of high definition footage of like, this is what the inside of this ride
looks like. That's true too. This is the grease stained dirty inside of the, yeah, really ride.
I know that's super cool. Uh, yeah. And I'd also like to say just all of the like restored film.
There's like, yeah, there's one movie, I forget the name of it, but it's like, it seemed like
just a very basic made in 56. We're just going to show Disneyland on nice looking film and it looks
so beautiful. This documentary is full of things that we've seen before, but seeing them cleaned
up and color corrected and looking sharp is just as, yeah, for a Disney nerd to look at some, a lot
of beautiful Disney footage was great. Yeah. Uh, world's fair in this, in the first chapter
comes to the world's fair stuff. Um, you know what I don't think I, you know what I think I was
disconnected from was that that ride that was it called the magic skyway with the Cadillac cars?
Yeah. Or it was four Mustangs or Mustang. And I don't think I knew that. I don't think I realized
that because, um, okay. So the, now when you go through the, uh, the primeval world, the dinosaurs
and the train at Disneyland, uh, how that was presented in the world's fair was you would drive
Ford Mustangs through a building and go see dinosaurs. I guess I knew that, but it didn't,
it didn't click with me. So watching footage of a bunch of old sixties Fords, that's, it's,
that's great. That's a kooky ride. Yeah. Not preserved. Like everything else picked up and
brought here the Ford Mustangs, just not the Ford didn't want to keep doing stuff. Just didn't want
to keep doing stuff where Disney just didn't want a giant car commercial constantly through his park.
Not told test track. I mean, tower, the four winds also just demolished, not preserved.
Yeah. So not everything, man, but I, I don't, I kind of wish just like you could still ride old
six. So today you pitch that ride sixties cars that take you to dinosaurs. It was sure it would
be like if they built a ride on the water outside the boathouse in Orlando with those hydro cars.
Yeah, that'd be great. Yeah, that's got a retro player. Yeah. Yeah. That'd be cool. Um, another
thing that hadn't really clicked with me, uh, is that, um, you, you don't know who came to what
department when, and we know about John Hinch and we know that John Hinch was like, uh, sort of the,
the comedy and character guy. Uh, and he, but he was still animating through the fifties. So not
till the like early sixties, did he move over to imagineering and, um, I didn't know, we've never
done a jungle cruise episode. So I don't know about different phases of jungle cruise. And I
didn't know that certain scenes were not there. And it seems that you would call funnier scenes
were his doing in the early six. Like some of the first things he did were, uh, the, uh, all the,
the, like the, the hunter and all tribes people like on the tone of polio, like,
they really credit him. I think Hinch was walking through the trend. I think he might be mixing up.
I think Mark Davis is the humor guy because I thought Hinch was like showing them how to
plow the trenches of jungle cruise. Like I think he was involved pretty early on.
I don't know. I have this all under John Hinch, but I could be wrong. But either way, I guess,
like, I didn't know that there was this, what the other thing is the elephant pool, there was, uh,
I think the jungle cruise was a very serious ride and maybe the skippers had started making jokes,
but I didn't know about this level of like early sixties redo where we added some comedy. And
that's kind of, I bet it seems like it was, it was probably an exciting ride when it first opened,
probably kind of dreary to just like, go seriously look at robots and none of it is silly.
Well, the four original lands had direct parallels by like Disney's, Disney's animated
films and fantasy land. And then his future films in tomorrow land, his, uh, David Crockett stuff
in frontier land, and then his nature stuff in adventure land. Like it's like a one-to-one
comparison and it's only as like the park developed in the first decade, it kind of
more took on its own identity. Sure. It wasn't just like, yeah, let's look at what you would
see on the show, but in physical space for it. Um, but I, yeah, I mean, things like that are
always, we're all good to just like a little reminders of this is why this is what this is.
Another big one, I forgot why audio animatronics is audio. You feel like it does phrase as a
lifelong Disney nerd, that phrase just rolls off your tongue. I forgot audio was a crucial
component and that they're all synced up to audio discs. Is it like, they also refer to scalloped
edge discs and that's how all these things move. Uh, like, yeah, these just like bizarre record
contraptions and that it's all like beeps and audio signals that make them work. Right. Um,
yeah, I guess, I mean, audio, I just, yeah, audio animatronics, like, oh yeah, they talk.
That's what I always thought. I guess that's what is what it means, but I never,
I never remember that it's like, is what it's about. I mean, I don't think it's not discs anymore,
right? There's gotta be some sort of digital, but some of them might still go off of how they were
probably. Yeah. I can only imagine a pain in the ass. Do I get with analog technology to restore
old, yeah, just brutal. Yeah. Cause if you don't have the audio sync, you just have them clicking.
You forget how loud the clicks are. I mean, in the Tiki room, you hear the clicks. Sure. Yes.
Yeah. But it's the first one. So you forgive it. Um, you hear all the clicks with Marty scar
talking to us in pirates. That's a very charming moment. That's, that's a really nice little scene
there. So pirates in this, they do go out of order. Like it is, there's one or two moments where it's
like, oh, they kind of break the linear structure in order to get the ending. Sometimes this one,
most noticeable cause they talk about pirates and then they talk about Walt's death in reality. I
believe six months apart the other way, but frame it as like his last accomplishment. Yes.
That and buying the starting the Florida project. Not the film, but the, no, not the years before
darling. But yeah, how tidy is that? They get rid of there. We're out of wall. We're out of the stuff
we know really well. And we're looking at, cause, cause the construction of Disney world and
everything is really fascinating. Um, just that it's like truly what swamps it all was. And, uh,
I bet a lot of people don't know about those tunnels. Um, that's good like stuff for, uh,
to find out about. And then I was trash can't like, not, uh, uh, that there's like trash
centers that are all pneumatic tubes that run through. I was, I, I had saw a friend over the
break that I haven't seen in a couple of years and I saw her parents who I haven't seen in
15 years, maybe, uh, or maybe like, I don't remember 12. Uh, and I w that was explaining
the podcast as you have to do to friends and family sometimes. And, uh, and he, her dad goes,
he goes, you know what I'd like to do with Disneyland? He goes, I want to go in those
tunnels. Yeah. I go, well, the tunnels aren't really, they're more pro like there's a few
things maybe at Disneyland, but it's mostly a Disney world. You're thinking of that a full like
tunnel systems. He's like, oh, okay. So like the tunnels are out there at the very least. I feel
like I I've known about the tunnels for a long time. I feel like I got to do it as a kid. There
was a class. You go in the tunnel here. Uh, no, in Florida or in Florida. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
We're not very publicized, not a ton of tunnels here. Right. No. Man. What was the class? It was,
it was like called like backstage magic. Oh, I took two classes. One where you could do it.
Like you, I drew a Mickey cell or I colored a Mickey cell. And then when I got to, you got to
talk to a performer in the golden horse shoe who showed like how their little like microphone
hidden in their hair works. And then, yeah, we went in the town. So it was nuts. Wow. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I, I marched in the band at Disney world and Epcot, but we didn't get in the tunnels.
And you didn't, well, they all in unison marched through the tunnels to get where you were going.
I think I had the chance. I was like, well, we got one more day in the parks or we could
try one of these tours. Not that they were free. You still had to pay for them,
but like they have those backstage and you can go in the tunnels and the,
I think they went through the tunnels and I think I was just like, ah, one more day in the park.
We got to do stuff and seeing just hallways. Yeah. Yeah. They're cool. Hallways. Yeah. I mean,
I'd love to, I'd love to go there today. Sure. There's a quote in it. They refer to it as a
10 acre cement labyrinth and we should call it there by the real title, the utility door,
the utility door, which is a very cool. It's neat. Yeah. Very cool name. Yeah. Um,
I also read at the top of part two, there's the, uh, notion that people, again, like I said,
I think I'm correct that it was like, uh, like, oh, no, no, no. Oh, I'm sorry. Vietnam and Richard
Nixon were somehow it was like space mountain was a smashing success, but with Vietnam and Richard
Nixon, how are these things related? I understand historical context, but I've never really tied
space mountain to, uh, but before that, I'm sorry, what I was going to say was a re the haunted
mansion that, uh, the notion that we have to get it open because there's a lot of people saying
like, is Walt buried in there? Just that weird house is there. I don't know. Okay. We gotta
get this open and people have to know it's a fun ride, not a tomb for our founder. Uh, going off
of that, cause you mentioned, well, it's at the very end of episode one, you know, you get Bob
Gurr and Roly tearing up talking about, uh, Walt passing away. I thought very interesting stylistic
choice. They were playing Christmas music over people talking about what's death. What were they
playing? They were playing. I came upon a midnight clear. It was the thing. No, I think they were
playing the barking dogs jingle bells, but he did pass around Christmas time. He passed, uh,
the summer 15 and just very, very, you know, I, I just thought it was an interesting filmmaking
choice that like they were, they were, you know, everyone's sad. They're playing instrumental
Christmas music. I hadn't really seen anyone mention that as a melancholy field. Yeah.
Huh. Um, so you get a lot of cool haunted mansion stuff and some of this footage. Yeah. Right at the
top. I mean, you get like footage from those pictures we've seen essentially, like those crazy,
cool old dress, uh, short sleeve dress shirt men fixing robots. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. See it in action,
which is great. Well, and you get young Kurt Russell on a pinstripe and double breasted.
It is a bright blue pinstripe double breasted suit. Adjust the levels. You got too excited.
You're hot and cold today. Hot Kurt Russell and labor unions.
Yeah. I think those are bio. Those are plenty valuable things to get the blood going. Double
breasted. Both relevant in, in 2020 as they were in the, in the sixties. Yeah. Yeah.
Uh, so yeah. And also, uh, so Kim Irvine, who's the Imagineer who, uh, is the daughter of, of the
leota tombs. Correct. Uh, so I mean, she's a cool figure and it's fun to watch her talk about her,
her mother's legacy with this attraction, but also to watch her just like walk through the ballroom
and explain how the effects work and the effect is just working around her in just an unadorned,
like it's just filming her from like, uh, as long as you're in that spot, it just, it looks as good
as, uh, you know, going through in person or shooting a nice unfilm. Um, and then she gets to
be, uh, she gets to be in the ball for the nightmare before Christmas version, which is
very cool. Yeah. I didn't remember. I was like, oh yeah. Yeah. That's really neat. Yeah. I think
she's very endearing and I think her talking about like all the like second generation, like the,
the apprentice, the, the Disney brats are the Imagineering brats and taking over apprentice
shit. Like this is the stuff that I thought what did have a family feel like I was like, oh yeah.
Like they're inventing this as they go along. So like, yeah, train,
you gotta train people how to do it anyway. So there's an LA times article about her, um,
repainting and like restoring the castle with the sleeping beauty castle, Disneyland,
which is really great. Yeah. Uh, and just also you feel really bad for it cause she's so stressed out
about this and doesn't want, cause she's like, talks about the times when the fans have been upset
with her or when they've been upset with things at Disneyland and she's like trying so hard to
get it right. Yeah. And it's like so clear like how much it means to her and it means to like,
yeah, I guess probably like in her mind, her mother and the whole history. And this is in another
episode, but I truly don't understand why you'd like pointedly be upset about the small world
dolls. Oh, why I don't calm down. I mean, I think, I think maybe in the hypothet, like when people
were thinking about it, hypothetically, they were thinking like, there's just going to be a big pooh
bear animatronic amidst the merry style, which would not go necessarily together. So how many
times do we have to do this dance of like, that's going to be awful. Then you see that the Disney
people do it well and it's not awful. Yeah. Well, I think, I think people associate, personalize the,
the parks so much. And when the corporate side, when if it feels like too heavy handed,
and I mean, you, I think you saw it more out here in the nineties and early two thousands of like
some big missteps where the corporate side was too heavy handed, where I do feel like you think it,
we're just doing big ABC ads. Yeah. Yeah. It does feel much more elegant now, although I mean,
they have missteps now, but there's clearly, yeah, there's like respect for the tradition of
things. Yeah. Yeah. A little more. So yeah. I mean, look, everybody gets, everybody likes
getting worked up in general. That's just a fun thing that humans like, because that's it. Yeah.
Hey, if you, if you enjoy it. But I could see where maybe you would think if they were just
going to add the exact same animatronics on a small world that were on like the dark rides, like, oh,
yeah, maybe that'd be weird. So, but they obviously did it very tastefully and yeah, but she, that's,
that's in the article. If you want to look at it, we're sure being stressed out about people being
mad. They also like, they did go to pains to like replicate the Mary Blair style, which is so
particular and beloved. Yeah. One little Mary Blair section is great. And the, the, the section about
yeah, her bold color choices. She threw out the color wheel. We're not just like, well, this goes
with this. She was like, she was bold and dynamic and didn't just stick with like, here's how color
functions and look how it like indelible all those, all those pieces of art are forever. Just took
chances. Madam Lyoto also acknowledged as the first use of projection mapping technology,
which I never, I was like, oh yeah, that's interesting. Yeah, that's true. Did you guys
know I watched some, I watched Christmas in Dollywood, the Hallmark movie. I watched some of it.
Plot point in that is will they get the projection show on the Christmas tree done in time? I was
like, and I'm just sitting there going like, well, clearly they would have figured that out by
fall at the latest. Like just me sitting there. There's no way they would let this timetable,
Dolly is coming that night. They would have it done if she knew she was coming. Who's the Dollywood
version of Bob Chapek? Where is he in this special? I forget. I, well, there is like a scary board
of like the board of Dollywood. It's kind of funny. That's all like a bunch of scenes shot
from the same angles. Like, okay, everybody change clothes back to this. We're gonna film
seven of these scenes in the next four hours. They did get Dolly in three different setups. I was
counting. She finally shows up. Pretty good. Pretty good. Yeah. Yeah. And I just hope there
wasn't any same sex kissing in this damn movie. There's no place that has a lifetime. Oh, I see.
Yeah. It was like, or I think it was lifetime. I think it was at Hallmark. Maybe it was lifetime,
but they're the same, right? They might be both. Which one? Wait, which one wouldn't show the kiss?
It wasn't lifetime. It wasn't Hallmark. Kiss. I forget. Maybe you're right. I don't know. I think
so. Hallmark's a little more like, is it religious? Backwards. Yeah. I think so. Now we're gonna
Google same sex kiss and then whatever. It's also one of those controversies. Mike has content
blockers on his computer. So this might get blocked. Unmute same sex kiss. Lifetime's twinkle
all the way, but with the gay, let's see here. The gay kiss and twinkle all the way could herald a
lifetime Christmas movie revolution. Okay. So this is a positive one. So I think you may be right.
Yeah. I think, oh no, Hallmark was in a commercial and they only showed it once and then three people
complained. You're right. I'm getting all these stories confused. Hallmark channel pulls Zola
ads featuring brides kissing. So that's what you're talking about. All right. Hallmark is
the correct answer. I apologize. And then they went back on it. They did start airing. After
people were honestly annoyed. Oh. All right. All right. I'm not going to say good for them
for restoring it, but yeah. Then what else we get? We get. Epcot? Is this about, or no,
the Florida project keeps developing. Mapo is created. Machine shop is the Mapo machine
shop is created. Yeah. So, so episode two, they're building a Disney world.
Ray Bradbury is looking cool. He's looking like Charles Nelson. So they mention in this,
that opening day of Disney world was not crowded because people were stayed away because they were
worried it would be too crowded. Galaxy's edge. Yep. Phenomenon. Although that was also in
junction with a large ticket increase and restriction of annual passports. That's true too.
Yeah. Well, history repeats itself, but not, but thank God those helicopters blew the ground.
They do. They do not get into any of the Bob Hope festivities at the opening Disney world,
but Bob Hope's very horny jokes. Yeah. Which we may want to declare. We'll do that eventually
this year. Yeah. And a not young comedian named Bob Hope told rooms that they're told jokes that
some of the room and stitches. Yeah. I thought the Bradbury thing, they don't really call it out.
Do that. Like he's just in a shot in a conference room. They mentioned him. Yeah. Okay. Oh, right.
Yeah. Cause they say he wrote the spaceship earth. They don't call out his cool clothes.
His orange bandana. I mean, yeah. He's the one who writes the thing about Peter Pan.
Yes. He, yeah. He had a lot of connections. He wrote the story about flying that Tony always tells.
Right. And he's dressed like a Dan Aykroyd as Liberace manager behind the candle. Also
coming from glasses from the, we got to go on that Liberace tour in Vegas. Oh,
where the weird guy picks you up on a limo. Wow. I don't know if we do. I'll do it. I'll do it.
And we'll talk about it. I was surprised thinking about, um, Disney never adapted Bradbury's book,
dandelion wine, which is one of my favorite books is about a boy having like one magical summer.
Like that seems tailor made for Disney. And in fact, no one has adapted it. Like the Wikipedia
said the rights were being, someone was trying to get it off the ground in 2011,
but it's I'm shocked. It was never made. I've never read it. Maybe Jason Sheridan is the one
to bring it to the screen. Maybe. Um, uh, uh, yeah. Roy dies around here. Roy, they keep saying it's
was four or five years where the best years of his life, you know, cause he started, I started
working in a magic. He was usually just on the office sweating it out, but now he was trying to
get, he was actually getting in the mix with imaginary and he was loving it. And the sweating
went to silver Fox card Walker, E card Walker. That's right. Big Texas guy is I I'm, I'm forgetting
how attractive E card Walker was. Let me look them up here. He wasn't kind of attractive. I book
silver Fox. Yeah. That white poppy kind of thing. A gray hair attractive man. Not the most attractive.
Kind of grizzled looking. We all attract to the different.
All the questions, only this podcast. David Brinkley. David Brinkley. Was David Brinkley
the first to appear? I love the news footage clips throughout these episodes of like the anchors
going like, well, the happiest place on earth was sad today as like the very cumbersome dialogue.
Was David Brinkley hot? I'm looking.
I there's a, there's a, I think in the Jason Sheridan style of hot men. And I mean that of
like your ideal, you said once it would be like your man, your ideal man would be like a Charles
Groton type. I think that you said Elliot Gould. I think we're most saying around the 70s. And you
said Charles Groton. I think you said him now over 75. He said that I think you could say
E. Card Walker and David Brinkley definitely hot. They got it. He could get E. Card Walker could
get it. Walker can get it. Epcot. They refer to future world as an industry trade show.
Did you catch that? Like that, that was interesting. I don't know why that, that, that stuck in my mind.
I was like, Oh, I guess I see what they're saying. I kind of see what they're saying. It makes sense.
It is. It does kind of a low world's fair, low rent way to describe it. But yeah.
I don't have a lot to say about the Epcot stuff, but you know,
love watching them put that together. Old, old creation of Epcot footage. Oh man.
I think they nailed one of the issues with Epcot inadvertently. When someone says,
as soon as people have this stuff at home, we have to move beyond that.
And certainly one of the issues with Epcot over the last 20 years is like
not moving beyond stuff quick enough. Yeah. Yeah. They can't put, yeah, things that change
with the times because they're never going to do it. Just don't try to do that. Do stuff that's
there. You know, you're going to build it once and never change it. So just keep, uh, this happened
to the whole history of the company. And they're going to be the play pavilion will have
supposedly things they'll change out and they'll never change. Yeah. Yeah. They put in there the
first time it'll be there for 15 to 25 years. So the future podcast, the ride type people will
be like, I love it. It's weird. So 20, 21. Yeah. Oh man. Remember onward.
The play pavilion had an onward experience for 25 years.
That's the movie, right? That's the movie. That's yeah. Yeah. That's the new like hip, uh,
Chris Pratt and remember Quibi generation one now, of course it's a tenant of Howard entertained
became self-aware and it's our president. Now the country thrived under president Quibi.
Oh boy.
Could be a silver Fox now. Oh boy. Is Quibi hot? Can Quibi get it? Yes.
Can Quibi get it fam? Um, I, the Tokyo Disney, I mean, if it's more an Epcot, tell me. Uh,
no, no, I like all that. Tokyo Disney school. Uh, uh, I like watching the Japanese engineer
at the blues named Daniel or his last name. Uh, but like, uh, just generally like presenting
why things were important, uh, culturally. And, uh, um, I mean, it's, it's in a subsequent episode,
but him talking about the, uh, what is it? The sort of hurricane or a tsunami, the tsunami,
the earthquake. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That's all very touching later. Oh yeah. He's an interesting, uh, figure. Yeah. Also like,
I don't recall seeing a lot of old, I mean, we've all watched a lot of old specials about Disney
world and Disneyland, but I don't recall seeing a lot of like archival Tokyo stuff. No. I didn't
really wasn't quite aware of what was going on. I remember seeing pictures and thinking it was
similar ish, but in the nineties, anytime they would cut the parks around the world, it was
either Disneyland or they were really pushing Paris. Yeah. Right. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. I didn't
know. Well, personally, cause that at the time that park is just such a clone of, of magic kingdoms
is not in the, it's the first castle that wasn't different. Right. Like let's just show there,
but I liked all this stuff about, like, you know, it's, it is, it was weird at the time in Tokyo
to have a place where you could go dancing street and be silly and, uh, uh, uh, just realizing what
a cultural outlier it was. The, the myth making in this, oh, just like feeling like they got one
over on the Oriental land company. It's like, well, tell them we'll do it if they pay for everything.
Yeah. And it's like, they went for it. And it's like, they still feels like they're going like,
we got one over on a, we got them. Like tell Japan to stop calling. Yeah. We're going to do that.
Yeah. What was the actual, the terms of the deal they claim? They, the, they would get the full
designs, full licensing, full Disney, everything. Imagineering, the Oriental land company would
have to pay for everything. Right. But then they own the parks essentially. Pretty much. Right.
It's a terrible deal. I don't know why it happened, but thank God it happened. I think it is a bad,
wonderful parks out of it. It seems like a deal that we never make today. I think they needed
money. And I think like the second episode, a lot of the theme of it seems to be like, well,
we did some good stuff, but we're the company was rudderless until like people like John Hench or
like Roy had to step up and take charge of stuff. Sure. But a lot of those older people are older
in the seventies and are starting to pass. So they end up rudderless again. And this Ron Miller,
this dork, you're not, he can't get it. Yeah. He was an okay looking guy.
For me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And anonymously handsome. And I got too loud. Too loud.
I got too loud. Defending attractiveness of front. Hey, this is a joke, but you're too far.
With men is all Disney, you know, CEOs and presidents.
Ron Miller was a very like football playery, like Johnny Unitas kind of a look. Yeah. Yeah.
But the, you know, the films are getting boring. There's corporate marauders.
Crazy to think about though, that Tokyo Disney and Epcot open within six months to each other,
within at least a year, similar later on to California adventure in Tokyo, Disney,
see, but less of a quality. Yeah. They're both the most beautiful places in the world.
God bless that early eighties. It's also, it's a bummer that you always have to see for me that I
always have to see Tron presented as like the nadir of, of the company and it's box office.
When Tron is so beautiful, but it's not the movies. It's a bad boy movie. I try every few years.
All the way through. It's really rough. Yeah. And I think you don't, I think with something like
Disney plus just go watch light bikes and watch the discs and travel into the Tron world. And
I mean, I think the aesthetics had a huge influence. Oh, I also think the aesthetics of
Tron legacy, like kind of that sort of blue. Yeah. Like I think that has aged very well compared to
other CGI stuff from the 2010s. Yeah. Yeah. But then also it's the same thing, like kind of born,
dreadfully boring movie. Yeah. But beautiful. But so then we have the cliffhanger, a better cliffhanger
than any Mandalorian episode. The tease of it's 84, we're on the brink of disaster. I mean,
I was just cootin' and hollerin'. I mean, it was sad to hear Cardwalker retire. And of course,
I hope he had a good retirement. But who's coming? But cootin' and hollerin'. What a hero. Thunder in
the distance. They say the direction would be determined by the next CEO. Oh, oh, it's so
exciting you think it's going to say created by Vince Gilligan at that moment. So yeah, hell of
a cliffhanger. And then scene one, next week, our man arrives. Our man. The Midas Touch. The Midas Touch.
I love that. Let's acknowledge that I have on record is to look, God bless you, Kevin,
in defunct land, but you're too hard on the man. You got to acknowledge that he had the Midas Touch.
He did, yes. You don't talk about when Jordan was on the Wizards. You talk about when Jordan was on
the Bulls twice. Michael Eisner's here. And let's not forget Frank Wells. I mean, I think a big,
a big part of Eisner's success. Yeah. The yin to his yang. The yin to the len into his McCartney.
That's right. You know? Well, and they show the mirror between that Walt and Roy vibe. I think
that's what we're, there was the crazy one and the guy reigning a man. The Riggs and Murtaugh.
There's so many films. The Hobbs and Shaw, I assume. I don't know the dynamic between Hobbs and Shaw,
but I bet it's exactly like Eisner and Wells. Yeah. The biggest memory hole in the whole documentary.
Jeffrey Katzenberg often cited as the third man because he helped revive Disney animation is not
uttered in this. And granted, everything was siloed, much more siloed back then, I think.
But those characters, it was animated like Lion King, Aladdin, Little Mermaid. Like they didn't
get rides immediately, but they would show up in the parades. They show up at character meet and
greets pretty quickly. Katzenberg nowhere to be found in this. Yeah. But he'll get mentioned in
the six part Shrek 4D saga. Oh, sure. On Universal Plus in a little while. Right. It'll happen.
But yeah, they don't want, there's still, I don't know what the relationship is between
Iger and him, but there was a lot of bad blood between. Oh yeah. Eisner and Katzenberg. Sure.
So yeah, I wonder if. Dream jerks. You don't come back from that. No, that's the ultimate dis.
Shots fired. So yeah, I was surprised they didn't even like initially mention him.
Yeah. You would think they would have maybe just like said the three of them came in and helped to
do it and then just talked about Wells and Eisner because they were parks focused. They shared a
picture of Michael Jackson and they mentioned Song of the South and not the Jeffrey Katz.
But the most canceled thing is Jeffrey Katzenberg. I would rather talk about those two things.
Lasseter's in a bunch of it. Yeah. Katzenberg is the most erased. Yeah, it is. That's how deep
the wound still goes, I guess. Eisner was like, I will only do an interview here if we don't talk
about Katzenberg at all. One drop of footage. Yeah. So, hey, but you know, let's give Frank Wells some
silver fucks. Frank Wells can't get it. Yeah. I think we can all agree on that. Boy, the vibe
that's broadcast about that guy, he seems great. What a cool guy. This mountain climbing.
The myth making about him, whether, yeah, true. It does seem like he's like a kind of a cool,
collected guy who likes to do fun, crazy stuff, but also very reasonable and grounded. And yeah,
they really, they make him sound great. Yeah. And yeah, as a kid, I was not, I didn't know who he
was. Yeah. Yeah. He was the, he was the boring part of the annual report that I skipped through.
But I didn't know him. Yeah. Well, he didn't introduce himself on television.
There should have been one where he did. Oh, that would have been fun. Mix it up. Yeah. Yeah. Hello.
He says hi. Yeah. Yeah. He can't find Michael. Like a honey, I shrunk the kid's one. It's like,
has anyone seen Michael? And he's like, I'm down here, Frank. That's great. Why didn't they,
I can't believe they didn't do it when we're he shrunk. Yeah. Oh man. That's what we should do
is just mentally go backwards to different films. And we should use like the, the footage,
like the de-aging footage that they've used in Marvel and Star Wars and stuff and make a new
Eisner. We'll shoot it with them and make one where he shrinks and we can't find him. It'll be the
intro to our next live show. To make, I mean, that's a lofty goal to make a new Eisner intro.
Wow. With us. Oh boy. That's the, you know, the dream when Eddie Murphy hosted SNL and some of
those cast members are like, I grew up with him and now I get to be in a sketch with him in his
studio. That's how we would feel being in a, an Eisner intro. Gosh, that would be great. I think
we'll probably have to just work on getting a 15 minute interview first. That's probably the
initial thing we should work on. Yeah. We'll see. Did Marin have him on you?
I don't think Marin has had him on. He's probably been on some weird podcast that we've never heard
of. That would be my guess. He may have been on Alec Baldwin's podcast. Oh really? Maybe. Possibly.
That makes sense. Eisner and Wells described as outsiders coming on board, which is so funny in
modern perspective. Cause I feel like now if you talk about a Disney outsider, that's like,
you don't have an MBA from an Ivy. I feel like I heard someone recently at a party was like,
yeah, Disney mostly hires, you have to have an MBA ideally from an Ivy to get hired there of like,
no, for like executive level of like a certain above a certain level. Right.
Is that a surprise though? It seems like not really, no, it was more bummer than a surprise.
Who should they hire? Huh? I don't know anyone. I mean, the whole history of this is that they
hired schmucks. They like just guys, like just guys who were, you're saying they were called
outsiders, but they're not really outsiders. No, no. They were like movie studio executives.
Right. They would have worked in the entertainment industry forever. So like the idea that they were
like Disney outsiders was like, well, maybe they didn't know the company that well. But I guess at
the time they weren't like the, like the, that it's all that it's Disney's son-in-law.
I guess that's true. It's always been like, yeah, yeah. That they would, it was, it did seem like
sacrilege, I think to people that this guy had like, yeah, worked at another studio and now he's
going to come here and treat Disney like a regular movie studio. And he's like, yeah,
make it like the biggest one. Right. In hindsight, of course. Yes. Yeah. But like,
yeah, I guess, I guess at the time, yeah, probably people like his name isn't Disney.
Yes. He's not married to it. This should be like the Royals. Right. Yeah. It has to be,
I guess, yeah, I guess people, people have always been weird about that company in that way.
That's why it's good that the Trump organization does it the way it's supposed to be done.
Family. Family first. Yeah. How else will we know if the people are any good? Right. They have to
come from the same bloodline. Yes. And that is the best bloodline. A perfect bloodline. A real
wonderful, wonderful bloodline. So it's a very dramatic moment. The patio meeting where everybody
summoned outside, like the new CEO is finally going to come talk to Imagineering. And this is
probably the moment where he lets us all go. And it says, he said, instead, he says that with your
what consider you the heart of the company. Yeah. And it ushers in this incredible new era. Oh,
yes. Because they said they went from 3000 people to 400 people after the projects had finished.
Yeah. Downsizing and building the new parks. And it's that is great. I mean, I who knows exactly
if that's all perfectly how they say it went down. But from reading stuff, that does seem like at the
very least, that was the gist of what people were feeling in Imagineering. Yeah. Of like, we may all
just get like fired. We may, this thing may go away. Yeah. Which is crazy. We built the last
things we had to build. Yeah. It's like we're not doing any more parks. I think that's a phrase said,
or maybe is that said after the end of this? That's said at the end of this. Sorry. Yeah.
It's crazy it ended up at that point. But it feels like that's the tone here too. Like, well,
that might just be it. We built it and people will maintain it and we won't really add anything. Yeah.
Yeah. Thank God. But instead what you get, this is the, this story really is the prequel to
something we've certainly been over and got to do with the man himself. The hallowed Tony Baxter
meeting with Michael Eisner, Breck Eisner, which has relived in this. We've certainly gotten to
talk about that before, but what a, if truly this is how this played out where Star Tours and Splash
Mountain are approved in the same meeting and this sort of dovetail, that's sort of the intro. Tony
tells all that and then you get to go find out about Tony and then you watch footage of him as a
kid and what a dork he is. Yeah. What just a big goofy dorky smile he's got and you, you watch that
old footage of him. He's one of us. He was like the way we feel about the parks now. That's how
he felt growing up with him. What ride is he on? There's a footage of him in the park. Flying
saucers. And I'd never seen that before. I've seen the, you know, some of the footage of him
in Imagineering and those old pictures, but yeah, I actually see him on the ride. I assume not working
there yet. How young is he in that footage? He looks young. I think he's a kid. Yeah. Yeah.
It's valuable to have that now that people are like, this is, I think some normies have watched
Imagineering story and it's been cool to go like, so the guy in that Star Tour, who like did,
thought of Star Tours and Splash Mountain a big time. That's, we've been on our podcast.
We aren't just wasting time. Well, I mean, we're cool people on the thing. Hearing them do the Breck
stuff in this Imagineering documentary, which is the stuff we heard on a season pass for the first
time, but we talked about it a lot on our show too. It was just so validating to see that in the real
world. Like I was watching my parents and I'm like, the thing we talked about, the thing there. We
beat them to it. And like, yeah, this is a story with Mass Appeal. And then I'm just cootin' and
hollering when adult Tony's scooping ice cream and taking a big old bite out of it. Like I'm just
like, yes, yeah. Reassert, go back to your home. He's an instant king at home again.
Scoop on, King. Scoop on. Took a big old chomp. Hell yeah. A big old chomp. Then you get to see
star speeders being airlifted in the roof. That is so damn cool. You get to see Anthony Daniels
recording VO. And in the VO, does he not say star ride? Yes, he does. He says star rides. So they
recorded some audio where he said, because if you haven't heard this, there was a time where they
weren't going to call it Star Tours. Michael Eisner wanted Star Ride, which we've been praising
a bunch. That is very stupid. But they acknowledge that in the documentary that Frank Wells will say
like, hey, maybe back off that idea, but this idea is good. Tony says something along the lines of
Michael Eisner had really great ideas, OK ideas, and some horrible ideas. He said really ugly,
really ugly ideas. And Star Ride certainly among them. But Star Ride got far enough that Anthony
Daniels in a booth. Oh my God. Literally someone outside the booth going, well, let's just have it
just in case. That was my question. Is there a version of it where they did it both in the same
thing or do they bring them back? I don't know. Yeah, we don't know. Did they have to do reshoots
as it were to change up the Star Wars narrative? Disneyland, they mentioned Disneyland opened for
60 hours straight when Star Tours opened. I always forget about that. 60 hours straight.
Geez. Just because of, yeah, people are so crazed for it. And then in my favorite piece of filmmaking
in the recent past, in my personal once upon a time in Hollywood, we get the vibe that I want
so hard where we're talking about how the park has now, we've doubled the budget on theme parks.
Yeah, people are staying for, it's open for 60 hours. They raise the prices of people who's
coming more than ever. It is, it's going so well. And that there's like this great postcard that
opens. You're watching my favorite shot in the entire thing. Pink sky with monorail going by.
We talk about Videopolis. We talk about EO. Great old photo of Carrie Fisher and Mark Hamill
at Florida Star Tours. This little, oh, fireworks going off above Videopolis. This is a wonderful,
this is my favorite documentary is just that. Just that. That's what I would nominate for the
Academy Awards. Everything is possible at that point in life. Yeah. For me, yes. I'm, you know,
what, you know, four to six, it's all in front of me. Disneyland is better than it's ever been.
It's only going to keep getting better. Yeah. It's pure optimism. They say running theme of how do
you top this? What's the next thing? Walt only cared about tomorrow. Like, and then, and then
a ticket price increase of 30%. That's the time. And it works. But that works. That works. It did
not work for Galaxy. No, no, no, no, finally did. But the, you know, it does show you what a, like
the, it's such like, uh, it is like a boogie nights montage. It's them like, it's when things are good
and it's the like, we're doing the dance. And then they, they talk about like, well, how are we
top ourselves? It's probably in a good place to do. That's where you want to be where we have to
top ourselves. And then they did with Indiana Jones and then they stopped topping themselves.
And then I hit puberty and it all fell apart. Me personally and theme, but they dovetailed
and the Simpsons got bad and Seinfeld ended. It all happened at one time. Hey, we got MGM studios
around then too. They had that great footage of the ladies coming off the ride going, oh,
Daisy really topped themselves. Yes. Uh, some great B roll footage. They say that MGM studios,
they're like, they were saying that the park was going to be a half day park or whatever. And then
every time Michael Iser would come in, he would add another thing or say, let's do that. Or
somebody would present him another ride and go, yeah, put that in. And they made it a full like
size thing by the end of the project. It sounds like the greatest time. MGMC is one opened first
few years were just the greatest. I loved it. It's just the way Tony taught. I mean,
then these interviews on season pass podcast, check it out. There's like nine interviews with
Tony or eight or something. He talks about this time like we're describing it. He talks about it
with such nostalgia and seemingly like the best, maybe the best time of his career and was during
this time. And who, like we go, we go and follow Imagineers into a ride that's important to them
or that's kind of their ride. Tony is four. Yeah. And he had Jones, Big Thunder, Star Tours,
Splash Mountain. Insane. God, how great does he come off in this? Yeah. Hopefully more stuff even
with him too. Cause as we've listened to all these interviews, there's so much stuff from a,
obviously from a lifetime in Imagineering. I mean, they get him talking about his ideas of designing
for the 20th ride, not the first ride. Yeah. Yeah. And it's big three rule of like, it takes
you to a place you can't go without the Disney park. There's a thrill nature. He's basically
saying close to death, but as close to death as you can and the emotional. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. All that stuff's great. This is probably the best episode is three. Oh yeah. Oh baby. Oh,
I have watched six. Give me that pink sky and that monorail. That's like the optimism.
Who knows what the nineties will be. It's all going to be great. I could see somebody ripping
this and just putting it on like an MP3 and I would listen to it in my car. It's so pleasant.
Yeah. Re-watching this one. And then, and also in this, you have the, I realized with that
nod to song of the south, that is the only song of the south footage on Disney plus.
Oh yeah. Good point. Film is not. Good point. Yeah. If you want to see any of it,
here's your two shots. Yeah. Splash Mountain, early days Splash Mountain footage is always
so wonderful watching Eisner flip a big switch. Oh yeah. Rare characters. A giant lever, I guess.
Yeah. A big lever. And then I don't want to jump around too much, but the, you know, I mean,
then the crux of this becomes, we get a lot of Euro Disney, but watching him
speak French to open the park. Oh, that was the greatest. Oh man. I do, I really laughed at the
phrase French communists throwing eggs at Eisner. Like that is, that's pretty funny. So yeah, so
what happens is they're at this, it's before the park is open and they're announcing things. And
Eisner is on stage with Scrooge McDuck and protesters. Why did they pick Scrooge?
Protestors are throwing eggs. Oh, it was the stock, didn't it, wasn't it traded on the French
stock exchange? Was that what it was? Oh, maybe. And Scrooge is the wealthy character? So they get to put
Scrooge and Eisner and they're getting pelted with eggs and Eisner and then somebody has to like
shuffle Scrooge off very closely, quickly. I mean, so yeah, Eisner and Scrooge had a bad day because
they do, and this, they address like French people being like, what the fuck is this shit?
Like, this is going to ruin our culture. This is like American commercialism. And these, we've
certainly heard all of these stories many times, but to see an official Disney product acknowledge
that phrase cultural Chernobyl and all that. Yeah. Yeah. To acknowledge any of the failures. I mean,
it's coming up. We'll, we'll cover this next time, but the, you know, when they, they truly
shit on Hong Kong Disneyland and they truly shit on Disney studios, Paris, and these are parks that
are open. You can go there. These are current products of theirs that they are saying, like,
especially Disney Studios Paris, they say it's so ugly that an Imagineer didn't know they were in
the park already. That's, that is bold of them to put this out. It is funny that we're praising
Disney for just the basic acknowledgement of the truth. Yeah. It speaks to Disney for being such a
controlling entity that we are praising. It's surprising. Yeah. Yeah. And even any day,
the big shadow organizations acknowledging the truth in any way is very rare these days. So that's
a little, yes, a little something. Yeah. They, they kind of were pretty cumbersome going into Euro
Disney. And what was the original, like they, the surveyors are like people where they're like,
where should we build this? And they came back and like, there's a bunch of land in Spain. Yeah. And
Michaelizer went, I want to go to Paris. Like there's some story like that. It does seem like
it was his pretension. Yeah. He was riding too high. Yeah. I like it. But understand it. But
it shows you what a good, how good a job they did phrasing framing. This is a story where you have
your like your party days montage. And then like, what happens after that? Things just keep getting
better and better. Now people start getting a little weird, a little overreach. Somebody dies,
just like little bill and boogie. This episode is boogie. Oh my God. You're right.
Jesus. It changes. It gets crazy. Wow. You're right. That's new year's Eve. It's new year's
Eve every night at pleasure Island. Oh no. Oh no. This is this episode three is boogie.
You're really single too. It was rough. Just like,
Turks. You got the touch. They wouldn't give them the tape. They wouldn't give them the tapes.
Oh Michael. You know, it's funny as we're saying that I am realizing, you know, at the very start
of the episode, we were talking about the five week long animator strike. And now we're talking
about the French rebelling against Disney. France has been like Paris has been in a general strike
for weeks now. Like, and I think it may have gone longer than the animator strike at this point.
It's just now occurring to me. Five weeks. That's the French. I mean, that's just the French are
mobilized more. So I don't quite know that they were so shocked that that happens.
What is actually more shocking? What's more shocking to me, even then them not thinking that
it's shocking to me, they would think that Paris is the place for this just culturally. It's crazy.
Yeah. But even more shocking and they bring it up in the special is that you couldn't get wine
everywhere. Yeah. Like Paris. Yeah. Do the, the stereotype, right? They do all, they do all of
their homework about everything where they don't want to make something that like looks too much
like the castle architecture of Europe. They made, they do all of this research on what the culture
is like. They don't like this kind of ghost in this country. Right. They're like, Tony explains
that they don't like comedic ghosts in Europe, which I don't, is that like, huh? Huh? Yeah.
I guess whatever. Like they did some sort of research, whether it's true or not,
but I guess they were trying to be like no alcohol in the magic kingdom.
I guess it was following up on that. I guess. Yes. But you would think let's throw these French
people a bone. Like, yes. Yeah. If they're going to dinner, there's not a single restaurant where
you can't drink wine in Paris or in the surrounding area. And another thing we know about Paris is they
love great food and they decided to build a park that still has no great food. I could be wrong.
Maybe somebody sat in that Ratatouille restaurant, but boy, my experience is like the worst food in
a Disney bar ever, ever, ever. It feels like you went right at the worst point of Disney Paris.
Yeah. It feels like there was at least, I'm not saying they knew they were like figuring out how
to fix it. You went right before they decided to turn some stuff around. Like they renovated
Fanta Manor. They renovated a couple other things and now they're doing a lot to the studios.
Fanta Manor was fine. I got no complaints about that. I'm just saying it seems like there's a
influx of energy. For context, this was December 2014. If anybody agrees with that, that I was
there in the worst possible time I may have been. Did you go on Ratatouille? Yeah. Oh, okay. Yes.
So at the very least that. That was great, but it doesn't save the park by any means. Especially
that park. Oh my God. Yeah. I mean, so they're going to have Galaxy's Edge and that'll be a
whole other thing, but like, and Frozen and that big lake. That park's probably going to get fixed.
It's not a full Galaxy's Edge. Is that right? What? Oh no. What? Boo. Oh, what are you doing?
They're getting Marvel stuff there too, right? Yeah. They might get the ride.
They're getting the same Rock and Roller Coaster. I don't think they're even changing the track.
I think they're re-theming the Rock and Roller Coaster. Yeah. You talk amongst yourselves really
quickly while I look this up. So Isner admits mistakes in Paris and that's also cool of him
to just to say, he does just say, we screwed up too many hotel rooms, too much money spent.
That is a thing. You walk around there and like, maybe now they sell out the entire thing,
but they were thinking, oh, it's Disney World. We just added a ton of hotels in Disney World.
We got to do the same thing here. So two, man, like just seven hotels. And I think they were
at like 40% occupancy for a long time and, and they aren't that good. It's like a lesser
yacht and beach club. It's the New York one is real cheesy. They just aren't great.
Well, and culturally Europeans get much longer summer holidays and they run a lot of deals to
get them to come to Florida. Sure. So they kind of were cannibalizing their own business a little
too. Yeah. Yeah. It is not as big as the regular galaxies that I was trying to figure out if it's
what the ride is right now. Idiots. They announce it might be, it looks like it might just be the
Millennium Falcon. Oh my God. That's so stupid. What are you doing? I could be wrong. They can't,
they can't. That's a bit, that's the biggest mistake. Paris. They've said what's the ride is.
It's just a Falcon, but they've tripled the size of the Cantina. Now they're catering to the European audience.
That would be something. I don't know. That's not bad. And you can buy coaxium. You can take it home.
Coaxium. Coaxium. Now would you like to hear more about coaxium? Yes, please.
Here's where it comes from. Yes, please, Hondo. Mine from the Southern region of,
um. So this is the, this is where, like this is, this is Eisner and Tony's episode. Like they really
give both those guys their time to shine. This is where Tony really gets to delve into big
thunder mountain stuff because they got to go so crazy with it in Paris and expand it. I really
like that framing. Again, not chronological, but it's cool being that it's kind of the center
of frontier land and one of the most epic parts and successful parts of Disneyland Paris. So then
they get to explain how it was Tony's baby. And then this was like the ultimate apex of it. And
that quote about fourth times the charm. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That was a great job. Great job, Tony.
And then Frank Dyson. And then Frank Dyson, which is also factors into, I mean, any like the waking,
sleeping beauty covers the same beats and like, boy, it seems like it just gutted the company.
Like, uh, yeah. And very, I like watching Eisner give that, uh, that, um, the, uh,
the eulogy. Yeah. I like, yeah. Very, yeah, that's brutal. It is weirdly cyclical because the first
time it happens, Walt dies and then Roy O Disney dies. And then later on Frank dies. And it's these
people, people have been given so much power and so much responsibility. And then I don't know,
it feels like it's more distributed now. Like I can't think of anyone at Disney now. If they were
like, Iger or to pass away, they would slot somewhat in. He probably, you know, the thing
that obviously that all those three have in common is that they, or maybe, you know, was Roy still
working when he died? I don't remember. I think so. Wasn't it? I think so. I think so. Right. Um,
but like, yeah, these are all people that die while they're on the job, which is like in the
middle of something kind of, not kind of unexpectedly, like people sort of knew Walt was on the way up,
but Walt didn't really tell many people about it. Yeah. Everyone always tells the story of like,
he came around the offices and like said, thank you or something. But I don't, I think he did like
spiritual or like sentimental things. I don't think he, he didn't leave projects in order.
Right. It seems like Roy left more pro Roy at least got, didn't really get Disney world open and
then die pretty soon after that. That's right. Yeah. Which also adds to like sort of that story
being so, I don't know, sad or interesting. So who, if this were cyclical, is there anyone now who
would gut the company so thoroughly? I don't know. I mean, it's interesting. Jason's saying, and I
think he's right that probably like the corporate structure is such that, uh, you know, this thing's
a machine of some kind that like it could lose a part and the thing would still roll. Well, there
is a major figure who is not dead, but he's dead to Disney. Well, yeah. I certain Hawaiian shirt.
I know what you're talking about. I was thinking about it the other day about like, cause he was
in charge. We're talking with the man who won't be named. Uh, he was in charge of the parks.
So I do wonder what does it look like if he was like a human being who could have just, you know,
interacted with human beings on a regular level, could have hugged his wife only,
could have just hugged his wife and has been nice to other women. Instituted a culture of fear while
he's like selling a cult. Look, it's a cultural innovation. Anyone can give notes. And it's like,
um, but I do wonder like, what is a galaxy's edge look like budget wise if he's still around?
Like, so maybe this is the, they would never acknowledge this in the story, but is, yeah,
is our current Wells dying? The, the, uh, I, this is a complicated question and maybe it's too much
to unlock right now, but I've been thinking about it. Like when you're talking about like the
successes of the Eisner era in the parks, you're talking about Cars Land and obviously DCA, but
Cars Land is the man who we're talking about baby and pushed for an insane budget. Like I'm
all of California venture, uh, getting that, uh, that huge plus up. Yes. So I wonder,
I don't have the answers to this, but I do wonder, cause that's the best thing you can say about
Eiger is that, is that renovation? What does newer stuff look like budget wise if he's in charge
versus JPEC was much more of a spreadsheet business guy. Yeah. I think the biggest person
at Disney right now that they would feel if you left is Kevin Feige at Marvel. Movie wise.
Yeah. But I think you'll have some parks influence a little more with, yeah, I think, by the way,
I think put him in charge of the parks. Yeah. He's got too many things to be in charge. He's
going to be in charge of star wars. He's going to show on the same sense. He's going to fix it.
Yeah. Um, but yeah, I, for sure that I agree with what you're saying about that, but as far as,
yeah, in just like the park structure and yeah, I don't know. I don't know. Eiger doesn't seem to be
that into the parks. The most excited I've seen him is when the NBA experience opened
and he was like, you could tell he was like an NBA fan and he was very excited about it.
And not addressed in this special, uh, the, uh, not the NBA experience, not addressed in this series.
They don't know. It seemed to widely be called one of the biggest Disney blunders in years.
Really? Yeah. Cause it was, we almost, we could have gotten in for free. We were told.
Like they were, yeah, yeah, we're going to Epcot. I don't know. Some days it's like, wow,
we had 100 guests today. Things like this never do well. Anything. It's like the NASCAR zone. It's
never hurt. Why do you, why does anyone ever think that's going to do well? If it's free and it's a
restaurant and bar. Yeah. Yeah. But I think, yeah, I think they just, I don't know. It's still open,
but I don't, unless something's changed, but like last we checked a month or two ago, it was like,
the employees were just sadly dribbling a basketball all day, not talking to anyone.
Yeah. So, but I, yeah, it's interesting. It's interesting to think about this type of thing.
Cause it is, again, we were saying like these companies feel like, well now like Disney can
never go away, but it is like, you could install a couple of different people in different roles and
they could totally ruin it. It could happen. Like it's not out of the question that, that stuff
can really drastically change in the course of a few years. What we're seeing with the country,
how you install the wrong people and maybe it won't be around for, things aren't set for.
So yeah, we'll, we'll see. I mean, everything on the horizon for the most part looks good
for the parks, I would say. Yeah. Yeah. But we'll see. I mean, I don't like, well, I think people
would agree. It's weird that like Eiger is the hero of this thing. He has overseen a good era.
I think they're giving him too much credit in this thing, but you know, he's approved spending
in parks. He's, he's, he's such a good, he's such a good businessman. So it's like,
Eisner feels more hands on with all of this stuff. It's not that he had the best ideas,
but it did feel like he was working where it's like Eiger buys star Wars. He buys Marvel,
who is, which is already cooking. He bought, he like, he, he fixed the Pixar. He installs
the Pixar people who seem to have been in a better groove than their own animation. And they
are overseeing all the movies too. Yeah. And then, yeah. So he's like saying, here's what your ride
should be called or, yeah, he's not getting in the mix there, but at the very least he's just like,
well, we'll see that's doing well by it. Yeah. So it is a benign figure that is approving money
that goes to things that we like. He is sort of ensuring the future of the company, but not doing
it internally. He's not having it grow from the inside. He's attaching external things to it,
which to be fair to him is the, what's, what's going on with every company. Yeah. It is like
some other giant telecom would have bought Marvel or star Wars. Like that would have happened. So
you can't be mad at him completely for being a creature of that, but it does feel a little less
homegrown, which I know is also like, who gives a shit? What does that matter?
Especially as we talk about an episode where it's like we put star Wars in the park and it was
great and everybody loved it. But it does feel like Eisner, it would, yeah, the, there is a feeling
of it coming from inside as opposed to outside. There is a feeling I have about it and I don't
know if that's fake or I don't know what that is. I mean, I think this chapter seems to be like the,
the like nitrous hitting the engine for Imagineering, like really hitting a stride,
couple generations in people doing it, who grew up with it, passionate, the passion is there and the
money is there and the follow through is there. Yeah. And I think I would be interested to know
what people now in Imagineering are saying, cause they have so many projects. They are pumping tons
of money into Florida. Like they're doing Marvel stuff. They're doing stuff in Tokyo. They're
building a couple of different. Hong Kong, they're changing the castle. Yeah. So I wonder if it's a
feeling now where it is like that again, where everyone does feel like it's busy and you can get
stuff approved or is it just still, is it still kind of a little restrictive in the sense that
it's all movies? I wonder, I don't know. Yeah. Is that IP thing a problem or I don't know,
but I give them toy, it gets money and toys to play with. Yeah. Yeah. At the very least stuff is
going on there and it was not the case a decade ago. Yeah. Well, I mean the sort of the cliffhanger
of this part three is kind of that, like after the failure of Paris initially, we got to like
get things back on track and there's weird, like maybe theming is out the door. Maybe we don't do
parks anymore. We don't do parks anymore. It's a, that's a heavy one, but you know, hey, we know
what happened to things picked up and we get a lot of fun in part four because part four is
our beloved superstar limo. Yeah. And a different superstar imagineer or T5. Four. No, he's four.
He shows up in a couple, I think. I guess he's in four and five. Yeah. Has some very successful
endeavors. Yeah. So yeah, so that's a tease now for next, what are we doing this next month?
I guess maybe. Yeah, I think so. Coming soon. Yeah. Second half of Imagineering Story. So you
survived some of what has been the one of the lesser comedic episodes of Podcasts, right?
We were just, there was a lot of analysis and stuff. Old man getting it. That was funny, right?
Yeah. Oh, that's funny. I think there were funny things. I would say like,
sometimes we get a little analytical, but that's what we're allowed to do. I like that. People
asked for this. Yeah, yeah. Absolutely. This is your fault. No, I had a great time. No,
I'm saying it's a thing that's on the table that we can do. We don't have to be, you know, Mr. Bit.
All the damn time. It's exhausting. Yeah. But so, hey, plus us up as I said a while ago,
hashtag plus us up. Tell us something you want us to watch on Disney Plus. But in the meantime,
we're going to do a part two of this. We'll talk about episodes four, five and six of Imagineering
Story. It's stuff we liked and we're really, we're going to have a lot of fun, right? Yeah.
Right. Yeah. Okay. Well, then that'll do it. And I'm like looking for one more thing, but I don't
know if I have it. Tell us which CEO you think can get it. Not just CEOs, but presidents, higher up
figures in general. Yeah. Yeah. Like vice or higher, I'd say. Right. And David newscasters,
like David Brinkley, reporters, Peter Jennings. Do we like, and what is the hottest age Charles
Groton was ever at? Is it this age or is it when he was younger? It is probably, I would guess
probably like modern life or real life. What is it called? The Brooks movie. Yeah. Real life.
Modern romance. Yeah. That's why I was transposing. That's what you're talking about. No real life.
You're like, yeah, he's not in. He's not in. That's Albert Brooks. But yeah. Okay. You have
your assignments. Get to work. Chop chop. Bye.