Forever.
Dog.
Warning, the following podcast may include confusing Marvel Universe distinctions, Hawkeye
crushing it on guitar, and a surprising amount of bullseye the target dog.
Marvel Comics scribe and podcast superhero Paul Scheer joins us for The Void's Avengers
Damage Control, the virtual reality experience on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, the theme park podcast hosted by three men who never avenge
but would consider it if the bar at the Carthay Circle stopped serving Manhattans.
My name is Mike Carlson, joining me as always Jason Sheridan.
Yes, and I would do that selflessly because that's not really one of my go-to drinks there.
You're saying you would aid us in our avenging.
Yes, mutual aid.
Yeah, that's true.
Scott Gidner here as well, but he is a Carthay Manhattan fan as well.
Yeah, yeah, certainly.
That would be rough.
I have been mad about, and it's not mad, I guess.
I hear that little private terrace that I love so much, the second floor wine area is
now AP only and I've heard the lines are crazy.
It's the alfresco tasting terrace.
The alfresco, okay, thanks, yes.
The alfresco tasting terrace is now AP only, which isn't a problem if you're an AP, but
I think it's made the lines crazy and that does make me want to hulk out.
Yeah, okay.
Hopefully those lines die down before the next time I go.
All right, well, let's bring our guest in here because we're going to talk about a whole
bunch of fun stuff.
You know him from Black Monday.
You know him from the comic book he wrote.
He's written many comics, but Cosmic Ghost Rider destroys the Marvel history.
Marvel history, sorry, not the Marvel history.
It's Paul Scheer.
Welcome back, guys.
I'm so excited to be back and I feel like we're not talking about something Disney related,
so this is a real big departure for me.
I feel like the two times I've been here we've done...
Well, the other was skydiving.
Oh, skydiving is not the end of it.
Oh, yeah, so maybe I am breaking.
But what we have not still done, this does not break the pattern of you haven't done
a ride on podcasts.
Oh, that's true.
Oh, yeah.
So it's staying in that.
How do you consider VR?
I mean, is VR a ride?
It's kind of a ride.
It counts.
I also don't want to poke too many holes, but Disney owns Marvel, so we are talking about
Disney.
All right, all right, there we go.
So we've just destroyed your whole argument.
I'm sorry.
Edit all of this out.
We've humiliated you in the first minutes of the podcast.
I'm sorry.
But does Disney own The Void?
Yes, they do.
I think they own part of it.
Because they do things that are not Disney related.
Jumanji is not, or they've done things that aren't Ghostbusters.
Yes, but Jumanji is a separate VR company.
Oh, I don't know.
There's a Jumanji escape room on Melrose that I drive by all the time that I'm fascinated
about.
Really?
It's like by where the Groundlings is.
Oh, yeah.
But it always is Jumanji.
It's not like, oh, it just opened up for Jumanji 2 or it came out when Jumanji came out.
It is 365, seven days a week, Jumanji escape room.
Wow.
And was before the new films, do you think?
That was why I didn't even, I saw it one time and I was like, that's odd that this is still
the Jumanji escape room because it was post-Jumanji, but pre-Jumanji 2 back in the dice or whatever
it is.
And also constantly change it.
Melrose, like any time I'm like, oh, is that restaurant I still like?
No, gone, gone two years ago.
Jumanji has the staying power of a great escape room.
We just did what we're talking about today, which is a void.
We're doing the Avengers void.
Avengers damage control.
Which is kind of a deceptive title because you swing by a damage control warehouse.
Right.
But like, you're not doing too much damage control.
You're not doing too much damage.
I mean, you're helping with the traditional term damage control, but in the Marvel universe,
damage control are these guys who help clean up after superhero fights.
This has been my literal passion project for such a long time.
All I want to do is a damage control television show.
Oh, sure.
And then I think last year on NBC, this is before everyone at Marvel TV got fired.
They did.
I think pilot a damage control show.
I think if you could do an I think that would be the only way you could bring some humor
into the.
I mean, like as a sitcom, you could do a damage control sitcom.
It really is a bunch of contractors just dealing with the fallout of all these great things.
They're not great things. These battles.
And that they never get to go experience themselves.
Yeah, they're they're strong enough to be effective, but they're not brainy enough to
be superheroes.
Sure.
You notice if they weren't there, they do.
These people do need to be employed.
It seems like at the end of the game, though, not to give away a spoiler for the void experience,
but the character that Taika Waititi plays in Thor Ragnarok seems to be a part of damage
control because he then tasks us with the cleanup.
Yes.
Yeah.
So now is that in Marvel lore?
Is he now part of damage control?
It seems like he injected himself for Scott.
So Jason and I are Marvel boys.
Yeah, I knew this was coming.
I'm just trying to I want to make sure Korg is the character we saw at the end who came
through Dr. Strange's portal at the end.
OK, but you're not even a Marvel boy in movies.
No, I don't do anything.
I feel suddenly.
Yeah, no, nobody has.
And feel free to.
No, I don't want to change it.
But I was coming into this thinking like I'm the least Marvel person and I'll need a lot
of translating.
And I was also suddenly self-conscious of like, I don't want to be a not Marvel guy
in like a snooty way.
I don't want to be like that.
Sure.
It's trash.
I do not.
Is that how I sound?
Even saying that I don't know really see the Marvel movies.
There's only so many hours in the day.
Yeah, sure.
It requires a lot of hours to watch all of these.
Sure.
22, 22 movies.
So 44.
No, probably probably.
Probably the 70s.
Probably.
Yeah, if you're really committing to it.
Yeah.
I mean, well, it's OK.
Different fun junk imprinted on your head.
I mean, some of the same stuff that imprinted in our heads.
But a lot of overlap.
Yeah, I'm just saying like, you know, this stuff imprinted on us as children.
But you guys and I find this, you know, your knowledge base is in the comic
books that then grew into the films.
There's some people who just know the film.
Yes.
You don't have to.
You don't have to do that work.
You don't have to do that backlog.
Yes, because they so in the movies, Damage Control is mentioned very briefly
as like the cleanup company that like kicks Michael Keaton's like salvage
company out in the Spider-Man movies.
Who is the head of Damage Control?
You see her for a second, right?
Is it somebody I thought a big name person like walks in with them?
Maybe I'm wrong. I could be totally wrong.
But let's maybe in Guardian Glenn Close is in Guardian.
He's in the Nova Corps.
Yeah, she's in the Nova Corps with John C.
Riley. Yeah.
Got to look just do you have a notepad?
Did you want to write all this?
I'll start taking it.
I get to relax in this way.
Yeah, sure. Yeah.
This will be fun.
This is the in there's only been like 12 damage control comics
spread out over a few limited series, a number of them written by Dwayne McDuffie,
who co-created the character Static.
Oh, yes.
From Static Shock, if you remember that cartoon and comic series and multi
award, he passed away a number of years ago, but a widely beloved figure
in the comic book world.
I would also say what I like about damage control is something that I really enjoy
in Marvel comic books, and I think they do it, but not always,
which is just these really weird one offs like they're not like
like damage control is a fun, bizarre idea.
And I think it may just be the state of where comic books are,
that you can't really take chances on on creating characters like that.
You know, it's a sort of even when I tried to reboot it at Marvel
at a certain point, like, oh, if we do that, we'd need to tie it into a main series.
And like it would be like an addendum to a larger story.
Like we'd have to like tack on three.
But yeah, so you I think there's something really fun about those
older creators at Marvel that were able to just be like, oh, here's a funny,
I weird idea that it can exist in this world.
And it was sold as like in the 80s.
It's like it's a sitcom in the Marvel universe.
Yeah, exactly. Which I love.
Yeah, it seems like yeah, it seems like I mean, you obviously have firsthand
experience, but it does seem like it's, you know, think people are like
they're trying to cater to the audience that watches the movies more and more now.
Yes. So it's like people are not they're going to just glaze over
if they go into a comic store and see the yeah, they're not going to get
it. Why am I why?
Why am I enjoying like these toughs?
Yeah, it's roughnecks who have to clean up all the garbage,
you know, after this thing.
But I did like the way they at least introduced it and continue to build out
the world because, you know, at least knows it in the Marvel universe.
There is a damage control, but they don't look like the roughnecks.
They look they look pretty much like shield. Yes. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, they don't.
So that's my question.
I guess we should just dive into it.
This is a confusing thing.
OK, so you're saying that Avengers damage control is like an area of Marvel lore,
but that name of this VR attraction is damage control,
but they are not particularly affiliated.
Yeah, I felt like they were trying to have their cake and eat it.
Yeah, they were. Yeah, yeah.
As you might know, yeah.
So there's like six Captain Marvel's spread out over a couple companies.
And there's an age of Ultron is the name of the second Avengers movie
and the name of a crossover that happened a couple of years prior.
Not the same story, though.
So it's like sometimes they like to use a phrase that gives you a feeling.
Yeah. So that's kind of what they're doing here,
because it's like a new damage control, essentially.
Yeah. Like even the idea of like a damage control, like it felt to me.
Like there's a thing in the Marvel universe
that's still playing a little bit of catch up about that shield
is not a part of the world anymore,
because it feels like that was like a shield facility that we were visiting,
not like a damage control.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, at least in my in my looking at it.
So and you're you're saying, OK, so we're going to have to delineate here
between different versions of the Marvel universe.
There is the MCU, which is a Marvel cinematic universe.
That's the movies and kind of some of the TV shows. Right.
But for sure, all of the Disney plus.
Yeah, the ones that they liked.
But they sort of like tried to ignore some of the shows.
Feige produced like I would say MCU is anything that Kevin Feige has touched.
The KSU. Right.
Yeah, because I would I would argue that things like The Punisher on Netflix
or Jessica Jones, even though they are in the Marvel, the new Marvel world,
that's not Kevin Feige approved.
And I think he's going to reintroduce a lot of these things
the way that he would like to do them.
The Disney plus shows will fall in the MCU.
Yes. Continuity. Right.
And then there's obviously the Marvel like comic universe,
which is 616, would you say?
616. Yeah.
Is the name of the like the multiverse worlds.
But it's still MCU.
No, no, no. You wouldn't call it MCU.
You don't call it officially Marvel comic universe.
No, you wouldn't call it that.
The MCU just became like the kind of the way they phrase it.
Now, my question is, I've heard Feige and other people talk about
there's a Marvel theme park universe.
I don't know what it's called.
Yes, I know about that, too. Yeah.
But it's a different continuity from the MCU.
Which is smart because I believe that what they want to do
at the theme parks is keep it evergreen because obviously
it can't keep up with the films.
You can't like rebrand the Spider-Man ride based on the specifics
of how that franchise grows.
You have to be like, and we're stopping here.
Yeah. You can't have a character meet and greet in the park
and then suddenly stop it because they are dead in the continuity of the movies.
Yeah, you have to kind of just embrace like,
I feel like there's going to be a lot of like hologram training facility.
That's the thing I keep on hearing about, like the Avengers training facilities.
Yeah. So it's sort of like they like the danger room and the X-Men.
It's sort of like you will be able to experience things here.
The Tony Stark will live large over the park,
but you will not necessarily be like, I think it'll be less like Spider-Man.
Come on and have this adventure with me.
Right. Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. So so it'll be not tied to the movies.
And my question, of course, is, is this void in that universe
or is it in the MCU proper? We don't know.
I don't have an answer to this.
Well, clearly it is all 100 percent
foggy approved because all the characters and actors and likenesses
and voices are in this, which I was very impressed with.
Yes. Yes, that's true.
Let's say right now, if you don't want to be this is will be spoiler
written. Oh, yes. You want to do the void.
You don't want to hear about what's going to happen in it.
Go do it and then restart this.
Yeah. Go find your local void.
Which there's a way there's here. I can say there's a few.
There's a bunch in SoCal and then Atlanta, Vegas, Minneapolis, D.C.,
Plano, Texas and Malaysia are the places where you can do this thing.
So if you're listening to this and you live in Malaysia,
A, I'm very surprised and B, go.
You guys are huge in Malaysia.
You guys are like the sugar man of Malaysia.
Like you just like this is the podcast.
Somehow it's like on all the stations down there.
We don't realize until we're in our 80s.
We never knew. Statue of Jason in the town square.
Mayor that as mayor. Yeah.
He did elect you mayor.
They took it. We cannot go there, though.
Otherwise, we will have turf wars with the Mercurial Casino owner.
Right. He's in Malaysia.
Oh, is that right? That is where the Mercurial Casino owner, the Maggott.
Yeah. Yeah.
Was he from he's the guy who from Fox with that?
I was a fox park.
And now it's yes, the one where the streets were not wide enough
and the emergency exits weren't quite correct.
And you're the mayor of that now.
Oh, cool. Mayor of an unopened theme park.
And the head of a banana republic.
I will say just to speak about the void for a second in general,
before we even get into this ride.
I love the void.
I think it is a brilliant idea
that I hope to see expanded across the country because it literally is a very
small space. We went to one inside a mall and I think they do interactive
experiences really well.
My only complaint with the void is the limited amount of
activities you can have in the void.
There's not like it seems like one runs and like the Star Wars one,
the rise of the resistance is fantastic.
It's great. But that one just you couldn't go like multiple times
in a day. It's a sort of like it's one that's kind of runs every now
and then they'll be like, oh, Nick Ademus runs every day at one forty five.
Right. Right.
Like they have to reset the you couldn't go do the Star Wars void thing
over and over and over. I mean, you could, but it'd be like
each experience is like five percent different.
It's different in the margins and not like, yes, I went down this door
and a totally different thing happened.
But I will say that based on the rise of the resistance,
to this ride or the other, you're saying you got rise of resistance on the brain.
Oh, sorry. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
As do we all. It's this is the week.
What is it called? The secrets of the Empire.
Yeah. So sorry. So sorry.
No, no, I don't blame you.
The the this one actually has a thing where you can get a score,
which I think is the best part of this.
This game that we just did today. Yeah.
You don't have so far in all my void experiences.
I haven't gotten like a score.
But if we get scores, Rick and Ralph, you get us.
Oh, you guys know where we supposed to be emailed scores or get ID cards.
We saw it there at the end.
That's not all that we have to kind of remember it.
Yeah, I don't think they gave it to us.
Attached to the picture.
I haven't looked at the show email yet.
I guess we can look. I'll bring it up.
But probably I don't feel like it's just a photo.
I think you just got to scan that quickly and we all got a letter grade at the end.
Yeah. Yeah.
To to do a little ways. Yeah.
We'll reveal it at the end.
But the void I'll say about the void.
Yeah, like the void is very cool and especially like for how easy it is in general,
like makes me very excited about five years from now or 10 years, because like really,
my only complaints about actually the physical void is like, it's a little heavy.
The heads at home, it's a little heavy and like the vest.
You're not wearing gloves.
Yes. You know, you only are wearing a backpack and a headset.
Like, I mean, like, which is kind of amazing,
because your hands play a giant part in this game, especially like you are shooting from your hands
and you're not wearing any sensors on your hands whatsoever.
No. And you need like precision aiming.
Yeah. Like you need to do very, very specific things with your hands.
Yeah. It's I guess we can say, though, that our hands scan our hands.
Yeah. Yeah, it's crazy. That is crazy.
It's also like what I've heard the rumor is for the Spider-Man ride in California Venture is that
you're shooting webs out of your hand and you don't have gloves.
You don't have any sort of controller. Wow.
It's just scanning your hands and then reacting like I don't.
I guess you do the actual I think or whatever.
Whatever is in front of the car will register your hands.
Well, this is like I'm just going to throw down a very large idea here and see what you guys think.
But I feel like I would have enjoyed and I like Smuggler's Run just I've written it many a time now.
I think if it was an avoid scenario, I think I would even enjoy it more in a weird way because
it is kind of mixing like you're in a tactile thing, which is like the Millennium Falcon,
which is amazing to be in that is great. But you also are interacting with it like a video game.
It's a weird mix. I kind of would almost like to be fully in or fully out.
And I feel like- Is it a ride or is it a video game?
Yeah. Maybe just decide a little bit.
Yeah. Interesting. Yeah.
And I feel like that like my issue with it is I don't feel I feel like I'm looking at a screen.
I don't know. There's something about it where this when we're flying and we're in part of it,
you're really immersed in it. And there are parts in the Smuggler's Run that I feel like
you are always going to have that distance of the screen a little bit.
Well, I always understood there was like I was definitely confused sometimes in this Avengers
thing. But in general, I'm going to hold my hand out in an Iron Man fashion and think and
I can see a little point and that's going to do something.
Smuggler's Run, I have these things I'm confused about. I don't know what I don't really understand
automatic firing. Yes.
When you're the gunner, I tried to I didn't want to do it again. I just do or wait,
I do automatic, not manual. I'm saying. Right. I do manual.
I've tried both. I don't think I get manual. I don't think I know how to go up and down or
what? The way that I was told to do it was you keep your hands locked. And so you have your
buttons on three different the three different buttons and you kind of play it like a piano
like that. And so you're just going up, down, that up, down, down. Like you just kind of like
so basically, I think if you just keep a steady flow of those three, you'll get a better you get
a better firing accuracy. I think there's some crossover with that and some crossover with this
void experience in that there you have to adjust to the rhythm because video games,
you press a button and assuming it's running a top speed, it's almost instantaneous like a blaster
or something. This like you don't really flex your hand or anything. You just aim it and that like
charges for a second and then fires and takes a beat or two to get used to. And then and then
you can kind of be pretty reasonably accurate with it and it is satisfying. I found it to be
incredibly like that and like to feel like you were actually affecting something. And that's why
Secrets of the Empire. I was telling you guys, I wrote it the first time by myself. I just happened
to go there. The void was empty. It was like the Wednesday and they're like, oh, you could just go
in. And it was kind of the best scenario because you could kind of just really explore the space
or someone else with you. But I felt like I didn't have much control over the end game. It was sort
of like I was going to I was going to leave their triumphant no matter what. I think the same way
here you were going to leave traveling, but they gave you a couple more elements that made you feel
like, oh no, I'm actually I am in I am get I am scoring here. I'm getting some points up on the
board. Sure. I mean, I think the big highlight of this was a lot of the spatial stuff like the set
pieces of like going from place to place. Yeah, because they use the Doctor Strange like portals
very well. Yes, I was very impressed. The game is long. Yeah, it felt long, which was really nice.
Yeah. The big travel you get to do into Doctor Strange is what? Yes. Well, it's located in what
part of New York do we know? It's in the village. Village. Yeah. OK. So yeah, well, so I guess we'll
maybe we'll just walk through it here and we'll get there. Because, yeah, so spoiler alert,
we get to go to Doctor Strange's house. Yeah. Yeah. So basically you get there. You park probably
near the target because some of those lots are a little more. It's a city target. Well, that's not
a city target. That is not. No, that is not at all a city target. It has the shopping cart escalators.
That implies space. Yeah, that's a free floor target, man. And we've got an episode on that.
Oh, that's coming. No, I would love to be here for the city target versus the regular target.
I have a lot of opinions. That does seem in our wheelhouse. Oh, my gosh. Let's get into it.
We're at the Glendale Galleria, we should say. And every void is I think every void seems a little
different. The Glendale Galleria, like there's some ones that are in malls that seem like they're just
a box. And I think what's really amazing about it is if you were to look, if you were to stand
above the void, I think it is only maybe like 15 by 10 feet, but they wrap you around so much.
And yeah, you I have never taken my mask off because I'm a good boy. Like, of course, I want
to enjoy the space, but it's very small, but they keep on just moving you. You think you're doing a
lot of movement, but you're just in a small space. There's this bizarre thing we talked about. I
think the first one we talked about the Star Wars one, but where you don't know, like you're actually
curving, but visually you think you're walking a straight line that goes and goes and goes.
And there's one of those in this and I'll wait till we get to that point, but there's an illusion
thing I read about that I still can't really process, but I'll wait till that point. Yeah.
So we start with, of course, a video like all good experiences and rides do. I love that video.
I'm so excited to be in that video room every time. That video, I have to, I want to hear what
you guys think, but I think that was one of the best video introductions by a character in a film.
They often feel like they're phoned in, they don't know the lines, like especially Casiel or
Cassian or Cassian. Andor. He looks like he is reading off a prompt. Like there is,
that is, that is, does not feel like he's in it, but he's not like, he does not have all the tech
jargon down. Oh, sure. Well, and the other, we'd also be comparing it to Wreck-It Ralph,
which John C. Reilly and Sarah Silverman participate in. And if they were phoning it in,
you can't tell because with the beauty of animation, you can bring the characters to it.
But they were, it was, I thought they were like as fun as they are in the movie.
But that's kind of great because they don't have to, like this is a, as from an acting standpoint,
a giant non-changing, like no camera changing monologue. Like it's a one shot and you have to
drop a lot of specifics. Like a lot. Jargon legally is that they're trying to make fun,
but that still is really mealy-mouthed. And she did a great, I thought she did a great job.
Shuri is our host. There's also about background. There's Dora Milaje in the background.
There's a Wakandan AI, which I think is a new character, right? Like what kind of like Martin
Freeman doing a Wakandan accent? I know it's not Martin Freeman, but yeah, I think it's like,
it is a Wakandan Jarvis. Yeah. Yeah. I can't remember. I saw Black Panther. I can't remember.
Did he have his own jar? They all have their own Jarvis. They had to have had some sort of
Jarvis, but I didn't seem to be as prominent as, like Tony talked to Jarvis all the time.
Right. Black Panther, like Shuri was the Jarvis talking to, I mean, essentially to Black Panther.
I feel like that was the conversation, you know. No, is this thing set in a specific,
it seems like it is like canonically post end game. Am I right? Like, does it, like,
because I don't know what I'm looking at exactly. Does it like account for the events?
It certainly created it like that. I think so, because it's the newer wave of Avengers.
They only have one thing that I noticed that is not post end game with one of the characters,
deformity, which is now a part of the, at the end of, we can get to it, but like the Hulk,
it would have a messed up pan. Oh, good point. Yeah. Cause yeah, so that's a spoiler at the end
of end game or no, and they're towards the middle, I guess. I can't remember. Hulk uses
the infinity gauntlet and he fucks his hand up because it's so powerful. Yeah. I forgot about
that. Yeah. So yeah, I did not, I actually forgot to look at Hulk's hands. Ooh. And there's, oh,
I'll get to it. I saw, I saw an Easter egg in there. Did you see that one? The thing I,
Oh, I, mine was more, not a blooper, but I think maybe just they didn't care about the actor who
plays Shuri. Has she always had a tattoo on her wrist? Like a tattoo from her hand to her wrist?
Because I saw that in the pre-show. I was like, I don't know if they just covered that up.
Yeah. They might've just covered that up. Or she got it after or what's going on.
I'm going to look at a wire image picture of her right now.
Find some premiere photos. Yeah. It looked cool. I was like, it makes sense for the character,
but I had never caught that before. So yeah. So, so Shuri, who is a princess of Wakanda,
who's Black Panther's sister, who was like a tech genius. She is telling us that we are going to be
on a trial. Yeah. We're going to be testing out. Yes. In one of the science centers that they
set up at the end of Black Panther. They run with like, there are Wakanda science centers around
the world. The actress who plays Shuri has a tattoo around her one of her hands, like a bracelet.
It looks like a bracelet. It looks like a bracelet. Yeah. But nothing coming from top to
not going up. So that may be covered. Interesting. So yeah. So can I just say that there's the,
I'm in a mall, I'm in the Galleria and I can walk into a room and watch a video where a character
from a movie says, we're recruiting you. And this is the center for such and such. Yeah. This kind of,
it kind of fulfills some of my like desire for there to be Chuck E. Cheese type things everywhere.
That why don't all malls have some place with the robot you can walk in and see that like in some,
in some boring mall characters talking to me. It's wonderful. Yeah. You can only see like a
handful of other places. Right. It would be nice before you go into a target. If it was like, you
got a pre-show video with Bullseye, the target dog. And we all know that Bullseye's personality
is, is great for that to really welcome you to spending. Welcome you to spending. He's, he's
eager. Yes. Welcome to spend. I have gone to a handful of these parties. They're called the night
before parties. They happened before the Oscars and they happened before the Emmys and is sponsored
by target and Bullseye, the dog is there on a pedestal, the real Bullseye. And you get to take
a picture with him if you like. I believe I have a picture. I believe there's a picture of Nick Kroll
and I with Bullseye, the dog, the real live dog. And it was quite a thrill.
Now that's an Avengers team. In the Schomburg target, which is my mother's favorite place to go.
So when we were back home for the holidays, we went, there are many like Bullseye little
animatronic kind of things in that target. What are you talking about?
You didn't take us. We were there. We were there. I didn't know until a couple of weeks
ago when you weren't there and Bullseye's like, bud is sticking out of like a package
and his little tail is wagging his seat. Bullseye's seat is sticking out of.
Well, do you guys know, I mean, Chicago is the home base for the target VR. Did you hear about this?
Like, so basically, so they are testing out this idea. Like I have an Oculus Quest. I also have a
HTC Vive setup, which my wife has made me dismantle. But the Oculus is great.
Where the ideally like so Target has been developing this technology that you would
enter into a virtual target and then you'd be able to walk the aisles and then whatever you
touch and put in your cart is sent to your house. So this is like the idea that you would be doing
Amazon style shopping via virtual reality in actual like amazing target store.
And so I've had two friends who have experienced the VR target and it's a genius idea because
it's like being in Amazon. Like you like, I always believe that you can't be in target without
spending like upwards of $60. I feel like you get there, like I need toothpaste and you're like,
well, but I also need these notebooks and then this pen and then I'll get that thing. And then
you walk on your go. What did I get? And I feel like this is what they're trying to create.
So they and so apparently they the testing ground for it because they also have the fake,
the giant fake Target in Chicago, which is where you go and you see like, all right,
hey, this is how we're going to display your items. And we send you bring, they bring in
customers to see like, well, let's sell if it's here. If we put a quiz on it at the end of the
aisle, will that be a thing? So they test out the way the store is like laid out.
This is my mom is about to become a big gamer. She's going to be like a virtual reality obsessed.
She's going to get a whole Oculus. She is going to be on that rig constantly. Well, I'm not. I was
thinking that all the time was Chicago. We'll see you again soon. Yeah. Back ASAP. All Target related
trip. Yeah. Oh my God. That's wild. I didn't know anything about that. You run through the aisles
in a Toys R Us dash kind of way, just like knock a bunch of shit into a car. And then,
but do you, what if, what if I don't though, can I get to the end then and say,
throw that all away? Yeah, it's just a robot. So he could, he could look, if I was, if I was like
Target, I would be instituting that. I mean, you'd have to have like a supermarket dash kind of an
element to it. I love all those VR stuff. I'm all in on, on VR. And I believe that I still believe
it's going to be the future of like, of like entertainment and stuff like that. It's still,
yeah, it's, it's feeling more that way. And the void makes you feel more that way. Like, like it
is the most successful like application of it. Yeah. I think that we send the most, the most fun.
Yeah. And then that's still because it's still a thing you get together with your friends to do.
But I also think it's because of IP. Like I feel like they're like you're going because it's Star
Wars, it's Ghostbusters, which I really want to do the Ghostbusters one. It's Avengers, it's Wreck
it Ralph. It's not just like, they do have this experience at the void called Nicodemus, which is
like their horror theme one, which is incredibly fun and really cool. But I think it's a harder
sell to say to your friends, you want to go check out the legend of Nicodemus. It's kind of like a
horror VR. It's like a horror, it's a harder seller. I think year three, I think this year,
after three years, Mike will finally have sold Nicodemus to more people to go and see it.
The demon of in vanishment. But I do want to. I went, I did the whole thing. I picked the card
at an amazing, it's super fun. I went with people who are very much into that level of experience,
but I think that the reason why VR has a hard time taking off a lot of the times is because
it, you have to like bring the concept has to be what people want to play. It's like, oh,
it's Terminator or for me, the Oculus Quest, it's at Vader Immortal. Everybody like that I showed
off to wants to play Vader Immortal because it's like, oh, I have a lightsaber. I understand this
world. I understand the world that I'm entering into, which kind of is a positive and negative
because we should have more adventurous senses. But things that aren't IP, but there's something
about like, I get the world. I've been here before in movies and in my dreams. So now when I'm in
here in VR, I kind of get it. It would be nice. I don't know if this is possible. I mean, I guess
it's possible. It would be nice if people sort of eventually come to think of like VR places like,
oh, honey, we should see what's playing at the void tonight. So like maybe you would do an original
one. You wouldn't necessarily like, if you can train a generation that this is entertainment.
The cool indie one. Yeah. Yeah. The cool, yeah. The low budget, the uncut gems.
Oh God, that's a horrible VR experience. It's two and a half hours of pure panic.
You're just anxiety inducing the entire year. You can't win. You're naked in a trunk for a part of
it. You look down in the VR and you're nude. It feels so real. That bell ringing. How do I start
it? You raise your hands, get help immediately. Sorry, I can't help with that one. I will say the
one thing that about the void, I don't know how record Ralph was, but I, it still is falling into
that same trap as most rides do, which is like, so glad you're here to test out our new suits.
Uh-oh, we're being under attack. We're going to get you on that field immediately. Like something
has happened and now you need to be there. And what I like about secrets of the empire is no,
no, you are on this mission. You have to recover this thing. Like, let's just go, like, let's just
get into, like, you don't need, you know, something went wrong. Yeah, something went wrong. I feel
like let's get past that part of the, uh, the game. I don't like that anymore. I feel like that's been
done to death. I feel like it's a, it's a hack ride. Justification. Yeah. Yeah. Of like, this is
why you are not captain America, but you are helping you're visiting. Yeah. It's like, it's
so bizarre because it never happened. It's never happened in any narrative function. It's not like,
we'll get these guys from the street too. Like, you know, it's like, they're like worried that if
they go, okay, you are superheroes here and like, like dad is going to go, wait, hold on a second
here. I'm not a superhero. Shut the thing down here. They have the wrong people. Like people.
I sell insurance. I can't help. I have no skills in this. What is going on? Can both my kids be
iron man. It's going to really mess up the day if they have to pick. Yeah. I don't know. They're not
giving anyone any credit for like, everyone gets it. Imagination. You've gone into a virtual reality
thing. Just play the thing. You don't have to be a character that we recognize. I mean, that's why
I think again, star Wars has a great element to it, which is like everyone's a stormtrooper in that
one. Like you're infiltrating. You're part of a bigger gang. This one, it's tough. You're in this
black Panther iron man mashup costume, which is pretty cool looking. Yeah. Yeah. Um, definitely.
But I'm like, I'm also down for, and I guess maybe this is where I've graduated too, as far as like a
person likes rides. Uh, I'm okay if it's all simulation, right? That's what we're doing.
Anyway, I don't need the real world to be at stake. Like that doesn't improve the gameplay.
It's like if they go like, Hey, you welcome to the Avengers facility. Here are three events that have
happened in Marvel history that we are now going to test our suits out to see if they, how we could
have, we will learn from our mistakes. Right. Yeah. Oh, sure. You know, you could be in those movies
and there's no consequences. There's no consequences anyway. Let's just, uh, let me just train.
Wait, there's time travel and magic and everything. Yeah. Like, how do we story justify why you'd be in
this event? Right. Yeah. No, you just do. Uh, you don't know else in this area of like justification
and why are you there? Someone, anyone tell me what, why you're there in pirates of the Caribbean.
I don't know. Right. Right. Right. Right. You know, like, but do we care? Do we go on pirates every
time and love it? Yeah. I don't know. I don't think they know why you're there. You're in a boat that
happens to be going near a lot of chaos, but am I in the past? Well, I don't care. No one needs it
to tell me any. Yeah. I think you're seeing the past. I think you're like an outside absurd. Well,
that's true. That's the narrative of the ride versus what the actual guest is supposed to be.
Yeah. We are ghosts. We are, we are Scrooge in it. Like we are, like, I feel like we are just like,
there's no boat captain, but we're just kind of, we're just, we're, we're simply on a boat ride.
When you leave skeleton world, do you become a skeleton? Like, do you know, you know, there's
that new, that thing they re-added where you're going, there's all, it's all skeletons at the
beginning. And then there's a skeleton split down the middle and it becomes a real person.
Have you seen this? That's really cool. Yeah. Of illustration. Supposedly what I have on,
what I understand is a time, you go back in time. So yes, if, if we were in a void helmet, would I
now be a skeleton and all of the pirates are real instead of vice versa? Oh, good question. No,
I think we would all, no, I think we'd all be skeleton. No, I think on the first part of pirates,
we'd all be skeletons with jewelry on. So you'd look down and you'd have like rings, but skeleton
fingers. And then once you went past that, then you would turn into a drunken pirate.
But now you see, I would quickly say, but you'll never have a ride like pirates against because
it, it's not checking the boxes, but then you think about avatar and you go on that ride,
which is really a bad version of pirates. It's like, uh, you're on that boat ride and you,
you don't do anything nor do you even see anything very interesting. It's sort of like,
except for the shaman of song. Yeah. The shaman of song. Yes. Uh, and then like,
and that is the biggest payoff that is so anticlimactic, but it's such a, uh,
I'll say it. It's a bummer. That ride is a bummer to me. Like I, I, I, it's beautiful.
I think I'm with you though. It might make some people mad. Yeah. I mean, it's beautiful. It's a
beauty. It's a, it's like, um, I don't know. It's like, it's pretty to look at, but it's not like,
not worth that line. That's the key. I think if you can just get on, which some have talked to
people who've just gotten straight on and you're like greatest thing ever, but like even, I mean,
well, no, we'd still love it, but even like Sinbad and Tokyo, which is so wonderful. If you,
if you had to do an hour and a half and then you got on it, still better, right? Still very,
yeah. But you'd be so much better. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm just saying there's the,
there'd be the annoyance of the giant line as opposed to so many boat rides. You just walk
straight on. Yeah. And you feel like you should someday. You'll be able to,
that boat ride feels to me, the avatar one, like a real, like the imagineers were shut down by
James Cameron. Like, I feel like James Cameron was like, they're like, this is the idea. I'm
going to do this. He's like, no, the most interesting thing is like the, the plant life
of the planet. That's what we really need to see. Okay. But we'll do this. I've entered. No,
there's no adventure here. It's just like, you're just like on a pretty boat ride. Okay. Yeah. But
maybe like for the ride, no, like I feel like he was like, no, no, no. Cause there's like,
there's nothing, everything that Disney does, there's an element to it. That is way more
exciting than that one ride. It's like if the blue Bayou part of pirates never ended. Yes. You just
like looked around and then did it again. I'd rather be on that blue Bayou watching people eat
dinner and hearing the music. If you were going by an avatar restaurant on the ride. Yeah.
If you went through Saltouli Canteen. Yeah. Into the kitchen. Yeah. By the roasting chicken spit.
I love how quickly Saltouli came out of your mouth. Oh, we're fancying it. I like Saltouli
Canteen more than Nabi River Journey, I think. In terms of if I had to list the experiences.
The bowls are really good. Those little bobas. If I could see the bobas being made on the boat.
Now we're talking. I think the reality of like, you know, when Joe Rody has talked about like
trying to achieve a feeling of peace or serenity in the boat ride is the practical reality kind of
cancels that out when it's like, well, the line's too long for flight path. Let's go on the boat.
And, or like, oh God, it's noon. It's lunch. Everyone is in the park now. Like, oh no.
I think everyone's opinion though would be different of it. Yes. If it was 20 minute line
and there were two other big sort of serene scenes. Yes. I think it's very short in addition
to a long line. There's something about like, I mean, look, I've gone on that ride in Disneyland,
the Storybook land and you're on that boat that you could say like pound for pound. It's equally
serene. Right. Like, I mean, it's like, and I enjoy that Storybook land one more. I'm not,
I'm not like give me waterfall drops. I'm not asking for. Not everything has to be Spider-Man
Transformers insanely high tech. Great. Yeah. It just seems like, and maybe, maybe I just wasn't
in that peaceful mode. Maybe it is the peaceful mode. Like I just think it's not, there's, it
needs a couple more moves. I always tell you, think about the ride and like, in like terms of moves.
And really all I remember from the ride is the shaman of song singing that wonderful melody,
and the frog, the technology, the frog kind of jumping above on the lily pads.
And then I remember like there's screens and stuff happening and it's nice and pleasant,
but those are the only two things I remember. So I feel like that's where the problems lie.
There's not five things you remember from the ride. There's two. I would say just convert that
into some sort of a dome that you could go into and use that as like an air conditioned break,
like lay down, relax, like at Disney, like listen to this song. You hear the shaman off in the
distance, like make it a little like. Coachella chill out. By the way, I'm, then I'm like,
that's the best idea. Like they've never done that before. Like you're like 15 minutes in like
a chill out tent. Like you'd be like, I'm cool. I'm relaxed. And I go back into the world.
Yeah. Energize. You're like backstage on the side of the stage watching the shaman of song.
Yeah. And you're just chilled out there and you're enjoying the set. They got close.
The shaman is playing at Coachella. Yeah. The shaman sort of playing at the Navi Coachella
with 90,000 people. Yeah. Which I think they will explore in one of these sequels.
The Navi Coachella, whatever that is. There was a Coachella in Star War and Rise of Skywalker.
Yes, that's right. The franchises need their Coachella. Yes. Yeah. There's deleted scenes
where the they have the wrong laminates. So they're like arguing. They're arguing.
Right. Where did you go? Right. I would love it if you saw Lando on his ship there and
and rise a Skywalker with just a bunch of laminates hanging on one of the doorposts,
like, you know, over the years, all the ones that Lando has collected. Yeah.
Which one here? That's for you. And the laminates in Kylo Ren's hand and then Ray opens her eyes
and it's in her hand. But that's how she finds out her name because they're like,
we can't give you the pass if you don't have a last name. Just right. Well, we need a last name.
We need a last name for the past. Now there's a reason. Yeah.
All right. That's the MacGuffin. I need to get the
doctor. Besides random people demanding to know your last name. Hey, no, last name.
What's your last name? Skywalk. Come on, man. It's not Skywalk. Come on. You're like,
stop name dropping. Yeah. Now, if you knew the target dog, maybe I'd let you in here.
An animated version of Bullseye, the target dog, told people before a movie to like silence their
cell phones and please don't talk during the movie. And I'm like, oh, I like that. Like this.
Would any of you guys, you know, obviously you're all writers, performers, and you know,
would you ever go in for a target that dog pitch? Like if they say, hey, look,
target is hearing ideas. Like Eminem's has been a thing that people have been talking about lately.
Like people have gone into pitch ideas to make an Eminem's style Lego movie. Is there, you know,
not Eminem's and Lego's, but like that style of, hey, we're going to, we're going to launch this.
Could there be a Bullseye movie? 100%. It's got to be real. It can't be like Call of the Wild dog.
It can't be like CGI dog. I feel the audience before cats. I mean, we're all in a weird mood
because we're about to see cats, but like, I feel like the audience kind of clenched up when they're
like, oh, that's CGI dog. CGI is not a real dog or a puppet or something. I mean, I could do a
Bullseye puppet or I would do maybe animated. I mean, animated Bullseye. Yeah. Yeah. Animated
is fun, but like a practical, like dark crystal Bullseye type puppet. I don't know that they're
adding dark crystal. Seems like it's going to be sinister now. Oh yeah. Baby Yoda. I now have a
pitch for him. Just, I haven't thought of this more than right now. What if target the Bull,
the Bullseye, the target dog is like a private detective, whatever you want he gets. Like,
so like that's the thing. Like he finds your thing. Like a Ray Donovan sort of fixer private
detective. And then of course he gets involved in a larger conspiracy. So it's almost like a film
noir take Bullseye the target dog. He is an investigator. Normally he's finding you whatever
you need. Oh, I have bad feet. Here's a foot massager. Oh, I got this other thing. Oh,
you know, I'm going to get you a special pencil holder, but then you ask him for something and
that's the thing he can't find. I think that's great. I think that's ever every kid's cartoon
in the nineties did a film noir takeoff episode or two part episode or something with the way.
I mean, with the way entertainment is going with IP, I mean, we would all be lucky to work on a
Bullseye show. TV show, ancillary web content. Yeah. I just add that the guy assigning the
missions that his Charlie essentially is Brian Cornell, the CEO of Target. I love that. I'm a
big fan. I hit, we discuss, he had really good walkout music at D 23 this year and I put lyrics
to the walkout music. He had a walkout. Why was he at D 23? I don't in the middle. Yeah. Disney
store. Like there's many Disney stores now in some targets. I mean, more target innovations.
I can't believe how many there are to talk about. Yeah. There's going to be many Disney stores.
So even it's a presentation that's all about like, what are we going to do to Epcot? There's a lot
of anticipation. Are they going to say what they're doing at tomorrow? And finally, and then instead,
like now, ladies and gentlemen, see Target CEO Brian Cornell. And he walked out to this really
jazzy but but but not down at down at down. I wrote lyrics to it too. Yeah. It's online.
I did them. That's the only thing they were missing. All right. So we're in the void.
Yeah. So after the pre show, you were you were then sent to you're in one of the Wakanda science
centers. Yes. You're in the suits. Shuri kind of walks you through like here's how you blast.
Here's how you do like a super blast. And here's how you do a shield. Yes. I didn't use the shield
that much. I all these things, I believe you should have two turns on them. I believe smugglers run.
You should have two turns. And I believe you should have two. Yeah, you are like you are getting used
to just the mechanics of it. And I feel like you're so much better like to do it right in
repetition. Because I think what I was having trouble with was knowing when to shield up to
get a bullet like because you have to get the idea is that you when you get hit with a target,
you're powering up. So then you could blast out hard. But it was like finding that rhythm of
shielding to protect and then shooting it back out. I think it's really only they really only
cue you to do it like once or twice, especially at the very end. I think that shields up so you can
do the last push against the bad guy. I was doing a couple shields up when we were in the helicopter
part and firing back out. And I found it to be very effective and fun. But I was also shielding
up too late or too early. And yeah, it's tough. It's tough because it would be nice if it was like
Captain America one hand shield where you kind of have your shield up but also shooting because it
would be like I put the shield up. But I'm like there's I can't my periphery isn't that good.
Yeah. So you can't quite I'm shooting but there's I'm going to make it hit with another.
It's like there's not a real good rhythm. Yeah, I feel like it's a I found my arms to be tired at
the end of this because you really are doing I would say like as close to exercise as I can imagine
which is like because your arms are always for most of the game outstretched either two hands
shooting like Iron Man one hand shooting or two hands up and you're blocking. So you never are
you very rarely are at rest until you're unless you're listening to like dialogue sections.
Right. I found throughout it that when I got hit and the haptic stuff was happening I think I got
hit less often but when I got hit it was really hard. You guys that happen to you guys I feel like
I heard some other good. Do you tie your suit tight? Maybe not. You see if I think maybe you did maybe I'm thinking
maybe you tied it too tight. Oh so that it was like really hitting my ribs. I might have yeah. Yeah. Okay so be
careful on that. Yeah mine was okay. I hear and there I would just go I would just get surprised
because I didn't think there was like an enemy on my right or something. Right. You really have to use
your 360 perspective. Like the opening is I like the fact that they give you a chance to play with
the tech. I think everything about this void even though we're having some issues with it is a step
better than every other void right. Like they're like oh great you have a moment to test technology.
Like what am I doing? I'm learning the basics of the game. Like it's not like in game grab a
rifle or do this. Yeah. Like you get a moment you understand the concepts you get to play all things.
You have a tutorial essentially and then you get to go in. Yeah and this one is so important for
that too because like on the Star Wars one which I did like that all of a sudden guns showed up in
the Star Wars one. Yeah. Because that is kind of cool of like you pick up you were like holy
shit there is a gun there. Yeah. This one you needed. I think if they did the gun every time you'd get
tired of the trick. So it's cool if there's a new thing. This one the practical things you touch are what?
You you you fly a Quinjet. You potentially fly a Quinjet at one point and you touch a rail. I use
the railing. Oh I hung out at the railing. I mean it's really funny because when you meet Dr. Strange
he is in the Sanctum Sanctorum but it says if you were visiting him in Colonial Williamsburg
because you're behind a railing that he is in front of like you are not in the same like it's sort of
like how they have those like glass walls. There's like this is a recreation of an old colonial
bedroom like he's on the other side of it. So like I was like casually leaning on the on that to
listen to him chat with us but he is on the other side. I was excited Dr. Strange is there but I was
more a little more excited that there was a little like knob on the rail. I was just like playing
with that. Oh yeah. Like I reached out and found a knob. So that's how I'm like such a baby with
these things. I would have just played with the knob for time. I completely agree. I feel like I was
very fascinated by the surface of the railing. So basically what happens is we're in the training
area. They kind of they say like oh there's a real problem and then stuff goes dark and one of Dr.
Strange's trademark portals opens up which honestly the most exciting part of the whole thing for me
personally because I went oh cool we're going to go see Dr. Strange and then we walk down
three like flights. That's what they're simulating. Like a spiral ramp. Yeah that was actually really
fun and great tech but why was there winter coming through one of the windows? Is that
another portal that it opened? I believe so because again in the first Dr. Strange they have
a whole thing where some of those windows are like he's when he's fighting remember he's fighting
what the villain Mads Mikkelsen. Oh yeah. And he's like shooting people into different like
areas of the earth to get them away from him. Yes. So I guess that's just a nod to that. I don't
know why he wouldn't close it. Yes I mean by the way it was a great effect on the thing because you
walk by a cold a wintry window you feel that cold chilly air which was great. There's a bunch of
like good sound and smell sensations throughout this game. Yeah and that descending is a really
crazy little sequence and you're on a pretty narrow little path which is a trick they keep doing and
that which freaks you out like I better hug that rail. On my HTC vibe there's a game called like
oh like walk the plank or something like that and so what's what kind of great is the way I had it
hooked up was like I stuck up to my television and so but if you're wearing it you like you're in the
VR space but everyone that's in your house can watch what is happening to you and what you're
looking at on the tv and it was always so fun to watch people walk a plank because you are
you're just in my living room and you're and you are so almost like I'm hands in front of you like
I'm gonna fall and there's nothing there and it's it's a great disposition of like how your mind can
really yeah because I was nervous to walk off that the the odd wheelchair ramp that he has in his
house that goes down yeah flights. I think this is the thing that I was bringing at the bizarre
illusion thing and I might be throwing out some bullshit but I think I did read this in like a
little behind the scenes before we did it I think in that part you're going up what I think I might
be insane but I feel like I caught that you mean just like there's a little bit downstairs in the
no void so yeah so so yeah basically you're turning three times and I the one thing that
kept throwing my brain is that I felt like I'm like your brain knows that we're not going down
but your eyes are telling you yeah that you're going down so I like towards the right it looks
like there's a drop there's not a second railing no you are yeah you could walk off of it yeah yeah
so you're saying that there was a little bit of an elevation there maybe it's a ramp and I think you
were going up interesting I'll look this up yeah look that up well I know the one thing about the
void that they do is it like you think of it like um like a Jimbery like a kid's play space they have
all these different objects they kind of repurpose so yeah all the objects that you are pretty much
using in secrets of the empire or wreck at Ralph are just repositioned in different ways and that's
kind of the economical way of making this it's sort of yeah yeah yeah we have like these 20 props and
we just put that here and then do that and like you know not they're not always reused in the same
way but I would imagine there's some sort of a ramp system like that that's an easy easy enough to
go up and go down like you know yeah that's got to be so because and like the other little plank
things I definitely there's a little bridge that comes into play in the Star Wars one too yeah that
must be like a primary tool for them this was like because yeah in the Star Wars one there's a
platform that lowers down that's what that's my favorite part of the Star Wars one is the platform
that lowers down to Mustafar yeah uh because that really blew me away you're on a little ride there
and that's a little ride and you like feel a little wobbly because you're like I could fall off and
well that's what in Nicodemus you're on a train and it's speeding and you and there's no caboose
around you you're just free hanging on a train and that's a that's a pretty scary moment um but this
this uh walking down to the sanctum sanctorum uh I was I was very like I guess just going like
three levels like simulating three stories yeah makes me go like oh we're going into the
were you guys were you guys having that same issue though because what I was doing was I'd
walk down a level then I'd walk through a portal then I'd walk down another it would go black for
a second I don't know it happened once it happened once to me where it kind of went black and then I
was confused I think I see I felt like I was leading the way so I think I may have gone a
little bit ahead of you guys or something because I would get down to the base walk through a portal
it would go black for a second and then I get back to the next level again I think it flickered once
on me like that I think it flickered once for me well I wonder it would be funny if it is glitched
that's the reason we had to go down three stories oh yeah right there we just send you right back
yeah that'd be crazy because the bar is there but yeah there's so the railing yes the railing
and this part is my favorite part of the whole thing I think oh really well just
there's a lot plenty of other things I really liked about it but just uh uh I talk about on
the show I like it when optimist prime at the end of the transformers ride says you did a wonderful
job whatever he says it's a great moment you have like this little connection with him and so we're
going down there and I honestly I felt this is the most uh like I felt something where I was like oh
my god we're going into this place that I've read and it was a quieter part because because I do
think like they want a lot of action and all this stuff so they don't always give you like a little
moment like that like to literally enjoy connecting with uh a character a character yes you and I feel
like that's what you really want like even though we get to see shuri she's on the video screen she
comes back a couple times but uh I felt like that moment was a nice it was he was giving you like
then like again an information dump is what we're doing yes go back out there which also is funny
enough because like didn't we just get an information yeah why do we need a second information
yeah to override that yeah right that being said it doesn't matter I was like if the whole thing
was in the sanctum sanctum and I could just look around at books like that's that's that's like
some of the vr games that are available at right you know where you can really take your time
just build blocks like more minecrafty yeah like you can exist in a space draw or paint or or even
just look around right and it's not practical for something that's you know in a mall and has to go
through but have you done sleep no more no oh guys we gotta get you guys to go see no I know I want
to do that for years okay no more is exactly so sleep no more is like this giant building you can
get lost in it I won't go into all the specifics but if you wanted you could spend the whole night
in one room right done yeah like you don't have to ever leave that room you don't have to get on
the adventure and there's a storyline that's kind of like Macbeth and it's yes it's the 20
but and like characters are going from room to room but it's a full old hotel and you can catch
snippets of the storyline but you don't have to follow it from like I've done it three times I've
had three vastly different experiences and I've done a couple here in LA too that everyone's
trying to be like no more and there's a great one I just did that was actually written by like I
think the guy who did like the grudge or something like that or the purge but yeah the cool thing is
is like so basically the show starts Macbeth starts and all the characters in Macbeth are
like think of it like if they left the stage they would be going to their office or they'd be going
to their thing so you may just catch one of the main characters off from their story interacting
in their real space until they come back to their the main story so you can follow the main story
or you can just follow one character for the entire story or you could just like exist and
just watch different it's fascinating so it basically is like there's a whole track that's
going on right but you don't have to be in any spot and at the very end they find a way to corral you
down to the final scene so you basically get to hang out in the haunted mansion and do it I mean
for lack of a better term and exist in it in any which way you choose that's fun yeah I'll do that
that sounds good um and if there's a yeah if there was a version of this where you could just
like be so Dr. Strange you want to like hang back yeah yes like a little while if you would like a
little about me you got a little magic like a little magic you could do and you could like pull
books out of magic like and just walk around and like look at portals and stuff because that's
that's the good stuff I mean you got the second closest like experience to like having something
either with the like a landmark in marvel or the character was like I guess Spider-Man on the ride
he was coming pretty close to us and giving us his quips but everything else was like you saw it
and it was very quick because we have to get to the action on this this was my I like this because
it was a breather a breather an early breather again I still think that the way that this gets
improved is you go it's a hologram we're going to recreate something and then all of a sudden
you're Hulk I'm Iron Man you're you know Captain America like we like we are like embodying
for this game we have their powers we're not we're not upsetting the MCU we're just sort of like
we're playing around with how those powers exist because I think we're interacting with them but we
are we never got to do anything we all are equally matched right yeah it's probably having at the end
where like we're doing what we can but ultimately all the characters we recognize show up and do
really do the stuff yeah part of the value added proposition of it of like this is still a little
more expensive than you would readily pay for like a movie even though movies always get more
expensive hopefully VR gets less expensive to bring the price down to get more people to do it
more often I think part of the selling point is that they go like well this is an experience it's
uh you know kind of a sequel to end game and you can't get it anywhere else and the characters you
like are here which I'm surprised because on the website they're like Ant-Man and and the Wasp and
Doctor Strange but they're like oh they got the less yeah they got the newer people who cost less
money but then a lot of people show up and but the thing is this is the whole thing that I read
um and my facts are probably a little bit wrong on it but after Iron Man was such a success every
contract that Disney put together there's a theme park clause in it which means that you are
obligated to do these things and there's I think a certain number attached to it so it is the only
one who doesn't have that is Robert Denney Jr. uh so everybody else has to perform the duties of
their thing now I don't think Thor talked in this no and uh Captain Marvel did she talk yeah she
guess she did talk a little bit oh yeah yeah that's right yeah Thor did not talk kind of growled
but it wasn't like yeah wasn't a ruffle out growl but I feel like they definitely cherry
picked some people for like because I think they're being calculated with who they're using for what
and yeah maybe the newer people that have signed have more appearances in their contract yeah I
mean I'm sure it's I'm sure it's a very interesting uh yeah how they break it all down I think they
make like Michael Douglas do a bunch of VR shit yeah well I feel like that like I feel like he
doesn't get one because if you go I don't know but there's that there's that Ant-Man and the Wasp
ride in Hong Kong that opened is anybody in it and they are Paul Rudd and uh is it Evangeline Lily
yeah I guess my thought is and I always go back to this which is like if I am a a character a
beloved character not a beloved actor a beloved playing a beloved character right it's it has
nothing to do with me like like the reason why people are going to Guardians of the Galaxy is
not because they're like I want to see Chris Pratt it's like I love Guardians I want to exist in this
world I want to see the collector I want to see these things if I am a beloved character fuck
yeah I'm gonna do a video like a video game or or uh or a theme park ride like there's no way like
what money I want money for this like no it's like it means that you live on yeah as part of this
piece of like like it's not it's not like it's not like do a commercial for Cheerios it's like
you're in like one of the most like you know established you know the only theme park really
like the only like like the top tier theme park doing something that is like immortalizing you
it's like I don't understand why you would even have to millions of people will see you
multiple generations you can take grandchildren there it's me yeah Puggy is still doing Soarin it's like let's do it
it's awesome yeah yeah yeah yeah they didn't change also some of these characters have the
full face mask so maybe they just need your voice like and also they don't want your face because
internationally anyone can be under that mask yeah so it's easier to sell iron man or darth vader or
ant man with the helmet on you know and I just think it's like and it seems at least based on
everything that I've seen from the harry potter rights all this stuff what is that maybe a day of
shoot a real easy day of shooting it's not like oh I gotta go away for three months to shoot this
theme park right like that guardians ride looks like that was shot and like an afternoon like
after a lunch break you never get different views on them it's never like now a short film a new
film starring these people it's like clearly and it kind of has to be they have to be shot from
their one way where they're facing you and talking to you so that's a green screen shoot that's an
old fod bsa video if that can get you in like you should be able as long as you can get in the park
for free if you're in a like if you're on a ride well that's we know that I think from the last
conversation we had on this show right that that is an impot like we knew somebody who wanted to
get a free thing because they were the voice of one of the rides I think it was Dave polis talked
about that where like he had to like go through a channel to be like I think he did oh he did
Paul Rubens I think has spoken of some problems I think now they've made things good with with
Paul Rubens like they can't he said like they canceled his pass as soon as Rex came off of
star tours maybe wow oh my god they might be more cautious with that because they're more cautious
about everything and with social media people could go like hey this big company screwed me
like sure yeah millions of people so that's obvious that's a fair trade off so if you're ever in
anything where there is a themed attraction what anything anyone needs I assume you're putting out
there I mean I'm I'm ready to go get me like I think that that's what uh Patton Oswald did
with Ratatouille he was like I think he does like happily does everything that Ratatouille like if
it's a toy or whatever it's like because oftentimes the toys don't have the actual right voices and I
just I guess my whole thing is like that's what you're signing up for like you are becoming a
character you're becoming the voice of this thing of this this thing it's like and it's for kids
it's ultimately for kids it's like if I'm Robert Denny Jr. I'm like yeah I want all my iron man's
that sound like me all right I'll say I'll go into the the vo booth for 30 minutes it's like
my pulsars are going get out of the way you know it's not like heavy acting it's not like you know
it's not like they're manipulating you I think you end up looking worse if it's not you I think you
seem lame if there's a bunch of products out there that are some bad impression yeah yeah it doesn't
well it doesn't we've learned Tom Hanks's brother does all the woody stuff Jim Hanks usually Jim
Hanks oh wow I know Eddie Murphy has a guy who does all the Shrek donkey shit huh okay yeah yeah
a bunch of uh a bunch of different donkeys at that cart yeah in universal oh my gosh hundreds and
hundreds of them it's so hard to imagine I wonder what the most like in demand of all the is there
like so much woody stuff we don't even realize it's just I would think that like Darth Vader would
be the one that you have to like because definitely not doing all of those no no I wouldn't think so
but he does seem to do a lot I guess maybe he's the guy who doesn't care maybe he's a smart guy
he's like yeah you want me to just record my things it's not like Darth Vader is like super
talkative either so it's like you know just lay down a bunch also with modern technology and
internet you can rig up a decent like a landline and just do it yeah yeah um and again how much
are we really talking about we don't need that much we don't know that much and it's going to be
filtered and fussed with so much in post anyway yeah actors get off your ass get off if you're a
major film talent listening I would only want I would only want yes like I can get in the park
for free if I'm like one of the guardians of the galaxy on the ride and I would just want like one
of each toy I did like if I'm doing the voice on a toy just give me a toy in addition to a good
amount of money for the actual well like but you're giving up like I mean who cares about the I guess
it's like like Harrison Ford not giving his likeness to the Indiana Jones ride is so
lame to me like it's like really that's what we're drawing the line like it's Indiana like there's
only one Indiana Jones like how much money you want to make on this that feels like a 90s holdover
that that was like the knife like well you just don't do that you didn't expect to be on a
television show Michael J Fox isn't in the back to the future ride I don't know if there was ever
a story where he was supposed to be but those things I think all set and like star tours is
c3pr2d2 but it's not right Luke Leia Haunt so yeah I think 80s 90s you were calibrated because
now you have you have everybody in the home I assume yeah I guess yeah those are spoilers I do
know hopefully yeah I mean I feel like I just just from the advertising material is it not
Adam Driver though I believe that Adam Driver is always the voice like Darth Vader but never the
physical face it's the mayors yeah right oh it's that okay okay basically what we're saying
Hollywood is we're all ready to work we're all willing to work especially if it's a thing to
show up show up 30 minutes early if you want to have breakfast you know we're all ready
free breakfast yeah it's just a funny weird holdout like you know it's just like a weird
thing it's like why make that your stand like you become this like and it's not like I guess
at a certain point Disney has proven like well yeah we'll do the Indiana Jones ride and we
will use all the pictures of you because we own that but on the ride it will just be someone who
looks vaguely like you and it won't be your voice fine doesn't stop anyone from coming to the park
or using that ride so who cares like you know it's well this is why I praise and congratulate
Donald J. Trump for appearing in the hall of president thank you sir for stepping up
showing leadership in this area home alone too he's always he somehow finds time to appear in
every piece of media it's shocking that he has not appeared cameoed in more things while president
yeah I know yeah he should be inviting them in left and right it's for the best but also kind
of surprising hasn't weaseled its way in the put him in more rides yeah for the void this is a star
studded event you're getting really is you're getting everybody in there Evangeline Lilly Paul
Rudd Tom Holland yeah Tom Holland in a big way yeah and I didn't realize Taika yeah Taika's
yeah like a cameo yeah yeah and again for cameos that's that's that's also surprising like like oh
did they burn up a maybe because the voiceover it's different like did they burn up a theme park
thing by just him going all right you guys clean up see you later bye now they don't now he's not
going to be in the ride yeah yeah we used our chip yeah but maybe he didn't because he mocapped
that in the movie right so maybe that wasn't his motion capture right yeah so that doesn't count
yeah I think a lot of that was I mean but it was interesting that many characters is that much more
animation and rendering and yeah man hours war machine in there too war machine falcon war machine
didn't really get to see um well I was gonna tell you this one spoiler that I saw that I thought
was very cool was uh Awatu shows up in oh I didn't notice him up in the clouds when you're fighting
uh when you're fighting at the very end you look up and there is his face wow you have to look up
up into the sky and to your uh to your right uh he was I just happened to turn at one point
and I saw his big face and I was like oh look and then he just disappeared but it was there
wow he's a awatu the watcher is the character that like when an important event happens in marvel
like history he just observes he's like a giant regal baby yeah he appears when something of
significance is happening in the marvel universe to like uh document it essentially so uh we
wouldn't know if this battle was important or not if he didn't show up yes but now we know it was
it was very worth hasn't really appeared in the mcu movies because he has falls under the has he
yeah he appeared in like one of them guardians of the galaxy 2 it's there's a cameo the stanley cameo
oh the same he's sitting explaining what's going on to a bunch of board watchers it's a funny
it's a funny comic but it falls under the fantastic four umbrella doesn't he uh well
that's all very unclear i mean because nick fury also killed him there's a lot he's been
assassinated yeah he's been assassinated there are multiple ones yeah we haven't played a very big
part in our uh cosmic ghost rider uh issues we we're very lucky that they let us mess around with
him uh as almost like this because basically in our marvel book comic ghost writer goes back
through history and he keeps on messing things up and a while too is upset about this and as he kind
of messes more stuff up he has to stop being passive and and be a little bit more active and
that was a big battle over at the marvel world but we were able to figure out a fun justification
for how he could be active and passive at the same time and and still we could get revenge and do all
this sort of stuff that's great that's interesting he's like i feel like they once in a while they
let him do something yeah yeah yeah it has to be a yeah it has to be a thing yeah it has to be yeah
i think we used him we had a lot to using mind control to do something so he didn't do anything
physically but he did use his mind they just wanted to be quiet and cool at the end of the day i think
that they because he's in a he's a watcher you can't make him be a doer you know he's a doer
it's yeah he's waving his around that harms around like us and this thing he's like the uh the eyes of
dr tj eckelberg the billboard and the great catspien that watches all the sins
like the lorax billboards around la yes the lorax billboard the lorax was the watcher of la yeah
yeah so when you leave the sanctum sictorum you are then now you're in this damage control
in quotes junkyard junkyard which seemingly just has a lot of old shield equipment in it nothing
no no real alien tech or that i saw yeah um and then that's another kind of tutorial part two
you're now you're kind of fighting but fun stuff happens you get shrunk down by ant man that's a
blast uh you meet spider-man that's great you get when you're shrunk you get there's a suddenly a big
piece of popcorn and you smell it smells like popcorn yeah which is kind of a good convenient
like what's the smell we could do i also was wondering and maybe i'm wrong about this but
like spider-man had no problem hearing wasp and ant man speak when they were also miniaturized as
well um but maybe they're all connected some some sort of bluetooth yeah probably there's some
avengers line frequency line uh i like spider-man uh saves us i think what there's like somebody
throws a giant vehicle at us and he saves us and that felt like a very fun it gets really close
again it's like the immersiveness oh yeah it's very much above we're a lot of standing on platforms
in this game like i mean like there's not a lot of the moving is to basically walk through portals
get on an airplane uh the quinjet and then but we're we're doing a lot of standing we're doing
a lot of walk walk walk stand for a while walk walk walk stand for a while and why are so many
void things about you're on some platform you're on like a balcony it's always balconies even
wreck-it-ralf right you're like overlooking some big city scapes it must be like one of those odd
here's something we can do well so try to back it in i think because you know you can't interact
with the environment per se like you always need to be like doing something into the like i'm
throwing this into the environment i am you're like and you got to be like you're gonna be
somewhere with like a rail something stopping you from just like walking forward into a right
so you have to be limited in what you can do in the environment but you also want to show off the
technology in the expanse of the world they're making right because you can't explore the space
like vr you can explore the space like right this is like kind of like vr but it's not like
it's not like you can't i mean you can like you're in these very small cubicles like the most
space exploration that we got was in the quinjet where we both had we had two people per jet
and but then they quickly again just bought all the windows of the quinjet and then you're just
again on a platform firing right and one person is doing a tactile uh you know uh piloting
but it that didn't seem to make a difference it didn't really yeah i was trying to do it to the
extremes and it wasn't really moving no yeah it seemed like we were just i thought i was excited
for some sort of like up down left right but now you're just flying it was like a boat it was just
like nice and steady yeah very uh lovely boat i would like to get on that river and avatar and
just listen to some beautiful song it's just a boat of serenity not not a crazy boat i mean i
think part of this is uh you are limited by the processing power of a computer in your backpack
right whereas millennium falcon they can have like something like 16 different high-end processors
to process a a totally destroyable world and modular world right this there's more limitation
you're not seeing battle damage in this world you're basically you're just firing you know
they're all that's not created characters who when you take care of them they're gone
yeah you're not yeah destroying a building in the building yeah you don't see any battle damage
right uh in the world you're just kind of there and that's fine i think what i liked about uh
secrets of the empire is that you're running around you are getting a gun out of a thing you
are working on like a a puzzly thing like yeah person's community there's a little bit more
interactive this game seemed to be like you're gonna shoot lasers out of your hand and that is
ultimately what we're doing we are shooting lasers and like that's and we're along for the ride but
that's all we're doing like there's no team but if you don't love doing that which maybe i didn't
if you get a little tired yeah or if you find it a tad confusing then it's it's a little repetitive
it doesn't heighten at all just sort of like and now we're on this platform shooting at the same
things and that's i think if you were if you were a character you'd be oh now i know that i'm with
mike and always hit my thor hammer and that gives a reverse like even just a different action if we
if the four of us were more different besides the colors of our suits yes yeah um we yeah i think
i mean yeah i agree with what you're saying and i also agree with it because like as a kid i was
never like i want to be like batman sidekick michael i wanted to be robin i also wanted to be
those characters too which i think is sometimes maybe a mistake sometimes when it's like and now
you're going to be the superhero and i'm like but i want to be one of those superheroes i don't want
to be me yeah i want to live the life like that's why that there's a batman vr game which is great
where you're just being a detective so you see a crime scene and as batman you have to investigate
the crime scene but you're in his outfit and you go back to his crime laboratory it's a little bit
more um it's a great it's a great way but you're batman like you want to be
you want to be batman yeah i want to be batman i don't want to be i mean i like being these
characters which i guess are just us with suits and the suits which we i think we all liked had
our names embroidered essentially on the breast oh yeah we got to wear personalized shirts
essentially which kept me and they and i think at the end of the day because i was feeling like it
was a little bit repetitive it was nice to know that they were keeping track of it because we did
get our letter of scores and there was something feeling like all right well that it meant something
like what we were doing yes yes yeah though i don't in retrospect i don't know how i would improve in
any of the areas remember it was very surprising if i we should say that i think the best score was
was mike uh though um mike and paul both a's jason i both b's just happy there were no f's sure but
mike also the highest number of uh friendly fire yes which is why i don't think i didn't feel that
i don't think you felt it during i think i was shooting at the heroes too much yes i think i
think i was i wasn't sure who was who i was very confused ant man and the wasp look like the bad
guys from afar yeah i just want to say i don't know we said yet the bad guys are ultron bots
ultron is back yes oh right this is the kind of uh which i i liked i like that they had a recognizable
villain i i want to say it was spader was it spader yeah it might have been yeah um but
ultron kind of a go-to avengers like lowkey always comes back in the comics lowkey always
comes back at some point ultron always comes back and ultron self-replicating so you can always have
a lot of goons like yes you always have a lot of guys to fight yeah that was and it was a fun way
that they justified it it was good and you kept it simple like again good story like as far as
you get to see a bunch of different worlds they move you through different worlds you get to see
places in marvel i would have liked to have seen some more i think the way we saw sanctum
the sanctum sanctorum like are there other places that we could have gone to
yeah that would that would have that same feeling of oh i'm in this spot because i think that that's
the most fun of it is like yes what's the recognizable thing that i'm in i want to be
in like a radically different instead of just like a different sort of cityscape right yeah we were
doing a lot of like i feel we were on a lot of barges like we were in a lot of junkyards and ship
like like a salvaged telecarrier but it wasn't super clear i mean i appreciate it that they use
i think this is like a macguffin of comics that i i think you can always is like always reliable
of like there is a warehouse or a junkyard filled with some fucked up super science and we forgot
about it and uh we're fucked now like something's going on it seems to be the the premise of the
opening crawl of uh rise of skywalker i mean it's like sure these ships are just been hanging out
there yeah no one uh no one the dead speak yeah that's big we're in we're in done 500 ships have
been under the water yeah no one knew no one knew just like this just like the enterprise also
hanging on under the water and yeah second film just hanging out we didn't know what to do it
water blocks auto signals there's no way to know it's there yeah the uh i think that probably the
designers err on the idea okay around the side of like teen boy teen boy is going to go in there
and he doesn't like a boring talky thing he wants to shoot lasers out of his fingers or whatever
and i think that like they err on that more often than not but i wonder i wonder if most people feel
like we do or most people just kind of like i like the avengers i want a gamified experience
versus like if dr strange took us to each of the avengers houses i think maybe i and like there was
just a little fun thing to do in each one i may have even liked it more and i i honestly i really
liked this i really had a great time these are nitpicky things yeah i'm just sort of the uh
we're thinking off the top of our head of what we liked and whatever and you just you want to see
the hawkeye's garage i want to see hawkeye's garage where he's tuning that guitar yeah because
you know i want to see a little bit of a like maybe we can see when he's working on heaven
don't have a name and he's sort of in the lab in the marvel universe hawkeye wrote the same song
yeah hawkeye is the most likely to use his fame of saving the world multiple times to put out an
album or at least or an app or at least an app yeah and he's got the hawkeye at the rocks and he's
got the garth brooks thing he's got hawkeye and ronan his alter ego yeah so he can do two different
musical personas yeah like it's chris gaines is his ronan so yeah that makes sense uh i want to go
to spider-man's uh amaze apartment in new york i think what we're talking about is i think home
virtual reality versus whatever this is this is much more of a uh interactive event like i think
like that stuff is fun to explore in the home you don't need you have your space you can kind of
look around you can interact with the space like uh justin roiland has at squanch games and like
one of the things is like like office work or desk job or whatever and you you just are in an
office and you get to pick up things and open file cabinets and you know and answer calls and
then it goes crazier but but like there's something about just exploring a space and
you're never going to get to do that here like you most you get to do is press some buttons and
do some stuff because they have to make sure they got a you're on a timer like that the game isn't
waiting for us to complete a task right if you don't complete the task at a certain point you're
just you're okay we did it move on so do you guys feel then like given the limited time then you
want like bigger blockbuster i am essentially iron man i am hulk well i think if you need to
adjust people to like this is what this experience is because how many people have really done
something with the helmet in the backpack and like that sort of thing you need to like get
get people into it what i'm curious of is when does the um when is the clarity of it
like it's it's the same sort of definite when does it get clearer because i i'm starting to
notice i'm sure it's been a couple years of fuzzy to me yeah i'm sure it's a lot of messing around
with and you're wearing your glasses on that i'm wearing my glass i think the void is the best of
the vr stuff i've done is the most accommodating to yes does it fog though no really i feel like
it's a sweaty end i feel you have to figure out a lot of jiggling around with the eye like where
does it fit the right way and then it really gets but yes you're still gonna have like i think it's
the processing power it's like yeah you're only like if it's only gonna get you you know it's
gonna be fuzzy on the edges you have a little glaucoma like that's basically every character is
a little glaucoma and like they probably have the technology to make it like a little clearer now
but like the investment of like opening all these things like they need to probably get another few
years out of the whatever they have currently yeah or it'd be shorter but i kept finding myself
having to like okay if i hold it if i hold the helmet like this it's much more clear but then
what if one of the guys turns yeah sees me looking like a four eyes they're gonna see this cool iron
suit man holding hands up maybe you guys would make fun of me i was really self-conscious i love
that i i also feel like to answer that question though like i feel like it probably has to do with
the the everyone going through it a million times like you can't necessarily like make it exactly
for your head like maybe in the future you go oh i got my own head i bring my own headset into this
you know or yeah you know my own glasses you know that you have kind of calibrated right like
like bowling you come in with your ball instead of using the alley yeah you don't use the alley
helmet i mean i feel like those 3d glasses sometimes work and sometimes don't work like or
yeah it does feel like i guess i when i was saying earlier like about the future of it it does feel
like maybe there's just like whatever in 10 years there's like such a there's a sleek version
of that it's not a big bulky headset it's something that like well there's so much easier that fits
c.s now they look like steampunk glasses oh yeah okay they look real i mean they're there i mean
the oculus is tiny it's getting tinier and tinier and tinier and i feel like that's that's a good
thing so like in 10 years it'll be hopefully like really just be something you barely even notice on
your head yeah and it'll be like scarily clear and you can live there forever you can live there
forever that's what we all want augmented reality too i mean right because augmented reality is like
another thing that could be they're more interesting it's rumored for mario kart oh wow so
augmented reality basically is like you wear glasses and you can see the world what it looks
like but it's adding like graphics to the world well and they were also saying that like that you
wear that you're going to be wearing glasses in the theme park land itself yeah i'm interested
in that i was because they there was a big we should probably talk about this on another show
but there's a big mario like news dump or nintendoland news dump there's a music video there was really
i haven't gotten to watch it yet it's fun it's crazy i think it's fun people i saw people saying
maybe it's set the bar too high if the land isn't like this music video it's possible it's too high
but yeah you're gonna be you're gonna have your own like nintendo magic band and collect coins
but then i also saw this but you can like there's a video on twitter somebody like with a band and
then they go under a box a coin box and then jump and then it makes the cling so that's what i so
immediately they are so weaponized now against like star wars and galaxy's edge and like just that
stupid dumb thing i can walk under a coin box and hit it but i also feel like this is like the kind
of things that we were promised when star wars land opened up it was like your ride like what
you do want to run is going to affect how people interact with you in the park that's not a thing
what were they talking yeah that was never only if you're in the app maybe i've been in the app it
doesn't like it doesn't seem like it doesn't even sync up your ride doesn't sync up with
the app it's not like you don't scan i mean i always thought you like because that you would
scan it like at the end like now use your app on your way out and scan your code and that would
give you points or no i mean you wanted to have trouble ordering at the bar yeah
or just someone coming up to you be like you know rough flying today like yes basically as
simple as that but that app is also i love that app but but it's it's all very small i think the
idea of these things are executable in a very controlled environment and then they go oh now
we have to take this out in a in a major thing we were talking about going to rise of the resistance
when it opens and i tweeted about something about that and somebody brought up a good point like
if it's even able to stay open for two hours on friday like you know like oh right the chances of
this even working at full blast on day one sure is a question you know people might be listening
to this on day one isn't this one we're putting out this will be out it's day one on day one
and we might i don't know come say hi yeah if you're listening to it i mean some people probably
right now it's 4 a.m and they're in a line at the disneyland resort so just lean out of the line and
say hey jason yeah maybe he'll say hi back and he'll or he might be at the labrea bakery line
waiting for the express to open uh for whatever reason my experience on rise of resistance like
okay we need your help go to labrea bakery for a long lunch and then come back in a little while
my man uh yeah that's your dream finn i mean that was another thing that was in the novelizations
but not in the movie finn loves the bray bakery i read that yeah to read the novel why was everything
in the bonus material it's all in the novel you gotta read it poe wears sanuk sandals yes that was
the twitch stream and the fan the labrea bakery was in the novel poe was confused though because he
didn't know that basin had become sanuk and then he learned about snook and loved the
changes and ray's full family tree was in the trunk of the uh the suv yeah that was parked next to
star wars there's a lot of things you gotta do you also get especially popcorn box you will find out
some more information about a babu freak oh i would love that you have to be done with the popcorn
it's at the bottom you gotta finish it and then read the fine print there's a series of pogs that
explain how palpatine came back but you have to find those in a specific area this is how sleep
no more affects them yeah yeah yeah uh what closing thoughts yeah i do wait let me really fast i wish
we could have stayed shrunk longer that's what i was gonna be all like weird no dumb popcorn gags
i wish i love this experience i love the void i will continue to bring people to the void and recommend
the void i just wish that they divided this ride into four distinct things one time you're doing
laser blasters maybe one time you're doing all miniature like you you didn't really get to get
much variety even though they were trying to create that like now you're flying the quinjet
now you're doing this it all was the same it just all felt to me like you're walking you're shooting
you're walking you're shooting like there was nothing that like changed up the gameplay that
drastically i would have liked that a set really different set pieces yeah like where you could at
least be doing different skills or even hey there's four of you you attack his arm you attack his leg
you attack his head i'll attack this you know yeah or like yeah some thing where you like maybe
peeled who have you peel off and you have to like infiltrate the robot and it's obviously we're like
next to each other but like you're just like climbing a little i don't know there's some way
to like do it where there's two different missions and you both have to do a different thing i would
have like a puzzle a simple puzzle yeah yeah that's kind of like just star wars yeah just give me like
a few different elements of gameplay and especially because they felt like that the quinjet was thrown
in there we had no stakes to it besides just another way to like now we're shooting and flying
but it wasn't like it wasn't different gameplay like i would have liked it when he described it
before we went in there like oh are we firing the quinjet because that's fun yes all right great so
now we're just gonna we're just gonna do this it's like money and falcon we're gonna do that now that
would have been at least different but no it was all just hand yeah yeah if you had if somebody had
to peel off and pick a song to put on from the guardians mixtape oh great oh yeah that would have
been great you get to choose so there's like a couple different options great like the rock and
roll roller coaster in universal studios where you get to pick your own song yeah that's not rock and
roll whatever that is that called not rock and roll it it's rock and roll and not rip ride rocket
not hollywood rocket jackie ogden uh dr augustine these theme parks love their thin slices
yeah updating your avengers identification card it's time to renew going to avengers dmv
being the guild fees yes yeah uh yeah that would have been good again i just wanted to
hang out in everyone's bedroom or living room i don't know why you're a bit of a no i don't know
i don't need to i'm not gonna watch them do things i'm just saying like i want to live in the world
i want to live there i want to not be in this world i want to live in spider-man's bedroom where
they can't see you he's under age michael no it's not a sex thing we're just buddies i will say
there is something so fulfilling in that batman game and it's so simple and basic but you're
putting on the batman costume yes putting on the glove you're you know and it's like and you look
at yourself and you're like in the batman outfit it's so fun but what the problem that the void
will always have unfortunately it's a four-person game so whatever you're doing you have to find a
way to make you all equal because essentially we are only one we don't do any teamwork in it
right so we all are having to have the same exact experience but yet have the conceit of it being
four of us because so we couldn't all be batman we couldn't all suit up as batman and i don't
think it's complex enough to be like you'll suit as batman you'll be hulk you'll be like it just
sort of i think the game i think there's an element of the game like you all need to be equal you're
all storm troopers right you're all ghostbusters you're all this black panther meets iron man
right characters and you there's no difference to you besides the color right but does it have to
be that way i think i think the technology probably is at this point where you can't be doing
disparate things sure sure right and it's just obviously yeah it's easier for them to program
that you all shoot in this one way because like if you had one of you had like webs and like we're
shooting pulling things which would be awesome i think like it's just so much more work and so
many more mechanics and so many more it's like those old video games that used to play like
with like operation like wolf for like the old terminator game where you all have machine guns
there's four machine guns on like a console and everyone has one it's like that's what we are
doing we are essentially doing the the avengers version of that we all have a machine gun we're
all firing at our at our distinct time crisis right it's all that you know it's like there's
nothing different to do in time crisis and again practically an easy way to get everyone up to
speed exactly you know what this is yeah in 30 seconds yeah the only thing that you need to do
is you know for sure so is there anything else any other ips that work in terms of like everyone's
equals like you're all the you're all the ants from ants or your uh that's the first one you
thought of yeah i don't know why yeah what's where's there just a field of identical i'm
always thinking about ants uh if we were if we were all i mean i think of star wars that's
i was gonna say if we were all like battle droids but the same thing as stormtroopers that's stupid
uh what else we're all jabawockeys
um
i love that that's pretty good uh there's a problem with the solving problems around the childhood
factory i think i'm talking agustas i i also think we have to think about masks because
umpa lumpas we'd have to we have a size issue oh yeah we'd have to you know we'd have and we
and our faces would be seen i think a lot of these games they are you're some they're figuring out a
way to what is your face in uh rocket realm you do speak a little bit yeah you have like sort of
you're like oh you're like people you're different citizens of the internet yeah okay yeah but you
are like a cartoon character and when you talk the mouth moves so that is something they can do
yeah what about agent smith's from matrix that's a fun one that's not a bad idea sure um that would
be also very good but you know what it would be it would be like hey i'm neo i've deputized you to
all be as strong as me you're always fight uh agent smith thanks for rising up with me now i
go to the rave the original inventor of the rave the matrix too uh the coachella the coachella
that's true they had a coachella before any of the franchise yeah exactly yeah we gotta give them
credit there well you know avatar will definitely be the next void yeah one you would imagine yeah
because it's already what it is you're already going into a body and suiting up i also think
they would never do it because probably too violent but a john wick void would be perfect
oh you know you all have to be like firing a john wick or something like that you know there's these
other other companies that are popping up too they're doing this so i wonder if they'll be
like an r-rated company yeah that'll do like a more violent one probably has to be there there's
so many great vr uh bullet games and like beat saber and all this sort of stuff that i think
you're never gonna get the you're never gonna get a game where you're firing a gun
in disneyland for good reason i think uh but i think there will be definitely the outliers
sure um and then i was the last thing i was gonna say is that it seems like we're getting some crazy
simulators avengers ride into california adventure yes and this i was like when we were in the
battles i was like i was very antsy because i was like i want to like fly and do something
yeah because we heard what we think that stuff that ride might be no i have not heard this my
speculation is there's two two or three pictures that came out where you start in a quinjet and
you're going to some sort of battle in wakanda and then there's a picture of a giant crazy avengers
battle and there's like the the guests are in little seats with their legs dangling which to
me seems like a soren type of a thing i don't know that it's probably i don't know that everyone
will have like their own individual thing but maybe groups maybe a little like harry potter
maybe that um but you can imagine what like whatever the ride system is like a very like
high impact version of that would be great if you actually were strapped in it was like a high
impact soren so like you're on the quinjet so you're flying fast then you're like bombing or
whatever my my fantasy version of it is like the bottom drops out of the quinjet and ejects everybody
into the battle see that's great because they don't do show you in like the same kind of things
in the jet so something has to happen to get you out of the jet it's not i don't think you're going
to leave the jet and get a different thing that's a comic book go-to like best case scenario everyone
jumps out the back and joins battle worst case scenario what often happens is uh the blackbird
or the quinjet gets blown up and you get tossed into the battle which would be amazing if they
did that sure so like yeah i mean i think it all is going to be about topping the rise of the
resistance style of ride where it's like four rides in one it's like you're going to have a
little bit of this a little bit of that like what was kind of like the smart track meets this meets
of that meets of this like you know because i think that's the only way to kind of upgrade the ride
it can't go backwards from that and the only way and i i think big insurance that uh would help
top that is if you were lowered down finally into spider-man's bedroom
a dream of it and then he tells me he's proud of me that would be so nice you're like great
dude and then you crawl back out the window you came in through fine i'll go in out the window
don't care you've moved the desk three inches like a creepy crawl it's not a family
swearing that up and down paul sheer you survived podcast the ride thank you for having me back it
was a pleasure appreciated uh let's exit through the gift shop anything you'd like to plug at this
particular time um no black monday comes back uh march 15th on showtime uh after uh homeland that's
uh that's that's what i got right now yeah wait and and comics are right applicable today is there
anything new yeah you know i actually have a documentary that i did for disney plus about
marvel which will be coming out this summer for yeah it's part of uh it's part of this documentary
series that the chef's table guys are doing they're doing a whole series oh wow really really
really fun big fan of those yeah those guys are great and it's been a blast uh and the whole
everybody at disney plus has been amazing wow cool nice all right wonderful uh and as for us
several more podcasts i'd follow us on twitter instagram and facebook and for three bonus
episodes every month sign up for podcasts the ride the second gate at patreon.com podcast the ride
hopefully uh rise the resistance info coming to you soon we can't promise oh yeah next week
it depends on if that thing holds together you hope it does you know brand new rides are uh built
on hope and that's all you can do i i really feel like disneyland needs this like they need they need
a fun they need a good launch day uh you know we're pulling for them we don't want disasters
no we don't want women's feet sinking into the cement no they're the runner of the magic i have
i have the belief that because it is already open in orlando they could be ahead of the smoother
yeah hopefully fingers crossed yeah that the whole ride doesn't just uh sink yeah but as you're
hearing this we're probably braving though we might be stuck on it we'll see lit on fire or something
all right boarding groups are getting ready to get in that boarding group we're ready to get only one
one ride we only got one that day only one 695 come on damn it um all right folks uh talk to you
again soon bye bye bye bye forever dog this has been a forever dog production executive produced
by mike carlson jason sharridan scott garner brett bohme joe cilio and alex ramsey for more
original podcasts please visit forever dog podcasts.com and subscribe to our shows on apple
podcasts spotify or wherever you get your podcasts keep up with the latest forever dog news by
following us on twitter and instagram at forever dog team and liking our page on facebook