Forever.
Dog.
Recruits, thank you for joining The Cause.
A podcasting team has infiltrated a highly anticipated ride
that has arrived in the Anaheim system.
Our mission is to tell you about it,
but first we'll have to navigate
through Jason's poor opening day dietary choices.
We'll regroup with you after the theme song.
Welcome to The Cause.
It's Rise of the Resistance on Podcast The Ride.
Welcome to Podcast The Ride, or as it's known today,
two hours of breathless gushing.
I'm Scott Gerdert joined by Jason Sheridan.
Bright suns, Scott, bright suns.
And Mike Carlson.
Yes, bright suns as well.
I assume it'll be rising moons
by the time we're done with this.
I think so, yes.
I had a question regarding the runtime of the episode
because if, all right, if our standard ratio
is about two hours for a three minute ride,
would we be forgiven for doing 10 hours on a 15 minute ride?
Oh yeah.
That's a fair point, yeah.
I think the audience would have to allow it.
And it might be what you get.
You're looking at the runtime now.
We don't know.
You know more than we know.
Could be 10 hours, and if so,
I'm sure it's all essential and compelling.
Sure is riveting.
We're talking Rise of the Resistance,
which is the new ride based on the Star Wars franchise.
Yes.
Oh my God, we got to do it.
It rules, it fucking rules.
Holy shit.
Yeah, yes.
Long awaited, delayed six months, eight months.
We don't know exactly when it was supposed to originally open
because they pushed up the opening
of Star Wars Galaxy's Edge, but it's here finally.
We did it at Disneyland.
We did not go out to Orlando.
Some people I think were questioning our cred.
Like we should have gone to Orlando
to have done it first day, but we waited.
Questioning the amount of credit card points we have.
Yes, I said credit card points.
Yeah, I finished the whole phrase.
Yeah, sorry, that's what I call it.
Yeah, I just kept replying by retweeting graphs
of cost of living increases in Los Angeles.
But yeah, we did it at Disneyland.
Opening day, we made it opening day.
Opening day, a real adventure.
It really was, and I think there was definitely a question
at the beginning of the day if we would even get on.
I think there's been that question for everybody going,
and there probably are some tales of woe of people
who did not get on and did not win the boarding pass shuffle.
My buddy, I felt really bad, my buddy Avery
went down on Saturday and the app crashed at 8 a.m.
And by the time they all got back up, it was gone.
Like the people had gotten them.
Sheesh. What a mess.
Yeah, and I think they went faster on Saturday maybe
than they did on Friday.
I think so, well, people off work, you know?
People off work.
People maybe knew how it worked by then.
People had realized that camping out from,
one of the parking lots, the Toy Story lot was open at midnight.
So people were there and camping out.
And then it was determined that by 8 a.m.
you did not have to do that.
That didn't help you in any regard.
No. Yeah.
So basically what it what it happened was, my understanding is in Florida,
you had to like have a very similar
app situation as the one in Disneyland.
But the way they were doing it is that first person in would immediately
get to join a boarding group.
So I don't know when those would start.
Maybe they started like at seven.
They started earlier.
So essentially it was first come first serve.
And as soon as you went through the turnstile, you get on your app
and find your slot and it would obviously go through sequentially.
So there was an incentive to being there first.
You would get a little more fair.
Yes, it is. It is more fair.
The most fair to insane people.
Yes. So the people at midnight would have benefited, at least
they would have been like the first people on.
But now they've randomized it on both coasts.
Yes. And I think we have a leg up because I saw one Twitter user
post about this and I text you about it of like the system
for doing it is built on the backbone of MaxPass, which we are familiar with.
We have it out here.
But it's they don't have it in Florida and everything in Florida.
The digital fast passes work a little differently.
Yeah. So I was I had that question.
So basically when we say it's randomized now, quote, unquote,
it means that everyone who has gone through the turnstile at 8am
gets on their app right at that time and gets added to a boarding group.
Now, I don't think it's actually randomized.
I think it's still doing first come first serve.
It's just that since it's a giant clusterfuck of a bunch of people
trying to get on, it's essentially randomized because there's so many people
doing it, you're not going to have second difference.
Right. More like, yeah, parse it even more.
0.000. Yeah.
I think it also helps if you have the fastest phone
and whoever has the best data providing in.
Yes. And where and what?
Yeah. What data received the best in that specific spot in Disneyland?
Let's start out with a hack.
Let's start out with what we believe to be a hack.
Really? A little bit of a hack.
Well, I don't use the Wi-Fi.
Don't use the Wi-Fi.
Don't use the Disneyland Wi-Fi.
Now you can leave after you go through the gate.
That's what we're talking about here.
Yeah, I see.
So the idea would be maybe go a day before you're going to do it
and test out where your phone gets the strongest signal.
Even you could do it before walking around the park.
I disagree with this step.
This is madness.
I need to do a prep day.
I yes. It's very funny you use that word.
The Twitter account is Madness Kingdom.
They write some.
They have some very interesting essays on Medium.
Check them out.
But you also could go to the Grand California.
You could go through the turnstile at Disneyland at 7am, leave,
go to Grand California and get on the Wi-Fi in the lobby
or somewhere, sit comfortably in a chair and then at 8 o'clock
try getting on.
If you live close enough, you could go to your damn house.
Sure.
So the hack is become an Anaheim homeowner.
Yes, that would definitely help.
Or just go have a nice breakfast.
A hack for every day.
You got to start off the good breakfast.
If Captain Kids Buffet on Harbor has Wi-Fi, which I don't know
the answer to because we haven't reviewed it for the podcast yet.
Go over there. Snip that word yet out of the sentence.
Yeah, for sure.
Do you mean for sure?
When we for sure?
Hey, let's not add any words.
It was a tidy sentence up until the end.
The moment you say, oh, hey, I'm going out of town for a little while.
Mike and I just start salivating like Captain Kid.
Captain Kid, Captain Kid.
Yeah, the first day.
That bastard's not holding us back anymore.
He's trying to have dessert for breakfast.
He's trying to have dessert for dinner.
Reviewing the by far the worst reviewed restaurant
in the vicinity of Disneyland Park.
You will have to come back from that trip because we have
we will list you as our emergency contact for Anaheim General Hospital.
We check in for any number of bacon, the poor and illness.
Scott pulls the plug on both of us who are in the.
I'm taking it one step further than Nick Mundy,
who yanked your microphone cord out.
Yeah, I'm yanking your living cords out.
They say that was a saline drip.
We were just trying to hydrate them.
Close enough. They'll die slowly over months.
So, yes. So to finish up the hack, essentially don't
find a spot where your phone has either good hotel
Wi-Fi or a good strong signal in the park vicinity somewhere.
And you don't necessarily need to because we walked over by the land.
I think that was maybe a mistake because it wasn't the strongest signal.
And we had problems getting right in and getting a group on the app.
But I watched some people.
People were counting down to 8 a.m. inside Galaxy's Edge.
There was a mass in Galaxy's Edge who all jumped on.
And some of them got earlier groups than us.
I will say that. So.
So some of them didn't get through on the app,
but they did accidentally get a transmission from a long dead emperor
and discovered he's still alive on a secret underground plant.
I didn't know I would have liked to have gotten that transmission.
Would have been cool. Very surprising.
I'll be honest, it sounds confusing.
No, I think it's pretty clean what I'm what I'm setting up.
It sounds like excess people die and then they come back to life years later
and have them like are kept alive by a big like cord tree,
but a big like group of dongles.
And they've built any number of country bear shows,
like hundreds and hundreds of country bears.
So you're saying I'm saying my theme park.
Yeah, the theme park equivalent.
Exegol has 20 country bear shows.
OK, so I see some of the ones.
So in this bit, Exegol is the Sith planet,
but the country bears are being built.
The bears live, the bears speak.
So the bears are the emperor.
OK, since Return of the Jedi,
the emperor has been building animatronic shows under that ocean,
that exegol ocean for 30 years,
and then they will all rise up at a certain point.
His favorite music, bluegrass.
He loves Steve Palpatine's favorite music is bluegrass.
The same name as that woman from Succession.
Yes. Yeah, that's where I mean, I look,
I would have loved it. They got the exegol.
It was shit.
Voila.
A different cinematic baddie.
So, yeah, so we got on the app at 8 a.m.
We had three of us trying.
So that's also another tip.
If you have multiple people in your group,
put your passes on each person's phone and have everybody try because,
you know, God knows the thing crashes.
It doesn't work.
I didn't. I look, I'm a masterchecker.
I'm not a master code breaker, but I'm a masterchecker.
And I didn't get the reservation. My phone kept crashing.
Cover the spread. Cover the spread.
That's what we're saying.
Wow. But this this was and I posted this on Instagram,
the moment of you preparing for your most
like the check of your life, basically.
Yeah. And I must have been thrilling.
It was. But sometimes you fail when you check.
You failed. But by enacting the plan
by which other people succeeded, it was still your victory.
That is true. Thank you for saying that.
Because I really hadn't thought about it.
I just sort of had felt bad about not being the one to get like a really high
because I you know, I wanted to get like, oh, I pulled Group three. Sure.
That's what I wanted for for my ego.
You win the game by one point or 30 points.
It doesn't matter. You still want to get one.
Yeah, you're right. Yeah.
And we did. And we did make it.
And just so it's like so for people who are going and trying to do this.
And hopefully it is still the boarding pass system.
But the time this episode comes out or all of this is irrelevant advice.
But with our sort of randomized and with Mike
having us all covered the spread, we got on.
We were 87, which as the day played out
and we know that there were several short breakdowns of the ride,
maybe 45 minutes to an hour.
This was 8 a.m. Group 87.
We got on at 7 p.m.
And that includes breakdowns.
So let that be kind of your guide.
If you get before 80, you're probably in for sure.
After 80, you're dancing on the line.
But maybe the app says like, you'll get in if you're 82 or under
where they don't want to promise it. Right. I see.
And I think Saturday they went over the amount they went on Friday.
So ideally it's getting better.
I checked on Saturday.
I know on Friday they capped it at like one like in the early one hundreds.
They gave it out to 120.
I think they capped it around 110, 111 by Saturday night at 740.
Second day of operation.
They were at groups 109 to 111.
So get a little faster. OK.
And closing the window to of like the the amount of groups that.
So if you're post 100, don't despair. Still possible. Yes.
And then you get a full day in the park.
But I think don't expect to go
and check out the ride in the morning and be on your merry way in the afternoon.
If you get there at 8 a.m., you are committing to potentially being there
all the way till midnight. Yes, for sure.
Unless you can find like the highest speed Internet
in the park and you can get right on.
But yeah, that's I wouldn't count on that. Yeah.
It's a and even then sort of like finger dexterity is
part of the issue and probably the biggest, probably the newest phone.
Making sure it's the newest version of the app.
Go a lot of factors. Go and upgrade your phones.
Go get the hottest new phone.
I don't know what it is.
Get the one with the best processing speed,
with the best network coverage.
You know, this is all prep you need to get on a ride.
And maybe know somebody who has fast fingers.
Maybe if you have a friend who's like a court stenographer
or something that requires or a pianist.
Yes, that's a good one.
Or pickpocket like Liberace.
Yes, if you know any Anaheim pickpockets.
For sure.
Although, you know, is that fingers or is that wrist is pickpocketing?
What is the what do you need?
It's applicable.
And I think I think quick fingers would have to help
because you have to make sure they aren't felt. Yeah, that's true.
They're in and out of a pocket without impact.
Well, when you think about close up magicians, when you think about that's another.
Yes. Yes. Good category. That's good.
That that is good.
But I'm saying when you think of because all I can think of is
the man who was playing Liberace in behind the candelabra,
which wasn't like they put Michael Douglas's head on that guy.
I am standing his hands.
I'm thinking that guy's got fast fingers.
Yeah. I think even if you're a pianist, probably get practicing.
Probably like make sure you can do Liberace double time.
Yes. Just like being like being able to play a nice little dirge
isn't going to help you. You got to be a fast pianist.
Yeah. So you got to be a piano kind of guy.
Did you do that today? Did you do that today?
Ragtime. If you can play if you.
Ragtime will be helpful. Play multiple different rags,
different type of rags where you can play would be helpful.
Guitar is applicable to if you know anything, Hale.
You get him in. Oh, yeah.
If you can shred, keep shredding, shredding also valuable.
You know, I really we mentioned Liberace before.
I'm realizing now like Liberace needs to come up up on the show.
I think a little bit more. Sure.
So I just want to throw that out there.
Well, there's not a museum anymore. Is there?
I mean, that weird thing you can visit when I'm scared of visiting.
The weird thing that Eva Anderson told us about where you just pay some money
to a guy in a limo who picks you up and then he takes you to some
like undisclosed location and you look at stuff.
He was like room temperature champagne in his limo.
Yeah. And I'll I'll do it.
I'll do it.
So we can talk about it, at least in that.
That's like the themed experience with Liberace, essentially, as far as I know.
I think there was a more committed museum at one point in time.
But for some reason, kids aren't going to the Liberace Museum
and they had to shut it down for whatever reason.
Dumbasses. I know what's happening to the kids.
Yeah. OK. But so fast fingers required.
Yes. We made it.
I think it's interesting to this.
A lot of playing with your expectations, training you.
The Disney parks training you.
This is training people how to use advanced features of the apps
because you have to link all of your party's tickets into, in theory,
just one app.
But like, I haven't done this a lot.
Like, Mike, you know, the ins and outs of this app, you know,
you know, the Max Pass system back and forth.
I feel like not a lot of people are on an X.
You know, it left and right.
Yeah. The Disneyland app is like my X wing.
You have no control over how fucking buggy and weird this app is
in terms of signing you out and making you log back in and just crashing
when you try to use one of its features.
Yeah. Make sure activate touch ID so that the footprint goes through
so you don't have to retype your password because you'll get signed out randomly.
Yes. Or face ID.
OK. I don't have that, but I get that.
Yeah, it is.
I don't know how many people were in the park in the morning
because I wonder if it's like,
I don't even know how to guess because there were a ton of people.
There were thousands. Yeah.
Oh, was it 10, 20? Maybe.
It was kind of crazy.
We're at like a super packed main street.
It was only half open.
And then dramatically, they opened it all the way to the hub.
And we were crouched over by the the plaza in or the other.
No, the Jolly Holiday.
Yeah, yeah. We're crouched over there for a while.
It's kind of exciting.
I hadn't been to Disneyland in the morning when it's dark,
probably since the high school grad nights I got to do.
That's a that's a fun way to do it.
There was a lot of excitement.
You know, you guys convinced me to come to the opening day of this
and of Galaxy's Edge. Great time at both.
I assume both were going to be a zoo.
I was still picturing what I know about when Indiana Jones
adventure opened in the 90s.
And it is clear how much Disney has learned since then.
It is so much more than just getting a big line,
which Hagrid's that we just talked about seems to just be getting a huge line.
Big line. But Disney has created these systems where you could
you could be shit out of luck.
You might not to get it might not get to get on the thing at all.
But, you know, in both of these cases are like the board.
The digital boarding groups worked great.
You know, we had to wait all day, but that's a whole day.
You get in Disneyland. Yeah, it was a blast.
Yeah, I wonder. Like, I don't know.
Now that they have the system figured out, I guess they'll just employ it
with most things they open, I would guess,
because like, yeah, Marvel land phase one opens.
I assume they'll use a similar thing
because I don't think like you'll always have obviously people
like that come for the ride that can't get on the ride.
And it's a big pain in the ass.
But it's not going to be like
what you're saying, where it's just like the line is all the way down
to Captain Kid's Buffet or something for like Indiana Jones.
You're in the line.
You might as well grab a handful of eggs since you're right there.
Yeah. Pay your force into the room.
Pay your four or five dollars for the buffet and get the eggs
and you get them to go and eat them as you go.
If a line ever forces you into a unrelated
buffet establishment. Yeah. Yeah.
But so I mean, anything else in terms of like
tips to do it or can we talk about the the ride?
The actual ride? I'm trying to think.
I think that's really all it is.
I mean, I would also just keep an eye on Disney social media
because they do change things from time to time.
So we're recording this a few days before this comes out.
But by the time this comes out, that could also be have changed.
All this could be irrelevant.
So but as it stands, if it's still the boarding pass system,
just make sure you're in the park at 8 a.m.
It's all matters. Don't do any camp outs unless unless you want.
Unless that's just for a fun bonding experience.
Just give yourself enough time
so you're not like cutting it close to 8 a.m.
because like you just want to be going to be crowded.
You want to be such like you want to be like in a spot
and you want to know where your Wi-Fi or your
you will lose at 8 or 5, 8 or 5.
You're you're done. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
So you got to be like firmly in the park, not like
like, oh, shit, at turnstiles at seven fifty nine.
Yeah. Like, no, don't be in the Starbucks line at seven fifty.
And like, like really, like, make sure you get in there with enough time
and 15 minutes to sort of
zoom around and see where your phone has good signal.
It seems like in Florida,
the window is starting to open up a little more. Yeah.
Like they're still get like 30 minutes in 40 minutes in.
You could still get into group here.
I don't know. I mean, I think these boarding groups will be in play
on both coasts for at least a couple of months, if not long.
Probably. Yeah, it seems like that.
And stuff's going to be buggy. Stuff's going to break down.
We've been told, expect this ride to break down
like four or five hours up, one hour down.
But like, there's a lot of staff.
There's a lot of people working on it to get it back up quickly.
But it made it pretty good opening day, seemingly.
I don't it certainly was not some PR.
We're talking about that with Paul Scheer last week, who joined us,
who was with us for the day.
And he was he said in our episode last week, they need Disneyland needs a win.
This has to go great. And I think it went great.
I don't know any bad PR out there.
Yeah, I'm sure there's a few people in groups that didn't get on.
But that's it.
Like, which, of course, sucks.
But it's not like people were in line for seven hours.
I saw Disney. I think even in Florida, they're going so far to try to may
still make it a win that they like.
I think there was a long amount of time that the ride was down
and they were handing out free chips and like water.
And then they made Ray walk through the line
to take photos with everybody.
So like we can't make the campy man.
We can't have like people being like our three in line on Rise of the Resistance
or anything. So they're even hypersensitive, I think.
Hyper. Yeah, like it's true.
Everybody was cheered up once they were like once Ray passed through
and everybody got to shout, no, no, your last name.
What's your last name?
She answered every single person what her last name is.
Yeah, they all wanted to know. Yeah. Yeah.
Really, actually, you talk about PR and Disney and Star Wars.
This is of the two products in the last month with rise in the title.
One of them has been incredibly well received.
That's and it's nice to see.
I don't want to say which one it is on your own.
Yeah, yeah, that's true.
It is that is funny that they're both rise.
They're both first.
Yeah, the resistance had to rise in Florida
so that Skywalker could rise on the movie screens.
And then the resistance had to rise again in Los Angeles. Yeah.
That's the getting back up.
Like this is the second second and like not.
No, it's not down now.
It hasn't been knocked out yet. Still rising.
Still rising.
Although we talked about, I think one of you pulled it.
I described it.
Carly had found the had taken a screen grab of the picture
that was briefly posted on the official Disneyland account,
which is like a beautiful Renaissance painting of like a child
and her dad seemingly running away from Galaxy's Edge and R2D2.
And in the middle of the photograph is just Bob Iger looking confused.
And it does look like they not know when they posted it.
What's that? Do they not realize that?
Iger is there.
I think they'd probably just were like, oh, this is kind of a cute picture.
And then maybe like enough comments were like, huh, this is kind of weird.
This is weird. And then people like, oh, we've got to get away.
Got to get it out of there.
He looks like he looks mad.
It does look like a little girl is upset running away from an angry Bob Iger.
Rob Iger and R2D2.
But it is like a beautiful, confusing painting.
It is like an abstract work.
Yeah, yeah, I finally caught it.
Yeah, it's very good.
I'm trying to think of things we can say because I think just out of necessity,
this will become a spoilery episode and will certainly
alert the firm, you know, point of no return on that.
But what can we say in terms of just what I was thinking of things to say
before we talk about it?
Clearly, a lot of credit has to be given to Scott Trowbridge.
I think this going on the ride is where it has registered with me
that he is the Tony Baxter of today.
I think he is the 2020s or the 2010s and has been for a while because
for people who don't know all the mythology, he's responsible for it.
He's been in charge of this entire project of all of Galaxy's Edge.
And if you watch the Imagineering story,
which we talk about on the second gate, he's kind of the most prominent
imaginary in episode six and the final episode of it.
And clearly with good reason, they like that he stacks up
with your your gurrs and your Baxter's.
He was a universal person
where his magnum opus over there was the Spider-Man ride.
The amazing adventure.
Yeah. And heavily involved with all the Harry Potter stuff.
Yeah. Seemingly like laid out the plans, like figured out
the all like the basics of it and the immersiveness of it.
And then before it was built,
got snatched by Disney and right over there.
And it doesn't seem like he's had like a super public.
What's his amazing Disney project until Galaxy's Edge?
But boy, that's worth the wait.
Obviously, he's been working on it forever.
And he's like, I think he's technically he's the head of Imagineering now.
OK, I believe isn't that no, isn't that God Bob Weiss,
the head of Imagineering?
Or is that like president?
All right. Yeah, I know.
I shouldn't know, because these titles are so confusing.
Portfolio. He's he's like in there.
It's like the top of some aspect of Imagineering.
I'm almost positive.
So it might be a different name than what I said or what you.
Yes. So Rodie, I don't know what anyone is.
Yeah, because Rodie's been there forever.
And he has to have.
He's he's like lead explorer of Imagineering.
He's head of the pack of Imagineer of Imagineer.
Which doctor?
Yes, he's chief witch doctor.
But I think when you this ride without giving a lot away yet
shares a lot of DNA with the basic adventures of Spider-Man.
And I don't know how much he had to do with the actual ride
Harry Potter and Forbidden Journey.
But it's like it's akin to those where it's
a really rewarding mix of physical things and screens.
And it's truly surprising at every step.
It rearranges types of rides into new configurations
like you've never seen. Great third acts.
I think these all have very similar third acts.
These rides with big surprises.
Yeah. And with really satisfying screen sections,
which if you're on a pure screen ride, you can just get like,
All right, sure. I think I get all your moves.
And he all of Trowbridge's rides have like surprising
just like something up its sleeve at the end screens
molded into sets and used more gracefully than some other attractions.
Yeah. And I think this is like the most of anything.
Like you would never and never ever would you call this a screen ride,
despite the fact that it probably has like 100 screens in it.
Yeah. It's like doing surprising things that are supporting
like the big headlines are the physical sets and the tangible things.
And there there was one and I'm sure we'll get to it later,
but there is an effect that combines the screens and physical
stuff in the location that I didn't realize when we were first in it,
because I was so affixed at the physical set in the animatronic
where I was like, oh, my God, that happens because something happened
on the screen. And it's so and there's a big audio cue,
but it's so of a one of one piece that I was like,
oh, I was just impressed by the one piece.
I didn't even see until later on. There's other things.
As we're saying, they're like we'll get a hardline spoiler in a little bit.
Who knows? It could be another hour before soon, I assume.
But there's stuff where stuff where I was like, I don't know how they did this.
And then it's so clear how they did it.
You just miss it when you're on the ride because you're
you're immersed in the story. Yeah.
Yeah. I also had to give credit to Disney.
I don't know what is again, I don't know his title creative executive.
John Lorena comes up in a lot of the longer articles about this.
He is talking to Trowbridge in the rise section in Imagineering Story,
which I went back and watched.
But they're looking at like the the, you know,
rehearsal runs of some sequence, like not fully 100% there yet.
But like, OK, this is what it looks like when you do this.
And he him and Trowbridge are like walking through stuff,
sharing little notes. Yeah.
A thing I didn't know about Trowbridge till I looked it up this morning,
his first job in theme park world, Sanrio Puroland.
Wow. I didn't know.
Wow. Me so happy now that I've been there and really enjoyed it.
Like there is some real unique spirit and energy.
And he was there in the very beginning.
I think he went in eighty nine for them for the opening.
So there's like original bones DNA at Sanrio Puroland of this guy.
Now clearly one of the theme park greats.
And the most wonderful thing about all this, we had been on the ride.
We were blown away by the ride.
We went to cool down with some some milk at the milk stand.
And who should walk by in a Star Wars cast member crew jacket?
But Scott Trowbridge, I love the fact that we recognize him.
Yeah. So shows the level.
So I hear Scott goes, is that Scott Trowbridge?
And I turn around and I go, oh, yeah, for sure.
It's Scott Trowbridge.
Yes, we're good. I'm glad we found each other.
And we said hi to him.
In my mind, we're like, well, let the television, let the famous man
kind of follow. Let's let him get out front. So.
I yeah, I went and asked, are you Scott?
He said yes. And I was like, I just have to shake your hand.
I just want to shake your hand on this day.
And we were gushing about the ride.
And all he wanted to know was about the new type of milk that we had.
Yes. Yeah. What's the type of milk? What's the milk?
Yes. He very home. Oh, yeah.
We'll get to the milk.
We'll get to the milk in the section where we talked before.
Sith artifact that may have been my undoing.
Well, why are we? Why do we have to wait on that one?
You're right. It's a true toy.
Dairy. Yeah, right. That's the milk from Toy Dairy.
Dairy and swirl. The toy.
Dairy and swirl.
Or is it not a ride spoiler?
So might as well.
You're right. Dairy and swirl.
Is it Toy Dairy in or Toy Dairy us?
World. Is there an end at the end?
I I wrote down an end, but I could be just double check.
I may have misread it.
It's from Watto's planet.
Then, yes. Yeah.
But it's like it's like it looks like spiced milk.
There's like something at the top.
There's an imagine.
He's the chili lime seasoning to heat.
There is an imaginary mango jelly inside.
There is an imaginary who loves Wado.
Yeah, because there's a toy.
Dairy and toy not shop.
What is it? Toy stall.
Toy. Yeah, it is with an end.
Toy Dairy and Swirl Green.
Someone wrote it wrong and I read it.
OK, so a couple of us had this milk
and he mainly wanted to know how the milk was, which was a nice
it felt like him deflecting.
He reminded me of when we met Tony Baxter and he just said,
have you guys done Guardians yet?
He didn't want to accept all this praise about his life and bodywork,
which he knew we were probably going to try to do.
He's like deflecting and let's talk about the greater good.
Like what else is happening?
Yeah, he wanted to talk about the cosplay.
He was like, oh, some great cosplay.
He didn't want to be like, oh, that's great.
Thank you so much.
What else did you like about my ride or anything?
He wasn't going to he wasn't going to be like he just wanted to.
Yeah, deflect and talk about everyone else. Pretty cool.
That's a that's a cool way to be.
Now let's talk about your stomach.
What happened, Jason?
So, OK, so we all got and the rise coming up to this.
So the rise coming after this after this 45 minutes.
First, we'll transport you to Jason's stomach.
You know, it was a long day.
It was like I woke up at 4 a.m. that day.
I think I went to bed at 11 p.m. that night.
A good portion of that spent at Disneyland.
Jason and I Jason and I Jason and I had seen Doolittle and IMAX
the night before, so we had a wild ride.
So still a little wound up.
It's OK to be sleepy.
I couldn't get to sleep.
I was just thinking that.
Did that sound like Doolittle's Welsh?
No, not at all. It's OK to be scared.
This is my if I had to do my Doolittle, it's OK to be scared.
It's OK to be scared.
Maybe the E is OK to be scared.
I mean, I don't want to drop a spoiler for Doolittle,
but the exit is not consistent.
I don't want to drop a spoiler.
And I didn't see Doolittle, but and I don't want to drop a spoiler for it.
But Dragon's asshole.
I did just drop a spoiler.
But I won't say how a dragon does.
Wait, wait, asshole, Scott.
Seat hole. Seat hole.
I think that's a word. I think.
So seat is more innocent than ass.
I think seat hole is more disgusting than asshole.
I don't know. Let the audience decide.
That's just me, though. Yeah.
Me and the dragon both having intestinal issues that day.
Jason was a lot like the dragon.
I was a lot like the dragon for Doolittle.
OK, I mean, I should have account.
I always forget that when it's cold out,
I'm going to spend a lot of time in the cold and I'm going to be up for a long time.
I need to watch what I eat.
And starting the day at 430 a.m.
with a large coffee and a donut from 7-Eleven, maybe didn't put me on the best footing.
So I wrote down what I ate to try and figure out where I went wrong.
Coffee and donut at 430 a.m.
around 11, 1130, a vegetarian Ronto wrap in Galaxy.
Very good. Delicious.
Then the Aloha Sculpin, the guava and pineapple
infused IPA at Ballast Point.
Not grapefruit, not grapefruit.
How did you find the price point on that?
Actually, I find I think it's fair at micro microbreweries,
usually because you're buying it right from the source.
How much was it? Pretty well priced.
Seven dollars for an eight ounce pour.
Not a full pint still.
And then we had some press.
If you buy the bottles from the store, it's much cheaper per bottle.
But that's just you're buying it at a bigger. OK.
We had some pretzel bites with beer cheese for the table.
I really like that beer cheese.
Before the Sculpin, that's where I had the toy
dairy and swirl. And I was like, this is interesting.
I'll try it for the sake of it being interesting.
But like spicy cold goo drink, because it had like mango jelly,
like boba kind of jelly in there, too.
That may have been undoing.
Then about three or four, we all got coffees.
I had a tall coffee at Starbucks.
Then I had a granola bar.
And this is where it's I think that many weird
that meant that combination of beverages without food.
And it's not like a firm meal in there, not like a firm meal,
which didn't come until about at nine p.m.
Mike and I stopped at Portillo's and I had a hot dog on the way home.
You had Portillo's. I needed actual food.
The hot dog was fine.
The hot dog helped because you needed actual food, not hot dogs.
It was a Chicago dog.
So the guard, I had the garden and the vegetables.
There was vegetable.
There's any number of pickled vegetables.
Basically like a salad.
It was like a salad, basically, with a little kind of like a salad.
But I thought about getting a Caesar salad and it made the thought made me ill.
Like, I don't know.
Can Caesar salads can be real dicey of like, is this a real Caesar salad
or is this the goo dressing?
Well, most places, it's just the dressing.
And so, I mean, by the time you get going to dock on,
you went to docking Bay seven, you ate a dinner dinner,
which had its own calamity of like the restaurants were just crushed.
That's something to watch out for.
We kept experiencing that people were waiting forever for Star Wars food,
just because everybody wants it while this ride is open. Right.
Did you say your Ronto rap?
I said the Ronto. You did. I missed it.
And that was fun, I think, like because it was like, well,
if I had breakfast at 4 a.m., lunch would come six or seven hours later.
That makes sense.
Did you have the veg? I forget.
Did you have vegetarian vegetarian and I really like Michael?
I'm sorry. I zoned right out.
I really like the list of what he ate for some bizarre reason.
I was like, honestly, and that is weird because I'm usually right along with.
So that is very tuned.
But I came back from the bar and everyone had ordered iced tea.
Well, Scott, you had a glass of wine.
Sure did. And I was like, oh, yeah, maybe I shouldn't have gotten a beer.
It like knew that was the other thing.
I was like, God, I am exhausted.
And it was 1230 p.m.
So I don't know. Getting up that early.
I need to force myself to go to bed a little earlier when I have to get out that early.
I was dressed warm. I was plenty warm.
What do you think cold has to do with it?
The cold just wears on me.
It just I do much better in heat.
I mean, I don't disagree with that.
But as far as like your stomach being concerned, like, I don't know.
The cold makes your stomach more stressed out.
You get stressed because it's cold.
I think maybe I'm not like mentally stressed, but I feel like I feel very flushed
pretty quickly.
And also, I was pretty like,
but while we were just killing time, waiting for 8 a.m.
to roll around, I was starting to lag a bit just because there was no
there wasn't really any. We weren't walking around.
We just kind of hang around, chit chatting, fiddling with our phones.
And I think that was like, oh, God, I need to, you know, once we start
going on stuff and walking around, I perked up a little more.
So what happened? You barfered you a lot.
No, I wasn't doing anything for a while.
I was just like stuck.
So we're talking Saturday. You were backed up Friday night.
I was Friday.
Like, finally, once the hot dog got the gears.
And we don't get too gross.
Maybe this is a lot of people's first time listening to podcasts.
All right. If it is. Oh, boy. Yeah.
Just skip ahead like 20.
Yeah, I also don't want to get too gross.
We'll say what's in the right contributor.
But I will say like this is a big part of the podcast.
You know, I just have to get used to it.
Yes. Saturday. I was fucking weird.
I was like, that's not how that's where I'm going.
But I also want to say, like, it is when you're at theme park,
it throws off the way your body gets rid of waste.
Like indicated, like if you would, it'll like stop.
It'll stop you from going to the bathroom because like you're on a move
so much. Yeah.
Because you're it's like, you know, you're always in flight.
And I think you're trying to avoid those.
But I think your body does not want to go sit on a theme park.
Well, and yes, I know where the good ones are, but it's never the convenient ones.
Good ones usually good because they're off the beaten path.
You said there is a bathroom in the line for Rise of the Resistance.
That's what I heard. I didn't see it. I didn't see it.
There was one kind of alcove hallway where I was like, maybe it's around there.
Yeah, I'm not sure where it is.
I don't know if I don't know if you asked the R5 droid nicely.
He might have driven us all to a restroom.
Let you to the bathroom.
And then yes, yeah, the bathroom and gotten us off of the ship.
There's a bathroom droid, I assume. Yeah.
You should. Yes, you should.
You should into the bathroom droids head.
It's let's see, is there like a dirty number letter situation
we could come up with with the Star Wars bathroom droid is got to be.
Oh, it's just number two.
B.M. two. Yeah, I was going to say like
P zero zero P like oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, that works for P zero dash zero P P OOP.
Yeah, that's good.
P OOP is here. Open your head, please.
Master Windu needs to use you.
Master Joe's Mace Windu.
I don't know.
Beep boop boop boop boop.
I like he says thanks.
It's what he lives for.
This is the best.
I kind of took it. Yeah, I think all of Saturday.
Building a bathroom droid instead.
Or no, Anakin was building a bathroom droid instead of C3P.
See, there is the first ready built that wasn't for pooping in. Yeah.
Welcome to podcast right if it's your first time.
So try to just just yeah, your bodies act in differently at a theme park.
So I messed up by not having trying to like have three square meals
because every now and then at the parks are like, try this new snack.
And I'm like, well, I guess I kind of want to try.
You don't know if they're going to keep it around for a while.
But like, be careful of that. Just be careful.
Don't go to a hot dog place after all this.
Try the pump that got that put me back on equilibrium
because that was a real real food.
I again question your use of I didn't.
I felt better after the hot.
I felt better out of the hot.
And like Saturday, I just I had like a granola bar.
I drank a lot of water at night.
I had a couple small slices of like cheese pizza, like very simple food.
How much did you sleep?
Because we were obviously we didn't get enough sleep.
How much did you sleep Saturday?
Like 10 hours or so, like Friday into Saturday, like 10 hours.
Yeah, OK. And then probably a similar.
I was wiped out on Saturday.
I took a nap on Saturday. Yeah, for sure.
It took it out of me.
But my stomach wasn't screwed up, although I didn't.
I did not have any alcohol.
And yeah, anyway, good boy.
I didn't want to get sleepy. Yeah, yeah, it did.
Yes, it did make me sleepy.
So are we there? Do we do it?
Yeah, I think unless you have any more stomach updates.
No, but I do recommend that veggie ronto wrap. Try that.
It is. Yeah, the veggie ronto wrap really good.
Sometimes like, yeah, like a veggie sausage or vegan sausage.
Kind of weird. But no, I really liked it.
Yeah. And the veggie thing in Docking Bay also very good.
Oh, it seemed to beat the enduring yip yip.
Which our friend Matt was kind of displeased with.
Right. You warned him, Jason.
So maybe stay away from that yip yip.
It was not like outstanding.
Which is funny because I half mile away
at the Plaza is like amazing. Very good.
And I think it's safe to say that the ronto has ronto wrap is very quickly
entered. It's come in hot as one of the best food yet.
Disney parks. Welcome, brother.
Welcome to the Sausage Society.
Just need a little more going on.
I needed my jerky and my fancy slaw and my cheetah.
It's very it's a very mature hot dog entry.
And they and I believe they ran out the first day.
People so wanted to pair their rise of the resistance with a ronto wrap
that they they ran out of them.
Then they had more rontos.
I want to try that.
I haven't tried the breakfast one yet either. Yeah.
So, yeah, they keep the variations coming.
Also, I say, yes. Yeah.
Yeah. So rise the resistance.
Yeah. Y'all.
Fuck. We're only two minutes into the podcast.
Yeah. We're so screwed here. God damn it.
So, yeah, I mean, I don't think
I don't think anybody was disappointed.
I think all of the speculation we've done over many episodes.
Is this going to be the missing piece?
Yeah. Makes the whole galaxy's edge picture work completely.
I know it's it's wonderful. It's it is.
It's really so good. It's really, really amazing.
It's really impressive.
I at the end, I have some nitpicky thoughts, but they're all, you know.
I mean, I think, yeah, any attraction, you're going to like
there's one or two things, but they like I can imagine
whoever worked on this would be right to tell me to fuck off after I say it.
But I will, because, you know, we have to.
This is what, you know, yeah, that's what we're doing here.
I said when we were there, I was like, it's such a flex.
Oh, yeah. I mean, of like what imagineering is capable of with the time and budget.
Yeah, I was trying to think of what is the closest thing even to it?
I mean, there's obviously it's it takes elements from every other ride.
Yeah. Yeah. That's the cool thing about it.
Maybe now we say spoiler.
Yeah, I guess we can refer to scenes. Yeah. All right.
You survived. I guess, right.
I hope you enjoyed all the stomach detailing and listen to it.
I have to listen to this after you go on the right.
And I don't also all of those individual items I had.
I think they were all fine.
I don't think any of those were bad.
The combination and the timing is what I'm pissed at that granola bar.
Fuck you, granola bar.
I will not have disparaging the fine people in the Nature Valley.
You said, OK.
Wait, you said the items are OK.
Yeah. Yeah. You live and you live mostly on kind bars
and I live mostly on nature.
Yeah, that's right. I do have one in my pocket currently. Yeah.
So, yeah.
OK. In terms of elements, yes, there are like
it is this bizarre.
How do you even describe the recipe?
It's there's there are definite.
I think Indiana Jones is probably the closest analog in terms of scale,
in terms of that it's not a roller coaster, but it's very exciting
in a surprising ride vehicle way.
It does things you don't expect it to do.
It's whipping around the biggest scale sets you've ever seen.
Yeah. Just I think the the height it is.
There are plenty of wonderful attractions that are not tall.
All of the Fantasyland dark rides are very short and they're all delightful.
But oh, my God, the like, I think not since Indiana Jones
has there been something so multi story
and we are exploring every possible corner of this massive building.
You know, I saw an imagine you're referring to like you have to
if you think back to Pirates of the Caribbean, this is a natural
evolution or extension, because that also similarly
puts you right in the middle of a battle.
Now you're a kind of an observer, an outside observer to it.
You don't really affect what's going on in pirates.
But yeah, pirates in Indiana Jones, kind of the natural.
Yeah, yeah. And there's yeah, definitely pirate component.
And that way, yeah, like here's the zone that kind of eases you into it.
And then it gets super exciting.
And then Haunted Mansion components, obviously, in that the cast members
have stuff to do.
There's finally I guess Jungle Cruise, too.
There's finally like a third answer to where do you where would you want to work?
Probably Jungle Cruise and Haunted Mansion, because you get to like
do the personality choices.
And now you've got this ride with this.
This is a wonderful role, I think, for a cast member.
Yeah. Yeah.
The biggest I mean, I guess I shouldn't say the biggest change, because, yeah,
we're talking about Haunted Mansion and Tower of Terror rides
where the cast members get to do a character if they want
and get to be weird or rude or mean, which is fun.
But this really felt much more because we've you know,
we've done a couple of immersive things in the last year.
And those are on the rise, I feel like.
And escape rooms are popular.
And like it felt so very much like one of those things.
Yeah, it feels like a mega budget immersive experience.
Like I wasn't even expecting it to feel like that much.
But it is like that's what it is.
Yeah. And the people they have opening this attraction,
the cast members are so on it.
They are so they're like they're performing great while doing just basic.
How many people in your party?
Yes, you could see a world in 20 years where the performance isn't like
I could see this decaying a little bit.
And it's a little more like how many how many.
But like opening day doing this in January, 2020,
you've just got top of the line people.
Everybody's doing a great job.
Everyone's psyched probably to be there still.
And two different varieties, because half of them are like resistance fighters
going like, come on, come on, we need your help.
And then the other half are like, Fasci first order, like stand in the line.
Like a British character actor, like you're going to be interrogated momentarily.
There was one man.
This guy can't really control how tall he is.
There was what I will describe as one of the tallest men I have ever seen.
And he was a first order guy and he was so good.
And he was like menace to small.
Like it was one of the best performance moments I've ever seen in a park
where like there was a kid going like, no way.
And this guy is like, you're going to get extra interrogation.
And I was like, this is incredible.
This is so good.
Yeah, they'll get they'll pick on specific people.
They'll get right in people's faces.
I mean, how do we do that?
Should we kind of kind of go back a little bit yet to the start?
I mean, all right.
The line, which in its current state, there may be a point in time
where you just you get in this line, you're in this line for a long time.
But right now, it's more like Indiana Jones, where they're holding you outside
and then you just breeze right through it, which is cool because getting to just tear
through this long series of hallways and not even really perceive everything
that's there is kind of neat.
I kind of like just getting to zip through all that.
But clearly, there's amazing details in the line, which is how would you describe it?
It's a resistance base. It's like a hidden.
It's like hollowed out of like a mountain or of like everything.
Like you go mind.
It feels like blown up.
Yes. Form the like the room base in 1917 or something like it is.
I mean, that's kind of what it is.
Like in a story explanation is that these are like ancient caves,
like hollowed out ancient caves.
And the rebels have ad hoc set up a base
that you can see like stuffs in temporary cages.
Wires look rigged up like there's a lot of hanging.
The equivalent of hanging clamp lights.
So they had to get out of here quickly. They could.
And then there's yeah, there's weapons and there's weapons or uniforms,
like computer consoles.
And it's it's a cousin to
Smuggler's Run in that both clearly start and end that.
But to they keep the general story of the two going.
And it's not like Star Tours, where once you enter the Star Tours building,
it's just, well, I guess, where are we now?
I don't know. And you end in indoor on whatever other planet.
And then why are you back in Disneyland?
Nothing that's ever bothered me about Star Tours.
But it's just cool that they both like to keep but to the live.
It's like it can be one long story going on all these attractions. Right.
Yeah, that's very cool.
And then, of course, as we know, we've said before, they tie in Star Tours
to but to in ways as well.
You see it in there, which is really great.
Yeah, because that because obviously, like they were so gung ho
about making sure all of this story wise made sense
and fit into the official Lucasfilm timeline for the movie.
Super strict, like it's kind of timeless, but it plays
sometime after Last Jedi before Rise of Skywalker. Right.
Some of the characters have been killed since this ride.
And some of the characters have been killed off screen
on by Wikipedia entries and then specifically nine numb.
Is that how you say it? Yeah.
The little little dude who drives you around, who operates a vehicle in this.
What in the world? I credit Mike Mitchell with the kind of helping blow that up.
He died in the battle in Resco, off screen.
And that guy, he's dead now.
Why? Why did he have to go? I don't know.
Everyone likes him.
You would think at least show him getting blown up.
Happy to see him here.
Somebody that I feel like somebody tried to dispute that
that he actually died off screen.
I feel like that's a debate maybe now, but I don't know.
Was somebody on a Wikipedia making a big leap?
I have no idea. Yeah.
The whole.
Do you know the story of the voice?
Do you remember this being talked about in a panel a long time ago?
Familiar. It's this is this was the case with
this guy. The guy who did it was his name is Kip Singh.
Rodech, that's the voice of this little pilot guy and I know.
And he he did he did those lines in Return of the Jedi
in a mix of Kenyan dialects.
Oh, I don't know this. Who he was,
was a he was interning.
He was like he had traveled from Kenya and was interning at Skywalker Sound
and had been helping out Ben Burt, who did all who did like design
the Sanford Star Wars and ultimately did Wally. Right.
That's the same guy. Yeah, I think. Right. That's right.
I think so. So he was.
Yeah, he was around.
And I think the way he made it over is that he met on a safari.
Pat Welsh, the old lady who voiced E.T.
Wow. Like a kind of a husky, raspy voice
that lend itself to E.T.
And they connected in Kenya and that caused him to come learn about making movies.
Oh, my God. In the Bay Area with Ben Burt.
So he had these couple lines and this was that character wasn't like anything
anybody was thinking about then.
So just like, I don't know, could you do it?
And he like, well, maybe it'll sound like an alien language
if I combine a couple dialects.
And then he goes back to Kenya.
This becomes legendary on the way to Force Awakens.
And this is last minute.
They cut to that character and nobody was thinking about dialogue.
And then in the sound step of it, they're like, we should give him some lines.
But how do you even write lines for that?
Because who knows these dialects? Right. Where's that guy?
And it was incredibly hard to track him down.
And Pat Welsh had died.
So that connect was out the window.
And it's as long as you can read it on Star Wars dot com.
The story of finding this guy.
And then eventually he was going by a different name.
And they did track him down in Kenya.
But this came up in a star in a panel with Trowbridge,
where they got him back for the ride, too.
And they went and recorded him in Nairobi.
Whoa. Wow. Yeah.
So this so when you hear his dialogue in this ride, that was recorded in Kenya.
And this man was just off the no one had like had eyes on this guy
through the 80s, 90s and 2000s.
And now he's back doing this character again.
And he hasn't like obviously he wasn't like going to conventions cashing in.
No. Yeah.
I don't think he realized the degree to which it had taken off.
I think he was surprised to be contacted.
And he also apparently when they got a hold of him, he told a story that he was also
he was around Skywalker when they were doing ET.
And Ben Burt wanted him to do ET.
Whoa. And he deferred to his friend, Pat, who thought like she deserves it.
She's the one who she brought me here and she should do it.
Like there was like, which one's going to do it?
And he gave it to her. Selfless.
He could have been ET to this.
This is all the strangest. That's wild. I didn't know any of that.
That's great. Shout out to tonight.
It was wonderful to see in this thing.
It's like it's a great trick of he's on monitors doing a lot more,
but you really only see the back of his head in the in the attraction.
A lot of animatronics in this.
Some very complex, some kind of simpler,
but works because they're either far away or they only have to do one thing.
Yeah. So there's many, many pre shows. Yes.
It's like five pre shows. It's funny.
I think we didn't know the amount of we'd always heard,
like it's kind of this pre rides and then the ride.
We didn't know in what order and how many.
It's interesting now, because I've been reading rumors about this for five years.
Five years. Yeah.
And at a certain point, there was a rumor, which I'm sure I excitedly said
to somebody in my vicinity, that you would get off in the middle of the ride.
Obviously, that was like a telephone.
I mean, I don't know if maybe that at a certain point was the idea,
but that that feels like a telephone thing
because there's so many different pre shows and then a bigger pre show
and another pre show and another pre show. Yeah.
And so that I could see where that kind of feels like you get off of a ride
and then you go on another ride, which is what kind of happens. Yeah. Yeah.
It's just not that the main ride
causes for you to like literally step off. Right.
Once you're on the right, you're on the ride.
But yeah, it is this multi room.
And even though there's there's a ride component
and then things you might consider lines in that you're not in it for very long.
Right. It's like and it makes story sense.
They've figured out a story reason why a bunch of people would be lined up.
And those are very interesting rooms to be in.
I'm just delighted talking about it.
It could be telephone or as we were told by someone that day,
every now and then, cast members will purposely feed outlets.
Oh, disinformation either for any number of reasons.
Either to protect stuff or because they're mad about something or just for fun.
What we were told was, yeah, maybe it was just like just for fun.
Sometimes there will be cast members trying to disrupt the flow of rumors.
That's so great.
Yes, because I'm watching you like a hawk now.
So is it possible that that rumor that Galaxy's Edge will be replaced by Aladdin
and that and as the website that I read it on,
where Aladdin is misspelled in the article is.
So is it possible that Disney isn't going to replace Galaxy's Edge
with a misspelled Aladdin?
Well, no, because that's been debunked.
It is going to become Lord of the Rings. Oh, OK.
Lord of the Rings will exist in two different parks after they bulldozed
Toon Lagoon.
Rise of the Ring. It'll turn to rise of the ring.
They're just going to put a beard on Hux and he will be. Yeah.
So not Gollum, who has a beard?
I missed that.
And number of our dear friends on Middle Earth.
Yes. OK, so
hologram room.
Oh, yeah. So the first room is
you're getting your first of many briefings.
Yes. And you first see BB8, who's sort of in a similar spot
to like where Rocket is a similar height.
But it's a little around a little shelf.
And he's rolling around, doing a ton.
And clearly, there's like some extra business of beeps that can fill delays.
And you're delighted to see him beeping.
You know, this is probably a stall, but it's wonderful to see.
You watch him talk for as long as possible.
Gasping in so many of these rooms, there's so many surprising elements.
And even I would say it takes a lot to surprise us.
Yeah. But there was one or two things where I went, oh, yeah,
I kept doing it throughout.
And even that first BB8 appearance, I don't think I was ready for something
that I wasn't ready to like see a friend already.
It's still unassuming.
There's two doors, and you're like, is this where it kind of kicks in?
But you don't expect to walk in the room and he's just there saying hi to you.
Yeah, because even there's a delay with Rocket.
He doesn't he's not immediately there. Yeah.
And he is like and they, you know, they have him.
He is like doing the things he does in the movie.
Like he wrote. Yes, Jason said he's he's rolling around.
He's beeping. He's doing all the adorable stuff.
Yeah. The only thing it misses is him doing the little thumbs up
that he does in Force Awakens.
They already looked expensive.
So I could only imagine what that would cost.
Yeah, really. And there's multiple of him because that's a point where you go.
I think you get to room.
There's a split off at that point. Yeah.
And then you get briefed by a ray hologram.
And that's a high quality hologram.
Yeah. Holograms have been portrayed and they like in many iterations
of Star Tours now.
But that's a boy that is a clean, good looking hologram.
And it's projected on a mirror.
Well, it's like there's a mirror and it's on an angle.
And it looks like the thing.
And I know there's multiple rooms that have the same pre-show and it looks like
like a lot of cave is behind her to.
But it's a mirror.
And as if there is like the hologram is just coming from the machine,
like up and down, like there's not a hidden thing behind it.
Yes. Right. Right. Right.
So it's a very effective effect.
I think the only way you can really like kind of see what's going on
is if you really get up on the side of it, you can kind of you can see that she
doesn't it isn't as three dimensional.
But like that's obviously a who's going to do that.
People were excited when that appeared.
People were excited when a second later Poe Oscar Isaac shows up on screen.
Yeah. This is we were talking about this in last week's episode with Paul
about people not wanting to maybe do actors, not wanting to do rides
based on, you know, the movie or whatever.
But I think we are in a new a new world where every actor does it now.
For the most part, because like Guardians, the whole cast is on it.
And the whole cast is here. Yeah.
And a few of them who had appeared in Star Tours previously
and kind of get more to do here.
And I think everybody does a great job.
I think particularly John Boyega doing all of the narration throughout,
like especially him, like the elevator part.
He's a lot of fun. Oh, yeah.
It's bad. Up is very bad. Yeah. Yeah.
They're all giving it their all.
They all feel like the characters.
And I think all of these things, all these scenes were shot between.
I heard that somebody somewhere that I think the Poe Dameron
part was shot in a rare moment of downtime on Last Jedi
because Rian Johnson was going to his sister's wedding.
So they had a tiny window where he'd been working.
It wasn't even like they didn't especially
they they got to the set and found a rare window where
everybody wasn't super busy.
OK, I will drop a nitpicky thing here right now
that took me out of it a little.
It the Poe footage is a little too clear,
like shot on iPhone level clear compared to the Chewbacca footage
in Smuggler's Run, which looks like the kind of 70.
You know, Star Wars is kind of stuck in 70s version of the future.
Sure. That that kind of I was like,
did they shoot him on a video camera real quick?
Like, I don't it wasn't a huge thing.
It was only a beat of like, wait, something.
You want a dirty lens.
I wanted it all a little grainier.
But again, who cares?
But that was my only thing.
And Nyan Nub is a CGI in this part, too. Yeah.
And this character, what we're about to talk about was his robot, I believe.
Or a facsimile of I don't know if it was the exact robot
or some of the video. Yeah, I don't know.
Because like Hondo in Millennium Falcon is
he's an actor with a suit on in the video, the pre-ride video. Yeah.
And then he's the robot you see in the pre-show.
Could be the same deal.
It could be a similar situation with kind of funny.
We don't know. But we should talk about him. Sure.
Yeah. So you walk outside, you see Poe Dameron's X wing
with BB-8 also moving around on the top, which is very cute. Yeah.
Oh, yeah. And she raised sends him off.
Like, shouldn't you be working on the plane?
And that's a payoff when you go outside. Oh, wait.
Well, and gasp moments.
The doors opening and realizing you're going back outside
because you are accustomed on any ride to think, especially in the line.
Yeah. When you were in an indoor part.
That right now, we're in the show building.
It is such a surprise that you're in this this alcove
that I'm sure is not that big of a footprint, but feels huge.
Yeah, it's really grand.
And probably the people are walking by on the other side, not that far.
But boy, does it feel like a massive hangar.
And you can't. Yeah. And you can't see it from outside.
It's only it's like a big reveal.
And it's a it's some sort of Karelian freighter. Right.
Is that the name? It's like a transport ship.
And then you have a black X wing.
I honestly, in all the reading about what this ride was going to be,
I thought this would be a longer queue area.
I thought you would hang out here for a while.
You go through it pretty quick.
I had to watch a few videos to catch a few little to realize like, oh, BB-8
Yeah, is moving in the X way.
Yeah. Yeah. It's kind of saying hi to you. Yeah.
Yeah. There's several points of this where you want to stay behind
and take pictures, but you kind of got to keep moving.
So it all it all leaves you wanting more, which is great.
It makes you want to come back and like hope there's a stall.
So you can take pictures of everything.
But you're pretty quickly in that transport vehicle,
which is going to take you to another planet where the First Order can't get to you.
Yes. Yes. That's not how it works out.
But when you when you are in there, when you walk into that ship,
I think one of our new favorite friends
and all of Disney theme park, yes. Yes.
Beck, Lieutenant Beck, the monk calamari
because Admiral Ackbar
coldly killed in Last Jedi, at least it was on screen, I guess.
It was referred to.
But I would have liked a bigger send off, I will say, for Admiral Ackbar.
I would have liked a big stream send off.
But since he is gone yet, that would have been good.
Since he has gone a new monk calamari, I guess they're just very good captains.
They can pilot ships very well or they can give commands.
He's not really he's just kind of sitting in there.
He's sitting in a little rotating chair while Nyan does the actual driving of it.
So he's like we were talking about Gilligan's Island recently.
He is he is the skipper and Gilligan is like Nyan. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But Lieutenant Beck, he is he is a full animatronic.
He is. Yeah. He does a lot.
He can move. He can. Yeah.
And you can get so close to him.
You can be right next to him. It's amazing.
Really? Just like, no.
I mean, is it I think any way you board, he's on the right.
So go to the right. Yeah.
And there's also if you get crammed in and can't really see,
there are screens everywhere of you can see communications between characters
and stuff. And then there's a screen at the back of the vehicle
and a screen at the front of the vehicle.
And there's only OK.
So this is OK.
So I don't know if anyone is actually interested in this, but there are two different.
I just said this.
There are two different rooms with Ray and BB8 and they're reversed.
So there's two different presure rooms.
And then you all load out into the same area,
which we're talking about the outside area with Poe Dameron.
And then the two and then you reform with one in this one group.
And you reform into this one group with this ship.
Now, I heard I read that there are three different
insides of this ship.
OK, that rotate. Yeah.
Turntable, turntable style. Yeah, I see.
So so you'll always get yeah, you'll always get Lieutenant
back and I and on the right and on and the back area
where you can see like you're where you're flying out of.
Which means there's three sets of animatronics. Yes.
This amazing among calamari.
There are three of them in the back of nine's head.
That's so cool.
And you're the turntable effect is so surprising
because you really think you have this thing figured out.
You think that this is haunted mansion elevator.
You think it's like kind of a false moving room
that's like that's because it's supposed to be a spaceship.
So you are you're shaking around.
It's vibrating.
And but you're like, well, it's maybe it's like haunted mansion
or it's like a journey to the center of the earth has in Japan
has something like this, like an elevator
that's taking you way down into the earth.
And so like I think I thought, all right,
so it's a stationary thing like Star Tours and I'll get out the other side.
Yeah. So you yeah, you walk in and there's a door where you obviously where you come in.
And then on the other side of the transport, there's another door.
So obviously everyone assumes I know how rides work.
That's the door we're leaving.
Whenever whatever happens, happens, because of course it does.
This is as you're saying, this is stationary.
We know how this type of thing works. Yeah.
But yeah, you go through the whole pre show and it's like, you know, as you imagine,
like you're going and all of a sudden the first order is there and they're shooting at you.
And what's really fun is that everywhere you are in the transport,
you can see different kind of stuff.
There's little screens with different like pictures of the
or the X-Wing pilots.
There's different like radar.
You can see yourself taking off from the planet and going into space.
Which it it stays.
The screen is consistent with the outdoor area that you just left.
So if you left during the day, then what's behind Beck is during the day.
And if it's night, it's night.
Which is insane. Yeah.
That's a whole other set of footage they had to create.
And then time of like, OK, the sun has set, switch over.
Yeah, there's probably multiple versions for like bright sunlight.
Well, that's what I want to know. Yeah.
I want to know, like on a rainy day, how does it look on a on a very bright day?
How does it look at dusk?
How does it look when it's dark? How does it look?
I don't know. There's also
the person who is kind of showing us around knew the ropes.
Showed pointed out there's a skylight that also is a point of consistency
where if it's during the day, it's not a full window,
but natural light is coming into this vehicle.
And then once you're in space, there's no more natural light.
Yes. Very, very cool.
Yeah. Delineates the time of day.
Because, yeah. So, yeah, we were looking at that.
And then, yeah, getting up close to Lieutenant Beck.
Yeah. Which just I feel like we were like I'm imagining like a like
like when someone's infatuated with somebody and they have their hands up
under their chin, you know, and I'm so how would you describe the motion I'm making?
Yeah. You know what I mean?
Smitten like if you have a crush on the teacher.
Yeah, there you go. That's exactly what I'm looking for.
That's what we were like.
I love run of Lieutenant Beck. Yeah.
Yes. Just kind of like because you can really post up on there and you try
not you can't you shouldn't get in the way because there's a lot of people
in the transport. Mm hmm.
But we were just like, oh, look at this guy.
So cool. You get close enough to see his little tentacles wiggle.
Yeah. When he moves around.
And this whole thing is it's like a subway car.
Basically, they found a way to do a simulator where you don't have to sit
or be in seat belts.
Right. There's rails you can grab on to.
You don't really need to.
But sometimes you feel like you need to.
Yeah. Yeah. Here and there.
Like, yeah, you're on a cruise ship or a bus like in your standing up.
It was more than I thought there would be, honestly.
Yeah. Bump wise.
So, yeah, you get it going.
I think, yeah, if I was a kid, as I've said before, I got scared
because I wanted this weird UFO thing at Santa's or not Santa's Pirates Cove Park
as a child and there were there was light coming out of the door
and I still thought we were in space.
So as a kid, I would have been fully believing that this was going on.
Oh, also, two characters die horribly in this.
Oh, yeah.
Downs to X-wing pilots blow up
as they often will do.
Yeah. Oh, I don't know.
What do we have their names or do we not know?
Can we pay proper tribute to them?
Red and blue. Red and blue.
Yeah. Poor red and blue.
Yeah. So you encounter some trouble.
We don't get to the safe planet.
The First Order intercepts us and we are told, prepare to be boarded.
And because you think you know how things work,
everybody looks out the other door. Right.
And then in many it really felt like there was full whiplash.
Everybody staring into the wrong place.
And you hear a voice and you look back out the door.
You came in. Yeah.
And an audible scream from the crowd.
Everyone just went, ha, like everyone was like
the one of the biggest pops I've ever heard in a theme park.
One of the biggest surprises. Yeah, absolutely.
Partially because there's a person there and the effect freaked you out.
Mostly because the last time you looked out that door,
it was real world outside.
And now you're looking out that door and you are in a First Order ship.
Yeah, it's it's crazy.
And I swear, I read this because there were there were people,
I think, when the press happened initially for Galaxy's Edge
that did this part of the ride, like leading up to just this next part.
Yes. And I believe this illusion was given away.
And I'm sure because I'm spoiler hungry and I read a lot of stuff
that I knew it, totally forgot it.
And I was just as shocked as everyone else was.
And because the room you open to the docking bay you open to is so large.
It's so big. Yeah.
So, yeah, what we were saying before is there's a turntable
with three of these things on it, apparently.
And yeah, there's one that's docked in the Star Destroyer.
There's one that's docked outside on the Resistance planet or whatever the base.
And then there's just one like in motion sort of.
So you can in transit.
So every every part of this, you can see how they keep the lines moving
and you can keep people going through it because it's so it's it's
it seems like what we were told, I forget the numbers,
but it's going to be when it's running a very efficient
kind of people eating experience.
Even though it feels like no one's on the ride.
Yes. Yeah. You think this is like Spider-Man or something
where you can't imagine there's like not that many people going through.
Like you feel like the line should it should be three hours to wait for it.
It's estimated like at full when this starship is at full capacity,
whatever they say in New Hope. Yeah.
Fully operational.
Estimated, they were saying, estimated at pirate approaching
Pirates of the Caribbean levels, which is usually estimated at 2800 people an hour.
Wow. Yeah. And yeah, of course.
Yeah. So and as you were saying, the difference is here,
they've done it and they've chopped it up in pre shows
to try to make it feel much more intimate.
Obviously, when you're in the line and when they when they're
just maybe having a standby queue, you'll be in line
up until the ray room for with a bunch of people for 45 minutes.
But once you hit the ray room, the idea really is supposed to make you feel like
it's kind of you and like 30 people, you and 25 people are on this.
And you shouldn't see more than that.
Yeah, you should probably want you shouldn't feel like you're being dumped
into just an endless line like almost every other ride it has.
Being given so many treats, you don't realize you're like you're already in it.
Like you're still being herded through. Yeah.
And everything's cool. Yes.
And all the pre shows it's because and you can see it in like
their their way of thinking with the tickets with Avatar,
because there are a lot of pre shows.
You could argue they're not quite as fun as this.
The scan scanning.
But you can see that they're they've they're slowly perfecting
mega e tickets that can really absorb a lot of people.
Yeah. And what's funny is it's all distraction and stagecraft
and little tricks.
It's all the like tenons of the actress,
like classical theater tricks and magic tricks.
Like it's all very old school, just done in different ways
and with a lot of technology.
There's so much technology in this.
Yeah. And there's a lot of technology like there's so much stuff
that isn't in your face technology, too.
I mean, we'll get there, I think, one more or more on the ride itself.
For it's like little tiny stuff happens.
And you again, you wouldn't like notice it really.
It's just sort of in the background.
So much technology is just used to like
help a little piece of something else along.
But if you really look at it, you're like, oh, that's an impressive illusion.
That's an impressive little piece right there.
Illusions, details Easter.
Like there's stuff I only caught rewinding like ride through videos of like,
oh, my God, I just realized the question I had of like,
where did that character end up is explained in the distant.
The deep background of a video is justified.
Geez. Wow. Wow.
And then I guess also presumably when you enter this transport
and you exit the transport, you when you're in the
Star Destroyer is at the when you're when you're in the Star Destroyer,
you see the outside of the of the ship.
But that's a facade probably. Right.
Like that never moves. But the interior. Yeah.
It's just yeah. So yeah.
Basically what is it?
Is it a Karelian transport? Am I wrong with the distinction of the craft?
So yeah, they just have a set like exterior for that spaceship
inside the Star Destroyer and then outside by the base.
Looks very similar to the transport ship Leia is on in the very first scene
of A New Hope. Yeah. The blockade runner. Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Yeah. Oh, sure.
So yeah, that's just that's obviously always sitting there.
That doesn't move at all. That's really cool.
That's what I'm really thinking about that.
So yeah, you get you get boarded.
You were told to proceed off to the right for interrogation.
You're trying to move you through clearly, even though you are brought out
onto one of the most jaw dropping sets you've ever seen.
One of the tallest sets you've ever seen.
And this is where much documented the 100 storm troopers are standing.
Yeah. And I think they're 50, actually.
It's OK. It's not 100.
But that was another the rumor was because I was again five years ago
was reading like then you there's 100 storm troopers.
And I think I don't know.
Maybe it was in blue sky or something, but I think it's closer to 50.
And they're standing in front of
the biggest screen I've ever seen, maybe outside of like when I was at
I was at WrestleMania and Santana.
Yeah. At the whatever stadium, Levi's Stadium.
But that's the biggest screen I've ever seen.
Disney, the Guardian screens and the screens in this attraction.
I'm like, well, these screens, how are these so clear?
Like, how are these so good?
And Guardian screen, which is very big, but Guardian screen, you know,
isn't nearly as big as the thing is.
No, certainly not.
So that was just very impressed because that's just looking out into space.
And I just yeah, this how do you think this is a two story room?
How tall do you think this is?
Three and a half, three.
It's a scaled down.
I mean, it's not full stop, but there's a there's an X swing in here.
Or not a tie fighter. Yeah.
A giant tie fighter, which I didn't even notice at first.
That's very funny because, yeah, yeah.
There's so many things I didn't notice until later.
And then the stuff that I noticed that you guys hadn't seen.
Sure. There's a transport.
There's the vehicle that you end up on later in the ride with an R5 droid.
Yeah. And I hadn't put together till later that that is that's showing you
there's vehicles we have in this
in the Star Cruiser.
And these guys are we have bad droid.
We have evil droids.
So register this. These are bad.
I believe that's also there for I could be wrong,
but I believe that's also there for
you taking a photo in it, because people sometimes want to take photos
when you actually load onto it.
And that is not a good time to know.
Oh, interesting. So if you do a quick one, like it's funny because
the people in there are playing first order officers and they're being mean to you.
But they also know that like everybody in here wants to take a bunch of pictures
and hang out for a second.
So it feels like you need to leave quickly.
But they give you a minute or two.
I think three or four minutes, they start to bug you.
It would be funny to I don't know what their directive is.
If it's like if somebody asks, can I can you take a photo of me in this vehicle?
What they do?
I found a video where the picture taking is justified.
A cast member says document your capture if you must, but proceed to the right.
That's good. Nice. Yeah, really like that.
That is good. Yeah, because that's a hard thing to justify.
Taking cell phone. Sure.
And they and I think on one of the times we went, somebody says,
like, what is the line?
Oh, I just I've never seen people so excited to be taken prisoner.
Yeah, that is funny.
The stormtroopers twitch.
Do some of them twitch?
Which are all of them.
Some of them are more static than others.
Mm hmm. Enough to keep it alive. Enough to keep it alive.
Yeah. And then there's like a bar like you between those stormtroopers.
It would have been nice for 100. Sure.
But, you know, this is working.
The trick works. Sure. Like, yeah, yeah.
Around this point, Jason, you mentioned maintenance issue,
which is very true that like they are going to have to buff these floors.
The floor is so shiny and everything looks so sterile
because it's supposed to be like the fascist first order.
So, you know, very tight Hugo Boss ask uniforms and very precise.
You know, everything's got to be clean and not dirty.
And yeah, I mean,
I don't know how much they'll care about that.
I think in certain parts it it makes sense.
In other parts where like the ride vehicles would be going over,
you can't puff out every, you know, rubber scratch or whatever.
Yeah, yeah. But boy, the upkeep in this room.
Yeah, I wonder because like on the actual ride itself,
you can see that there's just marks where the vehicles are going over.
So I wonder. Yeah, I wonder what their buffing plan is.
Yeah. What is the procedure?
How much buffing needs to be done?
Somebody can message us if they know.
We should have asked that.
We should have figured that.
What's the buffing plan? What's the buffing budget?
It's got to be high. Buffing alone.
Do they buff in the middle of the day or is it just end of the day?
Yeah. But yeah, they're going to buff it.
How will they buff it?
Like a place I would describe as like impossible architecture.
Like I if you walk through that, I don't quite know.
I'm sure there's blueprints or stuff somewhere.
But it's like the full on Winchester mystery house where like,
well, you have to go up to go down.
And this hallway is a dead end, but it gets you to this endless hallway.
And it's like so crazy.
If you try to think about it.
Somebody has it. I saw on one of the videos I was watching.
Somebody does have the layout and it's interesting. Yeah.
But yeah, I had no I couldn't have drawn a map after doing.
Oh, you're so confused. You're so turn around.
And this is the true on the ride part, too.
You feel like you're in a confusing spaceship.
Like, where am I now? Yeah.
Is this a safe place to be? No, it's not at all.
Yeah. Even when I got off the you get off into the room,
the big Star Destroyer room and you look back and my brain wouldn't fully
it knew that right outside was outside where we just were.
It knew that. But I that when I it didn't fully accept. Yeah.
So you were like, well, I am on a ship now.
So then I'm very disoriented. Completely.
You get into a part that's a little more line ish.
They just said, I think we saw it with a big backup.
We saw it not with a big band.
I've now outed maybe that we got to do it a second time. Yes.
And so we are our main group when it's the way the regular way we did it
when around seven p.m., we got to do it another way.
Once again, I will say podcast privilege.
I admit it. I cop to it.
I apologize for it.
And I think the person are our spy on the inside who are more in the
in the first.
Was it a toy? Darien?
That it was it a monk, El Mari?
I don't know. Podcasts are built on hope.
So, you know, was it gin or snow?
Gin or so is dies on that beach planet.
So it's not gin or so.
Was he quickly shot like Hux?
We don't know. We don't know.
No, we don't know.
We don't know what became of this brave soul.
No. Hopefully it's OK. Hopefully.
So, yeah. So where were we?
We're in the are we in the line?
All right. The more line, right?
Isn't guaranteed to have a big backup.
But then you're kind of so you're in a line.
But it is now a plot justified line.
Perhaps the first time this has ever happened in theme park history.
You are lining up for process and you're going to jail. Yes.
And it's I will say in that big room with all the stormtroopers at the holidays,
I saw pictures where they had set up rope queues in that room.
And that for me would break the illusion a little.
But if you're getting record Christmas, like giant Christmas crowds,
they could get it. You'd get them.
So it's like, but you are being processed.
You are prisoners being processed. Yeah.
Yes, you're right.
Diagetically, make sense for a line.
Amazing. And then you've got mean people saying how many in your party?
Proceed to the left. Proceed to the right.
We've found a re a plot reason to ask how many in your party.
It's the first is the first time this makes sense.
Like to have like the I mean, they don't ask how many in your party
on the man on the Haunted Mansion, but like on Tower of Terror,
like how many in your party for the for the elevator?
That doesn't quite make sense.
Yeah, yeah. I guess Indiana Jones, I guess, you know, Salah
had people to go through the thing.
Yeah. And you would have people helping him out in a limited amount of space
in those transports. Sure.
But this is we're in a this for sure is an experience where nobody
if pretending we the audience don't know anything and the first order
people don't know anything, nobody knows a riot is coming.
The point of this part is you're going to jail.
Yes, you are.
This is a simulator for processing at a jail,
which is what a great we talk about how I kind of love the theme park trips.
I kind of love you're getting on this thing and but something's going to go wrong.
You're going to test the thing at the special facility.
But oh, the real thing from the movie happens.
I kind of love it.
But certainly it has been done a gazillion times.
And boy, this is not that there.
You don't know there's a ride until you see the vehicle.
I mean, I am so I I read rumors, but I didn't watch any ride throughs
and I tried to go cold on a lot of stuff.
I wish I didn't know a lot of this because
I can't imagine totally going in fresh.
Imagine you didn't know anything about it.
Yeah, I didn't know a lot of the big set pieces.
I didn't either. Yeah, I knew I was legitimately.
I didn't know how they got you in and out of places.
Yeah, I didn't know stuff like that.
And I knew, you know, there was ATATs and stuff.
But if you're listening to this and you have someone in your life,
you have a kid or a parent or a friend who doesn't know any,
who doesn't pay attention to this stuff, but enjoys Disneyland.
If you can get somebody on without telling them anything, do it,
because they will lose their shit.
Yeah, that's what it really seems.
Honestly, that I was like, oh, yeah, I'm trying to think of who I know
that I can take. Yeah, because I'm very interested to see everybody's reaction
to it, because yeah, because they have most.
Even if they've heard me drone on about rumors,
there's no way anyone retained any of that garbage from me.
So like they'll be fresh going on this.
It's funny. It's very fun.
Surprising. Sets the bar high.
Certainly, very that Avengers ride.
Although we've been told.
Yeah, it's set your bar.
I go ahead. Yeah, they know they have to match.
Yeah, you would think because with the Avengers being like the number one
franchise. Yeah, yeah.
Moment, you were sort of I think I think we don't without saying
any type of we'd not that we were really told much, but I think it's
if you've watched an engineering story or you've been to this thing in person,
it's maybe the scope.
Maybe it's our version of Shanghai Pirates.
There's any they are an element.
Yeah, yeah, something of that and the scale of this kind of.
But it seems it also seems like it's far away.
It seems like it's very far away and anything can change.
Yeah, so I was just so and this is this is
this might sound like a wrap up thought I could say to the end.
But while we're talking about scale and everything, I mean, like I remember
how this this whole experience flashed me back to being 10 and going on
the Indiana Jones adventure and thinking it's never going to get topped.
And then it wasn't topped for a long time because the dark ages
set in and they did a bunch of off the shelf shit.
And I was really wondering, I was like, I guess I experienced the peak
of Disney Imagineering and how wonderful to be around
25 years later and they set the they reset.
Yeah, I don't.
That's an interesting thing, because with Galaxy's edge in the whole land,
it feels like they can't keep doing this, though, because a lot of a lot of stuff
is coming. No, but there's just no way that's not.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think, you know, we're going to do an episode soon of the Slinky Dog Dash,
and that is not a bar topping.
But it's wonderful and it's cool that it exists. Yeah.
And they need to do those things.
But it's like they need to do it every once in a while.
Just as Jason said, to flex to show that they can.
And I think Universal's been doing all the flexing until this.
Well, and it's funny because the experience you're describing
I had at 13 in 1999 on Spider-Man,
which, again, 20 years later, Scott Trowbridge still going strong.
And that does feel like that was like for the time.
Very doing new stuff, using simple tricks, using sets,
using real explosion, using practical stuff, meld it with screens
and an interesting cue.
There's nothing there's nothing ever that you've never felt anything like that.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
And that's it, which is that's a tough there can be very, very good rides.
But you go, oh, it's kind of a version.
You might even say, though, I would rank this as one of the greatest rides ever.
Radiator Springs racers, you recognize the bones as being test track,
and that is no slam against it because boy does it rule.
It doesn't reinvent the reinvent the wheel.
Not what it's trying to do. Right.
But it's how cool to get a reinventing the wheel.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
I mean, for me, this was baby's first trackless ride vehicle experience.
Yeah, that's true.
Well, except for Luigi.
Luigi's. Yeah, yes.
It's your first room to room.
First. Yeah, I haven't done Ratatouille or Mystic Manor.
Pooh's Honey Hunt, like,
you know, which I mean, I think it's the best one of those.
And I made the complaint that I thought the Ratatouille ride was like a little dopey.
It's a little you're going.
You're kind of just it's not you don't have like the whipping around.
It doesn't feel it didn't feel madcap to me.
And this completely does.
This was like exciting ride vehicle travel.
Yeah. Pooh's is awesome.
Yeah. Yeah.
Pooh's is really great.
Good to do it.
I mean, hopefully the Ratatouille in Epcot is like draft two.
I think I wonder, I think because I mean,
apparently here at Disneyland, they were able to fix some stuff
that were bugging, like nagging issues from Florida.
And we also found out that we have like twice as many vehicles as Florida does.
So apparently, yeah, maybe going a little smoother, a little quicker out here.
Maybe so.
I mean, the little extra time we had to wait might have might have helped.
So as we said, cast members are being mean.
They're lining you up.
They tell they really warn you not to step on this glass behind you.
And we were told that's for real.
And you feel it if you step on the glass.
Don't step. Yeah.
Like they do need to like haunted mansion, keep you away from the sides.
That seems like, yeah, somebody's going to break that with their heel.
Yeah. If a woman on the line, not the glass.
If someone is wearing like a spiked high heel, this is going to be a big problem.
Yeah. Or just a long high heel.
That's going to be you're going to go right through that glass.
It feels like a second later, you do need to stand on a colored oval
that looks very similar to the color white lights.
I was confused by colors.
I didn't know what color I was on.
I don't know where I was looking for that color.
Yeah, that's a confusing aspect.
I will say when it's like you're orange and then like you need to know it
two rooms from now. Yeah.
And I didn't realize till the second time that they then it correlates
with the color that's in the vehicle. Right.
I told you I was very that's confusing.
I see the logic, but expecting people to remember after like a couple
of very impressive moves.
Yeah, I think that's a little too much to expect from gas.
If you tell me I'm orange, then you say go there.
That's all you're going to get.
Like, yeah, my memory. Yeah.
But so after this wonderful cast member business and boy, great job, everybody.
Keep it up.
Then you are brought into the cell.
You're brought into a detention cell. Yes.
And you are on the bottom of it.
It right. It rises up very high.
There is like a cage above you that really kind of restricts
your vision of the storm trooper that's watching you.
And there's a little bit of stall there.
I like the second time where we could just there was just animation of like
helmet clacking. Yes.
Yeah. Just to fill the space.
And then Hux comes in.
Yeah. General Hux.
He's in this in multiple forms. Yes.
And then the big bad Kylo Ren himself.
Mask on mask on.
Yeah. Driver did just had to do a voice. He did the voices.
Yeah. But there's been questions about that. It is him.
Yeah, I think it's him.
Although there's a very funny there's there's a line that stuck out to me later
on, and I'll point it out when we get to that.
OK, sure, sure.
But he uses some force threat on you.
Room shakes a little bit.
I also around this point, I mean, I thought this the whole ride,
not to just complain about a thing that a lot of people
have done a lot of complaining about.
It was nice to be in a Star Wars experience where what where the motivation
is very clear.
If there's one thing, there's one thing.
You know, the location of the base, Kylo wants it.
He's going to kill you if he doesn't get it.
Right. And we don't have gadgets and dude heads of plenty.
We don't have knives and compasses and galore.
Well, yes, knives and compasses galore.
No thingamabobs, not 20.
I think Rises, there's Rises Skywalker definitely had 20 thingamabobs, if not more.
I want to shout out one of my favorite actors, Domnoglison.
I think as General Hux, consistent throughout doing a great,
I think, gets that like this is there is a fine tradition of imperial
first order people played by like British actors being very stern.
And I think he does a great job at it.
I think it's very kooky.
And this is a spoiler for like Rises Skywalker.
But when he yells, I was the spy, like I was very funny.
I thought that was a great delivery.
Like he just go be a little silly.
And Martin Short would play it.
Yes. Yeah, it was me.
But I just got a look.
Could have used Martin Short.
Yeah, sure. Throw him in.
He's busy on the morning show.
And why wouldn't you be Domnoglison and in Rises
Skywalker, Richard E.
Grant, I mean, just doing great job doing that part.
Makes you think, wait, didn't he do this in?
Was he an empire?
I'm surprised that hasn't happened already.
Yeah, it seems like I was like, oh, he was in the other two.
At least right, Force Awakens?
No, no. Yeah.
No, similar to like Karl Weathers and
John Carlyle Esposito.
Both feel like they're so like hasn't this happened already?
Yeah, they're so like made to be Star Wars people.
Yeah. Yeah. And Werner.
Werner Herzog. Oh, yes.
Yeah, he's a lot of fun.
So room travel is a force.
You're stuck. How are we getting out of here?
And then one of the coolest and this was a spoiler.
I didn't know this. I didn't know this.
I didn't know this either. I didn't either.
Oh, great. Yeah.
It's you don't know how you're getting out of here.
And then Orange Glow around an arbitrary spot spot on the wall,
which reveals itself to be a door, which slides backwards in this very clever way.
And so, yeah, so they like burned through the door.
Yeah, they blow torch through the wall.
There's a projection inside the wall.
I don't know where it was coming from that makes it look like, yeah,
they're like searing through it.
And then like if you look on the sides of the door, it looks like, yeah, like
it's still glowing, a jagged cut because they whatever instrument they use.
Just this. We haven't even gotten to the main ride.
We haven't been on the ride yet.
Is. Yeah, we're doing our own.
This is like our haunted mansion series.
Just in the one.
This is the second time the whole room went, ha, like, they're so surprised by it.
And I'll say this, depending on which room you're in, it might be the one wall.
It might be the other.
Oh, oh, that changes.
There are four of these.
There are four of these. Oh, that's right.
And they all go to different places. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
And I think one of the in a day of many great Star Wars actor
cast members, maybe my favorite one just goes combined with the surprising effect.
Then a guy coming in and saying, I'm with the resistance. Follow me.
He gets like, yeah, like whoever this was nailed it.
It's so exciting. Yeah.
This guy, he said this ride operator saved you.
And they're waiting are the the right vehicles.
Now, I know this, but I don't know that they spell it out narratively too well.
The idea that they reprogrammed the evil droids. Yeah.
As I said, back in the room you saw earlier, these droids are not friendly.
They're here to watch you and make sure you go into your detention room.
But now these ones that you're in front of are good.
Yeah, they don't. It's a lot.
That's an info dump that is I don't know how you get it out.
Yeah, because like it's supposed to be very urgent this moment.
This moment is supposed to be like, you got to get out of here fast.
It's so urgent that you're getting like, please keep your hands and arms inside
while you're moving.
Like, yeah, you're throwing so much at you and like, OK, make sure you're OK.
Bye. They have Lieutenant Beck say it to you.
Yeah. A friendly voice, a friendly voice and pretty funny.
Like in this part of the raw, like there's a moment where he goes like, did it work?
OK, great. Like the resistance is great.
He's great. He's great.
The resistance, the resistance force wants to make sure
that you tug on the dirty yellow strap.
Yeah. Before you get out of here, they do want safety.
They want safety because they're a force for the first order would let you
fly out of the thing. They don't care.
And the and the Empire First Order, whatever you call it, first order.
They do have dirty yellow straps on the seatbelts as well, just like a theme park.
So that one's a tough one to justify.
But they have to make that strap yellow, I think, because it's easy to see.
There's a lot of you know, they should explain that there's a lot of
ton of wills in the strap.
Oh, yeah. Of wills, the little creatures that make up the force.
Yes. Yeah. George wanted in these yellow as a high concentration of wills.
So once you're officially loaded into your ride vehicle,
one of the computer displays starts to play a video from Finn.
And this video, I thought this looked pretty good.
He shows you a schematic of like, all right, you're going to get to escape pods.
You're going to take these elevators to escape pods.
Yes, it's funny. This is all I was saying.
Like, there's it feels chaotic. Yeah.
Yeah. I feel where to look.
Yeah. Lots happening.
So I like the idea that he's showing you like where you're going, but there's no way.
Yeah. You know what you're looking at or will remember in two seconds.
Oh, yes. So yeah. So quick. Observe all this. OK, here we go.
Got it. There's a plan.
Whatever you you know, you know, you're doing.
Turbo lifts. A lot of people say turbo lifts for the rest of the attraction.
Turb does he say turbo lift? Yeah.
OK, because I always think of that as a Star Trek thing.
Oh, but I guess is that maybe actually a term?
I'm not sure.
I don't know. There's somebody will have to chime in.
And technology of.
Yeah. So yes, they're shouting at us.
Peep cast members are shouting at us.
Yeah, we're tugging on yellow straps that are dirty.
And then Lieutenant Beck tells us to what?
Keep our hands in the vehicle.
Yeah. Your hands, arms and children. Yeah.
Oh, and then you're then you're on your way.
You know, not to shoot past the just that it is trackless.
I feel like I'm talking to people who have never been on a trackless.
They was your your first trackless. Yeah.
Ride. I think it probably will be a shock to a lot of people
who haven't been to overseas ones that you go into this room.
And like, what is that? How is this going to work?
I should also point out that the room you're loading in the vehicles,
like almost every other like traditional dark ride,
you see where the vehicle came in and you see where it's going.
This is the smallest room other than maybe like the Tower of Terror.
It's like bedroom size. It's tiny.
Yeah. There's two vehicles in there.
And my thought, of course, first was, how do these get in here?
Because there's and there's no like it's just a wall behind them.
So they didn't come in from behind.
They're not loading like that, which is how almost every other ride.
Like Pooh's Honey Hunt.
They come from behind.
It's it's still like a standard load unload process.
It's not it's not the cars ride.
It's not like it's the ones in front of you and the ones behind.
It's just a conveyor belt for most rides.
Private room.
And you pointed this out after the first time we went on it.
And the second time you gave everybody the mission.
Let's figure out how those vehicles get in there the next time.
Never felt dumber because I saw it.
I saw it the first time because it's two things.
It solves two problems.
One, you go out of this room, you see two empty ride vehicles and Lieutenant Beck
This is where he tells you, play it cool. OK.
And the droids talk to each other.
Yes. Like Lalo is just tell them it's a prisoner of transport.
And you get by them and they're going backwards into the room.
And you are going forwards out of it.
And that's how vehicles get in and out of the room.
Yes, I had no clue.
I went by it. I was like, OK, these empty ride vehicles got it narratively.
Those are just they're they're just, you know, on their way to get somebody.
And we're just supposed to not be weird in front of those other droids.
The next vehicles are right in front of you.
So funny. The very beginning of the ride.
And you don't really realize what's happening.
Yes, I had no idea because I I was thinking like maybe the maybe the back wall
opened up or something.
But I was like, that doesn't really make sense.
Find the spot where it has so funny.
They just yeah, you turn around to and there's going in back into the room.
It's not even like it's that hidden.
Yeah, it's just that your attention is directed in such a way
that you don't even really notice what's happening.
And it sells the idea that these vehicles are flying around this star cruiser.
They're like these guys are going in and out.
This is how you take people around this ship.
So nothing weird about that.
So if you see other people, this place is full of them. Yes.
And you start moving.
And the track, you realize that the trackless ride vehicle
is the perfect way to do this idea
where the droid is driving you and it doesn't know where to go.
It has just been reprogrammed.
It doesn't know left from right.
It doesn't know the lay of the land.
So you're trying to find ways out of rooms and you you don't know.
You don't know what's around what corner and the spinning.
Like I think the trackless vehicles are very good at spinning.
And it lends itself to that nicely.
Like, no, no, no. Get out of there.
You have to whip out of a corner really fast.
Yes. You keep getting caught or you keep running it and you have to fix on fly.
Yeah. So you the very first thing you come around, you go down some hallways
and you hit a dead end, which looks like, OK, you'll get on the elevator
right by this and then a full size probe droid drops down
a full size like an empire strikes back probe droid lowers down.
Yeah, the one that tortures Han.
Or the one they shoot on Hoth.
It reminded me of the one that they.
Oh, oh, yeah.
Oh, I see. No, it's not the you're right.
It's not the interrogation, right?
It's a pro. Right. You're right. You're right.
But it's lens is turned away from you.
So it misses you and you barely get out of its sight.
All right. So obstacle one. OK.
But then you get into the next room.
Stormtroopers, they spot you.
Here is the first firing of the ride
and the little bits of laser damage throughout.
Yeah. Yeah. One of the coolest things I've ever done.
So, so cool. Yeah, they they.
I'm I read about it and I'm still confused a little
because is it is a projection covering up the damage and then it goes away?
Or are they projecting the damage on?
They might be projecting the damage.
Maybe that makes more sense.
It's a mix.
Well, it's a mix later on when there's bigger damage, I know for sure.
But yeah, it's it's hard to spot exactly what's happening.
There's there's like they use
like little bursts of lasers because like it's hard.
Like you can't do a straight laser because they're trying to mimic the way
that the blaster shoot in Star Wars, which is a little bursts.
So it's like they can't shoot a real laser because that would be an unbroken beam.
Yeah. Yeah.
So like they do these little like bursts and then it shoots and hits the
like walls and stuff.
You really can't tell where things are going.
The screen that the troopers are on looks fantastic.
Yeah. They it feels very real.
And yeah, you're avoiding laser.
You're avoiding lasers for a little bit.
And then pretty quickly, you end up in this hanger with the ad ads.
I think you see I thought this might have been more of like the climax of the ride.
Yeah, I think so. I see it so early.
And here again, one of these big gasps.
That's where they go into this.
This ride is like being at a baseball game or something like people are
just like you'd be on your feet if you didn't have to stay seated.
Yeah. Yeah. People are screaming.
It was so wonderful doing this opening day.
Yeah. And this is this is the full top to bottom of this building,
which is three stories and which many a time on a parking garage in the last four
years, I've made someone walk up to the top and gone, look, it's the skeleton.
It's the ATAT that's going to be or ATATs that are going to be in there.
Yeah. And yeah, it is building around.
It is incredibly impressive in scope.
How cool to finally be there.
You're staring at it from so far away from the stairs.
And now you are at its feet.
Yes. Also, I didn't notice this.
There's a giant mirror in the back of the room that if you look,
it gives it another sense of like there's more back there.
It's a mirror. So if you look through the look of the mirror,
it's the back of one of the ATATs.
And but it gives you the sense that there's more ATATs if you keep going.
Which is crazy. And I'm sure like I didn't notice it when we were on there both times.
But like subliminally, you're kind of absorbing everything.
And I'm sure it's giving you the sense that this room is even bigger.
Yeah. Yeah, it actually is.
And this is where you get a little variation.
There's a few moments of variation throughout the ride,
because the way the building is designed,
you could not have two elevators next to each other
where you take them both up and look at the ATAT like cannon
cockpits head on.
So one goes up an elevator and you're looking head on at the ATAT.
The other goes to the side.
And like you see a bunch of scurrying first order guys pull out a heavy gun.
And in both cases, you get fired upon.
And in both cases, you see Finn.
Yes. There's two Fins hidden in this room.
Yeah, which are a little easy to miss initially.
He's talking. But you've heard voices just pumped in.
So you're a little surprised when you find him.
And they I love that he's a little he's not like super presented in front of you.
He's crouched. Yeah.
The person who took us around, like who told us some secrets said how the,
you know, they had to limit the amount of like incredibly.
This couldn't be all Hondo level animatronics.
So if you look close, he's his body is perfectly still,
which makes sense with him being in a crouch and it's just his head moving.
But great. Clever. That's awesome.
And he and another soldier are blasting at stormtroopers.
There's stormtrooper projections in here or the digital peppers goes kind of things.
Yeah. And there is a firefight.
You're in the middle of a firefight and like I one thing I think is wonderful
is how also with the ground that the track list can cover.
It's cool that I was always wondering, OK, so you're in a room with the AT-ATs,
but I bet those things can't move, especially because we saw them.
They're made out of like steel.
So what's the like, is it exciting to go between their legs and stuff and the vehicles?
I mean, there's so much other stuff happening.
You're you're in crossfire.
But the vehicles are really what's making it exciting because now we're
zooming in between their legs.
You get to see them from down below and see the degree of detail.
And then you zip around.
You really see so many angles of the thing.
And then you back up into these elevators and shoot way up.
And suddenly you're looking at them in one case straight down the barrel.
Yeah, that elevator. So exciting.
It's like a little mini tower terror.
You get a little like just enough of a little like,
yeah, you know, a little stomach lift, whatever you want to call it.
I think the ride throughs don't do this justice.
I've been watching it.
I'm like, that feels dopey, the rise up if you watch it just on camera.
I think when you feel it, it's it's rad.
And I guess I knew there were elevators and drops, but I didn't know when.
And truly, this is the moment where you realize, oh, my God,
this is a multi story ride fast.
Yeah, very fast.
Yeah. Yeah. This is maybe my favorite section.
Yeah, because I think like they were trying to figure out, I think,
how to differentiate blasts between like stormtrooper blasters
and then the big AT-AT cannons.
And they do a very cool effect.
And correct me if I'm wrong, but they make it look like you're getting blasted
out by the AT-AT cannons by just sort of changing the already
like the already lit up lights sort of on the ceiling, completely red.
Yeah, it's a big thick tube. Yeah.
Lights up. Yeah.
But it tricks your eye into thinking this giant red blast has come.
It's like a pulse of color along a string.
And I found that more effective in tricking my brain
into being like we're being shot at. Yeah.
Because like it's because all the effects on the walls and everything before
are really cool with the stormtrooper blasts.
But it's not as it's not quite as effective as this is
in making you really feel like you're being shot at.
So I like this might be my favorite.
Have your heavier duty, probably.
And sound is real weighty. Yeah.
And so I think it was just like they had to differentiate between
this has to be more powerful than a stormtrooper.
So they do use this effect for all the stormtroopers.
And it would probably be too hard because they're like shooting wildly. Yeah.
This is when I realized you realize there's like an I'm in an attic of the
and I know this building footprint is huge.
So I'm going to we're now going to go explore a whole other.
Yeah, it's like it's like now we realize there are essentially two
giant show buildings, one on top of the other.
It's crazy.
And then where do we head?
Oh, you know, side note,
going back and watching the Imagineering story, some of your episode on Patreon,
but we're going to do part two soon and we just kind of gloss over
the Star Wars stuff.
Now, I haven't gone back and rewatched that the previs is that you do
the computer simulations of these rooms are perfect.
Yeah. You go back and watch like that is exactly the memory I have.
That is precisely the POV. Yeah.
Just the speed. It's just the way it like it's.
It's so cool that people have been digitally going on this ride
for five years before it existed in. Yeah. Yeah.
And yeah, they were doing it all with wireframe footage and laptops
and VR goggles and just like and then inactive construction sites of like,
OK, does that look right?
Like how many degrees the technology is wild.
And then like it's only going to get, I mean, crazier from here. Yeah.
As far as yeah, like what you're saying, where it's like previz down to the like,
who know, like whatever you would say, like a centimeter or whatever of like,
we know exactly how big this is going to be outside of probably just like
having to juggle all the different effects.
I think that's what we've been told by a few different people that like
maybe there wasn't necessarily one giant thing wrong.
It's just like this is just so many effects juggling things at once.
It's like stuff will go wrong for a week or two.
And then another thing goes wrong for a week or two.
And oh, that's yes.
Our man on the inside told us that there were certain things
that the Internet took hold of and said they're having big problems with this.
This is a huge problem.
And we'd say, now, is this accurate? Is that accurate?
And he'd say, yeah, but it was a problem for a week.
And then the next week is a new problem and a new problem. Right.
Nothing was ever stuck on for that long.
It's just that there's 200 things in this that could go wrong.
Well, and to say now that of like the four, you know, you always hear four
ride systems, which I guess is think about the transport trackless vehicle
drop system motion simulator.
I guess motion simulator is both the ending and also the transport ship.
Sure. Sure. So four right trackless drop.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I think that's it's no, it's no one is clearly cataloged it.
In my in my mind, I read through a bunch of articles and I'm like, wait, so
that that that that OK, drop.
In motion are two different ride system. OK.
That if the only track, if you're in California and the only trackless
vehicle you've been on is the little Luigi car, those the shiny cars that dance.
Imagine you're getting on one of those
and then it drives into the Tower of Terror and goes up the Tower of Terror.
And then drives into Star Tours and goes on Star Tours.
And then leaves and takes you outside.
Yes. But also, there's a sitting Star Tours.
And at the very beginning, there was a standing Star Tours.
Yeah. So
which Star Tours and it's on a turntable just heads up.
You are on a turntable.
And there's and there's little hidden rooms like Rocket and like Haunted Mansion.
And they're mean to you like haunted and the cast members do stuff.
Yeah. And it's like a living wax museum.
And there's a trap door.
But it's not the trap door you think it is like ten types of things
all piled on top of each other.
So now you're on the now you go to the bridge.
This is where I've been calling them like little cubbies that you like
tuck into this cozy little spot.
Under. Yeah.
New and now you have not seen in animatronic form Hux and Kylo. Right.
And it's I love that you're just you just nestle in.
Maybe they won't notice us.
Maybe we're fine here.
Maybe they're just going over some mundane business.
But no, but just roll up.
Well, yes, Kylo, there's a little bit beat where he says like, raise the
raise the shields. That's it.
That's the line, the two line punch of he goes,
you underestimate their conviction.
Raise the shields.
But he says raise the shields like a kids of the hall character.
Like, I don't know what it is.
It just hit me if only because I've been thinking about the report trailer
where he goes like everyone was scared.
And it's just like such an interesting delivery.
We did see these, I think, in bemoat
because they're supposed to turn around and look at you a little.
Oh, yes, yes.
Yeah. I watched the video and I saw that they fully turn around.
But I don't either.
Neither time they turned around.
Neither one of them.
What Kylo was was turned around.
Kylo's first turn around and Huck's like half turns towards you.
But in one of Todd Martin's articles about this, he talks about how
the with the Imagineers talk about, like if there's a stall,
you get to see bonus stuff because you get to see the stuff killing time
that you don't get to see in the regular ride.
So we accounted for the stalls to we accounted for for wait.
Well, there's a big crazy.
Did you see what be mode at the end is? No, no.
Oh, we'll get there. I'll tell you.
I watched it. It's fun. I was crazy. It's so different.
How do you get out of here? Do you go backwards?
Well, you have to go backwards.
And then you see kind of a similar like, I don't know.
It's not all Peppers goes to. Oh, of Kylo.
Kylo drops down. And when you're going backwards,
I think we didn't see the version he says, how brave, how ultimate,
but ultimately hopeless.
And then at some point he yells, there's nowhere to run,
which I think of as a like universal go to line on rights.
There's nowhere to run because I think Imhotep yells it at you.
Someone else at you.
I think maybe Trowbridge did some mummy, too.
I think I've got like the Florida mummy.
He loves yelling. There's no there's no where to run.
I read or I watched, I think, on a YouTube video
that the Kylo in that section is a projection, but the lightsaber is real.
What the lightsaber is emitting light. And that's like real.
I don't know what is holding it. Where he like pounces
when he drops down and like walks toward you.
The lightsaber is practical. So it emits light.
We didn't talk a little bit about the shadows in one of the pre shows
in those videos, did we?
I don't know. You know, in the the pre show, we were being interrogated.
They have this crazy thing where the projections are projecting shadows.
Oh, like elsewhere into the room?
Well, on the grading that's in front of the. Oh.
So like, that's the difference between like that.
And I maybe I don't think Harry Potter has that one, like you see the kids
up there, but like when Hux and Kylo are walking,
there's a shadow in front of them.
And there's a crazy way like even I forget which YouTube video
there's YouTube videos about like the secrets of it.
And there's a way they now project shadows from the screen.
Oh, my God.
So, yeah, this is a different one where it's actually the lightsaber
is actually some sort of practical thing that's emitting light.
And then he's just a projection walking toward you.
Wow. Well, so much backwards on that.
A ton of great backwards moments. Yeah.
And then you then you are cornered.
You're trapped. The door.
Again, the writers don't show you that that door
that closes just slam so fast. Yeah.
All the motion in this is just huge pieces moving really quickly.
And now you're trying. Now you are in the commercial moment.
So it's even this has probably been spoiled, but still seeing it in person
is so fantastic. And it's less the commercial makes it look.
It's really cool, but the commercial makes it look better.
Hmm. That's my memory of it.
But that's also the Indiana Jones commercials made it look like. Yeah.
There was a physical Indiana Jones in there. Yeah, that's true.
That's all in their playbook.
Yeah. So he so Kylo's saber goes through the ceiling
and is trying to slice into the elevator.
These are that and the him dropping down.
Those are like horror movie tropes. Yeah.
Those are horror movie go to the clip I've seen from the trailer
makes it look like he's slicing all like around the corners of it
as opposed to like there's a little section
that's different than the rest of it that he slices into,
which is still a very cool effect. Yeah.
But yeah, they did. And I do. You guys know how this works?
I look I know how it works.
I didn't know. I couldn't guess.
So I had to look it up to see how it works.
There is a so so basically there's a little like section
of the top of the elevator that's different than the rest.
And it's just obviously different material.
And there's almost like I don't know if it's a complete circle,
but it rotates like, I guess, much like the pre show the on the on the transport.
All of a sudden, like, so like, I think this is going to be impossible
for me to maybe fully explain.
But there's like the lightsaber here and then there's this.
And then it rotates and then a section opens up with a hole.
And it goes in there and it slices along like this.
Does that make sense?
Not really. OK, is it like like a bunch is turning
that already has a whole pre-cut? Yes.
Yes. And it only reveals itself as the saber is.
Yes. The front of the hole.
So like there's a circle that rotates.
It has a pre-cut section out of it.
There's a lightsaber above it.
And the lightsaber goes down as soon as that hole
this start of the hole appears.
If there was no lightsaber, just suddenly you'd see a C.
Yes, exactly. Pre-cut.
OK, exactly. And the stuff inside the lightsaber is spinning, right?
We yes, I believe so.
Yes, it looks more like it's flickering. Right.
And in Kylo's Hilt has a very unstable and like sputters.
So is there some projection in there, too, to make it seem like like
because it feels very textural.
I don't know the answer to that. I'm not sure.
But it does feel yeah, it feels
yeah, it feels like you would touch it and burn.
So cool. I think also instant iconic moment is the droid going, wow.
He does scream and agony. Yeah.
It's really fun.
And then we get into what I will declare,
not just my favorite part of the ride, but maybe my favorite part of any ride.
I think this room is incredible.
I did not know about this.
I also did. I had no idea that this was here.
Even though we all saw the teaser a long time ago, right?
Where the ships just suddenly flash appear.
Yes. And the woman at the console goes, what?
That's the. That's in this room.
So we were always looking at those cannons,
but we didn't know what they were capable of. Right.
I'll take Trowbridge is behind the scenes description of it
that you are essentially playing a game of cat and mouse
in your vehicle with giant cannons moving in front of you, moving backwards.
They're so tall. They hurt much taller than your vehicle.
They seem like they should weigh, you know, five tons.
You obviously they don't, but that's how they look.
And you are trying to find openings as best as you can
when the thing is in front of you and you're nervous as you move in front
of the cannons, is this thing just going to spear me down the center?
And my thought on this for some reason, it feels extremely super Mario to me.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
It's like, OK, wait for that, like, especially, I guess, like the ice blocks or
it just feels like like an odd little.
I have to like figure out the rhythm of this.
Obviously, you have no choice in the matter, but you are thinking about that.
You're like, wait, we're moving. Is that going to work?
Is this thing just going to crash into the side? Yeah.
And I'll say this is maybe the only part of the ride
that does make me feel like it could go wrong.
The rest of the ride is very impressive and cool, but there's not a lot of
danger. I don't feel a lot of legit danger.
But this part does make me feel like
something could crush like it could.
I don't know how. I'm sure they can't.
It certainly can.
It's I'm sure like that's a lot lighter than you think they are.
As they look heavy.
Although apparently, if the cannon, I mean, not that the cannons would hit the cars.
I'm sure there's a million stopgap, like there's a million failstakes for that.
But apparently they are moving with such force that if they go too far,
they can hit something and shake the building.
Oh, sure. I mean, they're giant.
Yes, man. So that is I that's the only part of the ride where I go.
Yeah, it is haunting.
It's all of the stuff.
This is the room I can't stop thinking about.
I want to go back very badly.
Yeah, I like did you guys have dreams about the ride?
I don't think I had leading up to it.
I did. Oh, nice.
Nice. Like I was on the ride and yeah, but I don't think I did after the fact.
I think watching Jason had dream about a toy, Darius, swirl, toy, Darius,
chasing me. Yeah.
And multiple hot dogs.
Even out of also cold, you fool.
It's a big day. Drink me anyway.
Yeah. Yeah.
This room was really intense because there's also the full screens.
There's a full battle going on outside that the guys are firing.
And you want to watch that.
Yes. You know, that's incredible animation.
But the cannons are so engrossing.
Yeah. I had to turn back and watch it again from behind.
Yeah, I can't believe those pieces.
Some of this I had to rewatch on video just to remember stuff
because it's so overwhelming.
And then we were, again, also punchy because we got up at four in the morning.
Yeah. So really surreal.
Been up for like eight hours or so by the time you finally rode it,
which I don't we have said you do not have to do that anymore.
And we also clearly didn't have to do our friend who got there
at seven fifteen was in the same boat we were. Yeah.
Which is but it's very funny.
It was a fun experience.
Yeah, geez. I mean, it's such a narrow hallway, too.
I think some of my like my big stuff in small rooms, I think, had my my Mario
born fear was coming true in front of me a couple of times in this ride.
Yeah, that was my question, because we had you had talked about it before
with those 80. I feel like the 80s did.
Did it get triggered in the 8080 room?
Not there. No. But here, much more because it's a much smaller room.
Right. The Cannon Room. Right.
And it's just and it's very Mario in general.
Now, will the actual Mario ride be more exciting than some of this?
Be more much.
I think that's now the like pressures on Mario.
There's a leaked there is a leaked Mario Kart track out there
that I have again.
I'm an idiot.
Looked at a little bit.
That is just if they can pull it off.
It has what this has where it's many rooms.
So many like eight eight different worlds, like some crazy amount. Wow.
Oh, boy. God bless this war.
Yeah. This is a wonderful war.
They yeah, if they could if they can pull off half of what I glanced at.
Yeah, it'll be in.
It could top. I mean, it could top this.
Yeah, possible.
They have. Yes, there's one thing on the horizon that might.
And it's opening in a few months until in Tokyo.
Yes. Hooray.
And then maybe next year.
What a wonderful world.
I think really, though, if Mario Kart, the ride doesn't top
rise, the resistance, they do have, I swear,
like people might be happier with Mario more than Galaxy's Edge
because you can ride Yoshi's around.
Now, the only thing missing is that Bantha.
That's true. Yeah.
I if they have if they have it and it delivers,
I will I have an annual pass into Universal a couple of years.
I will get one. And any time I'm driving by,
I will just like park on Lancashire.
I'm on Lancashire.
Take the shuttle up the hill, then go down the hill.
It's a two hour and then back up and back down.
Like Homer parking next to his own backyard.
Oh, man, I should just get like a security guard job at Universal
to get a pass. Oh, yeah.
Like I just want to work three hours a week, three, 30 minutes a week.
Well, but they might lock that down.
I mean, I think once we're now that rise is open, I believe
passholder passes may be blacked out a little in some certain parts.
You're right. The plan wasn't sound.
It wasn't a good idea to become a security guard to get on Mario.
I mean, that might but it may be the jobs rewarding.
Yeah, get some connections. That's true.
Well, maybe maybe I'll just shift out of the entertainment industry,
get into the security of the entertainment industry.
And maybe we all will. And maybe we'll all have no choice.
Yep. It'll be more stable.
So then you still you
a new giant room like how are there still giant rooms to go
and battle damaged hallways? Yeah.
The cannon room in the next set piece, there's battle damage happening around.
This is this is cool. Battle damage.
It's bigger and it's like, yeah, because now they're being shot at more by the
the I was going to say the Alliance.
That's not right, right?
The resistance, the resistance. Yeah.
Not the rebels.
The naming the naming change between original trilogy and new trilogy
is so like confounding and unneeded.
And it's bizarre.
So there are people who are resistance and rebel alliance, like nine.
They're both. Well, yeah.
Yeah. And then in Rise of Skyrock, there's the last order in the first order.
But then it's also like old empire
tech in a lot like it's empire star destroyers.
But then there are Sith troopers.
But in and then in the extended universe, like books and stuff, they were like,
it's the New Republic and the remains of the empire.
Go ahead. Go go for it.
It seems right. Yeah.
You know, if you were going to pull anything from what I think we can
now agree, there's been a I think all we can say in general, step back from it.
There is a mixed reaction to the Disney Star Wars.
And I think the only thing the thing you can pull that I think nobody would disagree
with set design, wonderful, great production design to these movies.
It feels like seeing like current built in 2010s,
like huge versions of the Star Wars aesthetic, very like current and high tech.
Sure. I think I think sets have been wonderful throughout.
And that's what the ride feels like.
You get to be in like the best end of the production design of the sleek
2015 and past and present in this.
In addition to that, the production design, the John Williams music,
there's some newer John Williams themes that play throughout this.
Sure. Everybody agrees on to.
I think. Yeah, I like the thing.
I like the race song. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, absolutely.
And I think like people like the cat.
I think some of the the parsing of it, like people just don't like
some of what has been done with all of the chess pieces that were set up.
But some of the chess pieces, very promising, great productions,
and great music cast pretty wonderful.
And the cast, I think, is great in this.
I think you go on this, you leave this ride and you go like,
well, that ride like implied a better set of movies, maybe perhaps.
At the very least, a more cohesive set of movies.
Yes. Oh, right.
It was funny in the first like Finn had some good lines.
Yeah, right. Yes.
I think this is the Finn that I liked.
Yeah, I assumed would be more.
That's not what we're here to do.
But and we even all of our opinions are all over the map.
But I like I think just like nobody's trying to hate on Star Wars
things just to do it.
And I think it's really exciting to have a thing that's like this.
I think this is the ultimate thing, I think, that came out of the Disney
Star Wars purchase. I got it.
After all the movies, finally, we have the ultimate thing
they got to do.
You just have to get to Disneyland at 8am.
Just at Disneyland.
Yeah. If they did a baby Yoda meet and greet in Galaxy's Edge,
people would lose their fucking mind.
I mean, it's weird.
I can't imagine it's not on the table.
I can't imagine. I heard somebody talking about it.
Was it Jim? It might have been Jim Hill.
I forget or Len or Jim were talking about it.
Like he would only be like 60 at this point.
It would only be like another six months.
And you know what happened?
It's like it's like right before the new movies.
It's after Jedi. Yeah.
I think I haven't finished Mandalorian yet.
I haven't gotten around to it.
But yeah, he I mean, they did the little baby Groot meet and greet in Florida.
And people love the same same basic thing.
Yeah. Yeah.
It doesn't make sense.
But can we just like ride on baby Yoda's?
Can we like, you know, like, it doesn't make any sense.
It doesn't. I don't care.
We need like a cute ride.
There are other creatures to ride on.
Yes. Baby Yoda is probably not it.
He could be in the car with you.
Old Disney, old Disney wouldn't have cared.
In the 50s would have been like, and then you ride a baby Yoda. Sure.
Doesn't matter. We're not thinking about like.
A rolly jumbo.
Baby Yoda would be like Yoshi and be different colors. Yeah.
Yellow, red, baby Yoda.
I want a magenta baby Yoda.
In the Trevorrow script that's leaked,
there was an evil Yoda that would train Kylo Ren, which I like.
I don't know if he looked like Yoda.
That's a fun idea. But that would have been a fun idea.
I recall before Force Awakens
when people were just speculating what characters were,
Mike Mitchell believed Snoke was an evil Yoda.
That was his guess. Yes.
Well, we also want to know how big he was.
Well, that was we still didn't know until the last Jedi how big he was.
And the answer was normal size.
It was not regular. Not big at all. Not big. Normal.
Is this still? No, I guess the timeline doesn't allow it.
So that's no you can ride a Snoke around.
Well, there's many Snokes we know from Rise of Skywalker.
Do we know that? We do.
We saw them in the tube.
There were multiple Snokes.
Waterpark, where you ride through empty Snoke tubes.
They're still building the Snoke tube.
That's good. Yeah.
Exegol Waterpark. Sure.
You go through the Snoke tubes. Yeah.
And you're you're Snoke.
It'll be like the Hulk ride where it's like your Snoke.
They'll have to figure out a safe way. We're turning you into a Snoke.
We're turning you into a Snoke.
Also, this is a water park with a lot of lightning effects.
You're going to like. Oh, yeah.
Your brain will think that's OK.
That's not a bad idea.
So yeah, this last room, you're and you're going towards the exit
and what does become the exit.
But then you hear Kylo Ren and you whip around and he's been in the room
and you didn't see him. Yeah.
He's well, he comes up. Oh, OK.
I believe he comes up.
There's also some blast doors in this room that I I need to ride this sequence
again, because in some of the videos, people were focusing the cameras
on other things. And I didn't they tricked me.
I was looking straight ahead to the more screens of the battle.
I was just he just was there suddenly. Yeah. Yeah.
They just pulled your attention somewhere like a magic trick.
You're looking over here and he shows up over there.
Now, we heard this little inside info is that this Kylo,
we were told to take a look at all of you.
But we were told that this might this may be the bones of Elsa.
From Frozen Ever After, or at least the offish is the same model.
Yeah, at least the same model and dressed it differently as the same capabilities
as far as like move waiving arms around.
Yeah, it is. It is extremely fluid. Yeah.
So and it does a lot. So much happens here.
He controls two vehicles at once with the force.
Then the fucking ship gets blown back.
Very cool. Yeah.
You feel that also thing that right there right there doesn't indicate
fill a big blast of space air
and then big debris falls down in front of him.
And that's another one of those. Those pieces are so big.
It really so big.
And it's so pieces and it covers the animatronic going back.
That's yeah. Oh, so he's able to reset almost immediately.
Yes. Wow.
So this is the moment I mentioned earlier.
The reason that blast happens behind him, because if you look to your right,
a tie fighter has been shot and is on fire and it comes at the screen.
Yeah, I miss this.
And it it's coming at you.
And in perfect sync, it goes off the screen and it hits behind.
Oh, it's in sync.
I didn't know this.
I we did it twice and I did not notice.
I didn't see it. A tie fighter in the footage explodes and comes right at you
and causes the corner of the ship to explode.
And that's why.
Yeah, he basically has a panel blow off behind him.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then there's a projection of like fire and or is it a screen behind him?
Projection to the sides.
And then there's a screen behind him of the vacuum of space.
And it looks like he almost gets blown out. Right.
So that's so if you knew where to look at the very beginning of that,
you would see the full you would see it coming at you
and then it would hit in correct time. Right.
God. Yeah, that's crazy.
I did not notice that.
So, yes, that has to be on my sixth ride.
I'll go back and look and see what it looks like.
A lot of reasons to keep going back.
And now so many things have happened and you've never got you're still on that
top level and you're thinking, well, when I keep hearing there is a drop.
Right. When is this drop?
I'm tense the whole time about the drop.
I'm still nervous about drops.
Then you pull up into a star tours.
It's not so evident that's what's happening. Right.
But once the once the pod doors open, like, oh, this must be it.
This has got to be it.
You're like you're suddenly facing little screens on the screens.
Your vehicles are getting dropped like, like just arms open
and they fall a ton.
So you really like what am I in for?
Yeah. You don't have any time to think about it.
And there's a drop that's kind of my it's not so crazy.
It's maybe two stories or one and a half.
Yeah. And you get caught too.
Like it's almost like you get like the the like if you were on a plane
and it drops a little and then you get caught.
That's kind of what it feels like. Yeah.
Did you see this?
If you watch the footage in the corner of the video,
you see the other escape pods and Beck is in one.
Yes, I saw. Oh, and he drops.
And then I believe it's Hux and Ren go into the other one.
And oh, I didn't see them.
Hux cues the drop.
Hux cues the drop and you drop it's the same time as them.
In the distance, he holds his hand up and that's when you drop
as like he gives the command to drop.
Oh, so we're in an empire.
We're in a first order escape pod.
We snuck into them and he's just dropping all the pods
because there's plenty of first order people.
It's a little hard to tell, but I'm pretty sure that's what you see
because that drops and goes to another Star Destroyer to like,
you know, take shelter in and you go the different direction.
And that's Kylo getting saved.
Because Kylo doesn't get sucked out of the ship.
He has to go do Rise of Skywalker.
Got to end up in his pajamas later.
His cool black pajamas.
So that's him escaping to go to the next movie, basically.
But you also see Beck escaping and then they're like, where's Beck?
Where's Beck later on?
And he's in an escape pod that is then
you see physically a few minutes later.
I didn't think about it.
I didn't. It didn't occur to me why he's in one of those.
That's really cool.
The only thing I want to know is did and it's probably in the footage,
but there's so much going.
How did nine get out?
Did he just get back to the transport ship and escape?
Like the only thing I mean, he maybe he's in Becks, but you can't really tell.
It's tilted up.
It is a little bit of a jump.
But yeah, right as you come out, you see a big practical version
of what you've just dropped in.
Yeah. And Beck is a full animatronic again.
And he's talking to you. Yeah.
So it's tilted up, I feel like, to maybe hide,
like to say, well, there were other people in there.
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe that's always logic.
So like there could be people at the back of it.
But Finn is like, glad you landed like you're a little off kilter.
You're a little off base.
So yeah. So you basically take a CGI simulator ride
then down through another Star Destroyer into the atmosphere
and you land back and back in Batuu, much like
Millennium Falcon. Yes.
I think this all I think it's a great free for the day for a Spider-Man fan.
It's kind of this is a great sequel, I think, to the big drop
at the end of that, like an inventive.
How do you get out of here?
I think it's a real like cousin.
I love that Disney has a Spider-Man now.
It's it's fantastic. Yeah.
And then you are outside and then you're delivered back outside,
which was very cool in the day.
It was very cool at night.
Both ways give you something cool to look at.
Yeah. And you you've transitioned
through three ride systems at that point
in the span of a minute trackless into a drop.
Drop becomes a motion simulator back to trackless and trackless outside.
That was just running inside.
Yeah, it's outside, which I'm trying to think like Alice in Wonderland
goes outside Guardians of the Galaxy Tower.
Terror open up and you see outside.
This is outside. Cars go cars go out in and nothing.
I don't think combines indoor and outdoor is surprising.
Yeah, that's nothing is effective.
And this is covered.
So I bet it can still run that last bit in the rain.
Oh, of course. Yeah, yeah, for sure.
I think so. And that that like atrium is beautiful with the winds
overtaking it and I like really like instantly iconic arcates.
So the way you pull up into it is so grand.
And then you just get you get this nice little last message from Beck
and you get chauffeured right to the gate.
Again, how it's not like a typical load area.
There's no cars waiting there.
You are just delivered straight to the end of the ride. Yeah.
Ratsatouille and similarly, surprisingly like, wait, do I not like getting a line
like when I'm getting off of pirates?
No, no, no. Here just here's the gate.
Here you are, sir.
It's a very, again, intimate.
It's you're not in a long line of folks.
It's just you. Yeah. Yeah. And it happened.
And you play the cast members still playing along like the one
that when we did at night, the woman went, yeah, heck of a landing, folks.
And I went, hey, anyone you can walk away from. Right.
And she I forget what her she had a good line to like, this is walking away.
We're like that. That's when you can walk away from it.
Like, it's very fun.
It's like I am.
If you work in that area, you just must see
such joy. Yeah.
Every second of the day.
That's where you get people applauding the end of this ride.
Like you saw a play. Right.
I suggest like euphoria in that room.
And we posted a picture of us there.
That's how we felt.
I just like that.
I just think a pure joy when I think about that atrium.
It's wonderful.
This is just it's just really did it.
And a little cherry on top that we found out.
At the end, the plant life that seems very lush and older plant
loya at the exit is replanted from Heimlich's choo choo train.
Yeah. Delightful, delightful.
Using every part of the buffalo.
Do you think in Florida, it uses like the the shrubs outside of the Golden
Girls house that they had to tear down to build?
It's the empty nest greenery.
River countries, greenery.
Oh, yeah. Transported over.
You actually just open out into the microbe.
One of those wonderful Florida Galaxy's transitions.
They just play a little like lever just like tosses you into a chair.
And there's a beer in front of you already.
Yeah, they were using overflow.
They were people were backed up to Muppets in Florida.
I just read. I believe that.
Yeah. Yeah.
Smother here, maybe.
I don't know. Greatest ride in the world now.
Does it have the title?
Yeah, probably.
It's I mean, it's crazy to think about with time and perspective.
This could be the like, remember the first iPhone?
Look how kooky this looks now.
I can't believe they did that.
You know, where it's like it keeps evolving.
But like next level right now.
Yeah, OK, here's what everyone's going to tell me to fuck off.
My one thing about it
is that and for whatever, like when you come, when it comes to e-tickets,
Johnny tickets, I feel like there is at least I have an expectation
that it's going to feel like I got like jostled around,
that I got like jerked around a lot.
And I don't have that feeling.
I almost felt like once we got off of it, it was more of a cousin
of like Fantasyland Dark Ride than it was maybe like
high tech ticket, because like almost every other ticket,
there's a thrill or like there's a thrill to it that you kind of when you're done,
you like shake your head because your brain has been knocked around a little bit.
And this doesn't have that. Sure.
This is almost purely like you're enjoying the scenery and you're immersed.
And it's got a little drop, but it's very, very mild.
Yeah. Up is exciting.
Up is exciting, but it doesn't have like whether it's, you know,
guardians or car, even cars, you know, you go 40 miles an hour or it's Indian,
Indian adjunct, you're getting knocked around left and right.
The one thing I felt like a little bit let down was that I just didn't feel like
they had fucked me up enough.
Like, I don't know if there's a real remedy to that.
And that's just a very nitpicky thing,
because it ends up just being a little bit more in my mind like.
And I don't mean this is a slam of Fantasyland Dark Ride.
But I think that was the intent of like, well, this is the Star Wars version
of a dark ride, not a thrill ride.
Yeah, families can do it.
And like, I think that was in their minds while they were designed.
That's the case. But I think the only thing I left being like,
it would have been nice for a little like something that really made your like
stomach drop or something. I don't know what it would be.
And like with these ride vehicles, it's so smooth.
I don't know if there's like Indiana Jones,
Tony Baxter's talked a lot about how they were trying to figure out that ride
vehicle, because that ride vehicle gives you such a sense of like
instability the whole time to really add to the danger.
Whereas like, I don't know,
because they have built like a thing that just rotated on top of a.
But then that doesn't really make sense for these type of vehicles.
So this is all nitpicky.
But that's the one thing where I was hoping there was a little bit of that.
But again, this is minor when we're in the scheme of the most crazy
scope in a ride like this ever.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't know.
I don't agree with you. That's fair.
I think it fucking rules.
I'm not saying it doesn't rule. Yeah. Yeah.
I think I'm just very curious to see how long this boarding
system, how long, how long until
it's just like, just wait in line, you know, just just wait in line.
Or is there a modified version of the boarding system?
Because not everyone who comes to Disneyland.
I mean, Scott, you bought a one day pass to do this.
It would have been a bummer to not get to go.
It would have been a bummer not to get to go.
And I'm wondering, like, well, is everyone are people prepared?
They are like, I think and I think they've been done a pretty good job
of preparing people like that. Not everyone's going to get to go on.
There is a boarding group system.
And if even if you get here very early, you could still get a reservation
for very late.
So I do wonder as the land evolves and grows, like how long
because those avatar rides still have really long waits like slinky dogs
still has a really long wait.
How long until they go like, OK, no more boarding groups.
Yeah, just wait in line.
I mean, I don't know how they decide when that shouldn't happen.
Yeah, I don't know.
It'll shift to fast pass it is a certain point.
Yeah, I mean, it was there's touch points set up.
I mean, I think they'll probably like figure out whenever the thing is running
at full capacity and it's, you know, whatever percentage consistent,
if it's like running 80 percent consistent. Yeah, that's true.
I'll just go like, well, this makes sense and we can run this many people
and they'll have plenty of data to say like how many people are coming to the park.
So like it makes sense. Yeah, do it.
But I bet it'll be a couple of months.
I bet it might be even be sooner than we think where it's not like this,
because like Galaxy's Edge had this system and they gave it up
the two days in really fast.
But that's a different story than this, because everybody is going to ride this
and want to ride it twice, I would imagine, or more if.
Yeah, yeah, that's a yeah, yeah, yeah, we're lucky we got to do it.
But the I think this all I think this like sets everything right, though.
I think now you don't have the feeling of and then the ride is this falcon ride
that people it's a little confusing that people have a little bit of trouble with.
I think it now like, OK, so that's allowed to be the slightly lesser one.
Like like the cousin, they the blockbuster is open.
I know I think I enjoyed Falcon more
this time with that perspective.
Yeah, we kind of a little bit of the pressure off
as far as Galaxy's Edge, like you still we still want as many aliens
and robots going around as possible and flash mobs and those like it doesn't fix
that, but it does certainly like take the pressure off Falcon being like
and like it needs to be like the be all end all for.
Yeah. Yeah. And it seems like that's coming slow and I mean, there's more
R2D2 sightings in the land.
I saw Chewbacca like three times the one day we were there.
And then and I think, too, this is giving us
I don't mind that they are kind of like with the Marvel land coming.
It's like, all right, you're going to restaurant.
You're going to get the bee ride to start.
Of course, Guardians Edge is Guardians of the Galaxy is here.
And there'll be characters and there'll be some meet and greets.
And then who, boy, wait until you see this Avengers thing in a few years.
Yeah, like they're not changing.
Like, oh, by the way, the big the big thing isn't coming opening day.
They've just taken that off the table.
And I think that's better because at least you've established an expectation
and you have somewhere to go and you have somewhere to go.
Exactly. But I just I think I you know, we've maybe I think we were so enthusiastic
right after we did Galaxy's Edge.
And I think it's waned a little bit.
And we've had our complaints.
We had Mike Mitchell on who had many, many, many complaints.
As it's how it goes.
And now it feels like it's like really things are things have settled.
And I think I enjoyed all the stuff more again.
I was we didn't get to the cantina, but just like having your food,
having your having your milk,
doing Falcon, seeing Chewbacca.
It just all like it was.
It is the thing that was missing.
And yeah, it's it's there.
It's nice to have it there.
It would be like if like you were like walking around New Orleans Square
and there was no pirates and you'd be like, well, this is nice.
But I don't I don't need to go walk through here every time.
But like going off like you go on pirates and then you get dumped
into New Orleans Square and then you walk around a little bit like
there is some flow to that, like when you have a land in a ride
like where you wouldn't necessarily go if you've like you hadn't
experienced something, whether it's pirates or whether it's
right, just little things that they're like, here's some new food.
Here's a new here's the veggie version of rap.
Here's a hot chocolate with purple whipped cream.
Like, you know, yeah, yeah, that stuff does.
Yeah, I'm starting to feel like I think I was feeling some weird
like like down energy of like, is this what it is?
And yeah, I like you feel the burst of energy, obviously,
with this incredible new ride.
But yeah, those little things, of course, I'm like, of course,
I want that damp of that or something or some like something that you know
you can just walk on or that's like a half hour wait instead of a blockbuster
that takes two hours.
I think the one thing they could do.
Yeah, I don't make it perfect.
I think it's impossible, like making the cantina a little more casual
like or that dinner show, whatever it is.
You can't do that every time.
But maybe they use first order area that feels a little bare as like expansion pad.
Maybe that ends up like, oh, we're actually we're going to do a new thing here.
Supposedly, the area for the restaurant is still there.
They could build the restaurant or they could build a more cantina.
Yeah, you would think that the canteen is so popular.
We've talked about before, like you may as well.
Like a full it's still crazy to me that they didn't think like this
is going to be the most popular thing.
And they wouldn't build like a kind of a cool like four room
cantina with different things and a different robot and like.
Yeah, that's such a slam dunk to get everybody.
Yeah, maybe they needed to test the waters to know like people would want this.
Right. Oh, yeah. People really want it. Yeah.
Well, and especially like just a few weeks ago,
they made the alfresco like tasting terrace APs only. Right.
And jacked up the lines because people here like, oh, limited opportunity.
And I get to do it like my precious private.
Precious like, yeah.
So but it also probably was not like
breaking in the dollars is a regular spot.
And they're like, well, how can we juice the business here a little?
And it seems like it has worked.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
So you will.
I mean, you'll just have to settle for that beautiful patio at the Grand California.
And that's nice, too.
Yeah. Yeah.
The number one thing they should I don't know if it's even possible,
but they should have built like a two story bar overlooking the Millennium Falcon.
It should have been a big, expansive bar with a couple different types of rooms
with like, yeah, Rex and one a different band could play, could be live.
And there would be two stories and you'd have a really great view
of the Millennium Falcon and they would make so much money.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, maybe this will like kind of like I think this will
offset the narrative that it's a disappointment.
I think it's going to be a swell that shows people are excited about this area.
I think so, because there's some big shortcomings in Cars Land.
I mean, there's some great stuff about Cars Land, but like
the restaurants, they flip the menu at the restaurant a couple of times, gone downhill.
Had the slide rides in and out.
Yeah. Yeah.
Flat rides. And I mean, I like the restaurant.
I like the ambiance of the restaurant.
I was going to say, you sit out on the back of floors and that's one of the best views.
That's got different rooms.
But like, yeah, it seems like they they kind of flopped,
flip flop the menu a few times.
Yeah. But the cones, I'm always like, oh, yeah, let's go get a snack of the cones.
Yeah, you got to love the cones.
Yeah, I think, look, it was it put me in a better mood about Galaxy.
Obviously, it's it's maybe the greatest ride in the world at the moment.
And I think, I don't know, just like I feel like the full puzzle is finally there.
And I also like to say, I think it put us in a good mood, a good enough mood
where I really enjoyed what we were doing with our friend, Mamazani.
We were with the the Doc Ondar uncut gems mashup.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We were just sort of like going from line to line.
Like that's real black coaxium.
That was a pain in the ass to get this fucking guy, Hondo Anaka.
He had the fucking he had to smuggle this out.
He had to fire it a train to get this.
Ondar is the handsome older gentleman.
How you doing, baby?
Come on up. I got I got the chef.
I got the chef from docking day seven.
He's coming up.
Friends are coming up this week.
We're going to want to make some food.
We had we had an OK riff about Joe Rody explaining what he liked about two and a half men, too.
Oh, right. It was a whole it was a whole of like, you know, it's actually about it's about family
and it's about experience.
That's what the comedy is about on two and a half men.
Every every episode of the Big Bang Theory actually is its own theory,
a theory about harmony, about how we interact as people, as if we are the molecules.
That's pretty good, too.
So we had a couple of great bits.
So we're having fun.
Yeah, we're having a blast.
They see three.
Say that that's real black coaxium.
See three.
Don't lean on the glass.
See three. That's that's going to break your robot.
You're strong on the line.
Don't see it on the glass.
Stand on the line quick.
Take the speeder to canto bite.
You put credits on the pod race.
See three.
You got to bring back the coaxium.
See three. Go get it.
See the shirt I'm wearing.
This is Lando Calrissian shirt.
You see the yellow and the black.
This is Lando shirt.
Look at this. This guy's an up and comers named Rex.
His name's Rex.
We got to get we can get him.
Yeah, he gets into a fight with the bathroom.
It seems the son of a bitch.
Rex, he's fucking my girl.
Oh, yeah, you should make a funnier dive video.
It's a really good.
If you want to hear this full audio play, we're we're willing to do it.
But until then, you survive,
podcast the ride, rise the resistance edition.
What's the runtime? Where do we end up on that?
I think it's about two and a half, two and a half.
OK, decent, decent ratio.
Not 10 hours.
If you want to hear more,
if you object to declaring this the greatest ride in the world,
what do you think, Topsy, if you've done we haven't physically been on Mystic
Manor and physically been on Shanghai Pirates.
It could be one of these.
Let us know. Write us on Twitter.
Let's keep the debates going.
We're doing big stuff lately. Boy, Hagrid's and and rise.
The war.
Whoever whoever wins, we win too. Yeah.
It's it's a reverse aliens versus a reverse alien
versus predator in quality as well.
Well, yeah.
So, yeah, follow us on Twitter, Facebook and Instagram.
And for more podcast, the right content,
go to the second gate at Patreon dot com slash podcast, the ride.
Hoo boy. All right, then.
How do we come down from this? I don't know.
Well, I've seen you in a callback.
Oh, what am I going to go in?
I was thinking about going this way. Sure. Yeah.
I was thinking about going like one day when I don't have anything to do.
I'll just go down early. Yeah. Try it.
Let us know what you notice. Yeah. Yeah.
Go already breakfast, you know, try to make your reservation on a nice breakfast.
I could do that. Yeah.
And I won't I won't overload on hot dogs.
Yeah. Stay away from the hot dogs.
Weren't the issue that they had fixed?
They're never the problem. They're the solution.
And then it won't be I won't have a problem using the bathroom droid.
Oh, yes. Right.
Zero zero P.
B zero.
P.O.O.P. Thank you for your service.
Master Sheridan, do you have to use P.O.O.P.?
No, I know.
I use zero.
Too much to me, Master Sheridan.
Usually bring a little bag with ibuprofen and Tums.
And I forgot it this time.
But if you're having trouble, just know P.O.O.P. is there for you.
Did you spend a little extra money on a ballast point?
Drank beer?
Well, no, it's horrible.
It's actually one of the cheaper drafts down there,
because it's direct from the supplier.
Fruit beers.
No, that's not.
You found them too expensive.
Well, you don't have to give me Greek P.O.O.P.
OK?
No, I am C3PO explaining P.O.O.P.
Oh, thanks, C3PO.
P.O.O.P. can't talk.
Yeah, he just makes an electronic fart noise.
I wish your memory had stayed erased somehow.
Quiet P.O.O.P.
Beep beep beep beep.
Hard.
All right. More adventures of P.O.O.P.
coming down the pike.
Thanks for listening, everybody. Bye. Bye.
Dog.
This has been a forever dog production,
executive produced by Mike Carlson, Jason Sheridan,
Scott Gardner, Brett Boehm, Joe Cilio and Alex Ramsey.
For more original podcasts, please visit Forever Dog Podcasts dot com
and subscribe to our shows on Apple podcasts, Spotify
or wherever you get your podcasts.
Keep up with the latest Forever Dog news by following us on Twitter
and Instagram at Forever Dog Team and liking our page on Facebook.